So did you see the title? Yeah, I got my save. I actually just had to go into the PlayStation account settings downloaded the cloud save because I just have my PlayStation gym membership. Right? You just forget that it exists. It just takes out what $10 a month forever. Even if you don't go and work out it still happens. So I was able to have my save. So give me a second while people trickle in.
See you in a sec. I just saw somebody say maybe he won't play Minecraft this time. Well, I mean, come on, like I was also drinking heavily that night. So what? I drunkenly played Minecraft. That didn't that I didn't whatever. I remember the last mission that I was on here. I have a distinct memory of walking around in a circle not knowing how to go down to the crash.
And I finally figured it out. And now we're moving on to the next part. I'll give you a quick rundown of the story so far hasn't gotten over ruined Kim's Minecraft world. No, that's that's that's in the cloud, man. That's we're good. All right, I gotta move my mic a little bit because I'm trying to trying to increase the volume here. Hold on. Try and find like the right spot where this is not obstructing any view, but it's also good quality. Okay, so let's go like this.
And we go like this. And there it is. Make sure it's synced. I know that's been a problem recently. Bring back the headset mic. No. Why on earth would I do that? All right, so here's, here's what you guys have to tell me. So you ready? I'm going to go like this up and down. And you should be hearing a click right when it switches and highlights a different option. Okay. Good. All right, now I'm going to match my voice with it. Ready? 121231231234. We good?
Voice is a smidge delayed. Okay, I'll try one more time. 1212312341234. Big delay. Big. So my voice comes after is what you're saying. Because this is an issue I've had recently. So the voice. So it's ready. How about this one? Ready? 121234123412345123412345.
All right, it's good. How about now? 1234551212345512. A, B, C, D, E, F, G, H, G, K, N, F, E, Q, R, S, N, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5. Are we okay? How about one more time? Can you guys tell? We're good, right? All right, let's go. Welcome back to LA. Oh, never mind. We're going to cut. So I forgot to tell you. I got to tell you the story so far. Wait a minute.
I can't pause it, can I? Okay, so this case, there was a crash. Somebody went sailing off the edge. Might have been intentional. Somebody weighed down the pedal. There was an actress involved. There's an ad when the actress is in the car and she might know more than she thinks.
Bang, they fly off. I'm going to visit the other lady that was in the car to see if I get more information because man, this might have been a fucking murder attempt. You know what I'm saying?
Hello, Detective Phelps. I'm here to interview a Jessica Hamilton.
Jessica Hamilton. Oh, yes. She's in the room.
You were drunk. Yes, I was.
You can't hold me here.
We're going to talk to Hamilton.
I don't need to be manhandled by a doctor. I need my lawyer.
You're little. Where is the telephone? Do you know who I am?
Wait, wait, wait, wait. Who's talking?
All right, Jessica, how are you feeling?
Hello, Jessica. My name is Paul Phelps.
Hard going back here after Red Dead. We might play Red Dead tonight. I don't know.
I'd like to talk to you about your accident, if that's okay?
Okay.
Okay, so remember, here's where I can review. Here's the evidence, okay?
There was a Chevy Steinlein. Boom, off the edge. The victims in that car may have been drugged.
Somebody sent a letter to her really worried about her and wants her to come home.
There was underwear. There was a pair of underwear that I found and I picked them up.
Then there was a shrunken head that was weighing down the pedal of the car that went off the edge.
Remember, actress, not an actress, but might be at some point, might be a protege to the other actress.
I'm ready.
Can you tell me what you remember about the crash?
It's all kind of fuzzy. I remember waking up here.
Nothing happened yesterday.
Okay, so she looks a little distraught.
I'm going to, let's, we're going to ease into this.
You could have died in the crash, Jessica.
Why would someone want to kill you?
Someone wants to kill me?
Got it.
I wouldn't know anything about that. I just went along with Junie. She knows all about the movie business.
See? Okay, so her parents sent her a letter. She might lie to me here.
She looks pretty, yeah, she looks a little distraught. Let's talk about the parents.
You need to get in touch with your parents, Jessica, and tell them what has happened.
Oh, you don't need to worry them. They sent me along to stay with Aunt June.
It's a lie.
They trust her to take care of me.
That's not true. I can accuse her. I can show the letter, right? Or should I bad cop this?
Or is that just doubt? Because, I mean, I do have the letter from Mom saying, come home.
You're lying, Jessica. How are we going to make this right if you lie to us?
Please, detective, why would I lie to you?
I got the letter to prove it. There.
Because you're a runaway, Jessica, and you don't have your parents' permission to be here.
Now, do you want to tell me what really happened?
Got it.
I went with June to this strange place. It's difficult to remember.
Someone gave me a drink to calm my nerves, and then I felt faint.
I think I must have passed out.
Okay.
So, how did you meet Mr. Bishop?
Mr. Bishop is the guy that is involved.
June is a big movie star. You probably know that. She's doing a new movie.
No, that's a lie. Hold on, wait, is that a lie?
Was she in a movie? Was she in like a new movie coming up?
I think she was. I think that's, yeah, she was in a movie.
What do you know about Bishop?
I don't remember.
He makes movies. I had to do a screen test.
Movies don't exist in the past.
That's when you say some lines in front of the camera with the lights turned on you.
Okay, what about criminal abuse?
I know what happened to you, Jessica. Where exactly did it take place?
Please, it's scary. It's really difficult to think of anything.
Come on. Come on.
What about, uh, this is me on the green screen.
We need the information.
Someone tried to kill you, Jessica. Do you get it?
Forget about being in movies. It's time to act like a grown-up.
I had to wear a robe and lay down on a stone.
There were lights, camera. It's not my fault.
I'm not a bad girl.
Tell us where he is.
Why are you trying to hurt me?
You should think about going home, Jessica.
One of four, correct?
We're going to be mixed up with people who will treat you like last week's trash.
What?
Are you crazy? I can't go home. I want to be a star.
How? I got the letter from the mom. She wants to be in movies.
It's the tale of this town, Cole. Lambs that go willingly to slaughter.
Who the hell is that?
Must be her lawyer. He certainly expedited her release.
I don't like it, Cole. Why is she in such a hurry?
We should follow her.
I didn't have any information.
Look, the last time I saw this story was a month ago.
If I read you the first five chapters of a book a month ago and then closed it,
and then a month later I was like, oh, hey, here's the next chapter,
you're going to be like, what are you talking about? What are we doing?
Think of all the other pieces of media you've consumed in the last month.
Ballard is definitely up to something.
I don't even know what the specials were at the restaurant I went to last night.
And that happened last night. That was last night.
And damn, did they sound good, too.
One of them had, it was a pinot sauce, white wine with some kind of fish.
It was a wild-caught fish, too, and I almost bought it.
But I don't know what it was.
You know, I wish there was a thing you could do at restaurants,
because they give you the menu, right?
Waitress comes over, waiter comes over.
Oh, here's your menu. Please take a look at it.
And then they come back. Oh, by the way, here are the specials.
No, I don't want to hear the specials. Put the specials on the menu.
I can't remember the shit that you're telling me.
You list off like nine different items and like ten different side dishes.
It's like, put it on the fucking menu.
I take cover at the door. I don't want to break in here just yet.
Enter the cafe without being seen.
I can't go through, don't go through the door?
Why would it tell me to go to the door?
What? Wrong door.
Look, we're in a restaurant right now. I can't remember the specials.
They were reading specials as I was going up to the door.
This guy's going to see me come. That's a newspaper.
Newspaper. That's a newspaper.
You still know people out here, don't you?
Then make some calls.
Let me be very clear about this.
You get this done or I'm...
Wilson's Hotel. Mr. Mark Bishop,
that son of a bitch, lives in apartment 803.
Got it.
Thanks for the info.
Sure, I got the film.
I got the film.
All right, I need to find the film.
This is reading the newspaper very close.
That would be really embarrassing.
So what's the story? I'm guessing she didn't stop to like refreshments.
She made a call. Sounds like Mark Bishop has a heap of trouble headed his way.
I've got his address. Wilson's Hotel, Apartment 803.
Oh, shit. You better step on it.
If he's got any sense, he'll be as far away from home as possible.
If he had any sense, he wouldn't have tried bumping off Guy McAfee's wife in the first place.
Or he'd have done the job properly.
McAfee will break a fella's legs just for looking at him.
You know what I want? Back on the restaurant bullshit again.
What did you make of the kid?
Do you believe her story?
I think she was dumped out of her tiny mind and given the casting couch.
That fucking bitch Ballard sold her out.
Okay, so if Ballard was doing someone a favor, why did they try to kill her?
What I want in a rescue front?
Take it easy, Phelps. I'd rather get there in one piece.
I think I can fix this.
All units in the vicinity in corridor 15, front.
Advice?
Get to the car before someone gets hurt.
You got any advice?
Give me another car.
Do we need to have that car?
Come here.
I don't want to go too far away. It'll fail the mission.
I think I have to be in that car.
I'm sorry, sir. Police officer. I need your car.
What? I think I have to be in that car, don't I?
Will he get in this?
I might have to dislodge this car.
Yeah, okay.
I can't even get up there.
How did I do this? I just fell off the edge.
I hope I don't need this guy.
Just fall off the edge again and dislodge the car.
I still have the marker.
Delete your save.
Is he running right now after the car?
Can you imagine a cop taking your car to commandeer it to drive into their car that is stuck?
That would be pretty weird.
You're a loose cannon, Jeremy. You're off to Cates.
They need somebody like me.
I might not do it well, but I get it done.
Except for that. That was really well done.
Did he say turn right?
Do I think he's in the car with me?
He got up. Bishop's apartment.
I'm Detective Phelps. We received a call about a domestic disturbance in Apartment 803.
He gets the option to do good cop, bad cop work.
Take the elevator and then left down the corridor. It's the last door on the right.
Officer, that was a lie.
Oh, shit. Yeah, it was.
Sounds like we're about to make it a hat trick of hysterical female witnesses.
Take the elevator where? He didn't say which floor.
There's probably only five, six floors apparently.
He said last door on the right.
There it is.
No, that's not correct.
Where's 803?
He said on the right. Did he say take a left? I don't know.
Hello? Did he say take a left first?
No, this place was torn apart.
Didn't you see her?
No, no, that was somebody else.
That was somebody else.
Okay, so we got some stuff to look at.
There's a vase.
Is it the Bible?
I don't think this is going to help us.
I don't know. God can't help us now, apparently.
What?
It's the Bible.
What do you mean, the Bible? It's the Bible.
It doesn't appear to be connected.
It's what? It's a Bible?
Presented to Mark.
Okay.
What's this? A fight game?
Ooh, five dollars.
I'll take it.
Optimistic, Cole.
It's got some nice weight to it.
I don't think so.
Put it down.
Twenty-five dollar bounty for stealing.
Apparently it's rock star week on this channel.
But to be fair, they do make some of the best games.
Old movie set.
Anything on it?
There's a bunch of stuff here.
Great wall of Babylon.
A replica of a replica.
Movie set replica.
Of a replica.
But this is not made by a rock star.
I don't think this is anything.
But they pressed accept on it.
You know what I mean?
They opened the email with the file in it for the EXE.
I don't think there's anything else in here.
What about this clock?
This painting.
Kitchen. Secret room.
A couple of melee weapons.
I don't think I need these.
Nothing else?
Just like coffee cups and shit.
The salad fork is going to blow this gate wide open.
What is going on?
What is happening in the chat room?
There was just like an unleashing of a Jupiter storm.
I need to get like the...
Mermaid in the background.
Silver screen.
What are these men in the picture?
My husband, Mark.
And Marlin Hopgood.
They work together on occasion.
That's Hopgood's shop.
Marlin Hopgood.
That's a new character.
There's a dog.
Another time and place.
I'm not talking yet.
Nothing?
Balcony?
Okay.
Anything else?
Alright.
Is there broken glass on the door?
This door is like broken.
This door is all fucked up.
Can I close the door and look at it?
I can't close this door.
Until I get a better look at it.
Do a cool trick off the balcony.
I can't.
Apparently I'm missing something else.
That, which I don't know.
Is the clock that I was talking about before I told you.
Nope.
What were they looking for?
Have you talked to the lady?
I've not talked to the lady, but don't...
Isn't there another musical cue when you find all the clues?
Can I offer you an egg in these trying times?
What are you guys doing?
Oh! That was a big gotcha moment.
There's a check here.
$20,000.
Two...
That's another language. I can't read it because it's cursive.
Lupra...
Allo rule.
Got it.
Hey! Can I ask you some questions?
What's up?
What about that check on the ground?
Who are you paying?
Do you know the name?
June Ballard is married to Guy McCaffey.
Have you heard of her?
That slut.
I've been flattering my husband for days.
Mrs. McCaffey alleges that your husband tried to kill her and her friend last night.
I think you should tell us what you know.
My husband's a movie producer.
This has something to do with his new picture.
He doesn't include me in his business.
Let me look at the notebook.
What about...
The letter from your mother.
She wants you to come home.
Who wrote this check?
I did.
Aye, aye, aye.
Can we get on with this, please?
I'm an officer of the law, ma'am.
Mmm...
I don't believe it.
June Ballard said she had a deal to be in his new picture.
Mark repeatedly told her no.
He had Joan Leslie lined up for the role.
That's how he got the finance.
June made all kinds of threats.
She was very rude to me.
You know June Ballard?
We were both on the same picture a few years back.
That's how I am.
Whose dead eye?
Do you know
where Bishop is?
Where can we find your husband, ma'am?
He told me he would be on set. That's all I know.
Is it?
If he was practicing in the mirror for this part...
What about this underwear? Do you know what this is?
Either we find him, or McAfee's people do, Mrs. Bishop.
If you care for him,
you should make sure that we find him first.
I do care for him.
But I don't really know
where he'd go if he were in trouble.
Hopgood might know.
Okay, the trace address of Prop Store.
Now who is this check for $20,000 for?
Why is your husband paying Lorna Hopgood
$20,000?
Lorna?
Marlin's ex-wife?
Are you sure?
Yeah.
We got her.
I have the check.
But I don't accuse.
I mean, I do have the check.
But what if she didn't
write it, though?
You're lying, Mrs. Bishop.
It's some kind of payoff. You know exactly
what the money is for and who it's getting paid to.
Do I?
Would you like to prove that, detective?
Yeah.
I got the check right here.
$20,000 made out to
Lorna
Hopgood on the account of Mark Bishop.
I got it.
Your husband looks like he's being blackmailed.
They obviously have something on him. If he's prepared to kill to cover it up,
why is the payment going to Hopgood
and not McAfee?
Lorna works at a check cashing place in
Hollywood. You need to ask
Hopgood why he needs that much money in
cash.
Your husband is in trouble. It could go easier
for him if you were more helpful, Mrs. Bishop.
Perfect score!
You're a big boy, detective, and so are you.
This is Hollywood.
There's always a deal to be done.
By the way, your necklace
is out of focus. Just want to make sure, you know,
take care of that.
Hello, I need to use the telephone.
Operator, give me R&I.
Putting you through now.
Phelps, batch 1247.
Detective?
I need a location on a silver screen prop store.
Just a moment.
Smartest streamer on Twitch.
Thanks, man.
Investigate silver screen props.
Get out of the way.
Use your own phone. Get out of my house.
Open up your cell phone, man.
I know this takes place.
Small complaint about the game.
I know this takes place in the 40s, but
fucking it's modern times now, man.
Just let them have a phone or something.
Let them have a pawnpilot with GPS and everything.
It's really annoying.
This game released in like 2007.
I know it's like 1937 or
1942 or whatever it is, but
no gamer wants to play like this.
Give me a fucking pawnpilot.
Mrs. Bishop knows more than she's letting on.
She doesn't seem to realize how much trouble
her husband is in.
The LAPD are the least of their worries right now.
You think she'd have gotten the hint that
the hatchet man redecorated her apartment?
Maybe she's just loyal.
No, they didn't have hint.
Small complaint about the game.
I know it's like 1940, but
where the fuck is the...
There's a handbrake on every car now.
Just put a handbrake in the game.
It's really irritating.
There is a handbrake.
I just pulled it.
It's like music.
Small complaint about the game.
Fucking seriously.
It's like 2007, 2008.
They claimed this boring, dumb shit music.
It's fucking irritating.
It's like Limp Bizkit.
They put like current music on it.
It's fucking annoying.
Watch what you're doing!
Why can't I put my own custom playlist?
They can
update the rosters on Madden and
MLB the show and stuff.
Why can't they update the playlists and the current radio stations?
Fucking annoying.
It's gonna get points off the game.
For real though, I just wanna make sure you guys are aware of that.
End this.
Someone's in that shoot of armor!
No, I'm not gonna do the sound.
The bare default sound.
Sorry.
Plus, a car just made it
driving by, so I didn't even have to do it.
Shoot the armor before it gets you.
This is here. Soundstage.
Let's have a look around.
Ooh,
would you look at that?
Ah, I found one of these
at the crime scene.
Didn't I?
Looks eerily familiar.
Is there a reason why I haven't said anything about that yet?
Why won't I
say anything about this?
Do I have to find a certain thing on it?
Because he's not like, oh,
there's a guy in there.
Ah.
This guy's got a peep den.
And there's drugs here too.
So this guy,
this guy is a bad man.
Well, gotcha.
See, now you're fucked.
Something else back here?
No?
Hold on.
They're everywhere. I already know that.
Yeah, I got a little soundstage.
You're gonna rot.
Can't be that way, Phelps.
You couldn't fit a rat through there.
It's right here.
There's a secret button on the wall.
How do I turn the light off here?
Where's the book that I have to pull out for the
wall to collapse?
It's right back here. Toilet paper roll?
Flush the toilet?
Wait, hold on.
Not everything here is going to be relevant.
Ah.
In the dumpster. Secret dumpster entrance.
No, nevermind.
Do you really have the fucking
ACME Road Runner
set up where, I mean, if that was a cartoon,
I'd be able to run through that.
And then the guy behind me would chase me and
smash into that.
Well, this is the 40s.
So that was relevant. Those things did work on people back then.
Okay.
So we have a secret camera room.
That's not fucked up at all.
Okay.
What's over here? What's that?
There's the toilet.
Okay, there's all these photos.
I wonder if they saw this,
how many budding starlets would still get on the bus
to come to Hollywood.
So, I was going to say, why am I stuck there?
Okay.
We've got, oh, this is the
film, I think, right?
So we've got a
Jungle Drums.
Eighth and Francisco.
These guys were running like a fucking fucked up
like secret spy.
Yeah.
What are you going to do with this?
Phelps, put on gloves, man.
You're tainting the scene.
Let's take a look at this one. These, like, creepy fucks
just filming people behind the wall.
Hmm.
Interesting.
I don't need any butterscotch.
Okay.
This is just somebody sat back here.
So, somebody had to,
it was a two-man
thing here. Cause somebody had to upright the camera.
They're both, and they're both guilty.
Is there anything else that I missed in here?
Sure, I didn't.
There's that. I got that.
I got that.
Nothing else? That's it.
But, there is a bunch of this,
this thing. What about back here?
Painting these.
All right. Well, this is very clearly.
Okay.
That's the one.
This is where you sprang from.
Here are the molds.
Should I take one of these?
I guess that, yeah, that's just, they're just making them.
This game, well, this game came out
in 1940, cause that's when it takes place.
Flood streets,
cops chase, war, surplus, contraband.
Let's take a look.
You want to be a doctor, and a dope peddler.
Interesting combination, huh?
Do we have a problem,
Mr. Cohen?
We might have. Yeah.
Selling your dope to my boy Lenny looked like a good move,
but Lenny has been supplying, uh,
wholesale, so to speak.
The Bindle Boys in this town
aren't used to the juice without a little of the middle man
taking his cut.
Lenny promised that wouldn't happen, Mr. Cohen.
And Lenny works for you.
What can I say about Lenny?
Let me think. Oh, yeah,
he's a putz, and he's lazy,
and he's greedy, but he's my wife's brother.
What were the specials again? I don't remember.
You have to make a cake with those ingredients, huh?
That was a bad call back.
So how was that my problem, Mr. Cohen?
Well, kids, the only way we're going to be able
to make this work is to do some repackaging.
We need to get the dope out of those dinky little cardboard
boxes. So we're putting them in the heads.
Dope in the heads.
Yeah, so reds. Great. We can put it into a big
vat so we can water it down a little bit.
Who bore you with the chemistry?
But it doesn't work that way.
You're likely to kill even more people.
Okay. Listen.
We want to buy you out, kid. What did I eat last night?
I'll offer you 50 grand.
Water.
There was water in...
Hey. Hey! A salt.
You don't like my offer? I forget everything else.
Where'd the phone come from?
Whose phone is this? I think I want him dead.
Thanks for the
part of the table under the seat
telephone.
The logistics of having a phone at that table back
in 1940.
That cable has to run through the whole restaurant.
People are going to trip over that.
All right. So we got some info here.
There's dope
is involved.
They're like, I'm going to cut one of these open.
Hello? I'm going to cut one of
those open. There's going to be dope in there.
Oh, come on. Let's go.
Come on, girl.
That's a good girl.
I played that other game. I played that other game.
And see? These were all
taken from Red Dead. Didn't I tell you?
Red Dead. Red Dead.
Red Dead.
That's a different game.
I got enough evidence to put this guy away for life.
So don't worry.
All right. Skip the dialogue. You're going
away for life.
You ever do any work for Mark Bishop?
Mainly do work for the studios.
RKO, Republic,
Warner Brothers. So yeah.
And Bishop is doing work for a studio.
Yes. When did you last see him?
Yeah, I'm doing work for his next picture.
Still pre-production though.
Is it? I haven't seen him around here
in a while. Really?
Hmm. Haven't seen him
around in a while, have you?
This letter from your mother says otherwise.
She's looking for you and she's
worried about you. All right, hold on.
This is the movie set photographer,
photographer, prop store photographer.
When was this taken?
It's got to be like a date somewhere, right?
Film reel. I mean,
like, when was this taken?
The mermaid statue.
How would that prove, like, that date
though? Is there a date on here?
What's the date?
Should I just accuse him and just put up the checkout?
No. I mean, like, he's clearly
in the photo here, but this is from
the mermaid movie.
Do I have any other information
besides that? I mean, this is
ugh.
I don't know the date on here. This could be any time.
Hold on a minute.
Like, none of these mean anything
though. What about, like, the fucking hidden cameras?
Why can't I bring that up?
I have, like, a check
and, like, a photo of these two.
How would that determine where...
Do you know where he is? I have a photo of you
too. And what about the drugs?
Like, I can't be like, hey, why do you have the...
I can't just be like, what is this?
Like, the empty... Yeah, but that's not the
question though. The question was like, do you know where he is?
Why isn't the first question
like, hey, what's with the drugs and cameras?
How would I know?
How would I be able to get the information of
where he is?
Where is he?
I have a picture of them two on a
set, but when was that taken?
So is this the reason why I can't bring up
all the other stuff?
Are you thinking too hard about it?
Was it really just as simple as
here's a photo of you two?
Like, that's it.
It's the simplest answer.
He will be bringing Mark Bishop into custody.
At least he's polite.
Kinda dumb.
But polite.
So it's just all red herrings and then one item is
correct or something? Is that how this game works?
Just pick up a bunch of evidence and then there's one
question. Please press this button on this one
thing.
Why?
Why would you start shooting?
Okay.
That came out of nowhere.
I didn't do anything.
Should I shoot?
Am I...am I was an accident here?
Alright, shoot him.
There are two cars here.
Okay.
It worked, but...
That guy is getting
stepped on.
Why would he get out of the car?
Alright, I did it.
Let's go to the set.
Kathy really means business.
Seems like we're the only ones who want Bishop alive.
I have a good mind just to let him go work
on the son of a bitch.
I'm about done putting my life on the line to protect
some child molester.
That's our job, unfortunately.
They don't get to dole out the justice.
Well, alright.
So I think I'm understanding.
Go investigate
guy's sick fucking
perverted place.
Do you have a photograph of me and him?
Yes.
Okay, that's it. Bye.
You need evidence.
Yeah, but that whole fucking house was an
giant ball of evidence.
That guy was standing essentially
at the scene of the murder.
With blood all over his body.
And three screaming people.
Dead and screaming, dying.
Mark Bishop, stop! LAPD!
He's not very fast, either.
We're trying to help you, Bishop.
Thank you.
He's a mad hatter.
He takes an uphill.
That was the mistake, you're right.
It's us or McAfee's boys.
Your choice.
You didn't do anything. Wait, come here.
I have a photograph I want to show you.
Hey.
Bishop, that's enough.
I have a letter from your mother. She's worried sick.
Yeah, that's right. Now you stay
right there. And what's this check made
out to you, sir?
Shit!
Mark Bishop, stop! LAPD!
I didn't know that was possible.
I thought it was just a run of...
I didn't know it was possible.
Plus, I'm reading chat
during this run behind the guy.
Sorry.
We're trying to help you, Bishop.
Thank you.
It's us or McAfee's boys.
Your choice.
We both did the same thing.
We both learned how to jump from the same
sensei, apparently.
Move another inch and you're dead.
Dead? Bishop, that's enough.
Bishop, you're under
arrest for the attempted murder of June Ballard
and the rape and attempted murder
of Jessica Hamilton.
All right, I'll come quietly. Just don't
kill me. If you found
me, then McAfee's goons will too.
We need to get out of here.
You stay close. Any tricks
and I'll save McAfee's boys the trouble.
Follow me. I know another way
to get out of this place.
I was going to make an elaborate
place. Christ detective,
they're trying to kill me.
How to stop the McAfee boys. Last chance to back
the hell down. Install a program that
uses the internet.
It'll break everything.
They won't know what to do.
This way. R2, I forgot.
McAfee doesn't make the rules.
You hear me?
Kill them for god's sake.
I don't want to die.
Pop it up.
Shoot the barrels to the stroll of the wall.
Fire away.
No, I'm not very good at this.
I'm not very good at this.
Am I not hit?
What is going on right now?
What the fuck is happening?
Do I need a different weapon?
Do I need an X to pick up weapons?
Am I too far away to shoot
these guys?
Why is it going down?
Okay, honest to god.
Okay, very finally. Now I'm out of
range.
Just curve the bullets.
This should be death.
I pressed
X on it. It didn't do anything.
I saw pick up weapons like three times.
I pressed X.
Okay, now I have it.
Weird.
Why would you do that? Get out of there.
I'm being a bad teammate.
Where the hell was he before?
Was he waiting for me to kill things before?
All the Red Dead Redemption 2 aiming
hasn't paid off?
I got news for you.
It doesn't matter how much
you train in console aiming.
It either auto-targets
or you have an eye closed.
That's just kind of how it works.
What are you doing?
What are you doing? Get off.
Hurry!
Convenient explosive barrels.
Pick up weapons.
Should I pick it up?
I'll try it.
That's not the people I should be shooting at.
Those are our officers.
Stay in cover.
You guys through the window?
It is just one guy left.
Who is left?
This is what I call a result.
Mark Bishop,
first wild film producer,
an all-around piece of shit,
catches a fast ticket to Quentin
for stach rape and attempted murder.
So he gets to spend the next 15 years
playing...
That is just capital J, Detective Phelps.
You don't have such a reputation.
I'm not going to be able to hold on to you any longer.
You're getting promoted.
Go on, get your new assignment.
It was good work.
Welcome, welcome everybody.
Lights on.
Phelps, Bukowski. This your work?
Can I help you, Detective?
My lights are all fucked up.
Yeah, I'll bet you did.
This is a traffic case. You need something?
I'm here to buy a drink
for the two LAPD traffic cops
who broke the back of Guy McCaffey's private army.
You don't have a problem with that, do you, Captain?
Go right ahead.
Get in. I'm buying.
I like this place.
A lot of movie people hang out here.
You like jazz, Cole? The hopheads love it.
Sure, I guess.
Big bands and swing, I can understand,
but this bebop palaver?
How are you supposed to dance to that?
What helps, Leroy? Be nice to them.
You'll like this place.
They treat you right.
You like a table, Leroy?
What do you think we want to do? Stand at the bar like chumps?
I'll get a table ready for you.
Don't look so happy to see me, Alphonse.
I might get the wrong impression.
Cole, this is Alphonse.
He's a French negro from Africa. Can you beat that?
The Congo.
A pleasure to meet you, Alphonse.
Come on, Cole, you can meet Elsa
while they're fixing us a table.
I like her. She's something else.
Maybe another night, Roy.
She's pretty beat up about it.
Get your hands off me.
Don't ever tell me what to do or what not to do, Alphonse.
You got a nice club here.
Don't spoil it.
If you will follow me, detectives,
just through the door.
He was my only real friend, Harlan.
We went through it all.
Do you realize what he meant to me?
Of course I do.
You said it was construction work.
It was an industrial accident, Elsa.
How can I be held responsible?
Elsa, are you going on?
Louis, for God's sake,
he was my best friend.
The only man who ever loved me
without putting his hands on me.
Hi, Elsa.
Here's someone I'd like you to meet.
Cole Phelps, war hero and
crime fighter extraordinaire.
Why would I want to meet another
fascist from the LAPD?
Sorry about this, Cole.
What an evening I'm having.
First a negro puts his hands on me
and then this.
Who do you think you're talking to,
you German junkie whore?
I told you, this guy sucks.
Do you hear me?
Evening, Doc. How's business?
Sanguine.
Louis, help me here.
I'm gonna have to give her
something before her performance.
Blow it off, Cole. These artsy-fartsy
types always get a little flighty.
Meet Dr. Harlan Fontaine,
doctor to the stars.
Mr. Fix-It to the mental wreckage
of Hollywood.
So what about
that drink, boys?
Alright. Case closed.
13.
Not great.
It gets raided, says nothing.
What? I just talked about it for like a full minute.
Only a minute?
Right, gentlemen, take your seats.
Let's get this over before lunch.
Clyde Rose of the
homicide squad has decided to take care
of the retirement. Sounds good.
We will all miss Floyd on the steely edge
he brought to his police work.
The department has arranged a weed
drink at the Galway Arms to quench the mighty
thirst a man gets from
25 years of police work.
Floyd's departure
leaves a place at the top table.
And the chief is seen fit to promote
coal felt from burglary to the
homicide desk.
Stand up, Phelps. Take a chair.
You're in the major leagues now,
Sonny. Rusty Galway,
a fine lawman of the old school, will be
taking you under his wing.
Your first case is the murder of a woman
found last night and bearing all the
signs of the werewolf.
Get out to the scene, lads.
Okay. The streets of LA
line you to patrol the city and attend street crimes.
Each desk off is a new set of street
crimes. Okay.
Do you have the address?
It's been all over KGPL.
It's off Temple Street
between Belmont and Glendale.
Get the sensor bar ready,
Galway. Are we about to see...
I mean, I have a giant one that's ready, so...
Oh, there's an oxymoron for you.
I'd rather you took the wheel.
Ow.
All right, let's go.
What happened to Rose? Parker lost the chief's job.
The word is the chief is going to be hammered
until they're both clearing the desk.
Where does that leave you, Galway?
We got a call. Hold on.
Please me saddle with a chump like you, Phelps.
I didn't ask for you, and I don't want you,
so keep it to yourself.
See if you can learn something about
real cops.
What did he mean by the werewolf?
A dahlia. The daily news
came out calling him the werewolf killer.
The examiner came up with the black dahlia.
Were we any closer to catching him?
Not a chance.
It's been months and hundreds of guys running down leagues
and we got nothing.
You don't think this has anything? Why would you...
Don't do that. No, I don't.
3% of murders are domestic, Phelps.
Some guy gets into a beef with his wife, he takes it too far.
This would be the same.
But, cutting someone in half...
This is very far away.
This is a very far away crime that happened over here.
This is a war.
All right, what's it do?
A possible jumper?
You need to get up there.
Let me do the talking detective.
I know a ton of this psychology stuff.
Take the back alley and find a way up there.
I don't trust this guy.
Come on, Phelps, let's get moving.
Are you jumping?
Get sure you warn me where you do.
All right, so I gotta get up there and I gotta prevent him from jumping.
I don't know why for a second, I thought he was gonna kick me.
I'll bring you down with me, Phelps.
Should we not be sprinting at him like this?
Are you crazy?
What are you trying to do?
He's not just gonna do it, right?
Should I not have spread it up there?
Like, as fast as I can?
Is this what you wanted?
I can't do it.
I'll come quietly.
I need some help.
Please, you gotta get me some help.
I made it.
You're a danger to yourself and to others.
Why is everybody cheering?
I just gave like that.
That's right, everybody down there in my audience.
Let's do it.
Back to work we go.
Back to going the streets.
How many chapters have I completed?
Um...
I think this is case 10.
Or this would be case 10.
Coming up.
I think this is the second chapter.
I assume.
No engine sound for some reason.
I don't know why.
Not a scratch, I got it.
Hybrid car.
I feel like we should be in a different video game.
This music.
No engine sounds.
I feel like I should be searching for hidden objects.
I don't know why.
That's what I think of.
Give me a break.
I'll take it.
Bank of America?
Alright, let's go.
I want to do like all these.
I want to match the pre-game.
That's what I think of.
I want to just match the pre-game sounds.
Like.
Cool.
Excellent.
Oh my god.
Slow and steady.
Come on.
It's not like I'm driving on the wrong side of the road or anything.
You know when people are in jeeps?
And they beep at each other.
This car is done.
Did anybody else hear the actual siren that drove by the house?
I don't know.
I did.
Out of the car. Police.
You can't do this.
Does this one have engine sounds?
Kind of.
This is GTA now.
Can you do that?
FBI.
I'm taking the car.
You can?
I don't know if I would believe that person.
You know what I'm saying?
You could go get a fake badge from the party store.
You need your car.
What?
What's the situation?
Half a dozen shooters, sir. Cold blooded sons of bitches.
Real professionals.
What do you mean?
Witnesses say they bounced in, aced the guards, and went straight downstairs.
Christ knows who they're working for.
But whatever's in that vault, they want it bad.
They also shot at us.
I got an achievement made out of wood.
Get off of this, please.
I sometimes just feel like my character is a fucking magnet.
And I'm running through a depolar field.
Take the elevator.
Alright, I'll wait here.
Don't give them a chance to regroup.
Wish me luck.
If this were real life right now, I'd be going,
Fuck! Fuck!
Okay, fuck! Okay!
Okay, here we go!
That leaves you, pal.
In the vault.
Oh, what's taking so long?
And where the hell are you?
He's like, standing behind the car.
You can't live to tell the tale.
That's it.
That's all of them.
Let him live?
He had his opportunity.
Reload loudly in front of him.
Car 11K.
Shots fired, suspects are down.
We're code four here, but I need an ambulance at Bank of America.
Seventh and olive.
Identify coroner and detective headquarters.
Okay, you ready to solve a mystery?
What is this fucking music?
What is this?
Everybody's listening to the same song.
Either that, or this is the intro
to a British television mystery show.
This is where the credits show up.
Calm down!
And Arthur Bradbury as
Detective Doohickey.
Gotta play some hidden object games now.
I was thinking about it.
Oh my god.
This is more side tracking than in Red Dead.
And I have to do it though,
because these are all interesting.
Oh, I almost bulled that guy.
Do the murder investigation.
What about these murder investigations?
Bank of America.
Guy jumping off the building.
I need to do these too.
How is this stalling?
I'm playing the game!
Stalling would be this!
Hey, um...
Does anybody know...
Does anybody know what time Evo starts?
Uh...
It's like next month, right?
That's stalling!
I'm playing...
What am I doing?
How can you be stalling if you're playing
the content in the game that you're playing?
Maybe if I turned on the webcam?
There's always a cop
that's just Kenny from South Park.
He dies instantly.
Give it up!
I can't scare him? He's not a horse.
I'm not trying to kill him.
I'm trying to scare him so he goes...
How did he get up there? A ladder.
Perfect. I'm not trying to shoot him.
I'm trying to make him freak out.
Oh, he's so fucking far away though.
I'm gonna have to shoot him.
All right, now stop. Give up.
I'm trying to shoot him like defeat.
Stop it!
All right, got him.
All right, you're going to jail.
See? I didn't use any force there.
Everybody that
likes to make fun of me for...
Oh, Djerba just shot him in the head.
But I need to find
those mystery coins.
I didn't kill him. What do you mean I killed him?
He's just gonna be missing a few toes.
4 means dead.
No, it doesn't.
No, what? Yes, it does.
Connect 4 means you won the fucking round
and you go on to play the next one.
He's fine. He just had a couple of bruises.
I don't know the
police numbers. I don't know the police numbers!
They just make him up.
That's not real.
That's just like a police movie
TV show thing. We've got a code
141-2652 at
South Point 4 Boulevard.
It's all just, it's like saying
555-5555 for a telephone number.
Oh, get the sensor ready!
I got a haircut.
He's good, Rusty.
He even sounds genuine.
That's Phelps, guys. The war hero.
Defending the honor of murdered humps.
It's the same face.
They're used to it, Phelps.
Moving along, guys. You got your pictures, you got your headlines.
Now scram.
Screeks. Tree.
Body.
Oh. Trollman, this your beat?
Yes, sir. Well, part of it.
Kids park here, they use it like a
lover's lane. It's a
neighborhood. Some trouble, but
nothing like this.
It's known locally as the Morse.
You were first on the scene? Yes, detective.
No one's disturbed the body?
No, sir. We cleared out
them vulture reporters so Pinker in the corner could work.
They're waiting to talk to you.
Go house to house and see what you come up with.
This ain't gonna work. Too bad.
Hold on.
It's not gonna work.
It's not gonna work, guys.
This is an adult
part of the stream.
If you're not at least
allowed to go to an R-rated
movie, then you're not
you gotta get out of here. Cause of death?
Could be the head injuries.
She hasn't been badly stalled.
The cuts look superficial.
I'll know for sure in an hour.
What caused the blunt force injury to the face?
Could be anything from a
baseball bat to a lug wrench.
I'll have more details after the autopsy.
So you're allowed to go to an R-rated
movie if your parents let you.
Yeah, but your parents need to be
watching the stream with you.
You can't prove that to me.
Am I gonna get in fucking trouble
for this shit? I don't know.
Hmm. Interesting.
Okay. Anything else?
It's not gonna work.
What about this wound on the
bite mark? Something removed.
A ring, most likely. I assume it was
taken post-mortem. Missing ring?
Okay. I don't know!
I don't know what to do!
Whatever. If you're not at least
17 with the parent's permission,
you're not allowed to watch the stream at this point forward.
That goes for all of you. 18?
You're not allowed to be here.
Unless your mother told you it was okay.
In fact, no.
You're not even allowed to be here.
Even if your mother says it's okay, you're not supposed to be here.
You understand? Okay, I got it.
Either way, I'll run tests on the lipstick.
Any idea of the time of death?
From the temperature, I'd say after midnight.
I'll confirm with you later.
Oh!
Oh my god!
I thought that was...
What can you tell me about the shoe prints?
Men's size 8.
Pinker lifted impressions for me to
compare back at the lab.
Size 8. Men's size 8.
And one of them has bird shit all over it.
Look at a globe?
Looks like some kind of puzzle or parlor game.
It opens up and there's going to be
chocolate inside.
Okay, okay.
See, that's
the top half of North America
and this is the bottom half of North America.
Okay.
Like that.
There's a couple islands in between.
No, not quite. Maybe a little bit more.
There we go. Okay.
There it is. Alright, now I actually
fucked it up, so hold on.
It looks like this.
There's no sense of any
globe geography.
Oh, I couldn't even do it.
The property of the Bomba Club
North Spring Street,
downtown.
That's not real. See, I told you.
Swiggity Swanky just gave $50
right now. 50.
50 bucks from Swiggity Swanky.
To prevent a Twitch ban,
delete the VOD.
Delete the evidence?
I'm playing a detective game right now
and you want me to delete evidence?
That would go against
Connor Phelps' Code of Conduct here. I'm not going to do that.
Thank you so much for the 50 bucks, though.
Really appreciate it, dude. That's a lot of money. Thank you.
The victim's bag?
We've got keys,
battery.
Looks brand new. Can't be the one used on the bottom.
I don't know why I was just going to say this.
And you're talking about me being concerned about
T.O.S.
I was about to just say two words.
That was it.
Three letter, four letter.
That's all I was going to say.
I don't know why I was just going to say that.
What's wrong with me?
What have you guys done to me?
I used to be so wholesome.
But I didn't even swear.
Can we get to the bomba?
Dude.
Come on. 15 seconds. I got the achievement.
15 seconds. Jump over three things.
How about we go to the bomba?
The bomba.
You're driving, you maniac.
My name's Jerma. I just look at map.
And see that it
I drive that way.
Blip is straight ahead. I drive straight ahead.
Me Jerma, me just fall off.
Cole, come on.
Okay, me go right now.
This is the cookie monster.
This is not in the right voice.
The werewolf? For my money?
We can't rule it out. We need to work the evidence.
You'd love that, wouldn't you?
A big head to hang on the wall.
For the decade.
Been working evidence and beat EKs for six months and got nicks.
There's a difference, Rusty.
Oh? Yeah? I just don't be working it today.
Okay, odd shot.
What's more like it?
The werewolf come back well, leaving us a note in the corpse?
He clearly has a thing for power.
Power over women.
Why not power over the police department as well?
Let me finish this.
A guy opens his mouth again after six months.
I can't believe it.
Come on.
Come on. I don't got all day.
Finish, Phelps.
A guy opens his mouth again after six months of shtoon.
Or some...
Breathe, Phelps.
Breathe, dammit.
I turned off the dialogue.
That's not totally fantastical.
You know, the examiner in the daily news might be good at coming up with...
Turn on cinematic camera?
Can you? There is none.
There's a reason we didn't get the son of a bitch after the short murder was them locusts.
What do you think the werewolf killer is now?
What do you think the tool keys are now?
...somewhere else with the armed forces.
San Quentin.
Another town.
Another country. Who knows?
So, Phelps, I understand you want to turn this into a big case.
But it doesn't work like that, alright?
A case will come and find you.
Can't make it something it ain't, understand?
So you don't think the werewolf has continued to operate in the Los Angeles area?
No chance.
We would have found him.
I need Sentra again.
Just go easy, Phelps.
Say something
Gentleman, what can I get you Phelps and Galloway LAPD chocolate nothing here last night? Yes
I help officer you can start with your name
Garrett Mason, you're the regular bartender on life. I'm a temporary barman. I work for an agency
I fill in at bars across town. Do you remember a woman who came in here last night?
Five feet seven about 110 pounds blonde hair about 40 years of age
You mean Celine Henry?
You know her name. Yes
Do you know anything about her? I don't but the owner mr. McCall serves her most nights
Would you like to speak to him? I would
He said to the back of the club. Where's the hibiscus? You can't miss him. Is there anything else?
Quiet away Phelps. I'll stay here. I'm a little parched
Warming three fingers of rye
Say honey, what time you get off?
Where is on a tip refill my coffee next time honey, that's probably the guy just sitting back here by himself
Detective Phelps LAPD. We're investigating the murder of Celine Henry going to pay you know her Celine
Sure, I know her she and I and
Jacob her husband we go way back. She was here last night
Sure. She's a regular Celine is
was a
Lovely woman. Okay
McCall
Hmm. Hey, you spray me with that flower
Was mrs. Henry here with anyone last night? Not at first
Celine already had quite a head start, but she attracted attention
certainly a
Few gentlemen became very enamored with her and her stories
One guy in particular one guy in particular, you know him going no
He's been in a couple of times. Did they leave together?
Yes
at around 11
If it helps I made the guy's license plate. Ooh
I think this could be a great help sir. Thank you eight eight nine nine
Okay, anything else? That's it
You're a license plate maker
All right, so she's missing a ring
Mrs. Henry appeared to be missing a ring torn from her finger, but not her wedding finger
Celine always wore a red garnet ring
on the large side
Larger than life like Celine herself. Did she have it a long time? Sure
It's way back in her flying days. Did her husband buy it for no it was
It's before Jacob
Haha. Oh, yeah
Really? You got an itch in your ass or what's happening here, man?
I think you know where the ring came from and I think you're gonna tell me. Okay, I bought it years ago
Got him. I carried a torch for Celine in those days
I guess I always have
Roll man never knew about it. Okay, so knowledge of we not now we know
You know a lot more than you. Yeah
You know the husband?
Sure. I know Jacob
He was in the corps
He met Celine on a furlough and married her when the war was finished
Put up with a load of shit
Do you think he killed his wife? No
No, not in my opinion
All right, this guy's got this guy that was very clear
Those are very clear. I do know
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I don't think so
So if it wasn't Jacob, then you probably let her out of here with the guy who killed her
How do you feel about that stole the attitude? Will you know maybe not I tried to get on to Jacob
I rang him up
Asked him to come pick her up like usual
But he refused
As she picked some night to push him over the edge
I rang him back around 11 30, but got no answer
One out of four again. Thanks. Mr. McCaul. Oh, do you think three out of three? Correct?
Would you have an address for Celine?
Three one out of three zero, correct union avenue knows I had to send her home in enough cabs to remember that
All right, we're going to investigate her residence
And see a telephone call it in
Let's get out of here. Can I use your phone? What's the hurry? My stool was just starting to warm up. What is this?
Coke jack doesn't pertain to the case
Sir, can you put that down?
Where's your telephone? Do I need permission?
Operator give me dispatch putting you through now coal felps batch 12 47
I got a code four
I need a registered owner on a license plate two boy eight eight nine nine
Yes, detective. I'll need to contact the dmv. Shall I relay the details via kgpl?
please
Thanks, ma'am
Okay, let's go
Is there anything else I need to do in here a waitress?
Can I have another spoon?
another spoon
Is the guy eating a candle?
I just love the waxy part
Um, okay, I think we just leave
Get some air in here, man
Where's my partner my part? Where's my oh, he's in the car already. Wow
Let's go to the uh, anri residence
Don't don't don't don't do any cookies about the just go this way
You find the booze helps you get through a working day sharpens my investigatory instincts
A smart lawyer might use that to throw out anything you collect today smart man might know it's unwise to stand between the patient
I know it's not a job as long as you're not falling over rusty. I'll let it slide
That's mighty kind
You know, you picked the wrong job welcome to the stream everybody
I hope you're having a good saturday afternoon to do the best we can in this position as homicide detectives that responsibility
Is all the more serious. What is today? No, don't tell me let me guess
It's not political. It's practical
Maybe the men combing hollywood boulevard. It was thursday two days ago yesterday more interested
So today is today is thursday that would have led to her killer. I think today's friday
If only you'd been there
I don't know betty short be alive the japs would have spared pearl harbor
Our ancestors wouldn't have tasted the forbidden fruit minor syntactical error detective galloway
Whoa there
I'm, oh guys i'm on pacific time. So it's different for me. I'm like a whole day
Minor syntactical error detective galloway. I never claimed to be able to prevent crimes. I only suggested a proficiency in solving them
Guess that's the drink slowing you down. Oh my god, brother. Oh brother worse than I could ever three hours equals a whole day
I know you thought nevada was mountain time. It is pacific time because it sits right there on the edge on the bottom tail part
right next to calc 40
in fact
driving from
Las vegas to los angeles takes about three and a half
That guy's gonna explode I didn't do it that's how we got it we got a code four
What's your code? No, uh, we got another code four
Maybe I drive better if you shut the hell up
See
That's what I have to say. Maybe I would drive better
Yeah, i'm gonna get another code four here
I'm currently sitting inside of a car about to explode just might as well call it in and get it ready
and uh have a
That's when they cut out because the car exploded
Hello, who's here?
I can't just go to the front door
What was that the back door?
I have to look in the
That I have to go in the front door
All right, come on. That's a weird front door. It is
What is this door? I've never seen a house with a door wedged into the side like that
I'll try the back door right here. That's what I just did
So I was already one step ahead of you
I thought I was gonna elbow the glass
This game would be more immersive if like every three or four seconds he went
And there's no way to turn it off
Oh, here's another
family burnt to death
Well, I'm saying house fire deaths are suspicious
That's okay
You said I had to go back doctor. The fires are cathartic
They allow you to confront your past. You said the house would be empty
Are you taking the medication I have prescribed?
You said the house would be empty
I heard them screaming
Circumstances were unfortunate
My colleagues had made all the necessary arrangements the house would be empty
You're killing me the deaths were unfortunate but you have dealt with death before
I want you to come here. You said the house will be empty
No, that's the weirdest wrong number i've ever had
Okay
Let's search
Come on. Give me some clicks
Give me some clicks
Goggles it would take a smarter man than me to connect that. Oh
I heard a chime. I don't think that's right though
No, where?
They have all these audio cues in the game and then they play a bunch of other ones
This isn't what we're looking at. That's a key though. You can at least test to see where it goes to
fireplace
Mirror, uh, he's definitely filming somebody from the other side of this wall
All right, let's we're gonna go corner to corner here start on the front door
Burglar used the pry bar. Why did you kick the door in?
You think i'm gonna climb through a broken window in a 30 suit. You got another thing coming buster
He's that's true
Because as we all know with inflation, that's like five grand
Everybody drinks the same alcohol
Oh good to me
Yeah, like that's just one small complaint
Is like I wish like it's 30 bucks back then but like it's fucking 2006
Obviously having problems just make it like that what it would be actually if it cost it would be like, you know
1500 bucks is like a really expensive suit
Irritating, you know, give us something to go. She's over up. You can find me at apartment two
Two
Okay
No, one of my edges drank like this to be feeling the back of my hand
That's when the game came out in burglary and get technical services out here. I'll talk to the neighbors
Don't take all day. I thought it felt so I get nasty when i'm thirsty
nothing
Galloway homicide badge number five sixty four
Requesting technical services for a suspected 459 at 142 north union
No, it's not
Uh, hold on you gotta wait till you hear that
the little the little
twinkle
See the goggles were important a regular Amelia Earhart in her day. The ring looks distinctive
That's the ring
speaking of rings
This is a ring
Uh, well, actually, I don't know if this could be a couple of different things though
No, never mind. This is a seed container
First the stuff is junk. Why explain the missing ring? You can tell because of how deep it is
about this
Don't think this is any use to us
Okay, and that's it
Congratulations. Now I have to go to the neighbor
Is that as simple as walking next door? Do I have to drive there? Wait, what was that twinkle?
See
Now it's the newspaper. Never mind a pretentious streamer references himself only things still important to him. What the fuck
Which neighbor is it?
There's a bunch of neighbors this how this one
Oh, there's a neighbor
Hey
It wasn't safe around here anymore. Are you the neighbor?
I guess
LAPD, I guess you're the neighbor henry miss horgan
Jennifer horgan
I've known selene for more than 10 years our children grew up together
What's going on officer? Did you see mrs henry go out last night? Well, I'm no busybody you understand but
Selene had been drinking and she and poor long-suffering jacob had a terrible row
What's around jacob may have given her a black eye
He stormed out and she went back inside. Did he come back? No
Selene was listening to music and shouting until she left around 10 pm
She was very drunk to have been driving
But she is not the sort of person you can stop from doing something when her dander is up
It was my hat. What is this about officer? Is selene all right?
I'm afraid mrs henry has been murdered ma'am
murdered
Oh my god
I'm afraid I need to go and then sit down
All right, make sure you lock your door too because the murderer said he was coming here to kill you next
Imagine you imagine there was an option
Have a good day. Let's see what jacob has to say for himself. I don't think jacob is our man
But we should see what he has to say
How do you start using these I have these free points
Jacob henry the husband strange husband jacob henry had a violent argument with his wife last night
He's looking more likely row
The rod keeps the house looking like that's probably deserved
The skipper says bring him in keep the hatchet back for a while fine by me hidden object
So it ain't the werewolf killer after all to every opening from mission impossible movies
I always said work the evidence
I only stipulated a connection to the bd killer as an avenue of investigation
We should leave open and as far as i'm concerned it still is
And then eventually this is gonna go
It's gonna be an elaborate intro
Just get out of the car
Climb over the fence like a real gamer
You but you can handle that one, but you can't handle this one
Whoa?
Okay
Going hard you follow my lead
It's right here
You jacob henry yeah, yeah
Who's asking la pd you're under arrest for the murder of your wife selene henry murder
Selene save the dramatics for rkl pal you got bigger problems
What the hell are you talking about?
You come in here. You tell me that selene is take a seat. Mr. Henry. We're gonna have a look around then we'll talk
Jesus
I'm sorry
Okay more let's see what else we got don't talk
Seems irrelevant. Okay living room living room. We've got a lot of boxes in here
And
I don't know what you're cooling here. You're pointed directly pretty much at the you put that in the living room, man
It goes in there something in there like probably toothpicks or something
Someone's trying to run away real quick
Why are you trying to run away
chickens
Move the pencil, uh
Shade an area what the hell what am I doing?
Wait, wait, wait
This guy wrote like something an invisible ink
Thanks
Thanks for the offer
Need you to do something about my wife
Okay, the old lady thanks for the offer need you to do something about my wife
Why would you write that in silly ink?
Well, we got you
You're fucked down, man
All right, so we go right to that. I mean you did it's like we could go right to like silly ink
So who could have killed Celine? Where did she go last night? Jacob a bar, I suppose
Look, I don't know writing on hold on a minute lipstick markings on body revealed. Fuck you
Don't force missing jewelry
size h shoes
Wait, he has size 11 though club owner mccall reports telephoning jp hamill prelee on night of murder
Oh
forced entry
Size 11 men's shoe to match victims injuries. Well, hold on
He put he put on different feet
What about his alibi?
You know where she went jacob. You're lying. Why would I help you if you keep lying to me?
Look, i'm telling you I don't
Know well that you got he got a phone call, right?
Hold on
You have different shoes club owner mccall reports telephoning jacob henry repeatedly on night of murder
But there's this is there's no cell phones. He didn't pick up
But he wouldn't be able to see there were missed calls
We know she went to the baba club the bartender there. All right got him
He calls me if things are getting out of hand and I go and I bring her home
He called me last night
I said no phone rang a couple more times after that
I ignored his feet grew
All right, i'm gonna pay attention. I'm gonna have to live with that last contact with victim
When did you last see your wife mr henry?
last night
I went to see her we talked things
Got a little out of hand
I left wait is that I think that's true. Hold on
Sure, can I take a look at the bottoms of your feet? I don't know. I would say that he's telling the truth, but
Isn't that what this that that's like within? Yeah
This is a good cup. No, wait, they fucking yeah, they did fight
They fought you tailed her watched her come out of a bar and then beat her to death admit it henry
They did get in a fight. The neighbor said that would I do that detective?
because the neighbor said
That you would you that is why?
My wife was a drunk
It was a sickness with her
Doesn't mean I didn't love her
Would you stop loving your wife if she was unwell?
No, I wouldn't
motive for murder
Why did you kill her jacob things will go better. Why did you kill her?
That's a lousy thing to say
I never
Gave up on my wife
Uh, he's not look at his eyes though. They're darting around. I love the place
So what did he did the fucking mystery ink? I don't believe you jacob
I think you didn't have the guts to do it yourself. Did you write it?
You want to back that up with something big mouth?
Huh? Yeah, I have a mystery ink here
Impression from no written by jacob henry concerning wife there it is get done the note by the phone suggests you meant her harm
You want the truth?
truth is I was sick to death of her
I was
Trying to have her committed
We're still going to need you to come downtown. Mr. Henry
How many points we get this all down on paper jacob how you got fed up with your wife and how you figured killing her
Would bury all your troubles
Kill my own wife
She was a loss of the trap and you just couldn't stand it anymore shut your goddamn mouth
So now you're gonna tell me you loved her. Ah, the da goes all gooey over remorse jacob
Now you assaulted him. Okay, here we go
Here's the problem, but I haven't played in a long time. I forget how to punch. How do you punch is it r2?
How do you punch?
I haven't done this in like a month. What's punch? What's this?
It's punch i'm hitting every single button
A square
I don't this doesn't look good for you jacob
I don't I seriously don't know what it is
Okay, it's x it's l2 and x
It's unfailable by the way, so that's good
I think
That was a month ago when I heard the special from restaurant guys
L2 and x and square i'll keep old slugger here company
Okay, use his phone
Where's his phone?
Trash, where's your phone?
Operator message for kgpl
Putting you through now felps badge 12 47
How could I help detective?
I need a patrol unit to transport a suspect back to central
certainly detective
You have a message from the corner. Do you wish to be put through?
Yes, ma'am
Carruthers, it's felps completed the autopsy several wounds to the head from a blunt metal instrument wounds
Closest match would be a socket wrench handle
So the cause of death was the blunt no the blast was from hemorrhage and shock from the fractured ribs and multiple injuries caused by the stomping
Anything else?
He's some kind of sex fiend
Jesus
Why everybody's such a fucking sex fiend thanks doctor operator give me r and i
jesus
Any word on an owner for that vehicle license was two boy eight eight nine nine
Yes, detective the plate belongs to a brown 1936 poniac
Registered owner is one alonzo mendez
a 402 south fremont street apartment 16
Thanks
any other messages
one detective
From captain donnelly he wants any and all suspects returned to central interviews to be set up immediately
Got it. We're coming in. Um
This is great. Let me tell you something. You know when you had a school project where you had to have like a an older female voice
If you're making like a video with your friends or something and you have like your mother do a recording
Anybody else do that? Like that was like your mom helping you do like the english video project
Did anybody ever do like a video project for like school?
None of you did
Or like for like a play or something you need to like an older woman's voice
And that was like one of the teachers which is record like a sentence for you guys. No one did that
Nice fucking kids these days
Didn't even record your mother like saying weird sentences for like your school project
All right, where are we going?
here
Alonzo mendez
Sound like a man who moonlights as the werewolf don't sound like a man. I'd let my daughter anywhere in here
You've got a daughter spend enough time drink. How old are you?
You guys know how old I am easy
Kids these days
It's been enough time drinking call you'll find yourself with any number of things you don't want. Nope, you just he cut me off
That's why you never sold it
Exactly
Do you have the vaude of your mother doing that? No
I use a pay phone guys. I used to call my parents collect because I got detention
I needed to tell them that they had to come and get me later. They know exactly what they're gonna get
This is the apartment
Wait, why was it? I got a little twinkle here. Hold on
16 mendez apartment 16
Why was I a bad kid?
I mean bad kid
Detention didn't mean you were a bad kid detention means that you had a teacher
That didn't like the fact that you would take your shnakers off in class and juggle them while they were trying to do a lesson
You know like
shut up teacher
Here the apartment's up on the top floor
I mean, it's not like one time I hid it in the closet in my history class
And stayed in there for probably five full minutes while the teacher was starting the class
And then I just fucking burst it out and fell down on the floor
That actually happened. All right, where are we going?
16 no elevator here
You just kick the door in
Oh, I've always wanted to do that
Oh more notepad stuff any more invisible ink
Elevators didn't exist in these times. Yes, they did. I just took them on
Don't lie to the streamer. Don't lie to me. I doubt it. It looked like anything
gee
Somebody said fear fear
Fear fuck cursive, man, probably nothing
What else is in your
record player
Books. Oh, wait, i'm not done with this. That's the only door i'm allowed to kick down, isn't it?
What does it want me to do cigarettes?
Did I miss anything else?
What about over here?
and uh
What is this weird? What's about this weird room?
This apartment is very strange
This is a weird apartment man that like the apartments aren't like this
Okay, so we have
the clothes on the ground
got a dresser
and then a painting set
None of that looks important
um
A toy
No, this is room's clean
a shoe
We got him how to get these to ray size eight could help place mendez at the scene this dad
This dude was there
Found the killer don't even need egg. I got this. This is like the feet crime
Insistent with selene's injuries and the blood can be typed
And this looks like some lipstick doesn't it same one same brand brothers could match the color and brand of the body
We have the murder weapon better get pinker down here. Why keep it? Why not throw it away?
I think these clowns are geniuses
Thank your stars. You caught a break captain donald begin to like you
Hey, what gives la pd you're under arrest
Do not lose that son of a bitch stay right there
Mendez stop right there
I just need to look at your feet. That's all I need to do
Can I dark souls him? You don't need to do this alonzo
Ow, he's gonna get away
No, don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. I had an opportunity and I did see
I could have driven driven right into the gas station
But I didn't where you going, man. I got an idea
Get him next to my window call keep me alongside his vehicle and i'll stop the son of a bitch
Okay
Hit him cold spin him out
Come on
Get it
Got it. I'm trying to shoot out his tires. All right. Well, well now what do we do?
No, he's he's he's in there get him out of there. What?
Get him out. You don't need to shoot his tires anymore. This thing's gonna blow up
That is that it did I beat him? Did I win?
I ain't saying a goddamn thing
and justice
Has been served
You did a grand job lads
folks
That's quite a way to acquit yourself in your first outing as a homicide investigator
It seems this city has a new and vengeful guardian
Considering the evidence against your suspect my feet do all the talking with which a report was compiled
I foresee a safe passage through the courts and the d.a agrees with me
Brutality on a scale such as this deserves retribution
the people
And the press of this city demanded I didn't oh, that was awkward
I did all the work though
So how was our report there 18 and uh, that was
Come on that's pretty good. That's close enough 18 out of 19 5 out of 6. I got one question wrong
I'm never gonna make any money though
5,000 that's like it's like
That's like what 50 60 70 thousand dollars
Do I have to make any money?
That's only a b
That's what that's fine
Thirsty
It is the golden butterfly the game is fun it's always a guy with a club
Galloway got it skipper
I think this is the nudity mission. Oh that we already saw the nudity mission
Unless there's a nudity mission after the nudity mission
New case in which case male dumped in plain sight in the grass at the end of hill street hacks are all over it
Captains trying to fend them off that sounds awfully similar
The first rule of police work is make no assumptions until you've seen the evidence wait
Are we breaking open like a serial killer case where so, okay
Hold on a minute here. I think we're getting to the meat and potatoes
I think I know the place where they found the lady it overlooks somebody's a serial killer. Let's go
All right. Oh, give me a second. Give me uh, let me just grab um, i'm like i'm craving something. You know what I mean?
I'll be right back
Give me like uh, give me like i'm gonna like blend up some fruits. Okay
I'll be back in like 40 minutes. I'm just kidding. Don't I me just saying that probably made everybody leave i'm back in two minutes
All right beer back. All right
I'm sorry. I had to make something
This one's even this one's even
see
Well, okay, that looks really fucking gross in this tiny camera
That looks like a blood-stained windshield
All right. Hold on. It's fruits. It's blueberries
blackberries raspberries
It's fruits guys
And it gets like stuck in your teeth. It's the worst
Anyways, I don't have cameras on because I don't do cam. I don't do it
You understand?
Guys, I don't do cam
I thought that was a close-up of a tortilla
No, that was my face
That was my face
Yeah
Yeah, yeah
He's so insecure. No, I don't like
I don't like this. Let me look. I don't like this
The reason why I don't like face cam is because like i'm it's i'm just like here
Just sitting here people just looking at my face
You did a decent job in the henry case felps not bad for your first time. Just in case you're curious. I'm still here
Don't go getting ahead of yourself. That's one clearance under your belt
Now it's a new day with a new dead lady that needs our attention
No assumptions until we see the evidence, right?
Right, I sure am adding a lot to this video footage here might get long after all
Phelps d what d what?
Where are we supposed to go up top? Okay, I fucked it up. You have to react more
Okay
Jesus felps, where am I fucking going? I have to go up get back in the car. I've got to go up and then right
Give us more reactions calm down
Reaction i'll give you a reaction
Oh boys boys, you know as much as I do
I'll be holding a press conference once the autopsy is being completed
I have two of my finest investigators on the case
Fresh from bringing down the sword of justice on the crazed sex captain aren't there similarities between this murder and the murder of selene henry?
Yeah, here's the big one elizabeth short for that matter. You don't believe there's a crazed sex killer at large
Women boys be sensible
We have the greatest police force in the world with the greatest guy. He's the serial killer
All right, let's play red dead. I figured it out. How can any killer continue to be that?
be advised
We keep the gas chamber at san quentin primed for the sons of king who continue to believe they can take a life in the city
Of angels. Yeah, right any new leads in the dahlia case
Run along boys and let these officers get to work
We have god's work. I'm still having fun playing this one. Why would I change games when I was liking and playing this one?
What do we have captain?
I got the same body type as him that same side like stomach profiles. I know what it's like
You know, you know what you have the same stomach profile
You were first on scene you
So what happened shows over keep moving all of you?
Who was first on scene? Which one of you?
You
What did you do?
What happened here?
Who did it? Why is there a blip here?
What do you want me to make sure the evidence gets back? What do you think sir?
Oh, god damn it. It's another fucking naked body
Is it like a guy?
Similar remote what the dahlia shit? I don't think so. Celine henry. That's a closed case
This is probably another sad sack who lost his temper with the proud. Is it naked bodies from here on out?
Watch your mouth though
All i'm saying is we got enough to do without reopening closed cases. Talk me through it now severely battered on display
Footprints would indicate that she has been stomped
Size of the footprints would seem to indicate a smallish men's shoe. What's a shoe did mendez wear?
You finished no, i'm not
At a glance, I would say strangulation is the cause of death. I need to do further tests for semen
Angry boyfriend they were married. They'd be at home not humping out here in lovers lane
You mind if I examine the body you might guess
Okay, whatever up
Look at your mark is very distinctive
I'll do some comparisons back to the lab and get back to you
She's looking around for like a car or something. This is fucked up. It looks like she was tied up
Does it first but that would leave a mark on her other wrist too. Let's check out her watch might have been torn off
No wrong. No, no
Quick quick quick quick quick. I don't want to be here any longer than I have to what's this another wedding ring finger
fourth finger left hand
wedding or engagement ring violently removed this is the same thing as the other one
Am I like in bizarro land? Are we doing the same one?
The stopping angle in the henry case was it reported in the press small men's footprint was
Every detail a copycat would want was there in the story
Okay
I think that's it
Anything else
Oh emote only mode
Emotes only
Okay, there's so many seeds in this
Oh, we have a name. Can you run deirdre muller by rni?
No, I don't like a second raspberries and blackberries. It's just full of seeds
And then it's like you're just drinking popcorn kernels. I need to strain this shit
I did money the motive was robbery. Why not take the money? That's it in here, right got a name
cash
Detectives rni says that deirdre muller of 130 north bonnie bray was reported missing this morning by her husband hugo muller
Maybe that's it grab the husband take him downtown and work him over and have this wrapped up
What about not making assumptions and going on the evidence?
Here we go
small feet
Okay
How's that? It's not it's good. So it can't be mendez because mendez had size eight
Feet
It's time to bring it up line up
only feet though
All right, so we're gonna go to the mall of residence residential address of murder victim muller
I got my small feet all over the crime scene
I thought you were on our way to lock up the husband if it doesn't work out that
Deirdre muller has suffered enough
More than enough
Cole she was a woman wasn't she?
Around about my third divorce. I realized women might not be the pure angels we imagined
They're married ain't you felt don't make any insinuation. She's not trying to get in the car
Hey, it's a woman. She's the mother of my children
You're a father cool, but don't tell me your eye don't bend this conversation is over
I can't
There's nowhere to go. I fucked this whole thing up. I could go this way
Why don't you drive a car down here?
Is there a jump I can go up to get out? There we go out
That was a shortcut too
Slow and steady. Come on
Okay, what kind of music do we have this time?
No, I know what we've got. We've got the romantic comedy
The love interest shows up in the bar where the two comedy guys are hanging out and it's slow motion zooms in
to her walking around and
Potentially looking in our direction
Eat your berry puree
Yeah, I will enjoy my baby food. Thank you very much
Give me a fucking vehicle damage. I can't help it
No, Jeremy. This is a different. No, this is I I want it to be the the romantic comedy love interest scene
Whatever your version in your head is fine
Had to skip the red dead streams glad you're back. Hey, it's good to be back
I do uh
I do understand that red dead is brand new game and along a lot of people you're driving you maniac must play lists
And I don't expect people to sit there the whole time. So welcome back. Thank you
It was gone for a day. Well that well that person was saying that they didn't watch my red dead streams
Because they didn't want to get spoiled and I completely understand
Hope you enjoy the game when you play it
I didn't watch the red dead streams because they suck phelps and galloway la pd
Is that's what are you?
That this was so much fun. What are you talking about? What's your name? I had so much fun on those streams. Oh, he's smaller
Can we come in? What kind of baby food are you drinking right now?
Thank you
Could you have a seat for me michelle?
We're gonna have a look around
He's getting high on baby food
Why do I always read the worst feedback?
Because that's that's just the cookies
Oh
Cookies, how about what was it? What was the joke? Come on. What was it?
I forget. I don't remember something about a restaurant. There's something about ordering from the special and then it was a cookies or something
What was it?
I don't know. It's a cabinet
We got uh, we got a
We've got a cabinet and we also have
I won't put down that
lemon
Cabot I can do that better. There's a lemon on the table. There's also a cabinet
I can't do it anymore
Too old i'm trying to have my jaw like snap up
This isn't what we're looking at. I got a mouthful of baby food. Whatever turn on the webcam. Why that's why it's not on
Half of these things are so fucking embarrassing
Times 10 if the webcam was on
Don't forget somebody's birthday
But I told you I would be doing this shit. I'd be saying like
Cabot if the stream was off. I'll give you a real story here. So after I watched infinity war, uh
Me and kim watched it
And I didn't even know I had no idea
Uh kim walked in
I was just sitting there on the computer and she's like, will you please stop?
I was like, what are you? What are you talking about? What do you mean? Please stop?
She's like you keep saying the same line from her body and I was just sitting up here going
I know what it's like to lose
To know so desperately that you're right
Like I was doing it like over and over again
I was just doing it. We're getting a couple of seed boxes. No sign of a wedding ring
So everyone everyone that thinks me saying like oh cabbage is like no I I would be doing that
In fact, I would be doing it like 15 times more if I wasn't on camera
It's actually keeping me in check being like recorded
feet
Oh, these are only size eights
Size eights
Oh, yes, the killer did have feet
Well, because why are we looking for like
Well, no, we're looking for smaller
Cookies cabbage
Is this about mommy
Daddy is trying to find her
Please tell me she's okay. Oh, this is not good. I'm sorry to have to tell you this michelle, but
Your mother is dead
Do you think you could answer a few questions for us try
Oh shit, okay. Hold on
This is the daughter is like this is
I gotta be careful because she put on some of your mother's jewelry was missing. Can you describe her things?
ring
But why would she know those I never paid much attention to that stuff. Well, she she would she would just know that right?
When you would I mean I just I just asked her
I just asked her for michelle. I'm not gonna bad copper. She's a kid. She wore a wedding ring
Let me chose it herself
Rose gold wedding band and the matching diamond and ruby engagement ring
She wore a watch
Yes
the yellow gold elgin watch
Daddy bought it for her birthday
It was kind of a makeup present
Okay, last contact. Let me hold away. Let me see this shit first. I don't want to fuck this up
All right. There's a rope on the lady's neck
Missing watch and ring so they both she that maybe she took them. I don't know
Small men are we sure that's a small men's footprint and not like a small woman's footprint
Do we know the make and bottle of that shoe?
I don't really have much to go on. So when did you last see your mother yesterday afternoon?
I went to a dance at Belmont high
I was supposed to pick me up, but she didn't show so what did you do then? I was upset
Daddy came instead
Okay. Well now why would she be lying about this?
Do I have anything?
And did he come and get you?
of course
Some boys offered me a ride home, but I don't I don't sense a why here
So you were hanging around the school for quite a while
What happened with your father? I don't know
what
I called and called and finally he answered
He came straight away then
Oh, we're getting rocky here. Your mom and dad are
Happily married
What are you saying? Of course they are
Oh, yeah
Why is dad picking you up instead?
They weren't happy were they Michelle? Did your father ever hit your mother? Just the once if the one
She said she would leave him if he ever did it again
Her brooch pin to make up for it
Always wore her golden butterfly
Thanks, miss muller tooth two out of three. What was the third? What?
Hold on. What was the third issue?
Daddy the police are here
I'll talk to the police
She wasn't telling the truth on she's not even out of school
You can't come in here interrogating her like she's your wife was found murdered this morning
Found oh
But she only
We have some questions that we would like to ask you
Sure. Yeah
Yeah, i'll do my best
Okay
footprints at the crime scene
What is that photo down there?
That's a really odd photo. What size shoe do you wear? Mr. Muller?
Why do you ask?
It's routine sir. Simple process of elimination
Nines, I think
Bullshit you got eights in the bedroom. You got eights in the bedroom
He's got eights in the bedroom
That's funny. The work boots we found here are size eights
Why lie about it if you've got nothing to hide book them because I always get teased about the size of my feet
You know small feet small always been true in my experience
small what
small
ego
Well, I uh, just to let you go I wear a size six so I mean I wear a size six women's
I I wear a size 10. Oh, you want me to prove it on stream? You want to go get my shoes?
No, i'm not you phoned in a missing person's report this morning. Yeah, that's right
Uh, my wife didn't come home last night. She left around she left around 9 30
Michelle was out of dance. She called me to let me know that deejay didn't turn up
Oh, that's bullshit
Because your daughter had to call you motherfucker your wife gotcha by herself to bars nightclub mother fucker
What are you suggesting you suggesting my wife's loose?
Now is not the time for you to be pushing me. Mr. Your daughter said you were having an argument
We argued about who would pick up
Michelle
I worked a full day. I wanted to come home put my feet up my vice my size eight feet by the way
Not that small
uh alibi
Michelle bolder reports calling home repeatedly with no answer on the night of the murder
Okay
So you were here all night? You stayed in while your wife went out to pick up your daughter
Yes, that's correct
Well, I didn't answer the phone. I don't wait right because
Yeah, you nobody answered. So you didn't yeah
Yeah, you're in deep shit.
Yeah, cause your daughter called you over and over again.
Movements of victim. What the hell does that mean?
Your wife went to pick up Michelle?
Yes. That's right.
What happened, Hugo? You got any theories?
Because we're starting to like you for this.
The car park by the school is kind of dark.
Maybe somebody jumped her there. Did you try the parking lot?
Your wife was beaten and then strangled.
In the case you had no alibi.
And the history of violence taught your wife.
That's not, that's not true. God damn it.
Do I have any evidence of that though?
Can I say your daughter told me?
I can't say that you did that.
Oh fuck, alright. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Cause he bought it cause he was trying to be...
It is true, Hugo. You're a violent man.
I got it. I got it. Oh my god.
Can I just take a second?
Your daughter and your wife were scared of you.
Brooch. Brooch. Brooch. Brooch.
I just wanted to look.
Brooch.
I know about the golden butterfly, Hugo.
And how you bought your wife off the last time you heard her.
She liked to spend money, alright?
Dresses, jewelry, her hair. It drove me god damn crazy.
Crazy enough to kill?
Do I look like a Rockefeller?
Nobody likes a cheapskate, Hugo.
Thanks for chiming in.
Getting hostile with us is a very bad idea, Hugo.
What was the... I'm no murderer.
Make some arrangements for your daughter.
And then present yourself to Central Station for questioning.
You gotta be kidding me, Phelps. Put the cops on.
Not good enough.
This is an outrage. I didn't kill my wife.
Your daughter is in the next room, Mueller, so I'm giving you a break.
Don't make me change my mind and don't make me come looking for you.
We should go back in there and bust his ass.
One, we need to break his alibi, check phone records, canvas the neighbors.
Two, we have motive of domestic violence, which probably goes for half the men in L.A.
Three, we have no evidence tying him to the crime scene.
Hello. Detective.
Oh, I thought the MPC was waving.
Why would we do this?
Yes, ma'am.
I heard the terrible news over the radio.
You heard the terrible news through the window.
Yes, sir. They had a row last night?
Seed baby food.
I heard Mrs. Mueller screaming.
Did you see Mrs. Mueller come home late last night at all?
No, not at all.
I did see Mr. Mueller put something in the incinerator earlier this morning, though.
I told him he was a god. Let's get this bum downtown and into his cell.
He's like incinerating his wife's body.
Look, there he is now.
There it is. There it is. He's incinerating.
He's incinerating. Sir, what are you incinerating?
Step away from the incinerator.
What is it?
I'll let him get away.
What is it? It's a shoe.
We need this guy to make the clean.
He's incinerating his shoes.
No time for that.
Can I get on the tricycle?
Jay's asking him on the tricycle.
Enough running, Hugo.
Hands up.
That's what we can see them.
Turns out it was just like a turkey.
No, you don't understand. I was trying to cook the shoes. Leather. It's beef.
This doesn't look good, Hugo.
I can explain the blood.
Get him booked in at Central, officer.
Then put him in an interview room.
Where's the shoes? The shoes did it.
Yes, sir, detective.
Is there someone you can call, Miss?
I don't...
No one's home and...
You need somewhere to stay, Michelle.
You have other family? Grandparents? Aunt's or uncle?
Call Aunt Helen, but she lives in Acres Field and...
Call her.
We're going to get someone down here from Juvenile Hall to talk to you in the meantime.
Juvenile Hall?
We ought to get some uniforms down here.
Why are we sending her to Juvenile Hall?
To take care of the kid.
What?
It would take a smarter man than me to connect that.
Start playing the violin.
Oh, that's evil. That's not okay.
Thank you for your assistance. Bye.
Telephone. I need a phone.
Operator, give me dispatch.
Putting you through now.
At first I thought the phone wasn't connected.
Phelps, 1247.
Help, detective.
I need an address on a Belmont High School.
That's not it.
Checking for you, detective.
Thanks for your help.
Nice made-up name. Told you.
Oh, wait, that's not it?
Didn't we just arrest the guy?
Homicide Division, badge number 564.
Go ahead.
Did we get Ray Pinker and a technical services team
to a house at 130 North Bonnie Blay Street?
Send someone down to Juvenile Hall
to look after a young lady.
What if I just tossed the notebook out the window?
I don't need any more evidence.
Oh, fuck, I did leave mine. Whatever.
No harm done.
Are they trying to get to me?
Why won't I pick up the radio?
I won't pick the radio up.
Sorry, I can't reach the radio.
Uh-oh, he's gone rogue.
I'm on my own time now.
I'll take care of this myself.
One hot dog, please!
What? What do I have to do?
Do I have to get ice cream?
One of them was assaulted.
Yeah! Yeah!
Do I have to go get my partner?
You're a great crowd.
Do I actually have to answer the radio
before I can come here?
God damn it. Okay.
Yeah.
Nope. All right.
Okay.
Is it all seed at the bottom?
This is going to be disgusting.
Who the hell is this?
Why are we chasing this person?
Watch out for the kids smoking weed under here.
Or cigarettes, either or.
You. You.
Oh, that wasn't you.
That wasn't you.
It's you.
Quick.
And he's slowing down, slowing down, slowing down.
Just enough for me to get him.
Scripted.
Who is this guy?
11K, go ahead.
Really?
What's your name?
So we got him.
Who's asking?
We can do this the easy way or the hard way.
Name's Eli Rooney.
You've been in trouble with the law before, Eli?
Some.
What are you doing around here?
I like to keep an eye on the children.
Strictly paternal, is it, Eli?
Don't sass me, boy.
A woman was abducted here last night, Eli, and murdered.
And I would love to make you for that, you low-key motherfucker.
Well, I wouldn't know nothing about that.
A woman, you say?
I like them a little younger than that.
Turn out your pockets, Eli.
Why would I do that?
Because I'm about to break your fucking skull, Eli.
What the fuck is wrong with you?
You're under arrest, Eli.
You're in very deep trouble.
It's a brooch.
Get some backup down here, Rusty.
We need to get this one downtown and into a cell.
Okay.
I'll tell them.
So wait, that means, all right, so what about the other guy?
What time did you see the person park the car?
Late last night, after school social, maybe 1 a.m.
Let me keep it a good eye out lately.
We've had problems with the child molester.
Eli Rooney, we've met him.
Filthy son of a bitch.
Excuse me?
He was here yesterday before the dance.
Was it him you saw park the car?
I don't know, sir.
I'm not pressing any buttons.
It's just going quick.
I'd like to say yes, but the truth is, it was pretty dark.
Would you say Rooney is violent?
Yes, sir.
I would say so, yes.
Thanks for your help.
Oh, okay.
Wow.
This is the car?
Yes, sir, detective.
Have you looked it over?
Superficially.
I was told to wait for you guys.
Thanks.
We'll take it from here.
Okay.
Well, I wonder what this stuff is for.
Right.
Blood and skin samples.
We better get Ray Pinker out here.
Just some bloody stuff.
The overalls are stenciled HM.
The motor is a mechanic.
I wonder what Eli does for a living.
It's from a Chrysler.
Could be important.
Chrysler, tire, iron.
Anybody have a phone?
No evidence in here.
Time to call it a night.
Phelps, batch 1247.
Detective?
I need interrogations set up at Central
for both suspects being held in the Mahler homicide case.
Oh, we've got to figure this shit out, then.
Certainly, detective.
I'll get in touch with the watch commander.
Thank you.
Interrogation time.
I'm not very good at these.
Is there something wrong with this car?
I mean...
I can't...
I guess so.
Get out.
I did not do that.
I say we make Rooney for this.
I think we should lay it on him.
More at the police station.
The DA will love him for it.
Even if he didn't do it?
Who cares whether he did it?
You have kids, Phelps.
He needs to be taken permanently out of harm's way.
And we let Mueller slide?
For a while.
He gets a free pass for now.
I don't know about Mueller. My gut says Mueller.
We caught him trying to destroy evidence in his backyard.
And that was his car with the bloody tools in it.
I never said it wasn't Mueller.
Hell, he probably killed his wife,
deprived that poor kid of a mother.
But he's not in immediate danger
to anyone else.
Rooney's a threat to every kid at Bethel.
He's a peeper, Rusty.
We could pick him up for something else.
Do we want to run that risk?
Why don't we just fuse them together
and then try them at the same time?
The court system is so backed up.
Just get them to like a
lab mad scientist lair
and turn them into Goro.
Epic gamer reference.
Hey, nevermind.
Massive ethical nightmare.
Wow!
Let's go to the morgue and let's take a look at some clues
and evidence
and find out
who's the bad guy.
Why is the morgue in elementary school?
Alright, what do we do with...
Hey, that's not the morgue, doctor.
Viewing gallery?
Staff only?
Oh, look.
I think he's any kind of doctor.
Correct.
Take a look at the samples on the bench.
What am I doing?
Oh, I need to... Okay.
Well, it's definitely not the finger trap one.
It's probably this one.
This is a baby's puzzle?
I didn't know it was a puzzle!
He just said, there are three things there.
Look at them.
Come on!
I didn't know what I was doing until I looked at it
for a second.
God, I get like
one and a half, two seconds to figure out
what I need to do with a thing I've never seen?
Come on!
I'm not superhuman!
What's this?
What else you got?
Drink everything in the cabinet.
Oh, these are clay.
Dinosaurs.
Let's see, which one of these is the T-Rex?
Am I supposed to
touch them?
That's it.
Well, thank you, doctor.
You've been a lot of help.
Okay. Thank you, doctor.
Okay. Bye.
Go get the nail gun?
Yeah, that's a really bad sweeping technique.
That's just gonna put it in the air and make everybody start sneezing.
Okay.
Police station time.
Did you have a red light?
I had a red light.
Have we got engine noises back? That's a good thing.
Funny job, that.
Corners.
Not even a scratch.
Small scratch.
We've played enough missions where I know
that if you just get close, it's gonna be fine.
Charge the suspects with murder.
Evidence rusty. Let him do the rest.
Okay.
Interview room one, interview room two.
Are they ready?
Bowler's in two and the pervert's in one.
Get in there and get a conviction.
Hey, you think those vice boys
get any on the side?
Alright, where is it?
Interview room two.
Who's in here?
Your next door neighbor heard screaming
coming from your house.
You were burning your blood-stained shoes.
You can confirm your whereabouts last night.
Your daughter says you're a violent man.
We have everything we need to send you to death row.
And all you have to say for yourself
is I didn't do it.
I swear I didn't kill her.
Give me that lie test. I can prove it.
The lie test.
Give me the lie test.
Why did you burn your shoes, Hugo?
This is what I don't understand.
Because I knew you'd never believe me.
I mean, what?
Why did you do that? Because you wouldn't believe me.
Are you going to tell me what I want to know?
Or do we have to take it out of you in lumps?
You're at your best shot.
I can take whatever you're throwing.
Do you know anything about ropes, Hugo?
As much as the next man?
I was a scout.
I learned some more in the army.
Do we have anything?
Can I look at those rope?
You learned to strangle with the rope in the army?
We've got a bad cop, this guy.
With rope, with my bare hands,
but mainly with wire.
I learned a lot of things in the army,
but I still didn't kill my wife.
For argument's sake,
what type of rope would you use?
If I had to, I would use a triple braid.
Less flex, easier to control.
That's what it was.
That's what it was. He just said the thing that it was.
We found your wife's car.
Someone parked it at the school late last night.
Do you have anything to say about that?
It wasn't me.
Where do you keep your work clothes?
I keep them at work in my locker.
Wait, where?
That was in the trunk.
You killed your wife in cold blood.
You're f-
Enough lies, Hugo.
Your overalls put you at the scene of the crime last night.
My overalls are in the laundry of my house.
Oh, well.
That evidence begs to differ
unless somebody faked it.
Green overalls, blood stained,
with the initials HM
found in the trunk of your wife's car.
They can't be mine.
Why, Hugo?
Because if they were yours, they'd be in the incinerator, too?
Your wife was beaten with a tire iron, Hugo.
An appropriate choice of tool for a mechanic.
I know nothing about any tire iron.
We just picked it up.
It was in the trunk, right?
Tire iron stained with blood
found in the trunk of
Muller's vehicle.
You're lying, Hugo.
You have to come clean on this.
I can take whatever you throw at me.
Put those feet up here.
Your wife drove a Chevrolet, Hugo.
What make of car do you drive?
Chrysler Airflow.
So I guess that explains why
the tire iron that killed your wife came from a Chrysler.
He did it.
You dared the crime.
You got the bloody tire iron. Your bloody clothes are in the trunk.
Check. Wait, wait, what?
Interrogate the other guy.
Oh, that's right. There's another person.
Do I, what? Do I have to like make a choice now though?
If I leave this, is it like,
ah, you fucked it up again, Phelps.
Like it happened before. Can I leave?
Okay.
Where is the other guy? I'm assuming he's in the other interview room.
Which is
where? Over here.
Captain, we were on our way to interview Eli Rooney.
Yes, Phelps, I know.
This particular fiend is an old acquaintance.
An old acquaintance? Equations?
He believes in a wrathful and terrible god.
Whichever way it goes,
he'd deal him personally.
What? Oh.
Okay.
You look like you've had it rough.
You see me asking for your sympathy, boy?
Ah,
fuck, hold on.
This is all we have.
You're down on your luck, Eli.
I had worse.
My family a roadkill during the Dust Bowl.
But you have a job. A parolee has to have a job, correct?
I have me a job down in San Pedro.
I'm looking for something new.
This place you worked have a name?
Hennessey Marine.
I don't like that.
This place, big yellow letters, HML.
This game's hard.
They give you any work wear, Eli?
Sure.
Green cover off.
Yeah, I know he has the brooch, but so?
You ever tie up any of your victims, Eli?
It's not a nice thing to go calling them.
What would you call them?
Calling them.
I can't say.
I learned a long time ago not to go talking about the things I like.
What?
Talking about it just seems to get people's dander up.
Answer the goddamn question, Rudy, before I brain you.
See what I mean?
Short answer is yes.
You have any preference regarding rope, Eli?
I know a good rope from a bad rope,
but that's what you mean.
That's not what you mean, is it?
Any old rope will do me fine.
That's not true.
This is a special rope, right?
This is a special rope would require
because it was the braided rope.
Because it was the braided rope.
A long boy like you, Eli, must prefer...
Don't give me the answers! Stop!
I prefer braids,
until I hitch a braid.
Okay, listen.
You can always tell when I'm like
nervous and waiting.
When I think a long time,
I'm like, what is this jacket? Is it correct?
What's the motive?
You killed Mrs. Muller and stole her jewelry.
That ain't so. Ain't nothing like that.
Bullshit.
I can accuse this, right?
Because of the brooch. He has the brooch.
He stole the brooch.
You're a liar, Eli. You needed the money,
so you killed her.
I've been around some, son.
You got some evidence to prove I stole that
butterfly from that woman?
I don't think I have evidence of that.
I done told you I found that pretty thing.
I never stole it.
What size boot do you wear, Eli?
It's all about the feet.
Kind of like anything I can get my hands on.
I'm wearing elevens.
Oh, really? Put them up here.
There may be five-five, five-six tops.
And you wear size elevens?
I don't think so, Eli.
That might be on the large side.
Maybe tens. Maybe eights.
Now that I've come to think of it.
Why punish children with your iniquity, Eli?
You think I was never punished?
You must know what you're doing is evil.
Well, son.
Nobody's perfect.
But, can I look at my book?
You're as good as done, Mr. Rooney.
All it will take now is some paperwork.
What happened? Did I take too long?
What? Hold on. Wait, wait, wait.
Did I, I pressed,
I tried to look at my, I pressed the middle
PlayStation thing.
Oh, shit. Okay.
The other guy has so much evidence against him.
But he keeps on going like,
That's what I do and I like it.
Like, what? How do we, how do I know
that he's just not murdering other people?
But the other guy may have murdered.
Eli Rooney, I'm charging you
with the first degree murder of Deirdre Muller.
You don't want to put me back
if I stir that badly, boy. You go ahead and try.
It's wrong. I'll beat that rat.
I ain't a killer. It's wrong.
Phelps, nice work.
You fucked it up.
Did I do it? Is there a, does it tell you
if you did it wrong?
Wrong person.
You lost.
Did I?
Will we never know?
I'll take it.
That's fine.
That's a good C minus.
He was innocent of the murder, but he was a weirdo.
Hawkeye,
Hawkeye of mine just came in with
$35.
Thank you so much, Hawkeye.
You say, listen to me, son. I'm your dad.
Destroy him. Thank you.
Thank you so much, dude.
They were both innocent.
Phelps, we kept your two regular armies.
Lieutenant, Phelps, we've been over this.
That sniper barely missed you back on the beach.
Until the mission is over, there'll be no more saluting
or signs of rape. I'm in charge here, Medier.
Do you wish to interrogate the prisoners?
They're beat.
Why do they look so sullen?
Wondering why we haven't killed them yet.
There's no greater shame than being taken prisoner.
Get this golden boy. I just seem to
know what he's doing.
See that, boys? He slapped that Jap right upside the head.
General wants us to backseat.
No, I don't.
But I do. But I don't.
I respect the Japanese, Corporal.
Respect? We're here to kill
the sons of bitches.
Do you know why we're fighting the Japanese, Private?
With respect, sir, these bastards
attacked Pearl Harbor.
And why did they attack Pearl, Private?
Because they hate the US of A
and our way of life.
They attacked the US because we cut off their oil.
What would we do if another country denied us
the gas to run our cars?
This is, uh...
Okay.
The ship-shocking murder!
I was just discussing with
Finbar here how well he would do it.
I want to eat a shitload of bacon right now.
A ton of it. Like, way too much for my body
to handle. I'll get sick.
What?
You boys have a new case.
A poor Hispanic woman murdered near City Hall
and left lying naked in an alleyway.
Another naked woman, sir?
Yes. We seem to have had quite a run
of them since the Dahlia fiends first struck.
Phelps is politely trying to hint
that he thinks the 10th is his hope.
Well, young folks, you win some
and you lose some in police work.
You're happy with the location?
Over the moon, boys!
The witness, the witness,
and the lack of banana.
Get out there and catch me another listener.
Murdered on sandwiches! That's what we're gonna do!
And then it's gone. All of it.
Alright, we're gonna have
another naked murder victim.
You have the address?
It's the alley off Aliso
between Los Angeles and Alameda.
You're kidding. The next one will be opposite Central Station.
There's been no random crimes.
I kind of miss them.
This is really funny.
Yeah. It means they can pop in
to hit the office supply of hooch
whenever they need it.
Well, that ain't a bad idea.
That is not a bad idea at all.
I was told bacon
is like the same as turkey.
Oh, and I spoke too soon.
Um, but...
Code 3.
Turkey, turkey, and bacon are, or they're not
the same. Turkey is
turkey and bacon is pig.
You can get
turkey bacon, which
tastes good, kind of like shoe leather,
but it's kind of like jerky
in a sense. I like it. I sometimes actually
prefer it.
Is this the remaster? Yes, it is.
This is the one that's on PS4.
I love turkey bacon.
I love everything turkey. Turkeys are my favorite meat.
Turkey burgers, turkey bacon,
turkey patties,
turkey dinner, turkey breast,
turkey jerky.
All good.
Whatever. Alright, here comes Kenny.
Oh my god!
They killed Kenny!
Clear the roof!
Ooh, ooh, ooh, he's going!
Alright, if I get a headshot, I get to eat as much bacon as I want tonight.
If I get a headshot, I get to eat as much bacon as I want tonight.
That's the rule, I didn't make it.
Headshot, I get to eat as much bacon as I want!
Yes! I get to eat a ton of
fucking bacon!
Mmm!
Yay! Was I not supposed to kill him?
I think I was supposed to apprehend him.
But, would you get some
bacon out of it?
Killing somebody for bacon.
Oh my god, wouldn't you kill for bacon though?
Epic.
I hate that word.
If I could delete a word from the English language,
it would be epic.
I would delete it.
I hate the way it sounds.
I hate how enthusiastically people say it.
I hate how
the word replaces every adjective.
No.
I didn't even do that.
Epic.
After the cutscene.
Why is someone naked?
No one naked.
Stop killing people and making them be naked!
Stop this!
Anyways, look. Let me just show you
what I'm talking about here.
That's all seeds down there.
You don't want to consume this.
It's just gross.
It's only seeds.
It's like a tiny little pond of liquid.
I won't do it.
Hey, Cole.
Let's get moving.
The lacerations on the neck
would indicate a great deal of force.
Only 21 years old.
But why the library card?
Did he want us to find it?
Kiss the blood, BD.
Other arm.
Another wedding ring.
Another wedding ring torn from the finger.
No skin under the fingernails.
Okay, good.
That's it.
The evidence in the Mueller case was solid.
I'm not convinced about Mendez.
The best way to get away with murder is to pin it on somebody else.
I'll bet a month's salary this is a copycat.
Strangle, battered, naked.
Yeah, yeah, yeah. We know the MO.
So does every jerk who kills his wife and girlfriend
looking for a way out.
I've spoken to Brown.
He still believes the Dahlia perp has medical experience.
Four women, all murdered,
all put on display,
all with messages.
Mueller had no message.
Look, Phelps, this is getting us nowhere.
Anything for us to go on, Mel?
Head injuries from contact with road,
bruising from a small man's shoe,
further blunt force trauma to the occipital region
at the base of the skull.
Could have been fatal, but
clear signs of strangulation would seem to rule it out.
Break the seeds.
I'm going for it.
I'll see if I can nail down a brand.
Don't look over here.
If she took a blow to the head like the others,
she was probably unconscious when strangled.
Okay.
Fucking epic.
Is that it? Wait.
What is it?
May as well follow the trail.
Do I need to walk there or what?
Antonio.
Same as the library card.
Okay. That's it.
Wait, what are you looking at? My help?
All right, that's it.
There's blood all over the door.
Did somebody shot a gun? What was that?
Oh, he took a picture.
Nothing in trash cans.
All right. Wait. Matches.
Matches are never anything. Ever.
It's never matches.
I still feel these seeds in my mouth.
I'm going to have to go fucking throw up.
It's rust.
They're in my teeth.
It's bad.
I'm going to smoke blood.
Okay. Drink water?
I don't have any water up here. Only seeds.
Shoo.
Proximity to the scene plus the blood stains.
No way is this coincidence.
Okay.
Shoo on head.
I better put this on my head or chat will think it's pre-recorded.
On it goes.
With a gun.
We kept the area pristine for you boys.
Let's check it out. No pocket.
Wait, there's a TV dinner over here.
Nothing.
Oh, there is a...
What is this?
Five house keys
strung up like bait on a hook.
That's a huge crime scene.
Any more blood?
Blood.
Blood. Blood.
It's got to be a code or a cipher.
Two five three.
Memorize that.
Okay. Climbed about here.
Where are you taking us?
Okay. To the roof we go.
What is on the roof?
That was record time.
That was record roof time.
Blood.
Blood?
Blood in the birdcage.
Now that sounds like a title of a great movie.
Okay. Mrs. A Maldonado.
Federal offense.
Empty.
Where is all of this meant to be taking us?
Okay.
He clearly wants us to find these things.
He left them for us.
There you go, Felt. You got a new M.O.
I told you it would. More blood.
Or he might just be getting more confident.
A D.S.
What do you got on here? An amald and gold plated.
This was precious to her.
Can I do anything with this?
I guess not.
The trail points up.
New Super Barrio Brothers D.S.
Who has this much blood?
You would have died
two pipes ago.
Oh look, another
wedding ring.
I'm the wedding ring killer.
I kill people
and take off their wedding ring.
Find me if you can.
Looks as though the killer was
decorating with this.
He's just a sick fuck.
This is the end of the trail.
Red bag.
The other half.
May 19th, 1929.
Okay, well we have an address.
I think that's the end of the trail.
Yeah, it kind of has to be.
Bag secured.
Whoa, that scared the shit out of me.
God.
That was like an explosion.
I'm going to pee again.
I'm going to be pissing out C.
Imagine if we didn't have
intestines and a
stomach and everything that could
process all this shit.
Pissing out, fucking solid.
Gone.
Yeah, imagine if you didn't have a stomach.
No, no, no, not a stomach, but just the way that it separates it.
You guys don't realize, your body
is a gigantic coin separation
machine. You know when those old machines
you put in the dime, the nickel, the quarter
and it would go, and put it in the right slot?
If your body didn't have one of those down
there, you'd be in a lot of trouble.
But the weird thing though is, even those
machines, sometimes you'd put like a penny in
and it would fuck up and go in the quarter slot.
So why are our bodies so good at it?
How come a nickel
doesn't go into the dime slot sometimes?
If you catch my drift.
Sometimes I read
the one comment that makes me laugh.
Are you this stupid on purpose?
I'm here. Which one's Kenny?
Well, Kenny's not here.
It's not the default police officer.
I'm losing my weekly cake to you punks.
Kenny's not in this scene.
Damn it, they went down there.
What the fuck?
$30 suit bullshit.
Down again.
House flipper. It really is
the house flipper bunker, isn't it?
Whoa!
Alright, the last guy I'm gonna punch.
I wanna subdue the last one.
Gotta reload, he's gotta reload!
How do I tackle him?
I tried to hit X, X is usually tackle.
We're getting bacon tonight!
It's time to eat
lots of bacon!
Code four.
So the guy did die.
Do you guys eat
eggs in one bite?
Or do you cut them up and let all the fucking goo go everywhere?
You go to a breakfast place
and you order, oh, two sunny side up eggs
or two over easy, whatever.
You do it, you cut it up and
you just eat the whole thing.
Typically what I like to do, I like to
separate it. I don't really like to have the yolk
and all of the other stuff.
So I'll drop like two or three drops of Tabasco sauce.
A little bit of salt and pepper
and the whole thing.
Just one whole egg, just gone.
Enjoy it.
Same, same, one bite, yeah.
That's disgusting, what?
You think like 30%
of the audience here is disgusting.
What do you mean, what are these topics?
We're talking about bacon! We just had a huge conversation
about getting bacon.
So I'm pivoting the conversation
to talk about breakfast because bacon and breakfast
and eggs is what goes together.
Guys, we're driving around.
I gotta think of something to talk about.
It's gonna be bacon, eggs, and toast!
Weirdos.
I wasn't even close.
I wasn't even close. I wasn't. I just wasn't even close.
That lady ate shit
and I didn't do anything.
Ready your dad.
I'm sick of this.
Oh old lady,
hello officers, it's so
beautiful to see you. I did it.
She did it.
I'm Mrs. Barbara Lepente, the owner of this
boarding house. Is there a problem?
I'm afraid so, ma'am.
Do you mind if we come in? Is there somewhere we can discuss this?
Of course.
Follow me through to the parlor.
Wap your feet as you come in, detectives.
It's this way.
Sorry, I'm gonna walk dirt all over her house. Fuck this lady.
Mrs. Maldonado was found
dead this morning.
Dead? Oh no!
She can't be.
I'm afraid she was murdered, ma'am.
Let's take a look at her things.
I can't believe it.
A person seems so alive
and then they're gone.
Antonia's room is upstairs,
last door on the left.
Thank you. We'll be back shortly.
Excuse us
a moment, ma'am.
Room is upstairs.
You look at that?
Someone's turned the place over.
Another broken window.
A smashed window explains why the place looks tossed.
Iron picket broken window.
This person smashes windows.
Shoo.
That doesn't matter anymore, does it?
An auto.
Another envelope.
That was a lot of reading.
Further to my previous correspondence,
I'm writing to inform you that your petition to the Superior Court
of the State of California has been accepted
in a court date scheduled.
Your case, document number 985,
will be heard on September 17th.
Your husband, Angel Christopher Maldano,
residing at 30433
N Hills 3, Los Angeles,
California, has been served with the official
papers and is on notice to appear at the Central District Court
Okay.
Alright, buddy. Thank you.
On the date above, though it is not essential
and many women in your position choose not to do so,
I would advise you also
to appear at the Central District Court on the scheduled date.
In my experience,
a woman plaintiff's presence in cases like this
one can do much to influence proceedings.
And if your husband does not appear on September 17th,
which you have told me is likely,
then it can only help your
our chances.
You are sincerely
my signature.
We gotta see granny's feet
before we reach a conclusion.
Charm bracelet wasn't among the crime scene
evidence.
So it means it was taken.
We still can't read cursive?
Can you?
Alright, now what?
Oh, I guess this is like a, nevermind, okay.
Well, we have some questions, ma'am.
If you're up to it.
Yes, detective. I'll do my best.
Why are you so
stupid to not hear somebody breaking into your
room upstairs? What are you, out of your
mind?
Do you have any idea who might have wanted to hurt
Mrs. Maldonado?
That ride of her husband, Angel.
She was serving him divorce papers.
If I killed every wife that served me
papers, I'd be a mass murderer.
Are you being flippant, young man?
No, ma'am.
I mean, she's got stone
cold lock-on gaze here. I don't
believe her. What can you tell us about
Angel Maldonado?
She married him when she was 17.
He was cruel to her.
Very cruel. She was a good
girl. Little on the religious
side, but a good girl.
Stone cold Steve Austin.
Movements of victim.
What time did Antonia
go out yesterday?
She left around 9.
Do you know where she went? No.
I have no idea. She was a good
girl, but she didn't invite me.
Oh, your stone cold gaze
has suddenly turned into
point eyes down.
A nosy old hag
like you knows everything about the people who live
under her roof. Where did she go?
I think she went to a bar.
She's been drinking quite a lot lately.
This bar have a name?
El Dorado Bar. Got it.
Latino place on North Los Angeles
Street. That's only a couple of blocks
from where we found the body.
Evidence of break-in.
You've had a break-in?
No!
Wait, did she just not know?
Antonia's rear
window smashed glass and damaged a frame.
Maybe she really is just like an
old lady and can't hear it.
This is her.
What do you have to hide?
I have no idea what you are talking about.
So Antonia lost her keys
and used an iron bar to jimmy the back window?
I heard a noise in the
early hours of the morning.
I thought it might be a raccoon at the milk bottles.
It'd be very bad
for business if this news got out.
For reputation to protect.
Antonia and her husband
were estranged?
Yes. She moved
here after she separated from her
husband two months ago.
But Antonia still wore a wedding ring?
She wore the wedding ring
and a necklace.
She always wore a religious
necklace. That's about all
of her jewelry.
That's not a necklace.
Lady. What about her bracelet?
I don't know anything about a bracelet.
Oh, you don't?
In her wedding photo, she's displaying
a charm bracelet.
She never wore it.
He gave it to her.
Show his captain that wooden jewelry box.
Thanks, ma'am.
Four out of four.
I got it.
Lock him up and throw away the key.
We can either front angel
seeing as the finger's pointing right at him
or we can check out the old Aranda one.
What do you want to do, partner?
You find him and you throw him away.
Arrest the grandma
for lying.
Residents are the bar.
We're just going
in a straight line.
A nosy old hag?
And I thought I was coming
on strong with the ex-wife's line.
Sometimes you have to be firm to get the information you need.
Eat the key.
How about we drop in on the husband instead?
See if your gut is right.
I'll take a bar over a husband
every day of the week.
Well, that wasn't in the first
line.
Cole, come on!
That isn't a road.
Goddess here quicker, didn't it?
Goddess here quicker now, didn't it?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
It's all in cursive.
His wasn't in cursive.
I could read it.
Three, oh, four.
One, two, three.
He does the same thing I do.
Since I was probably like
twelve, I've never walked up
the steps one step at a time.
I always do one, two,
two steps at a time. Check it.
Yep. Wait.
I don't do that.
That's three, no, that's two.
I can just feel myself doing it.
Watch out!
Here comes a fight.
I remember how to fight now.
What did he say?
Sit back down.
Can you please stop getting up?
Sit down.
Okay.
Canvas the Neighbors.
Let's take a look.
I didn't.
Well, see, the problem here, buddy,
is I didn't get hit once
and you didn't.
I didn't.
I didn't get hit once and you did.
You weren't paying attention to my
flawless victory while you were getting
stomped on.
Pay more attention next time.
Just picked fruit market.
I wonder if Angel gets all his
groceries from this place.
Epic Victory Royale.
Blood on the shirt.
In two places. Check this one.
This will take some explaining.
Maybe one of the neighbors
took notice of Angel's movements.
Got no alibi.
Neighbor.
So this is a neighbor.
Is this the neighbor?
It's the neighbor.
We're making some inquiries.
So you weren't home last night?
No, I was at work.
You know nothing about Mrs. Maldonado
fighting with her husband?
They're always screaming the place down.
Thanks.
Why does it sound like you're talking
from the bathroom?
We can't go this way.
Oh yeah, we can. Come on. Get out of the way.
Wait, I missed a neighbor?
I missed a neighbor?
What are the neighbors? Like down the hall?
Oh.
There's 20 people in this building but
they don't know each other?
Whoa!
Sorry about that. I'm playing with my kids.
LAPD.
Were you here last night?
My wife and I
are separated.
And I had the kids last night.
Why are you wearing this fucking mask?
Thanks.
Okay.
Well, there's that.
He's playing rollercoaster tycoon.
LAPD. Did you hear a disturbance last night?
Yes. Yes I did.
Mrs. Maldonado
lit out of here and her husband ran out after.
You saw this, Miss?
A randa.
I had the door open a crack.
Did you see Mr. Maldonado come back inside after he ran out?
No.
I didn't.
Thanks. We'll be in touch.
I kept thinking you weren't going to call that one a nosy old hag too, Phelps.
Do you know how much I've sacrificed?
I'm executing
restraint right now,
Finbar.
Just picked fruit.
Uh...
And Francis Langford.
Yes, for lovely, lustrous hair.
For all types of hair,
use green shampoo.
D-R-E-N-E.
Green shampoo in the familiar
blue and yellow package.
Alright, if I get in a car accident...
Watch where you're driving, you maniac!
If I don't get in any car accidents, and even a fender bender,
then I get to have all the bacon I want tonight.
Nice.
Don't ruin your cholesterol.
I won't. I won't. I won't. I won't.
What can I get you?
LAPD. Detectives Phelps and Galloway.
Diego Aguilar.
How can I help?
You were at a bar last night?
Yeah, being a temp guy from the agency.
Did you have a woman in here last night?
21 years old, Hispanic, drinking heavily?
We have a lot of ladies like that in here.
But yeah, I know who you mean.
Antonio Maldonado.
What did she do?
She was murdered last night.
Oh, shit.
Do you know her well?
Was she a regular?
Hell no.
She was good and tight last night, complaining about her old man.
Working in a bar.
She was so hammered last night, she left a letter on the bar.
More letters.
I'll show you.
A waitress. Can I have another spoon?
Okay.
Is this one also empty?
The horse papers.
Did you open them?
No need to. She was shouting about it
and waving the letter around.
Said she was going to show him.
Whereas Antonio Maldonado
did on the 8th day of August,
1947,
prefer her petition that she
might be divorced from the bonds of matrimony
entered into with you,
Angel Maldonado.
Would you therefore command that Angel Maldonado
that said defend? This is boring.
You did a bad job with this one.
What an uncreative mad lid, man.
Alright.
Hold on.
Did you bleed on the trail?
Can you remember
what jewelry she was wearing?
She had a necklace.
Some kind of religious thing, I think.
The temp guy would have more of an idea.
She took the beer he served her and cried
into it all night.
What time did she leave?
Can't say for sure.
Where did she go?
Give me something or the LAPD will start getting
interested in this place.
Closing squinting his eyes.
My phone was out of order.
The closest one I knew was at the fruit market
across the street, so I suggested she try that.
Fruit market.
We have a place, fruit market.
Did Antonia say
where she was going when she left?
She said she was going to serve the papers on the husband.
Said that would take the smile off
his face.
If you ask me, she was scared.
And the drink was
for Dutch courage.
Did she attract any interest?
An extremely drunk young woman? What do you think?
She managed to scare them off, though.
Thanks.
You've been a big help. Perfect!
Perfect!
Hey, get the guy, will you?
We'll do our best.
One last question. What size shoe do you take,
Mr. Aguilar?
A broad nine. I have wide feet.
He thinks he's a bit of a gang.
Okay. Show
feet.
Get out of the way. Why would you? Get out of the way!
Can you?
Why would you get
in this way?
I feel like they're out of a bar still here.
What? Isn't this where I am?
Didn't I just do this?
Uh...
Out of order.
Talk to temp guy.
Give me those feet.
Where are his feet, Ben?
Let me see.
Wait, wait, wait!
I didn't get your number!
I saw a telephone.
Is there anything else to do here?
Can this be over?
Do I use the phone?
Call it in.
What is happening?
Detective?
Where does Hatt go?
Thanks, ma'am.
I think his name is Phelps.
I read about him in the paper.
You're talking about me?
Those aren't in this game.
Sorry, man.
No, the other Phelps.
Apparently I'm famous around here from solving
all these mysteries.
I'm not actually waiting for him to get in the car
and then move out of the way, am I?
You don't think it's strange that all these murders
are happening to girls who've been out drinking?
No, no. A broad drinks,
she gets a bit tired, and she starts mouthing off.
Is there something I missed in here?
And she ends up in an alleyway.
A sad story that this town
has seen it play out a thousand times, Cole.
Why don't you want to see a connection here?
Because there are perfectly good
real-life suspects
for every one of these murders.
We don't need to go looking for the monster
under the bed.
Move, I need to turn the other way.
Another letter? I thought the letter was from a nut.
These letters?
There goes the bacon.
Now we sent another.
I really hate this fuck.
Shut. Great.
We'll need to come back later, Phelps.
Maybe somebody here saw Antonia
the night she died.
I have to come back at night?
Why don't you get in?
Okay.
Back to the police station, then.
Oh, that's cinematic camera. Okay.
Alright, if I get in one car accident
in cinematic camera, then I get all the bacon that I want.
Did I just...
Did I just yell...
He yelled that out the window.
Why wouldn't you stop me?
Why wouldn't you stop the car?
The captain is waiting for you downstairs with anchor.
The captain's waiting for you downstairs.
We gonna go downstairs
and see Donnelly or what?
There's downstairs room.
You have to spell it out for me. I don't know.
I'm receiving hospital this way.
It doesn't say downstairs room.
How to get downstairs.
Isn't that the cop that caught the guy that was pretending to be Donnelly?
Downstairs. Ooh, now I know where I am.
What's up? Hey, what's up?
Phelps, have you met Finnis Brown?
Pleased to meet you, sir.
This information is confidential and doesn't leave this room.
The new letter was left in the back seat of a cab.
Ow, my elbow.
The driver thinks it was put through the window and not left by a customer.
We're checking all the spares back 24 hours, regardless.
Good.
Like the previous letters, it's been assembled from headlines
and typed from the Times and Examiner,
then glued to an envelope.
What is the other note?
This one? That's also new.
A poem, hand-typed.
Do you mind if I take a look?
Go ahead.
You've been over both documents pretty carefully.
They've been wiped with gasoline,
so there's no chance of prints.
That works.
Have changed my mind.
You would not give a square deal.
Fuck you.
Buddy.
Heap upon thy soul by virtue of this curse.
He'll read it.
Ill deeds,
then be thou damned, beholding good,
both infinite as is the universe,
and thou and thy self-torturing solitude,
an awful image of calm power.
The now thou sittest,
let thy hour
come, when thou must appear to be
that which thou art eternally.
And after many a fake
and false fruitless fruit station
fruit market crimes, scorn track thy
lagging fall through boundless space and time.
That's why we called you in.
Do you think it's original?
Not unless he's a genius.
You like this Nat Jobs poem?
No, I like Shelley.
It was written at least one hundred years ago.
Shelley? One hundred?
Sure, I knew that.
You see, Finnis, I told you this lad was a bright boy.
Sure, but what has it got to do with the case?
Prometheus Unbound.
Prometheus was a titan,
a superhuman character who defied the gods
to bring fire to humanity.
The Dahlia Guy
believes he's Superman.
Your guess is as good as mine.
One thing presumes that he's educated.
What about the link to the Henry case?
He could have got the wording from the papers.
As you said, he's fiendishly clever and takes pleasure in taunting us.
What's happening with the Maldonado case?
We have the husband in custody.
We haven't interviewed him yet.
Well, upstairs then lads
and see if we can break him.
Interview Maldonado?
That was a boomer reference?
How is that a boomer reference?
My father watched like
fucking Zorro.
What are you talking about?
Improved your attitude, Angel?
What do you want me to say?
I was with Antonia the night she died
but she left the apartment
and that was the last time I saw her.
Wow!
Religious necklace
Necklace worn habitually by the murder victim
Okay, bloodied shirt
A men's button down shirt stained with blood
and neighbor, Mrs. Arnada
testifies to Angel pursuing her from
apartment buildings.
Let's go.
I can't select this.
So your wife paid you a visit last night?
What time was that?
Late, around midnight maybe?
She didn't stay long.
I mean that's not...
I mean he chased her but
is that technically wrong?
Because
she didn't stay long doesn't necessarily mean
anything. He could have chased her at
ten o'clock or chased her at two in the morning.
I mean it's definitely a lie but
that's the community.
Okay, so
You're lying, Angel. You went after her.
I think you killed her.
You're out of your mind. My brother will tell you
I was at home.
Divorce? Okay, I have the divorce paper
so he can't really lie about this, can he?
You and your wife weren't getting along. She was divorcing you.
Is that why you killed her?
We fought, yeah, but
we weren't getting a divorce.
I mean that was his plan.
I don't believe you, Angel.
That was thrown in my face five times.
She pushed you too far and you lashed out.
I told you.
I asked the community once and they were wrong.
Where is it?
Divorce paper. This is for him, right?
Yes, okay.
The judge had set a date. You were going to be
paraded in front of the whole city for your cruelty
to her, Angel.
Antonia, oh Jesus.
She gave in drunk out of her mind.
She doesn't normally drink.
She was looking around in her bag.
What was that?
Said she wanted to serve me papers.
Me, her own husband.
I slapped her down and she ran out.
That's the truth.
What size shoe do you wear, Angel?
Excuse me.
What difference does that make?
When we found your wife,
her jewelry had been removed.
Was she wearing her religious
medallion last night?
Sure, she always wore that.
What about the charm bracelet?
Was she wearing that?
She never wore it.
She kept it locked up.
Your wife has been brutally murdered.
So how do you explain
your shirt being covered in blood?
You found that?
I cut myself shaving.
Really, did you?
Wait, maybe he did.
That's such a bad excuse, though.
If you cut yourself shaving, you don't have
a pint of blood all over you.
Angel, I'm not going to waste any more time on this.
Give me something or I'm going to have you charged.
My brother.
You cut your mouth and your eyebrow?
He said some bad things about Antonia last night.
I cut myself shaving. My eyebrows.
We got it.
Keep talking.
She said she came from the El Dorado bar.
It's not one of my places.
We used to buy fruit at the market.
Cut my throat shaving.
I think there was always one in his eyes all over my wife.
What's the name of this fruit market?
Just picked fruit.
Ord Street downtown.
One last question.
Do the words kiss the blood
mean anything to you?
Is this going to be my first perfect?
Sounds sick to me.
You're not in the clear by any means, Angel.
You're going back into a cell.
Can I get at least one perfect
and not have a C minus on everything?
The coroner says it's going to take
at least a week to get an ID.
I'm going to get zero out of four on the next one.
Just watch.
We need to go to the fruit market.
I recognize that guy from the papers.
He's a cop.
Heavens to Betsy!
You alright, lady?
How do I get out of here?
I need something that says exit this way.
Oh, thank God.
Just picked fruit.
Didn't I try to go here already?
What's your read on Maldonado?
I still like him for it.
Seriously, that line about the guy at the fruit market
making eyes at his woman?
I'll get to the market and the guy behind the counter
will tell us he saw Angel drag his old lady off.
I wish I was a boomer.
What are you talking about?
Hey!
If someone reports this...
Somebody recording this.
I'm recording this.
Just picked fruit.
Why aren't I getting five stars?
I'm not a five-star driver.
I'm a five-star deductive analyst detective.
Bog, bog!
Stop throwing food.
Hey, you look like somebody that works here.
Sir, I'm the...
Wait, you look familiar.
Hey, from the bar, right?
Who brings you here?
LAPD.
Detective Phelps and Galloway.
Clem Feeney.
What can I do for you?
Did you happen to see a young woman last night?
21 years old, Hispanic?
Sure, she came by last night. Why do you ask?
Because...
She's dead.
She was wearing a necklace?
I didn't notice.
You weren't paying attention, Feeney?
Hey, you're getting the wrong idea.
He's doing the...
Blink, blink.
Eyes.
How much fruit do you sell here after midnight, Clem?
Uh, not much.
I sell the odd bottle on the side to the after-hours crowd.
I don't want any trouble. I'm just trying to make a buck.
Clem.
Feet.
Size.
Now.
The young lady arrived around midnight?
Yeah, something like that.
Used the phone for a cab and then left.
Got him.
You already knew Mrs. Maldonado, didn't you, Clem?
You make it very easy, while they just like...
Eyes dart back and forth.
Her husband went apeshit one day when he caught me talking to her.
She hadn't been back until last night.
Where did she go from here?
She wanted a cab, but I couldn't get her one.
I was about to offer to drive her, but a car pulled up and she got into that.
His eyes are not going crazy, but do I have?
But does that always mean that it's the truth?
Look, I got a lady's hat that you were wearing.
Can you describe the car?
Brown Ford Coupe, I think.
She seemed to know the guy.
Did I do it?
Do you mind if we look around?
Why would you want to do that?
No one has ever done this mission as good as me.
Don't you have to get a court order or something? I have rights.
Clem?
Boomer voice?
It's a Boomer thing.
It's like the Boomer meme thing.
Why, because I'm 33?
33?
What am I even looking for here?
Sorry, but you are a Boomer.
33 year old Boomer stream.
I just snapped at that lady's neck.
I put my hands up and everything.
What am I looking for?
Go in and register.
Ah, secret entrance.
Get their vitamins.
Check through this stuff before we get back out there.
Looking for meat?
Am I looking for meat?
What are you talking about?
So what are we hiding in here?
Found the meat.
This thing needs a combination.
Wait, I have that.
Clues.
2, 5, 3.
How do I change this?
Got it.
And this is the bracelet.
Reliquus, 522.
Wives submit to your husbands as to the lord.
23, for the husband is the head of the wife.
Christ is the head of the church.
His body of which he is the savior.
Hands.
Prayer hands.
That is the bracelet.
Got it.
Oh, tire iron.
And a scalpel.
I caught someone who was already dead.
Because he wanted to take their
body parts.
This step is dead.
The creep usually feels they can do whatever they like.
Must have seen it during the war.
This fruit stall punk gets about
10 seconds to explain before
he pulls his fucking arms off.
Clips.
I'm trying to shoot out his tires.
Trying to shoot his tires out.
This guy is just the tire shooter.
He doesn't do anything else.
I bring him along for his...
One party member that has like revived in the group.
Jump!
Nice.
Ah, that was going so cleanly.
Get the tire.
You idiot.
Alright, get it.
Hit him, Cole. Spin him out.
You shot him with a bumper, dude.
Keep it stabbing. I'm trying to bust his tires.
Did I kill him? No.
You're under arrest.
You're a sick man, Clem.
You need help.
Perfect? Did I get my first perfect?
Oh, no. Don't. Come on.
Is there more?
He wants to personally talk to everybody.
Just like throw him down on the ground.
Just start fucking cuffing him.
Oh, yes.
I did it.
17 and 17, 13 and 13.
That is an A plus.
But, with all the damage that brings it down to like an A minus, probably.
Well, I'm going to get one.
You're sitting there field stripping a cigarette and suddenly he's there looking down on you.
Hello.
Why do you think we keep saluting that jab-loving son of a bitch with bad juju.
That's enough out of you three.
Bad juju?
Where were you dragged up, a swamp?
All right, I'm going to pee.
And I'll be back one more time.
We will do the next case, probably, and see where we're at.
We'll do another case.
The white shoes slay
more
more shoes
I'm just gonna go into the games like I'm gonna data data mine the game and just look at the guy's face
Good morning gentlemen. I'm what a grand morning. It is too. We have just cause for celebration
Galloway and Phelps are sending another fiend to San Quentin a nice shall we trial and he'll be struck down with gas
seeping into his tiny reptile brain
Now the fresh business
Yeah, you could the address is on the hill north downtown or Fremont Avenue
Just to get signal crime scene murder victim crime scene. Is the new letter genuine? Let me be now boys
We all know how many?
Give him a second. I'll be right back
We will do another case and then we'll see where we're at. We might call it
Eight and I tell let's like 11 Eastern. Yeah, I'd say one more will be be decent. I think
alrighty, oh
Hello
Pinker will let us know in good time. What are we doing a?
Fine morning indeed. We keep locking them up, but the bodies keep piling up
Weather effects greetings from sunny, California. Oh stop
It rains in California
When
That's the most surprising we've seen people get murdered
Cars flying off clips people getting shot, but rain in California
shocking
First the letter and now another body. Come on. You can't keep on telling me. There's not a killer still out there
Getting a vicious killer off the streets is more important than my reputation
Really and besides lending a big fat Marlin is more impressive than an ocean
The minnows make it the man
Please you've got a call for help. He doesn't look real good quick
What happened some punk held up my stand this guy tried to help and got a bullet for his trouble
He got hit and a high tailed it through the parking lot get going
That wasn't enough apparently
What is with that AI patent? Come on? What nobody can do that. They're pursue. They're pursuing we're pursuing
You come any closer. I'll pull the trigger put the weapon down now. I
Did it
Got a code for
Got a code for 11k calling KGPL shots fired suspect is down. We're code for but I need an ambulance on grand between 4th and 5th Street
Oh
Wait there was a guy was down there wasn't
Another crime no, maybe the rains gonna put out the fire see it's fine
So what do you mean that got hold on a lot of car stealing myself
I know where it is. Do I need to follow this dude still?
apparently
Two naked bodies three naked bodies is like really rolling dice here
Let's hope it's somebody's pick a sweater on my homicide
Seen secure the rest of the patrolmen are going door-to-door canvassing for witnesses. Thanks. Keep me informed will do detective
This looks awfully familiar. I think that's the impression the boys from the examiner took with them as well
There's nothing original under the Sun. Why should murder be any different?
What do we have so far not much trace evidence to speak of?
Storm blew in around 10 last night and the rain washed most of it away and the boss did it away
She was tipped out of an automobile from the tire tracks and superficial injuries
Strangled with a length of rope from my money. It's triple braid again
Time of death from her temperature, maybe 2 a.m. But it was cold last night usual head injuries
Yeah, one forced trauma knock him over the head then strangle. She's wearing a sweater
No message with this one. At least she was left clothed. I doubt very much
He was concerned with her dignity green silk dress is very distinctive any sign of her other shoe
No
And no handbag or other personal effects. All right time depths, too
Let's take a look. Here's that braid at braided strangulation. Oh
There appears to be a dry cleaning label superior laundry services f1
Okay, what about the wedding ring? No wedding ring
Okay, so she wasn't married
Anything else? I can't do anything else more shoes. No drag marks
Booth killer is moving around surveying the scene
Okay, it's always five dollars
Circumstantial reminds you left for dead. Well, yeah, like when you find a witch
This is the you found a witch music are most likely one in the same
phone use phone every time I see phone I use
These the other cops
We're about to be relieved. Is this FBI kind of?
I've been working the houses across the street and up the block. This lady thinks she has something for us
Detective felts la pd. I'm mrs. Barton. Catherine Barton. I live just across the way
Witness and signal hill resident
Did you see anyone around here last night? Not last night, but yesterday early evening. I saw that awful hobo
uh
Why would you come to no, why would you come to us to lie to us tall gaunt?
Horribly disfigured. I think he may have had an accident in the war officer here. I have some information for you
Let me flag you down angry man
Any idea where we might find him?
One of the hobo camps around here. He's some kind of hobo leader. They all follow him around a hobo leader
Thank you, ma'am. It's been a big help
Of course, why would you lie right off the bat?
Just to you flag down a police officer could happen right here and nothing to be done about it
phone felps batch 12 47
detective
I need an address on superior laundry services
Just a moment
12 60 west first street. Can you track down reports of hobo camps in the vicinity of signal hill?
Just a moment detective
There's a large camp under the bridge on grand between temple and sunset. Hey detective. You're hallucinating. This is a bird house
Oh shit, okay. Sorry
Okay, should we go to the laundry place or should we go to the hobo camp?
I don't know what you guys are gonna say
But we have to go on we go on a straight line
I don't do them out of order even though you maybe you're supposed to at some point no message
If we survive this it's gonna be a miracle
Start saying your prayers
Excuse me. There was no message where i'm the vic the last bodies had something written on this one
Didn't i'm failing to follow it can't be the same guys what i'm saying, right?
Before you start trying to link this to maldenon all the others
There are more factors to consider than the messages rusty. This doesn't fit your pattern cold end of conversation
understand
Okay, and he has a point
You do have a point
At least the rain stopped you can change back into those white bucks now
All right laundry
laundry
Who's got laundry information here felson galloway la pd?
We're investigating a case and one of your laundry labels came up f one three six three
If you give me a minute i'll go find a register and you can take a look
Okay
What was that like a little hesitation? I've got clothes that need pressing
This guy acted a little weird down on that dress is it there
Uh, I hold on
What the hell is this name?
laundry label
Uh laundry liver find a victim f one three six three
F one three six three
F one three six three there it is mrs. T
Torraldson 43 emerald street
one times green silk dress
And go mrs. T. Torraldson 43 emerald street westlake
Yeah, I just wanted to read it
Did it so I just put coins in everybody's machines and turn it on to like two more hours
Or should I take out laundry and like put them in random tubs?
Just fuck the whole thing up
Just throw up somebody's like you've been that one one goes into four four goes into three three goes into eight eight goes into 15
You monster. Um, all right. Well, let's
Just go to the hobo camp large vagrant camp under we ought to investigate the hobo lead onto the bridge
Now I get why you guys are doing resident sleeper with that because that that music comes on
Oh, I get it
I get it now
That seems like a really dangerous song to play when you're driving I guess
Oh, I was trying to make an entrance you're gonna kill us
Do I actually have to go all the way you can just jump the fence, right?
That's fine
We're looking for a tall man with a disfigured face, you know him
Huh, what I thought two more as you know, son, I think I earned some peace and quiet
We should follow the only
Okay low and steady come on
He stole your gun
He stole your rifle
So I can't do anything
I've got a feeling we're about to meet another wife killer. You've always got that feeling rusty
Yeah, and it's usually correct, please that was a waste of time for once
Can you not let your assumptions color your detective waste of time?
Just go easy felps waste of time
Just you wait nordic types show a particular disposition for this stuff
Keep la safe drive safely. Sure thing. I'll try
preferred toppings and a toasted bagel
Oh, that's tough
I mean this two or three different avenues you can go down there
uh
The luncheon in me would say
one slice of tomato
tuna fish
and
Maybe maybe a slice of swiss cheese
Now this is a breakfast scenario you're talking about
I'm making an egg and bacon and cheese like bacon egg and cheese is one of my favorites
or
chive and onion cream cheese
Now if it's a dinner scenario, uh, we're talking a piece of turkey hot turkey and gravy
uh for dessert
You could put a little bit of
Maple syrup on it
And throw just a little bit of ricotta cheese on it and that's uh dessert bagel. It really depends
Hello. Yes detectives felps and galloway. Is your wife home, sir?
Fancy bagel dinner. She hasn't come home
Can you describe your life? I love salmon, but I don't like sand. I don't like walks on bagels
She was kind of dolled up
She had her green silk dress
Open-toed white shoes
Those are her favorite shoes and we come in. Mr. Tarrelton. I'm afraid we have some rather bad news
I recognize this actor
Do you have someone who can look after your children? Mr. Tarrelton? I've been trying to arrange a sitter. Look, tell me what's happened
I'm afraid your wife was murdered last night
Her body was found this morning. We're very sorry for your loss
I know this is a difficult time. Mr. Tarrelton, but we are boomer alien eats disgusting bagels. First
We're gonna take a look around what for you don't think the procedure
You see to your girls
Dad, what's murder mean?
Oh jesus
Stay here till daddy's finished talking to these men. Where's mommy? Everything's gonna be all right, sweetheart
We would like mommy to come home now daddy. What's the problem tarrelson? Let him search
You got nothing to hide
You want to hear something funny tarrelson funny some bums think filling out a missing person's report actually rules
You know more cigarette stuff more of matches
But this is important check if baron's bar
Toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat got it
This doesn't pertain to the case is it chocolate optimistic coal
Isn't that the butterfly brooch?
Symbol is this gonna be like some weird thing where that shows up all the time
Wait, wait, wait, wait, we might have some fucked up drawings here
No chocolate
Is this bottom right one like murder and blood and shit?
I don't know. That's weird
Not sure this means much how more baron's bar
Baron's bar again
Someone must be real sweet on this dive
Why the picture was turned down?
That is odd
But i'm somebody may have knocked it over. It's in a really weird place
That's in a very knockable over
place in the bedroom
Hi kids, if you'd excuse me ladies
No incidental so she went out without her handbag. No, okay handbag. What's this like little mini chalkboard?
She'd have to be in quite a state to leave this behind
driver's license
At least she was spared that particular indignity
Is it?
Nothing
Nothing of interest
That's it. Oh feet
Let me guess
size
It's eight you can match the impression to the crime scene
Why is every case have size eight shoes?
Is it blood ours was out in the rain last night
Jacket
Okay, I can break
lawnmower
doghouse
No dog
Toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy boat toy fuck
I match with the ligature marks
So this is the killer rope
How's your phone?
I need to call and get the gps to the new place. I need to go
Free real boat real boat real boat real boat
Operator give me r and i
It was the boat the boat did it
Cole felps batch 1247
So are you aware that your boat is a fucking killer a bobby ross then send some uniforms over
Would you like him picked up?
No
Suspect says he was with ross last night. We need to confirm the alibi
I'll get a proud car dispatched
Thanks for your help
Okay for the record. Mr. Taraldson. What is your wife's name? He doesn't even know his wife's name
Why?
It's judy
Ah shit. All right, you might as well take me in
2 a.m. Is when she died
She went to the laundry store
his boots
tires
There's a laundry store
baron's bar
Hmm vampire handbag. Hmm muddy boots size eight. Hmm wet jacket freddy kruger style. Hmm
Triple braid pattern on the bow road. Okay, i'm ready
Do you have any idea why anyone would want to hurt your wife? No
Everyone loved teresa
She was so full of life
It can't be anyone who knew her
That's pretty that's pretty truthful
Like he looks anyone who would want her dead
No, I don't
Okay, does he have an alibi you said you went to a party at bobby ross's place. That's right
Bobby had a bunch of people over we were having a good time
She said she was bored and decided to leave
You know your drunk wife leave the party and go off on her own
Look, I was angry. I was having a good time. She has to go and ruin it
We always have to do what she wants to do
Last night she wanted to go dancing any idea where where she always goes
bar down on north baudry avenue
Barron's bar there it is baron's bar. She goes there drinks too much gets maudlin and calls me
I go and bring her home victims state of mind. Mr. Terreltsen was teresa happy at home
Yeah, I think she was
Why can't you just look straight ahead you're gonna play more poker man spill it terreltsen
Or just wear sunglasses wear sunglasses during okay, if you ever get investigated by the police just wear sunglasses
She wants to go out dancing. We only have the sitter until nine
I get mad. I tell her to go ahead but i'm staying she storms out
Look, i'm doing well at cards. I hardly ever do well
I married her because she was so much full but now she drives me fucking crazy
What time did she leave the party?
About 8 30 maybe a little earlier. All right, well she died at two so that would make sense
Why is he looking at the ceiling? Why even was the last time you saw your wife around 8 30?
The card game at bobby's was wrapping up. I played out my hand and drove home here
Paid the sitter and went to bed
He's got
Hold on are these
But what are these the right boots though?
I'm, not sure these are the right boots
The size eights, right?
You're lying larz. You didn't come straight home. Did you?
And how do you figure that?
Because you have size eight shoes like that's that's as a stretch, isn't it?
You were out you got soaked larz. We found your wet weather gear
I guess okay. I stayed a little later than I said
This cute little brunette was hitting on me
Theresa noticed
I was half cut. I walked her home from bobby's but nothing happened
I walked back and got the car this morning
Thanks for answering our questions. Mr. Terrelson
You'll need to go downtown to identify your what do they get wrong?
I should have taken her dancing in my experience mac be given to brodge
Be given into them your entire life
It sounds like the terrelson broad had her last drink at bar. We should check the place out
first one
Appreciate your time, sir. Do you believe this guy's story kind of rings true?
baron's bar
I'll see there folks capital hill in washington is again
The nation's focal point as the 80th congress convenes during one of the periods in the nation's history
Following the Jesus felt
That's an explosion waiting to happen
That's an explosion watch out for that. You don't want to make an explosion
That's noted. All right, what's going on?
recommend the specialness
gents
drink
Felton galloway la pd i'm benny clough
It's about teresa terrelson. Yes, it is. I heard about it on the radio
They're saying it was that black dahlia freak again
God, you know, I rang that husband of hers. The babysitter said he was out if you don't mind. We have a few questions
What time did teresa leave around?
10 30, I think 10 30
husband said 10
She died at two
He's just answering a question
On foot in a car by bus. How was it? She called for a cab. Did you get the number? Sure. I did
I like teresa
The only time she has a drink is when things aren't going so good at home
I was worried about her
I thought he's getting a gun. Whoa, that went crazy there for a second put out an apb on the cab
3591 should be traceable. Oh, yeah. Nice manhattan gin ricky
four drinks
Okay
uh
What about the hobo?
We've had reports about a tall gaunt looking hobo. We lose that whole section here. I don't understand. I get plenty of bums in here
But nothing to fit that description
Okay, it's always the eyes is the eye the likelihood is that whoever she left here with killed her
Give it up benny
All right, two creeps were all over
Promising to take her dancing you get a good look at these guys. Sure. I got a good look
One of them was a sailor in uniform his cap said, uh
USS indiana and the other man
The other guy
Is richard bates?
He's sitting in the back right now
red polo shirt
Okay
What about any idea where she was headed? Nope, I didn't get that
No, really?
She was murdered benny brutally murdered if you like this lady. I don't know where she was
You're telling me i'm not cooperating
Watch it pal. Thank you for your help. Mr. Clough. We'll take it from here
Hey, no problem. Well
He's telling the truth. This is bait
That's him
LAPD
The usss toy boat can't let the son of a bitch get away
It's a very long drawn-out
Who knows what this guy will pull when he's cornered we could have a killer on our hands
I really love this in gator zim music
Oh my I don't hear a killer my gear back in the bar. It was so loud viking listen
A creature of habit is your killer for some reason. They're sticklers for routine
Oh my god, that hurts so bad. It fucked up my whole game how it's done
Come on felps. You're letting this lust get away from you. There was too many audio clips played in some time
That's what the loud sounds
Turn them down
Maybe you shouldn't have waited for me felps
Damn it
Oh
I tried
I thought I had it
I thought I had it. Shoot his tires. I'm gonna drill. I'll try to shoot out his tires. Wish me luck
Let's end this bar
Put your hands where I can see them
Okay, baits, you're gonna answer some questions
I have a choice in this
Contact with victim
They kind of got out of a flipped over car
Last night you went drinking with a lady last night. Now she's dead
And your face is all messed up. I'm in the clear on that
She preferred a sailor. You could lay it off on him. Are we finished?
I I don't know
I mean that
It looks like he's not telling the truth, but he could just be a weirdo
Oh, come on
Well, do you want my partner to sap you tell us what we want to know she was okay drunk
Pissed off at her old man wanting to go dancing. I thought I'd ply her with a few drinks and get my end away
Looks like you're salty at the same idea
account of movements
So what happened when you left the bar?
Sailor boy laid one on me a cheap shot
After that
I don't know
It's like getting into car accidents behind us
It's a car accident like every 10 seconds glass breaking beeping how many cars are here
They're like 30 cars
Come on if we're doing this get it over with shut up. I'm listening
Is that it? Oh, no
It's already just fell
So it was just skydiving landed behind us. All right, that's it
He's gonna fucking piss his pants
Is it a jackhammer?
Why is there a construction?
If we're doing this get it over with
You've done time. Haven't you?
I mean, come on. That's funny. There's nothing behind us sexual assault
Look, I was lying there on the sidewalk. He flags a cab and jumps. There's nothing behind us
Uh, we're taking you in baits. How come just for a chat nice private chat
I'll explain my theory of once it's like one of those hearing tests
Take him to central. He's a material witness in a murder case find him a cozy cell. Richard here knows the drill
Oh, it wasn't the it wasn't the car beeping that was making me laugh. It was the fucking like
crashing and the
People falling down and the jackhammer
I love the king to kgpl
Did I break the phone I did didn't I water but i'm not with him what is going on here
Phelps one two, four seven
Detective I need an apb out on a yellow cab number 3591 ask dispatch to relay all sightings to car 11k
Nope radio
Were there any incident reports filed in the vicinity of barron's bar on north baudry avenue?
We're tracking a sailor who was involved in a fight outside the bar
I can check the reports detective
I have a message for you from captain donnelly message reads james jessup u.s navy abel seaman has information relevant to your case
Jessup is currently being detained at central station. Okay could be our man. Thanks
interrogate james jessup
Central police station
What's your beef with this guy phelps? All right station central division
Let's go
Should I do that now follow the cab
I left my partner again. He wasn't fast enough the other part
Damn what I had to go now
This is the cab that she took so why did you do
I don't think this guy's the killer or anything. I just need to ask this guy where the girl went
Where's the cab cab
Did you see a cab?
Reggie's cafe found it so what do I do will the guy pull over
I don't have to smash into him
Thank you for pulling over sir. I really appreciate it
LAPD we're investigating a murder. What's that got to do with me the fare you picked up from baron's bar last night
What was the woman wearing? It's a green dress
Oh, don't tell me something's happened to her. Tell me about her
She was with this sailor and he was all over
She really animated said she just wanted to dance
But he had that look in his eye
Where did you drop them off?
Said the crystal ballroom what time?
After midnight
About 30 something like that. Thanks. You've been a big help. Well, that's gonna ruin my day
Sorry, I just ruined your day even more can we fit through this person's house
Easy take home that holds six bottles. It's the quality drink that's as refreshing as it is delicious
King of refreshment for that anytime first the thirst of a king can be quenched for just the nickel
with cola king
What instrument is that?
the kazoo
Trumpet with
Plunger
This is 11k we'll handle the 415 jesus felps
Clogged the trumpet. You can't trump. You can't trumpet that you can't jump over this
My god, please
Why don't you come on out jimmy? I won't let them hurt you not my honey boy
I told you not to call me that woman. Now shut the hell up
You shut the hell up
Is that the lady of the house
It's a nice story. Two old lovebirds just moved in together, but they had a falling out and chased across the yard with a 12 gauge
Now it's him
This is funny to you rookie
Yeah, that's funny. You're gonna laugh at me smirk at that
I wanted to just be one two three clean shots
Just one two three, we've all tried to run in the front
Oh, well that was a lot worse
Okay, I don't know fucking that up again
Why is it gone?
No
Yeah, we were the npcs at that point. You're right
well, uh
Never mind did not press x. I didn't really have an option to I was trying to run in there and punch him
What is the why does it keep popping up in this spirit?
See that it's still possible to do it. It's down here
All right interrogation he's an interview too
Thanks. What do you make of him sailor on furlough? Who looks like he's in trouble and knows it
straight through the red light
Detectives felps and Galloway
We know why you're here. Jessup. So what would be best if you answered our questions truthfully?
I don't want any trouble. That's why i'm here
I heard on the radio about this lady getting killed. I got lead from my co to come down straight away
So why did you kill her?
I didn't kill anyone
Look, you need to believe me. Let's start at the beginning
contact, uh us
Maybe able sea man seen with victim on night of murder. You went to baron's bar. What time did you arrive?
I got a 24-hour pass. I got there around seven. That's where you met teresa tarrelton
Sure
We had a couple of drinks
So you tried to make a woman who was incredibly drunk look i'm not proud of myself, but I never hurt her
You took her dancing. That's right
Cut a cab to the crystal ballroom
That's true
Right. You had a fist fight with richard bates over mrs. Tarrelton
You met the guy. He's a creep
You should take a look at him for this
I mean he's pointing the finger directly at you jessup. I only had one night before I was back in the tub
He had all the time in the world to look for some action. I belted him. I'd do it again
She was better off with me. Sure. You're a shining example of chivalry jessup
Movements prior to murder. Where did you go after the crystal ballroom?
I think the wind had gone out of her sails by then
She caught a cab and I caught a cab and I got a bus
Uh, they started shaky at first but
No, no
They're not it's not he can't only
No, we spoke to the cab driver
Tell us what really happened at the crystal ballroom
I'd had enough
She was all upset about her husband bawling about her kids. She she looked old
Left around closing maybe 130
Got on a bus and she fell asleep on my shoulder. We've only told lies an all-american
249 he hasn't said anything else besides a lie place. She jumped off and I stayed on it downtown
After that, I caught another bus to san pedro. So that's probably also down there. She's being scrapped
And that was the last you saw of teresa. Yeah, that's right
We didn't say much. I think she was kind of embarrassed
Cab ride cab driver said that you were getting pretty familiar with teresa. It's not how i'd put it
But is that that is that his okay, so this is that he's telling the truth
You look at how confident he is right there
really
so
Wait a minute. Can I like accuse with the cab?
hire tracks
Well, okay the first three questions he was like his eyes were darting around and now all of a sudden he's like smiling
Tell the truth jessup. You're running out of time. You wanted to get laid and teresa wouldn't come across
It made you crazy. So you strangled her with a piece of rope
For christ's sake. That's not true
I felt sorry for her. What proof do you have that I strangled her?
The cab statement
We got you
In the cab
That's the proof. We have you took a cab
Wait, I can back out. I made a mistake
You can actually do that
Oh, okay, so the last thing you wanted was her playing hard to get did that make you mad sailor told every single thing
She knew what a guy's looking for all broads do dancing comes second. And what happened at the crystal ballroom?
Nothing, not even a little hand relief. She had another couple of drinks. There was no fun left in her
Just poured her guts out to some bartender
We're holding you till we can clear this with the driver. He literally did
Yeah, my co said as much didn't tell the truth every time
Can you put the guy in two in a cell and inform the commander? Sure detective. Okay
Got a message for you
Siding of your disfigured hobo on brand between temple and sunset and looks like the bow has a record too
He's wanted in connection with two female assault. Thanks
What now drive all the way to san peter and check his locker then we already do the bus story checks out
There's a depot at 1660 february boulevard
Investigate interstate bus depot three suspects in the can one on the hoof
Still no hard evidence on any of them
Watch it, will you okay? Go ahead
11k roger that on the autonomous contact
It's possible
Thank you earlier on
Your sandwich is awesome. I love it
I could arguably say
That I could eat tuna fish every single day
I probably could
Satan like appears in front of me and it's like you can only eat tuna fish for the rest of your life
How do you plead?
I'm like guilty
I do it. What kind of trial is that?
All right bust up
Somebody
And thank you, ma'am. You have a safe trip now
Where are you boys headed today?
LAPD we're after the driver of all-american 249 would have been around midnight onwards last night
Uh, just a minute
Do you like raw tuna? I do
Spicy tuna is probably my favorite role. Where can we find a restaurant frank is out on the seven four?
Can you tell us the route? Hang on? Uh, I'm should have I don't need it that often but
Yeah
I like raw tuna in the spicy tuna roll, but I don't like raw tuna
just
Eating raw tuna
I know that's a lot of people really like that
But not not for me. It's got to be in something else
I'll need to run the loop locate all-american 74
Route number 74
Do I have to memorize this or is this going to be on the map?
We're not going to drive the whole thing. Are we?
Won't take long
We have a siren
Okay, wait, I can't decide between the tuna fish and the chicken
uh
Tuna eat the tuna. That's the best one
What novels all-american 74? Let's go get him about the back door. God damn it
All right, so we just have to drive there this line
Okay, you get in the car like he's never in the car with shit
I'm just too fast with this guy
Get in okay looking for a bus
bus
74 could be a long trip col
Or it could be a short one and here's me without my hip flask and only a pain in the ass for company
Way to kick off the drive in high spirits rusty comments like that put me in just the right mood for some leg work
Touchy, you know what your problem is
You don't like hard work to find this kind of rigorous search is what police work is all about
Discipline say how big is the bus just as bored as I am
I'm sure i've seen a bus the whole game
let alone
Try to find one now
I'm currently driving with traffic. So that might be a problem
If so are they
No, i'm still no sign of him. Did you doze off rusty? I think you slept through my solving the case
Yeah, very funny. Just give me a nudge if you see him, right? How about you nudge me found that's a job
For your wife
That's the bus we're looking for ease in behind her and get her to the side of the road
All right. Yeah
Hello
There's some kind of problem buddy
LAPD we're investigating a murder you had a sailor and a woman in a green dress on your bus late last night
That's correct. And the woman got off first around 2 a.m. Yeah, that's right
And the sailor stayed on all the way to downtown. Can you tell us where you let the woman off on california street?
They tell you the truth. She looked a little lost like she got off on the wrong stop or something this voice
I didn't like dropping her off near that hobo camp. Who is that a big help? Mr. Zeffirelli?
I've heard it a million times
So sailor boy escaped by the seat of his bell bottom trousers left the broad alive
Left her by the hobo camp
Which means he's as good as kill
We can't eliminate any of them, but the disfigured man should be our starting point
I'm gonna call for some backup. These bows hate cops. These bows hate cops
um
Okay, so we're gonna
Go to the hobo camp
This is a long one
Breathe though breathe. Damn it
That was not danny devito
Danny devito, who are you getting that?
No
No, we're about to go to the hobo camp too busy right now. Sorry
Is it weird that I don't like to have this on because I think it's too loud
It's annoying I'd rather deal with driving into people nice dodge there's a lightning reflexes there
We'd like a word with you save it for someone who's interested
They're fascist
Come to move us on and steal what little we have left six rounds won't get us far. Do you have a fire axe?
Um, these men know they're hovering a murderer
Beat up the main guy
I've seen every movie. I've seen every tv show every video game. Once you beat up the fucking boss everybody else stops
And they change their mind instantly
What's your name?
Comrade star very funny
We'll find out from your personal effects
Stuart ackerman, you're under suspicion for murder every video game. We're taking you downtown. Yeah
Every single one thing more to me than what the japanese have already done
Every single one the kremlin's over here felps tossing
One that came out three years and two days ago
well, I mean you gotta be specifically a movie or or a
tv show or a video game dude, what are you talking about? Come on
still working jack
I'm off to the lighthouse club in santa monica
Hello jack. Mr. Benson. This is cortney sheldon
He's a buddy of mine from the war. Well, i'm sure you two will want to polish some old war stories
Good evening jack
Mr. Sheldon
Good night, sir
Take a seat cortney
We need your help
jack
I told you I would have nothing to do with that
I'm fine, too jack
Medical school's going well
I got a part-time job
Do dope peddlers need part-time jobs?
We made a mistake and we're in trouble jack
A local gangster micky cohen is putting on the squeeze
So hand it over walk away. What's stopping you? We had a deal with them that they would dole it out slowly
They said they were the peanuts movie by the way clinics and doctors like but they've been moving it on to addicts
And they can't cope with the purity. So your problem is with gangsters being dishonest. My problem is that people are dying
And then if this gets back to us, we'll all end up in jail
So, how am I supposed to help cortney? This isn't the war. I can't just wave a magic wand and clean up your mess
due to negotiating
jack
The only thing these guys understand is force sheldon
They got to the top back east by proving to be more vicious than the english the irish and the dutch
I googled the exact day and exact moment of the movie coming up
Society
I'd say cortney you want to be a doctor. Give me another one. How can you fight with that?
We give me another year for a day
I didn't make it through the war to come back to this kind of shit sheldon
1999 17 made that herald and kumar go to white castle
16 years ago four days night before christmas
It's none of these ropes
Looks familiar safe bet it'll match the mark under teresa terrell three years ago sean of the dead
purse
last friday
venom
It doesn't look like much of a dancer
terregate stubert ackerman
Two years six months ago
Ah, damn that's got me though. Oh two years and six. It's the six months. That's getting me
The husband has an alibi, but no real motive other than neglect. Uh, the the antebell free
antebell for whatever it was
Pulling the same stick antebell for the doll is back
Not you're gonna kill us
Have the evidence we know she was here
All we need is a confession. We can charge the bum with murder
I mean, no
I'm just saying when movies came
All right. Fine. You guys think you're so smart
Let's go you got I i'm gonna if you take more than five seconds here, then you go there
One of the mighty ducks come out the first one
We're going this way
I don't even know. I don't know
No guns
I need to where's the interrogation room?
Follow interview room one
Ackerman you were in the marines. How do you know?
The corps selected big guys for flamethrower duty. That's how you got the burns
Life expectancy was five minutes for guy in flamethrower detail
What kind of a government puts weight like that on a man's shoulders? You'll get no argument from me
It was a heavy load
You feel like somebody actually got it?
Okay, how about this one guys willard? I need a year and a day
Okay, nice job. Why did you kill mrs. Terreltson?
I have no recollection of the people I have killed
Why lie lie?
You hate women ackerman
How much did you hate mrs. Terreltson?
I ache to put my seed in them
I have guards
We use for them. Okay
so
So you did it a bus driver dropped mrs. Terreltson near your camp around 2 a.m
Why did you take her up to the hill? Which hill?
I have many places
I go where I please
You're clearly insane ackerman the state of california does not execute mental patients. I don't know the names of the women i've killed
But i've killed many of them. So this is the guy their necks are so fragile
This is the guy this is the dude he's the guy that's killing all the people
Where were you around 2 a.m. Last night?
at the camp
Hold on. What what do we got?
2 a.m
At the camp we brought her up there
Laundry boots. Well, what's what about his shoe size?
The rope the boat though, where are the tire the tire tracks?
Turned tire tracks on muddy ground close to body. This got into a car
What are you staring at boy?
bus driver frank
Testifies to dropping teresa near the camp
rope matching
Put your mark on victim's neck found in ackerman's lean to
And this is found in stuart ackerman's lean to her purse and the rope that killed her
So wouldn't it be like the rope that killed her?
I mean, that's that's obvious
I wanted you to take one of the other ones away
You were up on the hill you were seen during the day. We have a witness. We have evidence
You got the blood on me ackerman and i'll see what I can do for you
I despise your pity
You have nothing that links me to this woman
Did he get rid of the rope?
Oh shit
It's not his boots. He doesn't have a car
This is the only other thing
but just
I was gonna say the rope
We have you cold ackerman her purse and the ballroom ticket were in your lean to
Tell us why you did it
I kill because people need killing
That's what I was trained to do
Stuart yeah, i'm charging you with the murder of teresa taroldson
Does that he did he do the all the other ones too then?
He's innocent a man down on his lot. I can abide
But a filthy red who chooses to live outside the rules of society. I cannot stomach
Maybe poor threes or taroldson will provide the catalyst we need
I've spoken to the chief and the mayor and I think it's time we send some men in to remove the godless and send them
On the way over the county line
A grand day that will be gentlemen
And a grand result you have brought me
You two are fast becoming my finest crusaders
Hey, thanks
Oh
15 out of 17
The tarltons might have just as steward ackerman is pronounced fit to stand trial
I feel like the last two
Crimes were the two crazy people that were like I did it. It was me
You know what I mean?
Did I fall for the trick?
This torched zone studio secretary murder will have to be for another time
Maybe tomorrow. It's getting late. We'll see how it starts though
Again, we got to see his face this time
Of course, we will look into it. Yes. I'm aware that it's an election year. Keep a hold of your heart counciler
Now is not the time to lose your nerve
It would appear that someone has hooked a rose gold wedding ring a matching engagement ring sound familiar
Deirdre muller
Press the pawn broker and see what you can find out. The address is 348 south main street
The muller case goes before the grand jury next week and the da does not want any egg on his face
Then get out to the railroad depot on santa fe avenue
We have another poor unfortunate found this morning beside a railroad line. Yeah, at what point is it like?
Right skipper, this is a serial killer
My partner just doesn't seem to want to connect those dots
No, it's all just coincidences. There's
steve's taking the wedding rings and just letting their throats and choking them with
And deirdre muller's ring
All right, that is going to be it for tonight
Uh, I will
Today is thursday
Tomorrow's friday. I will probably i'll see you guys tomorrow
We'll do it again tomorrow
We will do we'll start we'll just keep I think
How far how close am I to being?
To the end of the game. I did not finish red dead 2
I'm very far pretty far. Wow, so this is a big this is a long game, huh?
Uh would is this something that could be done in like another?
Like six to eight hour stream
Two more streams
Well, can I even can I look?
Oh, okay. There you go
13 out of 26
35 game completion. Holy shit. This game is long
Well, okay
Depends on how many jokes you make
All right. Well, we'll see how far we get tomorrow
We'll probably start it on the same time
two to three ish pacific, which is
Five to six ish eastern something like that
But i'm having fun. This is a fun game
Take your current time and double it
So, I mean so probably two more streams
We'll see we'll see how you guys are gauging it tomorrow
Because I can just at least three things to hop between over the next week or two
But yeah
Uh, I will catch you guys tomorrow
Right where we left off here
And let's do the bits
Thanks for sticking around. See you tomorrow and we drop that out of the way
Let's head back here
to
six hours ago now
toshiro ahti
Thank you for the one dollar
Well, i'd watch the stream, but unfortunately I have schoolwork to do at any rate
I'm glad you settled and it seems like you're really beginning to enjoy yourself and relax
I am
I am things are looking things looking up
Glad to be back and back in the swing of things. So thank you toshi
Thank you garfield the monday killer for the one dollar early garfield bits
He's yeah, they're very early right at the beginning
Uh, welcome to the garfield party germ. I'm actually at my toon versity taking an online test
But i'm donating bits to you instead
Uh, there was a funny sunday comic that was released on thursday
anyway, jim um
If you if you would take
every garfield roleplay comment
That's happened so far
I i'm pretty sure it's getting to be book level here. I think we're getting to be at like book level
Oh, if we drop some frames. Yeah, we're fine though. Jim davis already has 10 books
At what point is the garfield the monday killer gonna have the same amount of content as jim davis published?
I think we're getting there pretty soon
Uh, but anyways, that just was a thought that uh
Jumped up into my brain there
Anyways, you ever look on that rooting hooting tooting high fluting noisy shooting red dead
Oh, what you're playing la noir
I am playing la noir. We'll see what we do tomorrow, though
Thank you garfield the monday killer
If you shut out one book every year, you'll be on your way
Thank you brilliant fungi for the 10 bucks. Thank you bring back germa craft
Um, I did I already did I did for one day only that was a one day only special
And I had to drink two full bottles of champagne to do it
But thank you. Uh, brilliant fungi for the 10 dollars. Appreciate it
Hit 5k on that stream. I know on a minecraft stream
But thanks a lot, man. Thank you div usb for the four dollars. No message. Thank you four dollars
uh
Logay, thanks for the one dollar
Thank you
Smarky mc. Thanks for the five dollars
Hey germa first time donating just want to thank you for being a light during these rather dark times
Uh, thank you smarky for giving five dollars here, but you appreciate it
um
I don't know how long you've been around but
I'm glad to be here
Thank you smarky for the five bucks
Anything else show official?
Thank you for the four dollars anything else
They say I wanted to gift you more money for all the later the later productions streams and jokes
Love you germa. Keep up the good work. Thank you. Anything else i'm gonna try I will do my best
Really appreciate the four dollars though
Contrast on twitch gave ten dollars earlier. Thank you contrast
They say hey germa just got my first job and this is the first transaction i've ever made on my debit
You're my favorite streamer and I always leave your streams and videos with a good laugh
Thank you for everything and enjoy the game
Uh, well congratulations on your first job
And I am honored to be your first ever transaction on your debit
first time
Uh, thanks a lot man. Thanks for the ten dollars
And i'm glad you enjoyed the streams. Thank you
And yeah, congrats on the job
Swiggity swanky gave 50 dollars earlier
We touched upon it, but I always want to touch upon them more than once
Because it's a ton of money. Thank you
swiggity swanky
Major clusterfuck gave
30 dollars
Thanks to the 30 bucks. Hey germa, you're a little cool. I guess here's 25 bucks
Okay, bye
And then they came back with five and they said hey, why not? Here's the rest buy yourself something else. Why don't you?
Well, I will I will buy something it might be tuna in the can
solid white albacore
In water don't do those chunk light bullshit solid white in the water, but thank you. Thank you so much, dude
Really appreciate it and now you're out
Uh, well, thanks for sticking around major clusterfuck. Take care waffle ranger. Thanks for five dollars. No message. Thank you waffle
Hawkeye of mine. Thank you for the
35 dollars we touched upon it
But again, that's a lot of money to give in a single
Bit donation. So thank you so much hawkeye
Much love to you guys free ipod. Thanks for the one dollar
Uh, they're they're shushing they're saying epic is an epic word, I guess
Uh hawkeye of mine again gave 19 dollars
So that puts you up there man. You also gave 12 dollars
Like not even 20 minutes ago. So that's 66 dollars here. Thank you so much, dude
Uh, this one for 19 dollars says hey, that's the nutribullet. Ain't it? My 62 year old mother
Loves that too
Uh, it's actually the ninja but yes, there are the same product is marketed on different infomercials
Same exact concept and it's so easy to use it really is
You just blend it and you turn it upside down take the top off and drink out of it sponsored sponsored by ninja
Uh, no, not quite but thanks a lot, man
Uh fort miner guy. Thanks for the five dollars best streamer to date. I'm glad you think that
Thank you for the five dollars and that
Incredibly nice thing to say i'm man 44. Thanks for the one dollar term
Have you ever tried playing the fighting fantasy books on stream? No, because the fighting fantasy books are very complicated
And
I don't know if they transition
Well to being on video because it's a it's an actual book in dice and
It would be very very hard for me to learn that and stream it at the same time
I just I don't know if that would be good stream content
But if you're curious fighting fantasy is the source is the sorcery. It's made by the same person
If you're curious of what they're asking here, but thank you. I just don't think it would
Transition well, but thank you. I'm in for the one dollar
Uh, thank you the long egg for the five dollars here. Thank you long egg
I have surgery at 6 a.m
Tomorrow and having your stream tonight is helping me out a lot
You're amazing and I can't wait for the green screen stream neither. Can I?
It should be a ton of fun
Happening pretty soon
I'll let you guys know the exact date, but I need to lock it down for either this weekend
Like I said, or probably monday or tuesday
Uh, but good luck on your surgery. I'm not sure if it's um, anything that's uh serious or
A difficult surgery or anything, but good luck to you. Wish you the best. Thank you so much for the five dollars
Uh, we also have
Hawkeye of mine gave the twelve dollars earlier at the top of all the other money
But for the twelve dollar message here is well here's for my next bit badge
And i'm super stoked to have gotten to see the la noir streams come back
You're getting great interrogations. Have a good one germa and I love all the germs in chat
Thank you hawkeye
Appreciate it
Thank you so much for
69 dollars
Thank you
And I think i'm getting the hang of it
Once I figured out that you just have to find the thing
The one thing it's not like oh, let's I'm I investigated the crime scene. I have to talk about all those things
I'm I I get it
It's a lot of fun
Thank you so much. Okay. Thank you wave let for the four dollars and 20 cents
Germa heart. Thank you wave let
4 20
Did you say germa heart nothing else?
Uh kirenski. Thanks for the one dollar
Germa go back and watch rat movie 2 real quick
That video was uploaded on my birthday and my name is michael and I couldn't have asked for a better gift in case
You don't read resub messages
uh
I would be breaking my number one rule. Unfortunately, uh kirenski. I I don't I will not watch rat movie on stream
Go watch it quick
but
sad faces
You already did you didn't know it. When did I do that?
Well, listen michael
It's your birthday today cake and ice cream is on its way
and uh michael
You've been such a good boy this year. You're gonna open up your gifts while we all cheer
Celebrate another celebrate another one a birthday bash celebrate another one a birthday bash. There you go
Rat movie anniversary stream or we're gonna revolt
But now happy birthday
Was I was I shitfaced when I when we watched it? I had to have been right?
How do you still have it memorized?
It's only like four lines and I recorded it
How the hell do you remember that thing that was three sentences that you recorded it was on the wasp stream
You're always drunk when you stream. That's your gimmick. I never ever
Maybe like once every two months
Once every like two or three months. I'll have a couple of drinks
Or drink two bottles of champagne or like a bottle of liquor like for labo. Look it happens sometimes
Once every month you aren't drunk
Oh my lord, but happy birthday karen ski
Uh redhead arama. Thanks for the one dollar. I love all your content
I usually just watch vods and videos, but I popped in to say keep it up
You're great. Seems good
Thank you redhead arama
Glad you can enjoy
Watching the streams even when they're not live or the videos that are on the second channel
Thank you for even participating at all. Thank you
And it's good to see you again. We don't talk about the labo streams. Well, I had fun
My favorite take from the labo streams was the first night that I did it
I was getting I was like drunk and I was having a ton of fun
and then the next time it was like people were yelling at me and people being very mean to me and
I wasn't drunk and somebody said dude
You were just having fun the first night and we weren't and you just didn't care because you were drunk
And I was laughing my ass off about it. Like i'm having so much fun and everyone's like this is awful
Not everybody just like 20 percent of everybody I would do it again, too
I'm not kidding if there was if there was another labo, I would build it tomorrow
Just wait until the stupid car comes out and I do that again for like eight hours
I'm going to do it again. But this time i'm gonna do it like in the wind
I'll go on location and try to build the labo
On some mountain in nevada and like just extreme winds and try to do it. But thank you
Thank you hawkeye of mine again for three dollars
Uh, your stream's addictive man. I gave my goodbye bits but stuck around so here's the rest of my pocket change again
Love you and all the germs here, too. I just i'm just glad you're having fun. I'm happy that you can
Sit here and enjoy it
Because I enjoy it too
It's out right now
Wait, wait, wait, hold on the the vehicle kit is out right now
Okay
I know what we're doing. I know what we're doing this like weekend after the green screen scream
It came out in september. Oh boy. Okay
Yeah
You you shouldn't have told me that
I'm gonna be the only guy on twitch that's built them all if you recommend any rpgs. Absolutely chrono trigger
super mario rpg, uh
lost odyssey, um
Chrono cross except not really you really have to be into it. That's pretty much it
Undertale that's another that's good, too
Just don't ever type undertale into google because you'll you just play it just play it and don't like go go look up anything
Just enjoy it for what it is
Sounds like i'll be playing some of those. Oh, they're some of the best rpgs ever made
Lost odyssey not so much
But that's just like a recent one that came out on xbox and it was pretty good
Uh, but dark soul. Thank you for those two dollars dark soul. Hey germa
You're my first sub and donation ever and when I make more money, I will happily donate more
You've been through so many phases in my life from when I was at my lower points to my highest peaks
Keep doing what you're doing because you make my life and so many others full of joy and laughter from even the shortest of streams
That means a lot. Thank you
uh
People that laugh together last together means a lot
Thank you so much guys and honey chain at the very end. Thanks for the one dollar germa heart. Thank you
Why am I getting booed?
Why am I getting booed? Why are you booing me?
Boo, let's get the credits on here before we end and I will see you guys tomorrow
With the nintendo labo vehicle kit
What if I just fucking did that?
There's a ton of people
more than half of the audience leaves
During this portion how fucking mad do you think everyone would be if I turned the stream on and it was the labo
I was doing it tomorrow
Part of me kind of wants to do that
But I don't know
I got you know, I kind of think i'm just gonna play la noir for like 30 minutes
And then i'm just gonna turn the webcam on and it's the labo behind me and we're just gonna pivot immediately to it for eight hours
Don't tell anybody
Well, uh, what time is it? It's
I'm maybe I can run to like the store
vegas never turns off man
I can I can go to the store at like midnight and like go get anything I want
Oh, would that be that would be such a I think i'm gonna i'm gonna do it
That sounds like just stupid enough for me to happy be happy with it
We'll see we'll see if I can get it
I'm just gonna play la noir for like 25 minutes and then i'm just gonna pan back
And that's it build the labo
Or am I what have I got sucked into yeah, like well it'll just be it'll just be ready behind me
Over the next couple of days
All right. We'll try
But let's run the uh credits
All the new subs and old subs. Thank you everybody here they come
Thank you all of you for supporting the stream as always
Every single one of you are all fucking amazing
Just start making just make labo puns the whole time
Yeah
You guys you guys really gotta keep uh quiet on this though because i'm gonna just reference cardboard and shit for like the first 20 minutes
I'll like bump into somebody a crash and oh that guy really crashed like crushed like a piece of cardboard
I mean nintendo really is like such an interesting company making like all these new things that people like played on stream
This is cool, how did I do this? This is actually part of stream labs
Um, it's not as detailed as I might like it to be
If i'm honest because you can really only do one thing and that's just scroll everybody
I wish it was possible to separate, uh by length of time subscribed
Why don't I read the credits anymore?
Well, there's two reasons
the first reason is
um, I think the the schtick of
screaming out
names
As as fast as I can
It's kind of uh, it's kind of over
And the second thing is there's so many of them though
So many people are subscribed to this channel now that it's
Uh, I I can't even fucking believe it
it's truly truly unbelievable
And uh, it's not going away. It's just changing
Because over the next probably month or so
There's gonna be something that happens at the end of the streams
In this spot right here
There's gonna be some fairly fun little interesting things that are not
It's not gonna be oh i'm gonna
Pick out some subs and they're like they're i'm gonna like shout them out. No, it'll be just something interesting
So there will be something fun at the end of streams that includes all the people that subscribe during that stream
You touched on this before I remember
yeah
it's tough because I really I want people to understand that like I really
appreciate and care that they're
Giving me their hard-earned money every month
Some of you guys like I'm treated like a netflix subscription, right? Like it's just people have been subscribed for years
And I never wanted people to think that I just oh, hey, thanks. Bye
That's why but I did something about just reading names
Doesn't do enough for me anymore
I'd like to try to do something fun
So just give me some time. I'll figure it out
But much love to you all
When is season five coming out season five of what?
Give me an attaboy for my support
Yeah, and I think there's like two different ways to do like subscriptions and bits and everything
and i've always been of the opinion that i'd like to keep it as
sort of like away from the stream as possible because my I my adhd is impossible to
Keep up with and i'd like to have them kind of just separated
in a way
If that makes sense, I hope it does
Can't wait for the season of fortnight. Are they in like season six or seven of fortnight?
I'm subbed to other people and when they read messages as they're sent, it's really out of place
well, I mean it really depends because I mean
the the only issue I ever had with it was
You know when when it's one person when it's two people, okay, I mean whatever that's easy to do
when it turns into like a hundred two hundred people potentially on a stream, it's
You know had a sub message notification comes up potentially every you know, 30 to 40 seconds every minute every two minutes
I've had streams where 400 people subscribed and it was like holy shit
And it's it's hard to balance between
I mean
I want people to know that I care and that I thank them and that they it means a fucking lot to me
but at the same time
there's
There's a stream to do you know what I mean? I would like to stream
It's something I think about a lot
The animation froze what did it?
So that's why over the years i've tried to come up with things to do like the end of the stream here
We sit and we relax and talk about you know
all the people that have donated money and I want to touch upon them and the subscription credits and
There'll always be something like that. I just have to figure out as if the channel continues to grow
more solutions and more things to do to try
but uh
That is for another day. I will see you guys tomorrow for the nintendo labo stream
I'm gonna piss a lot of people off
It's it has to happen though. Thanks a lot guys. See you tomorrow
Take care. Have a great rest of your night