So I'm sitting here questioning a couple things about the state of media and how, hear me out.
So why is it that I can play The Lord of the Rings The Fellowship of the Ring on PlayStation 2
with a bunch of cutscenes and all the fucking music, but I can't watch The Fellowship of the
Ring on Twitch? Why am I not allowed to do that? Why can I play The Fellowship of the Ring the game,
but I can't watch The Fellowship of the Ring the movie? It's, I don't understand.
What happened to my fucking, my cord got all fucked up. Aren't they under the same boat? Is it
licensing? All right, but okay, but if Shadow of, Shadow of War came out like two years ago,
if I listen to The Hobbit's song in Shadow of War, but then I play a clip of The Hobbit's song
on YouTube, my channel gets, gets muted. That's weird. Like, is that, I don't understand.
Dermot, your audio is sounding nice and crisp today. Ha, well, look at you. We're playing Lord
of the Rings The Fellowship of the Ring today because one person guaranteed I wouldn't get
past the first level. So, that's what we're doing. I don't know why you would say that because I,
weirdly enough, my memory does not remember this one. Yeah, there it is. Lord of the Rings,
you won't make it. Here we go. Just for, just for context, for those of you that are curious,
here's the context here. You won't get past the first part of Fellowship, I guarantee it.
All right, I wouldn't, all right, I wouldn't remember your name because when I get past
level one in Fellowship of the Ring, I'm going to fucking scream your name. Right. What was
the name? Fake what? Here comes another hype train. Wait, I, I like made, I made this harder
to do. I increased it. All right. Well, here we go. Here we go again. When I get, when I'm done.
Fake. All right. Fake, fake. Here comes the hype train. When I am done with. Uh,
thanks for the hype train, guys. All right. Free, free hype trains in three days. This is like,
all right. When you, when you go to, when you, when you ride a ride at Disney World,
right? When you get on the hype train and you ride, you ride the fucking new Star Wars ride.
And it's like, holy shit, that was hype. That was insane. That was incredible. Oh, oh my God,
when Han Solo like flew by, dude, I shit my pants. Let's do it again. And you ride it again.
On the third or fourth ride on the hype train, on the hype ride, you look up and you start to see
where the fucking mechanical shit is. I, oh, wait. Oh, there's Han Solo. I can see the wire.
I can see the wire up there and it's connected to an arm. Oh, hi. Fuck. We're getting, there's
too many hype trains. All right. This is fucking ridiculous. Rusty bars. Oh no. Wait, hold on a
minute. Is there, is there a scratch on that LCD screen? Yeah. I didn't notice that on the first
fucking hype. Ah, Gary, should we have rode this ride 10 times in a row? Where are your kids?
Level three complete already. Level three. Here comes level four. Get on the hype train. Never
get off. Never get off the hype train. Already level four. You guys are not fucking around today.
We're just doing it. But okay. That's my point with this whole thing is I got to tweak some
numbers on this because I don't want to ride the Han Solo ride 20 times in a row and every day
I'm just sitting there. Get hype for the hype train. There's Han Solo. There he goes. Yeah.
Get hype. Oh, fuck. You've given me so much money in four days. I don't want it to be like
just going through the motions thing for me. I'm going to tweak the numbers. I'm going to make it
harder to do. We'll see. I thought I already did that, but you guys are fucking, you guys are so
generous. Like even if I keep making this harder to do, you're probably still going to do it.
You're still going to do it. Get hype or else. Oh man. Thanks guys. Seriously. This is fucking
too much. There's a lot of the rings. All right. You did it. Hype. You did it. Hype. Hype. Hype.
Hype. Hype. Hype. Thank you guys. Seriously. Level four. Oh, dude. There's only five minutes
to get this train out of the station. Dude. Four minutes and 30 seconds remain. What the?
Let's go. Start it. Do it. 27%, 28%. Come on, man. We can do this. We can do this three days in a
row. That's going to get my VOD muted. This is, okay, this is mute the VOD day. We got Lord of
the Rings music, Lord of the Rings fellowship of the ring in the background. We've got a hype train
getting on the ride again and it's going to complete and it's going to keep going.
We like to party. We like to party more. I can't even fucking keep up, man. This is insane.
Oh my fucking God. Get out of that hype train. Hey, Eleanor, $50. I like this video game. Thanks
for the 5,000 bits. Thanks for completing the hype train. Should I just play the song?
Should I just play this song and that's it? And that's what we do. And we just ride the hype
train and then we get off. It's too loud. All right. Hold on. Let me just be very, very... Did
somebody say that the Venga Boys was too loud? The Venga Boys are only allowed to be played at an
audio level of at least seven out of 10. If you play the Venga Boys under a five out of 10 in volume,
your computer explodes. It's like Speed, the movie with Keanu Reeves. A hundred dB.
Anyways, we did it. You did it again. You did it again. You did it again. You fucking... You blew
through another like three, five hundred subs or whatever it was. What is it? Let's just see
what it completes. It tells us. Play the song. You're getting the song. Actually, this is kind
of the royalty-free version of fellowship of the ring, isn't it? It is. This is not really fellowship
of the ring. So now I understand why I can play it. Where's Jon Snow? Wrong franchise. You're
thinking of a game of thrones. Where's Jon Snow? Toss a coin to the streamer. Oh my fucking God.
Another 5,000 bits from numb legs. They say hype in all capitals. Fucking... I'm making that
goddamn movie. I'm making that movie. Here's the part about this though. The projects that
are in the pipeline now became... I just fed all of my Pokemon that magic fruit that makes them
all stronger. I've got like 10 Pokemon in my Pokedex thing and I just gave them all the magic
fruit that makes them like 20% stronger, whatever it is. What's it called? Rare Candy. That's right.
You guys just gave Rare Candy to the four projects that are coming up in the next three,
four months. There it is. You achieved a hype level of level five. You did it. Let's get the
Vanga Boys on here to show just how fucking hype that was. 129 subs, 23,000 bits. Jesus Christ,
guys. In the first 10 minutes of the stream. You guys are too much. Thanks for sprinkling
Rare Candy all over all my fucking Pokemon videos that are coming out. Or streams, you know.
Anyway, let's play Lord of the Rings, Fellowship of the Ring. We'll go over all those at the end
of the stream like we always do, but holy shit. Hype is over. Back to sleep. New game. Lord of
the Rings. Okay, I was gonna say hopefully it doesn't hang. He's playing a game. Wake me up,
but he's not. We're gonna get a cutscene I think here. Is it the actors? Is it the original actors?
We'll find out. Hello? It's the old PlayStation 2 buzzing sound. Here we go.
That's the Harry Potter memory thing.
In the shadows of Morgdor, the Dark Lord Sauron forged the one ring to enslave all elves,
dwarves, and men of Middle-earth. The three people of Middle-earth overthrew Sauron,
but lost the ring. Now the enemy has returned, and from his dark tower in Morgdor,
he seeks his ring. We must find the ring first and destroy it. Who is that supposed to be?
Don't- I should know this.
Dendril? Dendril? Gabriel? No, not Gabriel. Gala- Gala- Gala-Leo. I don't know that- I don't
know. I'm such a fucking shitty fan. I don't know her name. Not Gandalf. Why are there no subtitles?
Gala-Dreel. Welcome back, Gandalf. Will we have fireworks, elvish lessons,
tales of ancient Numenor? Today, we must talk about a shadow of the past.
The ring you inherited may be very dangerous. Is that Ian Kellan? Uncle Bilbo's magic ring?
Magic rings, as you call them, were made by elves. But this ring, I think, was made by another.
Give me the ring. That looks like the Christian Bible game show host.
See, Frodo, it was that easy. You just gotta toss it into some fire.
Let me save you 16 hours worth of movie. I see fine lines, lines of fire, in a flowing script.
What does it say? One ring to rule them all, one ring to find them, one ring to bring them all,
and in the darkness, bind them. This is the one ring to rule them all.
The ancient kings of elves, dwarves, and men use the rings of power to rule their lands.
See, I don't have to pay attention to this cutscene, because I already, like,
know this. Oh, dude, pay attention to the cutscene. Everyone's seen this movie.
A strange creature called Gollum found the ring and was corrupted by it.
Bilbo won it from Gollum, and now it is yours. But the lord of the rings has returned,
and all his thought is bent on finding the ring.
Let's destroy it. It can only be destroyed when it was forged, in Mount Doom, the fire mountain in
Lorda. Take it there, take it. No, do not tempt me. If I bore the ring, I would become the Dark Lord
Gandalf. It's not like a piece of chocolate while you're on a diet.
I'm a danger to the Shire. I must leave. I could set out on the road just like Bilbo.
My dear Frodo, hobbits really are amazing creatures. But you need not go alone. If there
are any you can trust. But take care. The enemy has many spies.
Uh-oh. What was in the window? I didn't look in the window. Did you look in the window?
What? Well then. Samwise Gamgee, isn't it?
Don't hurt me. What are you doing at Bag End?
Nothing, sir. Trimming the grass under the window.
Oh? The sound of Shire stopped some time ago.
Bootleg Lord of the Rings. We're just watching the Lord of the Rings on stream.
Finally. I get to live my fucking fantasy.
What have you heard? Oh, Frodo, don't let him turn me into anything unnatural.
He won't hurt you. Just answer his question.
Well, I heard a lot. I didn't understand about lords and rings in the fiery mountain.
And elves, sir. I had to listen. I dearly love to see elves.
Were they? Keep it a secret, Sam.
Or I hope Gandalf turned you into a spotted toad.
I've thought of something better.
Why don't they shave their feet?
You will go away with you, Frodo.
Me, sir? I don't understand.
Go and see elves and all. Hooray!
But where should we go?
Towards danger, but not too rashly.
Just grab like a wax strip and just-
Take time to settle your affairs before you leave.
I could leave in autumn, on my birthday.
Very well, but no later.
How come there wasn't like a 40-year-old virgin
part of these movies where Frodo gets like his feet waxed and he's like,
Oh, I'm killing Ornstein!
Every time they rip it off.
I'll have to sell Bag End.
The Sackville Bagginses have been trying to take over this place for years.
A shame to let them have it.
Indeed. And now I must go. I have much to attend to.
As do I.
That would ruin these fucking movies.
That would ruin everything.
They would not get nominated for any Academy Awards across the entire three movies.
Oh, yes. Not a word from Sam Gamgee, and that's for certain.
Once you leave, travel as Mr. Underhill.
The name of Baggins is not synced outside the Shire.
And do not use the ring, for it can corrupt the most innocent heart.
I understand.
Gandalf, how do you use a ring?
You just paused on it.
I'm going to see elves.
Farewell, Frodo. I'll return by your birthday.
Oh, my birthday?
I'm going to get Gandalfs coming to my birthday party.
As the nights grew longer, I decided I might have to leave the house.
You're not coming to your birthday party.
On the morning of my birthday, September 22nd,
I set out for one final stroll around the Shire.
I had to say farewell to my neighbors and sell my home to the Bees Sackville Baggins.
Scroll back up. What?
He's coming to my birthday. That's my birthday.
Gandalf, just come to my fucking birthday party.
Not yours.
He could be making it up, though.
All right, let's go.
Happy birthday. Gandalf's coming to my birthday party.
Oh, I have to get ready.
You picked a Bag End key. Get the key to Bag End.
Press and hold R2 to view Frodo's inventory.
Use the left analog stick to scroll through Frodo's inventory.
Walking stick.
Oh, you can punch and you can hit.
All right, so I got the key to Bag End.
Anything else I need to do?
Stick in Bag End.
Shut up.
All right, let's go. I got the key.
Wait, I don't want to miss any secrets.
Hey, by the way, what qualifies as the first part of Lord of the Rings?
Fellowship of the Ring.
Getting out of the house here.
This is the first level is getting out of the house.
Find the deed to Bag End before leaving.
Oh, shit.
Is there a sprint?
Fucking ugly ass game.
Yes, I know it is PlayStation 2.
I know.
But it's pretty ugly.
He's gonna quit it.
He's gonna quit.
Oh, no.
No, I'm not gonna quit.
I can't.
Bring us in this chest.
I best leave it here until I sell Bag End.
He sells his house?
I don't...
Wait, hold on.
Frodo sells his house in Fellowship of the Ring?
Where's the deed to the house?
You never watched the movie.
Yes, I did.
I don't remember them being on a house sale.
You didn't read the books.
No, I didn't read the books.
Because...
Where's his deed?
The movies were so good that I couldn't read the books.
Okay?
I'll be...
I'm gonna be honest.
The movies were too good.
So I could not read the books.
Hold on a second.
Let me just do something here.
I think I can turn the brightness up a little bit or something.
Something's wrong.
It looks like shitty, crusty.
I think that just might be the game.
Let me see if I can tweak this.
I'm not cheating.
All right, here we go.
Is that better or worse?
I can't even tell.
That's like worse.
Wait, oh, there we go.
That's a little better.
Is it worse?
Do we saturate the colors a little more?
All right, now we're looking okay.
Now it doesn't look like total dog shit.
Have you dropped the contrast a little?
Put the gamut down.
Gamut down, sharpness up, brightness up.
I don't have access to those.
That looks better.
That looks all right right there.
Looks like I put the ring on.
All right, let me walk around for a second.
Oh yeah, that's like a thousand times better.
Before it was like I hurt my head.
That's so much better.
All right, let's close this back down.
Am I playing this in a bathtub?
Yes.
Yes, I'm in a bathtub right now.
I'm playing in a bathtub.
I bathe and play.
That's how I game.
That's how you know that I take it dead seriously.
Oh, oh, by the question.
I was scared to do this and I didn't know.
Okay, let me ask.
This is a real question.
Because how does electricity even work?
So if I bring, let's say for instance,
if somebody was to hypothetically,
if you would like to be in a bathtub, right?
Like if you're taking a bath and you want to,
oh, I have like my phone with me
or my iPad, right?
If you have your iPad in the bath,
if you drop the iPad into the bathtub,
is it going to electrocute you?
No, right?
No, because there's no current.
That's, there has to be a current.
Yeah, because there's no like current to let go.
Yeah, okay.
Oh, that's correct.
Yeah, because I was taking a bath and I was like,
I want to use my iPad.
But if I like slip and drop the iPad into the bath,
am I going to get like fucking killed?
I was scared.
The amperage is too low.
I don't know.
It's like, okay, what if you dropped it?
Listen, what if, okay, an iPad won't do it.
But what if you had like a big fucking like Alienware laptop
that has like an i7 in it?
And it's like a $3,000 laptop.
If you dropped it into the bathtub,
would that still do it?
No.
Okay.
Where's this deed?
Where's this deed so I can tell this person
that I beat the first part?
All right, I'm going to check every fucking room.
We're at the end of the hallway.
This way.
Okay, is it in here?
In the dining room.
Not in the dining room.
Nothing sparkly to look at.
There's nothing in here.
Okay.
Next room.
This one right here.
No deed.
Okay, found the deed.
Complete.
I got it.
Hey, hey, fake Grumbo, if you're here.
I'm about to fucking yell your name really loud.
I actually can't get out of the house.
Hey, I beat the first.
This is not the first level, never mind.
Imagine dropping a whole laptop in the bath.
What's with the flame?
There's like weird scan lines right now.
Do you see that?
The Shire.
Press triangle to talk to others.
Good morning to you, Mr. Frodo.
Good morning, Sam.
All ready to set out for Buckland?
Already?
Or will be as soon as I tend to Bag End.
Lobelia Sackville Baggins is buying the place.
You don't need to weed Bag End ever again.
I'd like to weed them Sackville Bagginses out of Bag End.
If you get my meaning.
What?
Bag End has the best garden in the Shire, thanks to your work.
Oh, no, I'm sure there are many finer.
This game is dated as fuck.
Mary Brandybuck said he was meeting Pippin Took at the Green Dragon and invited you to join.
They took a long walk out here just for a drink.
This game sucks, actually, is what you-
Begging your pardon, sir.
But there's little mischief to be found in the Green Dragon.
The Keeper won't stand for it.
We will see.
Wait, but hold on a minute.
I'm-
What a pretty bird.
What?
The two towers is like one of the best games ever made.
What happened?
I'll be here when these pumpkins get turned into pies.
More's the pity.
I hate this camera.
It's so stupid.
Okay, let's keep going.
Number three, Bag Shot Row.
Home of the Ganges.
We'll send this hit as much-
No, I can't.
I can't, I can't.
I'm not stopping.
Mushroom.
Frodo can eat mushrooms to restore his health.
Okay.
Hi, Milo.
Hello, Frodo.
Seen any elves lately?
I'm afraid not, I'm sorry to say.
What about trolls?
No trolls either.
Good.
It's about time you found your hobbit sense again.
You know, some say you're as mad as your uncle.
Carrying on with an old wizard-
And to complete the first mission.
I know, that's the-
I'm gonna-
Well, at least they have something interesting to talk about then.
Good day.
Somebody fucking guaranteed that I wouldn't do the first level.
They guaranteed it.
I can't let that person win.
Where do I go?
I gotta go find Marion Pippin.
What is it?
By the garden or something?
Howlfast Hornblower, number six.
These people's names are out here?
You probably should have let them win.
No.
Is there a game here?
Or do I just have to play as a hobbit?
Don't we traverse mountains and shit?
Isn't that like big battle sequences?
What happened in the first movie?
Right, hold on, here we go.
Hello, Ted.
I wanted to say goodbye before I-
Can't you see I'm busy?
Actually, no.
You seem to be just standing about.
Well, if you knew about mills,
you'd know I'm trying to locate a very important metal pin
that must have fallen out of my mill wheel.
Is that why the mill isn't working?
I have to-
Oh, never you mind about working or not working.
I've sent Mugwort to Brie for a replacement.
I thought I-
Wait, I have to go get-
If I haven't found it yet,
there's no way you can find it.
Metal pin next to the-
It looks like a plain metal pin.
Now, good day to you.
Holy shit.
Imagine having a movie that was made with like 150 to what?
200 million dollars.
And your tie-in video game for one of the most celebrated franchises
ever in the history of human cinema and human literature
is find the pin to the fucking watermill.
All right, where's that mill?
This isn't based on the movie.
It's not?
Yes, it is.
Official game based on the literary works of J.R.R. Tolkien.
I call bullshit on that because look at the costumes.
This is the same-
Like, this is Peter Jackson costume design and-
What?
Like, Peter Jackson designed this cape.
What do you mean?
No, it's not.
That's Ian McKellen's Gandalf.
No.
What?
The costumes are described in the books.
No, I'm telling you.
We're gonna get-
I'm telling you, though.
This is based on the fucking movie.
This-
Bullshit.
Fellowship of the Ring.
When did it come out?
What?
You just magically decided to-
Oh, you just magically, less than six months later after the movie comes out,
you decide we're gonna make a game based on the literary works of the Fellowship of the Ring
four and a half months after the fucking movie comes out.
Bullshit.
You can't develop a game in six months.
All right, one guy's not winning.
I'm going to do this right now.
Peter Jackson based the film on this game.
I have to-
All right, let's go.
Come on.
I have to get to the first level.
Nope, nope, nope, nope.
I refuse.
This is why they said it.
It had nothing to do with the game being hard.
Fuck.
I thought it was like,
dude, the game's too hard for you.
Like, the combo meter, you're gonna fuck it up.
Like, that's in the second and third game.
I get it now.
Now I know why he said that.
I just skipped dialogue in the first-
All right, let's go.
Get high.
Ah, yes, my favorite Lord of the Rings character.
Minto!
Yes, I know.
This is-
It's okay.
You're right.
Yeah, Minto.
This part's not even in the movie.
Got it.
Wait.
This is my house.
Where are you going?
I don't know.
I have to go find Marion Pippen in the garden.
Where's the garden?
Fellowship of the fucking Ring.
Oh, I found the well.
Ladders can be climbed.
I wonder how many lucky wishing stones are at the bottom of this well.
Oh, I wonder how quickly my legs would break
if I would have fucking fall straight down to the bottom.
How do I do it?
Brodo can grab ledges and hoist himself onto them.
Jump to what?
There's a-
Okay, well, that worked.
Got default pig sound.
That's pretty hype.
Okay, wait.
What?
There's only a mushroom up here?
This is a bootleg copy?
No, no.
This is a real copy.
The game was just not-
No fucking way.
No.
Yes way.
What does this have on, like, ratings?
All right.
If I just splatted and I died and I got a game over screen,
that would have been very, very funny.
Click the link.
Omega low.
All right.
Hold on.
What is it?
Hobbit Day.
Hobbit Day is the name used for September 20th,
a reference to being the birthday of the hobbits.
I can't even-
How am I supposed to say about this?
I can't even combat this.
It's not fair.
That's not fair.
And it's not-
Life isn't fair.
Okay?
Wax you-
How hairy are they?
They're a little hairy.
Oh, show, show.
You think I'm gonna get baited?
What?
You think I'm gonna get baited
to like be in somebody's permanent folder on their desktop?
Oh, dude.
Yeah, you should show-
Oh, I wonder how hairy they are.
Click that.
Yes.
Yes, I got it.
Oh, yes.
Okay.
Hold on.
Calm down.
Calm down, Frank.
You just got it.
Okay.
Now save permanently to computer.
Save permanently.
Make two copies of it.
Okay.
Oh, yes.
I can watch this every-
I can watch this every day.
I can watch it every single day.
Come on, get baited.
Sandieman's mill looks a lot more cheerful than Ted Sandieman.
Installing.
I don't-
Okay, where's the garden?
I don't care about these little quests.
I don't want to just go meet the other people in the movie.
In the book, whatever.
Oh, Mary and Pippin are in the garden.
What?
Where's the garden?
What garden?
And where was this?
The metal stick I have to find?
I don't even have a map either.
This is the-
I'm about to grapple.
Okay.
Why do I keep hearing cat puke noises?
I don't know.
Guys, I don't think you understand.
What's the over-under on like the-
Oh, dude, like show-
Hey, sweat check.
Sweat check.
Oh, yeah, let's do a sweat check.
Hey, got it.
What's the over-under?
Do the game.
There's a garden right here.
Oh, no.
Let's go.
Why can't I talk?
Will we be off to see the elves soon, Frodo?
Soon, Sam.
I have a few things to take care of first.
God damn it.
I can't let this person be right.
I guarantee.
I guarantee you not gonna get to the first-
through the first part.
A fellowship of the regular PlayStation 2.
Guaranteed.
Fucking-
They can't be right.
Oh, there's-
I can't.
You can't win.
I can't win.
I have to find a metal stick
next to the old water mill.
But where is the old water mill?
He said, you'll never find it.
You're never gonna find the metal pin needed for this.
I guarantee it.
He looks right in the fucking camera and winks at you guys.
Hello there, Hal.
Oh, hello, Frodo.
You have a beautiful day to begin your trip to Crick Hollow.
Yes, indeed.
I'm too old for such long walks.
I can't even climb high enough to fix my weather vane.
No.
What's wrong with it?
The thing's stuck.
Sorry to hear it.
That rascal Sancho Proudfoot was throwing sticks at it.
Now it won't turn at all.
I'll take a look at it before I leave.
All right, I just threw up.
It's been 45 minutes.
I have to fucking do this now.
The ladder's right over there.
Ladder, let's go.
Throw a rock at it.
What?
Let's go.
Enter target mode, press L2, and use the analog stick to aim.
I'm not tall enough to aim at this.
Wait.
How do I throw a rock?
I don't have any rocks.
Where do I get a rock?
I don't have rocks.
Is there a rock like right next to it or something?
Throw a rock?
Did he?
Wait a minute.
There's just rocks just sitting right next to it or something.
There's one where?
I have to find a rock and come back here and throw it.
Holy shit.
Follow the road.
Please, for the love of God, go to the next area.
Okay, find a rock and find the pin.
Can't Gandalf just fucking help me do this?
Gandalf is waiting at the end of the road.
Who's taking this little shit so long?
I've got places to be.
Should have left it to a dwarf instead.
All right, seriously.
Where's the rock?
This is...
I don't understand.
Don't...
Stop walking in circles.
There is nowhere else to go.
Guy!
There's nowhere else to go.
Minto is a minor character.
I don't...
I don't care.
I need to find a rock and the pin and...
This book sucks.
Garden...
If there's an item on the ground that's able to be picked up, it glows.
Stay on the road, Jerma.
Stay on the road.
Okay, I'm going to stay on the road.
Only on road.
Only.
Here we are again.
Wait.
Guys leave?
Oh, I thought I had to do the quests.
You just walk out.
I thought it was like, oh, find my...
I just beat the first level.
The Shire.
By water.
Holy fuck.
I can't believe I just did that.
I thought I had to do all that stuff.
Turns out I didn't.
Was that all just a joke?
I'm going to be realistic with you guys.
Do you honestly think a hobbit with a stick is going to do a goddamn thing?
Give me a knife or something.
Or give me like a gun.
Give me something sharp.
A hobbit with a stick.
That's not going to do anything.
Or like a bow.
I don't know.
Anything.
Will I?
Stay on the road.
What about the guy playing chess?
Hello, young Baggins.
Cheers on your birthday.
Thank you kindly, Daddy Two-Foot.
I haven't seen your wizard friend about lately.
Daddy Two-Foot.
I do miss those fireworks.
So do I.
I remember the day when all those dwarves came to call on Mr. Bilbo.
Dwarves and a wizard.
I'm sorry.
It's automatic.
I have to do it.
Such strange stories these days.
Long dead better whites waking near the old forest.
Great armies in the east and south.
Dwarves and big.
All right.
That's enough out of you.
Don't care.
Ring the bell.
What's going on?
I don't hold with reckless bell ringing.
Oh, if any wolves approach the Shire, the bounders will chase them off.
Just as they chase away foxes and such.
I'm glad the Shire is well protected.
Now, if that's all, I've got a mug to return to in the green dragon.
Okay.
All right.
Bye.
Okay, Gandalf.
I'm ready.
Okay.
Hey, Gandalf.
I'm ready.
This is the way that I came.
No.
Yes.
Is it the way that I came?
He's so bad.
What a little dick boy.
All right, dude.
No.
Did I come this way?
I did.
Didn't I?
Yeah, I did.
No, I didn't.
Wait, is this guy again?
Hello, Nox.
Good to see you up and about again.
Hi, thank you.
I'm fit as a horse again.
Folks will be calling me well-preserved like they do your uncle Bilbo.
That does kind of look like the German painting face.
Why, it's this new herbal tea I've been drinking.
Good.
Well, I'm off to my old bones.
It's that must be Nox.
I had perhaps I.
I don't care.
Find four healing herbs in Green Hill country.
For old Nox.
How about we find Gandalf?
The guy that I'm supposed to find.
You're ignoring side quests.
Why would I do the side quests in this game?
The Shire.
Green Hill country.
Okay, what we got?
When are we going to get to hear the?
Here's one of those packets of herbs Nox spoke on.
Great.
Hello there.
Good day, lad.
Thank you.
Bilbo.
Frodo.
Frodo faggans.
Living that grand place atop the hill.
Frodo.
It's me Frodo.
Not Bilbo.
That's my dad.
Where?
Not time to chat.
I'm off to great.
On an Arab.
Uncle, uncle.
I know it's uncle.
Stop.
Thanks, Bilbo.
We need that meal and Ted says he's too important to go himself.
Okay, bye.
Good devs.
Nice work, guys.
Give it up for devs.
Good devs.
Devs not in chat.
Oh.
Oh, shit.
Wait, I'm streaming a game and the dev is not here watching me stream.
Really?
How many viewers do I have?
I don't know.
I'm just saying.
What the fuck?
Why they're not here?
Okay.
Fuck.
I'm like, I don't want to be annoyed by that, but I mean like, fuck.
Do not let pharma maggot's dog spot you.
Use rocks to distract the dog.
I'm not gonna throw rocks at a dog.
Where's this dog?
Woof.
What's all this racket?
That would be me, sir.
Well, well, we have a burglar in the fields.
Burglar?
All done with your mushroom thieving?
Or would you prefer to take it up with the lads?
Are there police in this world?
Right, you are, sir.
Who are the police?
Now off with you, or I'll have the lads disperse you.
Is the lad supposed to be the police?
Okay.
Well, I'm stealing your mushrooms.
Don't let the dog see you.
Okay, I'm not gonna, I'm gonna make sure the dog, there's a sneak.
Use rocks.
I don't fucking have rocks.
Why does this game think I have rocks?
I don't have rocks.
Put the ring on.
Does he turn around?
I have rocks.
I don't have rocks?
Oh my god.
There are no rocks.
I don't have rocks.
They don't exist.
I don't have fucking rocks.
L2.
X.
Circle.
Y.
X.
Circle.
Y.
It's circle.
What am I supposed to do with these?
Is the dog distracted?
Stop.
Oh my god.
Turn around.
What?
He turned around for one second.
All right, hold on.
I'll get it.
Oh fuck, was he gone?
What the fuck was that?
Get it!
Healing herb.
All right, I did it.
Go in the dog house?
I got it.
That's all I needed.
I wonder what broke this fence.
What broke this fence?
The fence is still fine.
How do I get in here?
There's a healing herb for grandpa.
Crawl.
How do you crawl?
I don't think you can.
What the?
You don't have to be zoomed in for this.
There is no crawl.
Maybe the other side?
Why does this look so blurry?
Well, because this game is from 20 plus years ago.
And it was not developed with any intention to ever have...
Gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme.
Got it.
That's four.
Training gummy.
I got it.
I completed the sequence?
Yeah.
That's one completed.
This is the end of the road though.
All right, I got the healing herbs.
No, there's still more.
wait what's in here is that just mushrooms yeah who cares can i knock that field of view though
it's pretty terrible i still have things to attend to before i set out for the old forest
all right boys and girls strapped in let's go i have my rocks i gotta find the guy's pin
let's go all right where's the look where's the pin he's mentioned a pin at the old water farm
at the old water dam at the old water farm where is it at the mill okay i got the healing herbs
it's two loading screens back yeah but is there anything else out here that i need to do
just check i don't want to have to come back here again for any reason are you enjoying the game
absolutely no absolutely not zero one hundred percent zero um i played my sheriff pranks when
i was sancho's age but i never took an old man's medicine he can't beat the first level but no but
i it might get better cast a lethal arsenal of magic as gandalf fight through hordes of enemies
as aragorn use stealth cunning and the one ring as frodo love to see that game i'd love to see
that one now where's the old man he actually believes the back of the box this is back when
the back of the box was reliable the back of the box in 2001 was more reliable than reviewers today
i have found these herbs for you thank you young frodo pagans for bringing me these herbs
please take this as a token of my gratitude you are such a basic fuck oh yeah basic huh
huh let me show you what you're missing
uh rock water water turn thing what's the thing called what's the water turn thing called it's
he called it something i just don't know i don't know what it was called a mill market oh this
square will be brimming over with the freshest crops is that what it's actually called though
what's the what's the divide what's the thing actually called the wheel the water wheel that
spins with the platforms on it what's that is that actually called a water mill okay rocks
them that got there's nothing back here you're pretending i know i actually don't know i really
didn't know that i said water mill i didn't know if it was accurate i don't know if it had like a
specific term a liquid wheel no milling is grinding you don't grind water is that true use the wheel
turn a shaft that grinds grain oh yeah you're right no you're right that wasn't me that said
that that was i was reading somebody in chat i know what a water wheel is i'm pretending for
views don't oh i'm a fucking idiot whoa what was it water wheel nope i'm just a fucking dope that
don't know view vacuum worst new character new care i don't know how is that a new character
what how many times have to hit this
all right barber how what's up it's a water powered mill i know guys i know
weathervane turns like it's my pleasure you've helped an old if you don't mind i'll just take
that metal pin that was jamming the weather oh this is a two-parter oh my god we did it it might
help my just trying to help we did it i got the pin so uh oh okay let's go uh where was this guy
anybody remember wait now that i can throw rocks that's not that's not like a secret or something
why do the hobbits paint illuminati symbols on their houses does that have any story reference
or anything all right what was that original guy use your brain jerma click the link quick
uh that's disgusting i'm gonna be completely real that is gross that's gross okay i don't
remember where this original dude was he was i don't remember it was right around here somewhere
next to the bridge where's this guy it's not this guy right no it's the guy by the
bridge was it if anyone's in this chat that hasn't seen lord of the rings and you're sitting here
thinking hey lord of the rings that's a cool i've heard that's pretty good don't base that off don't
base anything off of what you're watching right now the mill wheel spins again the movie is a
just read read the book just read the book you've done me a valuable service today someone in this
stream right now is going i'm never gonna fucking watch this movie what a shitty movie
no the movie's just watch it all right that's it this i don't have any more quests it was
nothing else right it's time to leave you forgot about the main quest what do you mean main quest
fine i find mary and pippin the ring is still in your house no
i do i have to take it uh go to the green dragon inn you're a fake fan i haven't seen lord of the
rings since i was like 17 i don't remember every scene i know he takes yes i know he takes the
ring but this is not even okay you can't give me a little bit slack frodo baggins doesn't go
throw rocks at a guy's weather vane so this is added bonus material in fact
i'm sure a lot of you would probably like that if there was a bonus super extended edition
the lord of the rings fans would go fucking nuts if there was a two hour long segment
of frodo just throwing rocks and stuff and picking up mushrooms the new bonus extended
extended edition it's six and a half hours long then it just you put the disc in and starts with
this screen where's this in no i've got the inn i gotta go to my i have to go to my house
there it is there's the green door there's the green dragon door that sounds like hog to me
all right give me my ring you've walked the area in circles for 40 minutes and you don't know the
layout oh we talked about this in pre-stream chat i'm gonna bring it up one more time here
because it's worth noting um if the game has no this people can think i'm an idiot i'm not
gonna say it if you're in pre-stream you know and any any pre-streamers here any pre-stream chatters
here if your game has move around dodge attack jump i'm going to destroy it if your game has
no minimap i will not be able to play unless it has follows that category it has to have four
buttons or less and it has to be constrained to one small area at a time but you give me that
scenario you give me four buttons or less put me in an area where i just have to fucking do it
i'll do it i'll do it better than anybody where's the it's in one of these you're a literal drone
i i am uh just give this thing one specific task to do in one small area and it'll be really good
at it oh i'm just a fucking sentry gun where's the ring i even make noises like a sentry gun too
okay i and so i'd like look over at chat look back look over chat like i've all right where's
the ring it's in here it's risen right here isn't it in here plot twist you already have it no i
don't tonight said i have to pick this up and take this that is the chest with the ring in it so
you don't need the ring all right
you put me in a you put me in a room with four buttons
you put me in a room with four buttons in a small room and i will fucking annihilate
i will destroy y'all have seen it i don't even i don't have to even tell you this
i will i had to prove this by people saying what are you talking about that doesn't make any sense
those of you that watched the like two or what was one terrible world of warcraft streams i ever did
uh this is real i pressed one through five on my hotbar and clicked everything else
i don't that's not me making it up you can go look at that terrible awful fucking body
okay now let me focus what was the final task was to find mary and pippin we'll go to the
green dragon inn that's the proud feat all right let's go in the garden arcane mage clicker omega
lol i was arcane mage before it was cool by the way can i be real with you here i was arcane mage
before it was even any good and then it became the best thing in the whole game and i quit world of
warcraft that's true that is a real statement arcane mage was dog shit they patched it made
it the best thing in the whole game and i quit world of warcraft and have never played since
i also played discipline priest when they didn't have any moves back in vanilla back when discipline
police did rewind delete snip pull complete uh when discipline priests had two spells and you
got kicked out of every party you were in that was me they had power infusion omega lol yeah
that where that's the worst spell in the whole game does that spell still exist that's the worst
spell in the entire game i just found it why did you want to do that because i was different
and i people would say oh do you what dude they'd say spec and a whisper and i'd say
discipline they'd go lol and now we get blocked but i was like i'm fucking cool though i got power
infusion and the one time that we were in pvp and there was a mage and this is this is presence of
mine pyro blast existed power infusion on that mage you could one shot somebody and i was that
guy that let you one shot the guy from across the fucking game fire mages were my best friend
hello frodo have time to enjoy a mug with me hello sherif just saying goodbye off on adventures
it's a made-up story adventures i don't have it played wow you know that's why not all the
great dragons in hiding from the fearsome bagginses don't worry frodo it's just my little
joke everyone knows you're a respectable hobbit i would take a lot to make up to know all those
mechanics of course well goodbye robin where's mary and pippen there they are mary and pippen
hello frodo what took you so long did that sluggard sam gamgee forget to tell you that
we'd be here never mind sam what brings you two scoundrels all the way to bywater breakfast
though oh yeah don't they eat a lot pull up a chair you came all this way just for breakfast
isn't there a line in the movie
why did i say that we thought we'd ever go at his garden again three is company just like old times
remember those mushrooms i remember his ferocious dogs i believe frodo's afraid are you afraid
pippen i'm never afraid mary those dogs are all bark and no bite salt and pork that sounds
only because he caught you well just be careful this time remember the smell of those mushrooms
cooking i do love mushrooms then it's settled who will meet you i go to the farm okay you're gonna
meet me at the farm huh damn it i'm too tall all right i want i need two points it's gonna bounce
off his head and hit him in the head damn it all right fuck it i'm out of here he said more
community subs come in from brineville on top of the fucking 150 thank you rival fill the bar
with rocks no it'll take too long and this game is already dragging out so that's gonna take way
too long dude here comes the hype train no i think i made the cooldown of the hype train
long so it can't happen more than once every like four or five hours i'm actually gonna probably
make it eight hours so it can only happen like once a stream make it once a week i can't even
do that pipe train scam fraud i got in the shower just there i i missed it i have no idea what you
said you said something about taking a shower i don't even know what it was it was something
about taking a shower whatever it was can we please move on i'm trying i'm making every effort
i'm trying to get there still a level one cell bag end to lobelia sackville
how the fuck do i do that what do i mean scroll down there's more no there's not this cell bag end
uh okay like the cell bag end where's that person live just throw rocks at minto
use the map this is a good map yeah use map the land of hobbits west of brandywine river
oh this helps me a great satellite image zoomed way the fuck out this is gonna help
what's with the title of the stream um just link the clip link the clip every time somebody asks
about the title just link the clip aren't we at the farm where are they then they say oh we'll
meet you at the farm well where are they then they say they're gonna meet me here you have to i have
to sell bag end first all right so because nobody's actually linking you the real clip
i'll just tell you in the amount of time that it could have taken somebody just to control c
control v um the right one i'll just i could have just told you uh somebody guaranteed that i would
not get past this first part and i'm proving them wrong that was so easy there was less than a
sentence that's why is that so hard for me to do where's this person uh another huge huge bit
donation just came in from ryanville on top of the community subs ryanville 5 000 bits from ryanville
huge and they say what if the hype train is in bits i think it combines them anyhow i just moved
had your vods on while i put together new furniture and such sitting here doing art
you ever want the greedy grinner to appear in a magic the gathering card let me know yes do it
are you serious oh wait did this the magic all right yeah yeah let's go let's go put put get
all right i don't know what i don't know what it's gonna take get the greedy grinner
into magic the other then i would have to play magic the gathering and show
what you've made and that i mean that's worth it best timeline for greedy grinner all right
where is this person i have to find them in the town that's ryanville again thanks for the 5 000
fucking bits dude ultra rare foil next to the bell thank you and that's one of the reasons why
i love this community helping me out nobody at this bell you fucking liar what's with this
community this community seriously like fucking always like fucking me up and shit getting kind
of sick of it oh there you are hello nobelia where's the sheriff where's that lazy robin small
bro i couldn't say now about bag end never you mind all that sorry i'm sure the sheriff is keeping
everyone safe how could he help ryanville if you're serious go away hit me up in a uh just ring the
warning bell i'm gonna follow you on twitter hit me up in a dm on twitter come running hit me up
on twitter and then i'm gonna follow you and then we'll talk in dms because that's that's
that's funny to me that if it's possible we should we should work on that we should work on that
am i not tall enough to do this anymore i can't just hit my fucking head on this
didn't i already hit this now we can leave now what's going on i don't hold with reckless bell
i rang the bell nobelia wants you to know there are wolves in the shire
oh is that all i've heard that rumor but i reckon no one's seen these wolves not even nobelia oh
if any wolves approach the shire the bounders will chase them off just as they chase away foxes
and such i'm glad the shire is well protected now if that's all i've got a mother return to in the
green dragon
you know how many club remixes of the shire song exist that might be one of the most sampled songs
ever in house music all right show quests sell bag end i can't wait what didn't i just do this
wait where is she i've talked to her again wouldn't she just right here where is she behind me what do
you mean you just ding dong ditched her there she is god damn it man give me a room with four
buttons and i'll fucking destroy it hey how many of you are here how many of you all right how many
of you for under tail and delta rune shit that's box this big on the screen with two buttons
remember jeffel yep well finally came to his senses and rang that bell now we'll have safety
and order in the shire i do hope so now then what did you want to speak to me about make it snappy
i have a lot of things to tend to it's about bag end you said you wanted to buy it what but
i thought you were lying you still bragging about it yeah i believe that's when i have the deed in my
hand did you bring it here's i'm the only person that's done that on twitch i can scarcely believe
it the deed to bag end i should but i can't show my gold medal sometimes i'll leave the bag end key
with master gamgee of number three bag shot row if you don't mind what gamgee that dirty potato
grubber and his son might plunder all of bag end in the dead of night good day lobelia yes yes a
very good day indeed my sweet little lotho will be so happy bag end at last oh why you can sort
with that kind i'll never know frodo having fathers and dwarves and wizards for company
and never inviting your own flesh and blood to tea honestly yeah whatever lady
you look like you're part of a fucking ipad match three gardening game the fuck out of here
we're done get the one remember the first fish i caught here with where we got to get the ring
we're almost done let's give it a leave dude you've walked up and down this road like 10 times
but i i don't i don't i just don't understand how you can continue to not know where you are
i if i know i know i just i don't pay i pay attention to the wrong things adhd and that's
what happens now i know i understand that you have like like attention like deficit issues but
dude like you've done it 10 fucking times just pay attention once i know i know but i like i'm
looking at i'm talking to chat and shit and i'm like talking and i'm i'm walking around he's not
gonna be able to pass the first mission laughing my ass off we're about to beat the first mission
and what was it i was gonna get 200 bits if i did it that's what they said they said germa i
guarantee you won't get to the first pass the first level i will give you 200 bits not even
enough to trigger the end of the stream message reading and i was like fuck dude i'm going let's
go there was a bee next to you i'll horn it don't hurt bees all right it only took an hour and a
half god it took that long no it didn't it didn't take that long i think it's time for me and the
ring to leave hobbiton and begin this journey there we go the one ring take the bag end key to
gaffer take the bag end key to gaffer gamgee at number three bag shot row and take the one ring
to rivendell put it on oh we're gonna get previously on the next episode here we go
what happened shire save game save game save game save game save game save game save game
oh holy shit i okay oh that guarantee just got fucking stuffed into the ground
that if i lost i'll go back to the beginning the very beginning oh man oh man i didn't know that
okay all right that person right now is just sitting there going fuck no why did he see it
oh
no mr baggins has gone away left this morning why is none of my business or yours
there's no secret he's walking to buckleberry or some such place
they don't know this is like weird yes quite a ways down the east road
never been so far why is he acting this is watching like a
this is like a fallout game he's the main character this is like dialogue options
i can't give no message now good night to you evening master gamgee good evening to you fredo
a peculiar ride i came asking after you i don't wish to make his acquaintance nor me sent shivers
up my back just to hear his hollow voice where sam he was waiting for you but that threaded
pippin too came to collect him said they would meet you at maggots farm maggots farm about a
shortcut what are they up to they didn't say but pippin seemed quite pleased with himself
and sam was none too happy about it he'd better not be up to mischief well here's the bag end
key for lobelia i guess i'll meet sam at maggots farm good evening master gamgee he was making it
up in his head the whole time all right let's go avoid being detected by the dark riders you
sneaking to avoid detection press lightly on the left analog stick to sneak wait this is not sneak
i god i guarantee holy shit i can't fucking believe i can't believe it i can't believe i
actually fucking saved the game oh my god that's uh i can't you seriously thank you for the savers
in this chat holy shit who fucking told him who told him wow oh my god oh my god that would have
been so terrible all right no whoa no good evening master gamgee goody i don't know where
they did well i'm telling you that person that person owes me 200 bits
that's unbelievable okay where the fuck am i supposed to go just throw rocks no not back at me
oh great where's he what's that what's that is that a rock i said another rock where these rocks
coming from who's doing that
there's another one over here what the fuck oh my god okay where did a fly fly into your mouth
oh
somebody please take that clip before the stream ends somebody do it i don't know
denominate who does it make a buzz fly buzzing sound and then like a
fly flying into my mouth sound and i have to hear it no oh this sucks evening master i don't even
here's the thing i'm such a stupid idiot i don't even know which way is the right way to go to the
farm it's this way right the way i'm facing guys the map is meaningless god damn it where is he
nobody here i don't even know where he is such such erratic movements too this is not even the
right fucking way use the ring you penis i don't what do you mean use the ring how do i use the
ring is it not on is it on there's a button for it well i've pressed every button the ruling ring
of power forged in the second age by the dark lord sauron in the fires of mount doom select
it's not select start it's not start all right which way do i go all right i have to throw a
rock over here right in the fucking sign l1 and r1 at the same time it's not it is it going look
look over there crazy i know go get it go get it look was i just here was i just here
i i thought it's this way it's this way it's not it's this way all right where is he
right there he's coming up the road fuck he knows i'm over here this is stupid he's not going to
leap where is he okay i thought he already ran by no no no no i heard like the dude dude dude i
thought he ran by already he's not gonna beat it ever yes he is where the hell am i
right no evening master okay this is ridiculous i'm just going will this hide me being over here
i'm not throwing any more rocks he's trying to come over here and he can't because his
path doesn't go this way but i tried fucking god damn it what is it hitting just quit i'm not
quitting no can i save it hold on i can save it wait watch this does it just save your state
evening master it does doesn't it okay avoid detection i'm gonna save it right when i get to
a safe place it controls us so bad so bad for a sneaking game oh yeah yeah don't throw any rocks
he's gonna come over here what do you wait no i fucking had it i was right there i gotta go to
the tree on the left now i gotta go to that tree i gotta get to that tree what if i just do it
immediately right i wonder okay that's the strat right there he's too stupid to run this way
they don't have pathing over here just don't go near a road save it here no don't wait if he
sees me from there oh my god all right does this game does this game have higher than a two on like
metacritic go right and immediate left just follow the path out of town but don't walk on it
it's supposed to sneak but there's nowhere to fucking hide oh and i just it's over i'm just
restarted will the sign protect me you say just sneak the amount of pressure it takes to sneak
is the hardest thing in the whole game you have it's like surgery to sneak it's literal surgery
you have to tilt the analog forward a tenth of a centimeter if you go further than that you're
gonna run don't delete i guarantee i guarantee
he started yeah i know can you imagine if i hadn't saved it imagine getting back here without saving
the game and having to do it over again so it's right and then immediate left is that correct
wait fly video is done is it really yes give it to me this is important i gotta put this on
screen fly flies into jerma's mouth ow okay let's see you can hear it right all right let's get it
on screen that'd be good wouldn't it oh wait hold on jerma hits a grand slam okay hold on
let me go i want to see no i want to see the video again i want to see them why can i hear
myself talking what the fuck is going on stop stop stop i want to see the video again
why can i hear myself talking this is fucked up for as long as what the fuck happened
dude autoplay on youtube sucks what a stupid fucking feature what a dumb ass feature by the
time that you get what you want oh that was a good like 10 second video what how about this one
how about that no no go back you know how about that one it's i go back i just i just and every
time i disable it it's enabled again just give me a clip of the just give me a clip of me watching
that i want to see it no one knows how to turn it off it's because youtube is fucking desperate
to keep people like engaged so these motherfuckers just make you autoplay every single place you go
so it inflates the amount of views on the whole website what if you're not logged in though what
if you're on a different device i've been logged in and it's auto plays turned on give me i give
you the right give me the clip of me watching it i can't my setup i got a fucking i got a shitty
audio setup here's the video all right i'll just watch the video no not the alcs grand slam video
oh my god i even have i haven't copied to my fucking clipboard i'm just gonna watch it i'll
be right back all right that's pretty funny good work hey thank you awakened fear for the five
community subs appreciate it stalling yeah i am because fuck this game i can't some of
i'm gonna get proved someone's there's one person in this chat that's gonna prove it right
and this infuriates me at the moment why won't he walk by where is he doesn't usually come out by
now where the fuck is it what we did you spawn did he spawn in i think the play is um run
let me try this run immediately right behind this tree run stop right here the rock is blocking me
of course it is god i beat this when i was eight i guarantee you didn't i guarantee you did not
beat this when you were eight years old you stopped here and cried and then your mother returned the
game you got you guarantee that guy yeah oh i guarantee it comes up this road i'm gonna use
this rock stop running do you i don't think you understand the amount the amount of movement it
takes to go from sneaking to running is less than a hair on your damn head stupid mechanic what a
dumbass mechanic why have a why have a fps throw mechanic if it there's an invisible wall in front
of me every time he's gonna need a youtube video to beat this one too if you made this game and
you played through this part again like did you like give this to somebody to play and say hey
what do you think about this level is this just is this just like a scenario where like you're
not going to tell your friend that this whole thing sucks hey dude i made this level uh lord
the rings oh the it's like a literally celebrated human franchise uh peter jackson just made a movie
it was like 200 million dollars what do you think about this level oh it's great it's really good
you should print it it's a book series this game came out like less than six months after the
fucking 200 million dollar movie i got an idea i'm gonna i'm gonna get up and throw fucking rocks at
him most one of those celebrated thing human franchises ever and you got a sneaking throw
rock mechanic is it working
go that way that way save it here save the game save the game right here save the game right here
new slot too 8 pm what time is it it's four o'clock in the afternoon what are you talking about
which way do i go this way which way do i go this way right
7 pm boston time don't forget where you came from am i going the right way what if i just stay in the
water oh this is not even a what the fuck are you talking about why is the hippo because it's like
five thousand feet tall
oh
i think right notice joel notice joel joel joel joel joel what's up joel what's up joel lied about
jump king well i don't know what to tell you all right we're good here just keep him don't throw
this it's gonna hit the fucking wall it's not first person mode it's just first person camera
you're actually just sitting in the same spot it's not a first person mode it just moves the
camera in front of your face where's the other one there he is watch this see you later i'm
going i'm going let's go let's go let's go go go go go right now right now go go go go go go go
look over there look over here what's that pay attention to that over there crazy i know look
at those rocks go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go look over there what's that no
no look over there look over there behind you what's that over there i did you see that shit
what's over that way what's over there look
and stop no whammies that's 200 yes why would you even look over here i'm
i'm riveting human gameplay you're riveting your quest is over
wow wow wow wow oh that's just ridiculous isn't it okay look it's the guy on the bridge i know what
i have to do what do you think dude hit that tree over there 600 fucking million dollars goes into
this franchise and i can't even throw a rock past the tree go look oh boy i did it did i make it
to the farm insta safe i did it oh fuck yeah no i didn't do it yet oh wolf i'm done for hold on
robin wait wait hold on he's getting fucking ripped up so he still wants to your purity has
increased you all right what's on discord oh joel wants to do uh keep talking to nobody explodes
we can do it tomorrow yeah we'll do it tomorrow keep talking to nobody explodes with joel tomorrow
no not today not today i no no i have to beat that all right what are you doing in the uh hold
on wait wait what are you all right joel what are you doing in like joel what are you doing in like
i i don't know however long it takes me to get to the end of first level
it's typing typing are you in the zone no no no no no no there is no zone the zone is i
one person told me they guaranteed i couldn't get past the first part
once i get past the first part it literally doesn't matter
oh frodo i am in your debt if you hadn't come along i'd be a midnight morsel for that beast
i'm glad you're all right robin we've not seen walls for a hundred years so i hear it's an ill
what could it mean he's not even here anymore i'd better get going what oh write you off rodo and i
should get back on patrol all right let's go meet him but tell the other sheriffs to watch for more
dangers in the shire yes of course everyone just got like an opportunity they're like wait we can
do it now do it right now oh not right now let's let's set it up actually let's set it up for real
but tomorrow we'll do it tomorrow we'll play for a couple hours he's like ah now man if you're in
all right all right all right we'll do it tomorrow we'll do it tomorrow hey come on that'll be five
days in a row of streams we're doing it tomorrow he didn't even say that yes he did on discord
you're a liar leak the dms you're a liar leak the dms the one ring what do you mean the one ring
well what is what's going on why am i beating up why am i being surrounded by dogs
oh this is what's going on what do you want to bring i don't remember this part of the movie
i didn't save it oh no it's right here it's right here it's right here it's right here it's right
here it's right here it's right here don't forget to save dying reset to do the last save i don't
worry i won't i will never forget that ever again i will never forget it again it'll never i will
never forget it again why do we get so close all right i'm gonna get up here and save the game
and then hopefully i get to play as gandalf because i don't i don't want to play
as furoto anymore and furoto's a swell guy but i don't want to play as him anymore joel must
have told him he'd never get well that's what said the dms he said yo man i just want to let
you know i don't think you're ever going to get past the first part so do you want to just keep
doing this or do you want to play the bomb game he's like i don't think you're going to be able
to do this so that's another person now i have to fucking somebody's give a lot of money
wait i didn't save the game uh ishanji gave 10 000 bits thank you ishanji really appreciate it
they say i was going to ask you if you realize you've been baited into playing a game that's
basically just a short joke but then you you confused candy for fruit and asked if dropping
an ipad into the tub would kill you so yeah germa iq here's to my favorite sentry gun
ps i guarantee you aren't pro gamer enough to build the tower of mammoth tusks they can reach
the sun in the ps1 cave land game tale of the sun whatever thanks for the hundred dollars that's a
lot of money new challenge i'll have to remember that you got baited into the giant short joke
that's fine but thanks a lot for the 10 000 bits this one's for you
you can't do it i can't do it but i'm gonna the lord of the rings and the fellowship of the ring
refund the game this game was just 20 fucking years old all right one ring how do i turn how
do i use the one ring hey remember the final load of the rings roto ran from a pack of wolves
does this happen use the run i can't there i can't use the one ring i don't need that
there's no buttons do anything wait did i put it on just run you have to activate it how do
you activate equip it with circle circle circle you threw the green yeah i didn't throw it on the
ground i gotta go i have to run i have to run to where though am i going the right way
i'm fucking great wait this is right this is wrong this is wrong this is wrong oh i know that
sword that is the goblin cleaver the brightest daylight another dark one must stay hidden
it's not the right movie dude this bullet drop use the bullet drop to my advantage
yeah just give him the ring i can't just give him the ring do you understand how much trouble i'd
get in yeah wait i have an idea i can hide behind this big log all right let's get where is he
oh my god get in the log where is he save in the log no i'm gonna softlock myself if i save in here
he stays like still right here does he know i'm in here okay i swear to god there was a winning the
poo episode where this happened what about rock i'm trying to walk right now but it won't activate
fuck i hit the horse in the head no is he coming i did it where are they i did it fuck yeah there
he is the old sluggered what kept you cousin stopped by the green dragon on your way out
never mind why but i can't stay i have to leave right now for cricollo you mean rivendell
and we're coming with you you thought you were so clever but our conspiracy outsmarted you
we know all about the ring and the dark lord so we're going to protect you but do you have sticks
you know how could we not know with you muttering will i ever see that valley again you really have
bring your best stick mary i was i love food on bilbo one day look at how useful i am also calling
him bilbo put on the ring and vanished we kept our eyes open after that we spied on mary
i'm going to eat double the rations from our truth until he got caught and gandalf did say
take those as you can trust it seems i can't trust anyone you can trust us to stick with you to the
bitter end we've kept your secret better than you did but you can't trust us to let you face
danger alone even though we're horribly afraid he's not c3po or following after like
hounds master frodo yes they are hounds please maggots dogs they're coming are you honestly
trying to tell me that mary and pippin are not the c3po of lord of the rings by the sound of it
so much for stealing some mushrooms before oh yeah do you mind what's all this chatter at this
hour of the night speak up good evening mr maggot well if it isn't peregrine took you're
lucky i know you were out to set my dog's loof the most outlandish fellow rode through here
asking strange questions here who's that with you pippin you remember mary aduk brandy buck
allow me to introduce samwise gamgee and fruto baggins uh good to see you again sir baggins
now isn't that strangest of all what do you think that stranger was asked fuck he came riding up on
a black horse in black cloak and hood and he asked for such a fucking weasel that would be a
different baggins i told him all the bagginses are inhabited he says baggins is heading east on
foot and now frodo baggins shows up on my farm the same frodo baggins who was one of the worst
frame roger rabbits seriously i'm just one of the weasels much better behave i have to embrace it
where are you headed to my new home in cricollo i can see you're in trouble frodo you should never
have gotten mixed up with those strange hobbiton folk i wager that outlander has come for the gold
bilbo brought back from foreign parts well i think it's time we were going no he'll be waiting
you will ride out in my wagon hidden from sight thank you sir it's a pity i've been in
terror of your dogs i've missed a good friend then i kill one of his dogs shall we go now
i already the wagon farmer maggots wagon carried us safely away from his farm and into the borders
of buckland but the black rider was still thundering along the east road we decided
to go south and cut through the old forest mary had been in the old forest and knew a little of
its ways it's a dark mysterious place but not as dangerous as a black rider did it i did it i beat
the first i beat the first level in the lord of the rings fellowship of the ring i don't feel
fulfilled at all zero fulfillment i'm gonna get those 200 bits pippin sam where are you oh wait
what happened brodo we're over here what do you mean did i get cutscenes out of the first level
these trees have a mind of their own stay where you are i'll find you um so i didn't do it
i saved the game holy fuck you're right you did this is level two did i fear of you torturing us
what how would you mean it's torture i want to play as gandalf i just want to play one time as
gandalf seriously just play the two towers i know but i just all right play half-life one resident
sleeper you would resident sleeper halfway point i know you would i would get to the first i would
i would be walking around in the first part of half-life one oh god it's good to see you again
and i would just see resident sleepers the the entire chat would be resident sleepers
this forest it's as if it had a mind of its own ah is that the sun oh man i don't like that that
sucks what the fuck that hurt why did i kill it say the line say the line say the line
you did you just die giant spot enemy where are they over here we're over here this way
i found them watch out for the spider smaller oh this one sucks wait you fight with me
i have a party now hold on i guess i have a party that's pretty sick all right get over here sam
see him? fight! busy! kill him! both bangs in his head. can he die? he's getting fucking destroyed
my god he sucks yes he does all right i can't get off the road giant enemy spider
there is the orchestra remix
okay uh what did i find do i just have to keep walking around in this circle
morty big bits big bits big bits we have five thousand fifty dollars from the mean machine
five thousand bits thank you mean machine for your fucking ridiculous amount of money
oh jesus christ uh for the love that all that is holy germa you finished the first level of the
game i am literally paying you 25 times the wager of that bet for you to go play with joe instead of
dragging this out holy shit it's not about the money it's about sending a message well if you
go to something never do it for free i hate this game i do i do you're right i hate this game
i do i hate it but if you're good at something never do it for free
but you're not good at it oh i found pippin all right now who do we need to find he's only
playing games for money no one's good at this game now who do we need we have sam boy sam
mary now we have sam pit but we are we just have to walk around in a circle so we find a
speedrun is it people speed around this game are there actually speed runs of lord of the
rings and the battleship of the ring yeah see that's the real play you find a game
that has nobody playing and even if you like you can have a really you could have a kind of sloppy
pb and it could be the world records and you just like fuck that well who the hell else is
gonna play lord of the rings besides me all right is he over here lost well i mean this is
called the lost forest or something isn't it that's the whole point okay i have to use the sun i
heard somebody scream over here i'm getting close i'm getting close i'm getting close
i'm getting close i'm getting close
my friend did that with the hello kitty game cube game well good good get a world record
all right what do you think is a game that exists that if you just sort of beat it
slightly quickly you would have the world record for the game should we try to figure that out
what if i found a game that nobody cared about and nobody played that i could actually just get be
the world record holder because i beat it slightly faster than normal because i'm the only one that
cared the lord of the rings no i definitely that's not real all right super frog nancy drew
make a route for now i wouldn't i'd screw it up where is this other character before i lose my mind
do superman 64 i wouldn't know that you kidding me that's like one of the most iconic shitty games
ever somebody already beat that and did that like a thousand times use your map map them do anything
the world record for this game is 58 minutes so slightly longer than i playing slightly shorter
than i will whatever dead spiders means you've been there i know i'm trying to find a alive spider
oh two mushrooms this is it could be an indicator that i haven't been here
harry harry there are no nancy drew speedruns i never thought potatoes could smell so good
a good meal will definitely ease my mind about this place but where is this place very close
to the witty window valley but we shouldn't get any closer why not the witty window
holy shit that's so accurate yes is online 5 000 bits oh my god this music is just bootleg
firelink shrine omega lult please stop this madness you already missed the pimp and skip
it's like they're leading us there mary thought he knew his way around this forest
but how can anyone find their way when the forest won't stand still do you know one of those trees
stuck a branch out at me nearly tripped me it did i'm sorry i let us into such a dangerous place
it all is seriously that black rider dude missed pimp and skip what does it say wait wait wait wait
wait wait wait what does it say this is important this says i literally just watched you beat up
several spiders with a stick for the past 30 minutes i'm going to haunt you until you sell
your 30 minutes of life force to me did you get it that was well that's 28 but it's all right
you can the other extra two minutes were on you know on you for clicking on the stream in the
first place i broke the audio oh there we go where are we going i wasn't paying any attention
to the last cutscene i i didn't see one single line can't go on no don't go into the puppies
less flies well that's a real giant enemy spider oh no it's not it's a tree i thought it was a huge
spider i don't like this tree i don't trust it hear it singing about sleep that's not right
it's not right at all giant enemy tree
the sequels never is good the sequels never is good the sequels never is good
is he dead never any people are trapped in old man willow's mouth attacking his trunk may anger
him oh my god i have to save it no he's about to hit me
mary all right not fair not fair that was unfair okay stop playing this game please
i we're at the first boss we're at the first boss i gotta continue bed of chaos
us
why am i who's walking all right go in
he squeezed him what am i just supposed to run around a circle do i have to get him stuck
it's true they're watching your stream because they whatever all right i don't what am i supposed
to do one ring all right these dudes you've got dudes got a magic ring on and i can't walk by this
i had the ring on for too long all right so i'm gonna say throw and then climb up or jump or
then just get double tapped what about sam over there well go wake up sam
who's lying on the ground over here someone's lying on the ground right here
what if i just don't move
uh did i get grabbed
hit him in the hand
man did you see how big that hitbox is okay what the fuck am i supposed to do
he'll squeeze me in too if you don't stop i can't go anywhere
run around him like what do you mean oh there there's all right i hit his hand
he's got me every time man
i wasn't even close that's not even hitting me
i can't even hurt him use gold pine resin i why can't i hurt him should i just put the ring on
and attack him or something
i'm invisible you can't see me all right so you can't see me so grab him
can i get up here take it off take it off take it off um the most celebrated franchise in all
of human history keep hitting the hand i hit the hand like 20 times and not one point of damage
i can't even imagine can you ever even imagine like playing this i would be if i would cry if i
was if i was a kid don't walk on the holes all right i'm gonna i'm gonna do i need to zoom in
and show you this you guys you gotta check your glasses on this one all right don't step on the
hole sure i won't do that oh that's interesting you want me to zoom in should i zoom into that
let's zoom in let's take a look i just have to get lucky and get flown over here
this is the equivalent of dying to pin bill do you need me to zoom in i'll zoom in stay in the
grass and not the dirt i can't go anywhere i'm fucked i think i have duck it see you see what
i have to do i have to trigger that cut scene so i appear in front of him hit the hand do you need
to zoom in do you need me to zoom in let me zoom in on the hand hit the hand look at the hp bar
you need to zoom in for you hp bar look want to zoom in did i get hit i haven't moved
i missed his hand i don't know in the armpit fuck
i was trying to time it so it was instant frame perfect
so
this is why didn't everybody tell me this was so loud why didn't anybody tell me this was this
loud why didn't you tell me it was that loud nobody told me it was that loud this has been
this is extreme loud that was ridiculous that was horrendous this is not working this is not
how you do it this isn't how you do it oh no there's no way this is this is absolutely not
a chance in hell this is the way you do it no it's not no it's not i can't do this anymore
hit the tree while you're invisible thanks appreciate throw a rock at him in order to
get past his roots without getting hurt then avoid his hands which slam in the ground and
hit his hands with your stick as soon as they touch the ground keep doing this while running
back and forth from side to side while getting knocked to the ground after doing this for a time
tom bobaldi appears and puts old man willow to rest that didn't even come fucking close
this game is so bad this game is so bad this game is very bad this game is very bad
oh no somebody fell off down into the lego well get the helicopter to save lego city
wait hold on where is it we need to get the this is lego city helicopter 22441
we need to land a helicopter down and pick up the guy i got funny fucking voices now
i know like a lot of people cried when they watched lord of the rings and when they when
they read lord of the rings imagine crying to the lord of the rings fellowship of the ring the
video game not because the story is touching you because the tree boss is the worst boss you've
ever played in a video game and it makes you sad childhood ruining okay i have to stop i have no i
don't not yet i broke an arm hold on does it work i threw i didn't even mean to oh my goodness
it's okay i'm gonna sneeze nothing i can do about it hurt my back
i got the strategy here's the winning strategy you ready back up back up that was the winning
strategy be fucking damn it come on closer closer closer wait just don't move no i gotta be a first
person so i trigger it first person come on oh he's baiting me didn't even get hit by anything
didn't even get hit by anything this game i can't believe it i can't believe it
oh my god did anyone beat this when they were younger i don't know if i would be able to if
you're like 12 i don't think you even know how to what to do i think you just get killed like
five times and i don't think anybody does i'll send you money equals my student loan debt if
you stop playing this game hey you student loans don't pay me where did you come from
what's the matter then come now tell me what's your trouble my friends are caught in that willow
tree they're being crushed willow i know they'll chat his marrow cold if he don't behave himself
you let them out again old man willow you should not be waking eat earth drink water
go to sleep bombadil is talking tom bobaldi yes thank you very much well my little fellows
you shall come to the house of tom bombadil where tie questions around the supper table come now
and help tom find lilies for fair lady goldberry after that we shall sit down to a table laden with
cream honeycomb and white bread and butter the sooner we find lilies the sooner we can eat
look at that stride find 12 lilies
okay we're i love this comment okay we're now we're done now please okay we're done
what excuse me excuse me okay they're gonna is he people tom tom turn around
tom tom there's a spider behind you tom look behind you quick oh no he has ear pods in he
can't hear us okay where did these all come from what the fuck i have to find 12 lilies oh boy oh
boy i don't know if we'll be doing this one how many others is one here no jesus jesus christ
why is the entire hive coming after us what okay i feel like i'm playing like dragon age
this is just dog shit dragon age with no pause we did it nice job guys you did a great job
quick turn it off turn it off turn it off turn it off um i'll read a bedtime story if you stop
how am i gonna hear it this shouldn't be too hard joe got rejected for this
no we just got we're gonna do it on another day what is that good thing i'm wearing a diaper
i don't know whose clip is this i don't get it well how many do i need come on i need my dragon
age friends or actually you know how this is more accurate you're playing an mmo you're really
desperately trying to play an mmo with three of your friends who just made new characters
and they don't know a goddamn thing about the fucking game and they're just watching you
destroy everything and they are just following you around yeah it's over here did you guys how
many you guys have i have two oh i have all of them already oh i'm not gonna say that though how
many do you have three what about you four okay cool i have all 12 um i think i saw some more
over here yeah i i have six i i'm still i have so hard to find them you know over here come
over this way i think this i'm over here and you got that one friend that just keeps casting the
same buff and they're the healer it's like you've been buffed you had 58 minutes remaining from 60
minutes like oh that's not the heal you're doing the wrong button but i'm not gonna say anything
you get the one friend that dies in every fight every single fight and thank god that you decided
that you were going to play a character with a rez because if you didn't you would not be playing
with these friends without a doubt in your mind if you don't play a character that can take care
of everybody you ain't playing your auto voice and your stupid voice are the same you implying
that auto is stupid no i'm implying that auto is a dog the worst part about playing uh mmos
especially with people that don't really care is a lot of people just don't get it and a lot of
your friends will treat an mmo like they're playing a game of madden all right let's go
let's say let's go on a quest 30 minutes goes by all right that's kind of fun i gotta go though
okay yeah um that's not you can't really play for 30 minute you we just did one quest and
i'm gonna like over level the fuck out of you if you log off right now
what's the i just gotta sell my stuff and then leave fuck when he logs back on i'm gonna be
like 20 fucking levels higher than him so what you do is you make another character you make an alt
for your alt so you can continue to play and then pretend like you didn't play and log on the other
character that your friend was playing with and then eventually that second character you made
becomes your main character and your friend never plays again past level 12 and you knew that was
gonna happen you knew it but you tried anyway animation is so brutal all right how many more
do i need i don't even know how many i have i've okay nine ten eleven twelve three more
two come on damn it did i miss some you had to count to 12 we want bugleberry we want bugleberry
we want bugleberry one person wants bugleberry and they really really want it no one wants that
really that don't matter you're gonna like bugleberries gonna return i'm gonna put
him in as many fucking things as i can all right come on let's go where are you guys get over here
where are they they're gonna get up they're not even gonna get uh they're not gonna be in
range for the kills they're turning their quests in all right here they are three more come on
please dude why'd you go back to town he only finished quest one out of five yeah you can't
you go to this person you go to this person's house this is the best part so you eventually
go to this friend's house and they are on hey i'm playing wow cool i'm playing final fantasy
whatever i'm playing um whatever game and you open up their log their quest log and they have
like 20 or like 18 gray ass quests that they never got rid of and you're sitting there going
oh man he just has no idea they could be level 40 and they have a full log book of shit from
the level 10 zone and you go in there and you delete them you delete them for them don't think
they don't need to know just delete delete stop tracking stop tracking stop tracking
start delete delete delete delete well i found you there is for the fair river let's go to meter
okay i did it they were doing them for the lord no they definitely were not how long is this game
come dear folk laugh and be merry the river here's my gold berry you are still afraid perhaps
hold on this game is only five hours long are you serious it's the only answer for who are
your name but you were young and i'm not gonna beat it i'm just saying that's i thought it was
gonna be longer than that tom remembers the first raindrop to big people he was here before
speaking of world of war crap that is before the elf that is a default and before the seas were
mage like level two green lord that she's wearing actually is i'm sorry i'm on that now it is time
for our stop making wild ref we ate our first good meal in a long time singing songs and telling
tales until late in the night we slept peacefully and were refreshed enough to
continue our journey keep to the green glass it's my brain don't go meddling with all stone
or prying into the houses of all dead barrowites is this kind of hobbit or dwarf or
thank you tom bombadil speed now fair guests
south wind in the left eye and a blessing on your footsteps make haste while the sun shines
farewell friends it was a merry meeting okay can we please play as aragon
take the ring to rivendell okay let's go hi guys rivendell is this the road to rivendell
i don't know save it holy shit you're right i haven't saved it a long ass time
you are absolutely a thousand percent correct you should shred this game no i can't do that i can't
do that don't tell him to save it makes him more invested whoever keeps telling him to save there
is a special place in hell for you god jesus big dog big dog here we go all right the next area
i'm done i promise i beat the first area i get to win i swear to god i promise this next area i'm
done with lord of the rings fellowship of the ring but aragon is next i don't think that's i'm
gonna die you have to beat this no nobody really actually wants me to do that i know it for a fact
i know it for a fact this is a chill game you know somebody just said this it is strangely
intriguing and it is like oddly calming to be playing this and just hanging out
play a good lord of the rings game i have all of them i have two towers i have return of the king
have them both go to get just play two towers now but we don't know the story
i'm as cautious about this place what about the hobbit game no far from the main road by my
reckoning splendid if we keep this pace we'll leave the barrow downs by sunset tomorrow not
soon enough for my liking i don't trust what's hiding in the fog on the barrel downs you don't
believe stories about all dead barrel whites not until today but tom said otherwise tom is the only
was there ever a tv show for lord of the rings he was here i'm surprised the answer is no
from outside outside what i wonder and whatever did he mean by eldest and why didn't he serve a
cartoon i could see a cartoon sausages i don't like spending the night among these burial stones
they look like giant teeth coming up from the ground if half the stories i've heard about
the barrel downs are true we'll need to keep a careful watch enough storytelling let's get to
sleep sam mary pippen no i don't i don't want to go fetch i don't want to go fetch where could they
be we already did this mary anyone you've already done this i've already done this where are you
all right that's it that's it that's it i'm gonna put the game that's it i'm putting the game you
said you were done and then when you got to a new area i know i'm putting the game i'm done i'm done
i'm done i'm done i'm done i'm done i'm done i'm done i'm done i'm done i did it i did it i'm done
i did i'm done i did it i'm already done i'm not even playing right now this is one of those
games where if you don't you stop playing for too long mario just like starts doing weird
animations and shit i'm not doing this um i don't have no idea where i'm going double or nothing
that's no that's not how this works no no no i'm done i'm done i'm done i'm done i'm done
that's it i'm done i'm done i just left him fuck him bye still alive i did what i came to do
what's next just in case i ever decide to come back i might i might decide to come back one day
he did not beat it that's the that was the first part the first part was after the ring uh ring
rates all right that was cool all right what do i want to do for the time being let's quit
let's get this out of here all right give me one i'm gonna you know it's been a few hours let me
go pee i'll be right back we'll figure out what we're gonna do be right back