It's popped over, I see. Roy Mustang, S tier, or Riot.
Do you think you're on the VOD?
Oh shit, I thought I was watching the VOD. He went live right when that happened.
So the chat turned into the live chat.
A new tier list. Binding of Isaac bosses. Binding of Isaac items.
No, no more tier lists. Sounds like a pretty good list though. It doesn't already exist.
That would take so long. Yeah, there wasn't like a thousand items in Binding of Isaac.
But speaking of Binding of Isaac, what a perfect transition to talk about what we're doing today.
We are going to, I was going to do this yesterday, but we spent a little more time in
Katamari than I would have imagined. And then we did tier lists. So this got bumped over to today.
We are going to play the Legend of Bumbo, which is the Binding of Isaac prequel,
but it's a different game. These are different games. If you think you're going to get that
classic Binding of Isaac gameplay, it's a little different. This is a cardboard
attack and defend match for video game. It's Edmund McMillan. Same guy. I trust it'll be a
fun experience. And everything's made out of cardboard. So this stream, I don't know how
long the stream is going to be. It might be a few hours. It might be seven, eight. Like, I don't
know. I might get really into this. I might think this is a lot of fun. I don't know. Incoming 30
minutes. I think it probably takes like 30 minutes to get through the tutorial. So I doubt that. But
something else to talk about very quickly before we move on with this. I just preliminarily started
to really start to put the resources in and truly develop the fuck the King streams.
They're going to be way more elaborate than I think anybody thinks. We're talking multiple
camera angles. We're talking about multiple observer views. The King streams are now actively
being started now. No spoilers. You're going to have to know how this works though, as we get closer
because there's, you guys need to participate in this stream. I can't just be like two days
before the stream starts and go, oh, hey, by the way, here's the server info.
No, this is going to be all kinds of systems that need to be talked about beforehand.
This will probably be happening a couple weeks after the new green screen stream,
which the new green screen stream, by the way, will probably end up being on date to be determined
the first week of December. I have to lock that down. I have to get the date locked down
with the green screen. So that means that there's, I was, I'm kind of waiting.
I was waiting a little bit for when I could know I could get in there on a given day to the studio
before I actually had the discussion board up. So it'll be probably a week or two after the green
screen stream. So probably mid December. And it's going to be potentially a weekly thing that we do,
maybe even more than once a week. Depends on how fun it is. There you go. There's your timeline.
So we're going to move to Bumbo. I have not, I've opened the game once to make sure that I can
capture it. What's he talking about? I will give way more details when, when stuff actually starts
to glue together. But December is going to have some fun streams in it. Let's just say that
anyways. Time for Bumbo. Let's watch the opening cinematic. Hopefully it's not too loud. It's
actually very soft.
I loved it. Bumbo take trash downstairs. Dermal want bits. All right. So this is how
teaching this tutorial. Hit me with some bones kid. I'll give you one move point. Use it to line up
four bones, then throw that bone my way. I think we know what we didn't know. Four bones. Throw it
where? So throw it right down the middle. Cool. Thanks. I needed that, but I need more. I'll give
you two more points this time, but I want you to line up five teeth and throw them straight into
my kisser. Bumbo make that. Throw teeth down. Okay. Wow. That packed punch teeth and bones
both hurt bad when thrown and the more tiles you match up, the more impact they make.
Experiment with tile combos. So if I get two lines, it's like teeth and bone.
Do I get to throw two? Oh, you're going to go twice. Okay. He's dead. Hey again. Now it's time
for me to hit you. Okay. I'm going to hit you. Whatever you do, don't match four booger tiles
and gum me up. Stun? You gummed up the works there, didn't you? Boogers only stop one action
by an enemy. So be careful. Here I come again. Uh oh. So wait. Oh no. Wait, wait, wait, wait.
How do I cancel that? So here he comes again. So I can't do anything. I guess I could go like this.
This is another turn. No, okay. I can do it. Throw poop at him. Oof. I just punched a darn poop. How
do you know how to do that? Oh yeah. Poops can shield you from one single enemy attack, but you
know that already. Okay. Now just finish me off and I'll give you a little treat. So I get two moves.
So should I pee on him? Plus one move. I get it. All right. Uh oh. Now just finish me off.
Do they have to be in a row? Or can I just like drag? It's going to be like, okay, it'd be like a
row. Uh oh. I did this wrong. Diagonal don't work. Okay. I'll take the money. Yep. Me again. Wow. I
really gave you a run for your money there, didn't I? You should probably heal a bit. Let me just do
heal. Okay. This is my health. All right. Hearts are a lot less common than other tiles, so don't
get used to healing so easily. This reminds me of 10 million, but potentially much more interesting
for one reason, because apparently there are like hundreds of items in the game.
Okay. It's time to get crazy now. See, each tile you match actually gives you specific colored
mana that you can use to cast spells. Crazy, huh? Here, take this. Okay. So I have bumbo smash.
Take- that spell takes bone mana to use, so just match some bones and when it lights up,
click on it and knock my face off. Spell's ready. Okay. So this is called bumbo smash.
Oh, I just knocked his body off. Okay. I think you are ready for a real battle, dude. Before you go,
let me give you a few tips. You can visit the casino. Best game ever! Best game ever! Best game
ever! After each boss, they'll save those coins. Bosses usually have more than one action a turn,
so be careful. All right. I think I'm- I think I get the basics down. Bumbo want coin, the legend
of bumbo. New game. Choose your bumbo. Bumbo the brave. Bumbo the nimble. Bumbo the stout. Bumbo
the weird. Bumbo the dead. Bumbo the empty. Beat the game twice with all characters. What are these
ones? Beat chapter one with Bumbo the brave. Beat chapter two with Bumbo the nimble. Okay.
So this is the lower his health, the harder he hits. This is just standard like Isaac. So
Bumbo smashes four bones and then Bumbo shake his two teeth. Rerolls the puzzle board.
Sewers of Dros? Bumbo the furry. Hey Jeremy, you got a nice looking bum. Thanks. All right,
here we go. Oh, shit. This is a lot. All right. Boogers. Uh oh. All right. Let's start off with,
huh. What do I want to do here first? I'm just going to do boogers. No, I got- is it four? Okay,
I get another move. What do I want to go, right down the middle? I'm going to go right down the
middle. End your turn. Spell is ready. Bumbo smash right in the middle. Oh, they move. Okay. So now
my turn again. Maybe boogers. P? Boogers? I'm going to booger. Booger on, uh, booger on middle.
And then teeth on right. Oh, shit. He broke out. Right here. You're about to attack.
Reroll the puzzle board. I don't think I need to do that. Uh, let's see. No one's about to attack
and I have one move left. So let me go. Should I do P? Can I get P without? Let me see. Uh oh.
Wait. Fuck. I'm going to take damage, I think. Not quite. They're about to. What does P do?
Oh, P gives me more turns. Right. Okay. Got it. Got it. All right. Uh, I'm going to booger
right here. One turn left. Can I kill it? No. Is there poop available? There is. Right here.
All right. I'm ready. Good. Okay. This is fun. Okay. This is a fun one. I'm going teeth. Teeth
on the left. No. Yeah. Teeth on the left. And then in turn, it's going to queue up.
All right. I got two turns to kill this thing. I got it right here.
Free coins. Uh, what is this? This is a item. Snot rocket is a booger, a booger lane,
a navy beam. Destroy a column of tiles. This is four, four, two. That seems like a lot.
All right. I got the booger lane. I need to get four, then four, and then two P's. All right.
Let me see what I want to do here. Snot rocket. Yeah. All right. I'm going to go.
I can do just bone immediately. Does that set me up for anything after that? Fuck it. Whatever.
This is wicked. And then no, not Bumbo smash. I could do teeth right down the middle. Bumbo
smash right down the middle. All right. Middle lane gone. This board's good. I'll keep it.
Oh shit. They've ranged. Those guys are ranged. Uh oh. Wait, hold on. That's three and then I
could do poo, but do this. Fuck. He's going to attack. Does this take up the whole lane?
I'm going to, I'm curious. Let me see if this works. Like if he attacks, will it hit that?
Yep. Oh, cool. All right. Cool. Very cool. I got it. Well, now I'm in trouble again.
I don't have enough. Do I have a P scenario? I could do five booger. I could booger this whole
lane. I'm going to booger this lane. And then I'm going to do a super booger on the,
like right over here. This is five boogers. I can do it twice. Let's go. Okay.
Now I got to start killing shit. I could do, I've got bones here. I could do bone.
Dammit. All right. Wait, hear me out on this one. Hear me out on this. This is stupid,
but I'm going to do it. That's six bones. How many throws is that?
Two, three. Oh shit. That's actually a really good idea. Now I can just bumbo smash him.
Yeah. Still. Do I like this board? What do you guys think? Seven is a super combo.
Nana drain. What the hell was that? I got teeth and I got bone here. I wish I could split this
up, but I'll do teeth and then I'll do bone. No bone and then teeth. How much damage does the
bone do? It's only one damage, right? Yeah. Kill it. Let's go. New item coming up.
All right. Flying insects. What do they do? I'm assuming they just keep going forward.
What does this mean up here? Does this just nothing or does what does this mean?
It's what falls down after. Okay. This comes next like Tetris style. I get it.
All right. We're going to booger. Booger. I wait. Can I do P too? Booger. All right. Hold on. Watch
this. Kind of. That was pointless. I thought I was going to give more turns to like then do this.
It's all right. I'm sorry. You're going to make a mistake once or many times. How do I salvage
this? I just fucked a seven bone. God damn it. Whatever. I'm just going to line up these bones
here. No one's doing anything yet. Let's go right down the middle. Wait. Let me make sure.
Okay. You go up top first. Bone smash. I wonder if now save it. Don't use it.
Do I have anything else to do? No boogers are in the wrong spot.
I wonder if these guys, they attack or is it just that they get close enough to hurt you?
Six boogers is an AOE. I don't want to reroll this yet. Uh oh. Okay. Now
I need to make some poos. One, two. What if I set up like a whole row? You need
seven for AOE. Damn it. I could do one. I could do this and then poo. Let's see if this helps me
at all. I'm not sure where to go with it though. Kind of playing defense. And then how about right
here? And then I'm going to kill this with bubble smash. Okay. I can booger the lane next. All right.
You're about to go. I'm going to keep that there. So cool. All right. So they don't attack. They just,
you don't, you do not take damage unless this pops up, right? This is like that you're about
to take damage. It's not just, they just walk forward and hit you, right? Oh, we got a bone here.
Wait, let's see. I could do bone and then smash. Yeah, let's just bone it.
And then smash right down the middle. Oh shit. It's, it's in the air. Uh oh. All right. I'll
booger this whole lane. Whoa. What just happened? What? Why did that do damage?
Oh hell, they had, oh it was poo shields. Oh fuck. Oh no. Okay. I get it. So they,
that was poo shields for the, I get it. Damn it. That's cool. Well, I got an opportunity here at
this. I might reroll this. No, I don't have to. Teeth and then just, I'm going to wait it out.
Yeah. You're going to run into that and I'll be fine. Heal. Did I just poop that? I could do an
extra. Oh, cool. All right. Uh, here, we'll take that. Wait, I can do a super poo. Hold on
everybody. I could do this. I could go, I could do, what does five poos do? No, no, no. What is
six poos? Holy shit. Could I get a huge one? I could do six poos. I'll just do five. Just
going to see what happens. The stars. Oh, it's wild. That's cool. Wild. Ooh. Well, I can,
what is, I can do a big heal. Spell ready. No. Oh, all right. Let's just go. I'm going to do five
bones. No, I'm not. I even do four right now. This looks pretty neat to be honest. It is. It
actually is pretty cool. That's what I like to see. And I can bumble a smash. Does this
save between floors? I can hold. Is this? No, they didn't. No. Okay. Okay. Eight coins. Ooh.
Plus one movement or trap door. Skip to next chapter. I don't want to skip. This is the first
time. This is my first game. Let's take the juice. Bumbo versus peeper. His eyes are slippery.
15 health. Oh fuck. Okay. So I can do, I'd probably have to freeze them. We'll slow them.
I wonder if I should just try to damage. Cause I could do one bone. I could do bone and then
movement. Check this. Wait, do they have health? Should I attack him? I'm going for him. Now check
this out. One movement. Bingo. Sticky on you. I guess. Oh, can I stick? I could have stick that,
but they would have been blocked anyways. All right. Thank you. This is not good. I could do
teeth, but can I even hit you? This is just resisted, but these don't take any damage.
Okay. So the plays you got to stick these sticky sticky and then hit them or move them by swinging
out. Okay. He doesn't move though. Well, let's see what happens. Oh, this is not good. I need poo
right now. Right? Oh, I need two poos. I'm going to get hit. Can I get an extra turn out of this?
Yes. Yes. That was poo and a extra move. All right. Oh, look at all these moves. Okay. This is
important. I don't want to fuck this up, but I'm going to. I could do booger over here. I could do
super poo, but that's not going to help me. Does it stack? Oh, shit. Will this poo stack? See,
that's just one. Let's try it. Oh, yes, it does. It does stack. Nice. All right. Then, oh, look at
that. Look at that. I could do five bones. Boy, I could do more than that. I could do six bones.
Wait, don't do that. Cause that's four. I, but I can't hit them. No, I'm not going to do it. Can
I just end the turn? I could do an extra turn, but will that help me? Big bones? I don't, I,
maybe I should move the bone down. Wait, wait, wait. How many turns do I have? No, I can't hit
them. Okay. What if I do this? Put this here or should I move? Fuck. I'm going to put this here
and then go for seven. I don't, I don't think I'm too slow for that. Do seven teeth. One, two, three,
four, five, six. I could go. All right. If this is wrong, it's wrong. If it's wrong, I'm stupid
and I messed it up, but you got to mess up at least once. Ready? One, two, three, four, five, six.
This is going to be, oh, I fucked it up. I was going to try to go for six bones. I fucked it up
because the whole thing. No, no, wait a minute. No, I didn't. I can still do it. I can get it.
One, two, three, four, five. I'll have six. Okay. I'll have six bones. Maybe more. Seven.
I got to move this out of the way though. All right. Here's the game plan. You ready?
Throw teeth, move that out of the way. Uh, fuck. This whole thing is messed up. Um,
I'm going to connect four anyways. Well, I'm uh, damn it. I'm set. So I can't do seven teeth
because if I go up from here, I'm going to connect. Hold on because that's four.
This is four. Can I go over? Can I do this? Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay. Hold on. Yes. I'm doing teeth. No, I'm doing bones. Seven. So if I go this way.
All right. All right. All right. So you saying bang right here, then bring it up to make three,
then bring the wild down to make seven. I mean, no teeth, not bones. We're talking about that.
Isn't that, that's not correct. That's going to take too long. Slide the third from the top to
the left third row left. I think you mean like right here and then just go up and then down.
But then I'm going to connect. You mean like this? I see what you're saying. You guys are
fucking pretty good. Well, my way would have done it too. Yeah. My way would have done it.
Perfect. Our way is better. All right. Here we go. One, two, three, four, five, six, 17.
All right. It does four damage to everything. Okay. That's cool. I guess I could go. Let me see.
I could just booger the lane. Try to get the extra turn and get a little move and I'm going to go
here. Give me a, uh, I probably shouldn't have even done that. But I don't know why I did that.
I saw one guy. All right. So we got one. Can I do a seven bone? One, two, three,
hold on. One, two, three, four. Okay. Down. All right. Here we go. You're ready? I'm going to set
up the seven bone scenario. That'd be one, two, three, four, five, six. Okay. I'm setting up the
seven bone. Let me make sure it is right. Then two, wait, and then, okay, let's do it.
Should I do this now? Because they're walking away. What does it do? Oh, I just fucking destroyed.
Holy shit. That's the best thing in the whole game. How much damage does that do?
Weird box in back of room. What in there? Bumble stink. Spider with long bite, big long bone,
bees with magic powers. It a mystery with no thinking. Bumble bash open scary box.
Another bumble. What a twist. Bumble the nimble has been unlocked. Just came.
Forlorn Hollow has unlocked. That's been bumble, guys. So we unlock the next area after that.
Okay. Let's do it again. New game. Let's see. What's the new bumble do? His puzzle attacks
gain mana. Remove a single tile. Damage goes up with each hit. What that bumble do?
Each cast of the spell in a single room. All right. So they have their own poo shields.
I'm going right up the middle. Set up the fucking bones. I'm just going to, whatever.
I could do this. I could gum up the middle and then could set up a five bone scenario,
a six bone scenario. Yeah, that's what we're doing. Fucked it up. This is what we'd like to call
fucking wasting time. Oh, let's go. What? But they have different moves. Oh, it's five. Five
damage. I thought it was like the big tooth that comes down. All right. So it's, if it's, it has
to be seven, not more than like five. Okay. Seven is the big one. I get it. Oh, you know when you
just like, when a run gets fucked up, you know what I mean? Uh, well, I, I think I die. We'll
find out. See if I can live. He soft locked it. I could do a bunch of pee. How many would that
give me? One, two, three, four, five. I can't do the six. Can I? I have to get all of this pee.
That'll give me, I only have two moves. I'm going to get hit. I'm dead. I can drink six in two.
Can I? This has to go forward and down. That's five. Forward, down. That's, I guess I could do
this. Yeah. Okay. What does it do? Not, not that good. Just what? Two more moves.
Right. Oh, actually that did help a lot. Wait a minute. I get three, one, one, two, three.
See you later. No. Wait. I'm dead. All right. No more joking around. It's time for the real one.
Uh, let's do, I had more. What? I could have done it again. Yeah. Only one more time. It's
only one damage. What? Really? All right. Let's get serious. What do I even want to do here?
A lot of flying enemies. It goes up one damage every time. So what can I start to set up here?
I can set up bones. If I bring this over here, that goes one, two, three. Oh, check this. Yeah.
Let's do it. Let's do a seven bone setup. I'm going to, I'm going to take damage here though.
It's worth it. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. I'm going to take,
it's not worth it, but I'm going to do it. It's not worth it. Like I don't even know why I keep
doing it. I'm dead again. It's not worth it. The ultimate greed. Yeah. I'm dead.
Cause no, I can't survive this. Could have had the seven. Oh, whatever. Yeah. Restart, restart,
restart, restart. New game. I'm not just going to set up seven and eight scenarios this whole time.
Quitter. No, it's not about getting like rows of seven. It's about trying to
control these little mutants. All right. Rocks. I don't know what they do. That's a bomb. I don't
know what that does. Let's start with this. Oh, let's just go poop to do P. Get set up a five P.
Yeah. I'll do a five P set up here. That's six P set up. Sorry. No, it's not. Stop,
stop doing six and seven P setups. No, it's not worth it. Just do the five.
Oh, I can get seven. No, stop going for seven. I don't have to go for seven every time. What's
wrong with me? I'm just doing five. Okay. Here we go. You gotta, you gotta go for it. I can't just
like set up five and six. All right. But I can do this. How many teats have I got? See? Yeah. I
don't have so I could get a row of 10. You're dead by the time you get there. Enemies move slower.
Stopwatch. Buzz down. Move a tile column one down. That one seems cool. So that's four bones.
All right. We got two. The bomb in the back. Poopsie here. Set up a, I could set up a fucking
six teeth scenario. Oh, what's that? We get a six teeth scenario. Wait. Uh, this is going to do
five damage, right? I gotta remember how that works. This is five damage. Okay. Five. Yeah,
right. Don't do that ever again. Uh, take a hit. Oh, sorry. The bomb is getting close though.
Use the toothpick. I can't. I need, I need a bunch of pee for that. Remove a single tile. I could do
this. Gives me a little more time. And then I could toothpick the, I've got three moves.
This might be a set up a bone scenario. If I go down, no, it's not worth it. Just get,
I have to kill something. I'm not doing seven bones. Use the needle. It's only going to do one
damage. I'm going to save it. Three moves. I go down and then left and then I have to hit something.
Do seven bones or riot. No, I'm not doing seven fucking bones. I can't. It's going to take me too
much time. I could do like this, which is, that's not even correct. I don't even know. I don't even
see what you're saying. Need poo to protect against the bomb fly. Wait, is he going to explode?
Pop the stuff under the bones. You mean like here? I mean, pop under the bone. You mean like pop.
All right. But how many, I have one. I only have, I can only do this once.
I'm talking about pop like here. Drag this down. I can't believe I'm doing like a seven setup.
You guys are going to get me killed. I need to get a tooth here first. Don't I?
No, seven bones. Oh my God. I can get seven bones this turn. You want to pop this one, this pop.
Yes, no, yes, no. All right. I'm just going to, I'm popping it.
I have three moves. So then I go over here, which is one, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Bring this one down. Yeah, this is it. Seven bones. Only seven bones.
Oh, what did I take damage for? How was the bomb fly? Okay. This is an easier one, I think.
Just kill it. And I have, oh, enemies move slower. Should I just do that? What does it do?
I've never, what does it do? Next wave of baddies move less. All right, cool.
Seven teeth, seven teeth, seven teeth, seven teeth, seven teeth, seven teeth.
I don't care about optimal reverse, like calculate every seven move. I just want to, I'm playing it.
Every move must have at least five to seven tiles removed each turn or inefficient, ineffective.
So I'm going to do, I have one move. Can I do anything with this one move? I set up seven teeth.
Or I set up fucking five teeth. Who cares? I'm thinking. I'm thinking. Speak. I'm thinking.
I'm trying to think. I'm thinking, I'm thinking if I drop, I don't know, I can move just over.
Just hold on. I got it. I've got it figured out. I'm going to drag this over and I'm going to drop
and I'm going to get a fucking five poops. Check it out. And you're going to be very proud of me.
Told you you're going to be proud of me. All right. Now we're going to go with this because I feel like
that was a huge mistake, but it's okay. Wait, maybe not. Maybe not. Maybe not. I think I
can do it still. Yeah. Hold on. No, that's not a bone up there. What about a tooth? I need a
tooth drop right here. Okay. Wait, everybody watch this shit. This is what we call problem solving.
Butterbean, knock back all enemies plus one coin. Knock back all enemies.
Nice. Bumble versus the Duke. Keep him small. Spell ready. Did I only use this once? I can use
this one time. All right. Give me chat. Give me a seven bone scenario. Let's do it. Let's set it up.
There's one, two, three, four, one, two, three, four, five. Move the one top to the right down.
No, fuck. I'm just. Stay still and make him move slower and give me some more moves.
Not yet. Seven P. Yep. This is not going to activate it, right? Seven P. So this is going to be one,
two. Is this even going to work? If I move. Okay. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
You can't. Omega lull. Hold on. Just wait. Up and then up. And I have fucking so many
peas next round. Up. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. Next round. All right. One, two, three.
Everybody back the fuck up. Wait. I screamed so loud. Hey, thank you, dad. Thanks for the 10
community subs. Dad. Appreciate that, dad. Thanks for the 10 subs, dude. Seriously. All right. So
let's, let's do a little, let's put it to a poop right there. And then we're going to drop down a,
I think that two more moves. Kill that. Maybe. To that. Yeah. Whatever. Then got another move I can
do. Go. Needle. Bang. Needle again. Bang. And then what's that? Oh, I'm sorry. I haven't been
slowed down. Fucking idiot. And then, yeah, just, just for fun. Just because, just because you're
ugly. You know what I mean? Okay. That's two rounds of stun to add to our pool collection.
Is that a bone scenario over here? Nice shot. Idiot. Seven bone scenario. Is there? I mean,
I could drop this tile here, move over, move down. Wait, hold on. Are you guys for real?
This is a seven bone scenario coming up? What if I go here? No. Here. Drop the tile there.
Let me think about this. I can remove two tiles. So let's go bang right here. I get it. I get a
bone here. You can remove. I can remove. Wait, hold on. Two, two, four, six. Holy shit. I can
do three tile moves. Okay. All right. So I'm going to remove. We need to have a communication
way if you guys talk to me in chat. Remember, think it's a board, right? So we're going to say
four. Like this is one, two, three, four. Okay. This is one, two, three, four. If you want me
to see something, you have to say one or like two, two, three, two dash three. One, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight, nine. They're nine. Two, six, two, eight, two, three. See?
I'm not going to, if it's more than two numbers, I'm not going to read your chat message.
Okay. So what do you, what do you guys see here? You've seen a scenario?
Now everyone's all fucked up. I'm going to do, I'm doing two, two,
two, two, three, two, two, two, three, two, three. That's my play. Two, two, two, three, two, three.
Right? That's what I'm saying. Two, two, two, three, one, two, three, four. That's only six.
Hold on. Wait. Oh, fuck. Wait a minute. I fucked it up. And then I can do two, two,
down. And then next round, do it. Okay. Two, two, two, two, down. And then back the fuck up.
You got to give me info. Two, one, two, two, four, four, full heal. Teeth deal plus one damage.
That's okay. These are both insane. Does this mean I can use it whenever I want?
Or does that mean it happens right now and that's it? Just once. Okay. I'm going to go with the
teeth damage. I like that better. The stat wheel. 15 cents for, hold on, this is a casino. Oh, fuck.
Randomized needle. What else is here? Five cents for heart or item or the shell game.
That's a lot. Randomize, reroll the spell. Spell charge less. Man, I need a spell cost less.
Spin the wheel. You never play the wheel at the casino. It's the worst thing to do.
What does that do? Oh, cool. Great. I got extra luck. All right. I'm going for it. Whoa. There's no way
anyone could figure that out. Nobody saw the end of that. Nobody did. Spells change each room.
I wish I had a heal though. Oh my God. You can just buy one. I have no more money.
So what's the trinket that I just got? Randomize spells? Oh, this is all different now. What's it?
Oh, this is actually, I don't like that. Destroy a column of tiles and then blind an enemy.
All right. Well, whatever. I guess maybe you could give us an error. Does this last the whole time
I'm down here? I'm going to do that more often. I'm sorry. All right. Oh, I don't like this board.
I need to do bones though, because I have the bone trinket. So we're doing bones.
I'm thinking, let's see. Bang. Yeah. Oh, oh, oh. And then I, oh, what's that? I call that a
one, two, three, four, five, six, seven bone scenario. So that's, let me see. Oh, I don't,
no, fuck. I don't have my thing. I think to break tiles. Oh, let me see. One, two, three.
One, two, three. I can do it next turn. I'm going to win. Am I going to die? No. Oh, all right. I
win. It was not, I don't think that was worth losing a full heart for though. This is pepper
and number one movement gaining attack. Ooh, that takes a lot of resources, but it's really cool.
Booger and knockback. I already have a knockback. I'm not buying the ghost pepper. This one is a
damn, you do damage and you get a move. I can stay alive. All right. No more fucking around.
What is this? Oh, it's, oh, it's, it doesn't matter. Everything's random every time.
Skip to the next chapter. Should, should do it. There is no next chapter. I haven't unlocked it
yet. Okay. Well, we're fine. Hmm. All right. I don't know what these guys do for, well,
I'm going to have to put some food down, I think. And yeah, let's gum it up a little.
Uh, let's throw a tooth to damage. Nice, uh, stink club. Okay. P I could just, I could move
and just get some, no shit. All right. I could do P and just kind of recalibrate. No, I can't.
I need the P though for this. All right. Hold on. Wait. No, I have to, I just gotta, I gotta get
this fucking going and kill. What is this thing doing? Blinding attack. Gain plus one damage for
the room. Why should I blind? I think this is like just a shield, isn't it? All right. I'm
hitting harder in the room. Gain mana equals to most common tile. Who? So if I gain, so I'm
going to gain six Pooh mana, but I don't, I don't even use Pooh mana, but just again.
Okay. I'll just do it again. Where the fuck did this come from? All right. I got to, um,
right down the middle, I got to get rid of this. I got to kill this thing.
Seven Pooh. No, I'm going to die. I get it. I've got to do bones. I've got to do bones.
Can I do bones twice? You know, I could kill the thing that's about to attack.
Yeah, this is actually really bad. Uh, I'm going to have to kill the thing. I have to.
Otherwise I'm fucked. Spell is ready. Blinding attack. We're going to do that on
left. Gotcha. Now you're in trouble. No one's attacking yet. I'm good. Oh, this is bad. Um,
I have to set up some Pooh defense. This is a bad board. This is not a good board. Gaining mana
for the most common tile. It's Pooh, but I, right? How many is it? Boogers or Pooh? It's Pooh. I
have to get rid of Pooh. Three, one. What about it? Two, five, two, four, two, one, two, three,
four, five, two, five, two, four. I know I saw that too, but I think that screws up. I'll go for it.
All right. But, uh, I can't defend myself against these guys. Is it teeth now? It's Pooh. Fuck.
How much damage is this going to do? It can kill you. And then I'm going to have to take a hit.
Dammit. You guys just keep coming out of nowhere. This is kind of shit.
Too much Boogers and too much Pooh. Reroll? I would love to. I can't. I think I'm dead here.
That gave me a bunch of Boogers, which I don't even need. Eyes? I think dead. I could put down a...
No one's attacking yet, so that's good. Where am I going to put it though? Over here.
I'll put it right down the middle. Yeah. All right. Come on. Give me your worst. And then I can do...
I can do an Ultra P. And then I can do a Super Booger. But where do I want that? On the right,
I guess? I guess that prevents me from dying right now. I need more teeth. All right,
Ariel. Let's just go like this. And I'm throwing this right down the middle.
Okay. Gain extra damage for the room. Yeah. I keep spawning these things. Shit.
It keeps... I gotta kill these things. I gotta get all the way to the back. Okay. New... Okay.
It's going to have to be Pooh Shield on the left. I need a seven bone scenario. I gotta just try to
kill one of these fucking guys. Can I get the bone? Can I set up a blinding attack? Wait, that's...
I got extra damage for the whole floor. What was it? Teeth? Okay. I gotta set up a... Let's
gonna go, I don't know, down here. Go over here. And then maybe I could go from... Shit.
That's all I can really do. Can I stop anything? I think that's all I got. Do a seven Pooh scenario.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. That's way too much. That can take a million years.
The two spread out. I could go down here and then... What do you want? What are you talking about?
Set up the heart. That's a much better idea. I've set up the heart.
Whatever else you guys want me to do. Disgusting. Now I can heal.
It's not three hearts. It's not three. It's four. Oh, no. It's four hearts like everything else.
Oh, no. That was a mistake. Shit. It's... I don't know why. I just thought it was three hearts
because they don't... It's all right. I'm fine. Jesus Christ. They're just filling the board now.
I'm about to take the... Wait. If I go like this, then I can do a shield on the right.
Hold on. Let me see what I can do. That's all you get? What kind of fucking messed up world is
that? It's only half a heart. I gotta kill one of these things and I have Pooh set up for next round.
No. I think I may have fucked it. I think I spent... I did this too many times.
It's not completely over. I can do two shields. I can go over here. No, no, no, no. I can go...
I can do one shield. One and then... If I like your Lich Escape, 5,000 bits. Thanks for the 5,000
bits on top of your like three of $5,000 you get into this channel. You don't get to make fun of
chat ever again because you're literally playing pee-pee poo-poo. Yes, I know. Four, seven, one,
four. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven. Left. What does that do? Thank you so much for
like three of those. Seriously. Two, two. Two, two. One, two. One, two. Two, two. Yeah, I know.
But I don't know if that helps me. I can... I know... At least I know I can do this. I can do that.
For that. Does that help me later? I mean, it stops whatever's going on here. I need to set the
bones up. Bone, bone, bone, bone, bone, bone, bone, bone, bone, bone, bone, bone, bone, bone.
Instead of the bone, bone, bone, bone, bone, bone, bone, bone, bone, bone, bone, bone, bone, bone,
bones. You know like that? Six bones only. No, I gotta free... Seven bones of bust. I'm just
gonna do this. I don't know if everyone's gonna be like, wait, what'd you do?
All right, these guys are the worst. Okay, now I could P. I could get P. And wait, is there a
better P scenario there? Maybe. If I go over and then down, that'll give me more turns to then...
Fucking no. And then... Maybe I could do bones. Seven bones scenario. You know what? It's actually
kind of funny you saying that, but I think I was... I needed to kill these things fast. I just didn't
know what they did. I was too focused on like the toilet paper guys when I should have killed
these guys immediately. I need the mana for the bones. Yeah, I know. I'm just gonna go like this
and then I'm gonna kill one on the right and then I'm gonna end my turn again.
I can't do anything. Thankfully, no one's attacking right now. So, all right. Any bones?
Well, if I blinding attack, will it kill it through here? Or is it gonna...
Are we certain about that or is it gonna block it? What the fuck just happened?
What the... It attacked me? Why? Oh, now I really am dead. Uh-oh. Can I keep... I can at least keep
this going for another... Who's... I'm gonna freeze you and then... No one's attacking, right? Oh,
you asshole. Right in the middle. Bones. I need bones. This is taking so much longer than it should.
I could go like this and then I need to block this guy. I die if I don't block that guy.
It's over. You know what the real culprit was? This guy right here. I'm dead. Holy shit. I'm alive.
Uh, I could kill them both but then that... I'm just like treading water perpetually.
BZ seven bones? No, it's not. It's gonna take like two turns. But I could do five bone in two turns
but that... Does that help me? I'm talking about like you go one bang and there's five there
or I could go... You're dead in one hit. I know. That's why I can't... I have to kill these two on
the sides. If I don't kill these two on the sides, I have to make them... I'm just dead. So, that's
what has to happen. So now, set up the five bone scenario. Or, wait. One, two, three... I got a
six bone scenario. Six bone scenario coming up. If you can do it... If you can do it, you can
survive these two and set up for the next. I... I'm about to die right now. If I... No, if I do
seven bones, this thing's gonna activate and it's gonna kill me. It's gonna kill me. Booger mid.
No, let me... I'm gonna do six bone scenario. Okay. Bang. Bang. All right. And then we're gonna...
I'm clearing it. And then we're gonna kill this guy on the left. And then. And only then. What do
you mean why? If this thing takes damage, I die. What happened? I can't attack these guys.
I can't attack them. Give me some... Wait. I can do six. I could do seven, actually. No, I couldn't.
Yes, I can. What does seven poo do? Have we even seen it yet? No, we don't know what it does. I'm
doing it. What does it do? Okay. That's pretty great, actually. That's really good. Uh, okay. I
think I'm okay for a while. But god damn it, these clouds! All right. Ugh. I need bones. I'm
just building bones. That's all I care about. If I go this way, this way, and then down, I'm just...
I don't... I'm just doing bones only. What did that just do? Bones only. Blinding attack. I have some.
I'm not using it yet, though. Game... Why would I press this? Stop telling me to do that. And then
gum up the booger. I know. I'm gonna do it. Let's see. What do I got? I could do this booger here,
and then... Who should I gum up? On the left? That's what I'm probably gonna do.
And then I need these blinding attacks. It's so bad. All right. Can I throw a tooth?
I have seven bone mana. Yeah, I need eight. I don't want to use it, though, because
they're just gonna keep spawning them. Yeah, I have to clear these and then kill that before
that little cloud there. I have shield. I have time. Yeah, I'm all right. I just want to...
I guess I could bring this down and bring the bone over. I could do this. I could do this. And then
get the teeth. Half-Life VR game announced on Valve's Twitter.
What? Are you serious? Half-Life VR. Half-Life VR. Oh, that's fucking cool.
We'll see, though. I'm gonna hold off judgment, because here's the thing about VR games.
This... Okay, if this is like a two hour and 25 minute Valve tech demo, then I don't care.
We'll find out. If this is the real deal, I'm in. If this is like a 48 minute long demo for their new
controllers, then I'm not in. Speaking of being in, why is he still on this level? Because it's kind
of hard. And these guys are... They spawn. You can't hurt these guys. It's pretty... It's cool.
It's a fun game. He's trying to challenge, trying to get through the fucking hard levels.
All right. I'm setting up Bones only. And I know people are going to be like, what are you doing?
Oh my... I can't believe he just did that. Dude, I can't even watch this stream because of him.
Bones. And we're going to the bright side. Okay. Drop that stupid gas thing. What's the better
play? This or this? Probably that. This guy set up a five poo scenario, maybe? The poo protects from...
Wait, what are you saying? The poo protects the clouds. If this is not real, I'm going to be very
mad at you. You guys are so fucked. Thank you. Appreciate it. We can... Now this game... This
level's got five times easier. So now I can do this two more times. I'm going to... I could go
bang bang. That wouldn't... It's not finally we can end this. We're not even close. We're not even
remotely close yet. If only it didn't take you 25 minutes to read that. I've only been on this
level for like 18 minutes. So like... Pump the brakes a little. Screech on the brakes.
I haven't even been 25 minutes. It's only been like 17 or 18.
All right. Let's go. Go for the health. That's a good idea. But I don't... I don't have any more health.
No, I'm set. Look. You know what? No. Okay. Go for a heart match. I need four hearts. There's no hearts
coming down on the menu. I'm setting up the shit. I'm setting up poop. Oops. Don't fucking... I'm
going to mess this up now. Give me the teeth. I was going to do like seven poos. Almost had nine of every...
Yeah. Almost nine of every minute. You're right. Three, nine, two, three, five. One, two, three, nine,
two, three, five. Three, nine, three. One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, nine,
two, three, five, nine, eight, seven, six, five. Excellent. New spells. Like all... This thing
fucking punched me in the face and then threw me in front of a train. I don't have any spells. I have
this one. I only have this one. All right. Let's do teeth, three, smack, and he wins.
But I do need... I'm going to... Let's go to the bones. Come on. So down, down. So up, up, down,
down, down, down. It doesn't matter. Uh, I think... Wait, wait, wait. Can I... Where's the poop?
I can put it down. Let's poo the right. Gum up the poop. Let's go gum up on this guy and then poop
on this guy and then see you next time. See you later. Wait, hold on a second. No, who cares?
Who even cares? I'm just going to win. Cool. Tough love. Tough love.
No, I... Finally. Let me tell you something about the word finally. I... This is all new shit every
single level. It's like I can't just... I don't know. I have to relearn my whole build when I
walk through the door. 25 minutes. Finally. 25 minutes. Finally. Oh, that's fucking incredible.
Too bad. I'm going to use this many times. Okay. Reduce the cost of your spells. Okay.
That's cool. All right. Add three wild tile. Spells cost less for the room. Heals half a heart.
So we need bones and... I mean, that's pretty awesome. Poo and goo. Let me see. How do I set
up a good poo and goo scenario? What does this do? What's the icon on the head for?
You don't like the music? Oh, there's no options. Here, I'll turn it down. All right. I can go... I'm
going to do a tooth. Should I just try to kill this thing right now? I wonder how... Let me see.
I'm just going to hit this thing. I don't know if it does. I guess it's just dead, I guess.
Oh, fuck. It's one of those things. Poo right down the middle. I need poo and I need goo. Although,
I could do five. All right. Hold on. Hear me out on this. I could do five. Damn it. No.
Just mute and play better music. You guys really don't like it that much, huh?
Now, if I go like this and then I go like this, I don't do that. One, two, three, four, five, six.
If I go down with this, I get another move, though. Oh, no. I knew that was going to happen.
Why did I do that? I knew that was going to fucking happen. Did you see how I stopped?
And I was like, no, wait. Why did I do that? I knew that was going to happen. I got a double
thing. Oh, fuck. Shit. I knew that was going to happen. Six poo ruined. Yeah, I fucked it up.
Well, I got... This is where it gets fucking hairy. Like, really hairy. I don't think I can do
seven bones. I think I'm dead before I do it. I could set up a... I could set it up, but
seven bones next turn. What are you saying? Like, down here, down here. Because that'll be six and
then I could drag. All right. I'm going to do it. I'm going to... I might die. Let's see if I die.
Uh, so far, it's a first, right? All right. This is... I win. No, I didn't. Wait. Uh, what do I have?
Nine? So I just had to... No, do I gum them up? I gotta be careful about this guy. And then, wait.
Oh, my. Oh, my. Wait, wait. I don't know what I'm doing. What am I doing? Holy shit. Okay. Um,
over here, and then you, then here, then throw, then... Oh, man. We got more wild tiles. Can I keep
this? There's too many flashing, like, Super Mario stars. Um, I want that heart. I want a super heart.
No, I don't. I just want one heart. I could do a big turn. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. I could
do... I don't know. This is a lot to do here. I could do a big, huge super go more. Oh, it doesn't
matter. Why did it not activate immediately? There it is. All right. Full health. Now, I just need to do...
Uh, I just win. Yeah, that's it. Yeah, I did. Mega battery plus three movement plus random man.
This doesn't matter anyways. It's gonna be fucking rainbowed anyways. Plus three movement
random man. I mean, what? Doesn't matter. Bumble versus dusk. All right, time. Let's go. Time to
reload everything I've known about my whole build. Movement gaining attack. Destroy all tiles of one
type. Blocks the next single attack. Charges random usable item. Hits the furthest enemy plus splash.
Okay. Plus three movement and random mana. Should I do it right off the bat? Go for it right off the
bat. Let's go. How much mana? All right. I got, I got a seven bone scenario I can do now. I got
one, two, three, four, five moves. One, one, two, three, four, five. There's seven bones on the board.
How do we get the seven bones to make a seven bone scenario? I don't want to mess this up.
No, it's possible. It is. It'll be possible next turn. If I go over, over down, that's three,
which then has this row. No, three. Okay. Hold on. I hope I'm doing this right. Okay. Then this one
comes up and then no, no, no, no, no, three. This, no, this goes down, right? Okay. This comes down.
Then this goes over. What? No, no, that was right. Because I have to move this one over.
That's too many moves. Use one, just all to the top row. What do you mean all the top row?
What do you do? What do you mean? Do it on the top row? Should I? So like this and then
it's all right. Let's go. Uh oh. Okay. He doesn't, he just hits you. Seven bones. I almost just
double clicked. Okay. Seven bone scenario. Light them up. Bang, bang, bang, bang, bang.
God, I couldn't do it in one move. Damn it. Okay. Hold on. Hits the furthest enemy with splash
damage. Did it in one move.
Someone stinky mom. The dog with human face. A hot dog with teeth. It's a mystery.
What's in there Bumble? Bumble back open scary box. What's this? Another Bumble?
This is the fat Bumble. You unlock Bumble the stout. And halls of Belial have unlocked.
What's your thing? Whoa, this game sucks ass. What? What are you talking about? This game's like
coal. I like this. This is fun. This is an iPad game. It's not an iPad game. Bannum. All right.
So this is Bumble the stout stick. Whack away. That's three poops. That's a blender blade
destroys tiles and touching tiles. Kind of a shitty stats setup though. Terrible
in everything. So far Bumble, Bumble's the best. Bumble the brave.
Let's try the new one. Yeah, you got to play with them to unlock the next floor anyways. Yeah.
Okay, so I have whack away. So might as well just load up poops, huh? I mean, I could just do this now.
Or I could load up a big one. Yeah, fuck it. Let's just do this.
Mana drain. Yeah, fuck it. Watch this. Whack away. It's two damage. Best character in the game.
Let's throw a bone. Actually, I'm gonna get hit. No, I'm not. Yes, I am. Should have killed this guy.
I'm fucking dumb. It's all right. I'm a little dumb, but whatever.
Stories tiles and see this is I need to use this to see how that works.
Okay, uh, there's bone over here. And then what cares, right? You lose mana every turn.
That's all right. Brown belt blocks next attack plus attacks or chaos. Add wild tile and a curse.
I'm not sure what a curse does, but one wild tile for two teeth is kind of cool.
I'm going for it. All right, let's do this poop in the way. Let's kill you.
I got out of wild. Oh, that's
all right. Sorry. I just like choked on air. That was ridiculous. I'm sorry. I tried to meet
as fast as I could. I got a wild tile here. We can gum up the mill. It's gonna happen again.
Maybe I should, maybe we should do bones. Do it again. All right. I gotta stop fucking around.
Don't fuck around. I mean, I know I could have used it again, but
curse insta kills enemies. What? Why would that be a downside? All right. I've got wilds here.
I could go here. I could start to build out a big bone, which would probably better this way.
Actually, no, it's going to take too long. I'm just going to do what's going to do over here.
I'm just going to throw a bone right in the middle. And then I'm going to move this out here.
And so if I block that, this is their shit, not mine. Right. So I have to block it with my own
shit. Okay. I'm safe. All right. Let's do gum. I need to do poops.
But let's just gum this because I wanted to get rid of it. Destroy tiles and touch.
I kind of want to know what this does. Take an area to destroy. I just want to know what it does.
Okay. So it just destroys all the tiles touching that one. I should have destroyed the curse.
Yeah, that would have been a smart idea, but I would have gotten rid of the bones.
All right. Let's set up, uh, bring this down. I could kill this, but I'm going to take a hit.
What's going to do more damage? Probably this. Uh, and then I just got to throw a tooth at you.
If I can make it work. I don't really have any great set up here. I can go up and then over
and then heal and I heal a booger down and then right. Good booger. I'm just going to do it.
Probably fucking this whole thing up, but whatever. Let's get rid of the curse
and then, I don't know, let's go. And then, uh, that was kind of fun to do that because now I do
this. It's only one damage. Oh fuck. Keep it going. Is that he's in front of the poop, isn't he?
All right. Poop on the left, kill thing in the middle. This is two damage though, isn't it?
See what. And now I could just nonchalantly throw a tooth at you and then get wild in there.
Do another one. Another one. Good. Now, I mean, it's impossible for me not to get something here.
So wild. Uh, it doesn't matter. I mean, I could have done something. I mean, that's cool. Pretty
cool. It doesn't matter the play there. You just got to kill it. Ooh. Plus one damage this turn.
It's only two P, but for this turn only or plus one damage and life gain. It takes three rooms
to charge. Which drug do I want? That's a good question. I mean, is this permanent? If it's
permanent, then just use it every single second to get it. Or this is just, you can. Yeah. Yeah,
that's probably better. Peeper. I'm a peeper. I have ADHD. Get the ADDY. Okay. I see what you're
doing there. All right. So, uh, should I do a huge poop here? I could do one, two, three, four,
five, six. No, I could do five. So I'm gonna do it. Yeah, I'm just gonna do five. Not like it
matters. I'm just gonna do it in the middle anyways. Uh, wait. Is it possible? No. Whatever.
Just do it. Could I have done six? I got a bone too. Move it out of the way. I'm not going to use
this because it's not going to hurt him. But let's, uh, I can do another turn. Can I hurt, can I hit,
hit it with something? Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Slow down. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Hold
on. Slow down. Hold on. Wait. I think, can I kill him? Plus one. I can do this two, four. I can do
plus three damage for this turn. Hold on. So that's three. I can do this twice so I can hit him for
what? Like I can do a shitload of damage right now. The teeth. Hit him with the teeth. Oh yeah.
All right, buddy. It's time for you to take an absolute shitload of damage.
It's five, 10 damage. Oh, that feels pretty good. It's out of wild too. You know what? Fuck it.
Let's add, let's just fill the board with wilds. Okay. I'm looking for shit here. Shit and piss.
Uh, I could just kill him, I think. Can I? There's a lot of different wild scenarios here. Uh,
uh, I think I can kill him if I just do poo. So hold on, get this over here.
That's poo. Hold on. Cause that's one, two, three, four. It's not enough.
No, we'll bring that back. Go this way. Shit. That's a lot to look at. Uh, I'm just gonna do it.
I, I, yeah, I'm just gonna go for it. So let's move this. Just, I'm just gonna just connect it.
I got plenty more wilds and shit too. So who cares? So I'm just going to cover up the you
and then I'm going to hit you in the face. Cursed. How did I get cursed? Oh fuck. That's how. All
right. Let's just kill him. One. Can I kill him right now? I just need poo. I could do four bones
on the left. Yeah, there it is. Goodbye. Nice. If you match seven curse, you instantly die. That's
not good. Rat heart. May gain soul hearts or modeling clay. Copy a trinket. May gain soul
heart. Or I can copy one of my trinkets. What do I have for a trinket right now? What's the scenario
how this plays out though? Is it just in the beginning of a room? Let's try it. See what
happens. All right. Spells hurt more. Spells cost less or reroll spell cost. Spin the wheel.
Spin the fucking wheel. Spells hurt more is absolute. I'm taking that. Pick a spell to modify.
Um, this one does three damage now. Okay. That's pretty fucking good. Spells cost less. I'm going
to do it to that as well. Check this shit out. Ready? This thing is going to be two. It's only
two. I can either spin the wheel or I can buy a heart. Set. Yeah. Yep. Let's take a look at that.
That's going to be, I mean, I'm going to be, I'm going to wipe everybody out. If I just only need
to focus on just match poos and I have a four damage spell that I can use many times I want.
Pooh wizard. Let's go. Four damage for two poops. Holy shit. That's ridiculous.
I can kill two things right now. Let's go right down the middle. Yeah. I'll put this over here.
Let's take a look at our new move. Bang. Huh? They, I, spell resisted. I can't kill those.
No, you can't do spells against these stone mushrooms. That's what that icon means.
This is the room that I get the set right after getting my awesome new build.
That sucks. This is horrible. I have to, okay, we get bones. I would have put the pooh here
if I had even remotely had thought this is a possibility. Um, wait. Okay. So I go,
this is one damage. I could kill one of these. Oh, fuck. How many bones can I throw? One,
no matter the scenario. I mean, I, I think it's time to set up a potential re ridiculous scenario.
No, I'm only going to be able to throw one bone. How long is it going to take me to do? I'll take
one. I'll take, I'll have one heart left. What'd you beat? Then I, next round I can do three,
three. Fuck it. Let's do it. Who cares? You know what I'm saying? All right. All right. All right.
Let's go. See you later. Hopefully this kills the thing in the back or at least the, hopefully
this does enough damage. Get the guy in the front. Oh yes. That was a really bad room for what I just
built splash damage attack. So wait, could I activate the addy like three times activate
splash damage attack and then use my stick. It's sick, but I mean, that's kind of, that's,
that's too pricey. Is it though? If we're going glass cannon, I might as well stuff it too expensive
50% of blind, but that's a, this is four, this one's six, 50% chance of not blinding an enemy
for four bones. You start from zero at every turn. Shit. That's right. Yeah. That's right.
That's true. All right. What do we got? Let's see what I want to do here. Start. Let's put down
some shit. I'm going to go right down the middle and then we're going to kill the shit on. Oh man,
this is so fantastic. Look at this. I did eight damage, but what's the most, what's the most
threatening thing here? I need to know. I want is the other thing. We're going in the back. Yeah.
I don't even know what these things do, but I don't want to know. Okay. I can throw a tooth.
I can throw a bone. I need more foos. Get some piss. Now let's do piss. Bring down the goo.
Hold on. Wait, hold on a second. Two, four. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Bone, bone damage. Bingo. Right. Yeah. That's a good, that's a play cause then I could
throw this once and it'll kill it. Six teeth. I'm just going to do the safe bone play. So this is
two, four, six, two, four, six. Bang. Let's throw this, kill this thing right off the bat.
Game sucks. Blind enemies. Yeah. No, I, this is actually really cool. All right. So we're
going to attack. It's going to hit there. I don't have any shits to line up, but I could throw a
tooth, which will give me some wilds. Actually I could throw, can I throw more than one tooth
is the question. I could do, I could do this. Okay. Hold on. Do this. Yup. I'm getting,
all right. I'm getting a little fucking. All right. Slow down. No more. Okay. Okay. Done.
What do I do about this? I can do down gum booger and then booger. We're going to break the tiles
here. Right here. Okay. Then we're going to go right here. Very cool. Damn it. Bad room.
Absolutely terrible room. Did they know what build I just made? What the hell?
I might have to try to do seven here. If I go all the way back here, like here,
I could do three. No, it's not going to work. Maybe this way. No, maybe this way. No,
I could do six. Is that going to take too long? That shit's going to take too long.
You can do seven and two turns. Can I though? Seven bones? That's not possible.
If I go, I could do four poos and one P. What do you see that? Wait, hold on. That's not terrible.
Let's go right here. Just do it because for fun, because we want to. Now I got a P set up. I can't
do this anyway. So that's yeah. I know I, I do have a pretty good P set up here, but P,
I don't think P is that very good for seven and you only get what? Five? Maybe. I don't know.
We'll see. I might be in some trouble here though. Cause if I go the free teeth column on the right,
what do you mean? I could set up P. If I do this, bring two down and then I mean that's six.
I'm just going to go for that. Knock back, right? Wait, wait, wait. What do you mean? Knock back,
right? Teeth. Teeth. Teeth. I'm not seeing this. Teeth. I can do four on one move.
Why am I not seeing this? Second, I got two, three, three, one, four, two, do seven teeth.
I, I, I see what you, I see you. I see what you're saying.
Fuck. Okay. Seven teeth. What does it do? I can't do it this round. I have to get, I have to take a
hit. Am I safe? Oh, that's right. I have to poo there. Okay. You're right. That's true.
I forgot about it. All right. I hope this works. Otherwise the runs over. Thank God.
Destroy a column of tiles. I have too many bones, too many things that require bones.
Copies spell at random. Let's take that. Bumble versus shy gal. Unmask and smash.
New, new boss. Copies spell at random. Should I just do it? I mean, what am I going to do? Just
not do it. Just do it right now. Whatever it is. What if it's a bone? What if it's a seven bone?
It might be. Oh shit. It's a throwable stick. Unmasked. All right. Hold on. Now, um,
I could do poop right now. Let's put it right in the middle.
Whack. Can I kill you right now? I just, I just want to. Yes. This is an insane build. It really
is really good. I might get screwed later though. Free spell at low HP. May add poison to attacks.
What is low HP? What would that would be considered low? Half a heart? Or would I have right now?
Probably half a heart. May add poison. Not will add poison. It may add poison. What's that
percentage though? I want the free spell. All right. 21 coins. What do we got over here?
Spell costs less. Oh, I can't break it. I can't break the game. Cancel. Too bad.
Cancel. Well, let's at least take a heart. Spin the wheel. Wait. Spell costs less. Reroll spell
costs. What does spell charge? Well, I guess that that's okay. I see what that means.
Copies a spell. It's just a, I see. It'll bring it down to one room. That might not be a horrible
thing to do. I mean, there's a wheel. So obviously everyone wants me to spin the wheel. I'll have
enough to do one more thing. That's absolutely incredible. 33%, 33% more health and we'll,
we'll do this. Wait. Reroll spell. No. We have to get the, uh, open the box.
Granny teeth? And I have one more coin, which that doesn't look right. The Halls of Belial.
Haven't been here before. This is a new content. What do these do? Can I look at it? Is there any
see what this does? You just get one tooth. Oh, all right. These guys are spell resistant. What's
with all the spell resistant? That sucks. Gum up the one on the right. Teeth. Put the music back
up. Uh, I'm just going to do, let's do the safe play here and dump somebody else. Or I could do,
I could set up a seven teeth scenario. Possible. It can take a while though. If I go this way,
I can do, so if I go that way and then this way, so if I, okay, hold on and then bring this
up and then one tooth. Wait, hold on. I don't want to do this wrong. It would have to be here
and then one tooth. No, I can, I think, I don't think I can, I don't think I can do it.
I'm going to do the bottom row. Wait, whoa, whoa, whoa. What happened? What happened? What? No,
I tried to put it back. I tried to put it back. I tried to put it back. What? No, I want to put
it back. I didn't put it back. Ah, fucked it up. It's, I fucked it. It's, I fucked it up.
That sucks. Okay. That's bad. Um, new plan. I got, I'm sorry guys. I got to go with a new plan here.
Hook, use the hook. Hook, use the hook. Hook, use the hook. What am I using the hook on?
Do one, two, three. If I break this, it's, it'll break too much, won't it? This is going to destroy
all this. Yeah, no, I'm not going to do that. Seven teeth spotted. Yeah. It's too much stress.
Okay. If I go one, two, three. Okay. Here we go. I'm going to take a hit, but we're going to get
seven teeth. Damn it. God damn it. Taking a lot of damage. Too much for my comfort. Wait,
I can't whack them. They were, they won't hurt them. Charges random usable item. Blinding attack.
That's so expensive. I'm never going to use that, but I'm never going to use the
lemon either. I mean, this is a guaranteed blinding attack instead of 50% blinding of enemies.
Okay. Let's think about it. Let's, let's, let's do, let's poop. Right. Okay. Who is the most,
what's the most dangerous thing here? The middle bro, I guess. I don't know. I'm going to kill this
though. Let's go on the left side. Okay. Right down the middle. You got to be fucking kidding me.
Fuck. Bad. Cancel. Fuck. What should I break? I have this. Not even worth done. Oh boy. Teeth.
Okay. Let's kill everything. Kill, let's kill everything. Shit. Oh, how do I kill this?
How do I kill you? I don't even know how to kill this thing. I can't take a curve. I can't take a
wild right now. Cause if it goes right there, then I'm going to be in big trouble. Look at,
look at this bro. Do it? I don't think that's a good idea. It's you have to do it when his
neck is up. But when is his neck up? No, I'm not doing it. No way. Fuck. Um, okay. Now his neck
is up and there's two attacks coming on this side. I need a miracle right now. What's my miracle?
Take a chance for once in your life. Pee into poo. Make the pee. Can I do only four
peas though? This is important. I'm in trouble. Pee and bones. Ah, bone. Oh, guys. I don't know.
I could do this. Let me do that and do, and oh, but wait, hold on. Let's do this.
Right. Oh, and that's an extra bone. Oh, that's a lot of bone. That is a six bone, but ah,
how many bones do I get to throw with six? Holy shit. This might actually, I might win.
It's three throws. Okay. Everybody settle down. Two, four, six. That's four damage a throw.
And then I can throw three times. One, two, three, and then up.
And then up again. Here we go. Eight fucking damage. Okay. And let's blinding attack on you.
And then on, fuck, this is going to get tricky. One heart. Bad. Although I can't kill this thing.
I could do a couple of whacks. I can't kill this thing with a whack though. Eight health. Fuck off.
Going right in the middle. And then kill these two and then give her the poop in the middle.
Sounds good. All right. Poop again. Can I do poo again in one turn? Or is it bones? I'm going to
throw a bone. Try to set the poop up. All right. So what if I go like this? No, no, that's too far.
What about down here? Let's go over here and then set up this. Just, just do a poop setup run.
I think I'm just going to throw. No, there's no reason to throw the bone. I just need to do poop
or bone and teeth. Yeah, I'm just going to do it. I need that might as well.
Shit. I'm trying to hit the toilet paper.
I can poop next round. In fact, I want more poos. I'm going right here. No, no, it's not even worth
it. It's not worth it. Just let it play out. I can poop next round anyway. So speaking of that,
I can go over and then up or I can go just pull it this way and I get it for free
without having to do two moves. And then would you look at that? I can set up for a booger
next round. Can I? Sort of. I cannot hurt this. I'm going to hit it anyways. It's fun.
All right. I'm safe. I'm just going to set up another. I'm going to set up another poop.
Could be this, right? Yeah. There it is. See you later. I need help.
It's all enemies rerolls a row of tiles. That's really good.
Heart bad. This is really good because I can activate the addy with this.
Right. That would be a huge, huge deal. Yeah. I don't want the random spell. It's too, it's too
much. Oh, bumbo versus sangry. Go for the soft spot. Okay. I can, I can do a poop right now,
which is good. Let's get it on there. Let's see if, can I hurt him? Yes, I can. Oh, he,
when you hit him once, he closes. He has to open back up again. I get it. Okay. We need to go. I
got to get pee because I need pee and then poo so I can kill him in like one hit. Cursed. Oh, oh boy.
Holy shit. He's right here. Okay. Pee and then poo. Is there, is it possible to do pee and poo
right now? I don't think so. Let me see. I can do pee, but I don't have a poo set up. Can I take
one hit? I can't take one hit. He'll hit you more than once. Oh, he's going to hit you three times.
Is it, what's the other play here? Is to gum him up for a run? Do the blind attack. Will that
actually do it? How long are they blind for? I'm going to try it. I'll try it. Let's go for the
attack with the blind. Blind is RNG, but could save the whole thing. Let's try it. Oh, he's back.
All right. So now blind him. Will this work? Is he going to just run up to me? I mean, I just pushed
him. He's really far back now. Please don't kill me. One, two, three. Oh, I'm dead. I could do pee,
but it's not going to help. Pee and then maybe throw a wild in and hope I get RNG.
Boogers. Battery and boogers. He's knocked back. That doesn't help me though. And then hold him
there. So you say and go bang bang and then just hold in place. Just booger him. I'm going to try
it. Stuck right here, I think. Oh, should I destroy the carcasses? Give me shit. I need poo
over here. Oh, should I press it? I don't think I should press it. No, I thought he was, I thought
he was frozen. Oh, it's only one. He gets three turns. Fuck. That guy sucks. Damn. Damn it.
Damn it. Oh no. Damn it. Super booger. I'm so sad. Oh, I'll just do poo. It's better that way.
That was a cool run. Yeah, it was. Oh well. It was cool. Permadeath? Yeah, there is permadeath.
You just start over. But every time you beat it, you unlock new stuff.
Why'd I do that? Hold that. No, I'm an idiot. I'm a dumb as a sack of rock.
I thought I could do seven. Yeah, we know. I don't. I could do this. I'm gonna get hit though.
So many teeth. I'm so sad that that build was so cool. Maybe I can do a similar one.
Change any tile to a wild. Yeah, immediately. Okay, this is a lot of boogers, but we go poo
first always. I guess I probably shouldn't put it there, but I can. I'll be fine. Who do I gum?
Huh? Do this. Not in any danger. I'm not in any real danger or anything. All right. Bones.
Cool. Show Otto. Show Otto. Okay, how many throws do I get? Two. Yeah. I'll do this.
Get you with a tooth. Now you have to show Otto. Otto's such a good boy. He's such a good boy.
Valve announced the new Half-Life game. Yeah, that's pretty big news right now, isn't it?
That is a pretty big deal. Change any tile. Okay, I need to pee. Although, I have a terrible
setup here to do this maybe. I can just do it now. Yeah, I need it now. Okay, I gotta start
killing stuff, you know? Half-Life VR. Yeah, hopefully it's good. I hope it's good. I got
a bone next turn. I'm gonna put this over here because I'm gonna kill these things in the middle.
Uh-oh. Uh-oh. That's actually a real uh-oh. I'm not gonna kill this. How many throws do I have?
Pretty you. Pretty you. Ow. I actually kind of somehow nonchalantly ended up making this way worse.
Um, the soundtrack isn't great. Uh, I think it's okay. I'd like a little more variety, though.
Try to make some wilds. I'm kind of in trouble. Uh, do I have enough to... I could do the extra
turn, but that's not... I don't think it's gonna do anything for me. I guess I could do the extra
turn and try to make a wild. Let's do tooth. That'll kill that. And then I could do the
extra. Yeah, let's do that. And with this, now I have any tile as a wild, which I could do that,
which I'm just gonna do because why the hell not? Don't win yet. I do win now, though.
Yes, I do. Wait. Yes, I do. Kill the rock. What does it get? Is there something in the rock?
Should I stall and heal? Is there actual shit in the rock? There's nothing in the rock. Change
anything into a wild. Okay, so let me... We're just gonna stall, apparently.
Am I really gonna do this? What do you mean wasted poo rock? I don't need... I don't need seven.
Why do I need seven? Hit rock with poop. This doesn't do anything. Uh, well, I want to get
rid of the bones, though, because if I am gonna just try to get this farm wilds to heal, then
that's the plan, then. There's a wild right there. Don't throw that.
Okay, I want to move. I'm gonna do anything. Okay, let's... I need pee to farm the wilds, too.
I got three hits here. All right, let's bring this with pee. Let's get some pee here.
You go down and then over. Whatever. Rock doesn't do anything. Yeah, I know. There we go.
So let's make this... Let's bring this over here. I gotta make sure I don't actually activate this
somehow. All right, we're good. Here's the heal, right? Yes. Let's go. Floor one. Plus three
movement. I'm never gonna have that. Gain one to two coins. I mean, that's just free money every
couple rooms. Vote to cancel. This is what we're playing. There is no vote to change the game.
This is the game that I'm playing. What's going on in here? If that vote passes, then we times
two the amount of time... I will spend a week playing this game. I will spend the next seven
straight days playing this game. If you... What are you talking about? I mean, I'm not gonna do
that, but I'm having... This is a good game. Well, free coins. Let's take them. I don't know what this
dude does. Uh-oh. Kenshi. Turned him a lot about playing Bumble for seven days. Turned him a lot
about pooping his pants. All right, let's set this up down and then I'm gonna do this. Freeze him.
And then... I think that's fine. He can't do... Well, he's gonna move twice.
But that's okay. I think he's just gonna get really close. But that's okay because... Do I have an
opportunity for a poop right now? I can throw a tooth at him. I could set up a five poop.
I could do one, two, three, four, five. Five head. I mean, I could go... I could set up a
down here and then up and then... All right. Cool. Might be able to kill him right now.
Ooh. You break up into little things. Right down Main Street. Let's go. Oh, every time you hit him.
All right. That's actually a pretty good thing to do. What is this? Are these extra poops?
Well, that's terrible. That sucks. I think I'm gonna have to...
I just... I don't know. Make a tooth. Yeah. Maybe it'll knock him back. Yes, it will.
And he destroys all that shit. Did he go over the poo?
Fuck. How am I supposed to clear all this? This is so much stuff to clear.
It's just... Wait. It's hiding them. Oh. That makes more sense. I guess I'm... Shit. This guy's
gonna kill me. I think this is R.I.P. Yeah. This sucked. I think I just need to get lucky and do
poo, right? I'm just gonna hope that there's a poo up here. Wait. How do I... I don't understand.
I thought it was hiding them. No? It is, but they have to be revealed before... Shit. Move the row
and it'll uncover the one that I'm on. Well, I guess I'm gonna do this. Damn it. I was just
where the shot... Oh, he didn't even attack me. He didn't even attack. He didn't attack yet.
What? Uh-oh. Okay. He hit the poop shield. Yeah, he usually spits and he goes over the poop shield.
So this is... It's the shape of these that matter. Which one is poo? Do we know? Teeth? Tooth and
wind. Tooth and wind. Where... I guess I... Yeah, I could do this, right? Yeah. It's only one damage,
though. Got it. That was close. That was really close. Hmm. Charge any item. More green tiles.
Uh... Damn it. I wish that was more poop tiles. Charge any item. What do I have for item right now?
I guess... Does the... I have the coin. I don't think that's worth it. It just means I can get
two coins every two rooms. One to two coins. Yeah, but I can only use this once, right?
Well, let's get the nose gobble. Let's try to build around green. All right. What do we got?
Spells hurt more. I mean, it's so simple just to make... To do this... Try to this again.
Try the same run again. I could try it. Let's see if I can do it again. And then re-roll
spell cost. Re-roll spell cost. Should I try to... But what if I make it larger?
Re-roll it to boogers. Wait. That's what that does? So there's a one in five chance that this will be
rolled into a booger. The worst one possible. Speed? I get an extra move. That's pretty huge,
actually. That's really huge. That's a big deal. Run fucked, run saved. Yeah, poop is not vital
at all. But it still is because I still... It hurts a lot. I just did the... It does another damage.
Three damage. It was four bones. No, but poop is so important anyways. And I got so much more nose
goblins. Well, go for five bones. Might as well. And then whack the fuck out of the middle. What
just happened? Why is it... What? Okay. Those die when you have them all in the ground. Oh.
Okay. Yeah. For those that die, I can't... These things, I cannot hit these with this... They are
resistant to all spells. Well, we're just going to booger. Booger the middle too, I guess.
And then I could do... I could do some extra moves here. Any tile of wild? Wait, did I already have
it? No. Fuck. I think I might have... Do some poop here. I could do up. I could do up, up, and then
wild in the middle. And then stick that right in the middle. Well, I don't really want to destroy
anything. I got to knock all these guys down. That's a pain. I could throw a bone over here and
then whack the middle again. Sticky them again. I got to deal with those moles last. I'm going
to throw a bone. I have three moves, so I could just... One, two... Yeah, whatever. Fuck it.
Fuck it. Like it matters. Okay. Can I kill you? I can kill you now with teeth.
And then I... Do I have a... I can do glue in the middle. I can do a big... I can do... Okay, hold on.
What does seven glue do? That's one, two, three, four, five, six, seven. I don't think I can... I
can't do it. I can only do like five... Wait, hold on. If I go up here, that would be one, two,
three, four, five, six. But what if I go over here? That'd be one... Hold on. What if I move
it over this way? That's one, two, three, four, five, six, seven. Right? I think I'm doing this
right. Because then I go like this. And then I go like this. Do nine boogers? What happens if... What
does that do? No, I can't do nine. One, two, three, four, five, six. Fuck. I can't do nine. Can I do
seven though? I don't know. I think I screwed it up. I can? I can't do seven. No, I can do... I
can do six. What do you mean you can? What? One, two, three, four, five, six. I can't... If I move this
way... No, I can't do it. If you just do it on the top row. I'll do six. It's not... No, it's not
worth it. Probably shouldn't do it. Whatever. Okay. These guys are a little annoying, aren't they?
You're a little irritating, aren't you? Let's get some wild bone. How many bones can I do?
Bone, bone. Don't even need the wild. Well, I have to use it though. I could go one, two, three,
four. Can I do five? I could do six bone maybe. If I do one, two, three. So you say one, two, three.
And then I could do a wild there. Wild here. No, no. Wild here. Move this over and go up.
So go... Do I have this right? Five bones wins. Am I fucking this whole thing up? One, two, three,
four. There's the wild. Okay. There's the wild. Hold on, Jeremy. Don't fuck this up yet. One...
Oh, five just wins. Don't matter. Heals one heart, lose one move. Attack a whole row.
You guys want to put on Chillstep? What do you think? Epic Chillstep.
All right. Let's put on some Chillstep for a while. Because yeah, this music is starting to like
burn into my brain. How do I turn this down though? I know you can. I know. I swear to God,
I saw it. Attack a row. That's pretty good. But heals one heart, lose one move. That's actually
bad. But this could be a big deal too. I'm always needing heals. Do the volume mixer. Yeah, but then
you lose all the audio from the game too. I'm gonna do the heal. They're both six. That's a full heart
from doing it. Where's that menu? If you use a move, is it gone forever? Only this... For me,
yes. Because it will not technically. There's two rooms. If I press this like I should have pressed
like last round, now in two rooms, this will be ready to be used again. Now, I have to collect...
I almost said claws. I have to collect bones. If I get four bones, I can use this move.
You store them until the end of the round for this character, which then you all go to zero
for all of your abilities. It's complicated. You need to read a book. All right. I think I want
wilds. I could go... I could just do... I need to poop. And then... What the fuck? What the fuck is
that? I didn't heard it. Oh, what? I don't... Okay. It still is three. Fuck me. I should have just used
that. Oh, I'm so fucking... I was so tilted from that last thing. I wasted the Lord. Oh, it's all
right. Check this out. My God. How many? One, two, three. Okay. Here we go. Ready? One, two,
three. Oh, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. Did I have three turns? Okay. I just did a... Hold on.
I did a shitload of stuff there. Should I hit this guy again? Will he die if I... Should I do small or
hit the guy in the middle? Okay. Hold on a second here. Look at all these turns I have.
Give me the coins back. Okay. I could... This is gonna take a much more calculated brain than me.
There's bone, bone, bone. I could do a lot of bones here. I could move this over. So I could have
one, two, three. No, I could do five bones with a wild. Could I do seven? I could do
two. No, I could do one, two, three, four. Teeth for the heel. Oh, man. Okay. I could do seven bones.
Couldn't I? It'd have to be very strategic because it would have to be make this a wild,
make this a wild, which would be one, two, three, four, five, six. If I go like that,
if I move over here and then I go down, down, and then make it a wild. Change this to a wild.
But let's go. Still, still not doing so well. Okay. I need teeth now. How many teeth can I do?
I could do one, two, three. I do five because if I do this, I can do the one on the right. Can I do...
Wait, I can... No, no, no. I can do one of that. I could do... Move this down and then move one to
the right. Go up. I need another wild. Shit, yeah. I could still do five or six because if I go over
here, that means bring the one on the right up, bring the one on the left down. Wild on the left.
Do I have enough time to do this? Wild on the left? I don't have enough time to do this. I thought I
had one more move. Fuck. I thought I had another move. Wacky. I know. I'm just trying to set this
up for success. Who am I whacking though? Guy on the right or guy in the middle? Guy in the middle.
Streamer doesn't read chat. Yes, he does. And then let's get rid of you. Actually, go right in the
middle. Uh, no. Right in the middle. Why do you... What happened? What happened? I can't swing because
you're in the... He's in the air. Oh, what have I done with this one? Okay. I can kill this though
and then I can heal. There's nobody attacking me right now, so let's just do what I was going
to do before, which is wild. Bring this down. I'll whip it at you. Insta-dead. Just kidding.
Heal a full heart. Good. This is Candy Crush with extra steps and it was made by Edmund McMillan.
I think I'm being stupid. Am I being stupid here? Wait. Uh, get the wild and then
put it here. That's not going to work. Uh, put... Move this down and then move this down and do that.
I don't know. Backseat. Backseat. Yeah. I mean, what is the nature of these games? You only have
two moves. Yeah. So I have to... You still have three... Yeah. I still have three moves. That
move... That's good at the very end. All right. I'm going to do... Let's do Booger and P. That's a
good one. So if I go down like this and then bring it down like that... No. Oh man. I get so... I
second guess everything I do in these games because even if there's like five ways to do it,
I will figure out somehow the sixth way that's the wrong way to do it. It just happens every time.
Uh, I'm going to go for this. I think. I think. I don't know. I haven't figured it out yet. I'm
still trying to figure that out. How about down from here? No. Let's go like this. Dumb this up,
which will then allow me to go like this, which will then allow me to change something else into
a wild. I could have two wilds somewhere over here. And where do I want those? How about...
I only have one move left. I have to kill... I have to kill this thing.
The dude right there and just throw the bone at him. But that's not going to kill it though.
I could whack it too. Okay. There's a heart scenario. I've got one more move to do. Let's
just... I mean, that's not going to help, but let me set up a super move for next round.
It's the first time we've seen that. Cool. Let's do a heart while out there. Right? No. Yeah.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I need to bring you... fuck. Okay. Up, up, up, up. Can I do this?
I need to get P. Okay. We're going to do P, wild, and then... fuck me. Bring this up? No. Bring this
up. Okay. Am I doing it right? I hope so. I am. Wait, don't use this yet. What if I get hit?
Make a seven heart stack. Hold on. Wait a second. Just don't get hit. It'll be stunned for an extra
turn. But what... Okay. What can I make? What happens if you do seven hearts? Do you get a
permanent full heart? Do you get a soul heart? Because I would only need two more, which I could
maybe do P's. That's a soul heart? Oh. That's not really worth it. I mean, they're like,
it's not worth it. Seven hearts stack. There's a two-way poop right here. Does that work?
Try to get the seven hearts. They're worth it? Well, I'm just gonna make this a wild then,
and then see if we can make it happen. Do the two-way poop. But no, that two-way don't work.
Uh, let's see. Can I get some more wilds here? I don't think so. That's... I don't... I think
seven hearts is going to be kind of out of reach. Yeah. It's going to take too long because there's
only three P's on the board. I can't... I'll just do seven poop and then I'm just going to heal.
Oh, fuck it. Let's just do it now. Who cares? All right. Let's set up a good bone scenario.
It looks pretty good. Don't look behind you. Munker. You can miss in this game. Oh,
because he went up right... Wait, let's make it a good end. Have we seen these enemies yet? I don't
think so. This might be the first time. So, hmm. P. I'm going to do P. Get a wild in this scenario.
Down wild. Uh, these guys have a lot of health too. I'm going to go poo on the left. Then I'm
going to do... Let's set up teeth for next round, dude. One, two, three. One, two, three. I guess.
Whatever. Let's do three down. One, two. I just need a... I just need a P. If I do one, two, three,
and then one, two, three, I could kill them all potentially. Fuck it. Let's go for it. Sometimes
you got to do the big play. All right. Then up, down, and then we got one move. Um, let's go.
There's seven right there. See if this does anything. Oh, fuck. I did not know that was
going to happen. Uh... Well, nobody's attacking. What do I destroy? I don't think I want to destroy
anything. Nobody's going to move. And let's go... Yeah, green doesn't hurt you unless you attack.
So I need to wait. I could do some wilds. I think that's a good idea. Up or down? Probably,
yeah, up because I want the bone. Uh, wild for poo. Or just stick a wild on the board. Who cares,
right? Yeah, just stick a wild on the board. Right here. Whatever. Fuck. Right here. Whatever.
All right. This should be the boss, right? Loose change. Gain coins equals to next damage. What
the fuck does that mean? Gain coins equals to next damage taken. So gain...
Rudolph's a real... This one's interesting. I like that one. That seems cool. That's one coin for
every damage you take. So like one, two, three, four. Let's just do the D12. Bumble versus Gibbs.
Heavy hits are best. Let's go. Ah, heavy hits are best. What the hell does this jello cube even do?
I could do poo just to get it out and make sure I get some safety here.
One, two, three. One, two, three. Should I set up a... I'm gonna set up a huge poo, I think.
How much time do I got? Enough, right? I don't know. Yeah, I'm doing it. Now. Hold on. All right.
This is important. Ready? One, two. There's my wild. Bring this down. Let's do it. Super poop.
And I can slow you down. So I'm protected, but I need to do big hits.
Reroll a row of tiles. Which row? Seven bone or super tooth? I'm probably gonna say bones.
Just reroll the whole top row. No, I got a wild here now though. I'm thinking drag this over here
and be able to bring it down. Second top row reroll. I could... But I can make a...
This is... Right now I can just throw a tooth at him. If I do this, then I can set up... Let me try
this. Yeah, this is the one right here. Check this out. Because I'm gonna go... Next round,
I'm gonna go bang, bang. Drag this down. Seven bone. I don't want to reroll anything right now.
Let's do it. Kill. Oh, but he's dead. That was... He was just kind of a big piece of meat. I wonder
what he does if you leave him alone. More brown tiles. Damn it. Now having me reroll that thing
is a bad idea. Me having the stupid bones for the smash, it could have been... Reroll it again.
I could. It raises crit chance, but how much does that mean? More poo for more hammer. No,
the hammer is bones now. Remember? I know, but my whack is for bones. Remember I rerolled it?
Crit. I'm taking the crit. Okay, what do we got? Reroll the spell. Reroll spell cost.
Spell cost less. Reroll spell cost. On this one, you mean to try to get boogers?
But what if it's... Fuck you.
I'm gonna do spell cost less on wild, I think, because that's just been such a...
It's the only thing that's gonna keep this together. On the heal, you think?
Maybe. I'm thinking the wilds, if I could place like... Because if I do one match,
I could place two wilds instead of one. That's the play. Spin the wheel. Movement.
Now, should I reroll the spell? Yeah, I don't... I don't care about this. I really don't. I would
much rather have anything else. Wait, this is an item. I can reroll boats as I can. Pick a spell
to modify? Is this not blocked out? I don't even know what the... What was that? More bones. I don't
even know what it was. Well, this is the run here. We're gonna try. This is the... This is the third
room, third area. Six bones. Halls of Belial. Come on, my build's terrible. Can you mute the
game audio so I can take samples of you saying those bad words? Gain mana equals to most common
tile. Let's do some P. Okay, I got two wilds I can put out here now. That's a big deal. So,
super booger, I can do bang, bang, and then go up. Yep. Right? And then, fuck. Go up. Wild,
go up. Bring the wave. All frozen for two turns. Let's do another wild on... I'm gonna say bones.
We're looking for bones, so let's destroy some shit. Try to make room for bones. Not bad. Pretty
good. Okay. Not bad. Really not bad at all. Let's make this a wild. No, no. What's the best way to
do this? Drag this over one. Might be hard to do this. So, I need to do three. One, two, three.
I'm gonna have to move these around because I... I'm gonna make four every time I move it.
I can only make one. If I make one a wild, it'll just close it. So, this has to be the wild.
So, that would be one, two, three, four, five, six. Yeah, I'm gonna... it's not gonna be good.
Move the left one down. Okay, so I moved the left one down. That would be... and then one, two, three,
four. Now, if I move that left one down, then this is a wild. It'll complete it. Move the bone on the
right away. So, if I move this out of the way, then that means I got one, two, three. All right. Yeah,
that's the play. So, the play is get this one out of the way, make this a wild, move this up,
move this down, kill him. Sounds like it. Hope I'm right. So, move this up, move this up,
move this down, kill him. Holy shit, I just got a double combo. I did. And gain mana to most common
tile. Just whack. Because it's not... is it bones? It's not bones, is it? Because I could probably...
I don't know, I could kill this stuff right now. Let's whack. Spell resistant. Fuck. All right,
hold on. This is not a bad... this is not terrible because we... I'm just gonna make more and more
bones or teeth or whatever. Look at that. Lots of bones now. Let's go. All right. One, two, three.
If I go this way. All right, here we go. One, two, three. And then one, two... uh, one, two,
I think. I'm just gonna tap the next round. Because this can come over here and make three.
Yep. So, I'll make three and then bring the... yeah, let's go. So, that makes one... oh shit,
in my pants. What happened? One... okay, we're good. Just do bones. Gain gray mana or blinding
attack. Gray mana. Which is great. That's bones? Is it teeth? So, I could infinite heal, potentially.
It's teeth, okay. I think that's better than this. Rerolls a row of tiles. This one sucks.
That's too much. I could heal. I can't... there's enough scenario where I would rather whack than
use this. All right, I gotta... let me get... let me beat the boss here. Let me at least get to the
end of this damn game. Or at least this area. All right. Three moves. I need some pee here.
What should I do? Setting it up. All right. Let's go. Look at how many wilds I'm gonna have.
Three wilds in a row. And I can move five times. Bones. All right, so we've got wild here. No,
I can move this down. No, hold on. Let me think about this. If I move this over, I could do
one, two, three. One, two, three, and then up. Right? Let's go. Oh, fucking hell yeah. Look at
this. I can just move and do it. I don't need the wilds. All right, I'm in a good position. This is
not a bad... now I can whack away. Can I kill you? Are you dead? Hold on. Yeah, let me kill you first
because you're the threat. And then that means I got one thing left to... I don't have any more
moves, but can I just end it right here? Yeah. All right, I'm gonna end it next turn. Did I get
further? This is as far as I've ever forgotten. Uh-oh. So I'm assuming the... that means I cannot
attack them, right? Yeah, I made it to the boss. Oh yeah, I did make it to the boss. You're right.
Okay. So I cannot... I have to hurt these guys with spells. It's gonna be a pain in the ass.
Does the big summoning bone... seven bone move count as a spell? Or do I have to kill them
with the whack? I wonder. No, it doesn't. Okay. Well, maybe I should just try to freeze everybody
right off the bat. So I could go like this. Set up a... yeah, let's set it up. So then I can bring
this down. One, two, three. No, wait, wait, wait, wait. Don't hold on a second. Don't mess this up.
I want to get a big wave of goo. Because I want to freeze everybody. So if I bring this down,
that's three. Up, up. I need to... I hope I'm doing this right. Shit. Oh god. Oh god, oh god, oh god,
oh god, oh god, oh god. I might have to cancel this plan. It's possible. I gotta... it's possible next
turn. I only have one fucking move though. What? One move? No! That sucks. I can do it all next
turn and then... no, I can't. Can I? I'm in trouble. It's okay. It's only one heart. Oh no! What?
What was that? I'm dead. I ha... this is my only opportunity. I just... everyone has to be frozen
and then hopefully I can make something happen. I hope this works. Oh no. I'm so disappointed. That...
that's so... that's so hard. I'm almost dead. Ah, I shouldn't have even tried to build the big one,
but as a play... eee. It's okay. I'm gonna try to get bones. This is not gonna touch any bones, right?
No? Okay. Holy shit. Are you kidding me? This is it. Game over. Yeah, it's game over. It is, right?
Is there any scenario where I can live? Maybe. If I bring this down here,
poop up the right side, get a bone, kill the rights... uh, I think it's over. Do poop for the
rerolls. Where do I put this though? On the right? Reroll a row of tiles, but which row?
I could do P, but that's not gonna be enough. What really ha... I got screwed here trying to
reroll this into the green one. That was the big mistake. Do the third row. One, two, three,
try to reroll this whole thing. Bone and then whack. Yeah, but I still... I'm gonna... I take it...
I take damage. There's no way I don't take damage. Try to roll for a poop. Reroll all the rows.
That's just like throwing dice in the air. I don't think that's gonna happen.
If only I had another move, I might be okay. Whatever. Let me see. Hold on. Cancel this.
Here's the only... here's the play that I see. The play that I see is try to... can I... is there a...
no, there's no way I can do it. Fuck. I'm so sad. I'm so sad right now. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait. Wait a second. Hold on. Hold on. Everybody wait. Don't move. I can heal, but I
need to... can I gain... oh wait. Hold on. I can heal a full heart. If I use this six times, I can
heal a full heart. Because this is only a half heart. Wild to heal, but then... yeah, but then
it's only half a heart. I die. I'm gonna hit three times. Wait, maybe not. Let me try it. Let's see.
Let's go for it. Fuck it. Here we go. Now rip. No, I didn't even know I had this up there. It
don't matter. Fuck it. It's fine. Everything's fine. We're gonna be fine. I'm gonna do this.
It don't matter. Whatever. It's okay. Well, I'm up against the goddamn wall anyways with like a
toothpick versus a wild bear. I'm up against the wall. Let's try to booger him. Wait. Not yet.
Bring this down. Oh, fuck you. I actually might not die. God damn it. If only I had done that
first. How am I supposed to know? They move twice in one turn. Yeah, I'm dead. Well, that was fun.
Well, that's fun while it lasted. Yeah, five hearts before. Yeah, but even still, these guys
move twice. They would have done like five hearts worth of damage. The real killer of this one was
rolling this and rolling it. Not only rolling it once, but rolling it twice and it was bones twice.
That sucked. Hold on. I'm not giving up yet. Hold on. Wait, I can do that next turn. Wait. I'm not
giving up yet. Oh, hold on. One, two, three. I guess I can do one. I can do a super bone,
but that doesn't matter. Does a bone dream exist a little bit, but not really? Wait, maybe it does
because then I can club. Club. I'm still dead. Move bottom row. One, two, three. Okay. If I go
like this, then that's one, two, three. One, two, three. I got two wilds. No, do seven teeth instead
and then heal. Hold on. I can't get seven teeth this round. Can I? No, I can't get seven. Can I
get enough to heal once? I get the two wilds. So if I go like this over, so then that's wild, wild.
I need to squish my eyes for a second. I have seven bones, but that's not going to help me.
I don't want to die. Bottom left row. Yeah, but the seven bones don't hurt these guys.
The seven teeth allows me to get a full heart. If I do seven bones, I could swing twice, right?
I got three wilds. Yeah. Bones let me whack, but bones don't heal me. And if one thing touches me,
I'm dead. Can I do seven twice? I need a defensive combo. Yeah, I need the seven teeth. I've got to
do a defensive combo. I've got to, I've got to do, I've got to bring the hammer down, heal a full heart.
All right, let's go. I'm fucking excited. Here we go. Ready? We got one, two, three,
one, two, three. Bring this one down. Wild in the middle. Wait, don't even have to do this. Wild.
No, don't do that. I don't want to use the moves though, because if I use my moves, then I,
I'm saying wild in the middle here and then over and then down. No, it's like,
wilds are better than the moves. I could do wild here, wild here, and then drag this one in.
I think that's what I'm doing. That's what I'm doing. Wild, wild. Bring this down. If I drop
this one down, then I could, but it's the same thing happens. So I could do there and then wild
in the left, wild in the middle. That'll do it. That's one less move. Yeah, that's true. Okay.
Wait a minute. Okay. Give me, give me the heal. God. Okay. You all thought I was done. Not even
close. You all thought I was dead. But hold on. Wait a second. I still have to worry about this.
Now I do a poo combo in the middle. Poo combo in the middle, then heal.
Yes. Drag down. Wild in the middle. Heal. Bone kill left. I can't kill the one in the left.
That's what I'm doing. If it's wrong, then by God, I don't want to be right. I have another move.
What's the move here? Reroll the, which one though? Top row? Third row. Right here. Top row,
but I lose the heart. Do I really want to lose these hearts to kill the curse? All right. Okay.
I got the heart back. Fuck. Okay. Fuck. I can do, I can sticky. I can do, I can do a sticky.
Sticky on which one is the question. This is tough now. Sticky the one on the left.
Right. What do you got now? What am I destroying? What do I need to do? I got a seven bone scenario
coming up, but it don't matter. But it does matter. Seven bone scenario is increasing odds
here, but I don't want to do that. I want to whack, which reroll something else. Hop out,
reroll the top row. The second row. Oh, reroll second row. Destroy two, three. What a good idea
that was from that person that said that. Now what? I can't do seven bones. It's not possible.
I can't do eight bones. I can do bones twice. Okay. Now destroy two, three. No, no, no, no,
no, no, no. That's not a good idea. Destroy the teeth. Talk about like up here. I fucked it up.
How did I fuck it up? What are you talking about? Destroy this one here is what I'm thinking.
I've got nine bones. Destroy one bone. I don't know what to do. I don't know.
This poop gets rid of this bone. All right. This poop gets rid of this bone. No, this one
gets rid of this bone. It doesn't get rid of this one, right? Break the first bone on the left.
I don't think that is that a good idea? This one, he won't break this one. Why? Middle tooth
gives you four bones. Do not. You guys, I'm trying. There's a lot of knowledge in this chat
lying around. Three, one, get this one here. Sure. But okay, then I would bring,
I guess that's correct. Is that correct? Why did you make me do that? Oh, thank God. You're smart.
And then I'm going to get a double. Oh, baby. Here it comes. Next turn. I am going, no, not
reroll the top row. Don't you freaking me out. I'm going to go up here, get this extra turn and the
bones. Good. I'm just going to go. We're done. I'm not going to reroll the second row because then
I don't want to lose this. But wait, hold on. I only have two turns. Think about the order.
Other one first. This is going to complete that. It'll, what do you mean other one first?
Yeah, this, that's what I'm doing. But I know left first. I'm not doing right first.
I'm doing the seven. I'm not going to do the right one first. That'll make four.
Okay. I got two swings. Oh no. What do I do? Kill the one. This is three damage. I can kill one of
them. I'm going to kill the one on the right first. Oh my fucking God. I just got a crit.
Give me two crits. Give me two crits and we'll go. We're good. My God. I can't believe it. Did
we just do it? I think we actually just did it. Don't fuck it up. Did I do it wrong? Wild. Two
wilds. Okay. We're going to do bone. I win. I win. It's over. I win. No, no, no. Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait. Okay. No, we're fine. Everything's good. Everything's fine. No, everything's okay.
Kill, kill them before I do anything. Now I can do, I can heal. Let's heal. Two wilds.
Bang, bang. That lets me heal. I think that's the fucking idea here. Wait, wild the hearts.
Only one wild necessary for the hearts. You're talking about, talking about, talking about.
What are you talking about here? Talking about going like this. What do you mean? Teeth heal.
What? Get hearts. There's a whole cafeteria of people screaming different scenarios at me
and I have my own scenarios, but we have to, you guys are doing a great job helping me. I love it.
I only have one wild, so not two wilds. So therefore we're going to do the teeth because
I can wild this, bring this up, which then that means I can use this. But it was, does that work?
Do poop because then I can just get mana. You mean play safe and make a poop poops. Three,
one poop, three, two wild. I got to, I got to like turn this music off. It's like stressful music.
It's hard for me to even think. Four, two wild, make a poop. Four, two wild. So you want me to
go right here with a wild and then drag this guy over and make a poop and drop it. And then
I'm rerolling. I don't even know the fuck I want to reroll. Make a tooth. Reroll number four. Tooth
and heal. Good play. Now reroll. Bottom row. Reason. Get ready for next row. In fact, delete
teeth for the bone. I need bones. You're right. I just like burped. Okay. I'm good. I got, I did it.
Game over. I win. I can't believe I have full health right now. Holy shit. I can't believe,
I can't believe, I'm going to say I did that, but it was like 21, 22% me, like 81% you.
Like it's 78%. You gain a soul heart. That's pretty good. Reroll next row of tiles.
I didn't even do anything. Pog jam. Yeah. I want the soul heart. I don't, I don't want this. This is
it. Bumbo versus Gizarda. She's, I got full health. Cannot do spells by the way. Very important to
know. Can only beat this with attacks. So I can do, we can do a big goop here. Get a seven bone
lined up. All right. Let me first, let's go up and then let's just goop. I'm not, I don't,
you know, what a fucking don't, don't even need seven boogers. It doesn't, it does the same damn
thing. It's two always. All right. Now we need bones. Let's start destroying shit for bones.
Looking pretty good. Now. Oh, fuck. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Big crits. All right. Let's not get cocky
here. Uh, I'm going to say just tooth it up. What the fuck does this mean? Uh, yeah. Uh, yeah. Oh,
man. Oh, man. Oh, man. Okay. Game over. I went whack. What? Oh shit. No, it's okay.
Oh no. I got two whacks. He thought he had me. Bang. I got a little too cocky. I didn't realize
it spun around in one hell of a thing. Weird box in back of room. What in there? Another
Bumble. Bumble the weird has been unlocked. Did I beat it? Three levels? I didn't see another
unlock. Maybe I have to beat the game like 10 times or something. All right. Let's see Bumble
the weird. When they kill, they gain movement. Magic marker adds more of a selected tile. That's
awesome. Removes tiles and throws them. Puzzle flick. You have to beat the game with Bumble
the weird. Beat the game with Bumble the weird. Let's go for it. Yeah, let's do it. I like it.
Wouldn't you guys help me do this game? It's fun. Options menu. Where did I see this options menu?
I swear. Is it the main menu? Can I get back to the main menu from here? It's before character
select though. I guess I can just quit, right? There was a bad bug in the sound setting, so they
had to take it up before release. This is going to be hard. Let's new game. Okay. Options. There
you go. All right. Epic chill step collection. Whoops. Reset progress. Animal crossing. Yeah,
I hate this. Animal crossing. We always go back to animal crossing though, don't we?
It's always animal crossing. Every time. No, not Katamari. Put on sea shanties.
Super Mario Brothers Super Show intro in every language. Put on Sims music. How about roller
coaster tycoon 2 building music? Or was it zoom out music? There we go. All right. What we got?
Removes tiles and throws them. I wonder how much damage that does. I didn't mean to do that. That
was my bad. Already fucked it up. Might as well reset and reset all progress. Reset all progress.
This is really loud for me. Why? All right, let's go. Bumble the weird. Let's unlock the
final game's mystery. Puzzle. Fuck. Puzzle. Fuck. Puzzle. I'm too old for that. Square. Okay. This
time we're just going tooth or poop. Right there. Right down the middle. That's a good idea. And
then we're going to go. I think we're going to move this up and prepare for a big one.
What do you think? Sounds pretty good idea. Thanks, man. This is three damage, but what?
Could just take out the middle. Why am I not? So they don't attack me and kill me.
Adds more of a selected tile. Oh, what's that? We're going to pick bone. Hey, look at that.
Ooh. Don't fuck it up. Um, that looks kind of good to me. What do I care though? Wait.
I screwed it up. This music is chilling me out too much.
Removes tiles and throws them. Wait, I'm getting moves. Every time I throw something, do I move?
Which tile do I want to throw? The poo? Oh my God. How many times do I get to do this?
Move on kill. Right. Holy shit. This is an awesome character. Oh my God. Move on kill one.
This character is ridiculous. How do you lose with this character?
That's so powerful. Oh, music's gone. Sorry. Uh, how about
Metroid? Relaxing and ambient music from Metroid.
Blocks the next two attacks. Move a tile row one to the right or blocks the next two attacks.
The buzz looks pretty crazy. Booger sink. That's a good idea.
Okay. We just need to kill one. So I'm thinking tooth. No, hold on. Yeah, let's get tooth.
This should lead us into a...
adds more of a selected tile. We're going to go with, uh, we're going to go with, uh, bones. Okay.
Keep up the killing spree. And we got to do it again. Removes a tile. So let's get rid of this one
and throw it this way. What are you going to do, huh?
What a room full of shitty enemies. I don't want to get too cocky.
That's pretty much it. I can do... no, I can do this. Play Half-Life music in honor of Half-Life VR.
I could, but will I? No. Just add more hearts. Yeah, I mean, this is kind of doing well for me now.
Turn one kill. I feel like, um, Bumbo the Weird might little, little bit of extra tuning.
Seems, uh, very, very, very, very good. So what's with these rooms? Is this
designed around just a bunch of random enemies in a room? Okay, let me go. Okay, I'm ready for
another one. Um, I kind of want to do... let's throw out... what do I want to throw out? This one here.
Yep, check it. And then that allows me to... like this. First turn. You never get a chance.
You're not going to get a single chance. Although, wait a minute. Maybe you do get a chance.
Do I have a four? I could do that. Move a tile to the right. It's... hold on. This is possible for me
to do this. Because now I can just move to the right. Uh, how many times am I going to do this?
Four times. So move a tile to the right. We're gonna do...
Let's get some bones. Um, now we're gonna remove the... this one and kill you. I think that's...
no, I'm not done. What happened? What do you mean miss? I... it's because I clicked in the wrong
section or something. What the fuck was that? I'm just kind of dumb. Whatever. Uh,
I've ruined it. Yeah, I guess if you miss click in the wrong row, you just throws it down the...
I guess. Okay, whatever. Oh, let's go this way. Yeah, that's... whatever. You can... that'll care.
One, two, three. Middle is empty. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. Charges random usable item.
Copies spell at random. These both suck. Bumbo versus peeper. All right, let's just pick a tile
to throw. Well, you made that easy for me. Now let's go like this. This is gonna be beautiful.
Add more to select the tile. We're gonna go with wilds. Bug. Removes the tile. We're gonna remove...
What should we remove? Uh, probably this here. Go again. And now we can do the sticky. We can do
actually a big sticky. You ain't going anywhere. Move a tile one row to the right. Well,
if you ask, I'll do it. Eyes? What about the eyes? They're not even gonna get a chance.
This dude's dead. I can move to the right and I would get... uh, no, should I do? What should
I do? Move what to the right? I can do it four times. One, two, three, four. Is that gonna help?
What should I move? The teeth. Row... the second row? Third and fourth rows? Oh, would you look at
that? We're just gonna keep going. I'm gonna remove this booger. Dead. That was turn one.
Items are on sale. 50% off. That's like automatic. That's an automatic click.
All right. What do we got? Spell cost? Spell hurts more. This has a question mark around it, but
can I actually increase this? Or is this a waste? It doesn't... it doesn't work. It's broken. Don't.
It's not worth it. No. It's a scam. Okay. Um, reroll spell. I could reroll this. Try to get
something better because this thing sucks. Um, that's insane. Plus one movement. I could, uh,
should I reroll its cost from poop? No, I need a poop sink, don't I? No, I need a poop sink. Spell
hurts more. That's fine. We'll keep that the way it is. Let's roll it. What do the puzzle pieces
mean? More spell damage? That's really good too. All right. Give me a hand on this one.
More yellow tiles. I need this one. This one's, that's huge. This is like, I'm guaranteed to win
if I get it. If I get this, this is, there's no way I lose again. Left? This is too important. I need
to pull. Yeah, it's way too important. I'm sorry. Because this is a guaranteed absolute 100%. There's
no way I lose. Okay. Give me a hint. It's random? I know, but I don't want it to be my fault.
Most people are saying left or middle. I would probably have said,
I'm not going to tell you because I don't want it to be my fault. All right. Number one is left.
Uh, but I'm going to go with right because it's the least. God damn it. Which one was it?
Now it is my fault.
Should I reroll the spells cost on one of these? What if I reroll this and it's like a two?
Oh, whatever. Koala brain. Yeah, I know. Yeah. I figured that would have been such like a pog
moment. No, for me. Sorry. We don't need it. We don't need it. We don't need it. We're just
going to kill the thing. How many, what do I got? I got three moves. Let's get a bone in here.
Toss it right up the left side. And then we're going to do, got another move left here. We're
going to do, uh, let's see. I wonder what I want to do with this one. I think we're going to probably
do, uh, anybody see anything? Anybody see anything? I could line up a pretty good, uh,
set up for a yellow, um, I could do teeth and set up teeth. Uh, okay. This thing's going to
explode on me. Okay. I need teeth and I can remove. I know here we go. I'm going to go like this,
which will be, no, no. What are you an imbecile? Are you dumb? Poop is movement. Yeah. Yep. Fuck.
Yep. Oh, hold on. That's actually not that good. Okay. I'm going to slow down here.
I have a shit load of teeth. Three, three. I could do seven teeth and I can kill the fly.
It fucking hurts. Okay. Then I'm going to, I gotta kill this other fly. It's screwing me up.
Get rid of this, uh, bone. No, which, how do I make this better?
Get rid of this bone, right? Give her to the booger right here. Booger, booger, booger, booger,
booger, booger, booger, booger, booger, booger, booger. Give her to this P. Give her to this booger.
Give her to the P at the top. Give her to the booger. Give her to the P.
Get her ready to do the poop first. Okay. All right. Okay. Then we can do, we can do the
one movement. Booger. Remove this tile. Bingo. Oh, what's that? Now, oh, I can move. Let's move
the tiles now. Don't waste any moves. Why don't I just go like this and then go like this again.
Get the bone, get my extra turn. Now I can remove this tile here, this tooth,
because who gives a shit? Bingo. Throw it. We're dead. No, you're not. I fucking hate this game.
I hate it. Okay. I messed up. He's so moody. I need teeth. I'm out of hearts though. This is
actually not good. Let's go. I'm an idiot. Oh, right. I don't lose it between turns.
I forgot. Different character. Explode. Make the hearts. Oh yeah. Fuck. I'm too busy.
Splash back attack. Attacking enemies. Attacking enemies take damage or splash back. I can't even
heal anyways. I think the splash back is the one. This is a lot of enemies. This is a lot. Okay. I
can't really fuck around now. I only have one heart. I could set up a huge poop. This is what
I'm going to do. And then we're going to do a teeth setup. So let's see, what's the best way to do this?
There's like a bunch of ways I could probably do this. You go this way. Go one, two, fuck no.
Do seven bones instead. I actually, I need the seven. I need to do the stomp. If I get one,
two, three, one, two, three, four, five, six, move this one down. Bone at the top. Um,
bones are good too. Yeah, I know, but I have a lot of teeth. And then if I go like this,
move you up. Wait. Okay. Yeah. I do with the poop shields. It's right. This should do it now.
All right. So we got seven here. Okay. They're all dead. Good. Cool. Okay. Bones.
Let's go right down the middle. I'm doing it again because you can only take damage from this shit.
Right. Let's get a poop on the left side. Yeah. And that allows me to add a movement and I can
make more tiles and you know what we're doing. I mean, obviously teeth. So I could go one, two,
grab it. I could do a big one here. Three. Oh yeah. Okay. Here we go. Let's set it up. It's
not going to kill that, but it'll kill these things. Okay. Bring it down. It did kill. Wait,
why did it kill that? Why did it kill the one that has, Oh, cause that's not magic.
Reduce the cost of your spells or flips a row of tiles. This one. That means I can just do the
more often. All right. Second boss Bumble versus Gibbs. This thing was kind of shitty, but I don't
want to get cocky. I'm trying to use this. No, not yet. All right. Oh, what do I want to do? Big,
big moves, big moves, big moves. Oh, that's extra more tiles bones. All right. Bingo. Good game.
Hey, what do you know? Splash back attack. That was came in pretty useful. I guess
may gain movement or enemies may take damage moving. Probably the battery, right? Okay. 21.
What do we got? The spell costs less. Which one remove tile and throw or add more of a selected
tile? Probably this one, the movement one with the piss. This is very difficult. This one are you,
but I can only do this once. I think it's this one. That'll be two, man. The marker.
Imagine how many times I'd be able to use this probably twice in one turn.
It'd be two and three. It'd be two and three. Okay. We're going to go marker. Spell hurts more.
Not worth it. Re-roll the spell. Splash back, but I'm going to use bones for this. It's too expensive.
Well, I'm going to get one of them. Spell hurt more on one. I thought that was, I thought I
couldn't do that. All right. Puzzle damage up. Oh, fuck. Are we certain that this doesn't work?
That's really good. I just, I'm just going to do it to splash back then.
Why would I not going to re-roll the spell? What just happened? How many times has that happened?
Okay. That's the third time in a row that I've re-rolled something into the same number that
it was already. Damn it. How is that even possible? One coin. Let's go. See if I can beat this.
You increase the damage, not re-rolled. Oh, but why does it still say two?
That's because I re-rolled the damage to two. Damage went from two to two.
All right. This is important. This is the one I got to win. We need better music than this.
Something a little more upbeat, but not too upbeat that I'm going to get nervous.
Insane aquarium OST. No, that'll drive people crazy. WWE entrance music. I like it. Okay. WWF
entrance music. These are, well, no, these are all the VODs. Yeah, this is bad. I can't do that.
Goodbye VOD viewers. I can't do that. Binding of Isaac OST.
Kata Mario. We just did that two days in a row. Not Banjo Kazooie. Metal Slug? Now that's one.
Metal Slug OST. Good choice. All right. Move one. We're going to throw. We're going to do,
I say we're going to go up with the, I don't know. I have no idea. Can you play for me?
What? Wait, what? Was this me going like what? Turn on the clicks? No, no, no, no.
Here we go. Watch this. This is, might be a, this might be a poor decision, but I'm going for it.
I don't care. Don't fuck it up. I want the more tiles because we're going to do
teeth. Set us up. It's set up and I get to drop poop right here. Oh, what's that? Look at me.
That's fine. All right. Now bone. Uh, yeah. Bone into, or should I slow?
Maybe I'll drop a poo over here just to be safe. I've looked at how many moves I have. Holy fuck.
Uh, I can't, I have to kill you with the spell. So let me get some bones and some teeth. I just
need bones and that's, I mean, I can't even hurt you. So let's throw a puzzle at you. Let's get
rid of, uh, over here. There you go. Now I kind of just have to wait until you open. Uh, should I
just, oh, how am I supposed to do? Okay. Add more, um, bones or teeth. Okay. Now just set up seven,
just set up seven of them. I can take as long as I want. Set up seven hearts. I can't do that.
Do hearts instead. I'm actually wondering if we should just farm hearts right now.
All right. Well, I can't, I'm, no, I can't. He's dead. Use the marker, but I, I, next time.
Poopy morph attack or gain gray mana. This is, wait, this is not even original metal slug.
Where's metal, where's original metal slug? Oh, this is like a compilation. All right. Look,
this is original metal slug is right here. There we go. Okay. Here's original metal slug. Okay. Um,
I wonder which one of these is even worth doing. Poop, maybe the poopy morph attack and take it.
No, but what do I want to get rid of? I just upgraded this, didn't I? No, I didn't.
Get rid of splashback. I don't think I'm taking it. No, how should I not take anything?
Splashback might be good later. No, I'm not going to take it. How do I just get out of this?
I don't think I can leave. I can't cancel. I'll replace splashback. That's a little too much
because I'm going to be using it for tiles. What are these guys? I don't know what these guys do.
Okay. We're looking for, first of all, very important, get the P. What do I want more of?
They have a double move. All right. Let's do poo then. Right down the middle.
And then let's get, I want to add more bones.
Fuck. Didn't want to do that. Didn't want that to happen. Oh, fuck. Maybe I did. Ooh.
Play this whole row. Another move. This is four damage. All right. Keep clearing it.
I'm all right with this. Can I kill this guy without doing anything? Let's see if I can kill
him. Okay. Let's add more teeth. That should be enough to at least move a little bit.
Get rid of the boogers. Beat him with a zero. Remove boogers now. All right.
Okay. This is a lot. I need to slow down. I have way too many teeth. Three. If I move,
I'm just going to keep this rolling. All right. Now I'm going to get hearts.
Do poopy mouth. Not yet. I'm just going to keep killing shit. Okay. Hearts. Now let's do tile
remove on this one on the bone. No, let's do this one. Just whip it right down the middle
and then do it again. I'm going to do it to this. I don't have any idea what I'm doing right now.
How about the poop over here or the bone? Okay. I don't know. All right. One, two, three, four,
five, six, seven hearts. Seven of them. Don't screw it up. This needs to move. This needs to move.
Oh, hold on. I, I, this is wrong for me. How do I get this to be right? Uh, it's, it's almost,
it's close. Kind of. Just take your time. Okay. And then this is going to come over here.
I'm just going to take my time. Yeah. I only take my time. Now why do I have one move? Okay.
Now this is, I need three over here. So move you here and then it's close. So now I go up,
up, up, and then I can move that one to the left. One more on the bottom. What do you mean?
Move wild to the middle with the spell. I see you Sam. There we go. All of this just to get an
extra soul heart. I hope it was worth it. Here we go. Cool. Cool. All right. Now, uh, whatever. Just
got to hit it once. Another move. I just need to kill it. Just who cares? No, I want to try and
bring this up. Dead. All right. Now I have two hearts. I think I have one more room and then
that's the boss after this. I already have a good scenario here for a, I got already. Already.
Bring this one down. Bring this one down. Already. I can fucking care less. Whatever you guys do.
Good night. And hell yeah. All right. Don't blow it. Destroy a row of tiles or plus three movement
and a random mana. That's the one. Yeah. I, what do I replace it? I'm going to, yeah. The heart's gone.
Why is the heart gone? What happened to the heart? They exploded? No, it was the fly.
All right. We'll have a mega battery and I'm going to, we're going to just get rid of the pot.
Put the morph attack. That's it. All right. Bumbo versus pyre matching specific color tiles is the
key. All right. I need to match yellow battery right off the bat. I think I'm doing battery
both these right off the bat. Okay. I have a lot of time to think about this. So we need to do
yellow tiles. Do seven P. Is that possible right now? I could go here. This is going to
take a lot of movement here. No, I'm not going to go for it. We're just going to do one, two.
Now what? Now is he hurt? Add more of his, all right. Is this, is this teeth? Okay. Um, hold on.
Now he's hurt. Teeth. How many teeth do I have? Seven teeth. Let's go. I can do one, two, three,
one, two, three. No, hold on. Do this first. Okay. Okay. Crush him. Ooh, that one stings.
All right. Hold on. More of what? Poop? More boogers, more bones. Hold on because I need to
make sure I'm protected. If I get hit once or twice, I'm dead. Bones. Okay. All right. Let's do it.
Not a great position, but it's enough for me to at least, let's see,
if I go, I'm going to have to do one and then can I do seven? Can I? I have two moves. Okay. I could
do bang, bang. Is that enough? This down, down. This is it? No, it's not. Use the spell to move
it once. Down, down. That's it. Where is it?
That character is really powerful.
Trap door under Bumbo. What do you think? More bigger coin? More better trash?
Even more bigger coin? That reminds me of Azazel. Original Azazel.
And the basement has been unlocked. The trap door. Let me see. Did I unlock anybody else?
Bumble the brave. Bumble the nimble. Bumble the stout. Bumble the weird.
Beat the game with the weird. How come I don't get this character? Do I have to beat it with
the fourth floor? You didn't beat the basement with Bumble the weird. You just moved the goalpost
forward. Hurry up and speed run it. There's a door there now? Yeah. So did I just do the
equivalent of you beat mom like five times or whatever? And now the video game starts?
Yeah, that's fucking awesome. That's cool. Only 20 more times did you get the real ending.
Except it's not that much more content yet. I think it's fun. Does it have the staying power
or something like Binding of Isaac? Probably not, but it is a cool little game. He hates it? No,
I think it's great. I don't think I'm gonna do... I mean, I would probably play this.
It's early access? Are you sure? It's not early access. No, this is released. This is definitely
one of those games that you just kind of play when you're just chilling like we've done today.
I would play the fuck out of this on my iPad. Oh, I would too. I mean, that's coming. That's coming
soon. Soon as in who knows how long that'll take. I know it's supposed to be coming on the Switch
or something, but I think it was pretty good. Yeah, that's another thing. Another really important
thing to remember about this game. When Binding of Isaac released just 1.0, it didn't have the
thousand plus items that are in it now. I'm sure that over the years there'll probably be at least
a couple of major additions to it. It was on Newgrounds in 2008 with two floors. Yeah,
I think it's great. I think it's 13... it's like 14 bucks. I think it's worth your time, but this
isn't a free game on Newgrounds. No, I think it's worth it. I think it's worth like the 13, 14 dollars.
I mean, I've been playing this game for over five hours now and it's...
there's still more to do. It's still... it's a game that you're just supposed to play through
like 30, 40 times in a row. We'll see. But you didn't. Well, not yet. It's got bad Steam reviews.
It's kind of mixed, I guess. People are mad about the bugs that were there last week.
I mean, that's completely understandable. If the game crashes in the middle of your run,
that's kind of... that sucks. But once they patch it a bunch of times and it's the game that
kind of, I guess, should have released a week or a half ago or so, a week ago.
I would say if you want to wait till... I mean, it's 10% off right now.
If you like what you saw, then you liked what you saw. I think it's an interesting mechanic.
Did he get softlocked? Yeah, I got softlocked. I had to go back to the very first save file
in Dead Rising 2. Is this a sponsored stream? Why the hell would I do a sponsored Bumbo stream?
Hey, yeah. Bye, guys. My first ever sponsored stream. It's Bumbo. No, I think it was cute. It
was fun. It was interesting. It's taken a long time. But I mean, it's only like a handful of
people that are working on this. I thought it was good. I liked it. And I'm going to play it
another time. Not on stream. I'm going to play it on my own. But, guys... No, no, no, don't say it.
Don't say it. Don't say it. Guys, don't say it. Oh, no, no. It's only been five and a half hours.
Don't say it. Guys, I have to go. No, but why? Why do you have to go? What? No. Dude, come on.
I am going to go start working on the lazy fuck sultan. What is that? What the fuck? Oh,
come on. What does that even mean? Liar. All right, let me explain for those of you that
are not sure what I'm talking about here. In the probably the second week of December,
I'm going to have a series of streams where I have an enormous Minecraft server.
That's probably going to be the first one. And it's going to be...
Fuck the king. I am going to rule over a kingdom with hopefully potentially hundreds and hundreds
of slots on a server. It's going to be a kind of slightly RP kind of scenario where if I die,
it's over. The king's dead. I am going to collect taxes on you. I'm going to have bodyguards.
Good luck. There's going to be an aging system, hopefully, if we can get it coded,
where you if you so people can't just turtle, you know, like five hours in game or 10 hours
in actual game is like you die. You're dead. He thinks the guards will protect him. I think they
will. Oh, they will because they're going to be all trusted. Very, very highly trusted people.
I'm going to be surrounded by them. There will be grievances with the kingdom. I will usually be
expected to make statues of me. Oh, there'll be consequences. There's a lot going on that it's
going to be a hopefully it's going to be a lot of fun. And that's not it. There's going to be
there's an this is kind of a series of like the streamers of fucking egomaniac because as we go
forward with other games in that sort of open no goal RP style, I want to do this where I don't
do anything. I physically do not play the game and thousands of you just just play the game for
me. I want like 50 diamond blocks and you just bring them to me and I just sit there and we have
like cameras that are observers that are going around seeing how people are doing.
If I'm unhappy, like I'll just make I'll call a court and we'll decide what we're going to do.
You need to protect me. I'll have loyal I'll pay I'll pay in like in game money. We'll have like
try to have like an in game currency of like have like mercenaries to protect me and protect the
kingdom. But there's a lot that needs to go into it and I want to start working on it and get it
solid because I need to like buy servers. I need to hire some coders. I've been talking to
people like producers for this to try to help get cameras and observer cameras and
it's going to be a whole thing and it's probably going to be like a four or five week series.
We'll do it like once a week with probably potentially maybe one or two in Minecraft,
one or two in like Conan Exiles. We're just throwing them. We're just it's in the phase
right now we're trying to figure it out. But I definitely want to have a the lazy king sucks
stream at least probably four or five of them. But I will see you guys in a couple days. We will
start. I don't know what we're going to start because there's like this Star Wars which I was
like eh. There's like Outer Worlds where I'm like eh. There's PlayStation 1 where I'm like
eh. I'm trying there's a bunch of stuff I could pull from. 200 people are going to just bum rush
you. Well that's I'm going to do you guys don't think that I'm going to have plans? What am I
just yeah sure you're going to build a ladder and climb up to my tower into my window like I said
the other day with like an axe in your hand. You don't think I'm going to have sentries just people
ready? Oh did you pay that sentry in the in-game currency to like look the other way? Oh that's
fine. I've got somebody in the bedroom that's standing there at the window ready for you and
he's paid way more than you could ever pay. You don't think I'm going to have like a series of
like 30 different tunnels built privately that I'm going to get I can always escape and bring like
30 of my most loyal men and women and we then oh then what then you're going to take over the
castle oh yeah you are don't think so and I'm going to be a good king I'm not going to be mean
to you at least unless you don't mean if you don't do what I say then then come on I'm the king.
He's going to be you're going to be Lord Farquaad. Somebody said this the other day I've been laughing
about it ever since. It's like everyone has you build up your houses we have like a series of
houses and people populate them and role play and walk around and give bring me things and like
somebody just pulls out an enchanted arrow and shoots me in the fucking head during one of these
like tell me your grievances and I'm instantly dead it's over and it's like all the work was for
nothing but that makes me laugh so I don't care. You're going to get like we're going to check
your items to see what you have you can't come into the throne room with like an enchanted bow
what am I going to let that happen there's going to be metal detectors that you have to go through
before you come to the throne room but anyways once an idea pops like into my brain and the
original idea for those of you that weren't here was WoW Classic where I didn't want to play WoW
Classic because I was grilled about hey why the fuck didn't you make the guild you should have
made that guild that you promised and I said I got to level seven and quit the game because I was
stupid I didn't like it right I don't want to do this again I want to play WoW Classic again
right I was going to make a guild and then it was like well if I play WoW Classic anyways people
are just going to be like a hundred people around me just like all bringing me shit and like killing
each other and I was like I'm not going to play the game I was walking around like looking at
stuff and then I was like all right well fucking I'll do it and if I if I die then streams over
and then it was like okay well that's incentive for people to like protect me and then people
to kill me and then it's like all right fucking I'm not gonna do anything I want to give I want
like 50,000 gold and like all the best bounce in the game and if I'm hurt I get the streams over
and then it's kind of just piled on top of that decided maybe WoW is probably not the best idea
it might still be funny to do that as one of the one of the weeks we'll see five minute stream
once a week well that wouldn't be the only thing I'd be doing that would just be like you know
Saturday night is the fuck the king you know what I mean that's like what we do on like Saturdays
for a few weeks fuck the king friday I just see all these scenarios where I'm like trying to escape
from my tunnel like okay we get overrun this castle gets taken okay they've risen up and
they've taken over and I go through one of my tunnels and I I like pop out I have to like dig
up because like I'm sorry it's like five of my loyal bodyguards and we're like fucking escaping
and I dig up and I'm like I got we get stuck and get lost and there's like a hundred people
surrounding me like me pop my head like a like a prairie dog you don't think I'm gonna have like
fucking dragons and shit good luck or you could just be civil and just we could be in the kingdom
and who cares I don't need to die but that's it we're gonna probably try to come up with
some incentives to why I would not be dead you know why why protect me what would you what do
you gain from that spitballing ideas for that sounds fun and then there's like other factions
that arise of people that want to take over they might even be fighting between the viewers
and I have nothing to do with it I step in I'm just like trying to like correct it music oh shit
but that was legend bumble I just want to play it for a few hours and end up playing it for more
than five I think it's very fun you let me lie in bed with that and I'll play it every night
for at least a few weeks any interest in halo reach when it comes out yeah I'm gonna probably
play all of them that seems like a really just fun thing to do because I've never played any of
the halo games that just seems like a no-brainer but let's go back to five and a half hours ago
we had martin had a meme gave a thousand bits thank you martin germa you got a nice looking
bumbo haha just kidding thanks to the thousand bits appreciate it by the way for those of you
wondering I will be back on uh Thursday Thursday afternoon pepe hands he hates us
you guys go right to that every single time I had a lot of fun today you guys it was fun thanks for
helping me it's just that's it was just chill it was just fun it was stressful sometimes but that
was just fun I'm gonna play more puzzle games with you guys no but thank you seriously to martin had
a meme for a thousand bits appreciate it peaceful hailey thanks for the 250 germa how are you I'm
doing pretty good uh I want to ask you a question maybe it might be dumb but I guess I just kind of
want to know do you ever think about your view count while streaming like if it goes below a
certain number does it bother you anyways hope you're well have a good night no not at all
the view count on this stream fluctuates huge because if there's a big event stream you know
let's say like once a month some months every like 30 to 40 days there's like oh wow there's
an event like the halloween stream or the carnival or the green screen stuff I mean they might be
eight ten twelve thousand people concurrently watching those streams and that's awesome but
yeah I can't I can't expect that that's not that's not gonna happen every time I also do like yeah
somebody just said that was my next point I play and do so many different things on this stream
every single time that there's no way it would be the same amount of people every time
like for like today right I mean this still there's still a lot of people here
but the dude the people that don't want to watch me play like a match for bumbo game
you know they'll just kind of take off whatever I think any genre any game it doesn't really I
don't care about like genres and what the exact game I'm playing is I don't really have like that
anchor video game where it's like hey guys two or three times a week I'm gonna play overwatch or
dota or something right there's not that anchor video game that I play every day or every week
so I can't let a view count get into my head for any reason because there's no it's these streams
are just kind of all over the place by design so how could I expect people to be that the views
are gonna fluctuate all the time so no that does not bother me at all that is I mean we make jokes
sometimes like oh all right well how many people just left 500 people just left because I said that
but it's all just bullshit and I'm just fucking around you guys know that but no it doesn't I
don't really think about it that much at all show it's we're begging you to show auto he's sleeping
in the other room I mean if you think I care about view counts I do you really think I would be
laughing as hard as I am sometimes about how bugleberry dropped two to three thousand
concurrent viewers on the halloween stream I that that like it made me laugh I wasn't like oh fuck
no my views that's like it's all right I get it I get it but I hope that answers your question
kind of long-winded but hopefully it answers what you were asking hey bob boy you get five
gifted subs I didn't even see it thanks bob boy it was the echo in the sound I know that makes
it so much worse but funnier is like the sound was so un-fucking-bearable that if people just
I can't listen as I'm fucking leaving and I did the loudest noise I've ever done on a stream
it's just there's so many reasons why people would leave
whatever it's all good it just makes me laugh but thank you thank you ball boy ball boy with
the five subs and 1500 bits half-life alex was just announced as the flagship vr title by valve
I hope it's thank you for the 1500 bits by the way but I do hope it's actually a video game I do
I really hope like I said earlier I hope this is not a tech demo for a new peripheral that's like
an hour and 10 minutes I hope this is a real game like a flagship actual full vr video game
it's supposed to be a full game but is it a full vr game because most full vr games are like two to
three hours it's 12 to 16 hours you gotta be kidding me okay well then that's awesome I'm
glad that that's now a known thing it's 12 to 15 hours it's not a tech demo for new tech it's a
demo for old tech they haven't confirmed anything yet all right well I'm gonna my hands I'm just
gonna pull my hands back and just not just be like okay whatever it ends up being I hope it's very
good because it has been a very long damn time since valve actually made a video game yes artifact
came out but did it though like I it came out yes it released but and then I know but uh they've
made a couple of games but if you love artifact and you like it then I'm glad you do but I would
have much rathered something else than card game number like 30 no one does any artifact fans here
click on the link all right yeah why what's why am I naked what I'm not that hairy what's with the
hair all it's probably hairy but I hope it's good I really do if I will play it is it index
only if it is and that sucks no okay good thank you squad dollar for the 300 bits
mr. elbertson uh jim houseman here from fgi fake gamers investigations we're here to inform you
that by reaching boomer age and never playing metal gear solid 3 we are here to revoke your
gamer license please don't leave your town in the next couple of days our uh fake agent prosecutor
will contact you shortly thank you for your patience I've played metal gear solid 3 it's
like my favorite one that's the best metal gear I that's my favorite one this is wrong info
camera license secured anyways thank you for the uh thank you for the 300 bits sir can and thanks
for the 250 hello mr. herrington um sad report that my son kevin the kid that you punched in
the face and you probably you beat up too many times and connect sports boxing you as you you
can't this is just a dog shit post like it's just this is like I wish why would I look hello
I'm sad report that my son kevin the kid you inflicted brain damage on in kingdom uh
connect sports boxing he passed away doing his inability to stop dancing to han solo
effson chat from my boy kevin oh great that's a good message that was just like
I what am I supposed how do I respond to this you don't it's word puke thank you for the 250
though appreciate it sad Vega thanks to 250 very excited for the germa king rp event what game you
think you'll be using uh also you should let kibo know as I'm sure that's something that's right up
her alley I was thinking about seeing if anyone wanted to do it I kind of want to do I don't want
to invite a bunch of streamers to do this I'll give you one reason why I'd like to do it once
or twice because if it just is a absolute mess then I just wasted a bunch of people's time
okay you you uh you want to do it yeah that sounds fun y'all be here at seven o'clock okay
you yeah well we're all doing it and somebody enchanted blows me the head and I turn my stream
off after five minutes it's just like what the fuck do these people do now well I want to I want
to get like one or two under the belt to make sure it's like even going to be something that's fun
it's an experiment that we're going to do so we'll get one under the belt maybe two and then
we'll start to potentially see if anybody else wants to do it but yes there's that is a thought
absolutely hey dark soul thanks for the 250 I said I wasn't going to donate bits for now but your
letter was very convincing anyways please play metroid prime one through three on stream and
I won't have to eat my game cube thank you imagine you imagine a streamer doesn't play
metroid prime one in like a week so you fucking eat your game cube who's there it's just what
you're just doing it in your room ah shit he didn't play it yeah I gotta go eat the game cube now
how do you eat a game cube do you just melt it down the plastic and then just drink it
that's an interesting thought those games are supposed to be really good by the way have never
played any one of them yes I know it's like oh whoa how have you not played metroid prime
I've seen it played I've seen it played for like 20 minutes I have not played it myself there's a
lot of games that I have not played that I'd like to I missed a huge bit donation from ab joe
five thousand and twelve bits thank you joe fifty dollars over fifty dollars hey
germbo looking forward to watching you play the new half-life keep up the entertaining streams
germa hart my man yeah I'll be playing that second it comes out along here's the thing though
I was gonna say along with every single other person on twitch I feel like VR and not very
many people stream VR they do but I will there be that many people actually streaming that game
when it comes out probably but they have they'll have to it's half-life well watch my stream I
promise you out of all the okay let's say there's like 5 000 people streaming that on twitch um
I'm gonna bump into my wall oh they probably will too I'm gonna swing and miss and hit the post
they'll do that too I'm gonna scream when I turn around I see something that I didn't know was
behind me they'll do that too watch me though come on you gotta watch me VR funny moments
now I hope it gets a lot of attention so then I hope valve decides hey wasn't it fun when we
made video games that people liked that was cool maybe we should do that again but thank you joe
yes I'll be playing it within three days of it coming out I would say thank you I think I can for
the thousand bits appreciate it germa you know many other content creators have gotten you know
you know many hold on I'm speaking strangely germa you know many other content creators have
gotten me to laugh some of you made me laugh crying but no one has ever made me legitimately
fear for my life from laughing so hard that it hurt throughout my whole body you uh you're the
greatest person I've ever watched and I want you to know that I absolutely adore your streams and
you yourself please keep doing this for as long as physically possible I'm looking forward to
your retirement home streams that's a that's a incredibly nice thing to say I hope you don't
end up being killed from laughing at this stream but I will tell you there has actually been three
or four times where I thought that I was actually in danger the last time it happened was um sims
four is I mean I was I seriously thought that something bad was going to happen to me and it
was not what you think it was the dogs the guy doing drugs and walking his dog in his house
it was so so fucking funny it was unbearably funny and then dogs were like rolling around
into the pee like why would you put a leash on a dog and then walk the dog in your house
that you're just so fucked up on drugs okay but the actually the last time recently was in planet
zoo when I was trying to get the the monkey to climb out of the enclosure and he kept taking
that way the long way and the alarms would sound I gotta be careful though because
it's hard if you laugh hard you can like I don't know I'm not even going to get into it but you
can like I feel like I may have given myself a hernia it's actually one of the things
that I'm being checked for soon so I mean full transparency here for the medical stuff I'm being
checked for a hernia I don't know I that's what I was told so it this is not what's happened I'm
just giving you a scenario that is so strange I don't even know if this is possible but can you
imagine a scenario where I laughed so hard at the sims 4 drug dog pee thing that I gave myself a
hernia last year can you imagine how fucking ridiculous that is I don't even know if that's
medically possible I am speaking totally out of my ass here I'm just saying that's fucking so
stupid I'm not even sure that that's even how that works but I am like out of all of all the
things I'm being checked for I've had my liver checked I'm having my throat down the tube into
my stomach to check for a hernia we're just trying to figure it out why I I I'm fine you know that's
everything's gonna be fine what a way to go you're gonna go no but I know but that's not even real
I'm just saying how fucked up would that be I want to make sure that's very clear on the record
that I have that's a total bullshit thing that I'm just saying so no that's definitely not what
happened but it'd be wild but anyways uh thank you I think I can for your 2400 bits I really
appreciate it the second part of your message here is I have an odd number of bits so this is
a separate message uh still appreciate you though my thoughts and opinions have not changed even in
the last 20 minutes good thing I didn't say anything in 20 minutes that you started to hate
me for hope you didn't watch last night's stream where I talked about mayonnaise and fries looking
forward to the coming of the king if life ever becomes too much I'll just lock myself in a room
and blast lock myself in a room and blast every germ of video full volume speakers right next to
my ears I would advise not doing that because you're gonna cause hearing damage but I thank
you I really appreciate it thanks for the 2400 fucking bits seriously you're gonna give yourself
an ear hernia thanks a lot thank you silent serenity for the 250 hey jerma if you could put
your brain in a jar and stream for the rest of eternity would you do it no no I don't want to
fucking be around forever I would rather you put my brain in a jar and like have me generate
electricity but hold on do we know if like I'm like like in a nightmare during that scenario
maybe we'll look into that he's already he already is a brain in a jar don't say that that's scary
it would be a low wattage now that is a factual statement but I know you're saying that because
you're saying I'm like stupid so it works both ways but it's not even real because your brain
guess what would have really low wattage too it wouldn't just be my brain it would be yours too
you got a low wattage brain too but thank you thank you elizabeth for the 250 you should hit
up criken with those fuck the king stream sounds like they're jam yeah I there's like I said I want
to get like one or two down I the lazy king that doesn't do anything stream with a thousand people
that's trying to kill you is fun on paper I just want to make sure it works in practice before I
ask it if anybody else is interested to come like have fun and role play on the servers
just make your character invisible hey vanilla grime thanks for the 500 bits please help I can't
stop you going to the bathroom well I would probably go to the doctor now here's the fun
game we like to play called does my webcam is my webcam turned on when I change scenes
because I don't have any clothes on so I'm going to current I'm going to close I'm going to cover
it it is not turned on okay good let's roll the credits silence serenity thanks to the 250 germa
have you ever tried saying I know I'm in a simulation out loud why are you alone you know
just to see if they let you out uh no I've never tried it but and phylactery again phylactery
say thanks for the 5000 bits phylactery here come the subs this is beautiful and I got hacked
what does this say it says it's beautiful and feature packed thank you for the subs everybody
appreciate it all of you the lot of you thank you but let's talk about what phylactery did say
they said you will go down in medical books as the guy who laughed at a dog rolling around and
pissed so hard that he caused himself permanent damage that was 5000 bits phylactery a fucking
huge amount of money today and always but like I said I don't even think that's physically possible
I'm just making up a scenario watch the clip no I can't I can't ever watch this clip ever again
it's dude he's it's the dog is doing it so much but the context you have the dog you have to piss
and make the stars around the guy's head this is the moment that gave him a hernia no I don't even
want that to be like jokingly a thing people say because it's definitely not true all right I'm
the okay I'll see you guys in a few days see you on Thursday 1 to 2 p.m pacific take care guys
have a great one good night guys good night goodbye