Well hello. Welcome to Christmas Eve, god darn it. Oh yeah, that was an ordeal. Taleks and I have been
painstakingly trying to get this ready for the last probably about three and a half hours.
We had some issues, but the issues have been fixed, I think. I hope so. And we're ready to
have a Christmas Eve party. Happy Christmas Eve everybody. And how the heck are ya? Hope you're
having a great day. Conductor drummer is on the case, as you see. I've got my costume on. I've got
my... I forget about the branding on that thing. I was going to cover it up before the stream
started, but I did it somehow. I got a nice tree. I've got my nice brick backdrop here.
Put on any presents under the tree here that was picked by you guys in the mods too.
Welcome to Christmas Eve. Yeah, sure, I started like an hour and a half late.
Typically, I would love to have started an hour ago, but camera broke. We had some lighting
issues. I had some fucking OBS issues, but you know, whatever. It's Christmas Eve. Merry
Christmas. Happy holidays. How are ya? So let's break down what we're going to do.
Over here, let's... You're probably wondering why the fuck there's a printer here.
This is the extreme magic fax machine. So anytime that you want to send me a message or want to
talk to me, you're going to use your magical fucking computer and I'll get it somehow through
a bit donation. Hopefully it works. I hope it's hooked up correctly because there should be
messages from the fucking people coming out here. And if there's not, then you know,
we'll have to fucking unplug and plug it back in. Presents over here, tree over here.
I got a train set ready to build. Oh, Jeremy, you look like a fucking dickhead.
Well, you know what? Sometimes you look like a dickhead. Oh my God.
Okay. So my fucking fly was undone in the very beginning. That's a fantastic start.
Why don't we move over to the train set? Because I'm in the conductor round,
couldn't might as well do it here. Welcome frame, everybody.
So I got, I can't fucking believe my fly. Did you see my fly undone? Hey,
you tell us. Was my fly, did you see my fly undone?
Was my fly actually undone? Why did you like tell me that?
He's fucking over there being a director. All right. So hey,
Choo Choo, what do you say here? We got our train set here. I figured it'd be a fun start.
The first part of the stream should be about building and creating.
So I have, this is going to be fucking ridiculous.
Here is the train that I have. We're going to build a train set on the frame.
And this is kind of going to be a present that I'm going to give to
probably a local library, I would assume. I'm going to probably donate this to a library
because what the fuck am I going to do with this after the streams over? I have no idea.
So let's get started here. It's called the South Pacific train. It looks like you keep and score.
Can you see the shit? Does this look good? So I got pieces here.
I got straights, I got curves, and I kind of don't know what to do.
I'm thinking like a figure eight. This shit, this, this moves by the way. If you're like,
oh, Jeremy, it doesn't move. How can it move the fucking mic?
Hold on. This looks getting good.
Good. Can you hear me? It's my fucking flyer. Jesus Christ. Okay. Hey,
Merry Christmas, by the way, everybody. How the heck are you?
So within 10 seconds of the fucking stream, my fly. All right.
I'm going to say if we start, because this is a real train. Like I said, it's going to move
in various directions. I need the plug to go in here though. The plug has to go in here.
This is a real fucking train, ladies and gentlemen. So we have to start.
I don't want to break this. This is going to a library. God damn it.
Just get the fuck over here. Right here. I'm going to plug it in. Am I going to get electrocuted
if I do this? Okay. I did not get electrocuted. Train there. Okay. So I have to start here.
Is that an error message? I don't know if that's an error message.
All right. Shut the fuck up. All right. You got to match the fucking lines up here,
folks. I got to get like a bird's eye view because I'm thinking straight.
And what a goddamn train this is. Straight and then around
and then maybe straight and around again. Yes, I'm aware that I look like a total
fucking dickhead. I'm aware. So like, here we go right here. So these trains.
Let me show them. I don't know why I'm so afraid of electricity right now.
Ah, here we go. Okay, that's in. So should I do like some tricks?
I'm thinking like at least two loops. Let's block it out. So if I go like that,
that's a huge you. But I got to make sure I can actually get off of me.
I got to make sure I can actually connect it. No, that can't go there.
I'll be amazed if this actually works. I can one loop around and then maybe straight
and then around again. That looks better. I hope you're enjoying your holiday here.
There. I got this little piece. Like, what is this for? This looks like it can go
across and then through this way too, right? But that's sort of figure eight.
Close enough. Maybe I should have wrote this down. Because right now it's going to be
like a loop and then another. Hold on. How can I get a loop? I don't think I can get
it to work because if I go like that, I guess maybe it could go around in another
circle and then through here. It looks like one more. Oh, that's going to look actually
really cool. One or will this work? That's not going to work. What if I go like
so through here and then this, how am I supposed to get this to go this way?
You know what I'm saying? Like how am I supposed to get this to go all the way around?
Is it even possible? This segment was supposed to be about 20 minutes. Don't think that's going
to be the case anymore. Get it like this. All right. I'm going to build out from here.
That's what I'm going to do. If I go out from here, don't worry. The train will,
you'll ride on the train in a second. Look at it to work. I'm going to say like this
and then like that. I don't care that much about how cool it looks. You know what I mean?
I care about it working. That's all I give a shit about.
So then we're going to fuck this whole thing up. Get in here. Plastic on it.
Don't break it. Don't break it. I'm going to break it. I don't want to. That's the problem
here. Get in there. Come on. Come on. I got a stream to run.
Somebody is probably telling me, Jeremy, you should probably put some jump in there and
put some obstacles in there. Yeah. I can't even get the whole thing built before that.
I was going to have like trees and shit to go around. Why is this going in?
What have I done that's wrong? All right. It's in. Got it. All right. Finally. Oh,
God. All right. Connect this. It's supposed to be easy assembly in my ass. Much easier
than the other one. All right. So here we go. Starting here, right around. This thing makes
noise and shit too, guys. So then let's get a straight track ahead. I'm going to lap my
ass off. I built this whole thing and it just doesn't work at all. I spend all the time doing
this and then turn it on and it just fucking sits still. Oh, get your fucking frog champs.
Oh, what the fuck? Ow. Seriously, that fucking hurt. This is designed for like 11 year olds.
How did I just hurt myself? Get in there. No, that's not in there, right? Get in there.
This thing's bent. How did I bend it already? Oh, you motherfucker.
On the side. So when I was looking at the box, this thing looks actually really fucking cool.
It makes noise. It has smoke that I'm not going to use. What am I doing? All right. No,
no, no, no, no. That's good. That's good. That's fine. Let's go this way. Yes. All right.
Do it again. I'll be fucking surprised. Okay. That's good. How does it look so far?
What are they saying? Anything bad? Hold on. He just went, he just went like this.
He just went like this. Well, you don't like this? You don't think this is cool?
I got a train set. God damn it. He just goes like this. All right. Fine. Let's build a
fucking train. Just wait till I turn this thing on. And that was a horrible voice crack,
but Dutch does it. So it's okay. Dutch made the voice crack cool again. Like made it like,
okay to do it. I hate it. I hated the train segment. That was the worst part of the
cryptocurrency stream. Like fuck that whole segment. What? He built a train on stream?
I hope he fucking pees his pants. Oh, don't. This is nice. Okay. Hold on. Let me tell
you. This is just part one of the night. Okay. So just relax around the circle and
then it's got to go this way. How the fuck am I going to get it to go that way? This? All
right. I gotta check this out. Watch this. Ready? Bang. What if this is the whole stream?
I just baited you guys so hard. It's just me building a fucking train set in front of
fucking 40,000 people. All right. So is that going to work? Oh my God. It's not going to
work. No, this is not going to do anything. Plug it in. Let me see. So I want to see.
I just want to make sure the thing works. Okay. Here we go. Ready?
Wait. Oh, this is stupid, Jeremy. God damn it. I need to see if it goes. Whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa. Oh yeah. Plug chip. Oh, this is bad. I need to get like a closed loop.
I can't even get it closed. I screwed the whole thing up. I mean, no, because this
has to come off. That. Oh, baby boy. He figured it out. Take a look at this shit. Oh, Jeremy,
this is the worst thing you've ever done on stream. Oh yeah. Has it? You didn't
fucking watch this part. Oh, look at that. Okay. Close. Get this connected again.
Oh man, this is going to be good. We're real good. We got starting here,
around, through, and then around. Stomp it. Stomp it. Jeremy, stomp the train. No, I'm not.
Why? Please give it a rest. Every little bit. Okay. All right. Then around this way.
Come on. Yeah, I know you can do it.
Round and then close it. And then if we can get a full loop, I'll be happy.
This thing is fucking cool. I might just be saying that because everyone's probably fucking
talking about how this is the worst thing ever. No, they're not. But I can't see. You know
what I mean? Right here. All right, that's good. As long as these things are actually
connected well. And they are. So I need to connect it here. And that's a full loop and
we're going full blast. I'm going to play the fucking noises. I'm going to play the
fucking sound effects. It's going to be so awesome. Just edit that part out, dude.
I know you're watching. Look, this is good. Some library is going to get this. A local
library. And they're going to make some cool display and it's going to be fucking awesome.
I'm just testing the goddamn thing, okay? Once you see it go around the whole track,
I think your mind will change. Good. All right. Kind of making a reverse squid.
Am I going to have enough track to do this? I don't think I have enough track
to do it. This is bad. Right there. Don't break anything.
I don't have enough pieces to complete this. Really? One, two. Oh, fucking hell. Come on,
really? How do I not have enough pieces to do this? Shit. I guess I could.
What can I do about this? I don't know. Take from here?
Let me just see what happens when I do this.
I need a complete circuit before we move on. Don't you understand? That's one
that goes up here and around and then... Shit. Let me test it. Is that good? What
happened? What happened? What? What's the fucking problem?
I think that's good enough. I think that's great. That looked really fun.
Wait, were you playing Thomas the Tank?
Are you fucking kidding me? Oh, my God. I need a complete loop. Just get this. I
fucked the whole thing up. I made a pretzel. I was supposed to make a figure eight.
I needed to go around the circle once. Just wait. Hold on. Get rid of this fucking
piece. I got it. I figured it out. Just wait. Speed run. Here we go. Watch this shit. Here
we go. Get it on there. I'm the best. I'm the greatest. Don't break this. This is going to
a library. How am I supposed to do this? Close. I just want... I need this piece.
I need the fucking piece that has power. Get out of here for a second.
Almost. Do I not understand basic physics? How the fuck am I supposed to connect this?
I just want a circle. I need like this here. Wait a minute. Hold on. I'll get it.
It's a merry fucking Christmas. Got it. Got it. Where's the electric piece right here?
I bent it. I think so. Oh, fuck. Yeah. We've got a complete loop.
Oh, baby. Would you look at that? Get it on here. Where's the plug? I just need a circle
Okay. It's on there, right? Try to do something fancy and you fuck it all up.
I think that's good. Get out of the way. I want a good view of this.
Okay. You ready for the complete loop? Here we go. Here we go.
Thanks for coming to the stream, everybody. That's it. No, you know what? Let's get on
this thing. You want to get on this train? It's a complete loop. Let's get on the
fucking train. See? Let's get on it. Let me get in. Let me get on that train.
Oh, my goodness. Oh, what's it? Oh, what's it? Oh, what's it? Oh, what's it?
Welcome. Happy Halloween, you fucking idiots. Welcome to, my magic book sometimes is a little
on the weird side. Welcome to an edition. A special holiday edition. A scary story
with me, B.F. Mugler Baron. Oh, and is it going to be a great one today? I'll tell you.
Yes, it will. I've got my fucking magic book. I wish it would stay open. That would be
fantastic. Sometimes you've got to turn off the batteries. Staying open, please.
The witches sometimes take over on their own.
Okay. So first, I have a selection of stories from my dark magic book. It'll be very,
very fond of with one of my favorites. Oh, it's Christmas time, though,
you'll be very... What kind of Christmas stories will we be getting? The first tale is called
Carol Singers. A collection of horrible fucking deeds. Carol Singers is a scary story for
Christmas about a kid whose father and grandfather go from door to door begging for money.
It is based on an old horror story by Bernard Kurtz. The vanity. You know,
my grandfather was a drunk and my father was a drunk, but I never touched drunk.
There's a reason for that. When I was young, times were hard and I grew up poor.
My grandfather and my father never did an honest day's work in their lives.
Granddad wasn't good for much, but he played the clarinet like an artist. He taught my
father how to play the accordion. This is upside down. It did cause a little bit of an issue.
They would gather a group of friends and go door to door,
playing Christmas music, singing Christmas carols and begging for money.
Afterwards, they would all go down to the pub and spend it on alcohol.
No! Don't do that! On Christmas Eve, they brought me with them. I was too young to play an instrument,
so they handed me a triangle and told me to strike it every now and then.
I was dark. The snow was falling and cold December wind cut through us like a knife.
We kept our heads down and trudged through the snow and sleet. Eventually,
my grandfather stopped and said, this looks like a pretty good place as any.
We were outside a big mansion decorated with Christmas lights.
My grandfather knocked on the front door and began to play some old Christmas carols.
The door of the house swung open and in the dim light I saw a young woman standing there.
She was holding a tray of glasses in her hand.
With a smile, she picked up a glass and held it out, inviting one of the men to drink.
My granddad rubbed his hands together with glee.
Just then I looked up and in the window above I saw a face peering up.
A face that was hideous beyond words. I looked back at the woman at the doorway
and her face was hideous too. Before I could stop her,
my grandfather put a glass to his lips and knocked it back with one big gulp.
Oh dear, said the woman in an eerie childish voice. Oh, you've drunk blood, sir.
With that, the door slammed shut. My grandfather stumbled backwards and the grass fell from his hand.
It's so sad that the deafening crash and he collapsed. I don't remember much after that.
All I recall is waking up in the lights of dawn and finding myself lying in the snow.
The other men were lying all around me, just waking up themselves.
My father got to his feet and rubbed his head.
The woman had disappeared and the house was boarded up and abandoned.
All that was left was a dark red stain in the snow with a glass that broke.
My grandfather lay there in the snow beside it, his face purple and swollen.
We hurried home that morning and called the police.
They picked up my grandfather's body and brought it to the mortuary.
My father told them what had happened, but they didn't believe a word of his tale.
They said the house had been vacant for a hundred years.
One hundred!
After that night, my father was never the same again.
He never let another drop of alcohol touch his lips and made sure I didn't die.
That is the story.
Two points!
This next tale is, say, one.
This next tale is called Vickalritha.
Those of you wondering, I didn't get my Halloween stream.
So of course I'm going to show up here.
Three months went by and get what I was supposed to get, which is a stream for Halloween.
Oh, but it's Christmas time!
It's Christmas time!
That's all I hear is that.
Vickritha.
I like this one because it has a lot of voices.
I love doing those.
They're a lot of fun.
Vickritha is a scary story about a legendary monster who lives in the icy
wastes of the North Pole.
Bah!
It was Christmas Eve and the family were gathered in the living room.
The family was gathered in the living room.
The father was reading the newspaper and the mother was knitting a sweater.
The children, Jimbo and Steffa, were stretched out on the floor with their crayons
and their coloring books.
Tell us a story, Steffa demanded.
A scary one, Jimbo insisted.
All right, all right, said their father.
I'm going to tell you about the fearsome, dangerous,
and appalling creature in the world.
It's called Vickritha.
Oh, now you've done it, said the mother.
You've said his name out loud.
Voldemort.
Where is he?
Said Jimbo.
He's the most awful thing in the world.
He lives in a cave in the North Pole.
The coldest, wettest place on earth is where Vickritha makes his home.
He sleeps in the rep of a ship that somehow got squeezed into the mouth of a cave.
He doesn't mind the cold and doesn't mind the wet.
But I think he hates the most.
Here someone say his name.
He was very good and he has very good ears.
And they get bigger every time his name is spoken anywhere on earth.
Sometimes his ears get so big he can use them to fly.
He can fly away with his ears.
I don't like this story, Steffa whined.
Play now, her mother said.
If we finish the story before he gets here, everything will be fine.
Do you know why the grither is called the grither?
Why?
Said the children.
Because he has fists as big as basketballs and his arms as long as ball constrictors.
Whenever he finds the people who have been speaking his name,
he opens up his fists, reaches out his arms and grithers them.
He squeezes them by the head and squeezes their head until it pumps.
Guess Michael Balloon.
Ah ah ah ah ah.
Give all that.
No, said his father.
He's not like Bigfoot and he's not like the abominable snowman either.
Nobody knows what he looks like for sure.
The only people who have ever seen the grither are the people the grither has eaten.
Gonna be you.
He's as tall as a tree and can bend all the way over and touch the ground.
His skin looks like a road map because it's transparent
and all the blue and red veins show through.
The blue is for the fear, the red is for the rage.
And hurry up and finish the story before he gets here, Stiffle cried.
Well, the grither was born on a sailing ship, said her father.
It was blown off course by a storm and got lost in the Arctic sea.
They drifted around for weeks and never saw anything but glaciers and icebergs.
Some of the passengers drowned, some froze to death,
some starved and the rest committed suicide.
The grither was born out of the fear and rage of all those people.
But why does he kill people, Kimball asked.
Nobody knows.
Nobody knows, said his father.
He just doesn't like anyone telling his story.
Is that all, Stiffle asked?
Is that the end of the story?
Well, not quite.
Not quite, said her father.
There's only one way to protect yourself from the grither.
Only one way.
Maybe you should stop, said the mother and interrupted.
I don't, I think, I think you've scared them enough for tonight.
You don't actually believe this story, said the father.
No, the children lied.
Well, you shouldn't because I made it all up.
I made the whole story up, said the father.
There's no such thing as the grither.
It's not real.
Oh, why didn't you finish the story, said Stiffle.
All of the sudden, the front door blew open
and the room was enveloped in an icy blast of wind.
There was a crash and the sound of breaking glass.
Then the two huge, gnarled arms reached in through the windows
and grasped their parents by the head.
As the children watched in horror, the hands squeezed
and squeezed their parents' fucking heads until they exploded.
Sometimes when a story is so good.
One of our final tales of the evening.
Could I use your printer?
This isn't printed out really the way that I want it to.
You print me out another copy.
I don't know if this is here for.
Doesn't work. Made by HP.
Are you sure I can't just, I need to,
if I could just get this printed again.
It's okay.
And just tell Jeremy that after the show,
$40 for my usual fee.
I can't use that.
Is this how it works?
Print me out another one that I have a file
or that I put on his computer.
I don't know if he has it or not.
This next tale is, I think I got it from Reddit.
A terrifying tale.
A horror tale.
A few years back, I went to my dad's house for Christmas.
My parents are divorced and I rarely go,
but my siblings put a lot of pressure on me
so I went.
It took about 15 minutes before the stress got to me.
So we all sit down to open presents.
Dad, his new wife, my sibling,
Prezian and my grandmother.
We make it around the circle,
opening presents for about two rounds
before my grandmother gets up and leaves the room.
My father starts fiddling around
waiting for my grandmother to come back
and spot something on the floor.
It appears to be cat puke.
He asks his wife if it is indeed cat puke.
She had gotten up and followed my grandmother around
and knew the truth.
It was not cat puke.
It was my grandmother's shit.
And the lady had shit all over the couch.
It doesn't take long before we can smell the shit
and no amount of air freshener was fixing that.
Grandma comes back into the room now
wearing nothing but a blanket around her lower half.
The couch is covered with plastic and towels.
My little sister is forced to sit next to my grandmother
and we are all expected to sit nicely
and open more presents
while pretending that my grandmother
had not just shit all over the couch.
Also the following day my tooth exploded.
Apparently I had an abscess,
but I never felt a thing until it exploded.
TLDR.
Grandma shit on the couch.
What a horrifying story.
What a terrifying tale.
I have one more tale.
A tale of a very recent one that came up.
The final tale is a recent tale
that I came across in my travels
and I found it to be so bone-chilling,
so absolutely disgraceful and horrible.
For warning to you all watching,
this last tale will chill you to your very soul.
This tale is called The Sins of Yesteryear.
The Sins of Yesteryear.
The winds blow cold this time of year.
The true of the snowy icy-filled days
are heartened to blame
and seeing your hot breath
turn to condensed clouds of cold silk.
Now your toes turn to numb rubbers
not under the oars,
not the sun-chilling breeze.
I would say.
The breezy before-christening job
around the neighborhood
to do track and field in high school.
And like stand active.
So I was usually running or walking everywhere.
The route I would typically lead
simply through a few side streets in the neighborhood.
Am I supposed to read these?
What is this?
When I was like 11,
I really wanted to be an iPod
for Halloween.
So my dad made me a foam rubber iPod costume
complete with speaker mounts
so I could play music while I trick or treat it.
No one wants to be an iPod anymore.
Oh, how dastardly.
I don't retake.
Ah, scary.
Let me go back to what I was saying.
That was a little humorous, I will say.
On a breezy before Christmas day,
you know the story was cold
and he got jogging.
He's a jogger.
He likes to run.
He likes to move around.
Okay, sorry.
I'm a major creature of habit.
Some very odd reason.
I strayed away from my normal routine
and it will haunt me until my final day.
I had always heard stories about this person
called the loud man.
It was an urban legend in our city
and the story is told differently from person to person.
It became a sort of running joke among all of us.
Loud laughing, noises, and sometimes faint screams
coming from a certain house
which is what made it so strange.
What were these noises and who was making them?
I was never afraid of urban legends
and always scoffed at the idea of a boogeyman
or a bigfoot among us
who were hiding in plain sight
waiting for the right time to drain us of our souls.
Oh no, he took me away to another dimension.
I didn't believe any of it.
The idea seems silly until the loud man.
You see, sometimes I take quick breaks during a job.
I check my pulse, make sure my shoes are tied,
nice and tight, catch my breath.
You know, do this thing,
do this thing, or whatever the fuck that is.
As I reach down to tighten my shoes
is when I heard the sound.
Quick, loud, distinguished, a swift thunk, a thunk.
The feeling was immediate.
Breaking bone, bending cold.
I thought possibly it may have been a reaction from the jog.
Was I moving too fast?
Did I push myself too hard?
No way.
It felt as if something entered my body
and froze it to its very core.
I went to one knee and let the chill dissipate.
The sky opened up at that moment
and for the first time in nearly a decade
rain started to fall in December.
I quickly brought myself up and checked my surroundings,
my body still aching from the frost in my chest.
Finding the rain back as I tried to move,
each step more deliberate than the last.
Finally, in the pouring rain, I spotted a figure.
A figure exiting from the loud man's house.
This was just a urban legend.
No one had ever seen anyone come out of that house
or near that house.
It was supposed to be abandoned.
And then a hunch over small, rail man emerged through the dark.
It was hard to make out through the rain,
but he was dragging something or possibly someone.
The faint jingle of bells could be heard
with each pull of the oversized sack and the gurgling awful grunts
coming from the loud man's mouth
sounded like they were grating through the very gates of hell.
I felt I had to do something, but I was frozen in place.
A statue of a man did I turn into.
Should I run?
Should I walk?
Should I scream?
Nothing seemed normal.
Everything seemed out of place.
What felt like an eternity had passed.
I needed to make a move.
I put one foot in front of the other and slowly.
Just checking in to make sure your printer works now.
We are watching the stream and saw you had difficulties.
Thanks for installing our easy print software.
Thanks to our monitoring agreement,
we will be able to fix it remotely from our end.
Thank you, Jerma985, for choosing DeskJet.
Fine, that helped me.
I don't know.
The loud man stopped dead in his tracks
as I put one foot in front of the other.
He stopped and dropped his bag.
His crooked head ripped sideways,
tilting over 180 degrees in a second.
His eyes lit up red like blood with piercing light skewing through my very being.
His jaws started to unhinge
and his mouth opened nearly a foot across.
The most unnerving sound I will ever hear.
I bolted away.
Far out matching any competition I had ever been in.
Street to street, sign to sign.
I ran as far as I could.
I ran within ten minutes.
Here in the distant worlds of the loud man's cries,
I ran until the rain dissipated
and the clouds let up
and the world seemed at unease.
It was very quickly I heard the news.
Santa had disappeared.
It was on every radio station, every TV channel.
You couldn't pass a group of people on the street
without some form of conversation playing out
about the recent event of his disappearance.
Oh, why?
That was one year ago today.
No one believed my tale.
I was seen as a liar, a fraud.
The debate rang out across the globe
on whether or not Santa was even actually real or not.
Nations in conflict.
Twitter ablaze with confrontations.
And to this day, we're still not so sure.
I've tried to live a normal life
questioning my own sanity
and the reality each passing month.
But hear me now.
I still feel those eyes.
I still see those shark-fanged teeth.
I still hear his scream
and the cold icy touch deep within my bowels.
It has not left me since last year.
Signed it hard.
Absolutely devilish.
I gotta eat this one.
I think I gotta eat this one.
That was a good one.
Found that one real recently.
Oh, yeah.
Good for joining me on
I gotta get my time here.
I'm told by Jeremy
that we are going to,
before the present opening ceremony,
we are going to go over
some of his favorite clips
from the past year or three
because it's been a full year.
I know it's crazy to think about that.
But I'll see you dastardly fucking dickhead
later.
Enjoy the fucking past year.
So it's all my fucking fault then?
You fucking...
Carol, you fucking...
You're gonna throw me the fucking water?
You're gonna throw me the fucking...
You know I didn't have a goddamn choice.
You know I fucking...
Fuck.
Fuck you.
I did what I had to.
I fucking...
You can't fucking blame me for that.
Fucking bullshit.
Tell it again, tell it again.
Listen, I've told the story like four times.
Just please, let me be the example for this, okay?
Stay the fuck away from yard tools.
Don't touch anything dangerous.
Don't like rake your leaves.
You're gonna like, duh!
And then all of a sudden you got
$1,400 worth of dentistry wear.
Actually can't beat him.
He swings way too weirdly.
And I can't even get the correct controls right.
Shouldn't do R2 twice.
Don't even think about it.
All right.
No, no, no, no, no.
Come on.
No, no, no, back up!
No!
Oh!
What the fuck?
Yikes!
Oh, okay, it's a big guy.
Uh, I don't know what to do.
Holy shit.
This guy.
I gotta jump.
And listen to this music that's playing.
Oh my god.
Sir, you seem to be having a trouble with your car here.
Well, let me fix that for you with a yellow...
Oh, and I farted!
And I farted!
I don't see how people think that's weird.
Why do you think that's weird?
You think that's weird that I've never
eaten pepperoni on my pizza before?
I'll get pepperoni for you here.
So it's all my fucking fault then?
I didn't mean it.
You fucking...
Oh, you fucking...
You're gonna throw me to the fucking wall too?
You're gonna fucking throw me to the fucking...
You know I didn't have a goddamn choice.
You know I fucking...
What the fuck?
Fuck you.
I did what I had to!
I fucking...
You can't fucking blame me for that.
Fucking bullshit!
Tell it again, tell it again, tell it...
Listen, I've told the story like four times.
Just please, let me be the example for this, okay?
Stay the fuck away from yard tools.
Don't touch anything dangerous.
Don't like break your leaves.
You're gonna like...
And then all of a sudden you got
1400 dollars worth of dentistry work.
Actually can't beat him.
He swings way too weirdly.
And I can't even get the correct controls right.
Shouldn't do R2 twice.
Don't even think about it.
All right.
No, no, no, no, no.
Come on.
No, no, no!
Back up!
What the fuck?
Yikes!
Oh, okay, it's big guy.
Uh, I don't know what to do.
Holy shit.
This guy.
I gotta jump.
And listen to this music that's playing.
Oh my go-
Sir, you seem to be having a trouble with your car here.
Well, let me fix that for you with a yellow.
Oh, and I farted!
And I farted!
I don't see how people think that's weird.
Why do you think that's weird?
You think that's weird that I've never
eaten pepperoni on my pizza before?
I'll get pepperoni for you here.
Let me grab some.
Let me put the mic over here closer.
Hold on a second.
There we are.
There we go.
That's a little bit better.
Okay.
So we've got to the present opening portion of the stream.
And if you're curious what the hell this is,
a while back the chat talked about how,
you know, oh, let's buy them Pikachu and
Pokemon plushies on the internet.
And I thought it was funny.
So I said, okay, well, what if we just gave
chat a budget to just buy some presents for Christmas?
And it was a decent idea, I guess.
People thought it was fun.
And that's exactly what happened.
I just put up about $400 or so dollars
for chat to suggest presents.
And the mods also suggested presents as well.
I don't know what any of these are.
I have absolutely no idea.
And by the way, don't believe any things
you hear from internet scary stories
because they're just, none of them are real.
And if you think the demons are real,
then you just, I mean, they're made up by,
like, you think the Ghostbusters are real,
but they're not.
The Ghostbusters are made up by a handful of guys
who thought it was funny to make ghost stories and shit.
But he's gone.
I made sure he got paid and he's gone.
So just don't believe anything you hear on the internet
because the internet's obviously fucked up.
They don't really fucking believe anything on the internet.
So I don't know what any of these are.
I have Kim Raptum and Italics,
my wonderful tech director here,
has bought them under my Amazon.
So I have no idea what they are.
And we also, by the way,
we have the Christmas Magical Facts Machine.
So if you do have something to say,
it's going to be printed out here.
If you give a bit donation,
Probably. Maybe.
I don't know if it fucking works.
But let's get started.
So there are, I think, 20-something gifts.
And I want to make this very clear
because I think maybe some people don't know
what's going to happen at the end of this.
If there are things in here that I'm not going to use
or if there are things that I think are not worth
maybe me keeping long term,
if there's some things that might,
maybe some of the family or some of the person
might get better use of a toy or something,
then that with the train as well
is going to go to a donation circle.
So we'll see.
I might just keep some of this shit.
We'll find out.
So the first one we're going to open,
and this is not like a bit, by the way,
like the last couple things with bits.
But, you know, this is not a joke.
I don't know what the fuck is in here.
So let's go and open this one.
This is the first present we're going to open.
I don't know what it is.
And it's like, we're like, oh, yeah,
there's like a few hundred dollars
to like buy me presents from my own stream.
It's like a little weird,
but it's just an unboxing kind of thing.
I thought it was fun.
And this is called, this is the nut button.
Okay.
I already can't wait to know what this is.
This is the first thing I open
and this is this fucking stupid thing.
What the hell am I going to, I can't donate this.
What am I going to do with this?
There is no use for this item.
It doesn't serve any purpose, not one.
Can I melt this plastic down
and turn it into like fucking water bottles?
That's all it does.
Oh yeah.
Oh, by the way, guys,
I'm going to donate most of the items here
to families in the, oh yeah.
Yeah. Let me dump.
I don't know what I'm going to do with this.
There's the nut button.
That's the first item.
Okay. We're going to go small for now.
I knocked it over.
Let's go with this one.
It's a Garfield costume.
I know what this is already.
This is a fucking Garfield.
I know it's a Garfield costume
and I'm just going to open it
because I know exactly what it is.
Captain Morgan,
I want to see the Grifters basketballs.
I don't have time for that.
What? Captain Morgan says,
I want to see the Grifters basketballs.
Frodingweapon says,
can you tell Ninja to stream on Christmas?
I don't know Ninja.
I don't talk to him.
What?
Thank you, Cobra Cat, by the way.
Best Christmas to be honest.
Hashtag charity.
Thanks for the charity, by the way.
There's the Christmas fucking fax machine
coming out here with some weird shit.
Here's the Garfield.
Oh, put it on.
Is everybody saying put it on?
Is that what they're saying?
I fucking knew what it was
when I saw it in the back.
What are they saying?
Yeah. Put it on.
I don't want to do that.
Like, I can't,
how am I going to donate the shit?
Hey, by the way,
you want a Garfield costume?
No, I'm not putting this on.
Okay?
If that was fun, let's get it off.
I'm sorry, Mom.
Mom is like watching the stream
and she's probably like,
what the fuck is my son doing?
So this is gift number three.
Again, I don't know what these are
and we'll find out.
Oh, you got to be fucking kidding me.
I talked about this like the other,
like not even two weeks ago.
This is an Airzooka.
You got to shoot me in the fucking face
with this thing.
I'm serious.
Airzooka.
These things are so awesome.
You can, like from a mile away,
you can hit somebody right in the face.
You'll see the air.
Oh, I can't, I can't wait
to like donate this.
Someone's going to have so much
fucking fun with this thing.
Seriously.
HowToPrinters is the great Canadian
with $50.
That's how.
Fuck.
Thank you from zero two for the $10.
Hey, Jerma, my name is Lucy
and your streams make me smile so much.
I made Jerma remix 10 for green screen night
and I felt so proud when it was shown.
This community is so great.
Thanks for the laughs.
Happy holidays.
Happy fucking day.
Edgemont, thanks for the $50.
Your fax machine is broken.
The thing is this thing sucks, okay?
You want to know why the stream
was like an hour late?
Because we were trying to figure out
so desperately how to get,
how to get this fucking thing to work.
It is a basic HP printer
that's plugged in with USB.
Oh my goodness.
Was it a fucking pain in the ass?
But help, I'm trapped in the printer.
It says Spartan cat.
Well, you're out here now.
You're out now.
And Airzooka, if you don't know,
is a device.
I don't have to read the rules.
So you pull on one end.
I'm going to shoot it out.
It's right in the face.
Watch this.
Make sure I box this up nice
because this is fucking awesome.
Awesome.
Whoa, this piece is here.
Yep.
So you pull back on this
and it gives a bunch of air pressure
forward.
So, hey, you're going to tell me
if this hits you like right in the face.
I used to be really good at this shit.
Can I take the Garfield costume off?
Like, can I?
That's like, that's funny, right?
If it's off.
It has to stay on.
I really-
You're going to lose viewers.
Is it weird that I don't care?
I want to get the Garfield fucking costume
off of my body.
You're going to lose viewers.
But the Garfield costume
gets to come off.
So that's like a plus.
So here's this part.
I could snipe people away from so far.
All right, hold on.
Let me get this connected here.
How the fuck is this?
Is there instructions with this?
Okay, here's the button.
I got to plug it in here.
Okay.
Dude, check this out.
I want-
I'm serious, dude.
I want you to stand across
the whole entire studio
and I want you to shoot me
in the fucking face with this.
People think this is a joke,
but this is the real deal.
Does that connect like that?
Do I actually need these fucking instructions?
Did I put it on wrong?
I think I put it on wrong.
All right.
Hey, can you like figure this out?
Can you like fucking-
Well, because it's like too hard.
It's too hard for my fucking tiny brain.
Just read the instructions
and figure out how to shoot.
I have the trigger on the wrong way.
All right.
Airzooka.
That's a lot of fun.
I can't wait to get fucking in the face.
Remember that one?
Pile over there.
All right.
Next one.
I'm sorry.
Damn.
All right.
Here's another one.
So again, this is just an-
I already-
I explained it like four times.
What is this?
Five pound box of assorted misprint
rackable office big bulk lot.
What the fuck does that even mean?
I don't know what that means.
That's a long sentence.
What am I gonna-
What am I gonna do with this many fucking-
It's pens.
Why?
Oh my god.
Okay.
Is this-
These are pretty-
Actually pretty cool.
All right.
Hold on.
Liberty Tools from the Bronx.
It's like 500 pens.
I'm gonna take like three of these and store them.
And I gotta like-
What am I gonna fucking do with these?
I'm gonna have to donate them or send them somewhere.
Jesus Christ.
Well, that's really funny.
What is this?
This is from Nationwide Insurance.
Who packaged this shit?
That's what I want to know.
Somebody had to put these all into a box.
What like weird pen company are you?
This is like a misprint.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I'm gonna like-
I'm gonna take a trip to like a bunch of law offices
and be like,
I want some fucking pens.
Well, thank you for the pens,
whoever suggested that.
That's good stuff.
Get this one.
You still trying to figure out the air, Zuka?
Get this off.
You're gonna have to like hire some more help for this one.
Is my hair all fucked up?
What is in here?
It's the Bitcoin Inner Gnome.
11 inches high gnome statue.
Exclusively designed by Joystick.
Hand painted with exquisite details.
Funny Bitcoin good luck charm.
Great for indoor and outdoor use.
This is gonna have to go on my desk.
It's not gonna happen.
Oh, God.
I have to see what it looks like.
I need to know what it looks like.
Fucking Bitcoin.
I haven't talked about Bitcoin in like seven months.
This thing sucks.
This sucks, okay?
I-
There you go.
This doesn't go in your-
Do you put this in your front lawn?
Is that what it's designed for?
I have no idea where this goes.
Do you put this like on your kitchen counter?
Why would you own this?
Hey, remember that thing I bought that dropped 75% in value?
This must have been a product that was sold like 11 months ago
and people thought it was cool.
Well, I'm gonna have to-
I'll just put it on my mantle.
All right, what's next?
I got some fucking trash.
Can you grab like a trash box?
Oh, yeah, yeah.
This one's heavy.
This is the walkeroo stilts.
Easy walking handheld stilts.
That's really, really funny.
Oh, great.
Yeah, let me like put these on and pretend I'm fucking 6'4".
I can't even.
Why do they have to have like children on here?
That just makes it so much worse.
Yeah, I'll just throw it in there.
Walkeroo.
I'm not even gonna be able to reach these.
We're gonna have to cut to the other camera while I-
Are you still figuring out the bazooka?
It's got four pages of instruction.
Who would have thought that it would be that hard?
Oh, my God.
Hey, Merry fucking Christmas and happy holidays to you.
How bad is my hair look?
Be honest with me, dude.
Like be real.
I want you to be honest.
Like, should I put like something on?
Should I put the hat back on?
The car feels like a bad one.
But I'd rather look terrible.
Look, I can't.
I'll open that later.
Look at all this shit.
What am I gonna do with the pens?
I'll do this later at the end of the stream.
All right, oh, we got some more.
There's a stocking here.
Let's go ahead and open the stocking.
Why not?
There's a single earbud.
Is this because-
So I get this one.
I actually do get it.
A single earbud.
That was my favorite one.
Because, I mean, it's pretty comfortable.
Okay, for those of you that have no fucking idea what this is,
I can't wear two headphones because I'm fucking strange.
And when I have two headphones in,
it causes me all kinds of distraction and stress.
And it closes me off in the whole world and I feel weird.
So thanks for the one earbud.
Do I get stereo from here?
Can I get stereo sound from this?
I'm actually gonna use that.
I'm actually gonna use that one.
Hey, how's that Airzooka doing over there?
What else is in the stocking?
I don't know what this is.
What is this?
This is black gloves?
What's the joke?
I don't understand.
Why, I don't, why, what's the joke here?
It's just long black leather gloves.
I feel care instructions.
Hand wash, do not wring, do not tumble dry.
Is this a sex thing?
Hey, is this a sex thing?
You know?
I said no sex things.
I don't think I can answer that question.
I can't even fit my fucking hands in here.
What?
Is this handle long?
Yes.
That's why I can't figure it out.
What is fucking going on here?
Oh, those are for your feet.
Are you sure?
Oh yeah, they're for your feet.
No, they're not.
They're gloves.
Those are for your feet.
No, there's a hand.
I'm not taking my fucking socks off.
You can't see your feet right now.
Are you sure these aren't just weird gloves?
They're gloves for your feet.
Why would somebody wear these?
One, two, three, four, five.
Don't look at me.
Don't put your feet up there.
Are you talking shit or is this for real?
I'm serious.
I put this on my feet.
Yeah, that's what the gift is.
It's foot leather gloves.
Amazon Prime, baby.
Foot leather gloves.
I just don't, I don't understand it.
Okay.
You weren't supposed to put the handle on.
This is the dumbest thing I've ever seen in my life.
I've seen a lot of dumb shit in my whole life.
And honestly, I went to fireworks one time.
I went to the fireworks show when I was probably 14.
And they did like four fireworks and it ended the show.
And I said to myself,
I'll never see anything stupider than this.
Never in my life.
I have now.
This is the worst thing I've ever put on my body.
It's the stupidest thing I've ever seen in my life.
You did the Airzooka.
You broke it.
I broke the Airzooka.
You weren't supposed to put the handle on here.
Take the handle off.
You take the handle off with your feet or something.
You've got good grip down there.
I don't, who would ever put these on?
I gotta move on because I can't handle this.
Don't, you're gonna, don't throw it to me.
All right, here, this is another gift.
Wow, that was explosive.
Maybe there's like feet in here.
Banana award.
All that's in here is this top banana award.
How much was this, do you know?
I know this is like 30.
There's at least 10 in here.
I don't even show them all.
How many top bananas can there possibly be?
Isn't there only one top banana?
That doesn't make any sense.
I'll keep one because I'm the top banana.
I got the top banana.
That sounded wrong, but what else is in the stocking?
Let's find out.
Okay, oh, look at this.
It's blue and what's in it?
Ooh, a sex thing.
This is called the Ubing.
Enjoy shopping.
This has got a kind of a fucked up,
like grayed out, blacked out kind of case.
This is a sex thing.
I know it.
No, this is cool.
I would actually wear this.
This is actually kind of cool.
I'll wear this.
You guys think it's a joke.
I'm going to actually wear this like on a daily basis.
It's got aeration.
It's got plenty of air.
I don't like what a daily basis.
What's wrong with that?
It's got breatheable.
It's I actually kind of like this.
This is sex thing.
Let's find out.
It's just a nice tank top.
You got to go full Garfield or full no Garfield?
Not working.
Says who though?
Hold on.
Let me use my like my like foot grip.
I knew this was going to happen.
Didn't I tell you that?
Didn't I tell you that one of the things
was going to be a Garfield costume?
I was certain.
It's funny that that was a self-fulfilling prophecy.
Are you sure?
Yeah, I didn't make the original list.
Yeah, but I just knew that there was going
to be a Garfield costume in here.
But if you hadn't have told me that
there wasn't going to be one.
No, but there was.
There always will be.
All right.
Has that does that look like I'm going?
Dude, my fly was down in the first
fucking 10 seconds of the stream.
I'm talking that was like a triple fly.
That conductor outfit had a like quad fly.
It was like from here to here.
So can I be embarrassed anymore on the stream?
I don't think so.
Thanks for the sex thing.
Whoever suggested that.
All right.
What else is in here?
This feels like clay.
Is this like a dick?
This is like a hairy dick.
I thought I said no like dicks.
This is not a hairy dick.
No.
Are you sure?
Yeah.
If I open this on streaming,
this is like a big hairy cock.
I'm going to be fucking really mad.
It's a fanny pack.
No, that's a big dick.
That's not a fanny pack.
Horizontal.
I hate this.
This is like a fucking hairy cock.
I swear to God.
I'm not going to win.
Oh yeah.
Top banana.
That's fucking great.
Oh, by the way, all these gifts are going to charity.
Can't wait to send top banana.
I can't.
Oh yeah.
What?
Like you want like a dad dick?
Yeah.
Give me a break.
Whatever.
I'm just going to wear it.
I thought it was going to be like toys.
All right.
Let's keep going.
What else is in the sack?
No.
There's nothing in the sack, Jeremy.
Just some Christmas spirit.
Here's my voice.
It's still like something high.
Is there anything else in there, Mr. Saka?
No, Jeremy.
Take a hear his Christmas spirit.
No, don't kiss him.
A bag gift.
A bag present.
What?
Why are you laughing so hard over there?
He's laughing really hard.
I don't know why.
He's fucking cracking up.
And I can't figure it out for the life of me.
All right.
What do we got here?
Oh, hey, there's a turkey.
Oh, it's a seagull.
That's actually really nice.
Nice job, everybody.
Nice work.
Why?
Why is this so funny?
You can't hide it.
I will.
This is great.
I actually like this.
This is auto.
We'll play with this.
It's a nice seagull.
We've saved up.
You know what?
We saved up with 50,000 seagulls.
You know that?
He doesn't give a shit.
He's like laughing at it.
He put on a fucked up filter on my voice.
I guarantee you.
That's what happened, right?
What is this?
Is this for a baby?
Oh, I know.
I think this is a dog costume.
Is this a dog costume?
This is a Pepe the Frog dog costume.
Auto is not going to fit in this.
He's way too big.
Yeah, there's no way he's going to fit.
Maybe your dog can fit in this.
Hey, Merry Christmas.
I got you a gift for you.
Hey, you want a sex thing too?
Hey, heads up.
Okay, which one's the sex thing?
No, the frog is not here.
Hey, I just don't want to fuck up the computer.
All right, sex thing.
Never mind.
Anybody in there?
You know how much I'm a pain in the ass.
Let's try to get this fucking thing to work.
Oh, I went about to just put my hand through it.
This is officially licensed stuff.
Okay.
I thought this was some knockoff.
Oh, lunch meal.
Thanks for the 10 bucks.
Hey, man, I was originally going to write some dumb chat meme here,
but in the spirit of Christmas,
I'd be more incisive to say that you have the funniest guy on this platform
and that's all that's there.
Guess who got cut off by this fantastic HP computer.
Oh, let me get there with my...
Okay, you know like in Breaking Bad?
No, what's the Adam Sandlin movie?
Where the guy is like the fucking foot.
Funniest guy on the platform.
I'm sure half the times I've ever laughed my whole life
has been because of you.
You deserve all the support you get.
Man, cheers and happy holidays.
Hashtag charity.
Thank you, lunch meals.
Yo, Merry Christmas says you have a smoke-wise ganja.
Thanks a lot.
1500 bits.
15 bucks.
Hi, Jeremy.
Hashtag charity.
Thanks for the rand-wraps.
Hey, Jeremy, happy holidays.
You're one of the few reasons I have as to why my depression is less than so much
since high school.
Keep me an amazing hashtag charity.
Thank you.
I'm glad you're feeling better.
And then Freudian Weapon for $10.
This stream is the best Christmas gift I could have hoped for.
Thank you so much and Merry Christmas.
Hashtag charity.
Thank you, Freudian Weapon.
Thank you all.
And thank you to the HP $30 at Walmart fucking machine.
All right, what is this?
I don't want to open that.
I'm not opening that one.
You can open that one.
I saw like a fucking bug, a scorpion, and I'm not touching it.
There's like a bug in that one.
I said no bugs.
I said no fucking live animals.
I said no fucking, I'm not, I saw the scorpion and I don't want to touch it.
Is there a scorpion in there?
You got to be, I don't want to fucking touch this.
Is there a fucking scorpion in here?
Glow in the dark.
Genuine giant wasp hornet.
I can't, I don't think I can fucking do it.
I'm not even kidding.
Is that coming up on screen?
Is this a real thing?
Is this for real?
Oh my fucking God.
I can't do it.
I, you do it.
Is that real?
Is that a real fucking thing?
Oh God, why would somebody want that in their house?
How are you, how are you touching that?
Don't open it, don't actually open it.
Hold on, it's an Angelina Jolie blood pendant?
Is it really?
It's a Billy Bob Thornton blood pendant thing.
Jesus Christ, how could you fucking, it's touching my face.
Hold on, wait, how do I put this on my neck?
Did they get like a, get a good view of that?
Fucked up.
That's real.
In you want it, it's genuine.
That's fucked up.
I can't fucking handle that.
I think breaks it, it's gonna get out.
It's gonna kill everybody.
That's it for the stocking.
I thought it was a scorpion.
All right, here we go.
What's this?
Thank you.
I was gonna buy these anyways.
These are Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles
insulated hard spout cups.
These are sippy cups
because I spill things all the time
and it's not embarrassing.
Look, there's two here.
You can have one of these.
You know how many times you've,
how many times have you dropped like a coffee
on your desk?
Never.
Well, I have.
And this is, this prevents spills.
This stops bullshit from coming out of your glass.
You're not gonna, I will actually use these.
This is another one of those.
I'm not even kidding.
I gotta get out of here.
I gotta go.
This is one of those scenarios.
I'm gonna actually use these.
Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles sippy cups.
I put coffee in these.
Like, fuck it.
I'm keeping those.
All right, we got some more.
This is, oh, I hope it's supermodel.
Mario 64 is an exfoliating foot peel mask.
What's with you guys and like the feet?
There's like three feet gifts here.
I'm gonna give these to Kim.
Don't tell her because like this,
I'm gonna give this to her.
For soft, healthy feet, natural ingredients
and botanical extracts.
Get this off.
Seriously, I'm getting uncomfortable with that on.
But here's the, this is like a funny joke
to like some of you guys,
but Kim isn't gonna go nuts for this shit.
She is gonna be so happy that I have these.
Oh, that's great.
Hey.
Oh, Kim.
Hey, Merry Christmas.
I got you a gift.
Hey.
What's in this one?
This one makes noise.
Bean Boozled.
Naughty or Nice Jelly Beans.
No, I don't want to do a thing where like,
oh, he's a YouTuber.
He's gonna eat the fucking jelly beans
and they puke because it tastes like earwax.
Fine, I'll eat one.
These are gross jelly beans.
You spin a wheel and oh,
what kind of gross jelly beans
are you gonna eat tonight?
Fucking dude.
I'm just gonna pick one.
This one.
I don't even know what it is.
This is just kind of yellow.
Nope, I'm not gonna eat that.
Not gonna happen.
That tasted like somebody peed in my mouth.
So I'm not gonna eat it.
I'm gonna put it right here.
Hey, thanks for the funny thing.
What's this one?
This one's a little white with some yellow.
I think it's spoiled milk.
It sure does taste like it.
Or it might be rotten egg.
Whoa, what's this one?
This is dead fish.
If this is dead fish, I'll throw up ice cream.
You're gonna have to cut.
I know you're busy doing something,
but if this is rotten fish,
go to the last funny clips thing from last year.
Not that one either.
No, thanks for the gift.
Thank you for that.
Thanks for suggesting that I get that.
That was just like,
I just smelt sardines in my nose
and I couldn't fucking handle it.
No, that's it.
My, that's it.
Who would make money with this gift?
I put it on a stand.
Can you imagine selling a product?
I mean, I get it, right?
It's supposed to be fucking disgusting,
but why would you ever say,
oh, hey, yeah.
Just buy these dead fish
and battery acid jelly beans.
They're fucking delicious.
It's so funny.
You prank your friends, okay?
My friends don't think it's funny.
That's not funny.
It's just, it's just gross.
Oh, I'll spin the wheel.
Fine. One more time.
Everyone's probably like,
spin the wheel, you fucking wanker.
And I'm just like, fucking mate,
just chill out, mate.
You know what I mean?
There's a wheel.
Dare to compare.
All right, let's spin it.
I don't know if you can even see that,
but this has landed on,
I already ate that one.
I'm not eating dead fish again.
Juicy pear or booger.
So this is supposed to be a booger.
Oh, I get it.
So each one of these could be
either a juicy pear or booger.
Let's see if this is booger.
I mean, pears kind of taste like boogers, so.
I eat boogers all the time.
So I know what it tastes like.
It tastes like kind of like,
sour and rotten pear.
Hey, thanks a lot.
Thanks for the suggestion.
Oh, no.
Okay.
What is going to do with that?
I'm like, fucking prank my friends.
Hey, Jay Talens.
Just in case you're wondering,
I'm going to give you a jelly bean for Christmas.
You're the only person in Las Vegas, by the way.
So it's all my fucking fault then.
You fucking.
Oh, you fuck it.
You're going to throw me to the fucking water.
You're going to fuck it, throw me to fuck it.
You know I didn't have a goddamn choice.
You know I fucking.
Fuck.
Fuck you.
I did what I had to.
I fucking.
You can't fuck.
We got another present here.
Ultimate Clay Sand.
All right, this is cool.
I'm definitely.
I'm going to donate this one for sure,
because this is fucking cool.
You ever play with sand before?
I've never made that noise in my life.
I just like decided I was going to make the noise.
Because like, it's funny.
And like I see my friend.
Don't trim.
Whatever.
He's like a friend and it's funny.
I don't make noises like that.
I'm not even loud either.
Yeah, this is fucking brilliant.
Really cool.
This is you pour this out.
You can mold it and play with it.
Now, this is a really, really awesome thing.
Definitely going to be donated for sure.
Because this is fucking cool.
All right.
Yeah, Clay Sand.
Never dries out.
Feels great.
You can make like sand castles.
And I'm doing that here because we're in studio.
And I ain't fucking up the studio.
So this is awesome.
Cool shit.
I was going to have a lot of fun with this.
Thanks for the suggestion.
Get in there.
All right.
Yeah.
I forgot I had this on.
I forgot I had like dad dick on.
Why don't we go back here?
Let's go to like one of these.
One of the table gifts.
What do you say?
Just use some magical powers.
My name is Steven.
Steven Frog.
What the fuck?
Is it real?
No, it's a soap.
Summer.
This is smelling up the whole fucking room.
Body butter.
This like stinks.
Oh, we've got some fucking magical Christmas fax machines.
Hey, look at that.
Can you smell this from here?
It's a frog soap.
Here, I'll show you.
That's pretty awesome.
I'm going to use it.
You say what the fuck?
What the fuck?
No, it's WFC.
Who would have carved that?
That's pretty fucking cool.
Brown speckled frog.
I'll be rubbing this frog all over my body.
He smells like Ferti Pebbles.
Oh, that's good.
That's pretty good.
Oh, that's kind of good, right?
That's great.
You don't like it?
It's fun.
Why do you not like it?
Sorry.
This thing's normal.
Back to your corner.
Is it not normal?
Is this thing made with something fucking weird?
What is this made with?
Is it made with something weird?
Is this a joke gift?
Thank you, Salad Gravy for the $15 hashtag charity.
Thank you.
Thank you, Ranglets for the $10.
I'm kind of drunk at this Christmas party
and I've never said bits before, so sorry in advance.
Anyway, I want to say you're like the funniest,
most genuine streamer ever.
Thank you for all you do.
Merry Christmas.
Merry Christmas to you, too.
Skip one.
I skipped one.
Oh, the great Canadian fuck club.
Thanks for $50.
No one's in here.
In where?
Did you see the train that I built earlier?
That was fucking cool.
Cut to the fucking, cut to the train.
Cut to the goddamn train.
Fucking cool.
Look at this.
Were you here for this shit?
Were you here for this?
I don't think you were here.
I'm gonna have to hit me in the fucking mouth.
No.
No, no, no.
No, no.
Oh.
Actually, did it get me like...
No one's gonna book it.
Whatever.
Some library is gonna get that, okay?
Well, a local Las Vegas library.
I'm gonna donate that to a library.
And you fucking, they're gonna build that up.
They're gonna put like trees and shit.
It's gonna be great.
I can't wait.
It's gonna be awesome.
Hey, unconquerable.
Thanks for the 10 bucks.
It's pronounced un-con-quer-able, you boomer.
Anyways, Merry Christmas.
You give me and my friends some of the biggest laughs we've had.
And I continue to cherish each one of your streams as you do them.
I can always appreciate the lengths you go to for your fans
and can say it with confidence.
Did I fucking hurt myself?
Then you, my favorite streamer.
A big hug to you, Kim Italics.
And Otto in chat.
Keep on keeping on.
Germa Hart, thank you.
Demonic Cucumber, thanks for the 10 bucks.
Hey, Germa, I wanted to give some big bits to say thank you.
I've been having a real bad time at home
and the first time in my life I wasn't excited for Christmas.
I want to thank you so much for the stream.
It made me excited and happy at Christmas again.
Thank you so much for making me laugh so much
that I wake up my mother.
Thanks so much, PSA.
Hey, Peter.
There you go.
And Genetic, thanks for the 10 bucks.
Genetic, hey, Germa, I remember watching you back
when you played TF2 and you have been there
for me during the darkest times.
I just want to say thanks to you.
Have a Merry Christmas.
Hashtag charity.
Thank you.
Merry Christmas to you too.
Happy holidays.
I got that from Bugle Mary.
Do I have any more presents?
Hey, you want to eat a booger jolly bean?
You want to eat a booger jolly bean?
You want to puke on stream?
What do you think?
Why don't we both eat one?
Okay.
Come on, get over here, son.
All right, if you puke, your channel has to get banned
if Twitch staff is here.
That's twitch.tv slash Alex.
Ban him if he throws up on my stream.
All right, so this is birthday cake or dirty dishwasher.
Okay, come sit down, have a seat on the couch.
So that's birthday cake or a dirty dishwasher.
Are you ready?
I don't get that away from me.
All right, are you ready?
Are we cheersing this?
Yeah, cheers.
Mine's awful.
Yeah, that was gross.
I'm out of here.
They're both dirty dishwasher.
Are they?
This is bad.
Is this okay?
It's like illegal to eat this.
Is it illegal to eat these?
No, I had some good ones.
Easy joke.
But seriously, but like really though,
thanks to italics for being like tech director.
He's been the one that's switching the scenes
and like taking care of things.
What am I going to do with that?
What do you possibly put, where do you put that?
Sub sound.
That's not going to be, no,
I'm turning off sub sounds forever.
Is it like a funny joke version?
No, it's just nut.
Some things are worth a nut.
Here, you like these, have some.
You like these?
Hey, we gotta talk about presents to unwrap.
I can't wait to like drink coffee.
This one first.
That one first.
Pacing.
Pacing?
We have to pace this production.
Why?
Because it's time for a little change.
Oh, it's the Lord of the Rings.
It's a Gandalf costume.
Hey, look at me.
All right, so thank you by the way.
Get this fucking Garfield thing off.
Do I have to wear the whole costume?
I have to put the entire Garfield costume on.
I mean, you know what?
This is actually, for all the shit I talked,
this is pretty comfortable.
I could see no one wearing this
and Jim Davis having a terrible creation
and the thing's not even funny.
And like after 1996,
they should have canceled the entire series
and there should never have been another book ever made.
And I don't know why it's an American icon.
But it's comfortable outerwear, I think.
All right, here's the frog soap.
Can't wait to fucking on that.
No.
Hey, Gandalf.
Define this one.
All right, do I have to put the whole thing on?
I shouldn't have to, right?
It's probably one piece.
Is it one gigantic piece?
How complicated do you think Gandalf's costume is?
I mean, it really is just like a big gray tablecloth.
Is this the beard?
Holy fuck.
Look at this terrible hat.
Wow.
Holy shit.
Is it inside out?
I feel like it is.
Did it come with a beard?
How am I supposed to put this on?
I'm like stepping in it.
I guess I'm gonna put it on like this.
Why Gandalf?
How many times have I ever talked about Gandalf on the stream?
Like maybe three times ever?
I'm surprised there's no hobbit costume.
Because like, oh LOL, he's got like his fucking feet.
He's got his small.
He's like five seven.
But you give me the Gandalf costume?
All right, that's fine.
That's the Gandalf costume from the hobbit.
Well, here's like the weird cigar that is his beard.
This is the beard.
It's like a fucking what?
It's like a lunch lady hair in it.
It's like a snake.
How is this a beard?
This is a beard.
This is the beard?
What?
Oh, it's a beard.
Where's the beard?
I don't understand where the beard is.
All right, when I say this, you gotta put on like a cool voice.
But wait till I get the whole thing on.
Okay, so where's the beard?
This costume didn't come with a beard.
Seriously.
Where's the fucking beard?
There's clearly a beard on that thumbnail thing.
Where's the beard?
Where's the fucking beard?
There's no beard.
What a scam.
Was I supposed to buy a beard separately?
All right, put me on.
I gotta be honest with you.
You shall not pass, you fucking dingus.
Tell me when you're ready.
So I'm gonna say you.
You need to point at me when it's ready.
I still taste dishwasher soap.
Ready?
Okay.
You shall not pass.
Okay, there's no beard.
What a shitty costume.
That's the worst fucking costume I've ever seen.
Fuck that company.
Fuck the company that made this.
Fuck that whole company.
There's no beard.
Okay, this is just like dirty guy with a funny hat on.
What's in here?
A piece of timer.
This is not a gift.
This is, this was supposed to be LED candles.
For when Bugleberry did his little thing.
It's a prop.
It's a prop that was supposed to,
and I was wondering where these were.
Remember I asked you specifically,
I was like, I think I'm missing a fucking package.
So was your two presents.
That's one.
These were supposed to be scattered around
and I didn't know where they were
and I think Kim accidentally may have
packaged them up.
And there's like somebody's card in here.
Okay, because I was wondering where the fuck these went.
All right, well, that's great.
Thank you, me, for buying a prop that never got used
and was accidentally wrapped up, apparently.
Hey, there's another one.
Who is this from?
The Mods?
Chat?
Are we sure there's another beard lying around here somewhere?
Give me yours.
Just like cut yours off.
All right, what's in this one?
Let's see.
It's more, it's more bananas.
It's more you're the top banana.
How did this get through?
A second gift.
A second you're the top banana.
That's not even funny.
I think he went two boxes
and she just wrapped them separately.
It's the same gift.
So we're missing three gifts.
Where did they go?
I don't know.
So these are supposed to be in one, in one package.
And she wrapped them in, okay.
It was the same order.
It's the same order.
Well, there's like 50.
They sell them in multiple boxes.
Let me, let me, oh.
Did they do anything?
Did these do anything?
They're just plastic bananas.
What a waste of time.
The smiley face.
Look at that face.
You could, okay.
You could seriously like give these to people on the street
and be like, hey, let me tell you something.
You're the top banana.
I got so many of these.
What am I going to do with this shit?
What a joke.
All right, well more top bananas.
I'm not sure how that happened.
I thought I had the dad dick on still.
What's this even for?
I thought.
Got it.
Oh, this is a magic science for wizards only.
I think I fit that category now.
Magic science for wizards only.
Nice.
Okay.
Cast color changing spells.
Is it, can I, can I try one?
Is it elaborate?
If it's elaborate, I'm going to donate it.
It goes into donation if it's like elaborate and fun.
If it's a Gandalf costume with no beard, it stays on my body.
That looks pretty fucking elaborate.
Have fun with that.
Son.
Okay.
Magic science.
It's like sorbitol and food coloring.
What's that for?
I'm not sure.
That's it.
This is cool.
Magic science kit.
Have fun with that.
Somebody's going to get that.
They're going to have a fucking blast.
They're going to make like.
I just kind of spit on it though.
Like I'm sorry.
And I fucking packaged it wrong.
I'll fix it.
Don't worry.
I can't use that right now because I'll be in big fucking trouble.
Thank you for the magic science kit to make potions and brain fluids.
Sounds fucking cool.
Just put these around.
Why not?
I was actually fucking looking for these too.
Like that's so stupid.
All right.
We got like seven or eight more.
One size fits most of those battery operated fan inflates costume.
This is an inflatable costume.
It's an inflatable frog.
All right.
Hey Gandalf go fuck yourself.
Your last three movies weren't even good.
They were good.
Did you like the Hobbit?
I mean the Hobbit was all right but like it wasn't as good as
Gandalf which is the number two one.
All right.
Let's put on the frog inflatable and then you have to.
I'm going to body slam me.
You have to fight me in the frog costume.
I'm going to one punch man you.
Remember that fucking anime?
I got batteries though.
I'm ready for this.
This instructions.
Oh Jesus Christ.
Body socks fancy dress.
All right.
What are the instructions?
They're in Chinese.
Wait.
All right.
Congratulations on the purchase of this costume.
Good fun and enjoyment will be guaranteed.
Please read the following.
Four double A batteries.
I got those.
You're going to you might have to help me with this shit.
God.
How do I get in here?
How am I supposed to get inside of this like a zipper?
All right.
I need where's the battery?
I got like double A batteries.
I need to put them in here.
All right.
Open is where the batteries go.
I got to unscrew this.
Hold on.
So it's all my fucking fault then.
I feel like they're over here.
Where did I put the batteries?
Where are the batteries?
I brought so many batteries and they're gone forever.
I got plenty of banana fucking toys.
They go.
Oh you're gonna knock the tree over.
Do you have any idea where the batteries are?
Where?
Where are they?
I don't know.
Oh I thought you just said you knew where they were.
God.
Stay over there.
Something bullshit.
Oh the spider.
This guy's battery's dead.
Okay.
Oh I need to help.
Oh.
What are you playing right now?
Where the fuck are those batteries?
So it's all my fucking fault then.
You fucking.
Oh you fucking.
You're gonna throw me to the fucking wall too.
You're gonna throw me to fucking.
You know I didn't have a goddamn choice.
You know I fucking.
Fuck.
Fuck you.
I did what I had to do.
I fucking.
You can't fucking blame me for that.
Fucking bullshit.
Tell it again.
Tell it.
Listen.
I've told the story like four times.
Just please let me be the example for this okay?
Stay the fuck away from yard tools.
Don't touch anything dangerous.
Don't like rake your leaves.
You're gonna like.
And then all of a sudden you got $1400 worth of dentistry work.
Actually can't beat him.
He swings way too weirdly.
And I can't even get the correct controls right.
Shouldn't do r2 twice.
Don't even think about it.
All right.
No no no no no.
Come on.
No no no back up.
No.
Oh.
Rock.
Got it.
I got it.
I just had to get these open.
The this open.
Where's the pepe the fucking inflatable frog.
They're double a never mind.
It's fucking what a waste of time.
He's a double.
Triple a and I need double a.
Bring like a whole box of that.
I brought a box of them.
And I don't know what the fuck they are.
What is it here?
It's a triple a.
It's a nothing.
Where are the batteries?
They're in this bag.
Oh god.
Are they over here?
What's over here?
Oh for the love of god.
Fuck.
Where are these batteries?
I'm going to lose my mind.
Shit.
They're in a ziplock bag.
Does anybody see these fucking things?
God damn it.
Like there's so much shit over here.
If I don't know where they are.
They're gone.
They're just apparently they're gone.
All right I'll put I'll put it on later.
I'll try to find it later.
Next present.
Thank you for the next gift by the way.
Thank you for uh this is this giant home.
An Ottoman alone.
What on earth?
I mean this is cool but
I've actually seen videos of this thing I think.
This is actually really fucking awesome.
All right hold on.
Where is in that one?
I don't see anything.
Next to your left leg.
I see a spider.
Your left thigh.
I need to open this with a screwdriver.
Fucking screwdriver man.
I bought like a pack of triple A's and a pack of double A's for this exact.
I see three.
Can you find me one double A battery?
Find it for me.
Double or triple?
Find me a double A battery.
I can't fucking open this thing with this.
Where the hell am I real?
Oh damn it.
Screws.
Why does everyone have to have a bunch of screws?
Fuck.
I need to turn the lights on.
You want them on either of them.
Series where I play Minecraft.
This is going to be a single player let's play.
And when I say let's play I use that term pretty loosely because I'm an idiot in this game.
You're going to see lots of fails.
You're going to see lots of triumphs.
At least I'm hoping.
So go grab yourself a nice hot cup of coffee.
Hot cup of cocoa.
I got apple cider right here freshly brewed.
Let me take a sip.
Ah that's good cider.
All right so let's get this started.
Create new world.
World name is going to be Germacraft.
Sounds about right.
Yeah okay.
Game mode is going to be Survival.
That's the most interesting I think.
More world options.
Seed for world generator.
Okay this is important.
I got to name this something crazy to get cool.
It's not Germacraft unless you have something crazy happen.
So I'm going to go fight this asshole over here.
Look at this cows too.
Do I have I don't have a sword.
This is going to be interesting.
I should have just made one.
I should have just made a sword.
What am I doing?
Why am I doing this?
Why am I going after this guy right now?
What does the matter with me?
Actually play this game.
I just I'm just using my walls.
Oh yeah that's fine.
I'm just going to tear down my own walls to get wood.
That's right.
Yeah let there be light.
Aim up.
Always cut down the whole tree or else it won't disappear.
That's what grandpa told me.
Look at that beautiful moon.
So elegant.
Okay so I got that wood.
Let's do something with it.
Make it into a bunch of things.
Shift click.
I promise this is not going to be this much of a mess through the whole series.
And if it is then whoops.
Welcome to another episode of JermaCraft.
And as you can see I'm doing a little bit of renovating.
Doing some renovations on the house if you could tell.
Because this thing is a mess.
Just trying to clean it up a little bit.
And oh my god no this has happened before.
Don't worry.
Keep going below with the coal.
Mine is steel.
We got a man at steel and man at cobblestone.
Where the hell am I even going?
All right let's go.
I will find something before this pick breaks.
Or it was it'll kill me.
Oh yeah aimlessly digging around.
Best part about Minecraft.
Torch.
Oh we found a little bit of coal.
Did I get the wrong way?
All right you gotta come zip me.
You gotta zip me.
Does this go inside?
All right zip it up.
Is it doing it?
It's all the way from the track.
You gotta start.
It's caught.
You have to do it.
It is caught.
It's caught.
You got it?
No the zipper's stuck.
Okay what's left?
Oh thanks man.
Thanks for the iPhone charger.
Sick.
I thought this was a friend.
Oh no.
I can't see in this fucking mask.
You don't even have to head off.
This is very disorienting.
What?
What are you gonna have?
Hold on.
I'm gonna have to pull against your neck.
All right do it.
Eat your own hand up.
I don't want these.
Don't drop them.
Pull that thing over your head.
It's in the back.
All the way at the back.
What?
No no no.
Here.
What are you talking about?
Grab here.
Right there and pull that thing over your head.
No no no it doesn't work like that.
It's like a double.
There's like frog eyes up there.
I can't see anything with this.
This is bouncy balls.
Uh cool.
I'm gonna donate these.
I can't fucking believe these all fell out.
Oh god damn it.
Stilts have screws.
This is the last part of them.
This is vibrating my ass.
This is the last one.
Oh and it is the best one by far.
Absolutely best one by far.
This is shot water tapping.
This is like the only thing I wanted for Christmas.
Seriously.
This is the only thing that I wanted.
What?
Does that work?
It looks like you've put something up.
This is the this is the best gift to do last year.
You look like scuffed Yoshi.
Yoshi!
Brrring!
Is that it?
I can't open this because I don't have the thing.
I don't have the I don't have a screwdriver.
Is that it?
Is that right?
Thanks for the tip.
Why would anybody fucking wear this for more than five seconds?
I I actually can't get out of here.
Listen the stilts have screws, Jack.
Oh how do I turn this fucking thing off?
Uh best gifts of the evening?
I'll tell you.
Rope the Iruzuka.
Uh Iruzuka.
Sick.
Seagull.
Salt water taffy.
Bouncy balls.
Kind of fucking cool but like not really.
Um bananas.
Not really that cool but like all right.
Uh wait I forgot the Pepe the Frog fucking gloves.
The pens were uh we'll never have to buy another pen forever in the rest of our lives.
What do these go on your hands?
Oh right the gloves like this.
What?
This is fucking stupid.
Well uh that seems to be the end of the of the gifts.
I'm gonna see what is donatable.
Train's gonna go to like a public library.
Some of this other stuff is gonna go to charity.
And uh you got it?
Did I like fucking that whole thing up by putting it on wrong?
Yeah put the handle on the wrong place.
The seagull's awesome.
I'm gonna be using that on my desk.
The bananas.
I don't I don't even know what to do with them.
This is too many of them.
There's fucking like a hundred of them.
It's gonna be fun to uh pick up in about uh 10 minutes.
But uh I'm just gonna wear this for Halloween next year.
What are you doing?
Oh you're showing the elaborate um pilot shit.
Thank you everybody for your suggestions.
Thanks to the mods for obviously I fucking spilled these.
That's gonna be a pain in the ass.
There's so many over here.
Thank you for participating.
Just a fun little thing I wanted to do.
Thanks to B.F. Fugaberry for doing the scary stories for like a Halloween Christmas
stream.
He was really really adamant.
He really wanted to come but don't believe anything you hear.
They're all just fun.
It's like um it's like Yoshi.
You know it's not real.
He's a made-up character and people make up characters all the time.
So just know that people make up characters all the time.
It's a made-up character with whatever they're making up for the character.
So uh thank you all for watching.
That's the end.
Hope you have a Merry Christmas.
Happy Holidays.
There's the stream.
And how long was this?
Like four hours?
No.
248.
I thought it was like four hours.
Well thank you everybody.
Hope you have a good time.
We need to get out of here.
We're we have the studio for only a fine amount of time.
So we're gonna get the fuck out of here.
Hope you enjoyed.
Hope you had fun.
Thank you again for the presents.
Well thank you for suggesting the presents.
I will get this to work and I'm gonna use this on the next stream.
So I promise you I've seen these things.
They go like...
Yeah good.
Racing!
Thank you for the $27 in bits.
Peter with the 20 bucks.
20 bucks from Peter.
Garfield the Monday Killer with 10 dollars.
Thank you.
Hope you have a great day.
It's probably 50.
From Hank Liss Crown.
Hey what am I waiting for?
There's a fucking fax machine that it was you know...
No I'm not gonna break it because it's all I got.
And I opened up the ink machine.
It's just gonna be okay.
Let's just keep it there.
I'm not gonna break it.
Thanks.
With 15 dollars.
Hey thanks for the 50 bucks.
Ow.
Ow ow ow ow.
I'll give you a filter.
And you're going to sing with like the filter with the musical filter.
Okay.
To basically end the stream.
Wish everybody a happy Merry Christmas.
Yeah I'll see you guys on
um the 25th.
I'll see you on the 27th.
The 27th is the next stream.
Maybe we'll play some Viscera.
Battery acid.
Jolly beans.
I'll see you on the 27th.
Have a very Merry Christmas.
Happy holidays.
Thank you for joining us.
We're out of here.
Sing what?
What am I supposed to sing?
What song?
And thank you for joining us on this stream.
With all the fun gifts that you have given me.
I appreciate all the fun stories we told tonight.
And thanks for the giant comb.
It's all right.
Is that good enough?
Yeah.
See you on the 27th.
Merry Christmas.
Happy holidays.
And fucking take care of yourself.
And take care of your fucking friends.
Take care of your family.
Have fucking fun.
Go take care of people.
Have a great time.
Merry Christmas everybody.
I'm probably going to actually use this.
Like actually.
It's huge.
We out?