Okay, hello. Alright, so here are the options. We can start season two and do like episode one.
Or we can wait and actually dedicate a whole stream to doing like two to three episodes.
Or I open up Mordhau and now that progression actually works, be able to play and level up
and buy stuff and actually progress in that game. Those are the two options. I'm probably
I don't know. I'm not sure. I'm leaning towards... I'm torn because I really want to
level up in Mordhau just because I want to see what's in the game. And then we can save season
two for give it its whole stream. Give it even so I don't have to just do one episode or
one and a half episodes or something. Alright. Yeah, I think that's what's going to happen.
We're going to play Mordhau for a little bit and then Sam and Max season two
will dedicate it so we don't have to have it be one episode spread out and then two
episodes. I'd rather just do two or three episodes in one night. But season one concluded.
Why ask? Well, I'm just curious, you know. I mean, I'm going to do what I
feel like I would have the most fun doing right now. You know, season two would be fun,
but I'd rather dedicate it to a whole stream. I didn't put a poll up. I was just deciding.
I didn't put a poll up. What are you talking about? If I had put a poll up and left to
go to the bathroom and come back, then yeah, I didn't put up a poll. I was just
torn on what I was going to do. Alright, so let's change this over. Plus, I want to see
what's in that game. We didn't get a chance to see the other items. I did do a poll.
Yeah, I did the what I did. What color am I? Poll. How do you do the degree symbol?
It's like a little, it's a little O, right? Because I can't, it's fine. That's, that's,
that does not look correct. But who cares? 360 O's. Alright, let's open it up. Alright.
Thank you for watching Sam and Max. It will return. We will do a, we'll properly do
season two. That's not a lie. Look, if this is going to be a Jerma lied about Sam and
Max scenario, you wouldn't have seen season one today at all. I would have been like,
yeah, I don't know. I don't know if I, I don't think I'm going to do it today.
I would have been like, nah, I don't think so. Maybe next week. I didn't want to
conclude it though. Alright, open. Hopefully this is not too loud. It might be lying
about Minecraft story mode. Oh shit, I was trying to mute this. Everything has to be loud
as fuck. Don't you guys know? So let's go over the, let's see what's, what's on tap here. We got
Wednesday, I want to do dreams stuff. So when you will probably, so dreams is Wednesday,
Thursday, I got something I want to do in there. Alright, here you go. Here's the block
out for this week coming up here. So Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, and then probably Sunday.
That makes the most sense. So you'll probably, we'll do season two of Sam and Max before
we started on Friday. Dreams is coming back because I, I want to show you some things
that I've made. So like, hopefully I can get some shit to see. And if anybody else has made
anything, if you haven't, if nobody's done anything, then whatever. I, you're not expected
to. Alright, here we go. Now the question is, will this work? Will you work? Is progression
functioning? Cause I really want to see what's available in the game. Okay, it does. Thank
God. Good. So let's, let's test this theory. I'm going to search for a battle Royale.
I gotta remember how to play. Don't do BR, please. Look how quick that was. That was in
seconds. He's just, he's turning into a normie streamer. No, no, I just wanted, I just wanted
to see. Yeah, last time this barely worked. Alright, I remember and this is the stab.
This is the feign. Oh, I forgot you can kick. You can kick. What's kick? What is kick?
Oh, I remapped it. I remapped it. There it is. Fuck. Does this play better than chivalry?
Um, I, I have this weird memory of chivalry where I remember playing it a lot, but I kind
of don't. I feel like I'm having more fun in this game than I did in chivalry. Like I
don't remember like really that much about chivalry. It's been too long. Alright, last
time I did this, there was like 10 people in each one of these. Rock and a bandage. Oh
god, I got a rock. Okay. Is that what all that was in there? Five ammo. I need to move. I'm like,
I'm freezing. There's a chest right there. There's like two chests. God damn it. I hope
they didn't. I'm surrounded by chests. Alright, I got a falchion. There's a, uh,
bear trap. I'm just gonna put it down like right next to the chest and I need a
shield or something. Shield. Okay. What is this? Light chest. Okay, it's on.
Ah! My, oh my god, what the fuck? That hurt so bad. I don't, that scared the shit out of me.
Why did that just scare me so much? I'm out of here. We're not doing Battle Royale.
Frontline. I'm just gonna do matchmaking. Okay, it's time for season two episode one
of Sam and Max. Finally. Come on, give me a server here. Come on. I'm trying to get
in your game. Come on, Battle Royale took like 10 seconds and the other
fun game mode is not gonna take. Come on. Maybe I should try a different region
or just go right in the browser. Uh, any game mode is fine. There are a shitload of these
servers. 39 out of 48. Oh goodness. This is gonna be a mess. There are 800,000 people
playing this right now. Are you kidding me? There are 800,000 people playing this?
That's insane. Let's just get in a game. It's 30,000. Oh, I was gonna say that's more than,
that's more than like Dota 2. This guy's so dead. I'm the one that get hit by that.
Really? Yeah! Oh shit, I thought he was red. Oh boy, too many people.
Do-O-Mega-Lol-Ota. Fucking Omega-Lol. Why do I find that so funny?
Yeah, I chopped off his arm, mate. All right, here we go. How do I, here we go. I want to throw it at
him. Watch out, watch out, watch out. I didn't mean to. I didn't. I promise. Damn it. I'm going
for a stab. Shit. Damn it. Oh, I stepped in the fucking fire. Spawn here. I gotta do more faking.
I like the fake into the stab. So you go like, I'm gonna stab. That works a lot. That's
really, really hard to defend against that. I just want to unlock a new weapon. All right,
here we go. Up here. Oh, fucking bear trap. I was so tunnel-visioned into trying to hit this guy.
Shit. Damn it. Professional gamer. Well, not really. Oh, that's way too many. This is bad.
Really? That didn't hit him. Who even killed me? I don't even know what happened to me.
Let me change classes. How do I change classes? It was me. Oh, that was the last stand. Right,
right, right. You're right. Really? Really? What was that for? Now I have 50% of my health gone.
He's just waiting for me to land. Watch out for this dude. He blocked it. Someone's gonna drop
down here. Come on. Thank you. Watch out for the fire. No, that's not a guy. He looked blue.
His left side is blue. He's like two-faced. I didn't think he was gonna go straight into me.
If I don't sprint, I'll regenerate HP. Good to know. Thank you. Heal by walking,
not by sprinting. LOL. Idiot. All right, let's make something happen here.
How did that guy block that from behind? How? I don't believe it. Nope.
Okay, don't sprint and just stand here and heal. That is so fucking funny.
This game is, I love this game. All right, I got him right in the head.
He's behind me. Somebody behind? Oh, God. What? This guy didn't even do the tutorial.
What? It's really annoying when these streamers just jump into a game and they just like,
they just play and they don't even do the tutorial and they talk about like,
what the fuck? What killed me? It's like you didn't stop and heal. I don't know what
we're talking about, but this game is like a fucking problem with the game. It's like you
have to press Q to feign he's not doing that. These fucking streamers. You know what I'm
saying? Nope. You were taunting. Let's see it. Clubbed. I'm going way too far up here.
I got to slow down. Getting too zealous. Whoa. What? That's okay. I died so fast and I spawned
so fast. I just saw myself dead on the ground. We lost. Oh well. I'm not in the last place. Yes,
I am. I thought I came in late. Come on. I'm not very good, but I still have fun.
Last place. That's what losers say. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
You can't have fun while playing games. Don't you know that's the worst thing ever.
Okay. Let's go with. I don't know. Maybe. Mm. Raiders. I like Raiders. It's fun.
You shouldn't be laughing. This is your job. It's my job to be really good at video games.
Come on. All right. I'm ready. I hate it when Jerma has fun. Why? Do you want me to be mad
and talk about like, I'm not just, I'm just fucking not even fun. Like this is like seriously
like fucking not even fun. It's like too hard and stupid. It's like everyone's too good at
the game and I fucking like it. It's like I died. We played against people that had been
playing for like 50 hours today. It's like not even fun. You want me to do that? No,
I'm not going to do that. I'm going to have fun. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. This guy in the
corner here. I'm going to go overhead like that. Holy shit. That guy killed everybody.
Easy with that. Don't come in too hot here. Somebody behind me. Ah, shit. You have to be
monotone and serious. Fine. That what you want. Here we go. Oh, fuck. I'm laughing.
I'm not supposed to be doing that. Hey, why is do some of you do this to me? That's not
nice. Oh, that's a, that was a legit misclick. Okay. All right. No, no, no. That's okay.
That's fine. Fuck. Oh, I'm getting so outplayed. Fuck. Died to stick. Well,
there were four of them over there. Oh God. That's the one thing I didn't like
about crossbows. They take too long to reload. That's the one thing I don't like.
What? What happened to my weapon? You don't even know who's here. Somebody's
coming behind you. Good job. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. Chat's going to yell at me. Where's my,
where's my health? There we go. Hey, what just hurt me? Did I get sniped? Don't,
I'm trying to heal the fuck out of here. I would have had more health. Too many. Really?
That was a weird arc there. Damn it. Attention. Horses in the stables. Red team OP. The blue,
it's quite funny. The blue team generally team kill more due to people mistaking them for
red players when they are low health because they're blood. That's so funny. I've definitely
been guilty of that at least five to ten times. What are you doing? What? What are you doing?
That guy just ran into the wall and died, I think. He put up the wall and the guy like
bugs-bunnied into it. That didn't hit him. Watch it. No, dude. Shit. You can't hear the game. What?
No, dude. It's really quiet. Is it? Is that better? It should be. Uh oh. Getting a little
bit of frame dropage here. The guy playing the harmonica or whatever it was just got
crushed. I get too distracted by the funny things on screen. Let's go. Got the roof.
All right. Makes that guy swing again. This is too confusing. I'm going the other way.
What? Hold on. I hit that guy twice in the back and he's still alive?
Frame rate. No, no, no, no, no. Oh, he's got that perk, right. Okay.
Fuck. Nope. No way. Get those bastards. Enemy is capturing the stables. Not good.
All right. I'm gonna go shirtless guy in here. Ready? Puck. Okay. I'm in the middle of everybody
now. They both did the same thing. I'm trying to go around the corner and like hit him in the
face. All right. I was doing okay. It wasn't like the top five and I'm dropping down.
Let me get another couple kills here. Minus 67. I'm gonna go. I'm gonna wrap around. Watch this.
Watch, watch, watch, watch, watch, watch this strategy. Never mind. There was no. Never
mind. Never mind. I was gonna wrap around that guy but he backed up too much. I thought
they're gonna fight in the tunnel together. Ooh. Oof. Should I? No. Bad idea. Hey, I'm just
trying to heal. Wait, was I blocking? I think I was blocking the whole staircase up here.
Got it. Somebody ran all the way over there. This guy doesn't know.
Stay out of his peripheral. I'm gonna hit him right in the head.
Damn it. Capture it. All right. Watch out for those spikes. Guy on the, on the, on the
treachery belt. Whatever. The trebuchet. It's our trebuchet now. Oh yeah. Now we got a
string. Now we got a string. Fire. Horse. Horse. Give me the horse. What? What happened?
Because it was in the fire? Oh. The horse died to fire and then stumbled on me. Did
that guy fall down? Is that a teammate? No. Damn it. Ooh. He went all the way around.
I know what you're talking about now when you say that they might, that they look
like they're red. Everybody I try to hit. What are they? Wait, wait, wait, wait. Hold
on. Hold on. Hold on. I mean like seriously. What? He just, it's like he's shooting rocks
over. I gotta go visit this guy. I have to get over there. Come on. That was right in
the back of his head. I took, that was clean on the nape of his neck. Ooh. He caught that
one with his teeth. Ooh. Hey. Is that all you got mates? Oh, but it is a take to take me
down. Seven. How many? Eight. Click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click,
click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click, click.
Really? Level two. I should be much higher than that. Come on. Oh. All right. I gotta
get the trebuchet guy again. This time I gotta take his head clean off. Oh God. Oh God.
Why are you standing there still? No, I can't play like this. He was alive.
Uh, he was probably rage typing. Definitely. Fucking idiot. Why do I have to get out of
always the losing team? Seriously? Like I have to just stop team killing. Oh my God.
I mean, okay. Let me be fair. If you were riding in on a stallion and you were going
in for the kill and there was a free target for me just standing there and some dude just
swung and cut your horse down and you fell off. What? I can't swing it here.
That guy's so relentless. I couldn't fight him in there. Oh, wait. Right. You're right.
Right. Right. Okay. I can hold the, I can hold it in a different way. Can I? Right. Come
on. Right in the fucking head. Right in the fucking head. Oh, crossbow. The horse is OP.
Um, I, I, maybe I'm just not experienced in the game, but it's hard to control. Am I helping?
No, not really. Oh yeah. Destroying these guys right now. This one's running. Please
close the door. All right. Let's all, let's get in there. This is not, we, nobody can move.
No, no. Stop. Open the door. What have you done? I'm just gonna stop moving.
Ah, ah. Oh shit. Guys. I got it. It's okay. Don't worry. Oh fuck. Close it. Close the door.
Close the door. Close the door. What's he throwing in here? Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no. Where am I? Oh shit. Oh my God. What? Oh fuck God. I was just in Super Mario
World. How did I not get hit and how did I not hit anybody? The never-ending Bowser
staircase. Can I open the gate? Nobody else fighting up here? Holy shit. Where did you come
from? He just did, did you see what he did with his hands? He just like changed hands.
He like switched hands. That was weird. That was bad. We can't just stuff in here like this.
Oh yeah. I know about Q. I use it sometimes. I know about you can, you do stab into faint
there. You can do a swing into a stab. You can Q. You can kick. You can kick into a kick.
You can swing into a swing. Dude, if you just had not walked right there, you walked right
in front of it, I could have healed. I did the tutorial last time, but it didn't count
because the servers were down. So I would just be doing the tutorial for money. But I don't know
if you guys want to see, I could do that off stream, you know, and we really want to do
that right now. I don't even know what's going on, right? I guess it is worth it for money.
How did he die? How many more? One guy. Oh god damn it. I've seen too many episodes of TV.
Doesn't work like that. The guy on the horse always wins. I was like waiting for and prepared
to strike him down. I've seen too many fucking episodes of TV. Okay. I've played too many
video games. I've seen too much TV. See you later. Oh, that would have been a fucking
champ moment if you ask me. How much gold? 600 gold. Finally leveling up and getting
money for playing. Nice. That wasn't the last place. That was right there in the middle.
All right, one more game and then we're gonna go spend some money. 600,
that's a lot of medieval money. Yeah, it is. This time we're gonna go,
I'll go protector this time. Why not? We have the smoke bombs, the mace, the shield.
Can two people get on the horse? That'd be funny if you could.
Archer on horseback. Let's see how this plays out. Are we gonna go? You gotta lead the charge.
Okay, capturing. Okay, on to the camp, wherever this is. All right, watch out. Nice work. Watch
out behind you. Did that hit me? I think I got hit. No. I took it down right when he started
swinging. Derma shield spam. I'm a protector. I'm supposed to get in front and put the
shield out. Can I heal with this character too if I don't move? Yes. So it's only, it happens no
matter what. Yeah, guys. That guy's, whoo. Oh, a guy from firefight with a fucking sword.
God damn it. Press end. What? Why is he still on the horse? We got three people smashing
him. Is that him again? No, that's our horse guy. That didn't hit him? Archer is so hard.
If you hit it, it's hard though. Oh fuck. No, no, no, no, no. 70 damage is pretty hard. That's
only two shots to kill somebody in the head. What is a headshot? Is it dead? It's a dead shot
is what that is. Damn. Really? I was standing still. God fuck. The little arrows. Like, okay.
I guess I got him. Ooh, the Pankai is just out to get you. Well, whatever. Let them come.
We just got destroyed. Vote scramble. I feel like I would really love that bow.
Uh, where have we not gone? This one's cool. Don't go in the bedroom. Oh, okay. Oh,
okay. Right, right, right. Along to the game has hats? I don't think that'll take very long.
All right, we're gonna stick with it. What are the breaks?
Is he chasing me? He's chasing me, isn't he? All right, somebody else take this. I don't want
it. Yeah, watch out. Oh, I can see them. Is that a balloon? That's a balloon. I'm helping.
I'm helping. I helped. Oh, that went right by his head. Hello? Let's go. Shit, I had it.
Where's this dude? Hey, what are they? Oh, this guy's right in the head. One,
two, three. Oh, no. He knows. He knows what I'm trying to do. That guy just killed himself.
Come on. Thank you for the help. I appreciate it. I'm coming out. Why did that not run him
over at least? I blocked it. Oh, where is he? I think I'm gonna hold it up like it's a sign.
He's gonna get hit in the face. I remember my bow. He knocked my bow out of my hands.
Why is he? I didn't do that. I didn't do it. He got R1'd from above.
Here he's running. He's running. Oh, didn't get away this time. Sorry, mates.
Oh, I blocked it. This is bad. I gotta get out of this. Uh-oh. Oh, I held up. I made it.
I made it. I finally did it. Even for five seconds, I did it. I gotta get closer.
Damn it. That guy distracted me. Wow. Come on. Just stand up there. People throwing
pans at him. That guy got a frying pan at him. Oh, shit. No. That guy has a lot of pans.
Oh, I thought he was gonna step back. All right. This guy's done. Headshot. Three, two, one. He
jumped. Watch this guy right here. This guy is just like fucking taunting. Oh, no. That guy was
so dead. Speaking of dead guys. Yeah, speaking of the guys that are dead. Hey, trying to take
out my fucking... He blocked that point blank. He's still up there. Oh, he's still there.
Oh, is he still... Are these even going? What's the drop like here? Am I shooting too low?
Get the fuck at it. Give me this thing. Oh, shit. I can throw it. All right. New plan. I'm going
to... Let's go with this guy. We got short sword, fists. All right. Let's make something
happen. Damn it. I'm so sorry. The guy with the hammer is seriously freaking me the fuck
out every time. Oh, you can throw it. Okay. Why was that just a weird like,
wiffle ball throw? Oh, that was a full baseball swing to his face. It's another one. Oh,
that's another one. Oh, who's doing that? Nice block. Oh, come on. Come on.
Oh, it's going crazy. Oh, my God. He's gonna die. He's gonna die. He's gonna die.
He's gonna die. Did he die? Why did he not... The countdown. Wait, how come that's his
territory? Oh, bullshit. I was waiting for him to have the four or five seconds countdown.
Nice. Oops. I hit like four people on my team. I was like a hundred miles away.
I reached across the Atlantic Ocean to hit that guy. They're killing their own teammates.
Oh, what are you doing? What the fuck are you doing? Watch out. Oops. Oh, the stupid catapult
just hit me right in the head. Dude, that... I want to see a replay of that. The dude with the
two pins. I came across. My sword was like 40 feet long. He blocked it. Nice. Come on.
I'll take the bolt on. Let's see. I'll take your fucking all on at once. I'll take your
fucking all on. I need to heal. Heal. Heal. Heals. Somebody heal? Damn. What do I need?
I need some more assists. I'm gonna go around the corner here. Watch this. One, two. Yes.
Uh-oh. It's pan guy. This guy with the pants. Seriously. Every time.
Oh, everyone is getting clubbed by my weapon.
Uh-oh. Damn it. Three pans and no armor. He just runs up and I end up just clothes lining
him every time. Sorry. I'm too busy fucking paying attention to other things in my mind.
You piece of trash. Stop killing the guys with the loots? What? Why?
Is that like a sandwich heavy or something? How is that not... Holy shit. That guy got hit
by five weapons. It's too hard to pay attention to some of this shit, man. Seriously. Like,
I need... I gotta focus again like I just was. I gotta go out on top here. Well, no. I'm not
stop playing, but... I was so focused. Now I'm just laughing. No, that didn't block. Damn it.
No. I'm so pumped right now. I gotta be in first. How much time is left?
Just presented my crotch to him. Guys down here. I'm gonna wrap around and see if I can poke.
Damn it. A little too high. I still don't have that down. Again, this guy again. The guy with
the pants. Come on. Kill him. Here he is again. The guy with the pants. Ooh, good blocks. Give me
it. Give it to me. Oh, fuck. I was gonna throw it at him. That guy is just a free...
guy is a free kill. There he is. Oh, my shit. Come on. Throw it. Throw it at me. Oh.
I was just desperately trying to kill this guy. Oh, right in the back of the head.
Damn. 35, 35, 14, 13, 10, 7. That would have been cool, wouldn't it? One day. One day
I'll get it. Ow. Is he dead? Oh, shit. I'm getting so into this. Did you tell us
tonight's powerball numbers? 8, 14, 77, 6, 2, 2. I guess. Holy shit. That guy hit me right in the
head. Oh, boy. Oh, no. I think I'm gonna lose my first place here. Come on. I gotta get,
like, a couple more kills right here. Ow! What the fuck? I probably could have done it if I
wasn't being a dickhead. Oh, I really could have done that, too. If I wasn't being such a
dumbass, I probably would have gotten another kill or two. All right, I'll make a character now.
Let's see what weapons I can unlock. All right. Armory. So, let's go down here.
What am I? What is this? Ain't gonna work. Okay, so, Archer's Camp Wanderer's Hood. Can't do
that yet. None of these. Chain Coif. No, it's too much money. Root Smokebomb Cleaver Primary.
Okay. A little Hand Axe. I feel like I'd like that. A War Hammer. Oh, why? Yeah, I think so.
War Hammer is so cool. I need to be level four for these. I am level four. Oh, four points.
I see. Well, let's get rid of this shit. Okay. I want to do- I think I want to do War Hammer.
Let's try War Hammer. War Hammer and Targe is not bad. Greatsword.
Maul. Execution of Sword. Evening Star. Well, I'm gonna keep the rock. I think War Hammer,
Targe will be all right. Utility Head? Popular Head and Gothic Head. Holy shit. Okay, that's
cool. Shaft. Hybrid Handle. Bar Handle. Let this drop a hybrid handle. Is it just cosmetic
or does it do anything? I mean, I like that look better than this. Okay, can I upgrade the rock?
What about Chest Mail? Torso Chain Mail. That's only 480 bucks. Oh, shit. Well,
that's okay. I can put this on. Shoulders. Basic Shoulders is 300. Yeah, put them on.
Okay. Arms. Anything for free? What do we got for perks? Fist damage? No.
Melee damage against structures increased. Repair effectiveness. Bloodlust. Full health on
melee kills. I mean, it's just- why would you not have that on? Passive. That's all I can do.
Wow, your character looks good. Well, give me a break. He's got a little while. Okay.
All right, I think that's good. I'm gonna try the War Hammer. We have to keep playing
to unlock cool stuff. All right, back in it. Please put on a helmet. No, we don't need pants.
Not yet. All right, this is official. Five out of six. Six out of 48. Los Angeles. Mountain
Peak. This is frontline again. Team Deathmatch. Let's see, we did a lot. We'll do Deathmatch.
We'll just do standard Deathmatch. Well, maybe not. I do like the frontline maps. So
much fun. I'm going back in. Do I not want to show the server? It's all right. I mean,
at this point, it really wouldn't be that hard for someone to find the server I'm in.
You know, it wouldn't take very long. Okay, so this is the War Hammer. What's it swing like?
Cool. Is there another way to hold it? I can swing it around the other way. I can do the
claw of the hammer. I wonder what the difference would be here. God damn it! I forgot,
because I was on the other team for so long. You just crit your teammate from behind.
I know. I know it's fucking bad. Damn it, that didn't hit. Yeah, assuming the blunt is probably
for better for heavy, right? All right, whatever. Boink! Oh shit. Damn. Oh god. All right,
so I had the hammer switched the other way. Seems like he had light armor on. I was only
doing 20 damage. Do I have that backwards? Nobody's playing the objective. The spike
should be for armor. Yeah, I guess. I had it the other way around. Too many. Yeah,
claw to pierce, hammer to bludgeon. Yeah. I don't know why I thought the spike was
going to do more damage to it. I got peasant armor. This is a really, really fun game.
It just, it's got, it hits all the notes. I can see you. Holy shit, your whole team's here.
Here. I killed him with the rock. It's just not, I'm going to go the other way.
Heal. Come on. Yeah. Okay. Sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry, sorry. Is that it? We got
two more, right? Yeah, right in the face. There's a guy behind. Is this a bad guy?
It is. What? We lost. I must've joined that one in the very end, huh? Nobody played the
objective. Yeah. You have to play the objective on the objective map. That's right. It's not just
TDM. Oh, I like this map. Middle fighting in Warsong Gulch. That really is what it reminds me
of. I don't want to get like across the mob. Rock kill. Can I reach? I don't think I can
reach. You can't reach it. Oh, damn it. Oh, well. Oh God. Oh God. I thought that guy was just
swinging over and over again. I thought he was going to faint. One of them. Here we go. This
is not good. Too many of you. Come on. Pierce that armor. Kick them off. God damn it. There's
too many of you. I can't. Back it up. Use rock. 36. I feel like this is the wrong side
again. It's got to be... Jesus. All right. Desperate times, guy. That's not working out.
I got to go with the... back to Brigand. I'm kind of getting rolled here. Who's playing the piano?
What? What is going on? What's this music? I thought that was a little loot.
Not like a band in a box. All right. He's almost dead. I thought there was a guy right
here. There he is. Oh no. No. They don't even see me. Oh, come on. Oh, the guy comes
at a fucking stage left with a horse. This is bad. This is bad. Yeah. We just got steamrolled.
Play the objective. It's hard to play the objective when the other team
kills all of your team and they're all still alive. You can't really walk out the door.
Red always gets rolled on that map, do they? No. I'm going to get auto-picked.
Just TK the loot guy. I can't do that. People will be mad at me.
I have no idea what I'm doing on here, but I'm going to do it. Is there a way I can
actually aim the sword? Oh my God. Oh, that's my first experience trying that.
I think he took my head off. Oh, he's using the lance. That's why.
Killed off by stage left by horse. No, I mean, I saw where he was going.
He killed me. All right. Let's go. Time to turn it back on.
Oh, come on. What the fucking horse. Stop. I need to play as the loot man.
No, I don't like loot man. You just do this and like dance. Oh God, here he comes. I smelled him.
Dude, can we just have the door fucking open? Does this have to keep going like this?
No one has been able to take that guy off the horse. He's been running around in a circle
for like eight minutes. I didn't do it. You understand, that wasn't me. I may have been
thinking it, but I didn't do it. I'm so concerned about everybody. There's somebody behind me too.
Look at how bad we're going to be. Look at the guy on the other team. We're going to be so bad
because that guy over there has 10 kills. One guy. Smoking is all. I just got instantly killed.
All right. I got to stop looking at the guy standing still with the loots.
They're distracting me. I'm not even looking at him. I'm going to, I'm facing the camera
this way. Damn. I thought I was going to walk into it. Damn it. Fuck. No. Look at the kill feed.
All right. Give me a break. Come on. Look at this shit.
I can't. I can't. I can't. Why is he going in a circle like this?
Oh my God. Oh, my face is itchy. No. All I can hear is the music. Oh my God.
I got to change it up for something, man. I can't even do anything. There's a dude on the team
with 34 kills. Somebody sign that guy up. Oh my God. They were just everywhere. It's almost
like they have a double spawn rate. Are they spawning inside of this building? I'm going to
get him when he comes around. Watch this. I'm ready for him. I told you. I ripped him out of
this fucking dimension. Who the hell is behind me? Get vehicle damage. Finally. Maybe I'll do
something with the bow. Got to get on the objective though. That went right through his
body. Stay on the cleaver. All right. I'm on. I'm on again. I'm turned on again.
Oh, that's not hitting him. Oh, thanks for the shield. Can I get anybody from back here?
Probably not. There's a guy over here. No, I got a guy in the back. Do I win the prize?
Is there? Will you leave me the fuck alone? Kill him. Please. I'm dead. All right. I guess
I'm going to go with like Raider for a while. There's not somebody back here, right? There
is somebody back here. Got him. I helped. All right. Heal. I took his head off. We did it. Oh,
I thought I could get him down before he could. You really want that, don't you?
You really want to get that, don't you? You want it so bad you can taste it. Oh,
I was stuck on top of the horse. I didn't know that little Labo supported this game.
New to the Nintendo Labo. That was pretty sick. That was perfect. Streamer, look at the chat.
What? What is it? All right. I'm going right up the middle here. Thanks. There's somebody behind me
in there. No, I thought, no, it's just a cage. This guy. He finally panned me. He finally found
me and panned me. He did it. Got it. Oh, I thought. I got it. Vehicle. Oh, my God. He
actually. Oh, hi again. Did I make my own class? I did make my own class, but I don't
really have enough money to make a good class yet. I could do the peasant thing. I need more
armor, I think, if I want to make a class. Because I'm walking around with no pants on.
I got that. I tapped that guy so many times. There's no way he stays alive from that.
He's been quadruped. He's got a triple tap. They're surrounding me with pants.
All right. I'm going to play something else to submit to the pans. I'm going to have to
become one. I'm going to get some kills here. Get away. All right. We're pushing out. Let's go.
As a team, we can do it. Why are you over here? What the fuck is this guy doing?
Loot man gets revenge. I'm going to need one guy over here. Guy on a horse though.
No, that's our horse. Oh, my God. They're doing like psychological warfare on me.
No, too slow. I'm going to go back tonight. That guy has 67 fucking kills. All right. New server.
Thank you. It's not going to do anything. It's going to take 30 seconds for someone to defy
this fucking server. I like this map though. All right. Fresh start. Let's go. Did that not
hit? I hit the flag. Ah, fire. All right. Am I going to die? Three, two, one. I'm alive.
Are you serious? How? He's typing. Typing. Got the guy typing. Sick. Typing destroyed. I don't think
he was typing that. I think he was typing. Hey guys, I got to go. Can you be faster than me?
How is he still alive? I was trying to fake that. Let's see. Holy shit. Oh, right in the mouth.
Why do they always run? Stand and fight. Oops. Whoa, too many. Why are you running?
Why are you running, dude? Loud as hell. People here. Well. Oh, come on. How?
That was no horse, was it? I thought that was a meteorite. Kick them. What did they do?
It was a medieval meteorite. That's far too many. We all just got killed there. Five of us
just died. Okay. Let's go this way. All right. Move, move, move, move, move, move. We can do
it. Oh, fire. Good, good. Clear them out. Clear them out. Fuck. There's really nothing I
could do there. How long did it take? It's all right. Whatever. He's on my team. It's fine.
I didn't touch. That didn't hit. I didn't connect. That was fucking funny.
Whoa. Well, that was okay. That's not a good idea. Back to the team. What's happening?
Oh my God. Well. Yeah, you can ride a horse in this. It's crazy. It's very fun. Damn it. Ah,
somebody behind me. Fuck. Got killed by Rockman. Probably. You stabbed him in the back.
Oh, come on. Just aim the thing there and just wait and then press the button.
You'll kill four people. Just keep loading it up. Yeah, let's do new game mode. And we're gonna,
we're gonna bring the sample size down here a little bit instead of like 50 person servers.
Okay. We've got four deathmatch death. We've done all frontline. This TDM.
Now hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Let's see what we got for team deathmatch.
Team deathmatch is fun. Do a dual server. Great screen while I'm picking a server.
No, let's bring down the player count and do a, let's just do like some TDM. All right.
Whatever you do, don't press tab. No, it's just enough. Oops.
I actually didn't mean to press that. I was trying to press Q.
Fire, fire, fire. Oh, I got hit in the head. Don't touch that dial now. We're just getting
started. There was just little congregation here of fighters. Well, I didn't want to hit
anybody in the head accidentally. Easy. Nice. Good job. Really? Damn. Oh, I probably should
have spun it around on that guy before. That was weird. All right. Here we go. Back in the
action. I just didn't know which way to look. Left and right. Both my blind spots.
Okay. This is just TDM. How much does the game get? I think it's 30 bucks.
25 right now. Maybe something like that. Oh my goodness. They're all over here.
I got to pick a spot and stay there. I'm just so, I keep trying to change directions.
This guy's walking. Is this guy role playing? Oh dear. That was a mistake.
Oh, that was a mistake. Was I enough of a bait for someone to get killed? Can I climb up
the rocks? I'm just trying to be like the guy that runs in for this guy to stab him in the
back. We won. I want to play like a full round. I keep joining and like did three
minutes. It's over. Loot, loot, loot, loot, loot, loot, loot. No, no loot. I'll do my final
round as a loot. Okay. Ooh, this is fun. I like this one. Oh, packet loss. That's not good.
All right. Let's go this way. No, that's bad. Let me regen. Oh, no more glass bottles of
gasoline. Good job. Kick him off. I think he did. I think he kicked him off. Looked like
it at least. I really, I thought he was going, I thought he was going to get blocked
by the guy in front of me. Apparently, I just got hit right in the head. I thought that he
was going after the guy right next to me. Oh, he walked into that. It wasn't my fault.
I'm trying to kick somebody. Let's do Raider. Oh dear. Oh dear. Oh dear. Not good.
It's going to be an extra kick perk. That would be nice. No, that's okay. Not good. Oh
my god. I'm just going to hang out back here. Let's go short here. No one's running
through here. Nobody else is going to run through the door, huh? No bad. No bad. How do
you minus one from team killing? Too many. Wow. I just, I got spun around. I just can't
get anything going. No. Oh my god. I'm doing so bad right now. I need like a smaller weapon.
Give me a scoundrel. Green and yellow would be better. That's actually a good idea. He's
gone this way. I didn't block it. He was doing the same thing waiting for me.
I just have to play defensively here. Good job. Damn. I didn't think he was going to get that.
Get him. Somebody get this guy. Oh, this is fucking Superman. We can't kill this one person.
He's just running around. I got it right in the face. Oh, at least that wasn't at the
very bottom. You haven't won a single game. Yeah, I'm one of 50 people. Is that really?
I had like four people play Lutz the whole time. Is that my fault? I can't carry. What?
You really think that's going to happen? The last game I had three people trying to pan me.
I'm the variable. Like apparently I am. Watch the sides. Sneak in. Sneak a little bit in.
Heal. Oh, boy. Oh, boy. I need to heal. This is not a good place to heal in front of everybody.
In front of- Oh, this guy's just wildly swinging over here. Get him. This guy's- Why?
I'm a psycho. Oh, right in the head. Come on, right in his face. No. Well, that was
probably a bad idea. I ran into him and he just over- it's almost too long. And I just
put my mouth up. I was like, yeah, take a picture of my mouth. He's over here. He just
hit me right in the mouth. Fuck. I didn't know that many people here. They'll kill each other.
Good. I need to be behind. We're both just the same thing. Nice. Good work. Oops. Stick
him. Stick him. Oh. Let's see if I can sneak in my skewer here. I'm trying to hit that
guy. No. Shit. Guy behind. All right. I'll try to- after this map, I'm going to do a-
try to find, like, another server. Maybe we'll do some 1v1s, maybe. I don't even know which side
I am. Okay. Well, I helped. He just got Stooges. I could smell that one all the way, all the way
over here. I'm going down. Yep. Ah, shit. I got locked up. This game is very squelchy.
What do you mean squelchy? Squelchy? Damn it. One in front, one behind. Not much you can do.
Does Jax do games like this or only shooters? Jax does anything that I ask him to,
as long as he's had enough rest. Usually he's, like, seven months. Seven months of rest.
Oh, fuck. Jax is just Jerma's competent alter-rego. That's- yeah, that's true.
All right. Let me get him to, like, a- we'll- we'll do a little bit more. We'll do some
duels. And are there any official duel servers? Or do I have to find, like, a custom one?
I don't think there's any official ones. Let's see. All right. We got 1v1.
I don't want 32 people to go. Duels. US West 1v1s. That looks pretty good. All right.
1v1s. How does one determine? Do I just pick out an opponent and we go? All right. Guy with
the t-shirt on. All right. Do I say yes? I think we just- you just fight. Hey, get- no!
I don't- I can't even, man. I seriously can't get over that. He just kind of ran up and started
swinging. I guess it's you and me again. Oh, boy. I'm just getting fucking killed by this dude.
Hey, you! Oh, fuck. That was long. Shit! I was pretty much sure if I connected that.
Like that? Ah. I don't know what to do here. This is- okay, you and me.
It's quick. I- I've tried to flourish, but where do I go? Over here? Somebody? I need to
get back in line. Where's the duel line? Hey, you! I guess we could fight each other. Wait,
hold on. I gotta- I need to heal first. All right. Me and you. Ooh, good. Ooh. Uh-oh!
No! I could have pressed two. I forgot I had another sword. Okay, you two fight.
All right. Let's go Minecraft Steve. That's exactly who this person's playing as. Like,
this is Minecraft Steve. That's a big swing windup, too. He's dead. I need to heal.
Okie dokie. Don't do that. Not nice. Really? Okay. Well, I- this is- I was supposed to fight
this guy right here. Did I cut his hands off? I'm so confused right now. I think I chopped up
both that guy's hands. Ah, I thought he was gonna fake it. All right. Wait, that's- all
right. That's not fair. He's throw- all right. You know, reset. Reset. Not fair.
Somebody's being a dick. Somebody's being a dick. Okay, here we go. He thought I was gonna
fake, didn't he? Mm-hmm. He thought I was gonna fake. All right, let's go. Why is everybody naked?
Over! That was fun. Am I- no, I'm not naked. I'm just default regular character. That was a lot
of money. 11 h- no, no, no, never mind. All right, I'm gonna do this again. I'm gonna do
this again, but I'm gonna do, um, what am I- maybe I want to play- I don't have enough
money to buy anything. I'll try spear. Let me see. The tutorial is gonna give you 2,500. Yeah,
that's true. It's true. So can I- spear is obviously you want- is there a way to- because
you don't want to swing a spear, right? It's all about stabs. Oh, fuck. He's relentless.
Damn, all right. He just was right up in your face with the dagger. I don't really
like the spears. It's- it almost feels like- it feels like I'm trying too hard to stab.
Whoa! That was a little laggy. Get a halberd if you want to swing. Yeah. I don't- I can
unlock it. It's all about spacing with the spear. Yeah, it's- I guess I just don't think
about how long it is. That's really long. Nah. Nah, I don't like it. I don't like it.
I don't like it. Let's go raider. All right, let's do it. You and me. Ooh. All right, I'm
gonna- my stamina is- I'm freaking out! Okay. I just got really panicky. Chamber you casual.
I don't even know what that means. Oh, he tried to throw that at me. If you stab
at a stab, you will chamber. Okay. I think- but we have the wrong idea here. I don't know who-
All right, I guess I'm fighting you. No, it was you? Oh, I thought he was gonna fake.
Ooh, nice. Damn it. Flourish. Yeah, I know how to flourish. Am I supposed to do that every
time I want to fight somebody? Damn. I must have got him right in the good spot. Ooh,
that would have hit me. Hello, Steve. Oh, I was gonna flourish. Ooh, that's a windup.
The pickaxe is really cool because it has a huge windup. Ooh, chop his legs off. I haven't
fought you, I don't think. You. Right there. A little belly poke. That's not how you hold a
sword. He's trying to blunt me. Okay, yeah, sure. Ooh, that like double pump. Nice. He does
like- that like fake fake pump. Minecraft Steve coming in. Oops. I tried to fucking fake
it out. Holy fuck, I didn't think that was gonna happen. You never expect somebody to
throw their weapon. Whoa, what are you trying- what are you trying to pull here?
Oh, pan guy. Oh, a little too close. Damn. That was fun though. Good job.
I can't play after that one. Okay, let's try this again. Let's try this again. Wrong
thing. This thing. Damn. Oh, that's fucking dirty. That sword is awesome.
I want to fight big guy with huge sword again. Nice. Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, nope, nope,
no, he did it to me too. Oh, did I kill him? Whenever you- somebody drops their weapon,
they just get- it's like panic syndrome. They just get right in your face. All it takes
is one little punch. Uh, I guess I'll do you. Whoa, that was weird. Wow, he's like
spinning. It's like he's starting over here and he ends up like over here. It's weird.
Let's try it again. Nice. Oh, oh, that guy's- this guy's good. Damn it. Again. Oh, yay.
Sorry, I pressed the DPI button. No, I tried to switch it. I'm trying to switch it again.
What the fuck? Good, good, good, good, good. All right, I gotta fight this guy here. He's
very good. He's very good. Oh, that little like- that little pump is so hard to predict.
Damn it. Oh, not good. Hey, you wanna reset it or how you doing? You good? What the
hell was that? Wrong thing. Oh, all right, it was a good poke. Okay. Whoa! I just opened
the developer console. Sorry. Wait, get out of the developer console. He just like put his
head down. He was like, oh shit. Oh, ah, I try- I was trying to block it. Do the tutorial
for money and to get better. I mean, I don't know if I could get better from the tutorial.
I know pretty much how all the things to do in the game except for I don't really chamber
that well. This guy's very good. That guy is phenomenal. That guy is exceptional. Did I say
what the fuck just happened? Hold on, did I just swing and hit his- I'm so confused
what the hell just happened. I just like hit him. I have no idea. No, I already did
the tutorial. I mean, I know what's happening. It's not gonna help me. I did it the last
time I streamed this game. The servers weren't on, so that's not counting. I'm so- what the
hell is- should I start going like this? Like, should I start like dragging my hands over to
like help with the bait? Should I like put my sensitivity way up and like- is it- how-
should I do that? I'm getting kind of fatigued. Gamer fatigue is kind of settling in here.
It's alright. Just push- hold on, like- no, you can't. I have the DPI button as high as
I can go. That doesn't really work that well. Damn. Alright, a couple more and then I'm
probably gonna be done for today. Yeah, I just don't stand a chance when people are this good.
No way. Yeah, I did promise Bard. I'm gonna play Bard one-on-one.
Yeah, I'm tired. I'm getting- just everything's blending together. I'll play one- and plus my
DPI is so fucking high. Remind me to rip these buttons off, by the way, and fucking
burn them. Alright, let's go, engineer. Mom said it's my turn with the sword. Alright,
here you go. Ready? I gotta play the song first. Alright, who- who am I fighting here?
There's too many of you. Wait, what? I've never used this as a weapon before.
No. Alright, last one. And then I'm gonna call it for tonight. Let's see if I can win with
the loot. And there is no flourish with this thing. Get out of here. What the hell? Like,
I was going under the fucking bottom rope of the wrestling ring. I'm gonna die. Alright,
I'm done. I'm done. I'm outta here. I can't do it anymore. Yeah, like perfect timing.
That was good. You know, I wanna see people- the guy with the execution of his sword guy.
I wanna see two guys like that fight each other. I feel like that'd be really,
really cool to watch. That guy was like in another league. Let me get a-
This game's really, really fun, though. I know I'm kind of just being like a silent
try-hard sometimes during this stream, but it's fun. Alright, last one. Actual last one.
That was fun. That game's so fun. But yeah, that's gonna be it. So I will see you guys.
Thanks for watching Sam and Max and the kind of part two of the stream, which was
dicking around on Mordhau again. If you got into play some of those duels,
thanks for playing. Some of you guys are really fucking good. I mean, that's really
cool to see. Keep playing and keep kicking ass. So you will see me on my return
What was part one? We did Sam and Max season one finale. So you will see me again on Wednesday
because Dreams- Dreams is gonna be on Wednesday. I'm gonna bring you guys a couple of things,
hopefully, that I've been able to make. And if anybody else has anything made,
we can go through it as well. If they have, doesn't matter what it is. We'll just kind of
chill and play it. And then after that, I might move on to something else for PlayStation
4.2 because we're gonna have the PS4 plugged in. So if we do that for like an hour or two,
couple hours of showing stuff off, maybe we'll hop in something else and play flick, you know,
because I do like to, unless it's a big event or something, I like most streams to go
at least, you know, five and a half to six and a half hours. But thanks for watching.
I'll see you guys soon on Wednesday to be exact. There's a guide for Mordhau. Yeah,
I don't know. I might keep playing. I'm not sure how much more I'll stream it,
but I think I'm gonna keep playing because it is just scratching a FPS, goofy, interesting
itch. So we'll see. I know I have like a ceiling of how good I can probably get in the game like
this. So if I ever do, you know, get to a decent level, which I don't know, this is
somebody first person swinger. Yeah. But it is a damn fun game. I highly recommend it.
So with that, we'll move on to the bits. Let's see here. There it is. So let's go back to about
five and a half, six hours ago here. The skill ceiling in the game is huge. But honestly,
you're doing great. You probably could get much better. Maybe, I don't know. Possibly. It's
really cool to see the people that are just already finding all the interesting things to
do. And it's the fainting that's just so interesting to me. It's a blast. Even though
a lot of times I kind of get my ass kicked, it's still a lot of fun. But Smelly Boy,
thanks for the 250 earlier. Just want to say thank you so much for being there when I have
a shitty week. Some days are really rough and it helps so much to stand outside your house at
2 13 a.m. every morning until 2 16 a.m. That's terrifying. Thank you Smelly Boy for the
scariest bit message I have ever received. Because that is so specific. That's very
Thanks for the 250.
Yeah, I came in and changed it. I woke up this morning and I was like, I feel like
not that great. But I feel, I knew that by the afternoon I was going to feel better. So
and I did so I didn't want to obviously and I did say that we were going to do five days
this week. And we did. So I did want to make sure that I adhered to that. Got to be a
Vaude Boy. This is a pretty, this is a pretty good stream. This has been a pretty good
roller coaster weekend. Don't you think? You know, we went up the, we went up the chain
in the first part of Labo. We got to the peak. I got drunk and said a few swears.
Just a few. And then we went down the roller coaster with the Labo drunk wine stream. And
then, hey look, we pulled into the breaks for Sam and Max. A few. What was the name of the
bacteria? It was Roy G. Biv. Mr. Bliss, Hugh Bliss. But yeah, thank you Frodeo. I'll see you on
Wednesday. If you'll be there. D Flyers, thanks for the five dollars. D Flyers, if you
enjoy point and click adventure games, you should play the Submachine series of games.
They have really good atmosphere and lore as well as being free to play in standard
definition. Or you can buy the HD versions. Speaking of Sam and Max, what is this?
Oh, the Max head. That is a perfect, that's perfect. Submachine. I do love point and click
adventure games. Especially the odd ones. I remember we played Harvester. That was a journey.
Sam and Max is cool too. When was the last time I got a sunburn? I got a little bit of sun
a couple weeks ago when my mother was here. But thank you D Flyers. I'll look, I'll type
into Google right now. Submarine, Submachine. You know what this looks like? I played a
series of point and click adventure, almost escape room type games. Is this more like
an escape room? What's the series? It's called the Cube or something. There's like 10 parts
of it. What is it called? It's called like the Cube. Oh, Cube Escape. Yeah, Cube Escape.
Cube Escape is, I've played all of them. They're really, really good. They're really interesting.
But this, this kind of looks similar. It's like a, almost like an escape room,
which I love the room. That's my favorite adventure game, escape room type game.
But Cube Escape is, reminds me of what you just linked me. You didn't link anything. I
typed it into Google. But thank you for the recommendation. I will look into more of that
off stream. Mr. Comcast back again for five dollars. Hey, German John Comcast here.
Just letting you know that I got a restraining order the other day. So I can't go near any
washed up YouTubers. Don't worry though, I'm working on it just for you. Anyway,
in a completely unrelated subject, I saw you in Walmart the other day. I was going to say
hi. But then you started fighting the other children to get the last V bucks card that was
sitting on the shelf. So I didn't want to disturb you. I found it weird when you started
crying though. Give me that. Give me that. Idiot. Idiot. Dumb idiot head. That's what I would do
if that were real. Hey, The Jack. Thanks for the three dollars. You said you needed money to get
Jimmy off the parking meter. So here you go. Hey, thanks. It worked.
Snooze and Crofter. Thanks for the 250. You mentioned Mordhau and I played Mordhau.
I saw Vinny stream Mordhau. I think you guys would play it together.
Now that the game actually works, you can create your own character. I'd like to see that.
Also, I was reminded about how some people here were talking about how they met each other
because of your Discord. I didn't. And my girlfriend is almost getting jealous because
I mentioned you so much. She kind of hates you now. Sorry. Well, tell her it's just
tell her it's like Netflix. What are you watching there? It's like Netflix. You don't
have to just just it's like Netflix. That's all you have to say. But I mean, I'm always
down to play with people that, you know, obviously like Vinny and Metallix, Joel,
even like Star. It doesn't matter. It just, you know, depends on what they're doing,
what people's schedules are, what people want to do. Pipe Joel again. Yeah, that's so funny
how that just was, that was all talk from the both of us. It's hilarious. Oh, even,
yeah, you know, even Star. Hey, multi-trip. Thanks for the $15. Silence Redditor. Oh,
I forgot to do Bleed Purple Don't Hit Me. I'm not going to, what are you talking about?
Thanks for the, oh, okay, I see. Thanks for the $15. And thanks for the extra bonus bits
are there too. Thank you. Multi-trip. 15 bucks. Also, Hohohokuma. Hohohokuma. Thanks
for the $10. Have you ever played Silent Hill 2 or would you consider doing a stream on it?
First of all, thanks for the 10 bucks. And yes, I've played through Silent Hill 2,
long time ago. And I have a kind of a rule on this channel where if I've already played the
game, especially if it's a single player game, not on stream or in video format,
I probably don't, I won't do it again because I like the idea of playing things
and experiencing them for the first time with people here. And if I know what's going on
and I know what happens in the game and I know what the major encounters are, it makes it almost,
I'd rather not. I'd rather experience it for the first time. But I have played it,
it is a classic. Explain Clock Tower. Clock Tower? I never played that Clock Tower game
before that stream. I just started and finished it in one stream. I forgot about that. But thank
you Hohohokuma for the $10. Appreciate it. Super Bruce, thanks for $5. Hey Jerma,
I'm going to be in Vegas for just a day for a business trip and I need a recommendation
where to eat. What's your favorite spot? Price is irrelevant. Hash house a go go in the link.
That's my favorite restaurant in all of Las Vegas. Torati right now, 10 community subs.
Torati gave I believe 20 community subs earlier last night. Thank you so much Torati
for your huge amount of community subs. It was Torati, there was at least three or four people
that gave more than 10 or 20 last night. But yes, Super Bruce. The Bacchanel in Paris,
not Paris, in Caesars Palace is insane. It's a buffet. It's one of the best buffets I've
ever been to, the Bacchanel. Hash house a go go is probably my favorite restaurant.
There's no shortage of good food in Vegas, that's for sure. But um, have fun in Vegas.
Hopefully you oh and if you go to Hash house a go go, you got to get the blue cheese burger.
The burger is the best thing on that. It's the best burger I've ever had in my life.
It is the best hamburger you will ever eat. That is a Jerma985 guarantee. The blue cheese
stuffed burger. There it is. Unless you hate blue cheese, which in that case there's a couple other
ones on the menu. Have you ever been to Gordon Ramsay's restaurant in Vegas? Yes, I've been
to Gordon Ramsay's steak once. And it was immensely expensive, but it was one of the
best pieces of meat I've ever had. That's another great one. That one is in Paris.
Gordon Ramsay's steak in Paris is fantastic. Yes, that's the third one I would probably
recommend. You've mentioned that price is irrelevant. Well, I hope that's the case,
because if you go to Gordon Ramsay's steak, you are going to do that thing where you open
up the check and go, and then close it immediately and look around and be like,
so we are splitting up who's who's who got what did you get? Did you get a drink?
So be prepared for that. He's a cheap streamer. No, you ordered the two vodka tonics,
right? I mean, I got I got a tea. And it was like 250. Your three vodka tonics were like,
45 bucks. So we split in there and we split in the bill. You're just going to give me like
cash or how does that work? I mean, mine was like mine was like 12. Yours was like 80.
Are we just going to split in half? There's a I think there's a whole entire Larry David
segment of exactly what I'm describing. I think this is an episode of Curb Your Enthusiasm.
I think it is. But have fun on your trip Super Bruce. Hash House at Go-Go.
Freudian Weapon. Thanks for the 250, Freudian.
Since you don't call your mom for money, I'll send you some instead. Have a good night,
sweetie. Thanks, mom. Appreciate it, mom. Let's see some Jerma Hearts from mom.
Jerma lied about 5k subs. Thanks for the 250. Your color is going to be piss brown
tomorrow. Wait, what? What is it? I don't know. What is this Jerma lied about 5,000 subs?
What's this a reference to? 5,000 gifted subs. Well, did I lie? I don't know.
Did I lie? What? I don't know what I even lied about. I got a video here from Effectator.
I don't want to put it up. Sorry, I'm being like silent because I'm trying to see
what just happened to my stream labs. Oh, Dr. Steen comes in with five community subs.
Thank you, Dr. Steen. Five more subs flying in. This is from Effectator. 250 from Effectator.
Finishing up the Hotline Miami 2 video felt contractually obligated to make this.
PikaBanana5 community subs back to back to back here. Thank you, PikaBanana.
Let's see what this is.
Jesus. Well, that was fucking awesome. Thank you, Effectator.
That was the most intense. That was okay. Sekiro was really hard and was really relentless,
but I believe that Hotline Miami 2 may have been the hardest I've ever tried on stream
in a video game. That is the most frustrated and annoyed and hardest I've probably ever
tried on stream. Sekiro came close, but I was able to like talk myself down in Sekiro.
I was not able to give myself a chill out talk at any point during Hotline Miami 2.
It was just, I stepped on the gas and just went until the car turned off.
I would recommend that game though. Mario Tennis was blood fuel.
Nah, Simpsons Hit and Run was not, I was not getting angry at Simpsons Hit and Run.
I was just going crazy. How do I feel about Mordhau? I think it's great. I think it's a
really, really fun, funny, interesting, cool, gigantic battle simulator. It's awesome.
But thank you Effectator for that video. It was great. Thanks for the $252.
Thank you Multitrip for the $5. Congrats on top fragging in a pub.
I'm not sure if, I'm not sure if that's supposed to be mean.
Is that like a, is that a, is that, that's not, because some people might be like,
hey, congratulations on top fragging in a pub. You know, there's, but there's no space there.
There's no dash. Okay. No, this is actual, this is actual praise because it's just
congrats on top fragging in a pub. What I'm describing would be congrats on top fragging
dot dot dot dot in a pub. So this is a good, that's a compliment. Thank you.
Appreciate that. Thanks for the $5 too. Thank you Rain for the $3.
Jerma is getting Kingdom Come flashbacks. No, no. I was just having fun.
Captain Worgen, thanks for the $4. Hey Jerma, cool to see you getting into Mordhau.
I haven't been able to catch these streams in a while and there are too many new VODs
for me to catch up on. You need to control your streaming addiction. Well, I mean,
a lot of that has to do with, I've streamed five times this week. I've streamed what?
Five of the last six days, five of the last seven days. I don't usually do that.
Some of them have been long. I typically only stream four-ish, four times a week,
three or four times a week. So I have streamed a lot in the last five days, six days.
Maybe that's why. But I was gone for a long time, so I kind of want to make up for it.
I don't really plan that. It just kind of, you know, if I feel like going five days,
four, five, six days, whatever. Do I have a date for season two of Sam and Max? Yes,
Friday. We'll do Sam and Max season two, at least the first probably couple, two or three
episodes maybe on Friday night. Dreams will be on Wednesday. Thursday's a mystery stream.
Could be anything. I wouldn't miss it. Could be anything. And then Friday we'll do Sam and Max,
and then we'll take Sunday, Saturday off, and we'll be back on Sunday or something.
So we'll do two days off here, three days on, one day off, one day on. That'll complete
the week there. World of Warcraft? Hmm. You know what I considered for a second?
Just doing a community World of Warcraft classic. Just be dickheads and just run around together
and take over servers. But I would only really want to do that if it was, if we could separate
ourselves. Because I really don't, I don't want to fuck up somebody else's game. If we can
find some low population server and nobody's on, and just start at zero and try to get
to molten core with 40 people and only the strong survive. You know what I mean? Like if you,
we've got to come up with 40 people to do molten core. And if we don't beat molten core
every time we wipe, something happens. I don't know. We have to beat molten core with viewers
only. Somebody just gave 50 bucks. By the way, that is probably impossible. What I just
described is not even remotely completable. Maybe we can do it though. It might be fun.
Tora T on top of the massive community subs gave 50 bucks. Thank you so much. 50 dollars.
And just want to say you're my favorite streamer and savior of my rough college days.
I've been gifting subs from time to time and will continue to support you in this amazing
community. Keep up the amazing work, Jerma. We'll all be supporting your future works.
Thank you. I'm so fucking happy to hear that you think this is an amazing community. That
you think it's a great place to be. Sorry about your rough college time. I am honored to be your
favorite streamer. Thank you for the 50 dollars. Thank you for the hundreds of other dollars
you've given with community subs. Thank you. And from that, we're going to be moving to
sly161 for 250. Hey Jerma, you may not have seen me, but I got into the first few Mordhau
games. It was pretty fun. Would you ever consider making a server on a multiplayer
game like this where fans could hang out? Yeah, here's my one issue with making a server.
The same kind of thing happened to the TF2 server that I ran years and years and years ago.
I just wasn't around to manage it. And you get admins and mods and sometimes it's almost
like you build it, you make it, and you have it just open. And then if there's ever a
problem or something, it comes back to me and they're like, hey, something's going on
on the server. And I'm like, oh, fuck the server, right? Okay, let me get in contact with an admin.
Honestly, it would probably be one of those scenarios where if I were to do something
like that, I would just pay for the server and it would just be like I would hand that
off completely to just somebody in the community, a handful of people that really
wanted to do that. And I would just pay for it. And it would be a community run server
that I was just essentially just keeping turned on. Because it's just hard to be that guy that
gets the message like, hey, there's a hacker in your server. And he's like spinning fucking
earblast music. And it's like, oh, okay, let me go into console. It's hard to manage that.
And I'd rather just have somebody in the community take that over completely.
But it's an interesting idea. Maybe I'll talk to some of the mods about it and we'll see if
anybody would be interested in if anybody likes the game or something maybe. But I do miss that
aspect of just being able to jump into my server. And it's just there's my server. And I always
know I have a spot on it. And there'll be people in it. That was a pretty cool thing.
A lot of the videos on TF2. I mean, maybe some of you people that are new to the channel
recently in the last year or two. But a lot of those TF2 videos that required
like 30 people to do something weird were done on my server. And people lining up and
listening to the things that I was telling them to do. So it was a lot of fun to have
that opportunity to do it. But moving on from that, multi trip, thanks to the $9 multi trip.
And he says, Oppa Gagnum style. Those are the people who, you know, know you from the
servers. Thank you multi trip for the $9. I think Gagnum style is a dance in the game, right?
Thank you for the $9. pasta globs thanks to the 250 haha manual blinking and breathing what
was it what is that manual blinking and breathing blinking fuck you fuck you what's
going on oh it's to force you to think about your blinking and breathing he's too dumb to
get it he's immune did it just bounce off me good uh gutsy thanks for the three dollars and 12 cents
gutsy sorry for pan but this game is a lot of fun germ ejects i i did have like three or four
pan guys coming after me there was at least three trying they were like in the back of
the crowd just throwing pans over they were lining me up in their sights oh i know he's
backing up i just trying to hit me in the head with a pan i was being pan harassed
reminded me of the brupac tf2 flashbacks
remember that i missed that noise do you really do you actually miss that noise
you'll hear that sound again and go whoa and pull the headphones off
but thank you gutsy for the three dollars and 12 cents and thanks for playing i'm glad you had
fun tingy thanks at the three 250 these are my last bits for a while because i need money
for my best friend's visit anyway i made this and i want you to hear it i made i made this
uh what is this this is a debated thing is that is that the new thing now people are doing
these are all just versions of rick roll and the gnome
that's we like to part yes by the the vanca boys but thank you tingy uh hopefully you and your
friend have a good time peekaboo dana 250 from peekaboo dana thank you peekaboo dana
and for the community subs and speaking of those subs what the hell do you say we don't
just put them on the screen right now let's see them here they come all the subscribers
i still have the what color am i thing and green is still winning what is it now
i refresh it yeah green thank you to all of you again for continuing to sub and support this
channel you are the oil that keeps the fire burning thank you again and there's been a
couple more came in again we have the 50 dollars from toro t thank you uh germa lied
and what is this germa lied and didn't draw sticks thanks to the 250 i don't even know
what half of these are references to wait wait i was supposed to draw somebody's fursona
oh i didn't lie i forgot you need to replace these it's not germa lied about x it's germa
forgot about x half of these would not be they'd be forgets germa forgot about ace attorney
forgot does not mean you lied lying implies there was intent and malice behind it why is
intent forget is you don't remember you i did not intentionally forget you intended not to
remember yeah yeah yeah anyways they say hey germa ever played bro force could be a fun
game with touts or stir yeah i've seen it never played it i've never played it that's
a kind of a side scrolling contra like shooter right looks pretty cool not in the plans not in
the plans at the moment to do something with story yeah i gotta hit up star see what he's up to
it's been a while the last thing i remember is he rage quit vr right
no am i am i misremembering am i lying about this story am i forgetting this story which one is
it but thank you have gone for the 250 i have a secret task you mustn't tell anyone
seriously though germa i really enjoyed your kingdom come streams and i feel that your
medieval game streams results in some memorable memorable material a loot guy for germa rumble
maybe we have a lot of characters that that might happen sooner than you think
i might have to put that together soon we've got a lot it's been how was it like it's been
four four six five months i've only done one since being in vegas right it's been about
six and a half seven months since moving to vegas we've done one but maybe yeah that's i think we're
getting to that once every six months kind of thing here we've got plenty of new characters
yeah it's been i've been in vegas since october of last year time is blazing by it's
crazy now thursday stream is not the rumble i that's it takes like a week to put those
together it's about it's like that's probably like three to five days of making characters
and figuring out what i want to do that's not going to happen in two days wednesday's dreams
thursday's mystery stream friday is sam and mac season two that's the tentative schedule here
but uh thank you thank you to uh nagel for the 250 will you go to kfc with me right now
i'm not gonna be able to make it yeah okay even if you told me where it was
and i and i knew exactly where it was and i was i wouldn't be able to get there in time
just get an extra chicken wing for me and then eat it and pretend to your me eating it
and say like a catchphrase you know what i mean be like and then take another bite
just pretend you meet for like a minute yeah just pretend you mean didn't lie lie to somebody
like after you take a bite of that chicken wing just like go to you the nearest person
in your house and lie to them all right and we get dr stein five dollars coming in play
overcooked too with housemates on stream it's worth it or did thanks for entertaining us
all these years we love you and they say it is a sweat check i i'm doing just fine
and to me and italics did to play overcooked too already on stream remember yeah we me and
italics already did that yeah yeah that's come on you gotta keep up with the lore here
all right that's my time i'll see you guys soon on wednesday take care of yourselves
we're gonna do some dreams hopefully i have something interesting to show hopefully i have
something fun to do see you very soon have a great rest of your early part of your week
see in a couple days wednesday good night good luck take care everybody see you soon and goodbye
i can't do stream legends i'm sorry this hasn't been 24 hours i streamed yesterday into this
morning i cannot do stream legends all right goodbye