Oh shit, what happened? All right, hold on. Let's skip suffocation. Oh thank god it's,
Elevitz is actually in here. Oh thank god. My goodness, imagine if it wasn't. Okay,
all right, let's go. Elevitz, you're gonna like this one. I don't know, what am I titled the
stream now? Like fucking magical creatures? Finding magical creatures? You like clean a house in this
game. I'm gonna love this. I was gonna save this for like tomorrow because this is what I was
thinking about doing tomorrow, but we're doing it today because these fucking video games I'm lied to.
Scam recovery. Let's go. I have to buy rabbits again. Elevitz is such a good game. Oh I know.
Sometimes you gotta pull out the big ones. Searching for magical creatures. There you go.
Your face cam. This game is actually like the ultimate PogChamp. You guys are gonna love this
game. All right, story mode, multiplayer, extras, we're gonna do story. In this tutorial you can
learn how to play the game and view advanced tips. Would you like to start the tutorial? Yes!
Oh fuck, hold on. This is searching for magical creatures with Cabela's Deer Hunt still on the
game title. How about, I don't know, clean your room. Clean your room. Done. Here we go. With the
remote, pointing at the sensor bar, slowly move it left and right to look, stop being so tangled
or I'll bite it. Okay, you can also look up and down, look up and down, left and right.
Let's give it a try. Let's try. It's really, it's really like high quality fluid game too.
It's really, really fluid and high quality. Okay, next step. Try slowly moving the cursor up,
down, left, and right. You move the camera. This is a really high quality fluid fucking experience.
Keep it in the blue frame. Slowly move the cursor up and down and keep it in there.
This is an incredible game. Yeah, I know. It was either this or I was gonna put in Beautiful Joe.
I had to, I gotta pull out all the stops here. Let's learn how to move. Move forward by slowly
tilting the nunchucks control stick forward. Tilt the control stick backwards and move backwards.
Tilt it left right. You move. Yeah, yeah, yeah. The thing to remember here is to point the
Wii remote the direction you wish to move. Let's give it a try. All right, let's see if we go.
Ready? Pick it up. This is moving up, down, you strafe, you tilt. All right, now let's do it with
the, with the controller. This is VR movement. You guys don't understand. This game is one of
this. This is probably the best game, probably like one of the top 10 games on the Wii and you're
about to see it live and in person on German 985. I'm selling this game up so high because
the last hour and 40 minutes has been a disaster. So I'm trying to just keep you here. All right,
let's learn how to crouch or C to stretch Z to crouch. That's a stretch and that's how you
scrunch. Stretch, scrunch, stretch, scrunch. Good. Live from Las Vegas and I got a face cam on.
Are you serious? What a day to stick around on the stream. Please, god, don't fucking leave.
Grabbing objects or catching elements is referred to as capturing. Let's learn how to capture an
object. You can grab objects by holding the capture beam over them during the game.
Press the A button or the B button of the Wii remote to shoot out the capture beam.
The beam will shoot while the button is down. If an object is too heavy, the cursor will turn
red while you point at it and you will be able to grab but not capture it.
Let's go. People saying F. F. Why F? While holding an object, move the Wii remote in the desired
gray. You can move it left, right, up, down. Why are people doing F? Oh, it's the block. Okay.
While holding an object, move the Wii remote back into pull it, move it forward to move it.
Yeah, you go like this. Twist the Wii remote left or right while holding an object to tilt
that object. You can open the doors. Try moving the red object into the red frame
and the blue object into the blue frame. Let's give it a try. Go. Got it. This is not a toddler
game. This is a cleaning game, which means I'm going to play them all. All right, we're almost
done. I'm going to have to back up a little bit I think here, which means I have to put pants on.
We're going to have to take a break and I'm going to have to put like fucking pants and like underwear
on and stuff. Like, uh, that's just, I'm just giving you real. Next, let's learn how to capture
an elephant. Look at these little things. An elephant is a living entity with a mysterious
energy. If you capture one, that energy will cause various things to happen. After an elephant
pointed it with the cursor and pushed the A button, the elephant enters your capture gun and tank
as watts. Watts of the game's unit of energy collect watts to fill the light bulb gauge,
which will turn blacked out lights back on. Give it a try. Here we go. After the yellow goods.
He's going to get banned one day. I've got him. All right, that's it. I'm going to take a break
here in a second and I'm going to put on clothes. I have clothes on, but it'd be more appropriate
clothes because I'm going to have to fucking move back for this. How to use capturing to do various
things. You can use the capture gun to grab and open or close drawers. Yep. Grab a drawer and pull.
Let's give it a try. Let's try it. There's an elegant mirror. You search for these things
through the whole house and you get them all and you can use them to turn on stuff. That's how you
turn a faucet or doorknob. Use the capture gun to grab a faucet and twist it. Let's go. Sometimes
they come out of the water. This game sucks. No, it does not. That's so, so unbelievably wrong.
It's such a good game. Yes, it is. Elephants are hiding. Grab items and shake them. You just go
like this. Okay. Okay. Got it. You're trying to hype this game. We'll see. We'll see how you feel
about 15 minutes. Thought break sound. What about it? This would make a good VR game.
It would. Elephants love small nooks and crannies and to hide between under things.
Find and capture them to turn the lights back on. Let's go. I'm going to have to stand up for this.
You're going to see the full boomer race. This is, I think this might turn into a stand up stream.
All right. What else we got? Here we are. Get them all. Yeah, this is going to be a stand up stream,
I think. The pants on. Don't worry. I'm going to. All right. Now the lights turn back on.
Would you like to do the next tutorial? Yeah. Streamer stands for the first time in six years.
Stages include doors that won't open until you have enough watts. The doors show how many watts
are required to open them. See? Let's go. A door somewhere just opened. Oh, there it is.
Let's go. Excuse me. This is a Pikmin ripoff. Oh, that's. No, that's not even remotely. That's
not. Just wait. Just wait 10 minutes. This is a stand up comedy stream. This game sucks. Oh, man.
Imagine if you just didn't know. Imagine if you didn't know. You know what I mean? I can't
imagine not knowing. Okay. Electrical appliances display the amount of watts required to use them.
So once you gather enough watts, they will turn on. Once an appliance is usable, point at the
switch with the butt sensor and press the A button after the cursor changes. Turn on the appliance.
150 for that. EV is energized. Turn it on. Look at that. What do you mean? What sensor?
Okay. Increased capturing power. I'm just getting my memory refreshed. You're stealing cable.
Oh, it's kind of pog, I guess. When you use an electrical appliance, yellow and pink
elements come out. These elements are called power elements. Capture power elements to charge
up your captures gun power gauge. Build this gauge to level up the gun's capture power.
When the level increases, you can carry heavier objects. Capture power elements and level up your
capture power. Interesting. TV energized. Let's go. Telephone energized. I can now carry 2.2
kilograms of material. Look at that. The game still sucks. You're making a mess. All right.
Review what you've learned so far and capture even more elements. The movement's so fun, too.
A door somewhere has opened. Good. We're not done collecting elements.
Telephone has been energized. Toy train energized. Let's go.
Gotta get them all. Open the fucking door.
Okay. I gotta stand up. Here we go. Ready? Oh, level three. Open everything. This would be a wicked
fun VR game. I know it would. All right. We got it. This is Viscera cleanup details are the worst.
What's with you guys today and only giving games like 12 seconds before you want to change?
What's going on with you guys today? This is like one of the best Wii games to release.
We can smell when a game sucks. Oh, no, you cannot. No, you cannot. I refuse to have you
guys say that this game sucks. It's like saying that Mario Sunshine sucks. I mean, it doesn't.
Okay. Items may have special effects such as temporarily improving gun capture performance.
Check this out. Grab an item and smash it to activate it. Here we go. Ready?
Homing laser locks on and grabs multiple elements. There are lots of items you can get.
Now this is my dopamine levels just exploded. Yeah. Elevates are emotional living beings that
cry, dance, and even run away in terror. Depending on the state of an elephant when you capture it,
the amount of watts you acquire will also vary. When an elephant is running away,
its watts will decrease and the bubble that appears when you capture it will turn red.
When an elephant is stressed or unconscious, they provide a normal number of watts. This
capture bubble will be white. Elevates that are sleeping or singing provide a higher
number of watts. This capture bubble will be as blue. Watch the elevates' actions carefully
and try capturing in the different states. All right. That one was having fun. Someone's sleeping.
That one's confused. That one's crying. See how it was different. Okay. Now let's like scare them.
Let's like throw a box over here. EM pulse ball knocks out all elevates in a range. Oh, it just
has to be around. Okay. They're all sleeping when this is around. And it makes them just
trying to collect. This game gets really fucking hard too. All right. What about here? Fleeing is
red. Yeah. You want to try to get them in a good state. Get to the first boss. Elevate cookie
attracts elevates for a time. So you go like this and they'll go after it. Go get that cookie. Wake
up. Eat this cookie. Oh, you're all idiots. Whatever. I only have this in all the items,
right? Do I have to just get them all? All right. We're good. Nice work. Electrical appliances.
Didn't we already do this? Gotta catch them all. Just skip the tutorial. Point to various places
with the cursor and look for activation methods. Some objects are activated in combination with
other objects by grabbing parts and moving them. All right. You can turn on like the coffee makers
and shit. Okay. I think we're almost done. You're getting hard blinks chat. The legendary pink
elevates are the rarest of all. Capturing them unlocks a new game mode. You gotta, you gotta
catch them all. Look at them. There are always three pink elevates on each non-boss stage and
they will appear in different ways. The first hides normally, but the second is in a potter's shoe,
which you will eat eventually. The third appears next. Once the special conditions are met,
find them all. There. You happy?
All right. Watch the fucking opening cut scene where I go put on pants.
Over to their research lab and left me at home. I don't care. My favorite show will be on TV soon.
Huh? That's right. Electricity and cars only work because of elevates, you know.
Wouldn't even be able to watch TV without them. Pick them up with my fair hands. I know. I'll use
Dad's capture gun.
Hey, look, we're in my room. I can choose the music.
You went to go buy raving rapids. What music do I want? No shit. No, no, no. Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait. I'm not ready. Pause it. Pause it. Pause it. Pause it. Pause it. Pause it. Pause it.
I can't. You can't pause the game. All right. Screenshot. Here. Now I can move back a little.
Let me move the mic. Let me move the camera. Full backpack cam. Incoming. He's wearing overalls.
No, I've got my fucking like bionic chest plate. I've got my, I've got my carapace on. Level one
armor. Yeah, this is, this is like fighting game person armor. You know what I mean? This is like
the, oh yeah. Am I protected? Just don't hit me here, here, here, here, here, here, here, or
anywhere, anywhere else in my whole body. PUBG armor. All right. I'm ready. I'm ready to fucking
play this game. No, the camera's not even in the right spot. Fucking big ass arm. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. Why does that look like that? Oh my God. I'm gonna play the game now.
Unless it's the angle. I'm moving, I'm changing the angle. All right, we're good.
Are you ready for this fucking game? I'm ready. Here we go. 350 watts. Turn TV on.
Don't wake him up. Yeah, I know what it does. Fucking Igor. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Anybody in there? Stretch my head up. Okay, good. I can't, I don't have enough. Wait, hold on.
TV turned on. We got ready. I have enough, right? No, not, I don't have enough. Fuck.
How do I leave the house? Can I leave the room? Not yet. Toy train's been energized. Turn it on.
All right, I got level two power. Stop, stop, stop, stop. Open up, open, open.
How do I turn this fucking thing off? All right, the lights are on. Finally. All right. Under the
bed. TV's on. Turn it on, turn it on. Come on, come on, turn it on. Get in there. Smash the TV.
No, no, no, not yet, not yet. Fuck out of the way. Rip it off the fucking wall. Why,
why am I doing this in this kid's room? I still don't have any more.
Holy shit, what's in there? Blue RC car has been energized. Where is it?
Oh, I am the kid. Where's the blue RC car? I just like, it's like a fucking robbery. All right.
Where's the RC car? There it is. What? Where's the car? How much do I need? 1200 watts. Fuck.
I need more than that. Come on. This is literally the opposite of cleaning.
Oh, there's the car, there's the car. Oh, there it is. Okay, it's over here.
Level three. Finally. All right, we can pick up the bed. Pick up the desk.
Um, got them all. You can clear the mission without, you can clear the mission without
completing. Continue? I mean, I did it, right? Wait, I don't understand. You can clear the mission
without completing? Just keep going? Just say yes? No? Total capture 97. I gotta fucking see.
Gotta see. You have to clean everything. No, I don't. You can now play this mode and score attack.
Cool. You can keep powering up, right? Okay. Next level. Mission two.
Play normal missions. You proceed through the game. Here we go. We're in the hallway.
The game is unnerving. Why? You like collect little creatures.
Elebits in the closet. Capture a thousand watts of elebits in 10 minutes. Go. I want to get in there.
Here they come. Ready? Slow, slow, slow, slow. I don't want to, like, wake them all up.
Here we go. Don't want to make everybody freak out. Hair dryer has been energized. All right,
where's the hair dryer? Where's the hair dryer? Oh shit, there's a cookie. Okay, hold on.
Electric drill. I don't want to use these cookies yet. Wait, wait, wait, hold on. Get this out here.
All right, turn it on over here. I need a thousand, right? Yeah, the music's fucking good.
Flashlights energized. Keep that open. Can't pick these up. Flashlight. Shit. Flashlight. Come on.
Flashlight. Floor lamp. All right, floor lamp. Here we go. Turn it on. Let's go. Wait, they're
stressed. They're stressed out. I don't want to capture them when they're stressed.
Wait, they're stressed. They're stressed out. I don't want to capture them when they're stressed.
475? What else was it? More subs? Five subs from you posted cringe, bro. Ten subs from you
posted cringe, bro. I'm sorry about that. Didn't mean to. Thanks for the ten community subs.
Uh, thanks a lot. And then SNK had ten community subs while I was gone.
Thanks a lot, guys. All right, I can pick shit up now. What do I want to pick up?
Let's get this stuff out of here. The door somewhere could be open. Oh, shit. They're
on the- they're down here on the stairs. Why is that one dead? Which door opened? This one?
Open. I took too long, so he died. Oh, shit. Okay. There we go. Here it is. All right. How is
there nobody in there? Why do you have a fucking urinal in your house? Why is there a- why is
there a- actually that's pretty fucking- that's incredibly smart. I would love to have a urinal
in my house. Got ya. You can't hide from me. Urinal. This is like Superman's piss. Blue piss.
Nothing else in here, right? Dr. Manhattan. All right. There we go.
I'm blocking myself in the bathroom. No, get the fuck out of my way. Go out the bathroom.
No, I'm staying. I'm staying. I'm staying. Look at all these things energized over here now.
I can open this. All right. We're gonna throw the cookie. I'm gonna- okay, I'm gonna turn on a bunch
of shit. And I'm gonna- here we go. You ready? I want that cookie. I'm gonna get the cookie ready.
I'm gonna make sure I get them happy. I already checked this out. Let's get this open.
I know. I know people like- I know they like the cookies. I get it. Everybody loves fucking
cookies. 30 seconds for the cookie. Turn it all on. Turn everything on. Quick. Go get the cookies.
That was it? 30 seconds to turn this on? Legendary. I got the legendary.
Honey, what's going on upstairs? Sorry, sweetheart. I was gonna find these little weird fucking
creatures and pick them up. Honey, there's nothing up here. Yes, there is. You don't see them?
Honey, honey, you're just pissing all over the place. Sorry, I'm not very tall, but I'm using my
elitist radar. Why is it still locked? Get this out. Oh, okay. Shaking shit. All right, move it out.
Get it out of the way. One minute. I've destroyed everything. What else is there to fucking break?
Oh yeah, that screen title is Clean Your Room. This is not how you clean a room. That's- yes.
I am- yeah. Oh, wait, this is the bathroom, right? I think I got everything I can.
Chibi Robo prequel. All right, any more? One here. I think I got everything. Not much else to move.
Oh, yes, there is. What's in the corner here? Umbrella. Come on. Wait, I can- I could go down
the stairs? I thought I couldn't go downstairs. I thought it was just the closets. Hey, there's an A.
You can edit shit? How would you edit? Are you drinking Windex? Sure. Windex is blue.
People can- that's a fucking feature, whatever. I don't care. People are gonna make fun of me.
At all the grocery stores, all the fucking water is gone. And sometimes, in some of them, what's
left is like the expensive stuff. So this is all that was available to buy at the grocery store
because all the fucking other water is gone. Just boil the water. All right, mom and dad's room.
1,500 watts of elevates for mom and dad's room. Music number three, let's go.
Get this one clean. Don't break that cookie. Don't break that cookie. Not yet.
Get them all in the middle of the room. I'm gonna press these all at the same time.
Don't play. Don't do it yet. Come here, you little shit. Epson picture mate.
Door somewhere could be open. All right, hold on. All right, I'm ready to start turning these on.
All right, here we go. Fuck. Sorry. Ready? Turn this on. Break it. Break it. Here we go.
Easy. Whoa, whoa, whoa. Don't break. Don't throw the whole thing over. Fun. Another one. Level two.
Level two. Hurry up. Just lost that shit under the bed. Turn the lamp on. Missing on the lamp.
All right, stay still. Mini TV has been energized. All right, where is it?
All right, I just locked myself in here. Actually did. I don't think I can leave.
It's all right. Shirts. Move them. Why can't I move the shirts?
It can't be opened yet. Why? What? That lamp has been energized. All right, let's go.
This should put me over the... Wait, can I pull the bed?
I'm like major focusing right now. Anybody in there? Anybody in here? No.
Antique radio. I got to get the fuck out of the bedroom.
Let me out of the bedroom, please. I can't move the books. One, two, three,
four, five, one, four, two, four. I don't know what this is. Shredder activated. All right,
there's a lot of shit in here that's activated. Bro, these urns. Flashlight has been activated.
No. What do you mean grandpa? Oh, turn it on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Oh, it hurts. Turn the fucking thing on for God. Turn it on. What the fuck?
Ugh. Cookie, cookie, cookie, smash cookie. Yeah, I got it. I'm gonna stick around. I'm
gonna destroy all these books. This is the satisfying part of the whole mission.
Watch out, the police are coming. Wait, out here. This is all the shit I can do out here, right?
All these drums open in the rung.
Am I strong enough to move this shit? How can I not be this strong?
There are, there's like a, like, there's like a piss joke here with like the Sith piss versus
fucking Luke Skywalker piss. I don't know if I can make it right now though. I just have to pee
into each other. Whatever. It's there somewhere. Oh, that's cringe, bro. Oh, I might need to tighten
this. He's not even making jokes. No, I'm not. I might have to actually tighten this. What did
I mess up here? What's the vest for? Uh, there's a whole lot of it. You would like a new tutorial.
What's this, what is this for? This is an improved boomer brace? Kind of. All right, I'll give you the
TLDR. I have a really bad pain in my ribs and my spine. I might have rheumatoid arthritis and
costochondritis and I have to wear this sometimes because my whole body hurts. There you go, there's
the TLDR. All right. Breakable objects have a mark on the lower right. Be careful when handling
these objects. If you drop or throw these objects, they will break. Gently put them back down. Else,
keep in mind that fleeing elements can crash into objects and knock them down. So be careful
in such situations. Look around before turning appliances on. Okay. Looks like life is actually
painful. Kind of. So I can't like just smash stuff anymore. I can't break anything. How am I, how am
I going to be able to do this? Don't break seven objects. I've been just whipping shit around.
Oh my God. Okay. Don't break anything. If I haven't broken anything, we're good.
I didn't break. What did I break? What did I break? What did I break? What did I break? What did I break?
I didn't break anything. What did I break? I didn't break shit. Oh, this vase is everywhere.
All right. Put them down. All right. Slowly. Are these bottles of water going to break? No,
they made it a plastic, right? All right. I almost have enough. I'm going to back up a little bit.
Flashlight energized. All right. The lights are coming on. Thank God.
Don't break anything. All right. We're okay. 15 minutes to do this. I can slow down. Why am I
going this fast? What turned on the lamp? The lamp. Okay. This is, it's going to shatter.
This doesn't count as me breaking something, right? Good. Level two. Not yet. Huh? Really?
Go downstairs. See, I see you can't go downstairs. The music's tight. Yeah, the music is really good.
The door opened. Oh, I did it. Hold on. Oh, I did. You're right. All right. Don't break anything.
Just slowly do it. Oh, don't break it. Don't break it. Slow, slow, slow, slow, slow, slow.
I have 12 minutes. These are pens. A colorful PC. All right. Now, careful, careful. I can lift
shit up now. All right. Okay. It didn't break. Gamer posture. Oh, I'm going to have to tighten
myself off. It's starting to, it's starting to hurt. I think it's the way that I'm holding the
Wiimote maybe and like going like this and just tensing up a little. It's kind of annoying, but
we'll see. I'm all right. I'll tighten it a little bit at the next mission.
Jesus Christ. I love elephants. I know. It's great. Okay. Be careful. Here we go.
Somebody in here. I lost control of the stream on that one. Plates. What do I need? 2,500?
20 watts do I need? What else is new? I've lost control of the stream.
Eh, it's a typical Saturday then. Here we go. Turn it on. Still not enough. What's, this is for the
Wii. What system is it for? It's for the Wii. Oh shit, I can go over there. Wait, can I move this?
All right. Da-da-da-da-da-da-da-da. Slow. TV is now energized. Got a pink one? This is a lot. Oh shit.
One sec. He's killing them. Where am I going? I'm just, I'm just tightening the back. What's
he wearing? Here we go. There we are. One more, one more side. Don't hurt yourself playing the game.
No, I'm all right. I'm just, this morning too, it was actually, I woke up worse this morning,
but I'll be fine. Invite Bugleberry to play with you. No, not giving up. Here we go, that's better.
Quick, invite Frog Detector. Where's this TV?
None of this shit is able to be, nothing in here is breakable. It's fine. All right, new door, new
door. I broke something. What did I break? Let Bugleberry play instead. No, if I, if I,
you guys know me, man. If it gets to be too much for me, I'll just, I'll just see you tomorrow.
You know that. It's happened once before. Can't break a picture, right? Bugleberry, no, Bugleberry's
not gonna play this. He's not even good at this game. That was like angry how hard I threw that.
I picked that up off of my head and fucking just whipped it into the wall. All right,
there's another door I can go on. Let's turn this on. All right, don't break that vase, easy.
Can I move these yet? Nothing breakable in there, it's fine. Oh shit, they're on the walls. Come on,
do it. Where are the elements? Oh, no, get me back out there. Give me, I just hurt it. Where are they?
Okay. All right, watch out. Toilet, energized. Heater, energized, good. I'm not, I'm not trying,
I'm trying to pull it off. Where's the heater? All right, let's do the cookie right in the middle.
Heater, energized. Heater, energized. It's right here, right? There it is.
30 seconds, fuck. I'm not, I can't move the boxes yet.
You're gonna stop, you're breaking our marriage?
3500 to turn this on, shit. Okay, we're fine now. It's the worst thing to do right now,
is like sneeze. He's getting sicker. I'm fine. I sneezed once. I was here because he sneezed.
I still haven't beat the fucking level. No, I'm saying it's bad because like that like detracts
my chest muscles and chest and shit. Where is he? Wait, somebody out here. I'm breaking in.
Why is it so hard for me to open a door? I'm done for. I'm gonna lose. Sometimes you gotta
crack a few fucking eggs to make your breakfast in the morning, whatever it is. What do you know
what I'm saying? It's gonna be only two of you in here. How did I move the bed? No, move the bed.
How did I move the bed so much? Air purifier. Where? There it is. 30 seconds, shit. I'm gonna
lose. I need 3000, right? Turn on. Come on. Come on. Hurry up, please. Where are they? Get out of there.
Where the fuck are, what? I think I lose. Oh, I got it. Thank God. I got it. Hey, I'm from the future.
Jerma doesn't do it. Well, you must be from the wrong future. I'll get what I can in 15 seconds.
I didn't get to go in the other room. At least I got to go in the bathroom. Wrong timeline.
Jerma, I beat Mario. Are you proud of me? Of course I am. It's a really hard game. Keep touching
your face. Well, I'm like, I know I really shouldn't be doing that, but I've been washing my hands.
All right, we get to do the kitchen. I'm gonna do the kitchen mission. Sure, I'll do a tutorial.
Quick, you're losing more piss jokes. So, you make noises. You don't want to make too much noise.
The volume gauge will fill as you make noise. When a certain line is passed, the count will decrease.
Zero is a mission failure. So, don't make noise. Don't let them run around. Okay, I get it. Hey,
we got a cut scene.
You better take my gun.
Gotta go. Be careful with that gun. It was like, the dad was just doing a tuber voice.
Okay, be sure when you have that Eliebrits thing, you don't fire it too quickly. I gotta go.
See you in the next episode. That's TTS voice. That is TTS voice. All right, the silent kitchen
after 4,000 watts. Oh, I can hold on. I'm gonna save that. It's just bread, man. Why would it take
that loud? Why is bread this loud? Oh, I dropped a fucking pot on the ground.
Noise canceler. Eliebrits won't hear noises. Okay, I have an idea. I mean laser. Yeah, here we go.
Oh shit, they can hear noises again. I just, I was passing out and you know when you're passing the
fuck out and then you lie down for a second and the world starts to come back? That's just what
that felt like. Oh, I have to insert what? Insert coffee. Insert toast. Insert toast in the toaster.
Is it not toast? Where's the coffee maker? Oh, this is gonna be insanely difficult to do this.
Got it. All right, I can't get the fucking toast in there. It's gonna take too long.
What do I need to put in the oven? Insert what? There's already a turkey in there.
TTS.
Put a potato in there? Everybody is the... what? There we go. Come on, get level two.
I still can't get this fucking toast in here. Dude, there's no way you're gonna get this toast in
there. Cancel all sounds. Okay, throw the pizza fucking everywhere. Break everything. All right,
give me the hoeing missile. I'm gonna beat it right here. What's the goal of this game? Is to
capture elli bits and transfer them into energy and then use the energy to open doors in your house
and turn your lights back on. Five, four, three, two, one. That felt fucking good.
Level three. Don't make noise. All right, what needs to go in here? What do you put in the microwave?
Uh, what goes in the microwave? What kind of food is on the floor? Onion. Uh, apple.
Bread. Metal. No, no, no, stop. Aluminum foil. It's like a front-loading dishwasher. Mustard.
You motherfucker. Open and stay open. Stay open. Oh my fucking god. Stay open. Stay open.
Every microwave does this shit and it's so irritating. This is actually what happens
when you have a real microwave. But this is, this really happens.
Stop doing that. Why do they, why does it do that shit? This is not a game problem. This is like,
that's a real world problem. Oh fuck, I can't make noise. It's upside down. What the fuck do I put
in here? Bread? What about the turkey? Should I put the turkey in there? How long would it take
to microwave a full turkey? Okay, it takes, it takes like four and a half hours to bake a
turkey in the oven. If you microwave a turkey from raw, what, how long would it take? I can't
move otherwise I'm going to fail the mission. Wait, Mr. Bean did that? Wait, where'd you go?
Where'd you go? Where'd you go? Wait, Mr. Bean really did that? He microwaved a whole turkey?
That's, that's very, very, that's very funny. That's very funny. What should I put in there?
I don't want to make any noise. Link the funny turkey video. Don't make any noise. Please just
pick it up. I'm going for a C. Wait, it's real. Oh, it's real. All right, after this, after this
level, um, I'm going to watch the Mr. Bean funny turkey video and take a second in the fridge.
Oh, shit, is it this? Yeah, we're going to do a react to the Mr. Bean video. Yeah, it's just,
it's bothering me. It's actually bothering me. That's why I was wearing it today. 12 minutes.
Preemptive Pog. Movie, movie night! Standing up help? No. Unfortunately. Take a break? Yeah,
that, don't, we will. I'm not, I won't push it. This game's fun though, but it's something about
this, like, way I'm holding it. I don't know. I had issues this morning. So let's watch the Mr.
Bean fucking turkey video. That sounds like fun to me right now. All right, hold on. Let me get it.
Where is it? This looks like it's going to be very funny. This video is 12 minutes.
Thanksgiving Bean. Mr. Bean. Wait, what? This is a 12 minute video. All right, hold on. I'm coming
over here. Plug this in and let's check it out. Bean Crew. Get this on the screen for us to watch.
Get it in a browser. Okay, here we go. Mr. Bean. Thanksgiving at Mr. Bean's house. Oh,
are we watching each other on each other's TV? This is nice. There is something we have to talk
about. This looks new. I don't quite know how to put this. What I am concerned about is, whoever
that is, I am getting rid of them. That's the guy from Ghostbusters 2. There he is. David, sorry
we're late. I love this guy. Terrible. You couldn't believe it. It's just the way she, it's the green.
No, it's the yellow. It's just, it's the yellow. Well, where is Allison? Well, I've got some bad
news and some good news. The bad news is that Allison has had to go visit her mom who, well,
is not well. That's too bad. Wait, this is from a movie? The good news is that Dr. Bean and I
will be cooking. But he's, that's Dr. Bean? Of course it is. All the greatest chefs in the world
are men. So what's on the menu, maestro? What the hell did you give them? What are we going to do?
Yes, I think they may be expecting something slightly more formal.
Hot dog. Just on its own? No, no, don't be ridiculous. It's for Thanksgiving. Allison would
kill me. Microwave the raw turkey. There must be something else. One of these before. Why would
it take like five hours, right? Not necessarily. No fucking, what? Why? How long did they do this
for? 20 minutes. I don't know. 20 fucking minutes. No, I'm not hungry. You're the chef,
just put on some vegetables. Wait, is the Mr. Bean video game? Holy shit, that's disgusting.
Maestro, my taste buds are positively tingling with anticipation. Play the Mr. Bean game.
No, no, thanks. I would actually eat those. I would eat those. They look good. I actually
kind of like raw onions. I'm a fucking weirdo. So Bean? Big day Tuesday. Your big day. My big day.
I have a question for you. Let's see what it looks like. He's very attentive to detail.
Everything must be just so. What? Is he all right? Is Mr. Bean okay? Bean, I think we need to be
honest with each other. I cannot deny that over the last days some suspicions have begun to
gather in my mind, and I would just like to ask you some direct questions.
Number one, are you a doctor? Okay, I can't do that. Why are you watching Mr. Bean? This is a
fake gamer stream. I gotta take a break, man. I'm fucking, I'm in pain. Watch the whole movie. I
can't watch this whole movie on stream. I'll get removed from Twitch. Fake react channel.
Just watch all the clips in order. No, you can't do that. I can't just watch every scene from Mr.
Bean the movie in separate YouTube videos back to back. I mean, that's like, that's skirting the
rules a little, and I would probably get some, I'd probably get reprimanded for something like that.
Give me, like, give me another Mr. Bean clip. I want to watch like a funny Mr. Bean clip. Any
other funny, like, classic Mr. Bean clips? Okay, here we go. Let's take a look. You got one here?
What's this one? Not, that's, that's a, I know, I know, that's a, that's a gnome.
Here comes a Bean stream. This is the Crispus Turkey funny clip. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait. Wait a second. Wait a minute. Wait, wait, wait. There's more than one Mr. Bean funny,
like, Thanksgiving turkey clip? Hold on, there's more than one?
It's just classic Mr. Bean comedy.
Christmas sucks.
Merry Christmas.
Wait, is he feeding the mouse Christmas cheese? Oh, holy shit, Mr. Bean.
That looks like a fucking folded up person. That's a, that's a human. This is a human.
Holy shit, that's a huge fucking turkey. That's a person. Mr. Bean is fucked.
Any more Mr. Bean turkey videos that we haven't seen?
Why is he taking it out? He lost his watch. Oh, he lost his watch in the turkey.
I knew it was going to happen. He's fucking a head crap. It's one of those scientists from Half-Life.
Holy shit, that's what it would look like if it was in real life. Holy fuck, that's terrifying.
Thank you.
All right, any more? I want more Mr. Bean food related videos.
I want, is any other Mr. Bean turkey related videos? Is there another Mr. Bean turkey video?
Sandwich? There are hundreds of Mr. Bean turkey related mishap videos.
This one, one last one. This one, this one. Just found it, found it, found it.
That's not it. This is a turkey one. Please watch this one. Should have watched this during Thanksgiving.
You guys are all, Lincoln says random shit. These aren't, these aren't even Mr. Bean.
Seafood bean. Mr. Bean, no, no, no, no. This is the one. This is the best one. This one is a French restaurant.
I love this one. No, it's got to be food related. Seafood is the best one. All right.
All right, every time some people, half of these. Okay, somebody just linked the scene where
Ace Ventura comes out of the rhino's ass. That has nothing to do with Mr. Bean. That's like,
honest to God, what the fuck are you talking about? Is this it? No, that's not it. That's,
that's, that's like a turkey, turkey video. Okay, here we go. Somebody got it. Somebody got it.
Somebody got it. Thank you so much. Thank you. Here we go. Oh, you don't know about Sprite, Ginger.
What?
He lost his voice. It's the same video.
He lost his voice.
It's the same fucking thing. It's the same one. I love it.
There's just no laugh track on this one. Now listen, David, I want a straight answer.
What do you think about the mayor? Oh, you know, maybe I should just go in and help.
No, please sit down. The doctor is in complete control of the situation.
You see, the problem with the mayor is that, well, how can I put this kindly? He's a total idiot.
This city needs this leadership, vision, vision.
No, I don't think you're going to get that from a compromised career politician.
Who wants to be in charge of this? Which is why George should be running for office.
This is a germist dream. Excuse me. This is a germist dream.
It goes all right there. Yes, thanks.
Wait, is this the same movie? 20 minutes.
Put some vegetables on it. Come and say hello. Wait, is this the same movie? Is this the same one?
You found another turkey one? Is this, is this actually another turkey one? That's not it.
The world isn't black and white. There's no set.
Oh, please go on his head. Please go on his head. Go on his head and have him hit walls and shit.
Please pinch your soul. Half a dozen oysters. Oh, they forgot to clean this one.
What the fuck is he doing? It's a germist dream. A can of peas.
It's a germist dream. We just say things that we're doing and then we do the same thing over and
over again. Oh, can of peas. A couple of oysters. A dozen oysters. Can of peas. It's classic humor.
It worked. Oh my god, he's going to get stuck. That's it? That can't be it. What do you mean
that's it? There's another classic turkey one.
Hello? Phoebe? Joey? What's going on? Get off the screen.
Dad, how did you get on? Hunter scared Chandler. Then help me get it off. Plus,
it smells really bad in here. Of course it smells really bad. You have your head up a dead animal.
Okay, this is going to be...
It's going to be the exact same thing. Shit, that was pretty sick.
That was a microwave. What the fuck? You got to do the same thing.
Oh. French fries and turkey. But it didn't go on his head. This isn't funny. I don't find this
humorous. It's not on his head raw. I swear to god, I fucking promise you, there will be a time,
not today, not tomorrow, not next week. I will do a fucking... Look at how funny it is with turkeys
on his head. I'm going to stuff a turkey joke. I promise you. What the fuck is going on?
Aurora Borealis. Smithers, whatever your fucking name is.
It's supposed to be as funny as the actual turkey joke.
He's breathing in the smoke. That wasn't even funny. Yeah, that kind of sucked, to be honest with
you. Okay, that's enough turkey videos for now. That's enough. No more turkey. No, no, no more
turkeys. No, I'm not playing the other one. No, this one, I don't want to play this one. No more.
No, he doesn't even do anything funny with this. He's just holding it in his hands.
Watch this, please. Watch this. This is toilet humor, Mr. Bean. No, no, we're not watching Mr.
Bean piss it into a urinal. The last one, please. Hold on. Oh, okay, fine. Do people still think
that's fun? How many of you guys, do people still think that that's funny?
Oh, the turkey joke. Oh, it's just like a Jerma stream. He does like kind of the same shit every
time. Let's link the streamer, the fucking gnome video every stream. You and I are not so different.
Hey, click this link. It's the, it's the, I think this is funny still. We're not so different,
you and I. Why do I need the lyrics? No, I'm not watching any more turkey videos.
That was a good break. Now, what do I want to do now? No, no more chicken videos. Clean your room.
Let me, let me stand up for a second. Let's actually take a just an actual BRB. I want to
stand up and like move around just a little bit. I think I'm going to take the brace off
and just move around a little. Give me one second. I will be right back. I'm going to take this off.
I've moved up and down a little. I don't want to say this, but I'm going to.
I'm going to have to call it here. I'm sorry. I got to like, I don't know what I'm going to do,
go lie down or something. This is hopefully not going to start happening more frequently
because this happened like a few weeks ago where it just like, I couldn't do anything and it was
just uncomfortable. So I'm just going to call it. Not going to push it. I don't want to. Sorry,
we only have like a three and a half hour for probably four hours stream, but we'll be,
I'll be back tomorrow. Tomorrow is going to be an interesting day because I'm going to play
the game that is on the GameCube. That is a microphone game. I don't know if you want to
miss this one. That's a microphone based video game. It is called Oh Dama. You control an army
with your voice while you throw a boulder into buildings. It's going to be a little weird,
but sorry. Uh, that the last like probably full hour or so I just was have not been that
comfortable and I really just want to kind of just, unfortunately I have to stop.
It started once I started playing like Elevates. I think this is the way that I was holding and
just how I felt earlier today. So I will see you tomorrow. Um, I'll make sure like,
I don't know what to do tomorrow, but I'll try to rest up and make it so I can sit here longer
because I was fine. Yes, this is, but I think this is, you know, this is like,
that's so annoying about this. It's like yesterday. I was, I was live for like eight
fucking hours yesterday and I was like, fine. I didn't need the brace and they woke up today
and it was just like, fuck. It like hurts. Put the brace on. It helped a little bit,
but you know what I mean? It's like, come on, man. Like this annoying. We'll see you tomorrow.
We'll do it again tomorrow. I'm going to play Oh Dama. I'll see you then. It'd be the weather.
No, I don't think so. I don't think so, but we'll see you tomorrow. Does he know that he needs a
mic? Oh, I have a mic. Actually, you know, let me see. Make sure it's in here. Oh, it's in here.
All right. I have to, hold on. Let's actually want to show this. So here is the GameCube Nintendo
microphone in the package still. Let's take it out. And apparently this does work in here.
Did I just ruin this by putting my dirty fingers all over? What else can you use this with? I don't
know. Apparently it works in the Wii. I know. I'm going to make sure it works before I turn the
stream on. Check the disc. Check the disc. Check the disc. Why does this have to be a thing? Why do
I have to like make sure this shit's in here? Here it is. Oh Dama. Oh yeah, it's in there.
It looks pretty. This is like a really sleek case too. Live unboxing. Here you go. There it is.
It's a nice case. Take a look in here. It's like a, like a really nice case. It's got the manual too.
Pretty nice case. It looks, this looks big for GameCube game. Doesn't it look kind of big? This is
like, does it look bigger? I don't know. Maybe. But that's the plan tomorrow. Uh, everything's in here,
so that's good. Uh, if you missed the stream today, uh, my body hurt. I got scammed and uh,
we watched Mr. Bean stuff his head in a turkey four times. Pretty good Saturday. Pretty good
Saturday stream. I think so. So I'll see you guys tomorrow. Have a great rest of your day and we'll
see you tomorrow. Thanks for the catch up. Sorry for Rick rolling you. The classic fucking food
mishap video. I love it so much. Take care guys. See you tomorrow. We'll do the bits. I'll hang out
for a little bit. Let's go over here. So earlier we had, uh, we had Spigot the bear for five dollars.
Thank you for the 500 bits. Hey Jerma, as a verified 2006 gamer and god skater, do you think you would
ever stream Bully? You do the Wii version for some boomer exercise. Um, I don't know. Aren't they
making another one? Aren't they like remaking it or something? Wouldn't they? I heard they would like
redoing it or there was going to be a second one or I'm kind of just waiting on that. Not confirmed.
Oh, they aren't. Oh, it got cancelled. Oh, oh, cancelled. Oh, okay. There's been so many rumors
about Bully 2. Yeah, I've played Bully. I played it a long time ago, but maybe let's get through all
this stuff first. I still have a bunch of stuff that I want to play and try on like the Wii and
the GameCube. Some classic, some not so classic. Obviously, I still have Eternal Darkness that I
want to play, which that's a classic. That's going to be really fun. Uh, both the beautiful Joes,
No More Heroes 2. Those still have to come up and be done. When can we expect more Cabelas?
Never. But thanks for the five dollars. Uh, Bulbaswag, thanks for the 500 bits. With the
coronavirus, Clown of the Town would have a new risk factor. Clown of the Town is just impossible
to do without 500 million dollars. I followed just for Cabelas. Well, I'm sorry. You probably
should unfollow if you followed for Cabelas, because that is the first and only time you will
ever see a Cabelas video game streamed on this stream. It's not going to happen probably ever
again unless, unless I get scammed again and somebody puts the wrong disc into a game that
I purchased. So if I buy like Raving Rabbids again and there's a Cabelas 2006 disc in there,
sure, got scammed. Well, I keep getting scammed with these used games. And that was live. That
was a live, I got fucking scammed. I can't believe it. I'm so annoyed by that. Send him a cabinet.
What a sucker. Hello again, mister. Thanks for the 250. Hey Jeremy, I just came back from Portugal
where I got to see my girlfriend for the first time in a while. When I got back I had to go into
quarantine where I'll be for 14 days. Getting back home to your stream made the situation easier to
bear. Thank you so much. Hopefully, um, you're good to go. Kind of a scary time right now.
Just uncertainty and what exactly this is and what it does. And it is kind of at that point
right now. We're, we're trying to ease the amount of infections as much as we can, I guess. So just
be careful. Take care of yourselves. Stay, obviously stay clean. Wash your hands. Don't go
anywhere. You don't have to go. That has a lot of people there. I mean, this is just basic stuff
unless for a little while, right? Yeah, it's, it's not, it's not a joke.
There's no joke. Be careful. Why did you cancel E3? I was looking for what I didn't have. What?
I'm a guy that sits in his underwear and watches it and like drinks coffee and like,
I have nothing to do with you. What are you talking about? Hey, uh, Sybeck, thanks for the
$15 Sybeck. Here, Jeremy, take some money to never do that fucking woody bit again. Well,
I can't promise that won't happen. Considering how many turkey mishaps you've seen on this stream,
I'm sure you'll see it again soon. Thanks for the $15 though. Appreciate it. Hey, smelly boy,
thanks for the $2.50. I'm not kidding when I say big game hunter 2005 was the first game I ever
played when I was like seven on my PlayStation 2 and it made me so happy when you started playing
it. It made me so happy when you got scammed. Can you imagine sitting here watching a stream
and it's like, Hey, I'm going to play raving rapids. It's like, Oh, okay. I guess that's what
he's going to play. And I opened the case and it's holy shit. It's the first game you've ever
played, like tricked you. We're on Egypt and I'm playing Cabela's and it's like, Whoa, that's the
first thing I've ever done. That's just weird. Isn't it? That's like a moment for one person.
That's the one guy. Thanks for the $2.50 though. Uh, option. I, well, thanks for the $3.47. If
Drew crew ever puts you under too much pressure, Jeremy, I can delete German walk and leave them
in shambles. Holy shit. You hold all the power. Oh man. That's a lot of power that you hold.
The nimble pickle. Thanks for the $15. It was my birthday yesterday and I just want to say,
thank you for six plus years of entertainment. Also, when do you plan on playing Viva Pinata
again? It was a great stream and we want more. Um, after this weekend, I would say,
so probably I might, we've done a lot of weird game cube stuff. I'll probably go back to the
X-Box, but also next week is the animal crossing and I'm playing animal crossing absolutely,
at least around somewhere around when it launches. So what I'll probably end up doing is we'll
probably do some X-Box stuff. Uh, like starting on like Wednesday and then we'll do like Wednesday,
Thursday, Friday, Saturday or something. And we'll do a couple of X-Box games and then I'm
going to play animal crossing for a couple of days, at least when it comes out. We'll see.
That's the plan. Thank you for the 15 bucks. Wait. Oh, I thought you said, I thought you said animal
crossing is not shipping until April. I was like, no way. What really smelly boy. Thanks for the
two 50. Thank you. So thank you for playing a big game hunter. Even if it wasn't for long,
it was hilarious watching you play. Just listening to the sounds and watching you chase the werewolves
Wolverines, uh, gave me such a nostalgia trip and have me laughing so hard. I've been sick
the past few days and very afraid because of it. Your streams are always a light in the darkness.
Love you, man. Keep up the good work and let's hope all this stuff passes soon. I agree. I remember
when I first started watching German with a super meat boy, let's play. I was pretty good at that
game. I did all the dark world levels and all the bandage girls level. Thanks smelly boy. Uh,
take care of yourself. Hopefully it's nothing serious, right? Hopefully it's not anything
to be concerned about. LM man. Thanks for the 500 bits. Jerma, you are king. Thank you. Uh, 10 Mario
or 10 Mari 10. Thanks for the 300 bits. I had a dream that you were streaming some game
when your cam accidentally turned on and you were standing fully nude in the shower.
Jack kept saying TOS and penis, but you didn't notice. I feel like this is an omen.
Um, I've had that dream twice, so trust me, I'm aware of it. Uh, you posted cringe bro. Thanks
to the 500 bits. You're losing a quick more piss jokes. I read it earlier, but I thought it was
kind of funny. Uh, you posted cringe bro gave another $25 and they say, Jerma, you're worried
about the Corona virus with you being a boomer cringe and needs to say cringe. Which one of us
is posting the cringe? Sure. It's me. Oof. Oof. No, it's me. It's me. Uh, thanks for the 25
fucking dollars in bits though, dude. Seriously. It's Luke can. Thanks for the $5. Jerma, are you
in a quarantine? No, I am not. Let's hope it doesn't get that far. I'm not, uh, future fashion
grow clown. Thanks for the $3 and 20 cents. Jerma, what's your opinion on mustard on hard boiled
eggs? Well, a lot of deviled eggs have mustard inside of the mixture, so I think that that's
all right. That's fine. That's good. It could be good. I don't know about directly on a hard boiled
egg, but part of the mixture of a deviled egg. Sure. I'd say so. Espada Escalada. Thanks to the
250. Mr. Bean is the bugleberry of the television comedy world. No way. Apollyon Abadon. Thanks to
the 500 bits. Can we talk for a second about how Bugleberry is the best character?
I hope you think that. I really do. I really do. And if you have been part of any of the pre-stream
chats over the last few days, you will know why. I really hope you do like him a lot. I hope so.
Okay. Boiky, thanks for the 500 bits. Hope your pain goes away soon, Jerma. Also, fuck the bean
team. What's wrong with you? How could you say something like that? He's a classic comedian.
I do too. It's getting to the point where this is actually starting to,
I went back to the doctor and I had more tests done and I have like my fucking rheumatoid factor
is high and trying some new stuff and this costochondritis might be, it might not just be
costochondritis. I might have like rheumatoid fucking arthritis or something. It's still,
we're just still on the fucking train and I want to get off, you know, I want to like get off the
damn train. So it's just almost, it's like, it's been like almost two fucking years of this shit.
I just want to know what the hell is wrong with me and just start treating the fucking thing.
I'm just being totally honest with you. You know, I'm not going to pretend or anything. Like this
is just me talking to you real. Like this is just me, but it just, whatever. Well, it just,
I'm going to keep going until it's figured out and then just treat it and try to get back to normal.
Oh, stop pretending. Stop, stop pretending. Unfortunately, funny streamer memes do not
work in the world of potential medical issues. Imagine like going to the doctor and he's just
like, oh, so what are your symptoms? Yeah. I still have like this kind of like spinal, like chest,
like core pain. Stop pretending. Okay. Oh, there he is. Jerva talks about the doctor and the doctor
has a funny voice. Put the turkey on your head. Here's the Jerva goes to the doctor and the doctor
goes, oh, what's wrong with you? Oh, I'm stupid. There's a laugh track with the turkey. Oh, it just
bumped into the wall. Anyways, uh, yeah, I just want to get it taken care of. And the problem is
like the medical, the medical like world just moves so slowly. It's like, okay, so here we're
going to do this testing. All right. See you in like two or three weeks. Like, can we just,
can I just come in fucking tomorrow? Like, can I just come in for the next eight straight days
and you just do everything you've ever wanted to do to me? Like everything that you could even
imagine. Just do it all. Like, oh, we'll see. Oh, we'll catch back up with you. Uh, in April.
But no, no, no. Can I, can I, can you just like do all this shit now? Like, well, we're going to
give you, we're going to do an MRI. Let's set the MRI up. Oh, this is a thing you're trying to get
figured out. Oh, we want to figure this out. Uh, so when are you available in, in, in four and a
half weeks? Uh, I guess on Tuesday, the fucking 12th. I just want to bang, bang. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's get it done. So like, well, it's a lot of hurry up and wait. And here's the thing. I also,
I kind of get it too though, because there's a lot of like processing and a lot of trying to,
I've had a bunch of shit done already and we're just bouncing around with these different ideas
of what could be fucking wrong with me. I did like a rheumatoid test and it's high. And it's like,
okay, well, what the fuck does that mean? Fringe healthcare, fail country. All right. Jay bum bum
7723. I remember you, but I don't want to have the, and this is the problem that I don't want to
have bleed into the live streams. I don't want to have this be a problem for me to bring into the
streams. I don't want it to affect the streams. I don't want to have it be a situation where I'm
just, this is something I'm complaining about a lot or every stream. I'm like, this is fucking
stupid. Fuck this. So I don't want it to be like that. And although this is an annoying problem,
it's not, it's not like debilitating to me. It's just there and it's annoying and I'll figure it
out. But I don't want it to create this like aura of just negativity around me on the stream
because I want to have fun. And like, and look 98 times out of a hundred, this is not a problem on
screen, but sometimes it comes up and it's just like, okay, what the, what do I do now?
Like what, what should I do now? Unfortunately. And I know that it's like, no, don't really like
a lot of you guys are saying like, don't worry about it. That's fine. Like we get it and
everything. And I really appreciate that. But remember I want to be here. Like I want to do
this. I want to be live. I want to hang. I want to like laugh and have a fucking good time. You
know what I mean? Like I don't want to be like, it's been three hours and like my back hurts. Bye.
So it's, you know, it's frustrating. I'll be honest with you. It is, but I don't want it to
be a thing that's because it's not really that in the grand scheme of things, it's not that big of
a deal because it eventually long-term, I'll probably have a solution for it. It's just kind
of short-term is annoying. There you go. Laying it out there, right? What a megalofucking maniac.
So we get, we're going to keep walking down the road until, uh, until I actually get the exact
thing that's really wrong. And that's pretty much it. I, I'm probably not going to address it too
much more on stream because I also don't want it to turn into a thing where it's like, oh, German
something's wrong with you. Something's wrong with German. Something's wrong with him. Oh man,
it's all right German. There's something wrong with you. You're okay. Well, don't worry. I don't
want it to turn into like a, there's something wrong with German. And, oh no, you know what I mean?
I don't want it to be like that. Something's always been wrong with you. Yeah, but I'm talking
about in a medical sense. There's always something wrong with you, dude. But anyways, that's pretty
much it. I just want to talk to you guys and be realistic and real with you, you know? Sometimes.
It's all fun and games until somebody wears a fucking boomer brace. You know what I'm saying?
Hey Mitchell, thanks for the 500 bits. Odama more like awesome streamer providing years of
priceless content. Clean Your Room title is just so fucking wrong. Clean Your Room playing Elevates
and Mr. Bean is the thumbnail eating raw turkey. It's all fun and games until somebody puts on a
turkey head video. Mr. Bean headcrab edit. Oh, come on. Don't, I gotta watch this.
The problem with the mayor is that, well, how can I put this kindly? He's a total idiot.
He needs his leadership, vision, vision, petition.
That's quick. That's, that you gotta, you have to remember, keep in mind,
you gotta render this shit. That, it takes a little bit to render.
You have to make this, render it, and upload it. Damn, that's fucking pretty good. All right,
let's keep going with the, with the bits. We have a little bit more. Where'd it go? We had, that was
Mitchell. Thank you for the $5 Mitchell and the video. Hey Lil Din Osor, thanks for the 500 bits.
Hey Jerma, today's my fourth anniversary with my boyfriend and we celebrate it by watching you.
We love and appreciate you. Hope all your health stuff gets better soon. Well, I appreciate that.
Thank you and happy anniversary. Four years. That's, that's really good. Thanks for the five,
that five ducks, five bucks. And I can hear myself talking because this thing is plugged in and it's
speech jamming me. So let me just turn that off. Here we go. That's better. Yeah, I can hear myself
talking to my own ears. Do a speech jammer stream. That wouldn't last very long. I'd throw up.
I could try it. I could try it for fun for like maybe half an hour or something at the end of
a stream. But yeah, happy anniversary. Thanks for the $5. Snoozing compter, thanks for the 250. Hey
Jerma, long time no bits. Please don't tell me Elevitz is going to get the God Hand treatment.
We played the beginning as part of a shit storm crack stream and forget about it forever. No,
it was just, it was kind of the catalyst to my pain. It was the way it was. I had to hold the
Wii mode and move it around and just the, I don't know, something about it. By the way, the director
that made Beautiful Joe also made God Hand. I knew you were going to talk about God Hand at
some point. Put it on the list. Jeremy, Jeremy, put it on the list, Albertson. Jeremy, push every
new stream week a day and put it on the list, Albertson985. Play Boom Blocks. I have it. It is
there. It's behind me. I will play God Hand. I will play God Hand. I will. It's not today.
Not today. Not tomorrow. Also, my girlfriend recently woke me up in the middle of the night
and told me not only is she a germaphobe, but also a germaphobe, she's still jealous.
Take care of your old man body. Wait, let me read this again.
Told me not only is she a germaphobe, but also a germaphobe, but she's still jealous.
And then a ton of laughing. She's jealous of you. She's scared of you. She's scared of you.
Did I finish Super Mario Sunshine? I did. I did. I got to beat the game and I got,
what, 71, 72 stars or something? Sticks Renegade, thanks for the 250. I hope this virus doesn't get
to me. If you remember, I take immunosuppressants for Crohn's. There's one case in my city and
20 cases in Rhode Island. Yeah, that's... Just be careful. Just be careful. Stay safe. Yeah.
Just try to be healthy. Try to be aware. That's all you can do. Dark Soul, thanks for the 250.
Here's Drink Bits. Johnny Blue tastes like cigars and assholes. Shout out to my boy,
Nier. Call of Fury War Zone good. Me drunk. Thank you, cutie.
I'm sorry that, I'm sorry that you have an opinion that is not correct. I'm sorry that you feel
wrongly about something. This tastes like cigars and asshole. Well, do you even... Okay,
do you like whiskey? Do you like whiskey? Because if you don't like whiskey, then don't take my
recommendations for whiskey, right? That's like, dude, I hate hot sauce. I hate it. I think it's
disgusting. Yeah, you should try Tabasco sauce. Oh, should I? Let me try that. I hate hot sauce.
Let me try it. Oh, this tastes like fucking assholes. He likes whiskey. He likes good
whiskey. Johnny Walker Blue is good. It's very, very smooth. It's light. It's whatever. Maybe
you should try poo wine. Oh, fuck. Don't do that. Don't do that. Don't do this to me.
That was the fucking craziest thing, man. This is a weird stream. What a fucked up stream.
The poo wine thing was so ridiculous and it fucked me up for life. I didn't think I was
ever going to do a stream that was going to fuck me up for life. And here I am, completely corrected.
And it was ridiculous. It was exactly the way that it would look. It was... That person that
said that originally, holy shit, you have messed me up permanently. Hey, Machine Nation, thanks for
the three dollars. Hey, Jerm, I just wanted to point out something. When you played Asura's Wrath,
you mentioned it was highly recommended, and I found it was mentioned nine times in the
recommendation channel. Today, you played Monster Lab, which you also mentioned you got from the
recommendations, and that was only mentioned once. Meanwhile, the game Fury has been recommended 12
times since December 2018. It's not been played at all. Well, that's not accurate. Just want to
put that out there. Well, you've got to get your facts right. I streamed Fury already, a whole stream.
Your facts are incorrect. Make sure you come in here with real facts, because I streamed the
video game Fury already when it came out. I got like 50, 60 percent of the way through the game.
So, I mean, if you're going to come after the king, what's that line? If you're going to come
after the king, make sure you bring sweets and give them to me. Yeah, that's it. That's the line.
By the way, just want to make this really clear. Just because somebody writes something in the
recommended channel, even if it's a hundred times, doesn't mean I will ever play it.
The reason why I played Monster Lab is because it was recommended, and I looked at it and I said,
hey, this looks like it could be interesting. Everyone's a big fan of Monster Rancher.
It's like a back and forth. You have a monster that you grow and level up, and it turns out when it
was actually played, it wasn't really that, like, I wasn't into it, and it had tracing in it. So,
I wasn't going to play it. Play purple plays. But the recommended channel is not about how
many people recommend something. It's about, do I think it's interesting enough for me to want to
stream it? Like, do I want to play it? I mean, that's, it's a recommendation. It's not a demand,
right? But to answer your question, I've already streamed Fury. I did. Come on. Come on. Come on.
I did. When? When the game, like, came out. I'm going to look this up. We're going to stop at
Germa Fury. Is it archived? I think it might be. Maybe it's one of those streams that never got
archived. No, it's not. There's not even a single clip of me playing this game, huh?
I love Fury. I had no idea he streamed it. If you Google Germa Fury, this is the second result,
and it is the Reddit thread asking if I've ever streamed Fury. There's no evidence that it was
ever streamed. That's so funny. No, I did. I did. I swear to God. People were here. I didn't imagine
this. I've actually, I swear. You can't prove it. You did. Yes, I did. It's a lost episode.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait, wait, what's this? What's this? Wait, wait, wait, wait. We got a clip.
Somebody has a clip. Get that back in there. This is me playing Fury, but it's me changing games.
Get in there. What the fuck is this? Come on. There we go. There we go. I was trying to stay
with you. I had no idea. I was your only hope. I told you. You had brought this upon yourself,
stranger. It's real. I told you it was real. Tactical visor activated.
What the fuck am I doing? Oh shit. Tactical visor activated.
Oh, it's Mercy and Soldier 76 combined. Whoa, new hero announced.
All right. No, no, no, no, no, no. Excuse me. Excuse me. Excuse me. Don't you dare minus two
that. That was an incredibly relevant fucking joke because Overwatch was in beta and it was
the biggest fucking thing in the world. Okay. Sorry. Four years ago, I made a jokey reference
to one of the biggest video game releases in 10 years. It was four years ago. I didn't just say
that last weekend. We used to stream Overwatch and then I just didn't think it was fun anymore.
Dude, cringe ages like fine wine. Get out of here. Get out of here. Get out of here.
Get out of here. All right. I'll see you guys. Looking into the credits.
Sorry for the four hour stream. Thankfully, it wasn't like a two hour stream because it
really could have been. Could have been. Thanks for watching regardless. We'll see you tomorrow.
I'm going to do the microphone video game and see if we can get three times. Third time's a charm.
It's either third time's a charm or strike three you're out because each microphone video game
we've played has been some of my favorite times on stream. Like I've had a lot of fun with the
microphone games. This could be strike three you're out or it could be third time's a charm.
I know. But I'll see you tomorrow. Here come the credits. We'll do the last couple of bits.
As always, thanks for your subs. This channel sees a lot of money like I say frequently.
Thank you everybody. Really appreciate it. We will finish the bits. Here's only a couple left.
Hey, thanks off futz for the 500 bits. The music is off. Off futz says, hi,
Jerma. I hope you're having a good day. Please read the following before you read it out loud.
Oh, okay. Temperature does influence joint pain. It's the barometric pressure. I have
rheumatoid arthritis and any major change in temperature really messes me up. Cold,
rainy, humid weather makes my joints, tendons, muscles tight while hot weather ups pain.
That's just me and I'm obviously not your doctor but hope this information helps you find some
answers. Because Vegas is really, really dry and I mean obviously it's been cold recently because
it's been the winter time. But when hot weather ups pain, I don't know. Let me, this is very,
very good information and I will take it absolutely. But let me get that like a
confirmation that that's what's really going on. Because that's another thing too with obviously
me talking about some of this stuff on stream. I don't want to come here with inaccurate
information and stuff that might not be true. Like, oh guys, I have rheumatoid arthritis. Like,
I don't. Like, I don't, that's not confirmed. I have this. I don't want to have you guys,
I don't want to talk about something that I have when I might not even have it. You know,
I want to be certain and not just like throw out nonsense that it could be not even true.
As much as I talk about it, I don't really want to give you diagnostic stuff. Because I've done
that in the past before and I don't, I just don't really want to do that anymore. I'd like to just
keep it just private until I have a certain answer. But on the other side of that coin,
it's like hard to not, because if I'm having like a problem and I have to like stop a stream
or something, it's like, well, why are you stopping the stream? It's like, I have this problem and then
I have to talk about it. And you know what I'm saying? It's like a, just try to balance it out
a little bit. That's pretty much it. Let's say health problems. Yeah. And like when I wear,
that's like, when I wear like the brace, it's like, I know we, I know a lot of people are
fucking around and I do, I think it's funny. I do think it's funny. So you're not like hurting
my feelings when it's like, he's got overalls on. Like, why does he have a backpack on? Like I,
that's humorous. It's funny to me. It is. But there are people that actually come in and they're like,
why is he wearing that? Like, is he, was it for? It's like, well, it's his backpack, right? That's
that's it. So, you know, it's, I'm trying to find like a healthy balance as to what it even is.
But goo berry juice. Thanks for the 250. Hey, cool. I love monster lab. So glad you're playing the
oops. Nevermind. Hey, how was rabbits? I love that game itself. Oh, whoops. Scammed. Hey,
well Cabela 2005 was the first game I ever played. Oh, he hates it. Whoa. Okay. I love
alibis. That might be fun. Oh, he just watching Mr. Bean now.
Oh, it's so true. It hurts.
It's perfect. What a perfect way to end this stream. That's perfect. Oh, I love that guy.
Whoops. Scammed. God damn. It's all good though. Whatever. It's all good. Hey, Bimmy. Thanks Bimmy
for the three dollars, Bimmy. And finally we had three dollars from Ozals, which will take us to
the end of the stream. Thank you Ozals for the three bucks. It's a relevant video. There's a
relevant video here. Turn that poop into wine. Turn that poop into wine. Turn that poop into wine.
Turn that poop into wine. On the second coming of Jesus Christ, prove it.
Take a poop in front of us. What's that even supposed to mean? Oh, that's Eric Andre's
is fucking hilarious. You should watch more Eric Andre. Well, I can't watch more Eric Andre
because I've seen all Eric Andre. I've seen it all. All of his show, all of his extended
New Year's Eve celebrations. I've seen them all. He's very, very, very funny. Are you going to see
the movie? I hope so. Oh, I hope so. I better. They're about Raid, Raid, Raid Joel, Raid Joel,
Raid, Raid Joel. What's Joel doing right now? What's he up to? Grand Theft Auto 3. What the
heck? Grand Theft Auto 3. Somebody did an uptime in this stream and I thought it said 20 hours.
Like, holy shit, it's been going for a long fucking time. So I want everybody to remember that.
You know, what's better than this? Besides everything, a burger with a crispy wheel of
cheese on it. Is it weird that I, I, this is an ad, but I wasn't looking and I thought that was
Joel doing like a voice for a second. I was like, wait, this is a, no, it's a Carl's Jr. ad.
All right. I'll see, I'll see you guys tomorrow. Have a good night. Again, sorry for the ending
of the stream, but you know, you gotta do what you gotta do. See you guys tomorrow. We'll do
it again tomorrow. Good night. Take care. Have a good one.