Hey, what's going on, everybody? Jerma here with a live Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
Tonight I'm going to be playing as the squirrel, and let's just play.
There we go. Whoa! Don't scare me like that, man. Don't scare me like that.
Let me try and get around everybody. That's all I want to do.
You think I'm still in here? No, I ran away. Probably a sentry right here. I would be shocked if there wasn't.
I would be shocked. No, no, no, no, no! Don't get stuck in the door!
Sentry? I don't know. I don't think so. I'm just gonna do it just to be careful.
No, there isn't. Okay. Well, don't be spotted. Maybe I can get like three scout backstabs here.
Well, that was kind of. Sort of. Sort of. I'm gonna go with sort of. I'm gonna go with maybe.
What is this guy doing? Uh-oh, we got a fight. We got a melee fight. Who's gonna win the melee fight? Soldier or Spy?
Soldier or Spy? Oh! I turned right into that.
I was too busy paying attention to the fucking pay-per-view Soldier versus Spy match.
It only cost me like 60 bucks pay-per-view to see that. Was it worth it? Bet your ass it was.
Move on. You, I thought you were a Spy, but you weren't.
Drink it!
That's a great screen. Huh? Are we gonna win? I think.
Ladies and gentlemen, we have won the game. Not yet. Almost. Yes. Yes. Yes.
Here comes your scramble!
Hmm, you know, I guess. Are you guys all real? You're all real. Then fine.
It's all right. We're just gonna play on the red team and your red scout on the red team.
This sniper is trying to shoot me. Don't shoot me.
Time to be a creep and creep up behind this sniper.
All right, I'll walk in his face. That works too. And this scout, you think you can beat a red scout on a red team?
You get away. Everybody, I made it out alive.
Fucking Mini-Sentry almost kills me.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Where is he? God, I don't know how I'm staying alive like this.
Hmm, I can't really go head on here.
I can't really do much. I have to wait till they move or I could just go right at them.
There we go. Now I can overheal. Now I'm not as scared as I just was.
There it is. What? They can't. Oh, okay. All right. Okay.
Son of a bitch. I thought I had that guy, but I didn't.
Move away. Um, all righty.
Just stop them here for 10 minutes. Ain't gonna be that long.
I keep on just barely not getting the last Mini-Sentry again.
Please don't kill me. One.
Okay. All right. We'll just respawn. We'll do it all over again.
And we'll just spawn right now. I'll come out with my delicious soda.
I'm not going to drink it. I want to save it because I'm going to a movie later and I want to have a soda for the movie.
But you can't bring like sodas into the movie. Otherwise they get like mad at you.
All right. Well, it doesn't matter. I'm not having a soda for the fucking movie.
Hey, hi entire team. Don't like turn around.
That guy's chasing me. Yeah. Oh, yep. Oh, yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. That's a spy.
I just see a heart. He's using the, uh, the lack of anger. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep
by you guessed it how many century oh no no no okay all right all right we're making the switch
we're gonna close this round out as uh soldier we're doing direct hit soldier to close this out we're
gonna go direct and we're just gonna try to smoke some people do we have any medics i don't know
i'm too busy i'm too busy trying to figure out if we have any medics oh that's a lot of stuff that's
a lot of things coming over the one crit that i get does not hit anybody but i'm okay though
he went down here shotgun don't want to shoot myself you can't have that much health i knew
yeah i was gonna say if you had more than 40 or 50 hp or something i would have been
very very not happy about that i'm just let me just do me do me a favor jerma just walk over
pipes and did you hurt yourself that's great we're gonna go down here uh you want to do
shotgun fight what you want to do somebody got him oh no a hat jesus i was looking at the hat
i should have been paying attention to something else besides the hat that fell on the ground
but it was a mystery i needed to know what the mystery was and i still don't know because it was
what was that like a green gibbous it's like a lime green gibbous that is a mystery hey hey
where are those mini centuries i'll take you out in one shot where are you where are those mini
centuries thank you very much you are a what was that okay you're real i heard a stab noise
are you real am i what am i doing this for no reason i feel like i'm yeah i'm just doing that
for no reason at all but this is a crits creek and i weirdly don't want to waste this uh so
let's hope i don't waste it oh he might give it to this guy which is equally okay oh oh hey guys
as long as i can get this guy all right don't want to get hit from behind
that's that do i have any shots left no i don't spy no scout do not no you don't it's that guy down
what else we got we're gonna win just don't let them do a final push and we'll be good to go
i don't want to get sniped either if i get sniped i'm gonna scream speaking of screaming where's
that health pack spawn damn you i am out of everything just go back to spawn no i'll let
you build your i i still want ammo though but i'll let you build it here we go last 60 seconds of
defense make it count gentlemen make it count and my gadget miss everything i mean make it count i
mean miss every shot this guy's got a crit screen though which i'm not damn there's one guy up there
what's going on over here what's going on over here oh give me that could be the guy i'm gonna
do shotgun crits let me do those shotgun crits for the final run shotgun crits for the final run
come on we have like a few seconds where do you go oh he's gone somebody on it so thank you all
so much for watching i really do appreciate it this has been live team fortress 2 on the map
upward and i highly recommend this game side effects may include dry mouth nausea diarrhea
eye pain gas bloating burrito cravings painful hands swollen face swollen tongue dizziness
fatigue farts burps drowsiness constipation painful constipation vomiting cheesy hands ear
bleeding and increased urination team fortress 2 is not for everyone consult your doctor before use