Hey, how's it going? I see that my title has changed.
Um, it's supposed to be Breath of the Wild,
Chill Zone, and I'm a little, a little irritated
that it was changed without my knowledge. I'm just a little
a little irritated about that. It was lame.
It's way funnier. Uh, no, you don't, no, you don't get it.
Nobody else is allowed to be funnier than me on my stream. Let's know how it
works. Ego Andy. Nobody said true.
Wow, I thought I was gonna see some trues. Okay,
uh, so let me give you a little bit of uh, what's gonna happen here today.
This is gonna be kind of a shorter stream. I
kind of feel like my head hurts and it's, I know why. I slept wrong.
I feel fine, but you know when you sleep wrong
and you know you slept wrong and you wake up and you're like, shit,
I kind of, if I don't go back to bed, then it's gonna be bad. It's gonna be worse,
right? And then you go back to bed and you sleep for another hour or two and
you wake up and you're way worse. I hate that. That's what
happened today. So, um, still gonna do the same plan
and maybe all the, maybe the horror game last night.
Maybe I had like a nightmare or something. I don't know. I mean, I may have had a
nightmare. But that, whatever. But yeah, here's what
we're gonna do. We're gonna do Breath of the Wild for like an hour or two.
And then we're gonna move to Gotham Knights uh, for the last couple of hours.
So the stream's probably gonna be like four hours,
maybe. I got some stuff I want to do later tonight and tomorrow I've got,
uh, I want to make sure I'm alert. So this will be probably like a four hour stream.
Uh, this will be the end of the Gotham Knights sponsored
content. I mean they, WB has just been, has been so good to this fucking channel.
I, like, that's all I can really say. They really have been.
Um, so if, if you guys want to like thank somebody, like it would,
WB has been one of the biggest contributors.
Uh, one of the biggest supporters of this stream in the last six plus months.
So, um, that's uh, they've been on point. It's been great. But that's not right now.
Right now we're gonna play Breath of the Wild and then later
in a couple of hours or so we're gonna do Breath of the Wild Gotham Knights.
I, I'm telling you I'm gonna be like chill today but I say that every time
and it never happens. So we'll see. Take a sip of this.
Ah, every time I say I'm gonna relax today, I end up, it ends up being the most like unhinged
stream of the week. So you know what? It's gonna be an insane day today.
It's gonna be so fucked up today. I'm gonna be, I'm gonna be loud,
I'm gonna be screaming, I'm gonna be making jokes. It's gonna be insane.
Just so you know. And here we are.
Uh, what was the last thing that I did? I'm trying to think. Where in the map are we?
Oh, right. I upgraded gear. Oh, no, no, no. I went through that weird maze thing
that everybody was mad at me about. Yeah, I brute forced the lost woods.
Well, I, I, excuse me, uh, you know, you think I need?
They're like, oh, I didn't know like the exact route.
No, I just put my chest out and fucking walk forward and I make it.
There's a raid? Oh, there is a raid. Oh, there is a raid.
There's like three raids. What is it? This is like a coordinated raid.
There's like three people raid me at the same time.
You look like a greasy today. I told, I was gonna scream, I was gonna say,
shut up to you. But I'm supposed to be chill today.
Uh, Jack Manifold, Slimesicle, and Oofs at the same exact time.
Just came in with like 3,000 people or something. I'm like, hi, guys.
Hey, everybody. What's up? Thanks for the raids.
All right, cool. Is triple raid song?
No, I'm supposed to be chilling out today. Oh.
Now, see, that was bad too. That was bad because I didn't give my all
because I have a headache today. And this is, this is your fault for making me do that.
You told me to do that. It's your fault. That was bad.
All right, we're gonna play Breath of the Wild.
Uh, welcome, everybody. Thanks for the raids. Hope you had good streams.
And, uh, I'm sorry. I, I can't, fuck, I can't press the button to turn the camera off.
That's like disconnected because I was trying to fix my camera from last night.
It's like glitching stuff. I still have no idea why that's happening.
All right, it's time to look over at the chat and have somebody tell me where I need to go next.
Because it's been about two weeks since I've opened the game. Just do it your way.
Okay, I'm going to go find a shrine. I'm going to do it my way.
Do the, do what's the Luddie? Do the Luddie?
Yes. Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hit the Luddie, hit the Luddie.
Wait, is that the, is that the Ludwig dance? Is that like the this thing?
I don't know how to do it. And I feel like I don't have like real pants on, so I can't stand up.
It's like you go whim, whim, whim. Data tutorial, ask him.
I don't have real pants on. Well, like I do, but they're like, there's a big hole in the middle.
That sounded fucked up. Um, listen, it's because the button doesn't work.
Oh yeah, we're going to move on. I'll do the, I'll do the Luddie.
Just not now. I'll do, I'll try the Luddie. I have to study it for a little bit though.
I'll try it next stream. Uh, I need a shrine.
There's a tower over there. Should I just go to the tower? Why not, right?
I'm just going to go activate that tower. Let's go. I forget what P is.
Shrine is done over there. Yeah, I'm going for that tower straight ahead.
Wait, hold on a minute. Isn't Calamity Ganon over here? I have to be careful.
Oh, what's the toothpaste story? You're right. I forgot to tell you.
Okay. So I was trying to, I'm multitasking, right?
So I'm brushing my teeth and like walking around getting the stream kind of ready.
Uh, cause it was like, oh, brushing your teeth takes like a few minutes
and hold on a second. Pretty sick. Yeah. I think that deserves applause. I think.
Oh, nice. All right. Thank you. I appreciate it. Thank you for that.
What about you? But you know, does that cover both of you?
All right. That covers both of you. Does that cover, wait, do you have something?
That covers both of you. Mr. Green.
I'm not, how is that extortion? I just asked. I was like, is that covering both of you?
That's like, ah, that's kind of fucked up. I get like a gift and I pointed the,
does that cover both of you? Oh shit. That means you want two things.
All right. Anyways, the toothpaste story. So I'm walking around. I don't even know.
I forget where I was walking. Whatever. I'm going this way now.
So I'm walking around brushing my teeth and I was, I, my switch wasn't plugged in.
So I'm like, shit, where's the cord to the switch? And I'm, I don't know.
I'm kind of a monster of ultimate extreme convenience.
So I have a, I have an iPad that uses the USB-C right on the switch. And if I don't know where
that cord is, I will just rip it out of the back of the switch and plug it next to my bed.
It's just because it's just a USB-C power cable. So that's there. And hold on a second. I'm getting
speech jammed. So I'm trying to tell a story. Shut up. Yeah. Look over your head. It's fine.
I probably shouldn't be using this weapon, right? No, it's fine. This thing's good.
Just pause it. I'm right here. I'll be fine. Okay. That's fine. So anyways,
these skeletons are the most annoying enemy in the game, by the way, just running.
All right. So anyways, start from the beginning. I'll start from the beginning.
You don't really need to know, but Troy, where is it?
Is it up top? It's below me. I think. Where is it? No, it's down here. Yep. Nice. All right. Cool.
Let me heal before. Actually, we'll see what it is. All right. So anyways,
I'm walking around brushing my teeth. I'm trying to do two things at once. And I'm like, fuck,
I need my switch cord because I need it's plugged into the, where the bed is. So I pull it up from
the wall. And as I'm walking, remember the toothbrush with a bunch of foaming toothpastes
in my mouth. So I'm like, let me get it out of the back. And I go and I pull it out and I walk
and I start to pull the cord and it's a long cord. And there's a cup of water next to the,
where the bed is, you know, I want a cup of water so I can sip on it while I, before I sleep and
stuff, when I wake up, whatever. So the cord kind of wrapped around the water and pulled it down.
And I went like this. I went like, Oh, like, cause I don't obviously don't want to spill shit. And I
inhaled like a whole mouthful of fucking toothpaste and it still hurts. There's the whole story. You
deserved it. Yeah. Don't rush. Oh, it's too late to bet on this. I think combat trial. Oh,
I have a lot of good weapons though, but I'm scared. I want to use them all. This is just a,
all right. This is a full recovery and hearts. I do defense, maybe I'm just going to go super
hard. All right, here we go. Or there's another raid. Oh, there is another raid. I'm just getting
everybody's channel. Holy shit. Uh, RT, RT game. What's up, man? Thanks for the raid.
Welcome everybody. Currently playing breath of the wild. Uh, probably shouldn't use this weapon.
This thing's very heavy. It's all right. Did you, I didn't tweet the stream out. Oh shit. Yeah,
I'll tweet this remote. There it is. There it is. There it is. There it is. What? Don't hurt me.
All right. What should I, what should I use? Probably the, uh, no, I don't, I want to save
that or the battle X. Yeah, I get two of these. Come on. What do you got? I got stuck on the
fucking wall. How come I'm not locked on? I guess I am. What just happened? I'm all right. So bad.
It's supposed to be an emote only mode. Turn it off. I don't want to see people write that.
That was awful reaction speed, by the way. That is another raid. How many people have,
is this like a joke on Twitch today? That's repster. What's up? Oh, right. I forgot what
to do about this. That'd be something good at this. All right. Go ahead. Do the. Yeah.
Shoot your bow in the air. What is it doing? Oh shit. Right. You have to, you have to just
sprint, right? What the fuck? Why did that take so long from do that? Nice. Nice. Okay. I forgot
what the thing on the bottom right was. Um, until two seconds ago, I thought that was my gas tank
for some reason. I was like, Oh, I'm full. Like, Oh my, I need gas or something. I don't know
what's in here. Frost spear attack when the blade glows blue to chill the air and freeze your foe.
Yeah, bro. I have to shut up. Seriously. Um, tweet, tweet the stream. I don't even know.
My phone's not even up here. I don't even know where I have no idea. My phone even is.
It's not even up here. I tweet this. I will in a minute. I'll go take a pre break in like two
minutes. What should I get rid of? I don't think I can get rid of anything. Maybe the guardian
spear is this thing. This thing kind of sucks, doesn't it? Yeah. Guardian spear is meh. Yeah.
I'll use this instead. All right. So now I can think this should be enough to upgrade.
You have Jojo's bizarre adventure here. Um, all right. Is that a good thing? Jojo's bizarre
adventure here. Is this just like a swoop? He's talking about like a swoop. I got four of these
now. Should I do? I'm going to health, health, health. All right. I'm streaming. Right. I forgot.
I thought I was just sitting in the chair. All right. Let's go. Uh, I need to go to one of those,
uh, spirit places. Where's the nearest one? Although where's the guardian here? There was
that lizard guardian. Should I do the lizard? Should I try the lizard guardian that's behind
you? I think I was right about to do the lizard, uh, temple, right? What was that? Somebody just
went like, what was that? Where's my mask? There's a Korok nearby. Okay. Well, where is it? Up there
in the stump. Probably in the stump. No help. Nothing. Oh, it is in the stump. All right.
Nice. You got all these bat wings and don't miss the bat man. Gotham night stream coming up in
about an hour and a half or maybe an hour or so. Do I have something that can break this? Smash it.
Yes. Link. Stop climbing and smash it. Let go. This game is a 10 out of 10 for all of you.
This game is like a 9.9.8 now for me. Yeah. I mean, seriously, it was like a 10 out of 10.
Just went down to a 9.999990. It's definitely at the top, right? It just started raining right
when I get to this point. I'm trying to come up the tree. Can I just jump? I think I can just jump,
right? The climbing gear on 9.9 is bigger than 9.10. You, uh, I'm a bit first. It's raining
really hard. Cut the tree down. Is that what will that work? Why would I want to do that?
Yeah. Nine. I know. Okay. I said 9.999999999990. That's higher than 9.1111. Yeah, I know.
The rain is almost over. We just have to wait five minutes. Just campfire and then sleep.
I think that just sitting here for another 30 seconds will be fine. Climb the side of
the stump instead. Is this not getting hit by the rain? I mean, it is, but maybe I can just leap up
here. Do the tweet while you wait. I got it right here. I'm going to tweet. I'm going to
tweet while I wait. I'll be right back. Be right back. I'm going to tweet. Oh my goodness. Holly
is so cute. Can I just tell you that? So I just walked, I was like, oh, I'm going to go find my
phone. I walked over and I noticed that my phone was on the ground, like in front of, like with,
she slid it under the door. For a second I was like, why is my phone on the ground? Oh, that's
right. That's okay. That was really sweet. Okay. All right. What's a good tweet? Breath of, well,
I'm only going to be for Breath of the Wild for like an hour and 10 minutes. That's actually kind
of a funny, there's not another raid, right? No. Somebody just said that. I actually think that's
kind of funny. Breath of the Wild for an hour and 10 minutes. That's so stupid. That's a banger tweet.
It kind of is. There we go. All right. Now everyone's going to know I'm live and take a
look in that amount of time. We're good. I can get my seed here. I did it first. I have four of these
now. I know you can't see it, but I have four. It's not enough. I don't think. Cool. All right.
So that's good. Let me go examine stuff. Where the hero's sword? Do I have to,
should I just go back and do this? No, right. I need to have, right, right. I need to have a
certain amount of HP to even attempt it. I'm going to go back here. Let's get another good view
of the kind of the world around us from what tower? This tower here.
You need 13 hearts. What's the, what do you mean? The top Twitter reply. LOL.
Who's like the Joker? Let's see. This tweet sucks. All right. Guys, I don't use Twitter.
I don't use anything. Okay. So what else should I do in the next like hour or so?
It's an eye headache too. It's like right here. Do the tower. Oh, right. I was going to go to
that tower. That's right. There's three more shrines in this area. Really? In the forest?
Like this way? Shrines are my favorite part of this whole game. So I go over here. I don't see any
inside the forest. They're inside the forest. Just teleport inside. I was just seeing if I
could get a good view. I kind of have a bad time to get transported somewhere. Talk to the Koroks.
Do you pretend to read comments out in chat? Um, I think what happens and I've seen people
be like, what are you talking about? I think as the chat moves fast and I only have a brief
second to kind of go like this, I will see, I think a lot of streamers do this too.
Where you will see like, let's say the sentence has 10 words in it. I'll see like word one,
word four, five, six, and word eight. And I kind of have to be like, all right,
I'm going to fill in the blank. Does that answer your question? Sometimes I can see the whole thing
depending how fast the chat is moving. All right. So I got to talk to the Koroks,
which they're in like the village I'm imagining, right?
They're like down in here. There's one here. Where's like the proper village village where
they're all hanging out and there's like shops and stuff. Oh, it's you. All right. I have seeds.
All right. How much is it? What should I get? Another weapon stash? It's three for another
weapon. I have four. I feel like I'm always low on weapons. I always feel like I need more weapons
or bow. I'm doing weapons. I'm always throwing stuff away.
Fields are fine. Just dodge forehead. You know what I mean?
I don't think I have enough to do anything. Go into the tree now.
Um, wait, who's that? Oh, you could it be your Mr. Hero. Mr. Hero is here. The mushroom on my
head suddenly sprouted today, so I knew something was up. It was a prediction that you'd come,
I think. Us Koroks all got together and prepared some trials just for you, Mr. Hero.
If you pass the very tough trials we prepared, pulling out the master sword would be a piece of
cake. Probably. Among the trials is an extra tough one designed by me, the elder of Korok Forest.
So will you test your mettle in the Korok trials? I'll do it. You're gonna get conned eventually if
you just keep doing what everybody asks you to. Anyways, where was I? Oh yeah, the Korok trials.
Long story short, you need to visit all the shrines in Korok Forest so that you can be
considered a real grown-up. Trial one in the southwest forest. Trial of second sight. Trial
two in the northwest forest. The lost pilgrimage. Trial three. I would say the worst of the three
movies. The test of wood. That does sound like the worst of them, by the way. That sounds like the
shittiest movie out of them all. You can overcome the Korok trials. Oh, and here comes Star Wars.
Episode eight. A test of wood. The other two were way cooler sounding. Okay, so I just have to go
find them. What about you? It's Mr. Hero. Yay, Mr. Hero came to visit us in the forest. What
took you so long? Peek's thought of a trial that will make Mr. Hero stronger. You won't have to
fight and it's not scary. Thermofans that are in their mid-40s are plus twoing that. I would have.
You'll need to be extra careful so I want to see a Bloopy. It's a blue glowy hoppy thing that glows
in the dark just about Peek's size. I just really want to see a Bloopy even if it's just a picture
of one. All right, I'll take a picture of a Bloopy. What's a Bloopy? I knew you were a nice guy, Mr.
Hero. Thanks for listening to Peek's requests. It's a little blue bunny. Oh, okay. Well, he just
explained it while I was asking you. I looked over, missed the part where he said what it was
because I was asking you guys. Okay, cool. Anybody else have anything in here? I have plenty of food.
Oh, Mr. Hero, welcome to the great Deku Tree's navel. Made a bed out of leaves just for you,
Mr. Hero. Take as long as you like with yawns and disease. Um, I have full health, I don't really
get it. You look like a million rupees. Yeah, I would have guessed that a Bloopy was a blue
rupee. That's what I thought it was. Sleep, sleep, sleep in the bed, sleep. Why is everybody saying
sad? Mr. Hero. That just reminds me of Otto. I always say Mr. and then whatever Otto currently
is doing. Oh, here you go, Mr. Treat. I looked, missed a good boy. Oh, Mr. Hungry, right? It's
just he's Mr. whatever he's currently doing. Okay, here's the shop. Mr. Otto. All right, what do you
have? Okay. Can we get a running gag for the rest of the stream? You mean you want me to do like Mr.
Otto stuff for the rest of the stream? All right, where are these shrines? One was north west. Talk?
To what? Ah, if you hope to extract the sword, you'll need to summon a hero's strength.
Let us see how brightly your life force burns. The wise mystical tree. Okay, so I have to go
north west. So it's imagining it's probably here. Can I just go here? The other one was south
something south. I have to select the quest. I don't want to. Oh, this one. Where is it?
There it is. Oh, very cool. Is anybody okay? I hate to say this because this is like a really cool
thing. But when I see this sword, I don't think that looks powerful. I think that looks like it's
on the shelf at Walmart. Like that exact thing is on the shelf at Target. And it's like it's
just like, look, it's a toy at Target. And I just go, it looks cool. But that thing's made out of
foam to me. Oh my god, I must hold my setup down. It's a cool and it sucks because that's
like a really cool design, but it's turned into a full foam toy for me. Yeah, I've contemplated
buying it. Any times I've walked by that toy, I made not making the entire story up just to make
it very clear. How many times I've walked by that sword at Target and gone, you know,
that might look pretty good on my shelf. And then everybody in the audience is laughing.
Like I'm a comedian. You know what I mean? Like, and I go like this. Look at the microphone. Like,
you what? Why are you clout chasing actual liar? Well, no, it's not entirely inaccurate.
Keep going and not get lost in the mist. Oh shit. I this is okay. Don't worry. I've got a cryptic
little hint for you. Hungry trees will show you the way spy their iron to win the day.
Didn't make that sound cool. Okay. So where do I go? I'm kidding. I'm not doing that again.
I'm kidding. Everyone just freaked out. They're like, no, dude, don't do that again.
Okay. The trees have iron. They like the way you'll make your way out of here. Link any day,
check the ground, check the air. What does that actually mean though? They have like iron deposits
on the ones that I can go walk over to or something. I just see somebody sitting. It's like a school
play to me. I just see somebody sitting like the person that plays the piano the whole time.
You know, it's like that older like lady usually is playing the piano and right now there's a scene
going on and she's sitting down in that little pit. It's like, like, and the kids are all up
there doing their scene. I don't think anybody realizes like how unbelievably talented and how
much stress that fucking job was. And I think a lot of them were just doing it for free. Oh, hey,
you need to know literally all the music. You need to know every single song you needed. You need to
be the cue for every single fucking actor. And by the way, you're going to an entire audience
of people watching you play the piano and you are the quarterback of the entire show. What?
That seems like you're the only, you're the sole musician of the entire play. Oh, there we go.
Iron leads the way. No iron there. You know what else is crazy about those musicians?
Those kids would just fuck up all the time and the timing would change in the song
in real time to change the song. So it matched what the kid was fucking singing.
Do you understand how unbelievable that is? That's unbelievable. The song would change mid song and
they would fix, fix, fix it. And I'm doing a different tempo, the same song, different tempo
to match your singing. Okay. Well, there's another one iron. No, no iron. No. Oh my God. I didn't
want to do that. I was trying to zoom the camera in. I went the wrong way. Just find the iron in
the trees. This one here is the iron in this one. What are you doing here? It's supposed to be like
a magical forest. Wait, you want to shoot that? Yeah, no. Do I have to break it? I tried to swing
at it. Iron lights the way. It's the only way. Find your way through the forest. With luck,
you won't act like a tourist. What was the poem? Yes. Yes. Yes. I don't know what that means.
Go through them. Wait, that one has iron. Which one? The other one has iron in its mouth.
I don't see anything else with iron. Like from here, this one. Okay. Iron camera, camera, camera,
camera. Okay. Take a picture of it. Oh, and then I can track where the iron is in the mobs.
Look at that. I get it. Then I can set it to the tracker. I get it. Okay. Let's do it. Start over.
Yeah, that's fine. Start over. Okay. So first one's over here. Let's get the camera out and
no. Gatorade. Yeah. Lightning. Yeah. Shoot it with a lightning arrow.
I don't even have a lightning arrow. I don't even have shock arrows.
Lightning picture. Picture of a lightning. Take a picture of the lightning. Football. Football.
Football. He scored. Take a picture of the lightning. Blah, blah, blah. Fool. Fool. You're
a fool. Put your arm in the air. It's this way, right? Because he's pointing this way.
Here's another one. Where are you pointing? Orc. Am I going to do this for like the whole time
before I play Gotham Knights? One of the mods just tell me where to go. All right. Just translate
one of the hieroglyphics. What do they mean by this? Just translate one of them. The ref does
not mean football. I'll tell you that much. Yeah. I mean, it's not that Legend of Zelda
presents Madden 2025. It's the shape. All right. Well, I'm not helping you anymore.
Piece of shit. Hey. Hey. Hey. Okay. Lightning. Arms up. Do I have to get struck by lightning?
Do I have to stand on top and like have lightning strike or something?
Did I just fucking softlock myself? No. All right. Picture. Picture. Picture. Up, up, up, up, up.
No, no. Octopus arm. Lightning. What shape are the arms making? Yeah. All right. Let me defend
myself. I need to defend myself. I forgot that the magnet power was in the game. What is going on?
It won't come out of the mouth. It was making a sound. Okay. Down, up, down, left. Why does it
say like put it down? I can't. You're almost there, dude. Take a picture of it. When it's
push, pull up, down, take a picture of it. It doesn't make any sense. Remember the poem.
I don't remember the poem. Let me ask the guy again. I can dodge a fucking battleaxe. I can't
wait. I cannot wait until everyone's like, oh, you know, I'm not going to like say he's like,
you know, I'm fucking stupid anymore. Cause like that stream was crazy. Like, holy shit.
Hungry trees will show you the way. Spy their iron to win the day. Do I just have to hold it
and walk away? Spy their iron. So where's the next one? Cause I'm currently permanently banned
the person that told him to go back into the woods. Shit. Yeah, I did. Like two of you said
to go do these. You're the reason why I looked over and I was like, yeah. All right. All right.
Illuminati eyeball. Illuminati eye. The Illuminati. I don't know. Eyeball. Lightning in the eye.
Illuminati eye. Lightning eye. Lightning in the eye. Shoot the eye with lightning. I don't have,
I don't have any shock arrows. Magnet eye. Magnet eye. Magnetize the eye. Magnet on the eye.
Why did I come in here? I'm going to leave. I'm going to leave. I'm going to go to the shrine.
I can't get stuck here for like an hour. Magnetize the eye. Magnet eye. Magnet eye.
Magnet eye. Magnet on the eye. I'm not getting stuck here for an hour.
I would, this is like the street you come back to and you just like melt on the couch and you
just don't care that like no one can watch you do this for an hour. Take a picture of the magnet
frame. Magnet frame. Magnet then picture. But how do I even activate that?
Magnet. What am I looking for? So magnet and then eye. Look. Magnet and look. Magnet then look. Eye.
Magnet. Look. Magnet then look at the eye. Magnet then look. All right. I'm magnet,
I'm magneting right now and I'm looking and nothing's happening. Don't magnet the iron
because it'll show up in the, don't mag, just magnetize and walk around.
Don't, I threw that. I didn't want to. All right. Where's the one from here then?
I just heard Ollie laugh. I heard it. I just heard it. I overthink everything.
Really? I always do this. I play chess when the game's playing checkers. I do it every time. I
seriously do. The last time I was here, it was like, oh, I need to find the song and go to the
beat and turn my back backwards to the song and go backwards. It's like, no, dude, the flame is just
pointing in the direction you're supposed to walk. It was so simple. Okay. But where the hell is the
other one? There's one right here. There it is. There it is. Yeah. Get over there. Edit your tweet
stuck in the Kokiri forest for an hour and 10 minutes. I need to, I hate these enemies.
They're so annoying. Skeleton enemies in every game are so stupid. They're like, you killed it,
but you didn't. It's growing back to life. No, just die. Just let it be. Skeletons always do this.
We need some variety in the skeleton enemies that we face in these games. They can't all be this.
What have I happened to the skeletal mage, by the way, like just like casting like
fucking fireballs and stuff. What happened? We haven't seen that since like Diablo two.
There's a rusty shield. Feed me the age shield guarded by monsters. Eternal. My brother will
repay you in kind. I have to shut up. Okay. So that chest, where'd that chest go? That's it.
One Amber, one Amber for doing this. Is there a leaf anywhere? Do I have anything? Can I just
like swing this and now it needs to be a leaf. I don't have a leaf. I just swim over there.
Oh, this one. Use the ice. Yeah, but I want to, when do I ever get to do this? Please place my
chest in my mouth. The shield eaters brothers stole it from me. Okay. And what does that do for us?
Oh hell yeah. That's sick. That's sick. Let's get a big fish.
Do bets. Um, you can get it done quickly. Yeah, do it. Place your bets. Will I do this in
seven minutes or less? Seven minutes or less? No bets. We do no bets. Just go. No, this one's
just free. Wait. Oh, you mean like actually free? Oh, you're still betting. Who is betting against
this? 25. Oh guys. Um, 32 million versus versus how many? 37, 38 million versus 900,000.
Interesting. We'll be back in 10 minutes. Take a quick break. Can you imagine? Yeah, that was fun.
Giant ancient core. These are important. I've been told that was a pretty cool shrine.
The staircase going up was a little challenging trying to get like one, two, three, four, five,
you know, one foot in front of the other. It was kind of a challenge. Now getting back down is
another story though, because that's going to be a little harder. It's a little steeper.
You're a scammer. I'm not a scammer. That was it. It will be a scam for me to keep that
hole in place. So now I can just walk around. I'm going to go to the other ones. Yeah,
bring me to the entrance. Ooh, the Luddy. Nice armpits. I burn so much fuel. I don't think
people just don't get this. I burn so much fuel inside. There's not a heart in here.
There is this like engine just with like, just like smoke and steam.
I'm just like an engine that's constantly burning fluid and like fuel. I run so hot.
I really am like a lizard. It's not a brain in there either. Apparently. Wow. You motherfucker.
Whoa. That was, wow, that was rough. That was rough. I'll take that one. I just underhanded you
of a fucking Nerf ball. Okay. Test of wood. You need to equip the Korok weapon set. Sure.
You have to keep the sword, bow and shield equipped the whole time. If they break or you
unequip them. I thought he said you die. I'm sorry. Oh my God. That didn't break in the face.
I didn't think, I thought it was just going to phase through them. I'm so sad.
I'm so sad. I didn't want to do that. My goodness. Okay. I have enough for, oh my God.
I have enough for a shield. What about bow? I got to drop a bow, I think.
Knight's bow probably. Yeah, I'll drop this. I've been using it. I feel so bad. Drop the frinic.
Last time I wanted to drop the frinic, everyone was like, don't do it. Don't do it. It's like one
of the best bows in the game. It's been sitting there the whole time. Go reach the shrine, but
nothing can break. By the way, I just want to say, I'm really sorry to you. I'm trying to apologize
to him. I'm really sorry that I threw that at you. Okay. We're cool. Do I need to fight anything?
Why don't I just run? I don't have to fight anything. Just make it to the shrine. What happened?
I have to stay in the fence. Oh, I jumped. That's why. All right. Well, I'm going to do this.
I went out of bounds. Okay. I get it. That's fine. Okay. Stay in the fence. Does this
count as staying in the fence right here? Does this count? That was scary. I can jump over this,
right? I have to break these. Wait, don't unequip. How do I? I don't want to shoot this. Whatever.
Okay. This way. What the hell was that? I should probably heal. What? Just run? Why would you tell
me to do that right now? What? Just run? Just run into the quicksand. Dude, what are you doing?
Just run. Run. Just run. So I just run. You didn't say just run in the parentheses bracket.
Watch out for the quicksand. You said run in all capitals. Run. Run. So I did what you said.
Jeremy, I'm really high. Have you ever seen your side profile? I feel like you would look like a
moon. What do you think? Dude, just run. Hurry up. What are you doing? Stop stalling.
Run. Just run. Okay. I'm just going to. I would have said if I was in the chat,
dude, run, but watch out ahead. It's a cautionary quicksand here. So how am I supposed to get
through this? I want to make ice. All right. Well, I have to kill some of these things.
Hmm. What should I eat? How about just like, yeah, I don't need whatever. I'll eat a roasted bass
and an egg. No, that's enough. Not here. I mean, the chili fish skewer seems pretty good.
Dude, watch out. Somebody say Wellington. Did you bring that back? Did somebody bring back the
Wellington? Everyone hated that. I have to heal these things. This is so annoying. All right. Nice.
We're good. I freaked out. I'm fine. Oh, you can have three. I thought you could only have
two up at one time. Did that upgrade? I thought it was only two. It was three. It's always been
three. Oh, I'm going to take another Tylenol. God damn it. All right. No, I'm going to relax now.
I'm going to chill. Like I said, I was going to. I was trying to. No. I was like, what happened?
I was trying to throw. I was trying to drop the stupid twig that I had equipped.
I wasn't trying to unequip it. I was just trying to get rid of it. I should have just dropped it
in my oven. Whatever. I got. You relaxed way too hard. Jeremy, you need to run, but be cautious
where there is quicksand ahead. If you don't already know, quicksand is a dangerous and can quickly
engulf link and potentially give you a game over. I hope this information is found useful in your
playthrough of the Legend of Zelda Breath of the Wild. Thanks. That's what I'm talking about.
No, I, I'm going to drop that in the inventory. That counts, right?
Jeremy, you should eat a slice of epic bacon. All right. Drop this stupid thing. Drop that.
What else do I don't want that is just clogging up my inventory like a huge turd? Why did you say
that? I don't know. I have a headache today. It's fucking fucked up and gross. I don't care.
I just don't. Oh shit. It didn't jump when I hit the button. It didn't jump when I hit the button.
It didn't jump when I hit the button. I, I hit, I swear to God, sometimes I will hit jump and the
input will just not process because I'm on the wrong frame. Oh, it's like I hit the jump button
and it's like a frame that isn't done being rendered. So it's like, no, you didn't.
Actually, that is not a bad strategy though. Get past this quick. Um, wait, do I have defense?
Yeah, I'm going to do the defense boost. Let's do speed instead. All right. Where's the fire guy?
I promise you that like no human runs off an edge and doesn't press jump. I, I promise you,
I promise you I'm hitting the jump button. I, I'm what I'm telling you. That's what's happening.
Like no human is like, oh, I'm going to put that there. I'm just going to walk off the edge.
No, you, I'm going to jump. No, we're doing it my way. You fucking idiot.
It's just Mr. Bean episode. Every time I play breath of the wild, apparently
it's literally an episode of Mr. Bean. I said I'm Mr. Bean. I'm going, I don't care. What are you
linking me? Change the armor. I, okay. I am self flustered. You have no idea. I'm like, somebody,
I looked over here and somebody linked me like a big bird walking around on the stage and I,
I'm fucking flustered as hell. Somebody looking at the airplane window or something. I don't know
what's going on over here. Did you, did you do Botox? No, I'm going to do it my way today.
Why do I want to change my armor? It's not that hard. No, it's not. I'm just distracted.
Let's get this up with better defense. Yeah. Okay. We're doing this my way.
I need arrows. I have no arrows. I do now. Like, what can I take? Hey, oh, arrow. Okay.
I actually would rather attack these guys. That's exactly what I needed.
I need to buy arrows. Oh no, I don't. I am fucking furious. I already. Yeah. Okay. Here's the
problem. I already beat this shit, but then I went into my inventory and scrolled to a different item
in the game went, ah, ah, ah, you can't do that here. Ah, ah, ah. I wasn't trying to equip it. I
was just trying to throw it away. I don't want my head hurts. What I don't care if this fucking
thing breaks. I'm not embarrassing myself for another 10 minutes. Get up there. Do you have
any arrows up here? Swing the sword. I beat the last boss in Sekiro in like less than three hours.
I don't care what anybody says. Okay. So there's nothing else shooting at me. There's nothing
else attacking me. Right. We're good. I'm to go and I can dodge a battle X in real life.
I can't just launch it back at him and kill him. You go down too quickly. Don't you dare.
The person's not even shooting at me. Okay. I'm going to block you. Good. Okay. Oh shit,
it's going to break. Stop doing the Mario. I'm sorry. I'm sorry, everybody. I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry. Just doing the Mario thing where you jump because you make the jump,
but then you freak out and you jump backwards and then you freak out and jump forwards.
I did the Mario thing. You know what I mean? When you jump, you do a hard jump in Mario and
you don't have the confidence that you made it. So you freak out and press the button again,
which makes you jump a second time. And then you are overcompensating going backwards.
You know what I'm talking about. I did the Mario. The game is not respawning the enemies.
I think I broke the actual game. I'm getting, yeah. No, nothing's respawning.
I'm just going to shoot you. I don't care how far away this is. I don't care what kind of
fucking arrow type it is. You have to die. You too over there. I'm not going to get embarrassed
again. Go ahead. Do it. Get up. Why are you all of a sudden? You don't want to get up now?
Good. Where are you?
Right there. I don't care how expensive these things are. It's worth it. There are a couple,
look at there in the ground over here. See it? I can see them right there. There's one here and
there's one here. How come I can't kill them? Oh, those are just twigs. I'm fine. What's this for?
Did I just walk it up? Let's see. What's going on here?
Ow. I just feel like I'm so nuts for this, but I don't care. I could have just made the jump,
right? No, I don't care. If I skip it, is it going to be mad at me? Is it going to be pissed
off if I do this? I'm not going to get disqualified if I do this, right? I made it. Oh my God. Thank
goodness. I can finally. Oh my God. That was so, it should not have been like that. It just
shouldn't have been like that. It shouldn't have been like that. I don't ever want to do that again.
In fact, I want to delete that from my memory. It was fine. I got one more trial. What was the
last one? Yeah, I think these are reward only shrines. Yeah, I have this would be number six
for orbs. Did you drop the game to a nine point eight? No, it's still a nine. Well,
it's a nine something so far. It's a nine something. It's definitely higher than nine point
one. It's definitely lower than a nine point nine. You guys remember when I gave the outer wilds an
eight point nine and everybody said I and everyone hated me for like a week. All right, let's go back
to the beginning and look how long that took. Just teleport out. I just did. All right. The
final trial of what's the name of this village? Oh, what is it? Mr. Hero. Hey, are you the hero?
Could it be? Welcome to Korok Forest. You're much cooler looking than I thought you'd be. Hey,
thank you. Would be sure you're up to the task. I prepared a trial. What do you think? Will you
accept my trial? Yes. Show me a rod with the power of ice, please. You can wave this rod
to freeze monsters in their tracks. Ice wizrobes love to. Oh, I have one of those.
I have one of those. Look what I got. It's not what he wants. This is an ice rod, isn't it?
This doesn't count. Is it? Oh, it's the it's the wand. OK, not like it's OK. I thought it had to
just be like an ice weapon. Let's do the final trial. The little one thing. OK, cool. This game
is so fun, though. You know what? OK, I'm going to make a I'm going to make an Elden Ring comparison
because that's what I'm going to do. So I don't want to block your ears right now. Go for it.
But I like how in Breath of the Wild, there's just a bunch of random shit to do,
just a bunch of random shit everywhere. And it's not stupid shit.
There's a lot of big open world games. They they say we got all this stuff to do, right?
This is like handcrafted stuff to do. Like this is here, right? This is here.
So they like made this completely unique to this area. It's great. I feel the same way about the
Elden Ring was the same way where every every single spot, all the missions and all the quest
felt like somebody's like handmade it. It wasn't just like, oh, we have this thing we can put here
and this thing we can put here. It was like, oh, no, you're making this area. You're going
to hand make this area. What's wrong? I told you to stop scaring me. What's what's going on?
I have to go back. Oh, OK. I'm ready for the trial. Yes, I am. My little Oki just now set
off to do the trial. Normally I'd go along, too, but Oki insisted on going alone. I'd let
Oki go. But well, I'm just getting worried. Would you please follow Oki without being seen?
I want to make sure nothing happens. He's right there. Look over there. So just make sure nothing
bad happens. This is an escort quest and don't get seen. What are you talking about?
All right. I have to crouch. I have to crouch. All right. Go on. Do what you're going to do.
I need like a GTA mission line above his head. When it fills up, I lose. Shit. Where to go?
Where to go? Where to go? Oh, there you are. Don't I have a stealth thing? Speed, speed. Where's
stealth? The purple one? Let's eat this. What are you coming over here? Don't look over here.
You know, escort quests I think could do with a little bit of kind of reimagining.
How much more fun would this be if it was like, oh, yeah, by the way, he's really reckless.
And instead of just the walk behind the person, it was they were sprinting through and aggroing
the entire forest. Like they just aggro everything and it's just chaos. Do you guys
Warcraft reference? Here it comes. Remember in Warcraft, you do the escort quest and you'd get
attacked by like five people and the escort would sprint way out of the way to fight.
And then after the big fight was done, they would run all the way back to where they were
currently walking from. Hey, they would walk, run all the way back to where they were walking from
and then start slowly going again. Like the game did not, their AI did not allow them to go further
unless they were walking the exact path they had to walk. What are you doing? What are you doing?
Get out of the fucking way. What happened? Hey, what's going on?
Don't do this to me now. I'm in the middle of something. What are we doing right now?
It's just a shadow. I'm not fucking around. I don't care if it's too long. Are you turning around?
What are you doing? Are you walking forward? I can't tell. You're just a blob.
Don't walk into the fire. Okay. Where'd he go? Where'd he go? Where is he? Where'd he go?
Where is he? I don't see him. I don't. Where'd he go? I actually don't know where he is.
Where is he? I don't see him at all. I don't see him. I don't see him. Where is he? Where is he?
I actually, I'm serious. I don't know where he is. Which way? Which way? Which way? I don't. I can't.
I'm serious. Where is he? Right? I didn't see where he went. Oh, there he is. I got it. I got it.
Thank God. All right. Something weird happened here. I made it. Yep, you did.
Are we good? Can I go and talk to him now? You did it. Nice job. Guess what, Mr. Hero? I did the
trial by myself. Aren't I brave? You're probably here for the shrine. The great Deku Tree said
that the monk's blessing is waiting in the shrine ahead. Why don't you go take a look?
Nice job. You did it. Nice work. You did the trial. I did it. Nice. All right. I did all the forest
or at least the shrine stuff. Do I get anything for doing all of it? Do you imagine a bomb
is going, like an explosion goes off next to you? Like, oh, what was that? I didn't have to,
I just shot an arrow. Ancient core. Cool. Yeah. So what's the, is there a, you did all three trials.
Do I get anything? Go upgrade your stasis. Is that from the village? Looks like you have plastic
surgery. I don't know. Is that a good thing or a bad thing? I love how you say this guy, but you've
been a sub for like three months at least. You know who I am. You know what, you, you're, you're
here and you, you're here. Hey dude, this guy, you know who I am. You were hanging out here.
All right, let's turn it in. Celebrity meltdown. Welcome back to celebrity meltdown. Funnyman
streamer German985 had a little bit of a problem in the lost forest in Breath of the Wild. Could
not quite figure out that trial. Our sources say that after the stream ended, Mr. Albertson actually
took a bite out of his drywall and then had to go to the dentist shortly after. All right, what do
I get? It's only a matter of time before you're able to pull the master sword. Hurry up and show
us what you got. Ah, I know that look. You want me to give you something since you visited all the
places, don't you? Yes, I have no choice. I'll give you my treasured item. Big hearty truffle times
three. Okay. This is like the, this is no omega truffle. Cool. That was fun. I want to go, I need
to upgrade my health. Is there one of those trying things in this town? I'm going to have to go back
to the village in the tree. This one inside because I have enough to do. I'll do health.
They did stamina twice. Where is it? Where is it? Sleep in the bed. Oh, okay. I want to do a heart
container. Thank you. Cool. Now somebody said you can say I can upgrade the stasis. Where do I do
that? Have you finished the game? No, not even close. I don't think I'm even at the halfway point.
I have one guardian down. I'm about to do the second guardian in the lab. That was, where was
that? Where's that lab? I feel like it was up. Wasn't it up? It's in the bottom. Oh, okay. Still
think I can't dodge a battle axe after hearing that. All right. Let's go. All right. In here.
Let's talk to you. Good morning. Did you bring me any ancient materials? Yes. Which rune do you want
to power up? Stasis. Three ancient cores. Yes. Thank you. Charging your phone. I like this little
iPad. I like it. Powered up stasis rune can now time stop evil creatures. The stored energy will
act upon the object when the flow of time. Wait, you can, I can freeze people now? That seems kind
of good. It seems really good. What's this? Perhaps you already went and powered them all up.
Suppose your Sheikah slate and your legendary swordsmanship have, we have nothing to fear.
Nothing at all. Calamity Ganon. All right. So I think I'm going to take a little BRB here.
There's our couple of hours of Breath of the Wild. Going to move on to, let's hear it. I want
everyone to say all capitals. What are we moving on to? All capitals. All capitals. Pump everybody
up. Pump everybody up in the chat. All right. I'm going to be right back. I'm going to pee.
I have to set up some stuff. We're going to play Gotham Knights. Sponsored. This is the last stream
of Gotham Knights you'll see that's sponsored for the culmination of the last three days.
Yeah. Probably play, I did, I do want this to be kind of a shorter stream. I have stuff I need to
do and I don't want my eyeball to blow out of my right side of my head. So I'll tell you what we're
going to do after Gotham Knights. What's today? So I will not be live for the next few days.
The next time you will see me live, we'll be on. This is interesting. Probably I will be live for
a short stream on the 21st. I'm still streaming. I'll be back on the 25th in the afternoon.
I'll give you one second. I'll be right back. We're going to play Gotham Knights for a couple
of hours and I might do some co-op too. Cause then I think WB I think wanted to show the co-op.
So we'll see. I'm going to take a break. I'll be right back. No one cares about your eyeball.
I care about my eyeball. I don't want it to break. But yeah, once, um, once I'm back, uh,
in the last kind of this last kind of area of October, like the 29th, 30th and 31st,
we're going to do a ton of Halloween shit. So be right back. Give me two, three minutes.