Let me just check and see. I should have it ready to go. Alright, so this is, like I said, a compilation of videos that have been submitted, and they have been viewed, and they have been not bought by me.
So it's still a surprise, so don't worry. There are 55 videos. We're gonna watch them all. I'm gonna change the title to just green screen.
Hopefully Cox behaves, because it looks like it's trying to not behave. Let me go like this. Alright, I believe we are ready. Here comes a Windows sound.
Alright, so are you ready? 55 downloads. Welcome to the green screen Encore movie experience. It should take us about an hour to an hour and a half maybe plus to get through all these.
Go to like the just chatting section, because that's kind of just what we're doing. We're just hanging out. And here we go. This first one is called Slap Tales. Slap Tales.
Let me make sure you can hear it. Yes, you can. Let's turn this shit up though. Slap Tales. How's that sound? Good volume? Sounds like it's pretty good.
Oh boy, it is. Here we go. Slap Tales. Oh, you want to fight? You want to fucking fight? Don't fucking come at me. Don't.
Okay, hold on. Hold on a second. Hold on a second. That was fucking crazy. This one clip that I like was so scared that this people were gonna like continue to watch this.
Put on a face cam? No, no, no. Not for this. I want to see this one again. I'm sorry.
Turn it up. Okay. Here comes the next one. It's called Bathroom Battles.
Chef Ramsay went into the men's bathroom. Can't believe it. He saw something he would never see in his entire life. You have bleach inside of the sink.
How will the blue team be able to recover from this? Will the red team capitalize in the women's bathroom?
I just, I couldn't believe it. She actually was trying to hurt me. There's a shotgun in the fucking bathroom. Let's tune in next time.
What the fuck is happening? Bathroom battle with Gordon Ramsay.
Activate windows. You're using like a bootleg copy of windows? At least 10.
The bigger they are, the harder they fall. It's a second dream.
What the fuck?
What do I have to say about this? See, this is bullshit.
Guys, I don't think pineapple belongs on pizza.
Tiny Dancer.
Okay, I need a second after that. That was fucking crazy. You elongated my chin and my nose. New emote? I'm cross-eyed. What's going on here?
Did you do this to me or did I actually look like this?
One eye is going this way, the other eye is going the complete opposite direction. Oh man, that was fucking hilarious.
Alright, moving on. Here comes the next one. Harder, better, faster German.
It's just a song.
Harder, better, faster, stronger. Never, ever, after, work is over. Make it, do it, make sense.
Harder, better, faster, stronger.
Harder, make it better, do it faster, make sense.
Stronger, make sense.
Stronger, never, ever, work is never over.
Work it harder, make it better, do it faster, make sense.
Stronger, never, ever, after, work is never over.
Never over, but it is.
It's gonna be burned in my brain.
I'm gonna see these images in my head.
That's a great song.
It's easy for you to say, you're an evil sith.
It's hard, but you're not.
You are my brother, Anakin. I love you.
I fucking hate you.
Okay, that was German Wars Episode 3.
I wanna see that.
It's easy for you to say, you're an evil sith.
It's hard, but you're not.
You are my brother, Anakin. I love you.
I fucking hate you.
This is called It Streams.
I didn't wanna move here.
We couldn't afford to live in the old house anymore.
Plus the new story I'm writing is here.
Is the story a good one this time?
I'm gonna write the best book that anybody's ever read.
I got a really good feeling about this.
You gotta be kidding me.
Family hanging out.
Barbecue 79.
You think these are serial murders?
I don't know.
The first one I found dates back to the 60s.
The link between all these cases is the symbol.
The symbol is associated with a pagan deity named Baguul.
He consumes the souls of human children.
What does something this big before?
Christians believe that Baguul actually lived in the images themselves,
and that they were gateways into his realm.
What's the matter? What's happened?
Get the kids. Pack the car.
We have to leave here now.
This is fucking...
That was great.
They're all waiting for the stream to start.
That's my favorite part.
This next one is called PlayerUnknown's Casino Royale Battle Royale.
Okay? Okay.
I didn't even fit it.
Just get the shit out of me.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Auto with the bonk helmet on.
That was pretty good.
This one's called Jerma's Got That.
Jerma's Got That.
Fuck!
Hold on. I want to see that one.
Hands up, man. I hear a boom.
It's that easy.
Space Channel 985.
Walking around.
The walk. You got the walk.
Meow.
That was fucking awesome.
How long did it take you to find...
How long did it take you to find me saying meow?
I wonder. I don't remember the last time I even said that word.
That was fucking great. Thank you.
Well, I just said it right now.
All right. Coming up next, we have...
I'm not sure. The Germanator.
I'm fucking killing both of you motherfuckers right now.
Surprise, motherfucker!
Oh, look it.
Give me that.
Come here.
Get out of the way.
That was just so fun.
That was fucking great.
This one's called Rat Groove.
Rat Groove.
This is pretty good.
Hold on.
Everyone talk shit.
This is pretty fucking good.
This is legit good shit.
Take a look at this.
No, not that.
Not that. This.
This one right here.
That right there.
I took dance class.
And I was like, I don't know, 12.
Oh, fuck.
God damn it.
No, no, no. Stop.
All right. This one is called Rat Heaven Karate German.
Ow, my butthole.
Okay.
Next one.
It's called Jerma Goes to the Museum.
Going to the museum today.
This is terrible.
Absolutely terrible.
Nothing about this is good.
Not one thing.
This is the thing I'm talking about right here.
I've told you guys this before.
Absolute perfection.
No ifs, ands, or buts.
This right here.
Is absolute perfection.
This is what it looks like up close.
From back there, this is perfect.
It's exactly what I was talking about.
Oh, no.
Oh, my God.
Fucking, what a gamer.
God, seriously.
Why would you walk around a museum like this?
You're like the weirdo.
Turn it up.
You have to shut this off. Shut them all off.
Turn your lights in your house off too.
Yes.
That's it.
What did you say?
Toilet water.
Why do I have an ad for the second channel?
Oh, my God.
Coming up next is Jerma
versus Jerma.
Looks like in Smash Brothers.
I don't want to bite you.
I don't want to.
What the fuck is that?
It's time for you to pay.
That was fucking hilarious.
I just want to see one.
Hold on.
I just want to see this right here.
What the fuck is that?
It's a recovery move.
It's fucking brilliant.
What the fuck is that?
It's time for you to pay.
Everybody uses
the end of the stomach
puke sound thing.
Jerma Theft Auto
is coming up next.
This is my house.
This is what he's here for.
He's here for money.
And he knows.
I got fucking 700 million bits.
He knows I have it.
What the fuck was that?
Hold on.
Wait a second.
Jerma and Odd Michael
at the water park.
Why did you do this?
I can't.
I'm not trying to replay it.
I'm trying to pause.
Coming up next.
I gave special
permission
to somebody to make
a longer video.
One person has special permission.
You've known a lot of their videos.
They do a lot of great content.
Special permission for this next coming up.
I have no idea what this is.
This is nine minutes.
It's called compact.
It's a short film.
If you want to know
who this is, it is
Trust No One.
Trust No One. We've seen at least
a half dozen hilarious videos
from Trust No One.
You guys get the popcorn ready.
Here we go.
We'll probably take a pee break after this.
We'll see where we are.
That was me.
Get out of the fucking way.
I killed like ten birds with one stone.
My pants almost ripped in half.
Fucking idiot.
You want to fight?
Don't come at me.
I hate it.
It doesn't even work.
Oh my god.
Made it to the top.
Fuck you.
What?
Come on, you can do it.
You can do it.
Oh shit.
Who's your daddy?
Constant conflict.
Nobody use that.
You'll be in big trouble.
Holy shit.
Nobody use that.
What the fuck is that?
Really?
Did I make it?
I'm 30.
You don't get any taller?
Alright, first of all
that was fucking insane.
That was absolutely fucking unbelievable.
Thank you, trust no one
for your full on
ten minute short film.
That was so good.
Academy Award nominee for short film
in 2019.
In the literal sense too.
Alright, let me see something real quick.
I want to see where we are in the
playlist.
I don't want any spoilers here.
We're almost
at halfway.
We'll do another five or six more and
we'll go pee.
There's probably a couple more.
We'll be almost at the halfway mark.
This next one is called
Germ of the Celery Man.
Good morning, Paul.
What will your first sequence of the day be?
Computer load up Celery Man, please.
Yes, Paul.
Could you
kick up the 43...
D3...
Alright.
Here comes the Germba 95 anime
opening?
Here we go.
Not even my real name.
Why do we...
What is this?
You still don't seem to get it, so maybe I just need to spell it out for you more clearly.
See, you have no chances
of beating me. None whatsoever.
Zip, zilch, serum.
No matter how hard you try, there's simply no
version of this fight where you come out on top.
Sorry, no dice.
You sure are talking a lot. Oh, look at me.
You know that? No, I didn't do it right.
Who would have ever thought
it'd be this ridiculously easy
for me to make a fool out of myself?
What?
Did you really think something like that was going to work on me?
This is a move made up by a little kid.
You're getting pretty desperate if that's the best you've got.
I just shit my pants.
I can't do it anymore.
So what to do now?
Hmm.
What are you waiting for? Get your act together already.
Ten seconds.
I'll give you that long to say your prayers.
Or whatever it is you need to do, then I'll blast you to hell.
Okay.
Here I go.
I can't just do it.
You are into a corner, there's only one thing to do.
So just do it.
Interesting thought process.
Not my head!
You're the one who should be saved.
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait.
This is really important.
You need to understand something.
This is a doctored image.
This is not even my head.
This is not my head.
Where is it?
Interesting thought process.
That's not my head.
That's not the top of my head.
That's a Photoshop job.
Look.
Where am I?
That's not the top of my head.
You understand?
Don't believe the lies.
Nice wig.
Okay, break.
Coming up next is...
Bizarre Adventure.
Here we go!
No!
That was really good.
Hold on.
We don't want to get any spoilers.
I keep fucking going to this.
I don't want any spoilers.
Alright.
Let's take a quick pee break.
I'll see you guys in like two minutes.
We're at pretty much the halfway point.
There is more to see.
I gotta get some water or something.
My face is starting to hurt.
See you guys in like two minutes, three minutes.
I'm back.
So far these have been fucking fantastic.
He's back, he's back.
Yeah, I'm back.
Alright, so coming up next, this one is called
Hyperdimension Germania.
Elbertson Breaker.
Sounds good to me.
Already got an interesting start.
You ready?
Three, two, one, here we go.
Life is paint.
You're dead.
I hate...
Jesus!
Oh no!
Please! Oh my god!
Yes!
Dry thunder for clean machine.
Vroom vroom!
Where's your teeth going?
Who the fuck is that guy?
What?
I gotta say this one again.
Who the fuck is that guy?
This is...
I love this one.
This one is called
Images of German 985
Real.
Do not watch at night.
Hopefully it's not night, wherever any of you are.
Which?
German Beat Undertale.
Come here.
I'm gonna push you and you all
watch this dog shit.
Just get in there.
Oh Jesus!
Oh no!
I don't know!
What?
Okay.
Wait, is this a new video?
What?
I saved the world right here.
I just saved the world.
What?
Why was I in Minecraft?
Oh by the way,
in any of these videos
there could be some television show
or animated show
or cartoon
or they might just yell out
a spoiler for your favorite show.
Somebody may have been watching that
in the middle of that game.
Just be aware that if you see a show
that you've been watching or that you will watch
just go to the bathroom or something
and come back.
Germando.
This is a 2018 trailer for Germando.
I want your kid back.
Then you gotta cooperate.
Right? Wrong.
Now
somewhere
somehow
someone's gonna pay.
Do you think that he is going
to give us any problems?
Move up in smoke!
Do exactly as he's told.
Hasta luego, fellas.
You're free, guys.
I'm going to kill you last.
Are you going to tell me what's going on or what?
No.
He's dead. He's gone.
But it was not informed about this.
Are you trying to do this all by yourself?
I think you know what I'm going to do probably.
Do you eat ass?
The answer is no.
I do not eat ass.
Why?
It's a mission
no man can survive.
I'm sorry.
Schwarzenegger here with a Team Fortress 2
gameplay commentary.
I'm the captain now.
Interesting thought process.
Look at me! Look at me!
That's what you sound like.
Roger, stop the tow.
Loot get!
He's blind to the watch!
What?
I'm seeing stars.
Hold on.
If you've never seen
that movie
just be aware
that you might
have seen the whole thing.
God damn it.
What the fuck?
There was so much going on there.
There was so much stupid shit
that he'd put...
I need a minute.
I was literally seeing white specks
in my vision.
That was fucked.
No, it's because I was out of air.
I was laughing
a lot.
The face with my...
It was too much for my brain.
German is the captain now
and now we're gonna move on to
Sonic the Hedgehog
live action Sonic the Hedgehog
official reveal or something.
That's what you sound like.
Ow.
Ooh, up in smoke.
Oh shit, another witness.
This is a pretty good beach party.
What's that guy doing?
Oh no, they're killing each other.
Give me that shotgun.
Shoot him with the shotgun.
Get out of the fucking way.
That's a new subject.
We need to take up the back.
We need to send in our music first.
We need to send in the pipes first.
This is the best part right here.
Okay, we are clear.
Houston, we have list off.
Watch out for that asshole.
I knew it was coming too and it scared me.
That was fucking awesome.
That was fucking great.
You guys are fucking awesome.
Alright, Jerva gets into a fight.
Let's see how this one plays out.
My favorite part is
like I said before
into the stomach puke.
I got hit during
that green screen when I was
in front of it. I took like
in the shoulder, in the back
the ten different injuries into the stomach.
But everybody
just uses the puke and I think that's
I love that because there's so many other
options. Do we always
see this one? I don't remember.
This Jerva's in the kitchen.
Well, I'm something of a scientist myself.
What?
Wait, hold on.
Got faded.
That was not one we have seen.
This is called Late Night Weatherman
Jerva 985 Green Screen Movie Night.
Here we go.
That's just a big old soap
if you know what I'm saying.
Fuck this Jerva.
You know typically I bring you the weather
but today I want to show you something
different. I want to show you
something that I care about.
Something that I want to show.
That I haven't been having on. I had no opportunity to do it till now.
Diane
that's my son. I just wanted to show
her. I don't know.
And Diane go fuck show business.
That was fucking awesome.
This is part one
coming up. Wait,
hold on. Did you guys hear me? Was I muted?
Oh, I'm sorry. I was muted.
I said this might be a, if you've never
seen a television show, just, I don't know.
Get spoiled.
Go fuck yourself.
Now that's funny.
That doesn't make any sense.
It's funny because it's Jero-Jero.
I don't have very much to say
right now. Besides, here comes
Jerva Blanca.
Fuck you.
What?
What is that? What just happened?
Why?
Why? What?
Don't forget about me. The newest turtle.
Socrates. I may be small
but I sure got lots of power.
I trust you correctly. I slash
those buddies like nobody's business.
Check me out.
You'll see a little bit of footage right here.
Don't touch it.
Spoilers
for every movie
ever made.
The climax of every movie.
In case you were wondering.
What a god
of a gamer, seriously.
Slow go-
Knock, knock. Who's there?
Hi. Hi. Hi.
Hi.
You're a scientist.
Relaxing or like I'm being
tortured in a dungeon.
It could be both. I think it works
for both.
That was pretty good though.
Next meme.
That's true.
Jerva plays- Jerva plays
Lobotomy Corporation.
I never did this.
This is the chat. Jerva went
and he actually went live.
What? I'm actually
really, really, really curious about this one.
Let's go.
I can't do it. I can't do it. I can't do it.
What a reference. What a
callback.
Here's the Nintendo Direct.
Did you make this?
Why is this here? Fortnite.
The gates to the burning
walls will open on Nintendo Switch.
Of course, we're talking
about Diablo 3.
The dark fantasy adventure that may just
consume your life both inside and
outside the game world.
Play as a demon hunter, barbarian,
crusader, necromancer,
witch doctor, monk
or wizard. Diablo 3
Eternal Collection invades
Nintendo Switch on November 2.
We're making this
party super.
Wait, I can catch that in midair? Are you kidding me?
That's going to be a fucking highlight reel. Watch this.
Alright. I'm ready.
Okay. I'm going to catch
it in my mouth. What is that?
Here it comes.
You got me. You got me.
You got me.
We have to be getting... No, don't sleep on the
turnbuckle again.
No.
I fucking hated this so much.
When that crashed...
That was the worst thing ever when it happened.
Official Blu-ray 2019
trailer HD2108P
IMDB... What's the title of this?
Does this have a title?
I died like 25 years
ago and I'm just in the house.
I wish I had the time and money to be able to go
anywhere I wanted to go.
And I've been going crazy, guys.
I've been losing my mind.
What the hell is going on?
We don't fucking choose sides.
25 non-smoker. When am I going to...
What's my death clock here?
Friday, July 4th, 2019.
Is this what you fucking
wanted?
The best thing
about this is
that could seriously have been
any trailer
in the last 5 to 10 years.
It was perfect. Comes out today.
Well, there you go.
Hope it's good.
The best thing about
going on a diet, it's not a bad idea.
Wait till he lands.
Interesting
thought process. Look at me!
Look at me! That's what you sound like.
Look at me!
What does that say?
This stream sucks.
Hey, fellas!
Ooh, up in smoke!
You're right on time, detectives.
It appears that the victim
was burned alive after
flying into the suspect's office
last night. We haven't located
any witnesses and there doesn't seem
to be any source coin for the fire.
Almost as if they suddenly
combusted it.
Well, you know what they say.
Smoke him if he got him.
Why? There's been two of those.
I love this.
Alright, coming up next.
We have Jerma's fantastic
journey.
Looks like we've got a potential balloon
video here.
That was
cute. That was cute.
That was really cute. I like that one.
This is the best TV news
blooper fails. I think
this is an encore of an encore
just in case people didn't see this one because
this is great. I believe
this is another one that we have seen before, maybe?
Here we go.
An occupational hazard while shooting a story can be
he was standing beside a skate ramp
when this happened.
Just take eight double
stuffed Oreos and put them in a glass.
Fill it up with milk and eat it with a spoon.
The Ninja Turtle, Michelangelo,
made an appearance
in July.
To draw attention
to our collection of Burke
Oreos.
Come on now.
I mean, come on.
Look at him.
He looks
really pleased to be there.
Wow, that was really dramatic.
There's a reason they call these people
heroes. I mean,
they were going at a really good clip there.
We've had some hot weather, I guess.
Yes.
That's right.
Send something, please.
Baltimore Ravens running back.
Ray Rice breaks his silence today, apologizing
to his wife and his fans for the allegations
that he attacked his wife, knocking her
unconscious in a casino
elevator this last February.
They're trading back and forth. Blue
men and German. Blue men and German.
Wait a minute. That is not the right
video, but Rice has been
suspended.
Scandals happen all the time.
The question is how do democracies respond
to those scandals?
And what will it mean for
the wider region? I think one of your
children has just walked in. I mean, shifting
sands in the region. Do you think
relations with the north may change?
I would be surprised if they do.
Pardon me.
I love this one.
My apologies.
Derva opens the door.
That was sick.
Here's what I have to say about
this. Don't do it.
Don't do it.
Holy shit.
How it feels to chew
five gum.
Stimulate your
senses.
You want to fight?
Don't come at me.
You did it.
I got a bucket of chicken.
Don't come at me.
That's three.
That's strike three.
This is called
unfinished
bad coffee Cheetos chicken.
Looks pretty cool.
Here we go.
Let's go.
Hey, man! Welcome to the stream!
All right, hold on, hold on, hold on. So that was pretty well done. That was pretty well done.
This is also 8 minutes and 41 seconds, you're noticing. This is Kewo's. I believe these are
Kewo's edits. For those of you that don't know Kewo, she's hilarious, really talented, really
funny person, and obviously wanted to show these. We did watch them before,
like maybe a couple months back. I'm not sure we watched them all, though.
So a couple people get some extra time, but I did want to show these, so here we go.
My name's Jerma, nice to meet you. Right there, bingo! Right there, that's the follow button.
If you click that, every so often you're getting notified that I'm streaming.
And I do lots of fun things on this stream, like...
Wait, what? I just get like an ad. That's the first ad I see.
I thought that was in the video for a second. I was like, I don't remember that being in
the video. All right, let's go again. Welcome to the stream. My name's Jerma,
nice to meet you. Right there, bingo! Right there, that's the follow button. If you click that,
every so often you're getting notified that I'm streaming. And I do lots of fun things on this
stream, like playing Hitman. We played that last night. That's it, it's right there.
You should have acted. They're already here. The Elder Scrolls told of their return.
Their defeat was merely a delay for the time after Oblivion opened,
when the Sons of Skyrim would spill their own blood.
No one wanted to believe, believe they even existed. And when the truth finally dawned,
it dawned in fire. But one that in their tongue is Dovahkiin, Dragonborn.
What's happening to our city, Yuri? I don't know.
Feels like the end of the world. Maybe it is.
Peter Parker, how the hell are- Absolutely terrible.
The city is in danger. We need our help. All of our help.
Fuck you. Gang of costume nutjobs is taking the city apart piece by piece.
Eat your vegetables and fruits too.
This is opportunity knocking. You know the closer you get to them, the more you become a-
Closer I get, the better chance we have to stop them.
You're a scientist.
I've ordered Silver Sable and her team to shoot you on sight.
Hey, Yuri!
This city's had enough of your vigilante-
Cool.
I'm something of a scientist myself.
It's time for you to pay!
Oh my god.
So why do you question for a real honest me?
Yeah!
Mom, I see it!
I'm gonna die.
Me getting killed.
It's like not being that bad of a lightsaber, you die instantly.
You wouldn't even get out of the academy.
Oh no.
Shit screams hack.
Yeah!
Kingdom Hearts.
With the steering wheel.
Fire?
Water.
Fire.
Long ago, the four nations lived together in harmony.
Then, everything changed when the Fire Nation attacked.
What? What the fuck is that?
Great.
Oh, the emotes!
That's cool.
So, that was all QWO, by the way.
Until we just got to the next one here.
I'm trying not to just like be a cackling psycho over these, so muting sometimes.
Oh man.
I think we're getting close to the end though.
Don't mute. Don't mute.
Well, I haven't been muting that much.
But yeah, that was all QWO.
So, I think we only have maybe a handful more.
Like five or six more, maybe?
I'm not sure.
But here we go.
This is Ultra Compact Dream Streamer.
This is really good.
This is New York.
Peter in New York City, but 50% of its population is germos.
Oh god.
Peter, I hear you.
Why designs it?
Well, I have something in the socks.
I got it right there.
Crying.
Asshole.
My face!
Why are we all psychos?
Why are we all like fucking NPCs with like our aggression turned up to 100?
Oh, I need to see this one again.
Why? Like there's one of them hiding behind the taxi?
Holy shit.
That was fucking funny.
Again.
Peter, I hear you.
Why designs it?
Well, I have something in the socks.
I got it right there.
That's my guy right there.
Yeah.
We're all so like fucked up.
I didn't want to knock you up.
Why would they be in a fight?
There's no reason.
They didn't do anything.
Hold on.
Jesus Christ.
My fucking head is killing me right now.
Hold on.
Give me one second.
Okay.
I'm back.
Holy shit.
It's just...
This is perfect.
I think we're at the end.
Here comes the...
I think this is the last video on the list.
End of the movie night voice.
Oh, this is number 56 or 57, I think.
So here we go.
Happy eighth anniversary.
It's been eight years.
What Evo is that?
Oh, that's...
Is that Mars?
No.
Oh, look.
Viva Los Reyes.
Thank you for that.
Oh my god.
It's my pleasure.
It's been an eventful eight years.
And that is going to take us to the end.
We're getting a shitload of community subs are coming in.
Bingo Sunshine, thanks for five.
Great Canadian Frick Club, thanks for ten.
Gnarly, thanks for five.
Oh, man.
That was the encore presentation of green screen footage.
I'm like a broken record now.
Oh, man.
Oh, jeez.
My head is fucking flying around in circles right now.
Kazzy, thanks for the five community subs.
And yeah, it actually, like last week or something,
was eight years on Twitch and YouTube combined.
It's been a long time.
I want to just thank everybody for all the awesome shit that they made.
If your video didn't make it through,
that doesn't mean it wasn't any good.
I just wanted to condense this down to like a couple hours.
Like one to two hours.
So the playlist, I think, let me make sure there's that.
There might be one.
There might be another one.
Let me see.
Let's just check the playlist to see just in case something was added.
No, that's it.
So I got the playlist.
It will be publiced.
It's not going to be unlisted.
Grump is publishing this right now.
Here is the playlist if you'd like to watch everything that was there.
You guys surprise me every single day with your creativity
and how fucking funny and interesting the shit you put together is.
All I could do this stream is just enjoy it.
So thank you for all these awesome videos and thanks for participating.
Here is a link to the playlist.
That is the current playlist.
55 videos.
It's about an hour and 20 minutes.
Hour and 10 minutes or so.
So I am going to, I'm probably going to call it early
because I have seriously like slapped myself
into like an even worse headache than I had like an hour ago.
So I'm probably going to have to call it early.
But what's today?
Today is Saturday that I will see you guys.
Let me see here.
Today is Saturday.
I got some work to do on the carnival.
So I'll see you guys on Tuesday.
We'll do Tuesday.
I am like, my like sensory overload here is
that last New York City one.
Holy shit.
I almost died.
The what?
Oh, if you don't know, I'll be talking about it a lot more
over the next few weeks.
But there's going to be a Twitch controlled robot carnival stream
that is going to be on the stream within the next couple of months.
And I kind of have to dial back streams to work on it.
So it should be a lot of fun.
So I'll see you guys on Tuesday.
I'm going to just take a quick break.
I'm going to grab a water and we'll come back
and do the bits and the subs and everything.
But thank you so much for being part of this community.
And if you just watch, if you make this kind of shit, thank you.
I love every second of it.
So I will be right back.
I'm going to like throw some water in my face
and we'll continue for another like probably 20, 30 minutes.
I'll be right back.
Okay, I am back.
Let us get to the end here.
Stream is over.
Well, kind of.
Let's do the bits.
I also want to do the credits too.
We had a shitload of community subs tonight.
Oh, like so many.
Like more than at least a few hundred probably.
At least two to three hundred subs tonight.
So that's a fucking entire like baseball stadium full of people.
Well, I mean, not really.
If there was 200 people at a baseball game, it'd probably be.
Well, whatever.
It's our baseball stadium.
It's a little league stadium.
Yeah, 250 people showed up to a little league game.
Wow.
That's a, that's huge.
But thanks again, regardless, everybody.
All the community subs.
Let's go back to earlier today.
We had trust no one gave two dollars and fifty cents.
Awesome, awesome job.
Trust no one.
It was a hell of a job.
They say the movie night is finally over.
But my green screen videos playlist is not.
After a rich dinner, let's have some sweet desserts.
It will last less than 10 minutes.
Don't worry.
Love to you, dad.
Love to chat.
Green screen movie encore night desserts.
We got desserts.
Oh man, we've got some desserts.
Okay.
This is trust no one.
Made of that insanely awesome nine minute full short movie.
We're going to get the after credit scene here then.
Why not?
Right?
I'm going to get it on the screen.
Here are the desserts.
These are all by trust no one.
Less than 10 minutes or so here.
We will continue with the bits after this, but this is truly like me.
If we're here, let's do it.
I just need to make this bigger.
Here we go.
This is chat.
Jermis chat during a stream.
I will link this playlist as well.
These were the final levels.
Oh, what?
Good.
Kill him.
Kill him now.
What the fuck?
Do it.
Please welcome the guy who will finally be Team 71 on screen.
That's true.
Life is pain.
Jermis tie issue.
I don't fucking care about this tie.
You are Superman, aren't you?
And now you have to go fuck yourself.
Oh, my head.
Zap.
Wait, this is spoiler.
This is spoiler incoming.
This possible spoiler alert.
For I don't know what movie.
They've made like 16 of these.
I don't know which one.
Just be ready.
Bugs Bungie Special.
You really fucking watching this shit?
Oh, please.
Oh, my God.
Fuck you.
Wait, this is interview.
German.
German 2019 interviewing German 2017.
What is this?
Excuse me.
I'll excuse me like Walgreens.
Are you here for the interview?
No, just sit down.
Sit down.
Absolutely.
What's your name?
German 985.
Oh, I was looking at your resume.
I have a good resume.
It looks like you've got some.
Content creator on YouTube dot com
with over six, seven hundred thousand subscribers
and over a thousand videos made.
Unbelievable.
That's really, really great.
Well, you know.
Okay.
All right.
So what is it about this company
that you think that you can add,
you know, some worth to?
I can do this.
Do this.
Okay.
Well, we're going to need a lot of that.
So it's really, really important that you understand.
I need valuable team members and.
Well, I can do this.
What's that?
I can count to ten.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Okay.
Well, I don't think the position is for you.
The position already has been filled.
So what can you do?
Just so you know who you're dealing with.
Nobody used any of that.
That's the only one that used guy at desk.
Interviewing somebody.
I sat there in January 1st and I did like five of those.
This is back to formula.
Who is this?
Is this me?
This out.
Why don't you do the other filming for us while I run the brand?
I'm going to give you this camera.
But first, let me just say.
Number one, don't talk.
I'm getting the hang of it.
Like this guy sucks.
Hey, it's time to play Dark Souls Remastered.
What do you guys say?
You ready?
No, no, no, no.
Damn it.
There it is.
Oh, I'm fucking dead.
Oh, my God.
This guy is horrible.
What about peppers and cheese?
Is that going to work?
Absolutely terrible.
Nothing about this is good.
Not one thing.
God, I hate this.
I hate this.
This is terrible.
I'm going to beat this little shit.
Oh, fuck.
Now that's a.
Oh, oh, boy.
It is time to say those eight magic words.
I am not smarter than a fifth grader.
Hey, it's Jerma from Jerma.85 and you're watching.
Wait, is this a point that like my channel sucks?
Hi, squash.
Oh, hi.
What are you playing as?
I'm playing as.
What are you playing?
I'm going to be playing Team Fortress 2 as.
Oh, but I like that.
What?
I don't what?
Why do I have to delete system 32?
Well, that was trust no one's playlist of desserts.
Those are fucking great.
No, I know that that was a watcher watching me.
That was a chatter.
But like, I'm pretending to be that channel.
Like, why would I delete?
Why would I need to do that?
It's my motivation of being a chatter in the channel.
But let's go back to saying good night.
Trust no one.
Again, great shit.
Awesome.
You knocked it out of the park.
Oh, I feel like I've exhaled.
Like 30 to 40 times tonight.
I've done the get.
I've been seated for so long as a 75 year old man.
And that's the noise that you make when you get up after about an hour of sitting done.
Ah, that was fucking awesome.
But let's get back to the bits.
Good shit as always.
We also had too many community subs to even count.
Like I said earlier.
Thank you, everybody.
Marvash Magali, thanks for the 250.
I swear, Jeremy, if there's a single Jojo dance meme in the playlist,
I will unsub and sue you.
Also, can you show Otto?
Otto is currently downstairs.
But they're I'm sorry that you have to unsubscribe.
I'm really sorry about that.
But there was at least one Jojo dance clip.
Thank you, peaceful Haley for the 250.
Hey, Jeremy, I don't really watch your streams that much anymore.
I'm sorry.
I'd like to stop in from time to time to donate.
And finally, I got some voice over gigs.
It's nothing fancy just reading articles and something for e-learning.
But I'm so happy I finally got something.
And there's even more gigs to come.
Can't wait for whatever is in store.
Anyways, hope you enjoy playing this baby game.
Mario, is it not a baby game?
Is it a game for adults?
It's a game for an adult.
But that's good to hear.
Awesome.
Keep chipping at it.
Thank you so much for the 250s.
And I think thanks for stopping by.
Happy to have you whenever you end up dropping by to say hello.
And good luck.
Hopefully you get some more stuff going on.
Mr. Comcast gave $5 earlier.
Hey, Jeremy, John, Comcast here.
I've been sitting alone in my shitty ripoff version of the Batcave.
The calm cave, you know, because I'm rich.
But I've been very lonely without you.
Going away for a week.
Disgraceful.
Anyway, I filled that time with writing short stories about you.
I hope you enjoy.
This is like three pages long.
Yeah, I used to know German on 8-5.
We go way back further than I can remember.
Back in those days, he was a somewhat normal functioning member of society.
We'd hang around bingo halls, giving high fives to old ladies as they left.
We'd go to see movies and eat food at places that sell food.
Sometimes we'd even go and eat food at the movies.
Life was great, tranquil, perfect.
It didn't last.
Nothing good lasts forever.
I noticed the change somewhere around 2010.
Instead of hanging out, he'd want to stay in.
We grew distant around that time.
If I only knew back then what I know now,
I'd have to try harder to get him to talk to save him.
But I was foolish.
Hanging out with Jerma became stranger.
It started somewhat innocent.
He'd go up to people, put on dumb voices, say dumb things.
But that was mostly the extent of it.
It got worse as time went on, though.
He went from putting on voices to actually being the characters of the voices he did.
He'd hide in my closet, pretending to be a crazy old grandpa,
mocking me for being bad at Call of Duty Modern Warfare 2.
His words hurt, but not long after his fist did.
Thank you for the five dollars, Mr. Comcast,
and thanks for the story, this creative writing assignment that you've given yourself.
Okay, if you'd like to read more, you can read more at your own pace.
Did I cut off my own mic?
No, I cut off my own throat.
I mean, I cut off my own...
I silenced myself.
I stopped talking is what I...
Thank you, oh my god, Teyon, for the 250.
Great stream today, Jerma.
Can't wait for the 20-second Switch Block Blast stream tomorrow.
Fourth consecutive line, thanks for the five bucks.
It's okay, Jerma, you're the world record holder in our hearts.
Oh, hey, thank you.
Thank you.
That means a lot.
Sirok, thanks for the 250.
Hey, Jerma, it's me, your agent.
After that embarrassing series of losses for the world record,
you're done as a gamer.
But don't worry, I have another gig lined up for you.
They're in the Las Vegas area and they even have a website.
You can check it out.
Las Vegas...
I'm not even gonna read that out loud.
But thank you for the 250.
We appreciate it.
Thank you, Sirok.
Also, Drew Word, thanks for the three dollars and ten cents.
Nice driving world record in my book.
Thank you.
Thank you, Drew.
We also had...
Not that long ago, we had Twitch Chat Main gave five dollars.
Pogchamped all over my pants.
You shit your pants?
What's that mean?
But thank you.
I hope he cleaned up.
Seize of the Roman, thanks to the five dollars.
Any gifters in chat?
Any oil princes?
Any hedge fund managers?
Any tiger owners?
Any oil princes?
Oh, this is during the insane sub blast that we got.
Me, me, me.
Thank you to AveryDroppedDead for the ten dollars.
Drew, I've been watching you for years and I've finally been able to donate.
I know it's not much, but I just want to show support to my favorite streamer.
Thank you.
You got me out of a rough place a couple years ago in the laughs.
You gave me a priceless...
Thank you for being your wonderful self.
I love you and trans rights.
Transgender pride.
Thank you so much, Avery.
Thank you for ten bucks.
And I am more than happy to be your favorite streamer.
I...
PeacefulHaley just came in with five community subs right now.
Thank you, PeacefulHaley, on top of your donation from earlier.
Thanks a lot.
You're my favorite streamer.
Thanks, guys.
Hey, Drew, I'm a hedge fund manager here.
I'd like to donate a hundred thousand dollars to you,
but I can only do so if you give me your Twitch username and password
so I can deposit it in your account directly.
I await your response.
Oh.
Yeah, okay.
I mean, that makes sense because, I mean, how else would you be able to...
How much would you do that, right?
I think I get it.
Because that's like a large amount of money I get.
No, that makes sense.
My username is obviously German985.
That's my username is what it is.
And my password is 24.
So did my stream cut out?
I got a long password.
It's like 600 characters.
I did that.
I think I got it all.
What happened to the internet?
No, I'm here.
Did you get it?
Yeah, it's like a 600 character password.
I'll just, I'll send it to you.
Thanks though.
When should I expect the money?
Just German98524.
224.
German98524?
I can't believe it.
Hey, thank you too.
Honey chain for the three bucks.
German, you have beautiful hair.
Thank you.
I take very good care of it.
I wash it and I condition it and I comb it and I brush it
and I eat lots of vitamin E
and I eat lots of high fatty omega threes
to make sure it's luscious.
I take care of it.
I don't want to lose it.
But thank you for the three dollars.
Another hungry hedgehog.
Thanks for the three dollars.
I can't stress enough how much I needed this tonight.
Thanks.
I'm glad you enjoyed it because it's always a blast.
It's always awesome.
I just wanted to make sure, you know, months ago
when I talked about doing this,
I wanted to have like enough time to go by
because this kind of shit is really overstimulating.
So I don't usually like to do the same thing twice.
And if it's something that a lot of people really want
and enough time goes by,
then we can kind of do it again.
So definitely worth doing for sure.
Cyanide Zero coming in with 10 community subs.
Thank you Cyanide.
Lots of subs tonight.
Wait till you see the credits roll by.
It's like 300.
But thank you.
Really appreciate that.
There was so...
I think I missed community substitute
just because there was so many in a row.
But whoever you are, however much you gave.
Thanks.
Really.
Eee half note.
Thanks for the five dollars.
Feel better.
Thanks for the laughs.
Yeah, I'll be all right.
I just, I had a headache last night
and woke up with a migraine.
And I knew that this was going to happen tonight.
So I kind of was preparing for this to be a thing.
But for sure.
Yeah.
Also, I missed from earlier.
Never Trust a Purple gave 50 dollars.
Thank you for the 50 bucks.
There was a huge amount of big donations
that came in about 20 minutes ago.
But Never Trust a Purple gave 50 bucks.
Thank you so much, Purple.
Been here for longer than I can remember, man.
You've always had such a positive impact on my life
and so many others.
Eight years of laughs and positivity.
Keep it on, keep it on.
I'm gonna try.
There's lots of stuff that I still want to do
and I'm still trying to keep myself interested.
So we'll see at 10 years.
That's gonna be so weird.
10 straight years is coming up.
I mean, it's gonna take like two years to do it,
but still never thought I would be doing
something like this for that long.
So thank you guys.
Thanks for watching.
But thank you, Purple, for the 50 bucks.
Thank you, Snooze and Cofter, for the 250.
Wonderful second movie night.
Love the talent and creativity this community offers.
Even though it's a bunch of bad jokes sometimes.
I always think about all the things
I want to write in a bit message,
but I end up not saying or asking any of the things
I thought about.
Anyway, do you plan on playing viewer levels
in Mario Maker?
Because I made some.
Yes, I will actually do a proper Mario Maker stream.
I just wanted to give some time
a couple hours before the movie night.
So we will do one.
It'll be proper.
Hopefully he didn't burn out
by playing the expert levels.
No, no, I was just,
I was just tilting myself.
So don't worry.
We will return to Mario Maker 2.
Let's go, actually, let's think about,
let's think about next week here.
So Tuesday, I probably, you know what?
Tuesday is probably a good day to do it
because Wednesday and Thursday
I want to do Dark Souls Randomizer.
At least on Wednesday.
So Tuesday will be Mario Maker 2.
Actual online levels, viewer levels.
Wednesday will be Dark Souls Randomizer.
Thursday, depending on how much fun
I'm having in either one of those things,
we might return to Cook, Serve, Delicious,
or that item shop game.
That's kind of the plan
for Tuesday, Wednesday, and Thursday.
We'll see.
That item shop game.
Yeah, I don't, I can't say it.
It's like recetteer or something.
We'll see.
Thank you Cripple Crusader for the $5.
It's been eight years.
The time really flies when you're having fun.
You've helped me in more ways than you know.
Thanks for the years of content.
Thanks for the five bucks.
That is how you say it.
Oh, that's good.
I got it right.
Yeah, time does fly.
As I get older,
the clock seems to be in times two speed.
But I'm having a great time.
So cherish, I cherish every moment here.
Great Canadian Frick Club gave $100.
It was a ton of money dropped tonight.
100 bucks from Great Canadian Frick Club.
I did a big laugh tonight.
Thanks, Jerma.
Well, thank all the people that made the great videos that you watched.
Thanks to all of you.
Thank you for the 100 bucks.
DeusMorte, thanks for the $250.
I don't know who leaked this video,
but I'm looking forward to the Carnival stream.
Who leaked this video?
Leaked what?
Well, I mean, we kind of have to watch this.
It's going to be fucking crazy.
That much I can at least promise you is it's going to be wild.
Prepare yourself for that stream.
But thank you DeusMorte for the $250.
Chat's going to be impossible.
No, there's a lot.
There's a lot of stuff we can do.
But thank you DeusMorte.
Feroidian weapon, thanks for the 10 bucks, Feroidian.
Can't really think of anything I haven't said already.
Jerma Hart, love all that you do
and glad you could get some laughs tonight.
I got a lot of them.
At least 10 to 20 of those videos, at least,
had me absolutely rolling.
So it was great.
Thank you Feroidian weapon for the 10 bucks.
I also want to get the subs rolling here.
This is going to be crazy.
Watch this, ready?
Here are all the subs and resubs tonight.
Here it goes.
It's going to be 200 or so people, 300.
Much love to y'all.
Try reading the names for old times sake.
16824810765.
Nope, not going to happen.
What name is that?
But thank you to Razlik Corgan for the five dollars.
Thank you for the amazing eight years
of wonderful videos and stream.
Hope for many more to come.
Much love.
Thank you Razlik for your five dollars.
And the really nice, nice words.
Look at that image, what image.
That's scary.
That is a creepy face.
Jerma Grin.
That is a shit-eating grin.
Maybe we'll add it to the list.
Hey Tingy, thanks for the 250.
Streams like these are so much fun.
There are so many talented people in chat.
It's incredible.
Cheers to you, chat.
Cheers to chat.
Cheers to everybody.
Cheers to the viewers.
Cheers to you.
That's right, you, for making this possible.
Never Trust a Purple.
15 more dollars.
Thank you, Purple.
Three years here with you, man.
Three years.
You've changed my life more than I could ever describe.
I'll be here for 30.
Never stop.
Best content creator on the internet in modern history.
That's incredibly flattering that you think that
you've been around for a long time, Purple.
So thank you.
Let's keep going, right?
Let's keep trying new things.
A couple more.
Here we have Nickname Jack for the 250.
Amazing encore.
Thanks for the laughs tonight.
So many talents in chat.
Love you all.
Thank you, Nickname Jack.
Really appreciate it.
Thank you Sir Black Mage for the 250.
Jermbo, EU pleb here.
It's 4 a.m. in Austria and I'm falling asleep at my desk.
But it was worth staying up for this hysterical stream.
Also been watching you since 2004 or something.
That's a long fucking time.
Back in 20... 2004.
I don't think you noticed.
Well, however long...
That's a long time.
Back in 1985.
But hopefully you didn't have to stay up too late for this.
Sir Black Mage, thanks for the 250.
Glad you enjoyed it.
And thanks for watching for so damn long.
That's a long time.
Thank you.
And then at the very end here, Nico Cat gave 10 bucks right at the very end.
Hey Jerma, always enjoyed your stream.
You're one of the best most genuine streamers on the site.
Gotta ask though.
Did you ever think you'd play Cave Story on stream?
Interestingly enough.
First of all, thank you.
And secondly, I did.
Anyone remember the old YouTube streams from 2012?
2013?
I streamed Cave Story a few times.
Those old YouTube streams from 2004.
You did YouTube streams?
Yeah, I did YouTube streams.
But this is before YouTube gaming.
This is years before that.
YouTube...
Yeah, I streamed like Diablo 3 and a few other things.
10 million.
I remember those streams.
I remember my power going up.
I remember the lightning struck a mile away from my house and turned off like my entire
street's power.
I remember I didn't watch the TF2 streams because I was like gross live.
Well, streaming wasn't really that popular back then either.
Didn't really catch on until somewhere in 2013?
2012?
But that's my time.
I'll see you guys on Tuesday.
We will do some fun stuff.
Have a wonderful rest of your weekend.
Hope you enjoyed the encore.
Thank you again to all the incredibly talented fucking people that made great shit.
And thanks for sticking around and watching it.
I'll see you guys on Tuesday.
Good evening.
Why is my stuff broken?
Nova, we got talent.
What's Nova doing?
All right, Nova's playing Mario Maker 2.
Go see.
I want you guys to prepare for my stream for Mario Maker 2.
It's been a long time since we've said hello to James.
Like more than a few months.
And he's playing Mario Maker 2 so it's pretty relevant right now.
Go say hello.
What's our battle cry?
Um sup.
Say sup.
And I want you to pay attention to how good Nova is at this game
because you need to be ready to watch me.
He ain't going to get a world record on a speedrun.
Here we go.
Are we ready?
I'll see you guys on Tuesday.
Take care.
Much love to you.