I'm sure you've tested it.
Oh, you're the first thing they heard, was you loudly yelling.
Yeah, hi guys. We're not currently live yet. I mean, well, Ster is.
That was just weird. The moment you start watching me play PUE on your stream,
you're gonna drop down to like 1k viewers concurrent for the rest of your life.
Just funnel everybody to you and they never come back.
No, they're just gone forever from both of us.
Oh, they just they just disappear.
Yeah, they like see what's on the screen and go, why was I watching this guy?
So maybe like later, I can follow both channels.
Yeah, and we can just go to Dying Light.
All right, fine. All right. Well, you show me later.
Yeah, we're gonna play Dying Light 2.
Or what would have been a more funnier title, Coffee Cheetos Chicken Remastered.
I didn't want to put that in the title though, because I don't want to.
The Zombie Jackasses 2.
Yeah. You know what's really funny about Coffee Cheetos Chicken?
That video's not even live.
That's an unlisted fucking video, yeah.
That is on your channel, it was a secret hidden video that you had.
I don't know how everybody found it and it became what it is.
It was a secret video. Did you eventually public it?
No, I did. I made a joke that I would and I never did.
Oh, that's funny.
I mean, it's unlisted, never made public.
It's about 200,000 views, which is like.
Which I mean, which is that's crazy for it being unlisted,
but in the grand scheme of things, how many people reference that exact video?
That's not very much.
Yeah, I would have thought it would have been more with how much it gets brought up.
All right, let's get in the game.
Do I just invite you?
Well, I'm not online yet. Are you online in Steam?
Are you like hiding like celebrities?
You know, I'm constantly offline, but I think I can invite you.
Let's see. Let's see, can I?
There's like a system where I can.
Uh, when you press escape, it's like F4 for friends menu.
Yeah, online link to the Epic Games store.
I'm not doing that.
OK, if I'm so I'm online right now, can I like, how do we like join a party?
Find games? No, wait, sort.
Is it can I sort by like friend or something?
I don't think so.
Yeah, we're early. We're a little early.
Well, stirs been streaming for like an hour, but this stream is like 10 minutes early
because we're making sure we can get in the game.
That's what makes sense.
Let's pretend we're not here.
We're not here. The streams are offline right now.
Because I mean, I can open up friends, but I can't.
If I see your name here, I can't like do anything about it.
I mean, I just open up your profile.
My name is gas.
Oh, well, I'm adding you to favorites.
No, it has you.
Oh, I guess I have you.
Yeah, I don't know.
I don't get it.
Yeah, I have no idea.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm sending you an invite.
Oh, how'd you do that?
I held down S to call for support.
And now wait, is your game private or is your game public?
I don't know.
Oh, you don't know your game is public.
You get this game is public.
We got to get out of here now.
I'm dropping out.
We're going to get we're going to get it.
Okay. Okay.
No, I changed. I changed it to private.
Okay.
Okay. I'm putting down the my mark in front of the boss.
You have to do the tutorial first.
We we've done that.
We're ready to go.
We just wanted to figure out how the multiplayer work.
It's not even two o'clock.
We're fine.
I sent you an invite.
Okay.
Accepted an invite.
Hey, I have a question.
I actually have like I'm deeply curious.
Hold on.
Because I got to show the actual stream.
I was already doing the wall.
Yeah.
All right.
Anyways, I got this.
Can you can you like talk a little bit to like make sure I get the audio levels?
Okay, I think I think it's good.
All right.
So what was your question?
Um, so whenever like you're like, oh, hey, like stern drummer are going to do a stream.
They come into my offline chat and they'll type exclamation point sus.
So I'm curious.
Like I, you know, me and you, we're going to know.
We know where that joke comes from.
But do people think now that that's like an Among Us reference?
Yeah.
Oh, yeah, they do.
Okay.
That's sad.
That's very disappointing.
All right.
That that is an Among Us reference.
Well, we took to the old viewers.
No, they know nothing of Annalander.
I mean, that's a great game.
Have you ever played that game like on stream?
Uh, I think I played through the first two.
You really should.
I mean, you're going to hate it, but you're going to like probably love it at the same time.
You're going to love certain aspects of that game, but you're going to like,
I just told you I played the first two and you're telling me like I've never you're all you're going
to know.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
There's a difference.
The first two are good.
The second, the third and the fourth are are very all over the place.
The fourth one is I would consider the worst of the of the four that you're going to hate it.
They're the worst.
You're going to hate it.
You're going to come to me and be like, why don't you tell me to play that?
Here's all the things wrong with it.
You're going to give me like a list of shit that's wrong with that game.
Are you ready for Dying Light 2?
I'm in the game.
All right.
So the story so far, we just jumped in.
We had to get the thing, the marker for our arm.
And does anybody really care?
Or do you just want us to go walk around and like, and hit each other with like,
I skipped every single possible cut.
I okay.
I kind of know what's going on.
Yeah.
So you meet this guy and you're running with him and he's like, yeah,
back before the place hit and you do all that stuff.
Wrong game.
Like, let's go.
You're like, you are the vaccine man because someone has to be a vaccine guy
or like experimental zombie.
And that's us.
And now we, uh, now we're going to do like parkour on zombies.
All right.
So we need to meet.
We need to meet the people of the, uh, of the Bazaar.
Yeah.
I talked to you first.
Anybody just talk to anybody.
I got, I got stuck on this quest.
You got stuck on this?
Yeah.
Did you not do this?
No, I once I was able to do, um, multiplayer.
I just left.
Okay.
Well, I came to a safe zone because I thought we'd have to be in a safe zone for me to invite
you.
And then it asked me to meet the people and I walked around and tried to talk to everyone
for like 15 minutes.
Okay.
Should I buy this?
I don't have any money.
Sell all valuables for $700.
Should I do that?
All right.
Well, I'm going to how to trade.
Okay.
You have to do the two quests.
All right.
So who do I talk to?
This is so loud for me.
I'm sorry, guys.
I know everybody like gets, everybody hates how quiet my like game audio is, but I have
to drop it because it's too loud for me.
All right.
So where are we going?
I think, I think we're going to do like a side quest or something.
Meet the people of the bizarre.
There's not, nobody here.
We have to talk to individually.
I talked to them.
I got a few side quests.
We can just like, let's just leave and like, you know, find our own way in this vast open
world.
I don't think we, dude, we can't leave until we talk to the right people.
One of the only way out.
Meet people in the bizarre.
What we can just leave.
The only way out is talk to us.
Oh, that's the quest name.
All right.
Let's go.
Funny stuff.
I can't, I can't hit you.
Yeah.
Because we're in like a safe zone.
You can't use weapons here.
So all right.
This is the front door.
We got something.
It's a main story.
Oh yeah.
That's the whole plot.
All you need to know is we're looking for a girlfriend.
We're looking.
Okay.
So we, we met that person.
Now let's go meet somebody else over here.
Let me, I'll tell you something.
You correct me from wrong history.
Is this game like in this game is very well optimized for me.
Like it runs at like a lightning fast, a hundred frames a second, no matter what.
Lightning fast.
Like I played Watch Dogs Legion and, and it was one of the worst experiences of my entire life.
If I alt tab, I can't click any of my other windows.
Is my experience like OBS.
I can't minimize or adjust in any way.
Yeah.
But the game looks great though.
Who paid you?
We got to go down.
Nobody.
Oh, we have to go in here.
All right.
So it does.
Oh, that's great.
Like I remember that first part when you're looking at the,
like all the trees and shit.
It was, it was blown away.
Game would be trash after all the delays and all those bad press it got.
Yeah.
I'm, I'm not going to say shit.
We usually talk shit about games.
That's what we do.
That's like our thing.
We have our little podcast that we do here once in a while.
And you're about to bet.
Okay.
But I'm about to get mad.
How the fuck do we just progress this?
I can like choose.
You have to do something.
Am I just like a guy that's here?
Like as your sidekick, like where I don't have like a quest marker.
Do you?
I think I can change our current question.
Well, so we have to meet in the bizarre.
Peacekeepers closed off the passage to the city center to get there.
Con and I had to find a way around the patrols.
Meet the people of the bizarre.
They're in front of us.
All right.
Hi.
How do we leave?
Yeah.
Okay.
Well, okay.
Cheers.
Let's go.
New quest.
What?
Cheers.
Find Marco the water supplier.
Oh, nice.
I want somebody to calm down.
All right.
I'm coming down.
You're looking for water chips.
All right.
Are we ready?
So, oh, now I got my bad.
Cool.
Don't even.
Oh, come on, man.
Don't it.
You're going to swing it.
You can hit me.
Friendly fire.
It's not.
It doesn't exist.
All right.
Where are we going?
You can't hit anybody.
Yeah.
I broke my weapon on him.
What is this?
Wait, he's not zombies.
Well, that was just a guy.
You got to clear them out.
It's just a person going through the trash.
Who does that?
You're all just going through the trash.
I don't think we're supposed to be doing this.
I'm from Austin.
That's what we do here.
What?
We got to go get the water chips.
Where is it?
Do you not have the objective markers?
Oh, I do.
Yeah, I do.
Why are you hurting innocent people?
What happened?
Wait, are these?
Can we talk to these people?
Oh, trying to talk after the opponent.
Wait, what's going on?
These are zombies here.
No, not that guy.
That's a normal guy.
It's a guy.
We are not supposed to be.
All right.
Don't stop hitting innocent people.
That guy ran away and said, who did that?
All right.
Let's focus here.
We need to focus on focus.
Turn off the health bars.
Hold on.
Hold up.
Don't don't don't.
I'm going to get this unkindled.
I love how they added metal gear solid neck breaks to the zombies.
Watch out.
Watch out guy.
Come right in.
Honestly, they're like so like you feel bad.
You hold on.
You feel bad for the zombies that you're killing,
but not for like the regular innocent people
that you hit that were in the trash can.
They can defend themselves.
These zombies cannot.
All right, so we have to get.
Okay, let's go.
Okay, let's focus.
Focus.
Mark number one.
Follow me, runner.
All right, fine.
Let's go.
If you guys don't know, Dying Light 2 has some parkouring in it.
It's all about staying on the rooftop, staying away from danger.
I'm trying to find your way above a roof to roof.
You don't want to alert the horde.
That's a big problem in this game.
Got to be very careful.
It's actually pretty fluid experience so far.
Jumping from place to place.
But we're going to give it the real review here.
I'm not going to be like those other reviewers.
We're not going to be like those other people that you watch.
We're not going to go into real, real super detail.
Yeah, we're going to do some detailed talking about this game and what it means.
Yeah, why is this weapon broken?
My game is not suddenly when we're fighting things.
Wait, you can jump on.
Oh, wait, wait.
I remember this in the tutorial.
Ready?
That didn't do anything.
I can do it.
You can do a drop kick.
Watch this.
Watch it.
What?
Is that you?
Oh, shit.
I thought that was you.
What's going on?
Why are we killing normal people?
I don't know.
Yeah, you're right.
In combat, my frames are dropping a little bit.
Not very much, though.
I heal up.
Can you guys play games normally, please?
What did we do abnormal so far?
We just killed a few people.
Wait, lockpicks.
Are you good at these?
I'm usually not that great at this.
How can you be bad at it?
You did it.
You're good.
You gotta have confidence.
I thought this said coffee sneakers,
and I was about to do it.
Do you get something in there, too?
Yeah, coffee sneakers.
You actually get this?
Yeah, yeah.
Do we share loot?
Okay.
Yeah.
All right, cool.
So.
Yeah.
Can you make the X?
That does not look like it would be safe at all.
It's one single spring mattress.
If you put a Tempur-Pedic down here,
it would still break all your bones.
This is bullshit.
You can't even break down.
I mean, I can, but not anymore.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
I seriously, why are you choking outside?
Wait, how did you flip it on me?
He started choking you.
He's like, get out of here.
I'll do that to you.
Probably didn't mash out.
Okay, dude, can you land on the bed of that truck?
Okay, I guess maybe.
Land on the bed of the truck.
Why?
Oh my God, that guy's coming up there.
That guy's so better than you.
They have bow and arrows.
They're throwing daggers or something.
They're ignoring the zombie.
Oh, what the fuck was that?
I got you.
It kind of worked.
I just got the guy's head off.
Make sure you're looking for, hit your gamer sense
because you need to craft stuff in this game.
It's a bit of a looter crafter.
It's kind of like Breath of the Wild.
Wait, he's fighting the zombie.
Oh, don't watch your stamina bar.
Why is the game so juicy?
It is really juicy, isn't it?
It's very like chunky.
A little bit creamy, a little bit.
Okay, so we keep going.
This is 200.
How far away is this?
Don't aggro the horde.
I'm not.
It's really creamy.
I'm turning it down again.
Our attacks.
Oh, that's right.
You have to dodge.
You hold the direction in space.
You'll do a Dark Souls dodge.
Yeah, I think you should.
We actually probably need to be looking for stuff
because look, I mean, like you go up in trash cans
and take scrap and stuff.
Why are we rushing through?
We've been waiting for this game for like seven years.
Have we?
You and I, we've talked about like, man,
that fucking dying light tunnel troll
and coffee and Cheetos and stuff.
We've been waiting for this shit.
All right, well, let's take some time role play
and make sure we really engross ourselves
into the environment.
Remember the guy?
Oh, I got to get home.
I got to get home.
My mom's going to kill me.
Remember the guy outside that was running away?
He was like the big zombie guy
and he ran into the fence.
Remember?
All right, we need to craft those.
You actually don't remember.
That was like one of the funniest things
in any of the videos we ever made.
It was like this special super infected guy
and it was light out.
Oh, that fell into the fence.
He ran into the fence and died.
Just say it already.
No, I'm not just going to say it
because we're in the game's sequel.
We have to actually find the thing for me to say it.
Everybody's waiting.
We got to go save that guy over there.
That guy's looking like he's in a little bit of danger.
Which one?
Oh, yeah.
This guy's a zombie.
I feel like all these bandits are just getting along.
Oh shit, I'm going to die.
Yeah, we got to craft this.
This game looks like New Vegas.
Am I crouching?
What are you even doing?
Like everybody's just swinging melee weapons
at each other outside.
Yeah, it just feels like Mordhau.
All we need is to press like the E mode button and go.
And then get vote kicked out of the server.
Where are you?
I'm right here hitting the guy in the Mordhau.
Okay, so let's go.
Hey, let's go up.
We got to stay on the rooftop.
Let's kind of get a little bit of parkour.
Oh, you're right.
Hold on.
You're right.
We do have to stay on the rooftops.
Shit's too loud.
I know people are going to be mad at me for this,
but whatever.
It's too loud for me.
Is there actually somebody up there?
Wait, I thought there were zombies.
I thought there was.
I didn't wait.
What?
I thought they were actually zombies.
I thought they were like monsters.
All right, we got to get out of here.
We got to leave.
We have to leave.
We have to get out of here.
That guy just walked off.
I didn't do that.
Where'd shit go?
Is he going to follow?
When do we get guns?
This is fun.
What is this?
We got to defeat that.
That guy's getting fucked up.
Get him.
Oh, go, go.
I just broke my leg.
He's running.
Why is he running?
I don't understand.
He just beat that guy up.
He's a thief.
Murder him.
You cut his head off.
Bandit caught.
Bandit decapitated.
What?
What do they have on him?
A little bit of street justice.
Oh, my God.
He had some...
You have collected a new collectible.
Every weapon I have is broken.
Are we not...
Okay.
Are we not supposed to be...
I have like a cane.
I don't think we're supposed to be
just whacking people with these.
I think we need them.
Need them for what?
I don't...
I mean, do you have any other weapons?
I don't.
I've got...
I think I got two.
I mean, we're still doing it.
I have like tiny Tim's cane.
You're like beating up a random zombie.
There's a guy in a ski mask waiting for me.
All right.
We need to...
I'm leaving.
I'm running away.
We're going to the quest marker
because we're going to break all of our weapons.
Okay, okay.
We got to go on the rooftops, Sharma.
This is a little bit of a parkour game.
Oh, that's right.
That's right.
It's parkour kind of experience.
I know the route.
Come on, pow down.
Did you make an arcane reference?
It's what's hip.
You got to stay relevant.
I only know that because I saw the first two episodes.
And you didn't watch the rest?
I mean, I probably will eventually.
I always watch like one episode of TV
and then never watch it again.
This game is so crunchy.
Why would he die?
Okay. League of Legends Andy.
I'm not the one that made the reference.
He did.
Oh, you're talking about a lot.
All right.
But look, before we go any further.
I need to make it really clear.
You're running.
I'm right here.
When a game has really beautiful trees,
that's usually an indicator
that it's going to run at like 15 frames a second.
Is that wrong or not?
I guess that's a fair assessment.
Every time I've ever played a game
where it was like, look at how detailed our environment is.
We have these big lush trees
with all kinds of particle effects.
It runs at like 12 frames a second.
And you have to turn all that shit down
and get it to even run.
This came out of the box running at like 60 for me.
We have to give credit where it's due.
I have to.
Okay.
And look at this.
This is beautiful.
You got a 30-90, 30-90 moment.
Yeah, the glowing sea.
You don't want to go through there.
Ster, what do you have for a graphics card?
280 Ti.
And you're running at pretty much like 60, right?
I have issues.
Generally speaking, I've got some issues.
In general?
Nothing to do with the game.
The game, I mean, we've got to give credit
where credit's due, apparently.
I am dead serious.
I am so sick and fucking goddamn tired
of games coming out that are AAA games
that are, whoa, look at how beautiful.
And they run like shit and they crash
and they don't even work.
This is like unheard of to me.
When was the last time you played a game
that came out in current year?
Watch Dogs Legion.
Okay, then yeah, what you're saying is valid.
Any major AAA game I played in the last two, three years
always kind of ran like dog shit, always.
This game could suck.
I don't know.
We have no idea.
Oh, wait, what's this?
We're going in the wrong direction.
I got to turn you up a little bit.
We're going the wrong direction?
Yeah, we got to go this way.
Watch out, there's heads.
Okay, so there's special gear.
All right, so we got, oh, climb up stuff.
What about Resident Evil 8?
Yeah, Resident Evil 8 was all right, too.
But was that like 70 FOV?
I ran out of, I need help.
Help, you need help me?
Why do I have no stamina?
I have to take your inhibitor.
Do I actually have to do that?
Oh, no, I got it.
I think we're going to get in the building.
Okay, very cool.
Up top, maybe?
Watch out, they're climbing.
We got climbers.
There's a book over there.
Dad here.
He's running.
He doesn't want anything to do with this.
What?
Nobody can do that.
He was so scared.
That's kind of crunchy.
This game's really creepy.
I feel like when we're interacting with NPCs,
I feel like we're seeing two different things happening.
That guy walked off the pole for me.
Yeah, he teleported to the pole for me and then fell off.
Oh, he ran across and then fell.
Watch out, we're inside the quest area.
He's just a five percent.
We have five minutes to do this, by the way,
so actually don't mess around.
Wait, what?
Why?
I don't know, it's timed.
Okay, we start picking up stuff.
We're going to be so underleveled by the time
we get to like the end game in the next few hours.
We're not getting past like level two at this rate.
Oh, wait, there's more stuff in here.
Do you see the secret like mine shaft?
I have like a mine shaft over here.
Let's go.
This is one of the hollows.
Be careful down here.
We slide?
I'm losing stamina.
How do you slide?
Is this going to hurt?
Oh, shit, be careful.
There's a dude.
Wait, quest?
All players required.
We're doing a heist.
All right, just let him talk for a second
until we even know what he's doing here.
Great.
Another just what I need between thieves and infected.
I'll be out of business soon.
All right, we're good.
I'm here.
You just do it.
It's your you're the host.
My god.
Okay.
Secure the building.
Find Hans the hunter before he drinks the poisoned water.
Wait, we have to stop somebody from drinking water.
Okay.
That's quite the quest.
You know what?
Wait, as a streamer, I'm morally opposed to this.
You need to stay hydrated.
Okay, so where are they?
You know what's funny about games like this, though?
Okay, so take a look at your perspective.
Like come over here.
This is a hiding spot, right?
Yeah.
I'm hiding right now.
This is the equivalent of like a three year old.
Where'd you go?
Oh, I see.
That's funny.
Okay.
Okay, ready?
I'm going to go do the thing.
I'm going to go into the corner here
and I'm going to count to 10
and you be the three year old
and find the best hiding spot in the room.
Okay?
Okay.
And we're going to do that routine.
All right, you ready?
Okay, here we go.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Here I come.
And you got to start like this.
Okay, it's always the okay.
Wonder where they are.
Where did he go?
Not under there.
Oh, I don't know.
I have no idea where they are.
Did they fit in here?
Oh, no way.
Okay.
I found you.
And then you have to go.
Okay.
And then we have to do it again.
Here we go.
Ready?
Why do we have to do it again?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Here I come.
Okay.
No, you're supposed to be in the same spot.
The exact same spot.
You did it wrong.
I didn't know that was a joke.
No, that's dangerous.
Get out of there.
That's dangerous.
That's in the drywall.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Come out, come out, come out, come out.
Oh, my God.
This is bad.
Mom, mom, mom.
Tim went in the drywall.
I don't know where the fuck they went.
Mom, I'm serious.
Zombies.
Help.
We got to go find them.
All right, let's go.
Help, I'm lost.
No, don't run in here.
Why does that door not work?
It doesn't work.
That's a that's a bait door.
All right, do the thing.
What thing?
Okay, if you stagger them.
You can't do it with the zombies.
You can't carry a zombie.
Yes, again.
I just did it.
Okay, I did it.
It's a lot harder.
It's just chivalry.
I'm not going to be able to get over that
the whole time we're playing, by the way.
It's just chivalry.
Watch out.
We got Zs.
No, we can open this.
Well, that we got to leave.
That's like leaving now.
I think that's giving up.
Are you sure?
You got to grab my call.
I'm collecting things.
I found a Molotov.
Oh, my God.
There's a lot of stuff here.
You're right.
I found a common bottle.
A brick.
My opportunity.
Wait, what?
Use of friendly fire.
This game got a full letter grade lowered.
How do I use the brick?
I'm a child.
You can craft options.
Lock it in friendly fire off.
Hey, go turn friendly fire off.
How are we going to do?
How are we going to do any like funny jokes?
It's done.
Was this it?
I think we just have to.
I think that was securing the building.
What we just did.
Parts for Carlos and his groundbreaking fence.
Hope he's still waiting at the bazaar.
Oh, I had the bottle in my hand.
Hayden.
How's it been, kid?
We're good.
The taste for city life.
I've been here and there.
You know, the best part is always happening in the center.
And that's where we're going.
I think we just leave.
Yeah, because we secured the building.
I'll tell you everything on the spot.
Meet me on the roof near the main metro station.
There's a time limit.
Yeah, we only have three more minutes to leave the building.
No help.
Oh, shit.
Don't skip this.
I feel like something interesting is going to happen.
I thought we were leaving.
Oh, OK.
You're safe.
Now, what's the story with the water?
Yeah.
Who did we stop from drinking?
I don't know him.
OK.
My head just hurt from that.
I thought that that was something wrong with the game.
Got to be a fucking criminal.
Or pretty damn fucked up to drag your ass
a hundreds of miles through a world of violence.
I feel like you're pressing right arrow key on a YouTube video.
Fucked up in a good way, of course.
So what about the water?
There ain't nothing wrong with my water.
The man at the bazaar was poisoned.
You'll be blamed if he dies.
All right.
Dammit.
OK.
It was an accident.
OK?
An accident.
It's because of these goddamn thieves.
Right.
They're always stealing my water.
Where is he?
I can't take it anymore.
So hold on.
I decided to set the trap.
Hold on.
Dude, you do.
I'll tell him the truth.
I won't.
Wait, is he mad at us?
Yeah.
Wait.
What happened?
We missed really important context.
Dude, even if your stamina goes to zero, don't stop.
Don't stop left clicking.
Double team him.
With zero stamina, it doesn't matter.
Don't fucking stop left clicking.
I have no weapon.
So punch him.
I'm swinging at him.
But now his head comes off.
He had flour on him.
I knew he was up to something.
We killed this guy for a bag of flour.
He's baking cookies with poisoned water.
Didn't even use milk.
This is going to be a fun game.
OK.
So I mean, do we own this place now?
The world is ours for the taking.
15% off.
Oh, never mind.
I was like, what is this?
Catch.
You threw that from your ankle.
You underhanded that to me.
Night has fallen and your immunity will go down.
Oh, that's right.
We have to go into the light.
We have to be careful.
Otherwise, we turn.
We can leave the room now.
I think.
Well, yeah.
Can we wait for night to...
Do we sleep?
Maybe we should sleep.
Yeah.
Is there a bed down here?
Or should we go up to...
Yeah.
Oh, that's really important.
Yes, we're infected.
And we are slowly turning throughout the course of the game.
That was something you missed in the first, like, 10 minute cutscene.
Sorry about that.
I feel like if there was a bed, there would be one down there.
You have to craft the...
You guys are making things up.
They make...
Wait, what are they saying?
What is...
I got hurt, but...
It's all imaginary.
Yeah, there's nothing up here.
There's no bed?
I thought there was a bed.
Usually there's like the...
Yeah, it's right here, right?
No?
I mean, we can leave, but we have to be really careful.
OK.
I mean, let's go.
I swear to God there was a bed here.
You don't want to be on the ground.
I mean it.
During nighttime, you actually don't want to be on the ground.
That was in the tutorial.
What did I get?
I got something.
He's not in the same room, though.
So I can't do it.
What are you doing?
I went back downstairs to go through the door.
Why did I just get sucked over here?
Oh, because I sucked you.
I'm in control.
We're not supposed to be on the floor.
This is my game.
Let's go on the floor.
We're not supposed to be on the floor.
Climb.
You gotta climb.
Right on the street side.
That's very impressive.
Watch out, we got Zeds.
Wait, somebody's yelling.
Yeah, the zombies.
No, no, no.
There's a guy in that building.
Somebody right there.
66 meters away.
Let's do it.
Isn't it kind of rude to look in someone else's windows?
This is like an office building.
Yeah, it's still kind of weird.
Right here.
Do you see him?
You need binoculars, though.
What is it?
Where?
Somebody's hurt on that roof.
Oh, he's hurt.
He's hurt.
Let's go help him.
Over here.
I'm going the other way.
Oh, there's a special infected over here.
No, don't go that way.
Go this way.
Watch out.
We got biters.
Oh, my God.
It moves.
Careful, careful, careful.
All right.
What are we going to do?
Immunity booster.
Or a shroom booster.
Or a shroom.
I think I have shrooms.
Do you have shrooms?
Oh, nice.
Do we get a point for that?
You idiot.
We already got the experience.
Okay, I'm going to put a point.
Okay, I got a parkour.
What are you going to put your parkour point in?
I'm going to put my parkour point into.
I like firm grip.
Actually, no, I'm getting a firm grip first.
Well, I don't have a point.
You don't?
No, I didn't get one.
I probably ran through too much of the tutorial.
Oh, easy.
Easy with that.
I'm just holding on to it for, you know, we get some zeds following us.
Okay.
Some zombies, some biters, some walkers, some crawlers.
I think we're going to turn in like three minutes.
What are we going to do?
I don't know.
We have to find a safe house.
Oh, this way.
Yeah, number one.
We have to go to number one.
Okay, let's go number one.
Oh, my God.
I fucked it up.
I'm fine.
Are you trying to throw that at me?
I couldn't jump with it.
Oh, now I got a parkour skill point.
Now I'm a firm gripper.
I just I don't want to.
I really don't want to like alarm you or anything,
but we really only have, I think, three minutes before we die.
Wait, question mark.
Somebody screaming down there.
Downstairs, we're going to go.
Ow.
Where'd you go?
I went down.
The other side of the building.
It's down.
Whatever it is, it's down like in the building.
Your immunity is low.
Use shrooms.
Oh, shit.
Oh, yeah.
We get over there room.
How do you shroom?
Mine's on my heel button.
How do we get in there?
We can see there's UV light in that direction.
We can go there is we can't get in there.
All right.
We have to actually get back up top.
We're going to get killed as a screamer.
Don't.
Oh, my God.
You're going to get us killed.
Don't alert the screamer.
I've been such a bitch.
It's tough.
I don't know where to go from here.
What did you do?
I jumped on the air conditioner.
OK.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Gas can.
Let's go.
180 meters.
Immunity is low.
What is shrooms on like the mini bar?
Mine is H.
I have no healing.
Oh, shit.
There's an inhibitor container nearby.
We're critical right now.
We're absolutely critical.
Up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
Why can't I grab this?
This is bad.
It changed my marker.
We have to go.
We have 49 seconds to touch this UV thing over here.
This way.
Follow me.
Oh, my God.
You're falling behind, kid.
Hey, I'm dead.
Did you make it?
Yeah.
Can you come help me?
I'm going to have lunch with these guys.
I'm dead.
What happens?
Are you actually dead?
Yeah.
I'm going to respawn.
I could.
It gives me the option to teleport you to me still.
Oh, can you do that?
Wait, actually, don't do that.
You're here.
I'm here.
Oh, OK.
Cool.
I don't know how to switch to my healing item.
It's still on shrooms for me.
All right.
We should probably make some weapons.
UV bar.
Oh, that's kind of cool.
Two.
Ah, hold two.
So I don't have any money.
Hold two.
Grade, scissors, craft parts.
All right.
I should.
Weapon mods, goods, fire arrows.
I wonder weapon mod grip.
Come back and I'll top you off real good.
I don't know what I should sell.
What's going on here?
Hello.
I'm Henkel.
This student here was curious about my lesson today.
It's a noisy chair.
Not when the guns were confiscated in villages.
You hear all that?
He wants.
Yeah, I'm in a cut scene.
Are you?
Yeah.
Oh, well.
No one touch it.
Henkel's got a problem.
History lesson, side quest.
Hold T to track.
I'm tracking it.
We're doing it.
He's important.
Reach the memorial.
Oh, hey.
OK, dude, it's two.
Yeah, hold two.
It's two to cycle through things on your minimap.
Yeah, really?
Are you serious?
Well, you already knew that?
This isn't a bit.
Accessories.
Make sure you have lock picks and stuff, man.
I mean, I'm geared.
I'm in the UV light.
OK, inventory.
Decoy, Molotov, throwing knives.
All right.
I have UV shrooms now.
Can you craft UV shrooms?
Oh, no.
OK.
How do you cycle through?
There we go.
I got my Molotovs.
Three, I'm assuming is.
How do you cycle weapon?
One, two, three, four.
You just completely tuned him out like it was your job.
It's still nighttime, though.
We have to go sleep.
I think I don't care.
Like, I'm a challenge.
Like, I want to move in stealth.
You know what I'm saying?
Like, the moon's out.
We can still see.
You remember in dying light?
Actually, it was so dark you couldn't see like more than a foot.
Let's pull your binoculars and start marking shit.
OK, there we go.
Discover the old lumber mill.
You definitely cannot see through those.
Those are way too wide for your head.
What do we got up here?
Look for things to mark.
I have them all already.
I always went out there.
Yep.
See?
All right.
So I think we just have to choose which way we're going to go.
Well, no, I'm doing the Reach the Memorial Squared mission
that this guy just gave us.
OK.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Let's move.
You're all crafted up.
All right.
You think you can make this jump powder?
I did, but for some reason I felt...
Excuse me?
That's classic power.
No, no, no.
But like, honestly, excuse me.
What happened?
Why did I die?
What happened to me?
I got you.
It's fine.
You're not fast like the others.
There's a zombie right behind you.
Why did I delay my death?
That was weird.
What the...
Weird's going on.
I'm telling you.
I tried to climb up and I couldn't.
OK, are we climbing back up?
Let's climb back up.
Yeah.
I can't stand on this guy.
Come on.
OK, from here we can go this way.
Yep.
Are we going to...
We got a little hovel here.
I wonder what's inside.
Do you want to explore it?
Yeah.
I'm looking to explore it.
Let's go.
It looks like we're both having the same problem
of how do you just go down.
The whole tutorial, I was like, what button lets go?
Use your gamma resets.
This is one of those pre-war buildings
with four floors and no rooms.
Nothing down here.
Run to the ground floor again.
Oh, wait.
I can open this.
Oh, yeah.
We get guns in the police car.
All right.
I got your back.
A couple of heads coming.
Watch my back.
Oh, dude.
ASUS Republic of Gamers.
What?
There's a hallow over here.
Up here.
Why did my...
OK.
Why did my stamina just drop to zero?
What did I do wrong?
What happened?
My stamina bar was at like 60 percent
and it just went to zero.
Lion power.
Stop saying that.
Why?
Because I watched the show.
If you saw two episodes, it's all you need to know.
So from here, where do you want to...
This way?
Half of our UV, our life is gone.
I know.
We're not supposed to be doing what we're doing.
OK.
We're supposed to have been sleeping.
This is where we started.
What?
No, it is not.
No, it's not.
What?
No way.
This is impossible.
It's impossible.
How is it impossible?
They don't have a bed.
Where can we...
How do we skip time?
I can't believe it.
I can't believe it, man.
I really can't.
How did we do that?
OK.
We need to find...
I'm taking the reins.
All right.
You're my leader.
What do I do?
Mark on your map the bed over here.
The bed over here.
The green bed that's over here in the middle.
If you hit...
Go to your map.
Mark this.
The green bed.
No, we're going to do the history lesson.
Shut up.
I'm going.
I'm taking the reins.
We're not...
I'm telling you.
The game has told us over and over again not to play the game when it's nighttime.
I'm taking the reins right now.
Can you keep up?
I think so.
I'll look at this.
We actually can open this, can we?
No.
What?
Bait quest box.
You see down there?
Do you see the marker?
That's where we're going.
Don't play this game at 3 a.m.
No, don't.
That's not something we can mark.
There's a lot of zombies down there.
Oh, what's the plan?
Electrical station.
All right, the plan is we're going to go...
Well, we have to go that way.
So should we jump on the X?
Yeah.
All right, you go first.
All right.
I'm going to show you how a pro does it.
I went way too far.
I'm fine.
That's a howler.
We got to go.
We do actually have to go.
Come on, powder.
You got this.
You're going to keep doing that.
We got UV light and everything.
There's a howler now.
And there's a howler.
Take out your sniper rifle.
Take the shot.
All right.
How do I throw a device?
You got to find something to throw.
I'm pretty sure.
I mean, OK.
Anybody screaming?
Oh, shit.
We got Zeds.
Somebody actually just screamed.
Help me, Marina.
Did you ever play Mission Makers for N64?
What?
Mission Makers?
No, I have not.
It's very good.
All right.
So this person is...
They're on the roof.
Oh, you're here.
OK.
You're trying to help the person.
I mean, we might as well do missions and shit.
There's two howlers down here, dude.
Just walk by them.
Get up here, Omar.
X.
Press X.
How do you blow that up?
Oh, shit.
Go.
You had to press X.
Oh, no.
I'm going to die again, dude.
I'm not kidding.
Survivor has turned.
Did you turn?
No.
Did I?
That must be you.
It's not me.
Oh, the person we were trying to save, maybe?
Oh, OK.
Come on, powder.
Silko's goons are coming.
Stop saying that.
Stay on mission.
Down here, we got a question mark.
No, I didn't want to grab this brick building.
Come on.
To the UV light up here.
Oh.
Zed's on me.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
Oh, no.
Go to the light.
I'm at the monument.
At the light?
You were right.
Breathe it in, quick.
OK.
There is much more to it.
You're getting burned.
They can't take the heat.
And they shouldn't stand in the fire.
Nice.
OK, we got it.
Objective updated.
Investigate the square.
Use your game revision.
So yeah, we have to investigate this area here?
All players required to investigate this plaque.
That's kind of going to get annoying.
What did that say?
Something detected?
There's a plaque here.
A lot of names on it.
People died.
Yeah.
Don't say this game sucks, bro.
No, it doesn't.
I'm really enjoying it.
It actually is pretty good.
I think the multiplayer connection is a little weird,
but that's not.
It looks OK for me.
Are you having lag issues?
It desyncs and it looks a little weird,
but it's just making it more fun, to be honest.
OK, so now investigate the square.
Is there more stuff we have to press?
Yeah, use your game revision.
OK, the thing right next to it.
This is one of those locked containers somewhere over here.
Yeah, we both need to investigate the same thing.
Yeah.
Come.
OK.
Wait, didn't we do that?
No, we didn't.
Apparently not this one.
Hold F and then press F and then press F again.
What happened here?
What happened in the last 10 years of PC games
where they changed E to F?
Have you noticed that?
They changed E to F and they made you have to hold it.
What happened there?
I'm going to blame Sean Murray and No Man's Sky
and all of his lies.
Shots were fired.
The army started shooting at people.
Is that person supposed to be in this cutscene?
We're killing him.
They are?
Light the candle.
Embrace the light, young man.
I don't think this person is supposed to be in the cutscene.
I think they just accidentally got through the barrier.
All players required.
Man, imagine playing with like 16 people.
Made a bad call.
Taking people's guns.
This is actual flop.
This is not a flop.
Why are you guys saying flop?
OK, so now we got to go back to where we're going now.
What's this forsaken store in front of us?
You see that?
Yeah, I do.
With the beep beep beep the box detected, box detected.
Are you getting that over here?
No, I'm not getting a box detected.
It's like container detected.
There's one of those G, what is it?
The inhibitors?
Yeah, we can use our key on something here.
When you're close to one of those locked chests, it goes like this.
Yeah, it goes box detected.
I don't know.
I don't see anything.
I don't know where it is.
You have to use your gamer sense.
I'm gamer sensing as hard as I can.
I mean, maybe it's in the forsaken store.
It might be like if you want to go to the forsaken store.
That's right.
Bottom left icon.
Oh, shit.
OK, it tells you how close you are.
Oh, it does.
Oh, we're playing hot and cold.
Yeah, so when we walk, we walk towards the storage.
Actually, probably stealth this part.
There's one behind you.
I opened up a trunk.
You're going to attack me?
Yeah.
Didn't work.
Go back to the light.
Embrace the light.
We're going to get a redo.
Fine.
I got a decoy.
I don't know how to throw it.
How do you get a weapon?
What?
When did I have this?
I've had this the whole time.
It's always G.
It's not G.
All right.
We have to open this crate.
There's one guy here.
We don't have to worry about this.
I'm getting park work.
You're standing still?
Middle mouse.
OK, hold on.
Hold on.
I'm going to throw the thing.
You ready?
Wait, hold on.
I have a skill point.
I just stood there.
I survived the night.
Air kick.
Yeah, I'm getting an air kick.
I'm a bit of an air kicker.
We're killing them.
You missed.
Yeah, I don't want to break my weapon.
It's daytime.
See, we survived the night.
We're good.
Would you get extra EXP?
Yeah.
Cool.
OK, so let's go find the thing.
Find the thing.
What is that?
It's my noisemaker.
Find the thing.
All right.
Go, go, go, go, go.
It's this way.
Container nearby.
Nine meters away.
There's so many people here.
They're not people anymore.
Where is it?
It's down that way.
It's got to be in one of these cars or something.
Get on top of this.
Yeah, it's over here.
A little bit further this way.
And then jump onto the sign.
And then we go that way.
Where are you looking for?
I'm going to die.
You're going to die?
What happened?
What are you doing?
I'm killing Zed.
What is happening?
Remember me.
What is going on over there?
Why do you have an infinite supply of these things?
What?
Watch out.
Somebody on the roof.
Somebody got sick of you.
It's like, who's the fuck throwing all those?
This is just...
We're making a skate video.
This is what a skate video would be like in this period here.
Are you just filming me?
All right, it's over here.
Oh, shit.
Oh, you get that, bro?
You get that on camera?
I did.
I'm uploading that to ZeeTube.
ZedTube.
All right, it's definitely...
I don't know where it is, but we keep getting closer.
Fuck you.
Where is it?
15, 13, 12, 10 meters.
I found some shrooms up here.
10, 9, 7, 6, 5, 4, 3.
It's like on top of me somewhere right here.
Help me.
Where's your bombs?
It's like, where is it?
It's right there somewhere.
It's got to be in the car.
Oh, it's in the subway station.
Okay, we're going under.
Let's go.
Make sure you press...
You turn on your flashlight.
Stealth, take down.
I choked him out.
We got to pick this stuff up.
I need to make some more heals.
Oh, it's right here.
Yep, nice.
So what's in it?
Anything good?
The defibrillator.
Why is that guy burning to death in the subway?
Oh, nice.
We need these things.
This thing actually...
We have to collect these.
Yeah, that's when your max stamina increases.
Hey, hold on.
Let me heal you.
We're taking a lot of damage out there.
Gas can.
Actually, we should actually...
Let me craft a little bit here.
This game is fun.
I need honey.
I can give you some honey.
Stop.
Regenerates a substantial part of your immunity.
Cool.
Huh?
What are you doing?
When you crouch and look down and move left and right,
your arms are just like...
I don't know.
I'm really coming...
You're holding a weapon, so it's probably not doing it.
Oh.
I think you press the X to put it away.
Did you turn your FOV up?
Yeah.
All right, let's get out of here.
I don't want to throw up.
Wait, we got Zeds.
Are you going to say that every time?
We should scavenge down here.
Yeah, that's true.
That's a lot of stuff.
All right.
Let's just clear out these Zeds.
I'm going to say that every time we see a new room of zombies.
I think.
We got fighters.
That is like the E3 party audio of all these single-player games, by the way.
Watch out, walkers.
We got Zeds.
Fighters incoming.
I just love how in every zombie show,
they have to call them something different
and they can't do what someone else has already done,
so they can't just be zombies.
They can't be walkers.
They have to be like...
I don't know.
You hear some weird ones.
How do you throw?
How do I throw Malte?
You have to have one on the middle mouse button.
Got it.
I love the smell of human flesh.
I thought they weren't humans anymore.
Huh?
They aren't.
They just have our flesh.
Get off my buddy.
What the fuck?
Why are they...
What did you just do?
That's not what fire extinguishers do.
They don't light on fire.
What happened?
I hit a fire extinguisher
and flames were coming out of it and it blew up.
It's contents under pressure, dude.
But there was literal flames.
Here.
Let me heal you up.
What is making this like...
It's kind of annoying me.
I don't know.
This guy's still alive?
Help me kill this guy.
No, I'm scavenging.
We got some alcohol.
We're going to party.
There's three more.
Oh, God.
You keep him busy.
Oh, never mind.
I thought it was a bomb.
Where are these people coming from?
I think they're using the...
Bro, let's...
That reaction...
What you getting?
We got to go.
That reaction was like,
I'm about to crash.
I'm about to crash my car.
Like, oh my God.
Bro.
We've scavenged pretty much everything
we can scavenge from down here.
I haven't.
I'm on low health.
Are you?
No, don't crush the mushrooms.
What am I doing?
These guys have honey on them?
Oh, that beeping that you're saying is so annoying
is your immunity being critical.
I mean, I just took a mushroom.
Because we're in the dark.
Oh, well, I just heard it.
I got to...
We got to go.
We actually do have to go,
but we need to actually be careful
because we're low on health and shit.
I need some honey.
Oh, I do have IV heal.
How critical is your health?
Very low.
I mean, I keep healing you
and I don't have any left.
Well, let me return the favor here.
Okay.
Thank you.
You're low on health.
Stop doing that.
Why is it doing that noise every five seconds?
Okay, where are we going?
I'm going...
Where are we going?
Okay, where are we?
Wait, hold on.
We need to go to the mission marker
and find a place to sleep.
It's daytime.
Why would we need to sleep?
Because we're tired.
I'm not tired.
I can keep going.
All right.
So where's our marker currently?
We don't have a quest.
We have one that we can do.
We have meet Hakann.
Oh, that's the guy.
Where is that?
That's over here.
We can go to that.
Okay, let's go.
We've already met him.
Well, we have to do more missions with him.
It's like GTA.
I'm bored of him.
Oh, we got enforcers.
Is that a bad thing or a good thing?
Ah, they've got spears.
Hey, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Come back here behind this bush, Gashkhan.
Okay.
What's the plan here?
We need their weapons.
I think we do need their weapons.
Okay.
You get behind one, I get behind one.
Let's see where they're situated here.
We've got this one facing us and then we've got one.
Okay, we've got two not facing us.
I don't think we actually can.
It's not letting me.
Yes, we can.
No, I meant like the actual instant kill takedown.
This guy's full of fucking knives.
He has so many knives coming out of his head.
Oh my god, I'm going to die.
Good luck.
He's almost dead.
Kill the guy on the ledge.
Don't push him off because now we can't loot him.
He fell.
Well, we can go down there.
I'm going down to loot him.
Kill the guys up here that are trying to attack me.
They're not trying to attack me.
Can I make anything?
Oh, easy.
Get some?
Get, get some is what he said.
He had shoes on him.
He didn't have a weapon on him.
He only had shoes.
And this guy's trying to dodge my attack so much that he's.
What the fuck?
Loot that guy too, please.
He didn't die.
Dude, what the fuck?
Stop dodging.
This is this guy's.
I need healing.
Oh my fucking god.
Okay.
Well, this is my character doing.
You push this one off too.
I was trying to throw knives at him and he killed himself.
Does he see if he has anything on him?
Oh, he does have this holy shit.
He's got a spear.
Oh my goodness.
It's a throwing spear, an opportunity weapon.
Where is that?
I didn't get one.
Oh, come up here.
There's a throwing spear on this guy.
He's not using it anymore.
Oh shit.
This is awesome.
Okay.
Where are you?
I got to heal first.
Come up here.
I also I've really I have no healing.
We have to find honey and stuff.
Keep your spear out because we need to use it.
I crafted it.
I dropped it.
There's another spear up here.
I have one already.
I think you can only hold one.
Yeah.
All right.
Let's go.
Well, hold on.
Hold on.
You see that guy down there?
Three.
Wait, hold on.
Yep.
Two.
One.
Action.
That was pretty sick.
I'm not going to lie.
That was really cool.
Let's go steal stuff.
He's definitely dead.
It was just like he was trying to cover up the graffiti.
Is that what he really was doing?
Hey, oh, medicine.
You had two heels on him.
Yeah, we don't need to find honey.
We just need to kill enforcers.
I don't have that in my inventory.
I can heal you.
You come over here.
Oh, no, you're good.
Yeah, no, I'm good.
Let's keep going here.
Get their attention.
You didn't throw it far enough, I don't think.
All right.
Okay.
Yeah, that was that.
That barely hurt this guy.
Probably a special effect of the explosion.
I mean, like they're all they're all feeling pretty okay.
Spears probably do so much damage.
Is there a way to charge up a swing?
I probably learn later.
Yeah, I don't think we can yet.
I think we got to do like the main quest.
I know we keep getting too distracted.
We really do.
Oh, there's no spear here.
What's the guy doing?
All right, let's go, please.
Okay.
This is like the starting area we were in.
I mean, this game reminds me of a video game.
Yeah, we're going to go speak to Hakan.
Hey, on that point.
Wait.
Oh, I think we have combat points.
I have one.
I don't.
Perfect dodge.
You have the XP bonus.
Oh, I like that.
I'm going to do air kick.
Are you serious?
Are you looking at?
Hold on.
Crouch.
You hear these guys talking?
Kind of.
Where are they?
They're just saying the same thing over and over again for me.
Got a hammer?
Let's get closer.
We got two.
Yeah, you can open there.
Don't why would you kick it open?
Taking so long.
Wait, somebody's about to blow a horn.
What's with the horn?
I don't.
I don't know what you're talking about.
What's taking so long?
It was just a horn indicator on the screen.
Like they were going to go.
Well, they were going to rally the troops.
I mean, these are like tough guys.
This guy's wearing camo.
Lots of stuff over in the corner.
You can craft a new item.
Ooh, what is it?
You can't craft a new item.
We got a question mark over here.
You can't craft any new items.
Lying game.
Want to go to this question mark?
Yeah, I'm just getting the loot, man.
We got a blue over here.
All right, what's this?
Is it a random?
Let's go to this blue.
I kind of like how they just add a random
stranger quest like GTA.
It's another bandit.
We got to chase this guy.
It hurts so much.
Oh, it's just a bandit.
It is just a bandit quest.
Why can't I pick it up?
I feel like I just got out with my life.
That was like my life flash before my eyes.
Oh, holy shit.
We got to get Spider-Man.
I can't climb that fast.
I'm going to cut him off.
He fell.
What?
I fell.
I got him, I got him, I got him, I got him.
Oh, shit.
I didn't get him.
I'm out of stamina.
He's still going.
Did I get him?
I got him.
Okay, I'm coming.
Oh, no.
I alerted the horde.
My hand.
I didn't loot him yet.
I don't have any weapons.
Do I have a weapon?
I got him, I got him.
Wait, I need to stop to loot it.
One, two, three, four cycles your weapons.
Inventory, you can equip weapons.
You probably keep picking them up and not realize them.
Okay.
Oh, germa powder.
Come up here.
Mm-hmm.
There are people every 10 feet.
Why?
These people have like a birdhouse?
Why are these guys wearing ski masks?
I don't...
They were both up here wearing ski masks tending to their beehives.
Oh, wait, because they don't want to get stung in the face.
That makes sense.
That doesn't make sense.
All right, we can actually craft them.
Oh, yeah.
We got chamomile and honey.
That's what they're doing.
They're healing up.
Okay.
You see this?
There's a police car down there.
A couple of zeds on it.
No, I didn't want to take the inhaler.
Oh, my God.
I probably needed to use that at some point.
Important.
Let me put this stuff on my bar.
Okay.
I have two weapons.
I want to get in this police car.
There's so much shit up here, though.
Look at all this stuff.
There's so much stuff.
There's like shrooms.
There's beehives.
These guys had a little thing going on up here, huh?
Yeah.
All right.
They really figured this whole thing out.
I think there's gas in here.
They had an axe and a birdhouse.
How was the axe?
You know, it's a raggedy.
It's a ragged chopper.
You know what I'm talking about.
That's not bad.
Did we get in a police car?
19 damage.
Okay.
Let's try the police car.
I'll distract them and you open it.
Where's the police car?
Right in front of us in the middle of the road.
I see.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm going to distract them.
How come I couldn't kick that guy?
I tried to do my kick.
I'm lowering him away.
Get in there.
I can do it.
I'm keeping him off you.
It's a lockpick.
I can't open it.
I have to do the lockpick.
I can't.
We have to kill these guys.
Okay.
I got you.
That what?
What?
That was it?
That was the sound?
Dude, watch my back.
They're all fighting me.
You have one person over there attacking you.
I've watched my freaking back.
Keep him off me.
I can do that.
You handle the car.
I'll do my work.
I'm out of stamina.
I almost got it.
There's a snake in here.
Get it.
All right.
We're in the clear.
Leather.
I don't know if we're being gate kept.
We can't find guns and cop cars.
Hey, what's this place?
We're getting distracted every five seconds.
Yeah, it's the terminal.
The main terminal.
My god.
Okay.
Are we about to do the first story mission of the game?
Oh, you went to Hakann?
He's the other way.
Let's go.
Dude, we've been going the wrong direction.
No, we're fine.
We got a little distracted.
We got a whole bunch of honey.
We got a whole bunch of heals.
We're equipped.
We know how the game works.
It's like that's all smooth sailing from here.
No more distractions.
We're running.
It's parkour.
Here to Sunday.
I hear people talk and ignore them.
But they're funny NPCs we can go kill.
Somebody's blowing their horn.
See?
ADHD should be illegal.
Okay.
I discovered the dark hollows.
There's a tank down there.
A tank?
Yeah.
We can really use that thing.
Maybe we can get like...
Wait, is that an Omega Zed?
It looks like an Omega Zed.
Is that Big Bertha?
There's explosives down there.
What should we do?
This is just like that one scene in that one show.
Like the tyrant is down there.
I got a Molotov.
Should we just throw it over there and see what happens?
You completely missed.
You're supposed to be the gamer.
I didn't know how far they throw.
Here we go.
All right.
Is it going to blow up the...
Oh, the propane tank is still not blown up.
Yikes.
There's ghosts.
There are ghosts.
Chain reaction.
Oh, whoa, dude.
Nice.
Wait.
That guy's flying.
There goes another one.
Another one.
I'm not sure if we heard them or not.
Okay, so...
They're climbing.
All right, they're climbing.
I'm frozen.
What do we do?
All right, let's go back.
I don't think we can do that right now.
I think we can.
I think you're giving up.
It's a tyrant down there.
We don't have a...
We don't have a gun or anything.
There's more explosives.
All right, go for it.
Ready?
Oh, my God.
One, two...
Wait, I'm not ready.
I'm not...
All right, I'm waiting.
When do you think you'll be ready?
I'm just curious.
Okay, I'm going.
I'm going.
All right, going.
Power attacks cannot be blocked.
All right, what was it?
What was here?
Something in the tank.
Holy shit.
Okay, what is it?
Open it up.
Dude, there's something we can do with the tank.
The back of the tank.
They're all coming for me.
See if you can get it.
I'm hurting.
What?
The back of the tank?
I don't see anything.
At the back of the tank,
there's like a lever you can pull.
All right, actually, you distract him.
Are you talking about the spear?
There's a lever here.
God damn it.
At the back of the tank,
right at the very back,
at the bottom of the tank,
there's like a lever.
I'm going to die.
You all right?
All right, just run away.
Run away.
Let's get out.
I keep pressing E to use
and I keep kicking things.
Just rebind it.
Can I craft like a bomb or something?
I'm going to craft some knives.
Just leave them.
I want to.
I mean, we already did.
We committed to this bullshit.
There's nobody here.
Are you kidding me?
I think I can get it.
Oh my God.
I'm going to get it.
What is it?
Rations.
All right, the hard lock.
Oh, no, don't do it.
Hard lock.
All right, help me.
Just protect me.
Where did the Tyrant go?
I don't know.
How do I throw this?
Ignite it?
I can't ignite it.
Why not?
You have to hold X.
All right, watch out.
I think we can just clear it.
Just clear it out.
Yeah, I'm clearing.
The Tyrant left.
Yeah, he was.
That's good for us.
All right.
I think there's one of these two left, right?
Are we breathing in chemicals somewhere?
Oh, this one's a lock as well.
All right, this is perfect.
Loot everything.
Don't read this comment, Jerma.
What?
You...
Oh, man.
This is actually cool.
I'm breaking all my lockpicks.
Somebody said press C when you land to break your fall.
I can't.
I can't do this.
Oh, shit.
How many?
I think I have one.
I have one left.
Okay, where would you see the most non-resistance?
I didn't see anything.
Did you do the ambulance?
Yeah.
Holy shit.
What the hell?
Yeah, we're just like not good enough to do very hard yet.
I'm not getting anything.
Oh, my God.
I got it.
Holy shit.
What a gamer.
It was all the way to the right.
Dust filter, solid shoes, and rations.
A bolted bludgeon.
28 damage.
Yeah, I feel like we're being gate kept from guns.
You don't find it in like the armored carrier.
Like, come on, man.
Didn't you say there was another thing to open?
This one here, too?
All right.
Let me see if I can get this.
I am...
Trust me when I say this.
I'm the lockpick guy from now on.
I trust you.
Please play Sam and Max VR.
Well, I put VR in the box and it's in the closet now,
so it's not going to happen.
I do own the game, though.
So eventually you'll see it.
Okay, can we like get in here?
There's a random person over there.
Hey, can we make it to this main quest right up here?
Meet Hakan?
Yeah, let's...
Okay, that's enough.
We've been playing for an hour and a half,
and I know we're having a lot of fun.
This is actually a really good time,
but we gotta...
We can't just not do the whole game.
We're having a good time,
but we need to like put it to an end right now
and like talk to this main quest guy.
Yep.
Hakan, you're a better climber than one crazy girl I used to know.
She was something.
Have you ever played Castlevania Symphony?
I climbed the tallest building.
Nope.
Right.
I feel like I lived it, you know?
I just like you playing the game is kind of boring.
There's an ad that might be...
Did you play Vampire Survivors?
That's a stir game.
I think we talked about it.
Yeah, that's a stir game.
I kept reading on the Reddit
that it's like a ripoff of Magical Survivors.
So on the plane trip out here,
I was like, oh, I'm gonna like download Magical Survivors
and like see what the one it was based on
and support the original.
And shit's not on iOS.
Is it actually?
It's like Android only.
I wonder why that one didn't take off.
All right, tunnels.
Dude, the tunnel troll.
Here we go.
Oh, wait, we're tunnel trolling?
Get to the station through the metro.
Wait, is there like...
Hold on.
Make sure that we can...
I don't want to just leave here
without something we can do or crafts of items.
Well, that's the objective.
Okay, so I'm just making sure.
Wait, which one is the objective?
Oh, down here, 20 meters down.
All right, it's nighttime, by the way.
So this is where it gets a little hairy.
Where did you get this two-hander?
It was in the military truck.
I got the good loot.
Oh, what?
We have to pick this lock.
Yeah, so clear the zeds, dude.
You're the one with the big two-hander.
I'm hitting them.
That was actually pretty cool.
Why did I just do the thing from God of War?
I threw...
I just recalled Mediolnir.
Hey, you're the lockpick guy.
Let's go.
That's me.
Zeds are coming.
Something exploded.
Don't know why.
That's me.
First try, Andy.
Bandits.
I think we should just leave.
I want these guys dead
for ever even considering fighting.
He had Siggy's name.
All right, let's go before we get killed.
My God.
I grabbed...
How do...
Help!
I don't know how to do it.
I'm honest.
Running out of stamina works.
Oh, shit!
Okay, I grabbed it.
I'm fine.
Ooh, pills.
Aspirin.
Pills here.
Cigarettes.
Hey, where are the rifles?
Where are the shotguns?
My chat is telling me
there are no guns in the future.
There are no guns in the game?
Good.
They said there's like two.
Like these gamers
have to fucking actually play the game.
They kind of spoiled it.
You know, I would have talked about it
for like six more hours, but...
Oh, we want guns.
Now the gamers actually have to fucking
play the game
and not just like shoot stuff.
Yeah.
Oh, shit!
Gary?
It was a fucking cockroach.
This is not how you would crawl through this.
You are deliberately
putting your ass in my face.
Deliberately.
I'm a spider.
Let me go in front of you
just so you can see.
This is not how somebody crawls through a vent.
I've been waiting years for you to say that.
Look at this.
Okay.
You wouldn't even fit doing that.
Wait, watch out.
Watch out, Zeds.
You get the one on the left.
All right.
You have to give one community sub
every time you say that from now on.
Say what?
Oh, Zeds, look out.
Oh, shit!
I owe a hundred community subs to my chat.
I hope I can do it.
You didn't do the one on the left.
My credit card got declined
like five times last time.
I hope I can do it this time.
Okay, I need a weapon.
Do you have any extras?
I do.
I don't know if I can drop them.
Oh, I can.
Oh, I got to take shrooms.
I dropped a slicer for you.
That didn't do anything.
My immunity is still low.
It adds like a minute.
It doesn't add like a full timer.
Okay, let's go.
We got to hurry.
It only adds like 30 seconds.
Okay, we got to speed run this.
The Zeds are coming.
That's one.
I'm in the tunnel.
Now watch out for the infected.
There might be a few or a few dozen.
You really are playing chivalry at this point now.
It looks like you're play fighting,
but you don't actually want to swing that.
You're just watching.
Do I give you my weapon so you can watch?
All right, take some more mushrooms.
We actually do have to go your right and run.
There's mushrooms right here.
Oh, sick.
Watch out, infected.
Don't alert them.
You can just crawl through.
Can you do the tutorial, man?
Oh, watch out.
Wait, oh, sick, sick.
What happened to don't alert the Zeds?
They were going to see me.
It was fate.
Oh, you said it.
Now you owe me 100 gifts for the community.
All right, this is lockpick door.
Lockpick guy.
Can you please do it?
I got you.
If you're actually going to protect me, I will.
I'm in.
Okay, shut the door.
Oh, there's a container in here somewhere.
They just punched me through the door.
48 meters somewhere.
That's definitely in here somewhere.
Cool.
Our immunity is getting even lower.
We're close, though.
It's fine.
Okay, that's like a dog tunnel at one of those dog shows.
What's the point of this?
You just went through the obstacle.
That's an air duct for the air to travel through this.
You see?
Yeah, but why?
Why did you?
What's the point of having it here?
The air is not going to circulate unless you make this tube.
48.
All right, let's get to this metro station.
We lost it.
We lost the center.
I don't know what we're doing here.
We had a beep beep and we lost the scent.
Oh, there was a beep beep back there.
It was.
Do you want to go back?
We only have two minutes.
It's too late.
There's a whole bunch of shrooms down here.
Like every 10 steps, there's a shroom.
You want to go back?
No, I want to do the main quest objective.
Okay, fine.
I don't want to get distracted.
All right.
What was that?
That's the sound I make when I swing my two-hander.
I'm going to play chivalry.
There are shrooms everywhere.
You're right.
All right, let's hide from this guy.
Does he know?
What?
How does he know?
Oh, your head was sticking out.
We got to run.
Okay, just run forward.
Oh, he had vodka and decoys.
Decoys on that guy.
Let's go.
And cigarettes and yep.
Yeah, I could.
I got to the flare.
Look around the technical tunnel to the main station.
Stand here.
Well, finally a new whip.
I'll chat them up.
Will you get inside?
Ooh, what is the immunity?
And it's drinking.
You put a mask on.
I think I'm sitting in the light.
No, you put a mask on your character.
Did you?
Yeah.
Oh, cool.
That's really cool.
Yeah, I really like that.
Here, you're the door guy.
I mean, I'm a walk-pick guy, not the door guy.
Oh, can you hold the door for me?
Watch out.
We got a spitter.
Oh, my God.
This guy spitting fucking squad out of his nose.
Oh, it's coming out of his hat.
What do I do?
Okay, skip, skip, skip.
Run forward and hit it with a hammer.
Okay.
Well, it's a medium walk-pick.
I got it.
Hakon.
I'm telling you, I'm going to first try every single one of these.
It's open.
Kill that guy?
Yeah.
Killing him took less time than the phone call.
Did he have anything on him?
Trophy?
He had a special zombie-infected trophy.
He was like, congratulations on killing one of my rare species.
Here is an award.
No power.
Watch out.
Yeah, you're going to want to stay behind me for this.
Are you doing like a, I'm like a gremlin routine.
That's like the, I'm going to go down and I'm going to act like a gremlin
to make people laugh at the party.
How often do you play gremlin?
I don't know.
Have I ever seen somebody do the thing that I just referenced?
I don't think so.
I don't think I've seen that.
I don't think gremlin is a game a lot of kids play.
Why am I, why am I imagining a fake scenario where like somebody's drunk at a party and
they go on all fours and are like, I'm the gremlin and like I'm running around.
Yeah.
I feel like that's probably happened.
I mean, anything that can happen has happened.
And then they like jump into the pool.
You know what I mean?
Like, it's me, gremlin guy.
And then they jump in the pool.
I think you're thinking of your Sims playthrough again.
Oh, we're getting some golden coins.
So these kind of like hitman, you just throw them to distract people.
I guess.
Are you sure this is something you did yourself?
Hitman VR.
Should I play?
No.
Really?
I thought you would have been like, oh God, yes.
Yeah, it's okay.
Let me, let me explain hitman VR to you.
So IO interactive, phenomenal company.
Like seriously, like what, what a great, they,
what a story, right?
Oh, the IO verse.
They bought back their rights to their game.
They made fucking incredible hitman games.
One, two, and three, absolute like masterpieces of games.
It was so much fun.
They decided to make a PS VR version of hitman.
Oh, it was only PS VR?
It was PS VR exclusive.
And when, what they did is like a year later,
because you had to play with the controller in your hand with the VR headset on.
A year later, they decided to port the PS VR version
to like all the other headsets.
And it's really weird how it controls.
We just got Westworlded.
Okay, imagine they took the controller.
They cut the controller in half and you hold the PS4 controller in two hands.
It's kind of, it's weird.
Is it worth doing?
I think it's fun and it's hilarious the shit you can do.
Here's the choice.
I still haven't played Half-Life Alex.
Do I play it?
What are you doing?
Do not even make that, that's, you want me to make the choice for you?
Yeah, or Wii Sports.
You've never played Wii Sports?
Never played Wii Sports.
So like if either Half-Life Alex, Wii Sports, or Hitman VR.
Oh, fuck the Super Bowl is today.
It is.
Oh, well.
You gonna watch?
No.
I'm hoping the Packers win.
Half-Life Alex, Wii Sports, or Hitman VR.
I'd say Wii Sports because I mean, that's a legendary classic video game.
Okay, I don't have a Wii.
The tunnel is going to be closed.
Well, then play Half-Life Alex.
I feel like I've been hyping Alex up to you for like a year straight now,
and you're going to play it and be like, that sucked.
Someone was hyping it to me, not that like a week ago as well.
Let's get.
I can't even click.
You're doing it too fast.
You shouldn't trust me.
I'm on trust where I can try.
There are people here that are probably wanting to watch this,
to even get even a sniff of what the story is.
And we have to both apologize.
I can recap it.
I don't have to apologize.
If you apologize to your chat, you give them power.
My feet off of that.
But anyways, play Half-Life Alex.
There's a couple of sequences in Half-Life Alex that were just like,
wow, this is what VR is supposed to be.
Okay, wait, are we just leaving here?
I think so.
How is it?
Okay.
Oh, it's the enforcers.
Oh, shit.
Speaking of Half-Life Alex,
if this is Half-Life 2 opening scene right now.
Well, you forgot to go.
But can't we all agree that, like,
Red Faction 1 is better than Half-Life?
Okay, I don't think you're going to be, like,
allowed to be on the internet anymore after saying that.
I want to make it really clear.
I have nothing to do with this person.
I don't really know them that well.
I don't.
I have friends who kind of,
I don't really know them that well, though.
Have you played Red Faction?
Yes.
Okay.
Well, are you going to tell me
Red Faction is not a good game?
I mean, I don't remember playing.
It was a long time ago.
Okay, well, do it again.
Better than Half-Life 1 or Half-Life 2?
Better than Half-Life 2.
Because it's basically Half-Life 1 made two years later.
Well, everybody can have opinions,
and, you know, we can respect your opinion,
but disagree with you.
I don't think anyone's respecting my opinion.
We can disagree with that opinion.
We all have opinions.
We can, you know, just settle down.
I'm driving so much chat engagement.
Okay, we can either leave or explore.
Yeah, I want to.
We got janitors.
Like, oh, we're in the metro.
Wait, are we in the metro?
Are we in the metro?
I don't think there's much we can do here.
There's a door over there,
and then there's a door that has a quest marker on it over there.
Yeah, okay.
Let's go to the quest marker.
We're going to distract it.
I'm walking.
I will say that when I got to the boat section of Half-Life 2,
I almost threw up every time I tried to play it.
Okay, but did you ever throw up during playing Red Faction?
No.
I also have to be fair to the game as well.
That's back before anyone knew what FOV even was.
Back in like 2006, 2007, like FOV,
people didn't even fucking care.
Nobody even knew what it was.
That was like a gamer enthusiast,
like only a few people really even knew or cared about.
You're kind of reminded of like the olden days
where every single video TotalBiscuit had to explain what FPS was.
No, yeah, like I mean,
it was not like common knowledge back in like 2005, 2006.
Like FOV was something that nobody really even thought really thought that much about.
Yeah, the human eye can only see like 20.
All right, where are we going?
Yeah, so there's that slider in the video menu
that it starts at 75 and goes up to 90, right?
I never touched it.
So during the boat missions, it was 75 FOV,
and I'm sitting like a foot away, two feet away from my screen.
And I'm just like, why the fuck?
I'm sick.
Oh, I remember having to lie down on my back on the floor.
I was in the middle of the boat mission,
and I seriously had to get up, hit escape,
lie down on my back and lie there for like a minute or two.
But I really wanted to experience the game
so that I got up eventually after I was not nauseous
and did it again for like another five minutes.
Felt like I was going to puke again,
lied on my back on the ground.
I had to do that for like 40 minutes to get through that boat section.
Okay, but how do you feel about the hour-long,
non-skippable in-character cutscene?
That's like, but all right.
But they like pioneered that shit.
Back, okay.
Pioneered you having to like stand still?
You have to understand something, stir.
Weren't you saying earlier that you like games that let you go fast?
Yeah, but listen.
You were saying like, oh, I'm going fast.
Back before, before that,
it used to be you had like eight Final Fantasy CDs
because there were fucking four CDs
full of FMV full motion video rendered cutscenes on them.
Like when they came up with that idea
to not have like rendered cutscenes,
that was a huge deal.
Having it in the game,
it wasn't just like a cutscene that you had to watch.
But I think just because you can doesn't mean you should.
I'm stuck on this.
Hey, can you sell all your valuables?
I actually think I'm going to sell some stuff.
Yeah, the like cutscene that is not,
you know, there's no loading screen, go to the cutscene.
There's classes in this game.
These weapons actually look pretty good.
This guy's selling joggers for a brawler class.
I think I want this axe.
Is that a bad idea?
I just sold everything.
I think selling all the valuables are all like things that don't matter.
Okay, I hope so.
Holy shit, there's grenades.
Ooh, stamina cost.
Bracers for a tank.
When do I get the wingsuit?
I'm pretty sure there is one.
They might be.
Yeah, I'm assuming they might be.
All right, we should probably get.
I know that they have like the grappling hook again.
Now, can't you upgrade and like craft your gear?
I think so, right?
I'm going to buy a few of these.
Yeah, I'm buying a grenade.
Yeah, buy a couple of grenades.
I think we can utilize them pretty well.
We got the craft master over here.
Oh, you get blueprints.
There's mines and shock arrows for my arrow.
Where do you see blue mines?
The other merchant over here.
That was truly a pleasure.
Reinforces your weapon.
Is your voice higher today?
You sound like a balloon.
What are you talking about?
I sound like a balloon?
What do you mean a balloon?
Your voice is a little higher.
Your voice is a little bit higher.
What do you mean?
Hold on.
I don't have my effects thing on, do I?
Yeah, you've actually like the whole time you've been talking.
You've actually been talking like this.
It's been really weird and I didn't want.
I thought you were doing like a new thing.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
How do I sound?
Should we both just do this and see what people say?
Just continue to stream the whole time.
A little bit higher.
And every hour that goes by, we get a little bit higher.
Just go a little bit higher.
A little bit higher.
And then when we get too high, we end the stream.
Okay, we have to have a base level though.
That's just high enough.
That's like one notch over.
Okay, so how do I sound with one notch over?
Is it kind of weird, but you can't really tell?
Are you doing it now?
I'm doing it right now.
I can't tell at all.
I think I got used to it.
What about this one?
I can't tell.
What about now?
Is it different?
Very slightly.
I think I heard there.
Okay, so how about now?
Is it too noticeable now?
Extremely noticeable.
All right.
How about now?
That sounds like something might be wrong with your mic, but like kind of normal.
All right, now you do one notch on pitch.
We both have the same product.
Are you doing gender or pitch?
I did pitch.
Okay, that's one notch gender.
Okay, I don't hear anything.
Two.
Oh, you can start to hear it.
It just sounds like something wrong with your mic.
Yeah, and then you go a little.
Yeah, this one.
Okay, this one I have to go pretty far and then it's weird.
Is that pitch or gender?
Which one?
I'm doing pitch now.
This is one notch.
Okay, yeah, this is just one notch and I can kind of hear it.
Yeah, okay.
I'm on one notch as well.
All right, let's go.
Okay.
This is so weird.
It is really weird.
Once we get to a certain point though, then we're gonna, you know, we gotta go.
I am gonna upgrade my consumable.
Yeah, you can get like shock tips for your weapon here.
You can get, you know, we can get some crafts for our,
you gotta buy those so you can upgrade your weapon.
It's not like a different recursive.
Okay.
Yeah.
All right, I think I got what I need.
I'm gonna buy a couple.
What's this?
I have a lot of heals.
I got eight heals.
I think we're good.
All right.
You went up higher.
I didn't go up higher.
Yes, you did.
You went up higher.
I just started talking a little bit different.
No, you went up higher.
You went like this.
I didn't go up higher.
This is what you just did.
What are you talking about?
You just went higher.
I was just talking different.
I didn't change the slider.
Yes, you just did.
I heard it.
What do you mean you heard it?
Do Aaron.
Aaron!
What are you talking about?
Can I get an Aaron from you?
Aaron?
No.
There you go.
All right.
Let's fucking play the game, please.
Let's play the game.
No, that's that's like chipmunk.
You know, it's not.
It's...
It's like...
Not like...
Oh, so you like you suck.
You suck.
Why you say it?
You just lost us like 3,000 viewers.
Thanks a lot.
Let's go.
Okay.
You're the one that like started this whole thing.
Thanks.
Thanks a lot.
You lost us like 3k viewers.
Thank you.
Okay.
Yeah, I'm at negative.
Wait, wait.
I wanted to ask what they...
What did they want from me?
They asked me to help them.
He might let me through to the center.
If I...
Okay, we're caught up.
Completely unwatchable stream.
Fuck you, dude.
All right.
Find the brass knuckle thief.
Find Hubert Kerbapsos.
Let's find him.
Oh, so you went the wrong way.
Pretty sure Hubert Kerbapsos...
I'm sorry that I said you sound like a balloon
and made you lose a thousand viewers.
Well, time that person off for five minutes.
How dare you do that to our stream?
I take my stream very...
Seriously?
I still haven't figured this out.
I still haven't figured out how to climb.
Oh, this guy's got a book.
I still for some reason have not figured this out.
What?
Like how to like properly like climb
without losing all your stamina.
Oh, you just climb up.
I think the more you press...
Like if you mash spacebar, it's just like...
Oh, it's just drain...
Okay.
It sucks it out of you.
Yeah.
What is this book going on here?
I don't know.
I was by the campfire.
Is this Life is Strange?
I know you're cycling through your secondary
to see if you have a grenade.
I'm not.
I'm sitting down.
I can't do anything.
That's what I was doing.
Oh, no.
I'm sitting down and just taking in the environment.
Did it do anything?
No, there's like right here.
There's actually like a sit spot.
Oh, no.
I see what's going on.
All these guys got to the boat level in Half-Life 2.
I see.
I get it.
I mean, I have a grenade.
Yeah.
Life is Strange.
Let's go.
Just kind of chill and vibe out.
So tough being a teen.
All right.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Is it...
Okay.
He almost...
I thought he was going to throw a grenade.
Yeah.
I thought he was going to throw a grenade at them.
All right.
Come on.
Let's go.
Sarah, stop.
I didn't even see it.
I didn't even look.
I didn't...
I thought that...
Okay.
I didn't even look.
I didn't even get it on camera.
Okay.
No, nothing.
Scraps.
I killed her for a box of scraps.
Oh, scraps?
Unlock faction structures and activate a safe zone.
Yeah.
I have no more grenades.
Let's just go do this.
Wait.
There's something going on here.
Bandit.
Oh, they're bandits?
That's not...
Okay.
They need to fix that.
That doesn't make any sense.
I'm sending an air support.
Like, how would that even make any sense?
I can't even climb that.
There's an explosion.
He's going to get away.
Wait, there was...
Oh, that's what you meant by bandit.
Band-aid.
Bandit.
Oh.
We got to...
Can we go to the quest?
I want to earn like a new parkour skill.
Fine.
It's up here.
It's like straight up.
Oh, my God.
It is.
How did you get on top of that?
I lined it with my arm.
Explain how microwaves work to Jerma.
Literally, who knows how they work?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I have a question for you.
Don't listen to any of these jokers.
Any of these idiots.
Listen to me.
These morons, okay?
I have to make it very clear.
We got to get a baseline here.
So, when you microwave food...
I don't own a microwave.
You don't own a microwave.
I don't.
Why do you not own a microwave?
Because Gordon Ramsey would be really disappointed in me if I did.
So you have a microwave, fine.
When you can put something in the oven,
why not put it in the oven?
It takes like two hours.
It takes like an hour.
How do we climb?
What the fuck is going on?
Oh.
The Sonic and the Hedgehog shit is going on right now.
Okay.
Well, anyways, you've used a microphone.
Yeah, I've used my microphone a little bit.
So when you use your microwave oven,
when you do that...
Yeah, I do that.
Yes.
When you...
Okay, you put it in...
Let's say you put it in like popcorn.
It doesn't matter.
Someone's sneaking up on me.
Oh, it's behind you.
Okay, let's just theoretically say
that I'm making my own popcorn in my microwave that I own.
Sure.
You put it...
And it goes for like a minute.
Yeah.
And you hear...
Right.
When it gets to zero,
and you open it,
does that like...
Would you put like putting your hand in there like right when it hits zero?
Don't you...
Isn't it like kind of weird?
Like that...
Isn't that like an odd thing?
That like there was just radiation in there.
Zero, open.
Oh, that's my popcorn.
Like isn't that kind of weird?
I've never thought about it,
but you know what?
That is kind of weird.
Like really think about that,
but just a second.
Like the fact that like they may be like residual waves in there.
Does it just go away?
I mean, I'm pretty sure if the microwave was on,
your hand could be in it for like a second before like you would even...
Microwaves are not radiation.
Yeah, but it's like radio waves.
That's not how it works.
Kids these days,
they just grow up trusting technology
because they didn't live through that.
Like all the stuff that we did.
I'm just telling you.
The radio with the announcement of the aliens.
What was that?
The war of the world.
They like they didn't have that.
They just trust stuff and we know to like
to filter through and find what's real.
All right.
Hear the news.
Because most news these days is fake, honestly.
And okay.
Is it weird that there's a concept of the...
Is the microwave a weird appliance?
I want to buy something.
The fridge is like a fridge.
It is cold in here.
An oven heats up with gas and heat, right?
A microwave like zaps with fucking microwave radio waves
your food until it's like nuclear.
It's kind of weird.
It's kind of a weird appliance.
That's why I don't own one.
And you were judging me for not having one.
We got to go all the way to the top
and then you're going to jump off.
And I'm going to laugh at it.
That's the end of the conversation.
He's running away.
Wait, who's running away?
We have one minute and 15 seconds to go this way.
So we got to go up.
Where did you go?
We're going up.
It was a timer in front of me.
It said one minute 15 on a marker all the way across the map.
Oh, there is.
What?
Wait, what?
I'm not crazy, right?
Am I crazy?
There's a red circle pointing me up here.
All players require.
What are you going to come help me?
How do you think your Wi-Fi router works?
I don't know.
That's fucking weird, too.
You know, that's weird.
We can communicate like with nothing.
No wires.
Dude just fell off.
What are you doing?
Where am I?
Why am I on the top of a construction site?
I fast traveled you.
I didn't realize I got 10 seconds to.
OK, anyways.
Yeah, we felt that.
Anyways, we got to pull back a little.
I'm not saying that there's something wrong with like radio waves.
I'm not saying that like your phone and wireless signals are weird.
I'm just saying it's kind of odd like that we have this technology,
but we can be able to do stuff without wires and cords and stuff.
He's running away.
OK, we got to go.
All right.
So how do we get down safely?
I see you.
What you're saying is you also similar to me,
this man of culture do not trust 5G.
No, I don't look.
You want to have this conversation?
Here we go.
When is it going to be enough?
How many when is it?
When is it going to be enough for you to sit on the toilet and go on Twitter?
How many G's do we need?
When is it going to be enough?
Are you saying like we already have enough G's?
Do we need like 8G?
I mean, has your phone ever disconnected before
and you were like, oh, I don't think I can go on living.
10G.
What is a G?
It's a gigabit band of wireless information.
Just said a few words that I thought sounded good.
Am I there?
He's not here.
Why do we still have 14 seconds?
Climbing up this?
We failed the mission.
No, I got here, but you climbed up this.
We got to climb this.
Hey, man.
Yeah, we got to climb up this.
How are we supposed to do that?
Fucking grab something.
You're like, oh my.
Okay.
I thought you were going to fall through.
That looks so funny.
Nice.
Good job.
Okay, we got to climb.
I'm not like anti 5G.
I'm just saying it's crazy that we have this technology.
Who gave the aliens gave it to us?
All right, I'm going to fall on.
You want to hear what I really think?
I do.
Wow, they silenced you that quick.
Like in real time.
I was going to hold that longer,
but I feel like that would hurt.
It was really loud.
Was it loud?
It was.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
It wasn't supposed to be.
Well, you know, I'm dying now.
Is this guy's name Tuber?
It's Hubert.
Oh, I just heard.
Hey, Tuber.
That's a restricted area.
Yeah, watch out.
That's it.
Will you get a glue onto something?
Oh, it's this way.
Wait, where?
Where?
When you get close.
I think it's just we just find him, right?
There's a door here.
He's right here.
You fucking.
Is this you?
Is this you Tuber?
Is this Tuber?
What are you doing, Tuber?
I don't know.
Why'd you run away then?
Is it the light has a higher frequency than microwaves?
I know I look.
I don't have a problem with microwave ovens.
I'm just saying I like they kind of scare me a little.
You know what scares me?
And people always make fun of me for but magnets.
I'm terrified of putting a magnet like anywhere near my computer.
So I don't want any magnet.
They have like metal cases for your computer.
And it's like, oh, you could put like it was like magnet for your course.
They're like magnet on your computer.
I'm like, isn't it?
You put a magnet to a TV like what happened with that?
Shit went south.
Yeah, everyone's saying fair, fair.
You're afraid of magnets.
Okay, and I and I like don't like microwaves kind of freak me out.
But like you're afraid of magnets.
But people are saying true, fair, fair.
That's true, true, true.
I don't like because, okay, we were at PAX East once.
And this guy was like, hey, promoting my game.
I think it was like Starbound or something like that.
He's like, here we got like magnets for it.
And I was like, dude, I don't want your fucking gamer magnet.
I want that anywhere near my computer.
And he was like really weirded out.
I don't want that near my computer.
Yeah, I can't believe you're getting trued.
Okay, this is you're getting true, true.
Oh, yeah, true.
Well, like I'm not afraid.
My computer is accidentally going to go in a microwave.
I think they're both valid opinions to have.
Even though you're okay.
You're not afraid of magnets.
You just don't want them near your computer or my head.
Yes.
Or your head.
Like, okay, mess with your brain waves.
If you were to take a magnet and put it and put it next to your head,
would you do that?
I have to figure out what your level of fear is.
You know what?
I don't think I would.
This sounds really weird.
Like, if it was a really strong magnet and you were just like,
you put this near your head.
Like, sometimes I sit on my phone and I'm like,
are my balls being cooked right now?
Like, I don't legitimately think they are,
but it kind of makes you think like, why take the risk?
Okay, so yeah, so you don't really like them.
You don't really, you're not like, you know, you know, you don't,
you know, they work.
You know what they do.
But you don't make fan like of having them around, right?
Yeah, I figured like, why bother with magnets?
I feel like we don't need magnets.
There are detriments to magnets.
Okay, the, the, the true people,
the people that were saying true are have you've lost them.
So I'm good at losing them.
Chad, anyone who's watching this stream right now,
take your cellular, your cellular device.
Let me make it.
Don't do anything.
He said on it.
He says, don't do anything.
He ever said.
Place it right underneath your crotch and just sit on your phone.
Don't do anything.
He ever says.
This is a big disclaimer.
This is the, I do not condone anything he tells you to do.
We need to go down.
There's a, I want to jump.
I'm not afraid of microwaves.
I just, they, they, they're a little weird.
That's it.
That's the only argument.
Oh, I, I have to get down there too, man.
How am I going to do that?
Climb.
Holy shit.
Okay, we're good.
Help me.
Why would it be R?
I really thought you'd let me die.
Okay.
Can you follow me?
Yes.
Watch out, watch out, watch out.
Just follow me.
You know, people are coming in my chat sometimes and are still mad that I,
I dragged you through Terraria too quickly.
What?
It's like an ongoing disappointment in some people's lives.
Well, because you like played Terraria while I watched.
Yeah.
I crafted like a, I crafted like a bow and arrow and you beat the game for me.
Yeah, but it was a good time.
It was a good, I had a great time.
Yeah, that was fun.
People were mad about that.
Yeah.
Like he didn't get to enjoy it himself.
I did.
No, it was great.
I played Terraria, Terraria a little bit.
Not with all the mods.
I had a great time.
That was a lot of fun.
I'm not, I'm not buying it.
Nice dude.
How does stamina work?
Did you also not, you couldn't do it?
Hey, let me know.
Tell me if you think I did or didn't buy how loud my Ernie laugh is.
Hey, I can't do this.
Okay.
We need to find another way up.
Uh, jump fence.
We're good.
You good?
Oh, we got one of the, I heard the inhibitor nearby thing.
We actually need to start doing that.
Yeah.
12 meters.
It's right, it's right this way.
You really did play Terraria.
Name the main character, Thomas Terraria.
Thank you.
There's a person up here.
Oh, there's a window down here.
We can go in.
Someone's screaming.
Someone's screaming down here.
Screaming.
Someone's in danger.
Hurry.
Loot this.
Lots of stuff to loot.
You're right.
I'm gonna gestalt it.
I hear screaming.
I don't hear any screaming.
Where do you hear screaming?
Oh, now I do.
A shithole indeed.
Did you keep going down?
I think the inhibitor might be in here somewhere.
Yeah, it's definitely in here somewhere.
I'm using gamer vision.
Where did you go?
I'm still in the house looking around.
Oh, there's a, we can climb up here.
We can go up?
Yeah, I found it.
Oh, shit.
Yep.
Okay.
Who is running around up here?
Someone had neighbors, huge footsteps.
Oh, there's a gamer up here.
Oh, gamers.
Oh, it's these two?
We're making all that noise?
Kids, I'm looking for a woman named Maya.
They were so funny.
Ain't a grown-up.
She's just a-
You were the one trying to sell a PK weapon to Hubert?
Yeah, but the jerk didn't want it.
Got all freaked out and chased me away.
Okay.
What is she holding?
Is she holding a grenade?
Yeah, it's a grenade.
What?
It's very important.
Yeah.
Do you expect me to just hand that brass Whozzy Whatzit over?
The Whozzy Whatzit's-
Oh, it's powder.
Stop it.
I can't.
I just scolded you like we were on a road trip and you're like one of my kids in the car.
And I'm sick of how like loud you're being.
Stop it.
Enough.
Okay.
So, report to Ator.
We need to get that.
I got a point.
Did you get a point?
No.
You should have.
I mean, I got to do the stamina point?
Yeah.
I don't know what to put it in.
Stamina or health?
I did stamina.
I don't know.
Stamina's probably more important.
Are you a tank or are you a bruiser?
I'm gonna do stamina.
Just feel like you really need that health.
Look at the health bar.
It's so tiny though.
Yeah, just don't get hit.
We got to go do-
Oh, you want water, by the way.
Have you had some?
Cool.
Get your ass to Ator with you.
No, I haven't had any water.
I have no idea when that prick was born.
I was dead.
I'll be near metro station.
Okay.
Will you tell them to stop sitting on their phones?
Are they doing it?
I don't know.
But you tell people to stop doing the thing you said.
Do they want to have kids?
Stop.
Tell them to stop.
Guys, come on.
Stop.
If you want to have kids, stop.
But you really shouldn't.
There's enough people in the world.
There's an airdrop over there.
Military airdrop.
We should go do that.
There might be like a gun there.
Let's do it.
We should do it.
We did two main story missions.
We're good.
Yeah, let's go.
Up on that roof across the way here.
Oh, I'm actually murdering.
I'll get these shrooms.
If you were to give this game.
Wait, wait, wait.
Why is it all green?
It's green.
Where's this coming from?
Chemicals?
Poison?
We're poisoned right now?
We got to go.
We're going to get our immunity.
The whole shroom thing.
Yep.
You were going to you're about to ask me like a thing.
Oh, right.
Okay.
You would have scored this game one out of a thousand.
What would you give it?
Are we doing like Yu-Gi-Oh numbers for scores?
Well, just imagine like it's like an experience points you can put in
and getting to one thousand points levels you up to a one out of ten.
I'm more confused now.
So so is it a score out of ten thousand?
No, I mean, like, do you want to put enough experience points in the games to be like,
yeah, I'm going to give this a rating.
There's parts of it that I feel like dying light one did better.
But overall, it's a good game.
I could give it like a nine thousand.
Okay.
An eight thousand before I, you know, we haven't even seen grappling hooks or.
So you need to take a long time to level up, honestly.
So wait a minute.
So you have eight hundred points out of a thousand into being ready to review the game.
Is that correct?
Oh, you're saying like how how leveled up is my review?
Yes.
Not the score of the review.
No, like you need a thousand experience points in the game.
Like how much do you have right now?
Eight hundred.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I would say I have like two hundred.
If we dropped it down to easy, then I would get like a journalist bonus of like five hundred.
Oh, OK.
I can feel you.
What are we doing here?
I'm just looking at the.
I'm just looking at the chat and people are just like,
I have no idea what's fucking happening.
I barely know what's happening and you're talking to me.
I know what you're saying.
The experience bar on are you ready to review this game or not?
It's like a two hundred out of a thousand right now.
And you're not going to play anything.
You are not going to play like the five hundred hours that it takes to beat this game.
Yeah.
So like, what's what's my cut off?
That's for you to decide.
Whatever you when you whenever you're like, I'm like a two hundred right now.
This area is weird.
You have to go up this way.
I think this is the Ubisoft Climb Climb upper.
And there's a bunch of stuff up there, though.
I don't see any way outside here.
Oh, my immunity.
I'm getting whipped.
Oh, this is actually really bad.
Remember, this is the kind of conversation you have to huffing fumes.
And I've been huffing.
What's wrong?
Oh, we I think we've kind of run out of time here.
Oh, I mean, I have shroomies.
It looks like from here.
Hold on.
We're trying to get to the top of this building.
What about on this side?
Is that platform right here on top of me?
How do we get to that one?
Kind of worried that maybe we don't have like
an ability for it.
Oh, wait, the metroidvania.
Yeah, I think there's a way to get up over here.
Yeah, there is.
Come to me.
Fucking Jesus.
I actually almost just shit my pants.
I'm serious.
I just almost jumped off.
I like the same thing.
That's right.
I'm not crazy.
Yeah, but like now from here, we can keep going.
Just keep going.
We fully wrapped around.
OK, we go up here.
Here we go.
Nice.
We're going up to the top all the way.
There should be a cache up here.
Not this way.
Oh, we got to do some jumpies.
Oh, great.
It'll be worth it.
Whatever's in here.
I have no more shrooms left.
We got to go.
I've got shrooms if you really need them.
I collected the artifact, the ancient artifact
left behind by predecessors.
You can hide under this table if you want.
There's a lot of them here.
I wonder if somebody chases you.
Oh, my God.
What?
Apparently, you can walk on that.
You can.
Oh, that was crazy.
I can't believe you actually made that.
All right, I'm fine.
I know you've waited.
You're turning the camera back because you know,
you're like, here goes.
You're going to fall.
I just want to make sure my little bro's making it.
Like, make sure powder is all right.
All right, here we are.
OK, right here.
Whatever this is.
Hey, are you about to turn, man?
No, I'm good.
I think I have immunity boosters.
Military airdrop, military tech.
Oh, OK.
We got military tech.
Is this an immunity booster?
You go to a craft master to upgrade your tools.
I need my tools.
OK, so that's an immunity booster.
I think I'll be here.
Yeah, all right.
So the immunity booster fills up your immunity bar completely.
OK.
The inhaler, the purple inhaler.
Where's the assassin's creed?
Jump down.
Is that the only thing that was up here?
Yeah.
Like a zipline or a...
You would think there would be something like that here,
but apparently not.
What the fuck?
I thought you just turned into Wally on my screen.
That was weird.
Yeah.
OK.
It really should be.
Here we go.
They're right here.
OK.
You ready?
You're doing?
Oh my god, you're doing it.
No, there's an assassin's creed thing right here.
OK, go for it.
Made it.
OK.
I'm critical.
Are you actually?
Do you have help?
Yeah, no, we're good.
We got to run.
Yeah, we actually do have to go.
All right, to the marker or?
To UV light or any kind of light.
Can't be out at night.
It's dangerous.
We're far away from that marker.
Oh my fuck.
This giant.
Is there fast travel?
I think there is.
Uh oh.
We got squelchers.
Make a new meme.
Oh shit, the chase started.
We started the chase.
I want to see if you have what it takes to beat me.
Top text.
The chase started.
Bottom text.
Oh no.
I'm going to offer you $50,000.
It says you can't beat me in trivia.
Trade request.
All right, Beastie, here we go.
You following me, powder?
Yeah.
Oh, you're going.
She's such a misfit.
Always ready to fight.
She's got a super beam.
And she's raising high.
If you believe you're strong.
So you know the whole song?
I don't know.
I heard like a minute of it.
Okay.
Okay, can we like not sleep or like pass time or?
We haven't really figured that out yet.
There's a couch.
You want to like chill on the couch?
I'm laughing.
Okay.
Yeah, we need to sleep.
Why?
I can't believe you did not react to me doing the the Vi theme song.
Did you just pretend I wasn't doing that?
Are those actually the words?
Kind of.
I don't know.
All I know is oh the misery.
Watch yourself.
No, you don't know.
Wow.
Fake fan.
I'm not a fan.
So we don't actually sleep here?
Yeah, either.
I feel like there must be a button to like pass the time.
I thought that would be right here.
Can you not do that on multiplayer?
I don't know.
Here.
We're going to survive the night and get the EXP bonus.
How about that?
I guess.
What's our current objective?
Oh, you can't sleep in all the safe houses.
Only some.
Report to Eeyore.
Let's go in this direction.
Oh, the church.
Well, church like right here, right?
Like Sunday mass, right?
Oh, this is a point of interest.
Yeah, push out that.
And now we can sleep here.
This is not.
No, we're going to the other area.
I don't want to sleep ever.
Okay.
This is this is why the forces of evil fear the Nephilim because they never rest.
What's your favorite Lord of the Rings movie?
Um, isn't there just one?
Just one of the Lord of the Rings movie?
Yeah, Lord of the Ring.
Mine's um, mine's return to the king.
I like the part that Peter that Peter Jackson wanted to remove.
Was my favorite part of the whole movie.
And it's the one that he said is his least favorite thing he's ever done in cinema.
That's my favorite.
I don't which scene I don't know too much about Lord of the Rings.
Honestly, the ghost people, the ghost ship people.
I don't remember a ghost ship.
Well, let me see if I can jog your memory.
What say you?
What say you the help?
No, it was a ghost ship.
Yeah, this is like a SpongeBob reference.
No, there was a bunch of scenes where they were ghosts in like this tomb.
And they had to go to the tomb and get the uh, the the legions of the ghost people.
Pirates of the Caribbean.
No, and the guy walks over and he's like, oh, you best not believe it in ghost stories.
Because you're in one.
And then they help them at that battle with the elephants and stuff.
Death will be repaid.
You don't this happened in that movie, right?
Thanks, but uh, sorry.
Uh, it was the Gondor, the ghost of Gondor.
Yeah, and they came in on a ship.
They were in the movie for like 35 seconds.
Now, I said she needs lavender for her.
I believe you.
Now, that makes more sense.
Metal scraps.
Nairo wants them Lord of the gaslighting.
Nobody even said that chase making perfume out of metal.
Sounds absurd.
I mean, I'm just trying to do quests and objectives here.
Oh, no, I'm dead.
Ow, my leg.
Hold on.
I'm going to do some.
I've got to do some crafting.
You good?
I feel like if you own old Aragorn a debt.
Yeah, and Peter Jackson said that was the worst thing he's ever done.
He's like, he's like, I wish I fucking deleted that from the whole fucking movie.
And I was like, what?
I like that scene.
Did you like it or did you like think it was funny?
No, I actually liked it.
I've I need a new topic.
I don't know what's going on right now.
I don't know what's real.
I don't know what's not real.
I owed Aragorn community subs.
I don't know why that's so funny to me.
Did you guys both take a tab of acid before playing this?
No, it's been a while since stir and I have like just played a game.
What we can't like we can't relax and have a good time.
Talk about microwaving stuff.
Can't talk about magnets.
I'm not all caught up on the microwaving and the other stuff.
Like this is new to me.
You guys probably hear it every single day, but I didn't I didn't know the microwave lore.
Oh, we were helping the guy from here doing a quest or something.
And now we're reporting back.
So we're completing the quest.
Whatever it was that we did for him.
I was to look for Eeyore.
We're just inside, right?
We're just inside.
Okay, I need all the characters.
I need all the players here.
Excuse me.
I'm here.
So you're comfortable microwaving popcorn even though it kind of scares you?
Like you'll eat you'll eat the popcorn.
I'm not afraid of microwaves.
They just are a little odd.
So wouldn't you just rather pop your popcorn on like the stovetop?
It actually is.
It actually is kind of better that way.
Anyways, I hear that get a nice little crisp to it.
But you do the thing that everybody accidentally does and you put way too much kernels in.
You think you're going to have.
Oh, no, that's not enough.
Let me just tell you right now.
It's enough at first scoop is enough worried about me.
Honestly, you're kind of making me want to pop some popcorn outside.
Yeah, no, you should.
But like I don't have a microwave.
So, you know, old fashioned.
I won't have to like worry about the radiation.
I love popcorn on the stove.
It's awesome.
But you end up doing way too much and then just gets everywhere.
We got to talk to Khan.
I just saw a ladder and I was like, I'm going to climb that.
You know what else is really good?
Can you come over here?
I'm trying to get down.
I didn't think he was looking at me.
It wants me to find Lucas's.
Only then will he help me get to the center.
Have you ever toasted your own sunflower seeds?
Dirty work only to know head.
So you buy just raw sunflower seeds.
Taking out of the shell and you just put it.
You got to take them all out of the shell yourself.
No, no, no.
Just buy the ones that are out of the shell.
They sell raw, untoasted.
You can do it yourself.
OK.
Yeah.
I'm like a king.
I don't have time for that, but you can control the amount of salt
you put on and any other little things you want to add to it, too.
I don't really add a lot of things.
You know, I'm kind of like kind of basic.
I'll just put a little salt on it.
It's good.
It's really easy, too.
Why?
I don't know, because it's fun to do the new things.
It's fun to, like, experience our world.
Why?
What do you mean, why?
I mean, why put salt on it?
Why not just toast it?
Oh, OK.
Just you could.
But the flavor wouldn't be kind of we're going this way.
It'd be a little dull.
Stir know that you grew sunflowers.
I think so.
Is it?
Do you hear about the sunflower?
I know.
Why would you know about that?
Actually, now that I think about it.
That's very weird.
It was like 10 feet tall.
It's huge.
Oh, and then you toast at your own sunflowers.
I gather from this tale.
No, you didn't.
I didn't.
I just grew some flowers.
Me and my girlfriend, we put them into a container
and we're going to plant.
We're going to pick out, like, the ones we're going to plant them again next season.
Why did I say it like that?
Like, season?
I don't know.
Wait, so OK.
We're not going to eat them.
We're going to replant them.
Because here's the thing about growing plants.
If you don't know, stir.
I don't.
If you want to grow, let's say, sunflowers,
you don't just plant one sunflower in the ground and go, OK.
Because it might not actually grow.
You don't plant one.
OK.
I didn't know that.
I thought you just did one sunflower.
Well, but then you were like, good.
And then like a whole field of them would grow.
No.
My point is if you want, let's say you want like two or three sunflowers in the same area.
You have to plant like 15 in that kind of small zone.
And then you have to get rid of the stragglers.
It's called thinning.
It's actually really sad.
Some of them are just not strong enough.
That is sad.
It is.
No, it is sad.
Well, what if you take the stragglers and you move them somewhere else?
Yeah, you could.
They get their own space.
You could.
But they might not go.
They might not keep going.
This is a really weird first date.
So it's in these microwaves.
Let me tell you something.
You can put a magnet on your head.
Why did you sit on your cellular device?
It's called you have to thin out your sunflower seeds and it's sad.
I can't plant them all on you.
This guy has so much to say.
Go that way.
Okay.
You'll see a giant man.
Yeah, we actually gave some as gifts.
Okay.
Yeah.
Let me mail you a sunflower.
That would be pretty cool.
It wouldn't make it.
Why wouldn't it make it?
Oh, shit.
You should email him a sunflower.
Like I didn't I didn't hear the story.
I didn't see a picture.
Your off stream life is a mystery to me.
Like I'm curious what you do as hobbies because you show up hobbies.
Yesterday you made you show up like for a new year stream
and then you're gone till next New Year's.
It's like, what are you doing in the meanwhile?
Looking for a job.
I don't know.
I just like live my life, man.
Trust you.
It's grown some.
I mean, I didn't know about the grown sunflowers.
That's the thing.
Yeah, I'm kind of into plants.
Sad update.
Really sad update.
I had a money tree and it wasn't doing well.
I tried to replant it.
I tried to help it give it some space and it didn't make it.
That was actually really sad.
The money tree is a perfect place for shade or.
I was looking for some support is what I was looking for.
Well, I'll support you when I know what it is.
All right.
So we got get some work at the czar and earn Sophie's trust.
OK, it's a tree.
You can get they come in different sizes.
OK, I can upgrade your blueprint if you bring me.
13 infected trophies.
Why is he posing?
I said fuck you up like.
Yeah, I like all the parts of this game that aren't like talking to people.
Well, I mean, you have to sell items and stuff.
Yeah, but like all the crap, I just like running around the city
and they're being, you know, zombies and, you know, you looting, you know.
This is so much more damage than what I have.
Twenty five.
I don't I don't get some work at the bizarre from who got a lot of good weapons now.
Oh, do I have your permission?
Mission for what?
Quest giver.
OK, I'm Damian.
Hey, hey, streamer, maybe you'd like to everything else more
if you'd actually talk to anyone.
I mean, people have people have a point, right?
Like we're not immersing ourselves in the story.
We're literally going as fast as we can to go swing chivalry weapons at people.
I'm immersed in the parts that I want to be immersed in,
which is like hanging out with an identical clone of myself
and just like having a good time jumping around rafters
and jumping off buildings and doing monkey swings.
I don't think we got we didn't get a mission from that person.
OK, yeah, we have to go talk to someone else now.
All players.
And see, then this guy's like, oh, give you a job.
You want a job.
I think you got to play cards.
A job.
Oh, you want a job.
I got to work.
It's like, how did the conversation take that long?
That's why I'm a secretary and wedding ring on the wrong finger.
Come on.
Don't fuck with me.
I'm serious.
Well, then it's not a wedding here.
Like you own the place sticks.
Coconut sized balls.
OK, I might have a just a ring, dude.
Oh, minor thing.
This is a ring.
But it's a ring.
Oh, why did I ask why?
OK, he gave us a small job.
I think we can handle it.
The balls in your court.
All right.
Track track that.
Now we're going to earn their trust.
I mean, once we have their trust, we're going to split their throats.
I think we are the family in infantry.
Oh, my God, man.
Not coming up.
You have six.
Yeah, it is.
I want to beg you to play that and then like play for like a day
and then never talk to you again.
Like I said, you would.
Yep.
I was like, oh, yeah, real fun.
We'll play again sometime.
And then like, I think three years went by.
Oh, I'm sorry.
I never apologize for that.
These bad guys.
Yeah, I'm not going to take the first swing because it's that's even.
I'm not.
It's not funny.
Like what do you think?
It's funny to just hit people and be mean all the time.
We got to find this building over here.
Oh, yeah.
But we're playing EDF six, right?
Maybe.
I don't know.
It depends.
It's going to be good.
Why wouldn't it be good?
I don't know.
Those games are so much fun, though.
Yeah.
So why do you doubt?
I mean, they take a long time to play, though.
If you're going to play EDF, it's not just like, yeah, you know, I'll play EDF for an hour.
You have to play.
You have to commit like 100 hours to EDF for it to be fun.
Or at least like 30.
Hubert, you here?
Dodger sent me.
Did he?
Are we going to find a way inside?
It's so pretty.
It really is.
Window.
I don't know.
I'm not sure where you're going, but I'm going to follow you.
I mean, I see a door over there.
I thought there might be a window somewhere.
We're trying to get in here.
Oh, there's a window right here.
There's heads.
Heads, bro.
I need your help, bro.
Thanks for the subs.
I'm trying to get off.
Watch out.
Came with a weapon this time.
Oh, there's tracks.
Yeah, because we're trying to figure out where the guy went.
Oh, cool.
In his place, his place appears to be infested, you know, from context clues.
But I'm just kind of looting.
Kind of what you do.
Yeah, I'm just opening up these boxes.
We're going to have to make it into the final circle soon, though.
Yeah, I see there's footprints.
They go probably up.
No, I'm going to climb this footprint.
That looks like we're going to be going down.
Where do we go from here?
Woodrobe.
Yeah, we've got to check and make sure there's not like another world in there.
Oh, we got a tunnel.
Perfect.
A secret gremlin tunnel where you like, you climb around in here for a little bit,
then you jump in the pool.
Yeah, you got to jump in the pool after.
It's Hector.
What are you doing?
This is for Rage.
How did you find my secret entrance?
You call that a secret?
It was supposed to be.
You're out of luck, though.
He hurt his leg.
You're going to have to put him down.
I think one of us is going to have to carry him.
He won't give a shit.
There's a lot of choices.
Which one?
I'll be back soon.
It sounded like a conversation under.
It did, yeah.
I gather we have to go loot like he was sent to go do a thing,
but he hurt his leg and he's going to get put down like a horse and he can't do it.
So we have to go do it for him.
And then like he's going to get the credit.
We're not supposed to go this way.
Yeah, the other way.
You have a knack for that.
I just I see arrows that are on the ground and I look at them.
You're going to send that guy to the glue factory.
Now, how did I hear these guys?
I tripped me.
You want to listen to them?
The same guy.
I think there's there's talking.
Like, is it really normal for you?
Are they going to notice him fall?
No, they're not.
I think I helped.
You fall in.
You're doing it.
Oh, OK, we got distracted.
You want to just like just get distracted.
You want to just like wander where we're doing quests.
I mean, we're already on this quest.
Let's just finish this one.
OK, I just want to, you know, go to some dangerous locales
and find some, you know, interesting go down in the metro.
Find out what's going on there.
What's with all these zombies?
I don't know what is with it.
It's crazy.
Like no one's talking about this.
No one's even talking about this happening everywhere we go.
It's like, oh, go over here and pick up my supplies like zombies.
No one's going to.
Wow.
See you later.
OK, 59 meters.
Inhibitor container detected.
Oh, inhibitor.
That's going to be in that zone.
Why isn't anyone talking about this with 200,000 tweets?
It's this is this is totally the mission from Dying Light one
where we go down there, open the garage door
and the big tyrant is going to show up.
Oh, it is.
You're right.
But they do it twice, though.
What they do is fucking guys will do anything.
Who made this game?
I rent tech tech land.
Yeah.
What else is tech land made?
They made Dying Light.
Besides that, obviously.
I need you to help.
I did it.
No, I swear that was when I was them.
You guys need help.
We'll be fine.
Thanks.
What happened?
We heard a rumor about the pirate.
It's just two other players.
When we're like pretending not to be in the same game.
We're going down.
Trash doesn't hurt either.
You can go down, too.
Yeah, there's nothing here.
Looks like we're going down.
Elevator.
All right, cool.
We should turn off the generator.
Why did we do that?
That just gave us a problem.
Okay, you go first.
I got your back.
All right, I'm going first.
Owler, straight ahead.
I could find the GRE container.
Easy, easy.
You're aggroing.
Am I?
You're aggroed him.
What are you talking about?
You're doing fake E3 gamer trailer.
No, we're not.
Oh, my God.
I'm aggroing him.
I'm the tank.
You're aggroing.
Let's walk away.
Uh-oh, we're aggroing.
There's a dude right here.
You aggroed.
It's time to run.
The Zeds see us.
There's no time.
Why would you hit the howler?
So he doesn't howl.
Oh, shit.
Except we gotta go.
Watch out.
Horde's coming.
Oh, my fucking heart is beating so fast.
There's monsters and shit everywhere.
Player number two up the stairs.
Come on, hurry.
Go, go, go.
My fucking heart is racing, dude.
Jesus.
Let's clear this out real quick.
We need to save them.
I need to stop.
I have to stop for a second.
Fucking God.
It's intense.
Stop for one second, man.
You need a heal?
I got you.
Let's patch you back up.
Thanks, man.
Jeez.
That's my last one.
Oh, shit, man.
My light.
My light's flickering out.
What?
I can't see a thing.
Oh, man.
Okay, guys.
I can't see either, man.
I can't see either.
It could be one anywhere.
I sneezed.
It turns it back on.
There's a volatile down here.
We're doomed.
Oh, what's all this goop?
Guy?
God.
Guy.
I think he's dead, man.
I think he's dead.
Yeah, he is now.
Yeah, I took the assassin perk.
Oh, my God.
Watch out.
Ow, my heart.
My fucking body hurts.
That was so fucked up.
He just touched you, grabbed you.
Kill him.
All right.
I don't know, dude.
I think...
Can we play Mario or something?
You gonna be okay, man?
Can we play Mario Kart or something, dude?
I don't think I can do this.
This isn't a game.
I think he's gonna explode.
Don't hit those.
Sorry.
I'm sorry.
I was so confused because it was moving around
but not spraying on my screen.
It was just like doing a worm move.
Okay.
Where's the GRE container?
It's all right.
We'll turn on the generator.
Get some light in here.
Nice.
Oh, cool.
There's his dead in there.
Oh, container.
This is the room we...
This is where we came from.
That's on the...
Watch out.
I'll get this loop.
Oh, shit.
Not again.
We're gonna have to run.
I don't want to do that again.
I don't want to do the acting routine again.
We need to find the container.
Which way are we going?
Are we going down this way?
I don't know.
We have to find one of those things.
Watch your back.
The indicator didn't beep yet.
I think this is the military storage area
Hubert told me about.
Yeah, it's down here in secret.
Okay.
I'm going.
I'm a runner.
Are you actually just running through this?
Yeah, I'm a runner.
Fucking idiot.
Call it next time then.
Call it now.
I don't want to be fucking mad, dude.
But call it next time.
I called it.
I don't know where to go.
Dead end, bro.
Fucking dead end, bro.
Through here.
Go through the fucking door.
God damn it, man.
This way.
Up here.
Not playing games with you again.
Oh, my...
This isn't funny, bro.
Help me.
Watch my back.
I'm turning on the lights.
Yeah.
Nah, I'm just not fucking gonna play a game with you anymore.
Go play fucking COD, you fucking idiot.
Oh, wait.
You're locked the guy.
I need you.
Hey.
Yep.
I'm on it.
Drops up.
I got it.
Stop.
Oh, coffee.
Oh, Cheetos.
Roaty vest.
Cheetos.
Chicken.
Yeah, how did they not put any of that back in this game?
We've been playing for like two hours.
I haven't seen one coffee, Cheetos, or chicken.
Because I don't think any of those items are actually in the game.
Coffee was.
Was it?
It was.
Yes.
Oh, we got a box.
But you're acting like they were Cheetos in the game?
There were no Cheetos.
There was no Cheetos, but there was coffee.
And we haven't seen coffee yet, and I'm upset.
You said we weren't going to do the bit unless you found it.
Well, we're not going to find it.
You're just giving up.
No.
I thought that was coffee.
It looks like extra gold.
A bottle of risen glory cognac and some cigars.
Cubans, the box says.
Some cigars?
Yeah, some cigars.
Well, we have all this stuff here.
OK.
Yeah.
Do you have a heal, bro?
Of course I got a heal.
You know, I've been crafting healing items.
I don't have any of the stuff.
Oh, there's still a few more somewhere.
Oh, we're searching containers.
There's a lot of stuff over there.
I see.
I'm hacking in with my hack stick.
I do like the idea of a hack stick.
I think it's cool.
Oh, we got a hammer.
Yeah, I like I like a hack stick, but I think it's way cooler if you like.
On like the end of an arrow and then you shoot it into a USB port.
Obviously, it would never go in right the first way.
It would bounce off because you didn't have it the right way.
Like all USB sticks.
And then you shoot it a second time.
I can't open that box.
Hey, bro.
Oh, man, dude, it's bad.
It was such an enormous joke.
Nobody said that.
I did.
What's with these fake boxes where it's only like an inch deep?
Yeah, it's almost like this.
It's like this is a magic trick case.
Yeah, the body's in the bottom.
The real thing is underneath.
You open it, then you close it.
You press the magic button that lifts this too.
And then the other thing is in there.
Are you really giving away the whole trick?
Yeah, that's like that's how it works.
That's not cool.
Did I just turn that offer on?
It was on.
We're looking for we got to search one more box.
Wait, was this it?
OK, we got it.
Apparently, we got everything of value.
Nice.
Time to head out of here.
Oh, you you you really need some DSing on that, bro.
OK, bro, we just climb over here.
That hurt me.
Did it?
And they do things, Bob.
Yep, there's like you made it until you jump.
But how did you make it over?
I don't know.
I did the skip.
Oh, OK, I got it.
Oh, back other way.
Oh, we got to move this.
Oh, my God.
It's like a piece of wood.
Get over it, Aiden.
He's a plywood.
Do you know how they make plywood?
From wood?
They spin a tree like they shave a tree really thinly
and they mush all the pieces together that they shave
with like water and stuff and glue.
OK, I'm hearing ghosts.
I think we can leave.
This game is fun.
Pirates.
Did you find the stash?
Sure did.
Thanks for the lockpicks.
But what are you still doing here?
Is this him?
Sure is.
He was kind enough to get the goods for us.
Saved us a lot of trouble.
Very good.
So he's got a fanny pack.
Well, it's cool now like Kanye brought it back.
I'm just kidding.
I don't care.
You should care about fashion.
And now we don't need you.
So do we get counted?
More people keep coming on from stage.
Oh, wait, do we fight?
Do we do a little shit?
Oh, my God.
I counted.
Five corpses.
Kill him and take the goods.
Oh, kill him.
Five corpses.
I thought that was in the game.
I thought that was one of those people here.
I'm going to get you.
Hey, how are we going to do this?
What tactical way are we going to?
Oh, yeah, you can't block power attacks.
I'm down.
Are you dead?
Yeah.
Wait, wait, wait.
Just hide on the truck.
How much health do you have?
How much time do you have?
Oh, my God.
Blow this up.
I got you.
Let's go.
Let's get this going.
Come on.
Watch out.
He's just taking it.
His head is thick.
He just popped him up.
Like we were on a trampoline.
What the fuck was that?
Wings.
You do these gigantic swings with two-handed swords in this game
and the person's head just spins.
Why do these guys have so many?
OK, I'm taking out two-hander too.
Two-hander versus two-hander.
I'm on the map.
How much health does this guy have?
I don't have any health potions left.
Well, whatever they are.
Hold on, mate.
Time out.
Damn.
Are we?
Why was this taking us so long?
I don't know.
Because our weapons are made out of duct tape, maybe?
There might be health in that box to your left.
He didn't even come close.
What was that hitbox?
He just berserker whirlwinded.
Take one of these.
I can't even look over there.
You are off-camera fighting these people.
I'm coming in.
I'm coming into camera.
I'm just waiting for a body to fly across the screen.
I feel like we're LARPing.
And I'm really disappointed right now because I feel like that sucks.
I came here, I dressed up, I brought my huge sword that I had crafted.
And somebody tagged me in the leg and it was like,
Dad!
And it's like, come on, dude.
Really, I get to watch the cool part now.
I got you.
Like, I have to watch you do that.
They're not going to stop me.
Get up, buddy.
You're fine.
You're going to stop fucking crying about it.
I take this right out of the pocket.
Yeah, you missed, by the way.
There's something in this chest.
I love when they have like a stream of blood coming out of their body.
Yeah, that was weird.
Like, snakes just came out of them.
Okay, honestly, God, why is it taking so long?
There's a skeleton here.
I'm in pain.
He's coming up behind you.
I got a new weapon.
What is it?
It's gone.
No, it's not.
Where's his weapon?
What happened?
What the fuck is happening?
It's gone.
What?
He doesn't have a weapon.
Where are you, asshole?
It's gone.
We are dead here.
This is a guy in a costume.
This isn't even a guy.
I'm dead.
No, please.
I couldn't save you, Gascan.
I don't think he can die now.
You cut his head off and he just kept swinging.
Can you pull me to you?
No, you're dead, man.
No, I'm alive again.
Can you pull me?
No, I can't.
Are you still running away from that guy?
He's dancing now.
Hold on.
I'm coming to you.
He thinks I'm invisible.
I gotta get there quick.
That was so stupid.
Okay, on my screen, he didn't have a weapon.
And then his head came off.
Yeah, you walked up to the side of him and cut his head off.
And he dropped his weapon.
He just started punching at you.
I thought it was like a...
I thought the game was doing an actual like chicken headless joke.
Hold on.
Keep him there.
We gotta like...
We gotta take this guy somewhere.
I'm almost there.
He's still here.
I mean, we didn't get the reward for the quest.
We didn't?
What's going on here?
Are you able to get in here?
I'm in trouble.
Hold on.
I ran into...
Who's playing a clown horn?
What was that?
Somebody just like, oh, look at me.
God damn it.
Okay, I gotta run.
You're not far.
Just come here, man.
Oh, shit.
Run, run, run, run, run.
Yeah, I don't know how you...
All right, so where is he?
I can hear him swearing.
Yeah, he's still talking.
You motherfucker.
So what did we do?
We didn't get the quest reward?
What are we supposed to do about this?
I think we're supposed to go turn in the quest to the guy now
because it's giving me the other marker.
Okay, well...
If you press Q, you can still see his head.
It's there.
All right, so we can just leave.
Yeah, he's gonna kill me.
How are you this good?
Can we kill him again?
I don't think we can kill him again.
Let's go.
Yeah, run.
Okay, wrap around here
because there was like a weird quest with this guy.
I had like, he was handcuffed.
Oh, so you want to like go unhandcuff him?
Yeah, I tried to.
He's right over here.
Do the Uwuga thing?
Yeah, he's over here.
Okay, they grouped up now.
Yeah, do it.
Oh, damn it.
Another headless guy.
Oh no, he's staying down.
Good.
This guy's holding a foam bat.
That's not gonna hurt anyway.
All right, we rescued this guy.
Excuse me.
What are you doing?
I'm doing parkour.
No, the guy that we rescued.
Wait, is he trying to fight you?
Yes, I don't know what happened.
He's keeper rescued.
He's mad.
Wait, is he mad?
I think he's, he gave up.
All right, take his head off.
Take his head.
We're doing like no damage to him.
Why can't we hurt him?
I think you might have to like harry these guys
to get their helmet off.
He's got a black eye.
After all that, he has a shiner.
Just leave him.
It's not worth our time.
Take some money.
Are we climbing this?
I like climbing.
Where are we going?
He's following you.
We're going on.
We're going this way.
Follow me.
He's picking up rocks and throwing them at us.
Yeah, he doesn't like us.
Let's go.
Hey, another cop car.
There's definitely nothing in there.
Let's go.
You want to stick to the roots.
Generally, you want to stick to the roof tops in this game.
Okay.
Who has the goofy horn?
I'm not hearing a horn.
Am I going crazy?
You don't hear a goofy horn.
I don't hear anything in that building.
I shouldn't have locked back.
I need lock that guy.
Oh, you're too far away.
I guess I'll just do it and you'll be like irrelevant.
Now you're kind of far right here right now.
Where's the lock?
There was this door.
I opened it.
There's nothing in here.
There's a question.
There's a question mark over here.
I want to go see the question mark.
Okay.
That was dumb.
Jumping off the roof.
Oh, you did it too.
I've made it, I guess.
I need to craft heals.
Apparently, we're supposed to come back at night.
I'm back at night.
All right.
Okay.
I don't.
It's a dark zone.
I don't know.
Oh, I can unlock far jump or running speed.
I'll do far jump.
When you get the cast like fireball.
So I seriously haven't like we've leveled up like one time.
Does that just mean we're not doing anything?
Maybe or we didn't get like the
About the halftime show.
I don't what do you want me to say about it?
I don't I'm not watching it.
Can you please react?
We have to actually go find honey.
Pretty sure we could like go to a place and buy it.
Yeah, I'm out of healing again.
Are you kidding me?
I fell at that last second there.
React.
No, I'm not reacting to the Super Bowl halftime show.
Who's performing?
I don't know.
I can react to that.
Is it fucking Barney again?
Barney comes on stage and they do like a whole routine with them.
Yeah.
Yeah, last year it was Barney and baby Bob.
I actually would watch that.
That was the halftime show.
Why do so many NPCs have this hair?
Because we keep coming back and talking to the same guy.
It's not it's a different.
It's not a different person.
What are you talking about?
Oh, that hair is what I don't feel like that hairstyle is always
selectable in any game that has character customization.
The just bizarre buzz cut in the wrong spots.
It's always like number.
It's only the second row always.
We got to rescue this guy.
Yeah, when dropping onto enemy from above.
He's like, what the fuck just happened?
He's like, holy shit.
Wait, you jumped out and died?
This guy's face is like, oh my God.
What was that?
I don't know what's happening.
Somebody's holding down a piano key.
He's got a song machine.
What was that song music maker?
I want one of those.
That thing is insane.
Who is this guy?
Why does he not have a health bar?
Where's his health bar?
This guy doesn't have a health bar, sir.
The sun's going down.
No, stop playing the fucking funny music.
I'm not hearing it.
Shut up.
All right, let's help this guy.
Look at all these homeless people that come off the street.
Like, oh, there's a fight going on.
I'm coming in.
We got him.
Holy shit, this guy's good.
Who is this guy?
I'm doing a 1v1.
Why does it have a trophy?
All right, let them 1v1.
Let them fight it out.
Let them fight.
Okay.
There's zombies coming.
I have no healing.
No, no.
What the fuck, dude?
I've had enough.
We gotta go.
Let's go.
Can we have a bar and kill him?
He has a trophy on him.
Let's finish saving him.
He's in danger.
Okay.
Does he, like, talk to us?
Oh, yeah.
I could, like, take it from him.
Take the trophy from him?
Okay, get it.
I got it.
How do I get it?
I can't get it.
I can't take anything.
That probably hurt so bad.
All right, here.
Thanks for the help.
Okay, let's go.
Rooftops.
We're in trouble.
Are we?
I don't feel threatened.
Somebody just called me Original Sin Andy.
Well, like, I haven't been baptized.
What the fuck is that message?
What is that comment?
Divinity Original Sin?
Good game.
This guy's gonna be a fruit.
Okay.
Can we eat those?
What did you do?
I threw a coin at his head.
He's on the run.
He's running.
Running for his life.
He's guilty of something.
What the fuck?
Like, he just...
He was just eating an apple.
He didn't even do anything.
You're a dick.
All right, quest is this way.
Let's go.
You gotta stop fooling around.
How are we ever gonna get the antidote?
Oh, wait, nighttime.
Let's go in here.
This was the place.
Oh, that's right.
You're right.
I'll watch out.
There's a, there's a scorcher.
I'd be careful in here.
Oh, there's one right there.
You don't want to alert him.
You wouldn't want to start playing the sound machine right now.
I think one person.
Oh, there's one more.
Sorry, I got it wrong.
One more person.
My zombie powers are showing that there's a lot of enemies in here.
Some of them in coats, some of them in pants.
I'm not seeing it.
I'm like an 800 on my experience here.
Are you actually?
Okay.
I feel like I'm starting to see a lot of the game and it's,
I've seen a lot of the same, you know?
So I feel like my experience meter is actually going up.
So you're, how far are you at the?
800 out of a thousand.
I'll say 823.
Nice round number.
You know what?
I'll be honest.
I'm probably getting kind of close too to be able to say that as well.
Blades.
You're gonna be.
Lock back guy.
We got some big loot in here.
This is odd.
I know where it is.
Don't worry.
I, what happened?
He fell over.
You're a bit silly.
You're doing some ditzy stuff.
Oh, you fuck.
That's right there.
A little bit more.
Ooh.
Urgent.
So, uh, from the last game, you just carried UV lights around with you.
And then the zombies went, I think you can, you can make them.
Oh, can you?
That makes a lot of sense.
I feel like everyone should just be covered in UV lights.
Like a RGB keyboard kind of situation.
This whole thing wouldn't really be a problem anymore.
Why are we getting intense music?
I'm not.
Oh my, I'm about to die.
Why?
There's a UV flashlight in a later mission.
That's cool.
That's all it was.
Let's go.
We actually could both die very soon here.
You guys are in the baby zone still because you're not doing any story missions.
You're stuck in the baby zone.
What?
You ran that fast?
We've been helping though.
He's been doing it.
I'm going to go to the craft master.
I need you all players.
I can't talk to this guy unless you got my back.
I'm anxious.
It's a skyscraper city that you haven't even gotten to.
You're not even going to get to it.
Shove up.
Shove them up your ass.
Okay.
That was a side quest.
We got to do some main story missions.
I mean, I learned a parkour point.
Okay.
So this only get some work at the bazaar and earn Sophie's trust.
Isn't that what we just did?
Yeah.
I guess we just do a job.
She doesn't trust us.
Perfect dodge will stagger an enemy.
That's cool.
Okay.
I'm going to go to the crafting zone.
I just, I don't even, I just purchased things.
I'm never going to use them.
Someone's going to tell me to use them.
I'm never going to do it.
I want to craft.
Oh, it's middle mouse button to upgrade your blueprints.
By the way.
I crafted.
I did it.
I figured it out.
Cool.
All right.
So I just got that better.
Yeah.
You did get that better.
Like a million degrees in here.
Oh, who's selling the, uh, healing items?
Anyone got any healing items in here?
Um, somebody probably does.
Come back here.
Oxygen.
The general shop, I think has them.
This is fucking losers selling cans.
Oh, these are nice.
Get a job.
Glasses.
Yeah.
Just buy all the heals.
I did.
I purchased a full stack of healing items.
Tell all the bullshit that you, all the weapons you're not using either.
I got to say I'm feeling ready to take on the world.
This thing's pretty good.
Antique hammer.
I'm going to actually do a PP while you do your shopping.
Oh, we're going to do, we're going to do break.
If you want to do PP or if you want to like
pour tea into the toilet or whatever.
Let's, uh, let's go pee.
We'll be right back together.
Yeah.
Let's make sure we flush at the same time.
Sink it.
Okay.
We'll be right back.
See you in a minute.
Oh, I am back.
I don't think stir is though.
We'll find out.
Are you back?
Oh yeah.
I'm back.
All right.
My war hammer.
I electricity going through it the whole way.
Electricity you say, huh?
Yeah.
Electricity.
Pretty cool.
It's a little bit more practical than just finding a handgun.
So I wired up my metal hammer with electricity.
And how did you do that?
When you press I and you go in your inventory and you click on your weapon.
Yeah.
Oh, modify weapon to modify.
And if you have the blueprints on the equipment, then you can.
I don't.
I think I sold everything.
Someone in here sells blueprints for weapons.
Or it was that other place we were at.
They were selling a lot of weapon blueprints.
Well, yeah, this guy has like weapon mods for the shaft.
You want like a different shaft weapon.
Oh, he's got some flame tips.
Oxy.
Fire.
I think I want the toxic and the fire.
I want them both.
Yeah.
Yeah, definitely.
Nice.
Okay.
Now we go to the weapon.
Wait, that's not the weapon I want.
I want to put it on this.
Let's go ahead and put my blueprints.
I just bought them.
Where are they?
Didn't I buy them?
Those tips might have been for arrows.
And I just buy blueprints.
Where do they go?
When you go to modify your weapon, that's where they show up.
That was a shaft mod.
Yeah.
I was toxic to one.
Okay.
Do you know a tip mod?
How do I?
You press C on the weapon and then I bought one as a tip.
And then there's a shaft and there's a charm.
If you want to put a charm on it.
Oh, I get you.
So I can put like a flaming tip at the top of my shaft.
Okay.
My venom shaft.
I have a fire on the shaft.
Okay.
Yeah.
I've got a flaming weapon and a shaft.
Oh, this is cool.
Yeah.
Okay.
You ready?
Yeah.
I'm healing.
Okay.
So what story mission are we on now?
Get some work at the bazaar.
Hold on, hold on, hold on.
Let me see if I have other quests.
See, I thought that was part of the main one.
Get some work.
I thought we just did work though.
Do we have to keep you inside missions?
We might have to do another.
Get some work.
Is there anybody else that has a job in here?
Yeah.
Story quest.
The only way out.
That's what we're doing, right?
I think so.
I mean, there's a person over here.
All players required to talk to this lady.
Yep.
We got to keep doing these.
Coming gas can, I'm sorry.
I just might be nothing.
I don't know.
Did we do it?
Yeah, I think we did it.
What?
We didn't do it.
What is it?
Hey, does anyone need any work?
Does anybody have anything to do?
Anyone have any work for us?
Anyone here you need?
Hey, all players.
Hey, this guy needs some work.
Please wait.
I'm waiting.
Yeah, I'm waiting.
Yep.
Okay.
We need some more.
Anyone here got some work?
He's wait.
All players required for this person.
Can I help you?
Can you help me to give me help to you?
Oh, perfect.
Thank you for the gift.
What do we get?
Who's Benny?
Who really is judging?
I'm confused.
This doesn't make any sense.
What are they saying?
Hey, get some work done.
Hey, this guy.
Please wait.
It still says please wait.
Look on your side quest for ones that say bizarre.
Yeah, we might already have.
Yeah, I probably already accept.
Did you already take one?
I took a bunch before stream started.
Side quest.
Cheers.
Yeah, they're saying these are side quests.
Return to Carlos.
Current objective report to the board.
Oh, I have to track.
I think that just kind of all they're all here.
They're all in front of us.
Skips all dialogue.
I'm confused, bro.
Yeah, that's the joke.
You got it.
I know.
Yeah, he got the joke.
We can't talk to this guy.
He's too popular.
We need to turn the quest into him and we can't.
I'm confused.
Is that okay?
Are we sure he's not above us?
No, it's over his head.
Okay.
Well, is there another one?
I mean, we did that quest.
I feel like I deserve credit for it.
Who else has a turn in?
Oh, Bebin.
Okay, let me look at what else we can do.
A different one.
Bring Lavender.
Oh, we can apparently.
Everything else is further away.
That guy.
I don't think we can talk to this guy.
Okay, let's go do this.
Then we can come back later when he decides to work.
Wait, are you still pointing me to what?
It's doing this.
I know there's someone out back.
Go to the main menu and then go back in.
No, don't do it.
Okay.
It's honestly a scam.
Oh, this is right here.
No, let's run 100 meters.
We're runners.
That's our job.
It's nighttime.
It's scary.
I'm honestly not afraid of the dark.
That's Aiden.
I've just been offered an extremely shady deal,
but maybe it'll turn up a lead on Lucas.
There's two random quests here.
Whatever it is, check it out.
Main quest.
That's right.
Yep.
Thank you.
Thanks for correcting me there.
All players.
Let's go.
Wait, I'm confused.
What did I agree to?
I don't know what just happened.
Didn't you hear what I said?
Get downstairs.
Oh, didn't you hear what I said?
See, they know.
I don't dig through the trash.
Does that hurt me?
This isn't a main quest,
but we can't do the main quest until we do all the side quests here.
I'm here for the job.
So you're new around here.
Damien.
Fly and say I'm a local.
Yeah, I'm a local.
Born and bred, if you must know.
Then why haven't I ever seen you before?
Couldn't say.
We're tightly packed, but it's still a big city.
I heard there's a new game.
This game makes no fucking sense.
It does.
We're just skipping every dialogue piece.
Double down.
Pilgrims are nomads.
The story is probably interesting.
I don't know.
It could be.
I have one.
That's another thing.
Almost got lynched at the bazaar.
Didn't have a marker.
When is this guy gay?
Some say he was recently infected.
Ring a bell.
What are they talking about us?
I double down.
I saw that guy.
He was taken outside by a hack on.
And killed.
Maybe he was.
Or maybe he will be.
Because he's sitting here lying to my face.
You know what they need to put into games for idiots like us?
What?
Like an audio tape you can play.
That's five minutes long that plays while you're playing.
That tells you the whole story.
We wouldn't look into it.
You don't think so?
No.
Okay.
And a lot of games do that.
Like when you're the master chief and you have the little blue girl telling you.
You think we would skip that if it was like oh hey for the people.
We're fighting these guys.
Yeah we're fighting them.
Did it matter?
Oh my god I threw a spear in that guy's head.
Wait why?
The guy lit on fire?
Yeah you got a fire weapon.
Oh that's right.
This is awesome.
Oh they got more goons.
Like that was the main guy.
He's already dead.
Wow I feel like our weapons are dealing damage.
Let me get that guy.
A roadie vest.
Okay let's go.
I'm a bit of a roadie.
This thing is awesome.
This is Fallout for people that don't want to play Fallout.
I mean it's not a mid-dime.
It's our business strategy.
We heard there's a lot of people out there that don't want to play Fallout.
So we're gonna make Fallout.
Okay board meeting approved.
Here's your budget.
I can't.
Oh I wonder who this person is.
I should tell Carl this.
You don't think it's like the little Microsoft paperclip guy was in the corner like.
So this is this is Damian and he's one of those players that you come across.
He's Michael's son.
Just for us to know.
Hey I got like choices.
Do I want to help him?
That sounds like a side quest.
Be careful he's a swindler.
Like and then and then the paperclip disappears.
Why do you keep doing that to me?
Because you were very hurt and I worry.
That wouldn't be immersive.
No but it's something you could turn off and on.
Oh so we're arguing against accessibility now.
No I said you can turn it off and on.
It's off and on.
I'm saying I'm saying the chatter like oh you don't want to go there.
Remember was the one guy that liked Clippy.
Oh look down there.
Oh is that Zeds?
You want to do something about this?
You want to defeat?
It does say defeat.
It does like that's a little Clippy telling us defeat.
We have any bombs or anything?
I don't have any bombs or anything.
All right well let's just go.
We got cool elemental weapons.
Hey you want to drop?
Oh there's a spear up here.
Nice good start.
We can double spear.
One two three.
We both miss.
No I threw it already.
I hit him.
Um okay careful.
He's on fire.
Nice.
You dare don't you dare.
He's dead.
Trophy.
Oh that was cool nice.
Perfume.
It's very weird how that just happened but I'll take it.
Yeah I finally unlocked power attack.
Seems kind of uh.
You got power attack?
I got power attack yeah.
Okay so let's keep moving.
Is someone ringing a bell?
The toll of the undead.
That is in every game isn't it?
Oh the toll of the dead.
You're saying bells are overdone.
I think they're in everything.
I think like the church bells symbolizes the undead has been.
Yeah what happened?
What happened?
I got kicked out.
Oh you said you left my session and then I dropped my weapon.
Did you get kicked out?
No I'm still in here.
What can you re-invite me?
Um help.
Try and re-invite.
Are you online?
I should be.
What's that all about?
Robo Yerma?
He sounds normal to me.
Wait did my stream die?
Whatever.
It was me oh shit.
I guess my internet effed for a second.
Do I sound weird?
A little bit yeah.
Well are you back?
Yeah you're back.
I think I'm back.
I think it was just a little a little chunky eff it's okay.
A little bit of uh yeah.
Uh can you pull me to where you are?
I can't act well I mean maybe if I go to this NPC I can.
Yeah that one counted because now Sophie wants to talk to us because we did the side quest.
Oh good.
We just had to do one side quest.
We've been running around for hours.
Hey she has a good one on her trust.
Okay fast travel.
Teleporting to leader in nine seconds.
Why can't I just do it now?
Yeah can you please call me leader?
Am I still dropping frames?
Do you want to see me?
I've been hearing about you.
Good or bad things?
How many people are streaming the super bowl?
The ones that make me believe it's worth giving you a chance.
Yeah don't you know what you're posing?
Go to one of the-
I do have fiber yeah.
Waiting for other players before proceeding okay.
Now I am.
It's probably just a little bump.
It happens sometimes.
I do have gigabit connection.
I have fiber.
It's very rare.
It's very rare that this happens.
Oh it'll pass it'll be good.
Well let's see if I come back.
Weird I'm back.
Yeah I just guys I just did a speed test.
I'm at a thousand a thousand.
I'm at full connection.
It looks like something weird's going on.
But um we'll try this again.
I mean maybe the super bowl is shutting down every-
Like maybe the super bowl is so crazy that like
nothing else is going to work for years.
Maybe it's the twitch server.
I don't think it's a twitch server
because I wouldn't be dropping from the game too.
Thanks for the invite.
Hey no problem.
Yeah I wouldn't be dropping out of the game.
Weirdly I'm not dropping out of the call.
That's kind of weird.
Well you're not even like-
Actually I think you did drop out of the call
for a little bit when you disconnected.
I couldn't hear you for a moment.
It's probably still happening.
Am I still here?
Yeah.
Okay well let's just try it.
Let's just let's just go.
Oh fiber omega low burr omega low whatever.
Yeah how much do you pay a month?
Like seven thousand dollars for this internet?
Actually actually way less than I was paying before
for like cable internet.
Yeah I bet.
Banana bro here.
Ditch that loser stream.
What does stir call you guys here?
The pineapple people?
No come back to my stream.
Come back to my stream.
Don't don't go straight away.
Hey welcome to the stir mada.
It's like an armada but like you know
let's hit 100,000 likes and show how strong we are.
The star mada is coming into the solar system.
That's actually pretty cool.
I would probably sub.
All right get over here.
Said no one ever.
Wait where are you?
I'm at the quest.
Oh I was facing out.
I was reading.
The stir mada.
What are the uh germa's group of inhumane psychopaths?
No the germamites.
You gotta get it right.
The germamites.
Have I told you?
Wait never mind.
How did Barney get hurt?
What happened at the Super Bowl halftime show?
Did he like break his leg like sprain his ankle?
Oh no not another Barney nip flip.
Wait wait after.
While exploring the city you'll come across characters
marked with the midnight carpet.
Okay.
And then you hold t to fast forward to night.
So I think it's that thing that gas station we're at.
Remember it's like come back at night time.
Yeah yeah okay it's giving us one of those missions now.
We can do a hold t I think.
We gotta go.
Oh is it now gonna be night?
Somebody said is the Super Bowl why Twitter is lagging?
I don't know.
Dude do you remember that like there was a horrible horrible day
not that long ago like I was panicked.
Um you probably like have your own story
like where you were on that day when Facebook was down.
No I don't.
Crap didn't Facebook just say that like
they're gonna pull all operations out of Europe
like if they don't like if they can't do advertising or something.
Can you imagine if Facebook just was like
yeah we're not in Europe anymore.
That was a bluff.
I don't know I'm just saying I've read that.
I mean someone would immediately take their place.
Yeah I don't I don't know about all that.
I feel like opinions are you like kind of cringe.
Somebody's talking like robbing somebody.
Yeah I'm interested in the main quest.
They bluff they got called out.
Uh oh am I lagging again?
Are are you?
Oh you like just disappeared.
Uh hello hello.
Am I still here?
Uh hello are you still here?
Ow I'm good.
Did you turn on the streamer DMCA mode?
I did actually.
Pretty cool.
Do you know DMCA isn't real?
I know you already went over this.
You already talked about a bunch of shit about this.
Okay I just want to make sure you're in the know
because if you're not then you look like a fool.
What happened?
What happened to this guy?
Can we actually find out?
Wait do you want to help him?
We're kind of tripping.
Yes let's help him.
I'll do what I can.
Let's don't skip this.
All right I'll do what I can.
Okay he's gone.
Was he a ghost?
Was he not real?
Hey where is he?
We have two things to do.
Should we go over there?
Climb the windmill and restore power.
Or search for Barney.
Let's turn the power on.
That was like the choice quest we had.
Uh okay.
It's a container.
I know main story main story main story
but it's fun to walk around and get stuff.
Am I lagging?
Is that you making a joke?
Yeah I'm making fun of you.
You're kind of robotting again.
What?
Wait what?
It's in here somewhere.
Is it on the roof?
There's one there's a one and a two.
I'm at the one.
It wants me to climb up top.
And I didn't get I didn't get the one cycle.
And every moment that you're not talking
I feel like you disconnected.
I'm still I'm here I'm here.
Okay like I'm worried about you.
Uh I found the thing.
I found the uh the thing.
I'm doing a different thing.
And I'm already like part way through it.
I feel like my thing's in precedence.
I mean can I loot this and do you get the credit for it?
I don't know.
Find out.
Oh dude you're gonna want to come over here.
This is a neck guitar.
Okay I'm coming.
There actually is one of those.
There's an inhibitor.
Okay teleporting to you.
VR hands.
It does kind of look like that.
Oh we did it we built a whole settlement.
Everyone's moving in.
Don't do that right next to your thigh.
Oh my god that was dangerous.
They don't know any better.
Oh you did it.
Somebody said iPad ad commercial.
It does feel like that.
Activate the windmill creates a safe zone around it.
Wow.
Okay cool.
There's a glider and a grappling hook in this game.
And at this pace you're never gonna see it.
Look at how pretty that is.
So the bitrate can catch up.
Just I'm not gonna move but damn.
Yeah I'm gonna use my glider right now.
But we're doing it on our own pace.
We don't have to be super gamers about it.
We're just enjoying the time.
Yeah speedrun already finished this game by now.
Just give up.
Yeah I'm giving.
Oh my god there's so many Zams.
What happened to the guy that was like help me.
And we're all on drugs while we shook his hand.
He wasn't real.
Oh my god.
What do you mean you're run.
I'm running.
Oh you're in.
I thought you were okay.
I'm in the corner.
I'm about to go down.
I have no stamina.
I'll heal you.
I'll do it to you.
Got you.
I'm electrified.
Oh wait I have one of these.
Do it.
Whoa.
Nice.
We got a lot of looting to do.
Players required.
Lot of loot.
Investigation.
Yeah I feel like we've done that a hundred times.
I know.
I feel like there was a whole tutorial.
I think we did that already.
Oh shit.
Wait how do we do this investigation.
There's like footprints here.
We just have to follow the footprints.
What.
Where are they going.
We'll find out.
Sophie.
It's fresh.
What am I doing.
Did you just eat that.
There's a crystal in here.
Power crystal.
Really.
Yeah.
You said you found an inhibitor in here earlier.
No I was backed up.
If you said that you'd give me a million dollars if I could show you where that was
I wouldn't be able to do it.
I have no idea where that was.
It was like 40 meters right.
I'm just looting.
Okay the blood goes this way.
I think we're getting these crystals.
We're smashing open these crystals.
We're doing a little bit of mining.
They go up the stairs too by the way.
Oh yeah you can sell these can't you.
The guy I remember them in the tutorial he's like these go for a lot.
Just remember.
Yeah he was like these are the most expensive things you'll ever own in your life.
And then he he like took it.
He didn't share.
Power.
I got them.
Shrooms.
Not much stuff to pick up.
Yeah I uh there's a person door here where we need people.
Is there any more crystals up here that I didn't get.
No you lied to me.
Wait Barney's dead.
Who am I?
Who are you?
Sophie?
Who's that?
Who are you?
I'm me.
Where's crystals Barney?
Fuck off.
Wait okay Barney.
Barney fuck off.
Come out or I'll make you.
Come out or I'll drag you out myself.
Oh yeah I am he's Barney.
It really just did that.
Oh fuck fuck you Barney.
Fuck off.
Yeah why does this feel like tutorial number two?
Because it is we're wasting so much time.
We walked around for like an hour and a half.
Yeah but we got all that sick loot.
I know we look I'm not saying we had to go faster.
I'm just saying we haven't done much of the story missions.
These aren't level one enemies.
They are.
Is that Barney?
It is fun though.
Get out of here.
Are you going to stream Angry Birds Star Wars?
That's a that's a question for stir.
Why is that for me?
I don't know because I'm not.
Angry Birds Star Wars um you know I'll try anything once.
Everybody has the same black eye in this game.
Have you noticed that?
Yeah the same exact eye.
It's never the other one.
Are we going to look for him?
Sure.
Where can I find him?
Follow Birdie's trail.
Uh we got an inhibitor in range 40 meters.
Are we actually?
Yep we gotta go outside.
Wait what am I?
Birdie's I should lead me to him.
How do you know there's so much blood here?
There is a lot of blood.
That's my survivor sense.
Hey I gotta follow these footprints.
Everybody's covered in blood.
Oh come on.
What?
I lost connection again?
What the hell?
What's happening?
I don't know.
Re-invite me.
I don't know does this make any sense?
They're trying to keep us apart.
Is my stream still live?
No that's fine.
I don't get it.
I think you're faking it.
Hey at this point I can't find a problem.
Oh like I have I guess I gotta go.
Um cast.
Oh this never happens.
This is a this is a new problem.
Invite you.
Did you?
Oh yeah I did.
Oh yeah I'm following Birdie's trail but I'm gonna wait for you.
I don't have an invite.
Okay I'm gonna I like everyone saw me do it.
Everyone over here on the Sturmata with the perfectly fine connection saw it happen.
Now this oh my god stop.
What the fuck?
What?
You just invited me to play like a hundred times.
Okay.
What's happening?
I wanted to make sure you got it.
Okay am I in your game?
Yeah.
Let's go.
Yeah I don't know what's going on.
That's weird.
You're like 200 meters away again but.
I can teleport to you in a second.
I don't know what this would be related to.
I don't know.
Can you pull me over there bud?
I can't until I'm like actually doing a quest thing that needs you.
I teleport to you from minimap and I teleport to you.
I can't.
If you just walk over here.
I mean it's 172 meters away that's far.
Plus I don't know how to get out of this house.
I mean I'm trying to find this inhibitor.
I actually don't know how to leave this house.
Okay I guess I'll go to the quest down here and then you'll teleport.
Every door it doesn't work if I get out of here.
Oh I'm following the footprints.
I actually forgot I need a tutorial.
Down?
I can't leave this area.
All the windows are boarded.
Open a door or something.
Every door is boarded up I can't leave.
Okay I'm teleporting you.
You gotta wait.
Oh there we go.
This is Bertie.
Bertie is on the ground.
He's hurt.
He needs help.
You're the younger brother with the disconnected controller.
Mom.
Mom I'm dying.
Is he dead?
Is that funny?
Is that funny to you?
It was.
Okay psycho.
You there?
Yeah I'm just trying to reach your brother.
You just ruined that whole moment.
It was just ruined.
What do you mean ruined?
Oh look military med kit in here.
He was just talking on the phone and all of a sudden he's just like in your arms.
It's just like was so off.
Just abnormal.
It was just weird.
And if...
I apologize.
I won't ever make it weird again.
Okay we finally can continue.
We can do the story mission now.
We've unlocked Sophie.
Who's your favorite NPC so far?
I don't know any of their names.
You just said Sophie.
Yeah but I don't know if that's my favorite NPC.
Damn it.
Whatever we gotta go this way anyways.
No we're going right here.
Uh oh door shut.
Here we...
We have to do it now.
Danger.
Things are better for us now right?
Depends.
Oh are we...
Dentists?
That guy was a prick.
The PK were painted hands with him in charge.
Conclusion's pretty straightforward.
Lucas is gone.
She patching up his eye.
It'd be better if you just shut up.
Same eye.
It's gonna be the eye.
No.
Oh.
What were they doing?
What are you doing?
Spying on me?
Yeah I mean I thought it was weird too.
Wait why'd you trick...
He tricked us.
You were supposed to wait for me.
Supposed most.
Plans changed.
Afraid I was after your crystals huh?
Afraid?
Of you?
Would you get any...
What like if you had to get one of his tattoos?
What role again?
Just to look after Pilgrim.
Uh...
Maybe the card?
I don't know.
I'm getting the vi tattoo he has.
Okay cool.
He had a sunflower?
He did have a sunflower.
Oh shit.
I picked sunflower.
Alright finally.
Carl.
I didn't auto tattoo.
See I have the opposite problem.
My game is way too quiet.
It wasn't love at first sight.
Barney has his downsides.
But on the upside he is unshakably loyal.
Oh.
Ask about the conversation with Carl.
That's...
Let's just say the cause in short order.
Oh they're worried about water.
Oh my god.
Just fucking turn the faucet on.
Carl is this California or what?
Unruly brother.
Oh shit a scrapper hammer?
Alright.
We finally can leave.
Go to the meeting place with Jack and...
Who's Jack?
Who's Joe?
Come here.
Come here right now.
You said somebody in your chat.
Someone in your chat said something.
What did they say?
Don't come...
Wait don't come in yet.
What did they say about somebody's head?
No one said anything.
They did.
What did they say?
They said something very specific about somebody's hair.
No one said anything.
Somebody in your chat mentioned how somebody has...
They all have the same hair.
That fucking...
That fucked up haircut?
You don't remember this conversation we had?
Like an hour ago they said that.
Come in here.
Oh okay I thought you were saying they're saying it now.
No like this they...
He was right.
They were right.
This guy yeah he does have that haircut.
Now that I think about it like...
Like four out of ten NPCs have this haircut.
You're right.
I actually saw this character earlier and I honestly was like...
If you looked like that in ten years I wouldn't be surprised.
What?
It kind of...
Like the face kind of looks like you.
You think I'm gonna look like this in ten years?
No I'm saying I wouldn't be surprised.
Like if you showed up you're like hey what's up?
And you like walked in and you were like a B.I.
I would be like oh okay.
I wouldn't...
With that hair though?
No my hair's not gonna do that.
No I'm not with that hair.
I'm not gonna look like that in ten years.
I'm gonna look smokin'.
I don't doubt it.
I just like it could go either way.
Well they could...
No actually I could see that.
Okay now you're on board.
I mean I love McDonald's.
I do.
That's not a joke.
What's the order?
The new order?
Okay.
Oh my god wait hold up hold up hold up hold that pot.
Press heal on me like start healing me.
Do I have bald head?
Do I have the hair?
Isn't that kind of weird?
That's weird.
If you like don't finish the heal it's like the World of Warcraft auto-follow.
That is weird.
Okay I'm gonna start using this.
Anyway what's McDonald's order?
McDonald's order.
Oh did they talk about this at the thing with the milkshake and the M&M's?
What?
I don't get an M&M milkshake.
What are you talking about?
An M&M McFlurry?
No I don't get ice cream with my order.
Okay well I'm just remembering from the thing that we did with the stuff and you know the place.
We had an M&M McFlurry?
No one of the German contestants said...
Oh oh oh.
That was a good order and I was like oh are you also an M&M McFlurry guy?
Okay okay.
Anyways.
A different terma sorry different terma.
Well there's always been me I'm the only one that's been here.
Yeah I know but we were gonna replace you like we had that thing going and like I'm glad
that we ended up not doing it.
No because that would be like weird.
Look I'm gonna retire I'll just say it right?
It's not like it's a big deal.
Good shot though.
Good job you got that uh you got that fucker.
Yeah that imposter was seriously like causing problems and stuff.
I'm just really glad that we don't have to worry about that that guy anymore.
What was his number?
Number 12 or something I don't know.
I'm not yeah but police let me off too because they were like well you know there's only like
one germa here the other guy wasn't even real.
Yeah that's fucked up.
It's just the number.
So that was fucked up.
All right so the McDonald's order.
I come back and this guy is like phasing through the wood.
I knew you were gonna kill him.
All right McDonald's wait 20 meters and we've got a thingy this way.
We're making progress.
Oh we got a thingy oh I never found the last thingy.
That's what I'm saying.
It's over it's over uh I'm playing hot and cold.
I see a window down here.
Yeah it's simply inside her.
No.
On either side of the building?
It's on this side.
It's inside the building.
It's got to be inside this building.
Yeah it's inside.
We got an entryway.
Latch.
You see any routes?
I don't see anything.
Ah ah I see bands.
Found it.
Buddies Sophie I'm sorry.
All right we got an entrance.
I knew it.
We'd betray us.
Fuck them Aiden.
Kill them all.
Okay so it's in the chemical.
Okay we gotta go.
Wait is this the right area?
I don't know.
No.
So no it's not.
I'm back out on the street.
Oh god damn.
No it's it's definitely in there up there.
Okay McDonald's order.
My McDonald's order is wait.
It's this way.
We're really close.
There's a guy I got a gold statue dude.
A crystal statue.
This is probably worth a lot.
I gotta go.
I don't know where I am.
Do something yeah scream or something in the game.
There you are.
Okay get up.
Get up.
Like right down here it's like two meters away.
I think I got it.
Yep oh we have to go up the stairs.
This is a chemical zone though.
Oh shit.
I don't know how you are where you are.
There's like a biohazard door here.
Walk from the inside.
It's a hard lock pick.
Oh no.
I'm about to be poisoned to death dude.
Do it.
You got this.
I got it.
Oh shit this door is locked.
What open it quick.
Another hard lock pick two in a row.
What the fuck dude.
We got a medium lock pick here.
Hi.
Got it got it got it got it got it.
There's nothing in this fucking thing.
This thing was stupid.
I got this one open.
Oh there's a sack in it.
Old world money.
Run.
Wait there's a crystal.
I thought there was an epic mace in there man.
Get that crystal.
What's this door.
I don't know get out.
Locked from inside.
Oh what.
Oh yeah there's like a nighttime quest here.
I'm dead down here.
I don't know where I am.
Oh my god.
Oops oops.
Okay pretty cool man.
That wasn't even that wasn't even the thing we're supposed to get.
Oh yes yeah that wasn't it.
Here see come.
This it was down the street.
Then you turn a right you make a right.
And then down this street it goes down to like three two one one.
Is it right here.
It's definitely it's right here to the right.
You can see behind this wall.
Can you.
Yeah it's right there.
Yeah you can.
Is there a way to get in from here.
Oh we got a cop car.
Not that many people there.
Oh the fucking order.
Okay what is this McDonald's order.
McDonald's order.
It has changed.
Before I had a huge order before.
But people misunderstood what I said.
It was like five sandwiches and like a bunch of McNuggets and stuff.
What people didn't understand was that was a group order.
That was supposed to be shared.
They didn't take into account the shareables.
You buy the nuggets for the group.
You buy an extra sandwich for the group.
In case somebody wants like a McChicken or whatever.
It's a family pack.
It's like a yeah essential.
The actual order is.
Are you ready get out your pen.
Coffee.
It is a.
Cheetos.
A medium 10 piece nugget meal with sweet and sour and honey mustard.
And then it's two double cheeseburgers not McDoubles.
Two double cheeseburgers without a pickle.
No pickle.
You lost me.
And a powerade.
And if I'm feeling a little bit.
If I'm feeling sloppy.
An apple pie.
If I'm kind of sloppy could go for the pie.
Okay.
I think that's pretty good.
No pickle.
No I don't I don't want pickles.
I like eating pickles individually.
I like pickles but McDonald's pickles I mean pretty low on the totem pole.
Exactly.
We got to kill these bandits down here.
I think that's our current situation.
I think we were talking to Sophie about some premeditated murder.
Okay.
What's your order from McDonald's?
My order from McDonald's is like go anywhere else.
You one of those people come on.
If I have to like if like gun to my head.
Two double quarter pounders with cheese.
Okay.
And no like no like made up extra stuff so that the person gets confused and is like
they're putting the pickles on anyway.
That's mine.
Like you can't go to McDonald's and say well I don't want to pick they're fucking putting
the pickles on.
No then they will take them off.
Shut up and like accept your pickles and then she takes the pickles off herself.
I think it's kind of weird too.
I like pickles so I'm not going to like make a big fuss about it.
I mean if it's tomatoes I'll tell them no tomatoes because that's like satanic.
Okay.
So you mentioned earlier that if you had a choice you wouldn't go to McDonald's.
So where would you where would you go instead?
Well when I lived in Boston you know this place Boston right.
Oh yeah I've watched it I know that shitty Boston.
Okay yeah so like there was a u-burger great place.
You know u-burger of course.
Yes.
And across the street there was a McDonald's and the McDonald's always had people walking
into it and I was like what a bunch of fucking morons right.
So it really depends on the location like in that case I'm going to u-burger.
But hold on hold on hold on you have got this all wrong.
I'm supporting local business wherever possible.
You got this all wrong here's first of all McDonald's is way faster than a restaurant
like u-burger.
You can literally drive to the drive-through or walk in and have your meal in literally
like 30 to 40 seconds.
Nice nice eye by the way.
Hopefully it heals like the rest of the entire world.
I was laughing I had a one of the gas tanks and it blew up during the cut scene.
It was right behind us.
I hope we're not dead.
Oh she's dead.
She died of a black right eye.
You did it again.
Oh my god anyways.
We'll talk about this after we fight the tyrant okay.
Oh yeah did you remember in dying light one the guy would always say oh fuck it fuck this
fucker just fucking guy was snotting his goon fucker.
I don't know how to change weapons back to my good weapon because it's my one weapon
but my one is my throwies.
Are you looking for crystals or are you making me do all the work?
Looking for crystals.
Yes that's the mission.
Oh I thought we got to kill the guy.
He just lit himself up he just walked right through the fire.
Yeah threw a bottle at him.
Oh wait what about this?
Okay so you were going to say something about my desire to support local business over McDonald's.
No what I said was there's a huge difference.
You burger is on a different tier than McDonald's is.
Are we doing a tier list?
That's like saying oh you know the local like authentic Italian restaurant down the street from
my house is what exactly versus but versus like a fast Italian like food place.
You always have a choice everyone's always like oh chipotle so like fucking
what chipotle is like wait the fence you want to you die on fences now.
What?
Like what people talk about chipotle.
Hold on I just I just threw this tank at him and did half his health by hitting him in the head.
Okay we'll do it again.
All right listen to me it's the how much it costs how fast it is how are you in a hurry
do you want to sit down at like a restaurant right like because you could order takeout
from some of these places but it's it's not the same as getting like a cheeseburger from McDonald's.
Okay well what is a ron?
A what?
You can go in and you sit down and you can rest but you can also ron.
Ron?
Ron restaurant like which like trick or treat I understand that restaurant I don't understand.
But anyway let's get back to the point that we were making before.
Very important point McDonald's and you burger are not on the same tier of restaurant.
In fact I would probably assume that's what I'm saying though is
that's exactly what I'm saying you get to choose the tier of place you go.
Yes but the different tiers exist for very specific reasons.
You get McDonald's within like five minutes of walking in the restaurant.
New burger is fast food as well.
But it's not it's not the same fast food.
It's gonna get better and it's probably more expensive.
Probably how much how much is a single like I don't know I've been years since I've done.
Okay but it's more expensive and it's gonna take a little longer to get your food.
So if you okay you got 20 minutes.
Oh shit okay there's a you burger right here there's McDonald's right here.
I have literally 20 minutes before I have to go to my thing I'm doing.
You're not gonna go order like a burger from you burger
because it's gonna take it's gonna take a little longer.
It doesn't take 20 minutes.
But you want to make sure that you can just get in there get your two double cheeseburgers.
Have you ever shown up on time for anything you're going to you burger?
Oh I might be like 10 minutes late.
Like you're you're not thinking about this when you're going into the restaurant.
All right but the point still stands.
There are oh movement speed.
McDonald's there's a tier McDonald's Wendy's Burger King Carl's Jr. Arby's.
This tier I'm morally opposed to the tier.
You'd go to Arby's wouldn't you?
Say it.
I've actually had a really good Arby's sandwich.
Oh and look at that he's gonna go to Arby's instead of McDonald's.
That's exactly what I was talking about.
I went to Arby's over McDonald's.
I'm sorry like was that a problem?
Yeah that's actually a huge problem.
I took Carl hostage.
What's wrong with Arby's?
It's all right.
Exactly I'm helping Sophie get him back.
I knew you were gonna be a guy that was gonna go to Arby's instead of McDonald's.
I mean Arby's I've only ever been like once.
Okay I've only been to Arby's because going on like
a bus like an actual public transport bus between Boston and New York they would stop at an Arby's
and it's like hey if you guys want food we're stopping at Arby's you don't have a choice.
So what did you get at Arby's?
I don't know I don't even know what any of their sandwiches are called.
Have you been to Jack in the Box before?
Jack in the Box and Sonic which I think are the same place both kind of just grossed me out and
I don't think I've ever been.
You're right about Sonic.
You got Sonic correct.
Is Jack in the Box another IHOP?
No.
Oh no there's Jack in the Box is not equivalent.
There's like Jenny's IHOP and Jack in the Box.
No no no he's wrong again.
Okay listen Jack in the Box is like a McDonald's.
I've I've never been so I'm just okay.
Jack in the Box is like a McDonald's but they have literally every food ever invented.
I think you can order fucking spaghetti at Jack in the Box.
Besides that did you have to do that?
No I didn't know.
Come help me.
Okay so we have to go to a trashy fast food like we have to.
There's no it has to happen.
What is your number one pick?
It's always McDonald's always.
Well how is it always McDonald's?
Because I like McDonald's and it's consistent and it's fun and it's delicious
and they had a clown it was Ronald McDonald's like really cool and
if you're going to McDonald's because of the marketing because of the clown.
Ronald McDonald's like cool and they got rid of them.
Have you guys noticed this they stir when was the last time you you don't go to McDonald's
so you do you can't relate to this.
I mean they're everywhere so I've seen them but no I understand Ronald McDonald's is really
they're kind of phasing them out.
Yeah they turned McDonald's into like a weird little like cafe.
They took out all the McDonald's there's no more grimace.
I I do feel like they're trying to Starbucks it up.
I I I get what you're saying there.
The food is still it's still the same though but they're trying to get rid of Ronald McDonald's
and they're replacing him with like yeah like a Starbucks window.
I don't think they did him I you know if they want how would this you know what I would have
been okay with if Ronald McDonald took the makeup off and he was Ronald and it was like look he's
a regular guy it's like Ron like Ronald like have him take the makeup off and just be like
a regular guy like what's the problem why do you have to get rid of him.
I don't know I could I could be down with a Ronald.
Like you know that he like puts the makeup on and like this like makes like people happy and stuff
but stop throwing bombs at me that would be creepy what
my god please the zombies over there got a couple dead yeah he would be Ronald McDonald right
like but if we just he wouldn't be the clown he'd be like a regular guy with
maybe they could keep the hair I don't I don't know what they would do
keep the nose I'm surprised like there's one thing in my life it's okay it's probably a
problem with me there's probably a lot of people that have no problem with us if someone orders
food they're like a an order food app yeah and it's McDonald's I'm like morally posed and there's
a nauseated disgusting feeling in the put in my stomach really yeah to see like oh here's your
delivery with like the McDonald's M on it it's just like you would you stay friends with this person
I wouldn't have you would you would avoid this fucking person we would you've definitely done
yeah we would avoid this person but this is what I'm saying you're like oh there's just 20 minutes
do you stop at a McDonald's okay you can order food from anywhere a person will magically appear
and be generated by the universe bring it to your door and then like disassemble as they leave
and you chose McDonald's oh but but what if it's not enough what if they're not open some
McDonald's is open if nothing else is open but when is nothing else but McDonald's open
I guarantee I get this in the window or I'll give a hundred community stops
thank you the point is if you are going to be in a scenario where you need something fast
yeah you don't have to order like uber eats McDonald's all the time right but McDonald's
is usually faster than all of them is usually cheaper than all of them but I like it so that's
all I have to say what is your argument is if there's you could just say you like it I like
the dogs you can be wrong it's cool it's not being wrong oh I think less of you but
okay then you have to answer me this question yeah McDonald's Burger King Wendy's Jack in the
Box Arby's where are you going if you had to pick one if I had to pick one of those
I think every time that's fair I think this guy's we're gonna kill this guy
permission that's fair will you help me kill this guy yeah hold on I thought you just puked
because like you thought he was gross I don't have enough stamina for these there's another
thing over here but no fast food I genuinely like McDonald's there's something else with it too
and you can call me oh cringe cringe cringe cringe Andy well I don't know when I was a kid
going to McDonald's was oh let's get I'm gonna get like five four nuggets I'm gonna get a happy meal
it's like a comfort food it's like oh yeah I like I love the nuggets from the comments right
doesn't have to be like restaurant quality high quality well it is a restaurant so it's
it is restaurant quality but which one would you choose restaurant if I wanted to go sit at a
restaurant of course my palate is enormous I'm dying hold up I have such a sophisticated palette
I could eat like the nicest sushi in the world and then have an uber eats delivered to the
restaurant at McDouble and I would be really happy about it oh what's this oh salmon sashimi
oh my god it's so buttery in your mouth oh yeah the orders over here for me yeah I had the 10
nuggets and the two cheeseburgers how did I get in here you know what it's fine you can like what
you like the person that said the venom movie was terrible and that he was pissed that it even came
out I what says the guy that was pissed at the venom movie came out and said the venom movie
was terrible and all if you would like the venom movie you're an idiot remember that one I didn't
say that but I wouldn't disagree what the fuck are we doing like where are you I've been doing
in circles come over to me I don't know where you are I'm just like bouncing into buildings
over and over again I'm trying to press Q for my supervision
this really is like a crack stream tonight my character can't climb ladders anymore what the
fuck is I need your help I'm bleeding out quick I actually did now I'll admit McDonald's is the best
I'll admit it all right no no I'll only revive you if you do the song I'll do the whole song
you have to do you have to say ba ba ba ba and you got to put a lot into it or you're not
getting revived I will do it I'll do it do it too late you dead I'm dead where do you go from here
I pull you was that you're just asking me what happens after you die no no I mean like because
you're the host so you can pull me I don't think I can pull you I don't think you can pull me I
respond okay well let's just go to the mission okay I'll meet you there sir I will gift I will
gift 25 community subs in your channel if you do ba ba ba ba ba but you really lean into it
and it has to be good and I'm the judge on if it's good or not 25 is how much I don't know
I started low because I figured you were going to negotiate I'm doing the math of like okay
McDonald's comes to your stream is like okay we're going to sponsor your stream and you have to like
really like we're going to judge you on how good this is and we're going to pay you like
50 bucks okay so you're saying you want more I'm saying okay that math was way off
for for like a sponsorship deal from McDonald's of like doing their logo
it's gonna have to be a you know and dude it's gotta it's gotta be like it's gotta be like
like you gotta really go hard yeah 50 50 community subs I mean that's that's I'm not going for it no
really okay 100 like you're I could tell like you're absolutely holding out on 100 community
subs I'll do it I'm telling you right now you need this better be good or else the money's
off the table if you you get one chance who gets to judge me you're never gonna think it's good
enough no I their number one fan I'll know if I'll know if you're giving it a half-assed attempt
I've known you for a long time it's got to be that I can I can give it the full attempt
and it won't be good does that still count by the way hope account hope hopefully my credit card
doesn't get declined because otherwise this whole thing is over yeah like you're you're homeless I
you don't even have 100 gift subs are you ready I need I want the I want the volume of this game
to be done gone by the way I want to bowl I want to hear this okay am I I was still questioning
if I do it and it's bad is bad the same as not trying no no I don't know that I'm okay you
uh you're gonna give it an attempt I'm gonna I'll give it to you 100 community subs
nah what nah it's honestly not worth what are you serious yeah what the fuck I have to go higher
I mean it's my integrity when we all agree that McDonald's is disgusting
I didn't say that all right 125 community subs I don't know I feel like any second someone's
gonna give me 100 to not do it the longer we stall I feel like we're kind of getting into that
territory he's not gonna do it like don't you all get to see fucking mr. Scrooge miser drama get
what he wants all the time he just buys people shouldn't I stand up to him no no nobody stands
up to me I'm not doing it oh what fuck I'll do it it can't not be done I'm loving it that's you
just you could just add you could have just had a thousand dollars sir that was trying like that's
your bar for trying really hard that was good give me the barrel back I'll do that I'll do better
no no you're not taking it's off the table beat you there's no deal at all no you you declined it
give me the barrel no you're not taking about because the deal is off you declined it you
declined the deal so you're not getting another chance the deal's off you didn't want to do it I
don't I don't like I said I don't need the money I just want to do it because like you're making a
fool of yourself up here and you're like what did you do it I didn't hear anything oh really
that cut out my discord saved you that joke didn't land then do you want to try again okay try again
I'm loving it off the fucking barrel get off the barrel that was awful get off the barrel
yeah and I'm loving it you'll never do better than that there's not a fucking chance in hell
well you are we doing like beatboxing no I'm just saying that that that was
incredible no one will do better than that yeah my chat saying it was forced what it's an ad of
course no there's not an ad I'm not this this is not sponsored this is not a sponsored stream
let me make that clear I'm just saying like the jingle is an ad
so it has to be like just go just do your thing please hold on hold on so like like we can like
you don't just do the jingle like the longer you do like some cringy shit before like
I'm loving it oh like the more you do like the better you think it is let's go to the mission
marker in the commercial they don't go
what are you doing well what were you doing you were doing like
you know you're like they don't like moan they don't they also don't beatbox
we just finished the mission for god's sake Ronald would be disappointed
oh cool all right mission time yeah wow you're never gonna get out of the tutorial zone
is this whole zone a tutorial we apparently are taking so long okay well I'm here I'll play
you're not here I'll be there in a sec also it it cut out you didn't hear I did not hear you
at all I heard for like a solid five seconds I screamed at the top of my lungs are you serious
yeah you discord did not like that all that we heard on my stream was
I guess that means I should wait here oh yeah discord was like noise cancellation you're gone
look at the clip hold on let me see what happened to the game uh we're inhibiting
what yourself up here this is what you did yeah and you're like
what did you do it I didn't hear anything it's like you just screamed in my face and I don't
hear that that's like I'm baiting you that has to be bullshit right yeah no I'm pretty sure discord
will like you can do stuff like you can snap your fingers if you're not talking and the snap won't
go through discord that was ridiculous but you screamed for so long you would think it would come
through yeah I thought like a little like even the beginning of it would but no are we in like
a dream yeah we are you got any you got any opinions on dreams that I don't know about I
feel like that's a thing you'd have a like a whole bit about what about dreaming yeah I don't know
it just seems like a thing that you'd be into I mean it's kind of interesting that we do that
our brains are so overactive that even while they're turned off they have to be functioning
and have to be doing things like a shark it's pretty weird oh is this like where we remember
that the girl we've been looking for this whole time actually burned alive and we don't need to
look for anymore and the game's over it's weird why that guy show up yeah is he a part of the dream
are you downloading um lego star wars angry birds whatever it was uh no I had a bad feeling about
it from the start he kind of lied to us then I said I would try anything once I did oh I mean
like I like if someone put it in front of me I would try it was a whole other story when you
don't like you gotta like if you manage to take out those I don't have an ipad jack cock this
game's fun okay meat has anyone ever told you it's weird that you call them community subs
by peace immunity subs yeah like community gifted subs I've never heard anyone say that ever and do
me a favor um scroll over the uh the gifted sub I'm sure that's what the full like long
exact phrasing of it is I'm sure it is but it seems weird like when you could say like gifted
subs oh but it's the same that's literally the definition of what it is it's a community sub
it's a gifted community it's a community sub I'm not disagreeing oh what do you call it a
gift thanks for the gifted subs thanks for the community subs gift it just gifted it's shorter
yeah but I mean it's classified as a community sub there are prime subs right there are community
subs and then there are like regular subs right but but when when the thing happens it will say
so-and-so gifted 10 subs they gifted a gifted 10 community subs are we reaching for like content
right now for like funny things no I was I thought there was one of those things there
oh there is okay watch out guys we got one of those things there is a tutorial area
oh it's 40 meters oh it comes to chase let's see what you have what it takes to beat me
I'm fucking done I'm done I'm being chased what happened you're dying I got tutorial yeah you're
dying in the oh there's like a super monster above you I think that's like an ultra volatile oh
what the fuck is this can you help me I'm bleeding out I'm dead god damn it oh my I thought you had
way more time I lost 113 community subs for that and I thought you're gonna say I lost like 10
quarts of blood I'm being chased oh it is like a super mutant do you want to try to kill him
I don't think we can I think so volatile it's kind of right in the way that I want to go
unless we run from him for like six hours and he falls into a fence you can't kill him
it's a container right here I don't know you probably don't care though I'm coming back to
you I made a loop around I lost him it's he's over here the big super mutant guys over here
he's he literally can see us right now he can see you they can't people saying that we can
people said we can kill this thing easily they think we're overreacting okay let's do it I'm
chasing this like thing I can't even what the fuck dude hey I just what has a homing missiles into
his stomach I just got a loot goblin oh it's daytime now maybe he'll just die oh he's gone
they play the five nights at Freddy's thing when you get to like 6 a.m. I guess uh we can't open
this let's just do the mission we got the like military truck here if you want to you know oh
sure the mission is also right there okay can we do more than one of these locks oh and there's
a 15 meters to an inhibitor yeah it's like right here I'm trying to find it
oh it's in it's inside here it's inside of this thing I don't know how to change my weapon
three oh I get it I thought it was okay okay just it's just three I think we have to go
in through the roof one two three four this doesn't open are we going to open this oh we have to kill
the monster that's annoying I was there's a night mission we can wait till night let's just do it
let's kill it wait how do we do that the mission we're doing is right here all right fine
we could also sleep too yeah I don't know what stir doesn't want to sleep we haven't slept in
the entire five hours we played the game I don't know how you just press e next to a bed
no come here right we need all people for this guy behind you there's honey here though and
it's important that you get it there is honey here it is important he's correct
that's actually not a joke important to have why are you not watching the super bowl all right
wait wait ready so who's in the super bowl the rams and the bangles the patriots all right
what is the score of the game right now stir don't look at your chat I'm going to give you a guess
don't give any time I think it's I think it's I think it's I think it's 10 10 3 rams what's
your guess say it before you had zero zero zero zero all right what is it 16 to 20 right now
oh 20 to 2016 bangles winning what do you want how much time is left in the game right in you can't
sophie sophies stop gambling take care of yourself pilgrims join the party want to
party how do we how how do we wait I don't know so you'd go to the nighttime mission and hold
to you but that's like a nighttime mission down there shouldn't we be there's like a bed in here
we can sleep in the bed there's no bed as long as we can actually uh somebody told us earlier
that some safe houses do not have a bed the safe house sucks what's the point I don't know it's
right it's little it's 56 meters away oh my god what am I doing I thought I could grab onto the
edge oh you heal at these oh my god you can just heal with us we can go to the windmill
windmill is over here right you want to go to the maple windmill uh aren't we doing like there's
our main quest like 50 meters away behind you yeah that we're that we're currently on and we
keep talking about how we're gonna do it and then we start talking about McDonald's for like an hour
yeah but I mean so what what else do you talk about when you're like gaming with a buddy what
um I mean I'm not judging the McDonald's conversation I'm just saying you know right
this objective and I feel like we should finish it I'm gonna get McDonald's tonight just because
you said that you're gonna order McDonald's on Super Bowl Sunday night what's wrong with that
you're gonna eat your McDonald's by yourself what are we doing here what do you think I'm
what do you think I'm by myself what are we doing here all players required I don't know
oh for what there's a thing here we can proceed where you say you're dead now fucker I'm looking
for yeah he said we're dead looking at I don't feel too well uh my throat's sore don't want you
to catch anything somebody's in trouble right near here all I hear is let me go help oh wait
wait where'd Sophie go wait what the fuck is this guy attacking me
I can't even take my weapon out of this guy in the cutscene this guy hacks the cutscene Jesus
Christ I can't do anything who is this guy wait why am I back up I've revived you I did it
why can't I attack him because you're in like a cutscene area he's like crawling deep
oh not in the cutscene anymore huh tough guy huh now we have to redo that here we're in a mask
wait a minute wait a minute somebody at this site had a mask on we first touched random
some random dude just started picking a fight what I saw him in the corner of my eye he was
just hanging out are we gonna ask around to find out where Sophie went who are we asking
we we got that cutscene screwed up we have to talk to the people here I'm looking for
if you could oh what did she say I don't know what does this guy have to say said ask around
this guy seems like he knows something how many years ago did the zombie thing happen
two I think yeah it's been two talk to this guy talk to this guy talk to this guy talk no behind
you talk to this guy talk to this guy I can't talk to this guy I don't have this guy talk to
this guy talk to this guy I am you're annoying what did you say oh I don't I don't have time
and maybe and thank that was really sad he looked really sad right there
if we killed his friend he's wondering where he went talk to this person okay oh I think it's
gonna be a big flurry night tonight I thought you said you don't get McFlurry's yeah but you
mentioned it I'll change it up do you like do you like the M&Ms in it when it turns all like brown
are you able to repair weapons I don't think so maybe I thought there was like a repair kit
thing just a hater delirious to it who am I hating McDonald's why you had you just you said like
three times you hate McDonald's um we should do this it's right here no repairs you got to craft
all that shit on your weapon then it breaks and you got to do it again every time are you aware
of what IGN's game of all time is ocarina of time they made a revised list of their game
I just I don't know what what was number one breath of the wild is now the new best game of all time
isn't yeah what's in the top five is there more than there I can't remember it was all very
upsetting but isn't breath of the wild and clicks isn't breath of the wild supposed to be really
good how could breath of the wild be any good when it all it did was coffee genshin in fact
would you rather it be ocarina of time can we be honest I would feel like I could see where they
were coming from if it was ocarina of time right but like it's ocarina of time is what everybody
says I get it's ocarina of time the best game ever made in all of history is on the Nintendo
switch so what oh turn turn around and look is this what you're saying look at how beautiful the
graphics are it's so wonderful this wouldn't run on a switch that's what you're saying so a game
can't be good if it has like not incredible beautiful I would say 10 out of 10 direct x12
I think graphics with the foliage the entire history of game development if you really think
about like what is the best thing if you just narrowed it down to what like what's your favorite
game of all time favorite game of all time yeah hide the sausage what the fuck is that
I mean you could play that on anything what's your favorite video game of all time I'm jumping
why are you jumping it got blocked we're gonna go down there to meet Sophie uh favorite video
game of all time you alive yes okay if ocarina of time is is acceptable to you breath of the
wild is not acceptable to you what is acceptable to you as number one like you what is your number
one like or at least something in the top well no this is about what is acceptable to me or what
I would choose what would you choose is not the best game of all time okay so what if I had to
wait a minute most acceptable one so you're saying that people have opinions yeah people
have opinions okay so what is your favorite McDonald's what's your favorite game of all time
um I feel like I'm gonna forget because I haven't ever like played one I could tell you but mine is
if it doesn't help you if it's Diablo 2 or like Bloodborne wait you close you had it it's I had
it it's probably Bloodborne that's probably my favorite game of all time but the reason why I'm
saying maybe not is because it only released on ps4 at 30 fps yeah it's just like it yeah so like
wouldn't it suck if the best game of all time was only on the Nintendo Switch yeah but still it
Bloodborne is like sorry for Bloodborne it's making you question it Diablo 2 the wild you're
like I don't know because I don't because I don't particularly because you don't want to
pick this fight because there's people in chat that are like me your breath of wild and you
don't want to like upset them and but you'll be like all Bloodborne sir I I talked a like a full
college essay about how I don't like the Zelda games so you're barking up the absolute wrong tree
Diablo 2 Team Fortress 2 and Bloodborne and um
that goes pretty damn good but that's not it was it was a fun list because of how lazy it looks
like around number 50 is all of the blizzard games it's just like oh I don't know Starcraft
Diablo World of Warcraft like whatever it's just one blizzard game that was made by Blizzard North
like 25 years ago I'm gonna hit you with this because you're a big fan okay World of Warcraft
was like top 50 in this top 100 list game of all times yeah I agree I think around top 10 or 20
was Final Fantasy 14 it's got the most guards are we talking about like cultural impact are we talking
just like what game was actually the best like video game I don't know I think I think it was
the best that still holds up if anything goes wrong we retreat to our base okay well you're
you're dashing you're dashing that you're you're dodging the question I'm dashing I'm dodging
what is your favorite game of all time I think it actually would be like the other two are
Bloodborne oh we're on the same page here so we completely agree okay yeah that's why we know
we're both right oh that's how we know our opinion is correct because we both have it oh yeah okay
like if anyone else were to come into the conversation and that's and that's not a
problem right that's not a problem well we have majority yeah you and I have the same opinion
therefore it's correct that's kind of how it works we're doing monkey bars right now kind of
I'm just I'm just vibing man all right so here you go so Diablo 2 obviously right uh blizzard
blizzard game yeah blizzard game why is it telling me how to do stealth right now we're getting a lot
of these we're getting a lot of these why does this game have four tutorials Jack and Jack and Joe's
camp is this Joe who is this that might be Joe behind you this is the same guy I think that
guy's on our side the warrior wait whose team are we on I don't know I think we're on blue
did you just hit me who's this person you're dying man
I don't okay I'm just gonna kill everybody just kill everyone yep I knew it what did you get them
oh I don't usually going back up here no I don't want to eat that I have a question
no uh what what are these pointed spikes preventing from coming forward like what
is this preventing helicopters uh like an orc invasion they're like things that they they put
on the side to climb up the building all right so we gotta we gotta go kill the jack and joe uh
jumpers oh we got jumpers that's true they do jump that guy has a one of those tape measure son
song machine things what does this thing do oh why are you silent me so much more menacing
when you don't say anything I yelled like on my screen he sprinted off this platform at like
10 times speed and then teleport it back and you're like why is he alive well I'm
because because he what is this what is this fucking nobody's coming man we killed everybody
here oh my what they're gonna keep trying to come up the ladder I'll take care of the guys on the
ladder oops oh he's doing he's doing it again he's doing it again it's I think it's working
it kind of it kind of is working wow wow get off he's dead hi I'm help I got I got this guy
I'm bludgeoning his face I'm bludgeoning his face I'm your savior I'm bludgeoning it thanks dude
more people are just coming up what is jack and jill uh jack and jill went up the hill
okay I need to craft a healer something man yeah I'm dying man where all these people live dude
there's a giant skyscraper right here okay this is fine city they're apparently still in here
there's a bunch of people down there at the um at the cultist symbol there's one of them oh do you
do that too do you call every human enemy in every game a cultist I know I don't I was literally
talking about this like weird symbol altar that they have set up I don't know why I'm always like
oh cultists yeah there's some cultists here by the way have you noticed that like oh look
out bandits there's bandits everywhere bandits all right guys doing the thing there are more
bandits in video games than people that are populating the actual towns have you noticed
this of course I've noticed this it's like for every one person that lives in these game worlds
there's like five thousand bandits well in order for them to sell me this game they need to
satiate my unquenchable thirst for blood and destruction
so like I have to kill this music machine guy is still up here he's gonna throw a rock at you man
you missed the first thing you unlock is this jump from the air kick how I'll distract him
oh my face what's that what's that song that's that song that plays why are we here why are
there a bunch of people coming all right bring him over here so I can do my jump kick I mean how
do you do it I don't know I think it's e or f you jump and hit it's e because the kick is e
what the fuck it didn't do anything that's what I'm saying god are we both dead
you can't believe it it's jumping f since you swapped I checked I unlocked it yeah it's whatever
your kick button is I did I press you press you do you have it unlocked I do I've never been able
to do it air kicks first thing when dropping on enemies from above nail them with a power kick
all in the air look down at an enemy and hold e behind the air look down I mean hold f to execute
all right well let's go kill that motherfucker let's go it's still e even if you change it
really no it's not it's a bug with binding somebody said there's a bug with binding
that guy's lying to you don't listen to him I feel like they're correct though don't don't
even listen well I'm I never rebind it and I still can't do it somebody said I wish your
computer was still bad I said why so I mean this is like a clean like 60 fps this is I help you
hey just take it out of my hands what happened what my hand is still my hand is still on it
what look I'm what I have no idea what happened there all right where is this guy
isn't he right here no we got weird is that the cultist he's a cultist oh yeah he's a cultist
yeah I call every human enemy a cultist or a bandit oh I did it I think it really
got him I got him oh you please our town you must go and just defeat the bandits that are
attacking our encampment okay how many people live here 12 how much was the population of the
city 15 000 okay so there there are there are there are 11 990 bandits stay away same joke
is five minutes ago I was really I was adding to it a lot of people join the stream that you
don't know how many people to come in and come out a lot of people didn't hear the joke I was
we took jack and joe's camp oh dude look at this we got great oh selling level two
the bomber man look at this shark teeth that's like buying the shark teeth I'm getting a vine
I'm gonna buy this hat too because who cares I'm gonna buy this too I mean honestly who gives a
hoot and a holler at this point come here let's be realistic here all right can I modify this with a
I'm gonna modify this with poison and I'm gonna put a rare weapon charm on this
how's it look I can't use a weapon why not you don't have enough strength some armor on you oh
yeah I have armor on if you ever need something just ask for Christopher Carl nice nice oh I got
a legendary why is every game an Ubisoft game oh I think this is better than an Ubisoft game
we're attacked I say that because it runs oh there's a homie hole let me show you my
Ubisoft game experience I'm going to look from this side of the screen to this side of the screen
oh what I need you you'll agree with me on this okay you stand here and you look in the room
like that's your room that's like your streamer den wouldn't it be really cool if you had a like
like how would dogs have the hole you can look walk in the room and see you've got a homie hole
so like your your homies can just like come in and join you at any time and it has like the
dog flap like hey what's up guys I mean you this is like the streamer room lighting yeah yeah but
also you've just got like a hole in the wall so your friends can come in why would I want this
I just told you why because because of my friends can come in yeah like you know like your webcam
isn't pointed there it's like you can't come through the door and like people know you're
coming in so you need to like come in in the homie hole and that comes out like under your
desk or something what why would it be under the desk I can't believe I let them fool me like
well so it's like a secret so you can like hide and crawl under the desk so okay you're telling me
that you want the desk here sitting here and you want a spot for someone to be able to come under
here under the desk why do you have like an L desk because they can like crawl under the whole L
what are you talking about that's pretty cool what like isn't that like fun did you ever do those
uh you like McDonald's right the ball pit and I love that place tunnels you can crawl through
or is that Chuck E Cheese you know Chuck E Cheese yeah I was last time you were at Chuck E Cheese
uh I went one time when I was very young did you ever bring your report card to get free tokens
I don't think so I remember that being a thing though if you had at least I've told the story
before but I'm telling it again if you had at least A or B average and you brought your report
card to Chuck E Cheese they would give you like 20 free tokens and it was a huge deal to every kid
and in the in the town and neighborhood whatever it was like oh I get free tokens Chuck E Cheese
so I would I had a brother and sister obviously right so we would go and I would have like Ds
and Cs I was a fucking dumb kid right and they would always just kind of lump me in with my
brother and sister that had A's and B's so I'd be like oh here's your report card you've got oh
yes you do you've got A's here are your 20 tokens kiddo and then like my brother oh here you go
here's your 20 tokens and they're like my mother would kind of be like oh and don't forget about
him too oh he's got and he would kind of look he would look at the card and be like oh yeah
of course of course you're gonna get 20 free tokens if you're that guy you can't be like
not sorry dumb kids don't get tokens yeah sorry idiots don't get anything why don't you try a
little harder and I wonder if I thought my report card was good I was like yeah I did good in school
and I got free tokens all the while my my poor mother's probably just like god damn I couldn't
have we had to like we had to like lumping in with the other kids oh fuck hey you coming
I mean I'm not the brightest bulb but I have a lot of power okay I may not be the brightest bulb
but I last a long time and I'll never let you down I'll always turn on you coming I'm trying
to climb to the top of this thing there's nothing at the top there was absolutely nothing out there
catch me I'm fine wow you're wearing like you're wearing like cool guy clothes did you oh you can
put your gear on you have to turn on I gotta turn on my gear you actually have to go into your like
equipment man I know but like I don't I don't think I didn't get any gear you don't have anything I
mean I'm wearing like a roadie vest I guess I have this quarterback okay that's a quarterback
jersey who said you're not an only child there are more of you I'm more I have like a family
well it's not like we're not all me walking around oh thank god I finally can get this
yeah I don't like eat food after midnight and like have gremlins come off my back
wouldn't that be like cool though don't feed him after midnight don't feed him McDonald's after
midnight you see like this is stupid right now isn't it well we need to make a choice
as Sophie was cooler I have to go okay what I'm saying like we're knocking a front door hey can
you let me in like wouldn't it be so much better if you just had a homie hole uh yeah that's cool
you just have a hole opening up to the outside of your house no it has a flap like a dog door
that's fine but anybody can just go through it so that's fine and you and you wake up one morning
and like your ps5 is gone and so is your tv okay your like just open side of your house
is cool until um until the ps5 is gone you can't like lock that you you you couldn't lock it
you're talking about putting a bike lock on a ps5 no on the door flap there's no conceivable
way that you could prevent someone from crawling in from the outside I mean yeah it's called a door
with a lock on it the door has a lock on it and also you can like slide down a covering for the
homie hole like I'm not expecting any homies today so you lock you close it so why don't you
just have a door to your house I would have it open as often as possible would you have the
front door to your house open all day all day all day uh yeah okay well then never mind do you like
just not trust people you just failed that by the way let a real lock pick over here please
you're the lock pick guy so I backed up oh nice that's a nerd stick and what is that also can I
ask what is every game has these doors that look like they're like sliding doors that come down
that are like this is the locked line door yeah why because it's to convey that you cannot go
through here because there's nothing to open but these kinds of doors don't exist yeah they do
only in hotel rooms and then you get embarrassed taking a shit in that room because it actually
doesn't even close it's like sliding like a closet door closed and you're like I don't want
to take a shit in here I have no idea what you're talking about the only time I've ever seen a
sliding door like that was in a hotel bathroom okay those doors fucking suck yeah and in between
all the question marks somebody understands what I'm saying where did you go uh the roof I swear
to god I'm fucking I think I'm done what I fell off I think you're done no I'm not can I not I
have to climb up there from a different place he fell off L ratio yeah okay yeah I was just
as confused as you were we have to go in the house I needed another tutorial why don't you just climb
the rope can I get up there from here I don't know where I'm in like an obstacle course someone
set up I can't get up to the building again where does this go what is the point who am I
what's my motivation can I climb on that I'm kind of lost I need to do the obstacle course yeah
you know I gotta get find a way back over here the yellow blind streamer I'm super blind
like I think I was supposed to go there it didn't seem like I was gonna make it
it's barbed wire here what we're both like equally lost right now oh well I wouldn't
butter dead what do you mean dead I died how do I get up there oh there's uh there's an
inhibitor container ah what the fuck where are you what why did that happen where the fuck are you
trying to climb up on this thing oh good we're all we're all caught up why does he keep what's
going on with this uh can you help yeah how do I get up there I'm helping I have to go through the
house it was open up the hole that you have I think the stick launches you that'd be kind of
crazy I have to go through the house I'm just gonna let him do it I I mean there's an inhibitor
here and you can't teleport me fuck okay I need to get up there wait wait wait wait no no no no no
no don't teleport teleport teleport teleport teleport teleport teleport teleport come to the
homey hole real quick all right 10 nuggets two double cheeseburgers man it's nine large frying
for the day we've been having fun man the time just kind of flies and you're having a good time
all right come back here other way gas can move oh don't touch that yo inhibit this all right
I'm gonna do stamina again hey man do you like berries not really I'm honest yeah bury this
dick in your mouth there's other questions over here you're on thin ice you're on thin ice
why do we do that when we stretch um to alert the horde you just censored that
he went oh shit you just actually censored him
wait does everyone betray us like literally like wait like we have to fight your goons now
oh no bandits these guys are still level one oh my god yeah why are they all one
he's dead dude so now we have to chase him
roll him up into against a wall and be like what do you know I don't know anything
where's Mia he's gonna have a detonator in his hand he's gonna have a fucking detonator in his
hand oh there's a bunch of uh the camomile out here I press this button and we all go boom
I better not press him he seems crazy enough to do it I think I got all the stuff there's a lot
of stuff up here I mean if you're into looting kind of like a looter shooter kind of situation
why don't we just throw that is that a brick oh my god it's a brick oh my god there's a brick in
the game yeah yeah no I want that back the brick okay do you think that the a brick
is like the perfect comedy weapon yeah something about it it's funny I was gonna say like oh yeah
brick like throwing a brick at somebody's just like it's such a dense rectangle object it's
kind of like it was made for hitting people in the head with there's someone at that door
where this guy's just standing on the other side of this door use your your hunter vision
you see that guy no you don't feel like a red outline that's scary yeah what do you think he
wants I don't know you figures I don't know we skipped the whole thing here comes the boss battle
music
I turned music down we don't even I can't even tell what it sounds like
keep mopping for a second oh you got a black eye that means he's almost dead oh he's blinking he's
blinking he's blinking a family guy joke did I steal that from family guy what I don't know
what the joke is like nothing about it sounded funny so maybe it's from family guy fuck that's
a family guy joke it is yeah we're Sophie now we're gonna get up there he's still alive he's
still making sounds let me get out of here have you ever heard the dead gurgle hate that word
gurgle gurgle yeah we can go up here oh where oh and then from here we have to go
my character couldn't do it my guy you know bad guys what movie is that from what movie is that
from what movie is that from what movie is that from what movie is that from um gorillas nope
where'd you come from I've got a sixth sense something be careful I always knew we could count
on Carlos okay you can't hit yourself in the head with a brick okay um the honey uh by the way how
are you doing me you okay you good I don't know I don't feel for long are you I mean it's been
about six hours you're all right you want to keep going you want to stop how do you feel
okay I can keep going okay we can keep going all players are required to go in this door
oh oh you're in the gas can room have you reached a thousand of your experience bar for rating the
game um we're definitely still in just the fifth tutorial if you ask nicely I'll shoot you in the
head yeah and if not you'll spend a long time dying until you turn so she'll be the one dying
Barney no you stop him not kill him give me the weapon give it to me brother hope you know what
you're doing what I don't know what you didn't say you were working for eight
I don't work so no one can remain neutral in this for survival without water the whole bizarre
will die in under a month the peacekeepers they won't help us just like when my mom died
what are you laughing at you're just a funny guy what try me yeah try me tell me who killed
who are these people the more things we did it waste of time shoot this is your last chance
sophie tell me who killed lucas before I break down this door what are you donkey kong this
just made it a steal but this does remind me of my favorite scene ever from one of my favorite
shows of all time the crazy new adventures of I came first name I couldn't I tried to stall
what Sabrina the teenage witch he has the new show my favorite scene of all time in all television
ever is is what happened yes oh man she like she just acts like she's so incredible all the time
and she just walks into rooms and solves the problems instantly but there's one part of the
show where she walks into this room is like I'm here Sabrina's gonna stop and they just
instantly cut to her getting shot with the crossbow and like the people just don't listen to her
what that's kind of funny yeah it is it's very very comedic timing what the hell you are supposed
to launch off of it chat was right I thought they were bullshitting me yeah you have to jump off
of it is that in the Olympics pole vaulting oh if I okay if I type in like what do you say the show
is so then whatever the new Sabrina the teenage which is where she's like hip and edgy on Sabrina
the teenage witch crossbow maybe you'll find it I find it if you find it I it's one of those things
I like rewatched like 10 times in a row but it really helps when you have the buildup of like how
this has gone in her favor for like three seasons oh I can't I don't I can't find it I'll try and
find it one day if you can find it uh I'd love to see your favorite joke of all time
it's gonna yeah I build it up it's gonna be a huge letdown you know how the situation goes
I don't think so some I can't something about this game means that I can't click anything on
my other monitors even when they're active oh should I what's wrong with my body oh the chase
has died the fuck is this a zombie merchant what the fuck get off of me I'm hurry chat found it
yeah I'm sure they googled Sabrina crossbow and that's what I did I couldn't find it
I mean even you wouldn't know I'm really far away from you that's not one of those I'm dead
was seriously the same exact color scheme as all this shit it's blue and white and it was like look
blue and white on this plank of wood that was not my fault where are you that I'm dead over here
that really did look like it was one of those things oh you jumped and okay you're dead yeah
but it looked like it was one of those safe x thingies blue and white and we found it's the
first 30 seconds of this right here oh I think somebody's got it did I watch do we watch this on
stream yeah go for it so this is the funniest thing you've ever seen you said right not the
funniest thing is just my favorite thing from tv well okay that's not fair it's like my favorite
thing that I don't think was supposed to be funny I'm gonna add a whole bunch of qualifiers as I
remember that like always sunny exists and there's actually like funny tv shows hold on
we're about to watch it on my stream if you want to come over you can give some commentary if you
want I need the context man okay so I'm at like 15 seconds or so I don't know if this is like a
spoiler for a Sabrina the teenage witch and it probably is would you call this a spoiler
as long as you it's not a spoiler as long as you like stop watching after she gets shot
okay all right so this is it right here are you ready I can't click on anything on my computer
okay what it was before that
I mean that's not is that the funniest thing you've ever seen it's up there I didn't even
know that's what I didn't know what Sabrina even looked like I thought that was another character
and see look white blue white blue the thing that I jumped on was white blue all right are you
where are you I like ran all the way to a safe house it was I'm telling you you didn't see the
like two seasons before that where she shows up and every problem is solved because she's Sabrina
is it literally just fucking get shot and died is it a good show you I guess you've watched
through two full seasons of the show is it good I've seen it all she um I think we're gonna get
married like is it is the show a good show I like can't say yes but I love how fucking
dumb it can be like I like love it as a basically video candidate pretty much like really I love
love it yeah really okay there's one episode that I don't even like describing it is is going to be
it's going to be too much we potentially see another basically on this uh show I have a
basically half made still oh I ever show it to you I think you did I need to finish that it's
a good one if I need to actually finish it yeah yeah it's been like a year of it being half done
all right so we're safe here yeah we're safe I'll get the honey and stuff out here it's everywhere
somebody has disturbed like anything unironically Diablo 2 Diablo 2 Bloodborne I love a lot of
things I just think it's boring to describe things you like you burger
yeah that's all right I'm not too into burgers anymore are you do you not let me ask you
something do you not like to talk about things you like because you don't want to seem like
like oh you don't want to like tell people how cool something is and then they don't like it
no I just legitimately think it's kind of boring and it's much more interesting to like analyze
things and like analyzing something you like is like no I like that it that's just that's all it
is that's like the whole conversation everyone's like oh you don't like any games all I ever hear
is you don't like this like slay the spire for me is like a 10 out of 10 brilliant game but I'm not
I don't like hey put the spear down put the spear down I get it why do I gotta put the spear down
use this you coming at me somebody said he wants rage clicks I'm getting them definitely
it's working for me no I think I can understand that in a way like okay I like this is like like
you like it right but then what more is there to say back in the day we could talk about like all
the weird shit within smite or I could go on for a long time about like overwatch is fucking weird
but like slay this bar it's just it's just a perfect great game just play it okay I mean I
played slay this bar good game right into this thing we can do this thing I'll do it oh my spear
um it was good I I kind of doing the math in my head kind of was hard and I was like
this is fun but it's not for me yeah math is like that I thought it was a good game though
it's definitely really cool you coming we're getting them let's go I think we're gonna try
to get them all right so we got a lot of explosives here a lot of explosives he jumped he's the
jumper I'm gonna throw an explosive I got him watch out kill him I throw that at you essentially
be careful oh we got a whole bunch of heads I don't know where they came from
but they're here hey
when it became like IGN game reviews were like that it's great and then like the reviews
this is no review yeah game was really fun we really liked it did that distract you
distract me trying to distract him oh all right he
I'm running around so much oh I posted them oh I'm gonna I'm about to throw a boomerang
all right talking about I'm out I'm out oh he did a bit of a jumpy
dad dad the only good said the dead said or old world wine bro played uh you played dark
messiah right I did yeah good game end of conversation all right but you you can
describe why something was good without just saying it was good I don't know if it's really
worth it because what if somebody's like well why do you say that okay what if somebody disagrees
with you that I don't think that game is good no no one disagrees with me like when when we
brought up like best games of all time Diablo 2 bloodborne like it's just not like we both just
agree it's very very obvious that we're both correct in this instance and same for dark messiah
well what if somebody said dark messiah that game sucks what would you say kind of a weird
opinion to just be like totally and completely wrong okay so they're gonna go why am I wrong
yes that's it's a bad game it's like stupid you fight orcs who cares like Peter Jackson did that
fucking hundred years ago I don't even know who Peter Jackson is like NATO do you like explain
why you like something we'll see that this this whole scenario like that doesn't bother me that
they don't like it you're like oh like oh what if I told you like I disagreed and I like don't like
like okay I'm upgrading my health someone comes up blood boy all that game fucking saw the souls
games the same all right I mean I could not wrong hmm interesting very interesting I think I want
to test this theory okay so if somebody told you that I don't like dark messiah and you are stupid
for liking it stupid like like you're you're an idiot like you like that game because you're dumb
now it becomes a personal attack do you defend yourself then no you don't I mean like that's
just such a fucking weird person where like the person is basing intelligence level of other
people on video game references and it's just a weirdo so you don't deny that you still like
surely I'm not I'm I am I could have a potential conversation about like oh yeah like I could tell
you why I like it but it's like I don't know it's not that's not an engaging conversation I'd rather
talk about something like engaging and divisive like Hillary's email like what's up with them
I don't know we're all just agreeing dark messiah is an amazing game
but yeah it is all right what do we need to turn in here that health upgrade was ass by the way
I oh I don't even know that I did it it's like plus one percent health it looks like I've just
been taking the stamina and even the stamina is not I guess I don't know I took this weird upgrade
and now if I press my sprint button I lose half of my stamina and I don't go any faster
oh that's right I got that too I'm not pressing sprint though did you get the the ledge launch
one that one's kind of ridiculous like he's forgetting to do it yeah me too you turn into
like spider-man you ever play prototype no actually I wanted to that's a really really
good game I tried to stream that game really yeah what happened the game ran like shit and
it was like all messed up the frame rate was fucked up everything on are you down
what did you play it on I think was pc who the fuck is this guy I don't want to be being chased
we gotta move I think they had it for sale on like playstation like a bundle of the old game
I tried to screen record it I tried to capture it but it was all messed up yeah people are saying
it doesn't work well on pc but there's a whole bunch of games I played in the last year I'm like
I'm not having fun this really feels like I should be playing prototype
I can see that I don't think I can make this jump
did you try I didn't realize there was an edge there almost just did it go off me get up get up
stir just maybe buy slay this bar on my phone good it's good get influenced maybe I should
tell people things I like more and then they buy them and then it didn't really matter
I want to lose place are you playing hearthstone still I saw you play it recently I tried when
they added like a new game mode thing to it not good I like watch people play battlegrounds on
the twitch tv if you've heard this twitch platform yeah I like playing and I'm I kind of really
don't care anymore and definitely not like standard I know I watch I watch I watch crypt too
I didn't say that's who you're talking about it's not who I was talking about
are you kidding me okay crip the poe streamer I'm shocked I'm shocked that you're not watching
preparing instead like for hearthstone I legitimately don't I mean like sometimes
but I don't stay up that late at night okay all right all right all right good good answer
you're safe I can't get in this fucking window I'm so pissed oh my god get in the window
why won't go in the window what's happening pretending right no I'm not pretending I can't
go in you can't get in the homie hole okay there you go oh we got a nighttime bonus
so exhausting pretending this much all right cool you made it I need to craft some stuff give me a
sec can you make these regeneration boosters that seems kind of I wonder what a small amount of
health is already maybe it's not worth doing already two percent per second hmm I'm gonna
go with what I know because I did upgrade these I could do one I'll get a few all tough yep
120 percent total how is that a small amount of health wait wait two percent okay this is a 60
second duration and it regens two percent health per second so it regens 120 percent of your health
how is that a small amount of health I don't know I didn't make it I didn't I don't know who who
are you I got a combat skill so kind of cool about that gets smaller over two percent is small
you know how percentages work it regens two percent of your health every second and it
lasts for 60 seconds am I how am I reading this wrong two percent gets smaller every time
oh because it's two percent of the current health that you're missing
yeah and two percent is this small you dunce you don't have to go be dunce
you can just say not I'm not talking yeah I'm not talking to you I did not I did not
all right you ready ready for what I got I got a bunch of mollusks super all over who won
we're going this way we're going this way 200 oh my god why what the cost of stamina from things
is really weird like exiting that pole ate all my stamina but holding on to the pole
probably gets better over time yeah I bet
so where are we heading now just to the marker I think we go in here and we tell the guys that
we're like cool and people are saying like these are the questions you want to do for these guys
and like we're doing them oh my god favorite hearthstone card favorite hearthstone card
for real no okay just passing the time I like like test gray main
somebody said I keep spacing out good you were right drink some water is a trap
and it looks like you were getting close to the truth eat a banana either they killed lucas
or they know who did will force so you'll take all right I'm gonna laugh if he was just dead in
your arms that does seem to happen at the end of those I think we got an item take over that
yeah we got like a hammer thanks thanks for killing that like hundred people you've killed
here's a hammer to do it some more scrapper is that what we just got this thing is terrible
yeah it was like a level one because we're still in the tutorial even though I this game's pacing is
bizarre are we just slow we're definitely slow yeah but we also definitely had to play for like
40 minutes to even start the stream that's true and we were not pausing for McDonald's orders
during that 45 to 50 minute I just I speed ran my heart out and it was still kind of like well
it wasn't slow it was fine it was a good intro but now it's like introing again that you're in the
city it's like going over the same stuff that's a little bit like you know like you know it kind
of grinds my gears you know you're gonna get your 60 dollars worth hey then looks like the bandits
fled the water tower who wants to take control and force the bizarre folk to talk you just started
running yeah you were just gone I thought you were following me honestly but watch out I was
kind of in my inventory I'm picking up all the lavender I'm getting some honey from these bees
I'm making I'm not even worried about getting stung bees are no problem for me I'm gonna pick
up uh these shrooms doing a little bit of live commentary right now I'm picking up gonna search
this guy the true question is which came first ranch or cool ranch ranch because then that
everything spun off of that we got a whole bunch of blues over here that I'm finding some blues
cool ranch always sounds like so odd to me I whenever I hear cool ranch for some reason I
think that it's got like free on in it I don't know what I'm doing he's just bouncing around
well you get like the the chain kick combo where you parry someone then you stun the next guy
but it's very awkward oh no bandits can I craft something new
um oh we're going this way come on we ever play the car dlc from dying light one
I don't think so we I tried to play some of it on my own but we did not play it
secret over there uh any secrets over here I really just can't I can't get over how good
this game looks and how I can't get over it I always turn all this shit off when I play these
games I go to the check boxes and I turn off bloom refractoring lighting shadows like I turn it all
off I'll see you got like a monster rig man what are those what are those specs tell me about your
monster fucking rig man all right I think crack my fingers here all right you want to hear
yeah let's get all right so my rig what happened we just explode what did you do
should we respond to the last story point yeah what happened I uh you see this giant pile of
explosives yeah I swung I swung on it oh what does it do what does it do he asked I wanted
to see the funny thing too on my screen I never actually hit it like the swing never finished I
was like oh do I gotta do this dude you gotta do this they're gonna blow it up that's like kind
of realistic though isn't it like we wouldn't see the explosion we just gone oh yeah I didn't like
the Sopranos ending don't talk about spoilers who hasn't seen the Sopranos that cares because if you
exploded like that it would just be like gone it wouldn't be like boom oh my explosion oh final
scene of Sopranos when he walks up to the fucking the propane tank and he punches it and it just
ends this is really weird hold on that was really funny
I just see Tony Soprano like at the end of the movie at the end of the show just being like it's
fucking stupid fuck you fuck this you fucking boom it's over credits fucking propane oh you
don't think I fuck what you think you're funny fucking propane I honestly if I'm in control of
any production or anything ever like that's how it's gonna end oh like that dumb my fucking head
how could you resist ending it with the person like punching a propane tank yeah like just like
sometimes shit happens oh okay not everything in life is like planned in a script room you know
sometimes I got something to fucking tell you oh fuck you oh come on it didn't happen
immediately yeah that's like the like you can see me do it but when you do it yourself it kind of
stops early it does all right all right all right all right all right stop it it says quest failed
on the credits oh we got to do this again you can't let that happen look at the fucking slime
guy he's been in the fucking line he's fucking got a fuck I gotta shoot fucking snot out of his fucking
mouth where's the rest of it where's the rest oh I think it's more find and disarm the explosives
oh yeah there's a whole like there's a whole secret route up here any secrets over here oh yeah
there's secrets up here I just keep thinking of like Tony Soprano's got like a gun in his hand
it's like three or four other characters and they're all just arguing now that you think that
that's funny mm-hmm that's Sabrina clip is that for me that's all right I get it because there's
so much build up and there's so there's no reason for her to just suddenly get shot by a crossbow
in the show to end so like in that my head cannon shows over there where's this other bomb I think
we gotta there's some we gotta climb up here we're gonna go in here and bombs in here don't swing on
these don't swing on we're gonna have to climb again I'm not I'm not swinging get it yeah there's
more we need to go we need to do uppies I think from here yeah inside what is this place why does
anyone care if it explodes I don't know it's an important building of some kind the water tower
maybe where did you go how did you get up there inside the building they're in this room arguing
Tony Sopranos in here jack shut the fuck up you fucking idiot someone's gonna punch it all right
I got it oh yeah it was a water tower I don't know why everyone's like worried about water most
abundant resource and they're like oh I'm to the top of the water tower I'm doing yeah we're doing
some climbing I think I think you're right what the hell is that that just reminded me of do you
want to go in that cage do you remember mr. show mr. who mr. show is this it was a show on HBO it
was Bob Odenkirk and my god what's his name David David David David David David I'm so stupid David
Cross it's that kind of it was a sketch comedy show and you want to talk about one of the funniest
things that you've seen which is a Sabrina thing they did this bit where it was like the Sopranos
but all of the violence and swears were edited out of the show because it was for like network tv
it was like and for the first time we're airing like the the Soprano family on uh abc
and dude it was the funniest fucking goddamn thing like every two seconds it's just like shut
and then like somebody appears like face down at the table with like a gun wound like
I gotta find it they didn't mute it they cut oh it's the I we're doing a youtube watch right here
do you do you know the like macho man thing where every time he takes a breath they cut
yep mr show pranos what would it be called yeah mobster movie edited for tv here it is
we're gonna watch this right now this is absolutely fucking hysterical this is very
relevant hopefully I can click on it this is what is open on my screen yeah I know I know I have
when unable to do anything on my computer oh right right I like if I alt tap if I end task
but not you know windows you know I'm going all right here we go you ready
okay wait but you're gonna have to shut the fuck up all right we have to do we have to do
at the same time but you didn't link me anything oh just type in mr show sopranos now I'm watching
on your stream but you need to shut up and you need to not pause it react and then on you need
to not do that I'm not gonna do that I promise we're just gonna watch it I don't believe you ready
one two three oh thank you this nice sauce thanks
loopy nerd we buried he's probably stinking up the whole parking course by now
hey watch your mother father mom don't you tell me what to do you little piece of shoe
hey that's my aunt you mother father wait what for both of you sir can grab mine on my book
you mother father chinese dentist you have to go through that okay that's good
I'll tell you why because one pallies the channel six sunday sunshine moving picture show will
return all right I mean that was it was it was really funny but not the funniest thing I've ever
seen in my life that is Bob Odenkirk yes that's Saul Goodman watch the mad tv one two yeah that
one's funny too they're all funny uh can you hear me I can hear you yeah everything locked up again
um you better call Saul coming soon I haven't I don't say anything I haven't seen anything
I don't I don't know if it's come out yet I just remember hearing that it would be soon
you're you're you're saying you haven't seen like any I haven't seen past season two so don't say
anything what are you doing I'm crawl what your turn okay oh nice move man huh you really learned
all your parkour thank you you have any grenades I do I do because I think we're about to fight
one of the bosses of the game up here you got a bit it's not I don't really have a bit I'm just
saying throw a grenade at him oh is that a oh we gotta we gotta open this hey come down here
I'm on top of the hey hey come down here where I am I need you to open this plywood door this
is an important cutscene we don't want this one yeah nice and easy it's really heavy lots of stuff
opens from the bottom in video games why um are you ready to grenade these guys it's going
through the ceiling dude I'm not kidding what is fill this room with fill this room with fire
I have one grenade I have nine oh what do we do
wait does he have the exploder in his hand he does he has the exploder in his hand see
called it oh no it's just a walkie-talkie no we don't trust anybody we're doing like a
fucking improv show for us just fucking fight so you're gonna start dancing I will no I won't help
you bargain with extortionists they're murderers you want to be on their side look at them they're
wearing leather jackets into the sides of the room immediately that's a walkie-talkie that's
not detonator oh do my mouth get to the edges of the room did we get him you got him how what
how you just threw like $400 at him yeah that was like a grand we both keep trying to do it
are we gonna land it
oh my god what oh why did you why did you do that I don't know he was dead turn the water back on
he was already dead man it really was so stupid though back when movies would air on tv on
network tv when you know netflix hb all this nobody that doesn't exist it was they would put
the stupidest shit in the play in place of swears they would really do this oh yeah I forgot they
actually would like change the words rather than believe it's control of the water and it would be
the actor would do it forgot yeah they were man how did I like miss the whole joke that's true
it'd be like you are out of your flooping mind the stuff that nobody would ever say
they would really do that it made no sense oh we get like a choice you seeing this yeah there's
either car traps or ziplines I want ziplines like who cares about a car trap yeah we ziplines for
sure I just want to go I'm voting zipline yeah I vote it we did it peacekeeper bow is the best
weapon in the whole game yeah so how did how did we go from like needing to find our girlfriend to
saving villages I don't know maybe that always happened maybe we should play the game and find
up okay you should uh not skip every single dialogue piece I mean I can't skip this for
some reason I've had it with these monkey fighting snakes on this monday to friday plane
yeah that's the class that's a classic one okay city alignment we're playing planet side yeah okay
city alignment tool yeah my city is aligning all right oh there's like a whole other area
you know there's like a whole other area in this game yeah we've been we've been hitting on darn
asses for the last six hours and six and a half hours dude there's like a whole downtown there's
the wharf very cool hey then where the fuck are you barney you trying to capture him jack and joe
warned him he could have avoided the trap but he went into it anyway that's when maybe we should
are you doing all right I'll make sure the place is safe are you are you worried about me
uh you want to but like half an hour 30 minutes uh yeah now that we unlocked the new area I think
that's about it for me I mean we've been playing for almost six and a half hours
you know I would be good honestly though you good I don't know if you want to play again or what but
okay it just seems like a funny spot to end but you're like yeah we've been playing like all day
yeah I wouldn't mind okay have you gone to a thousand points now uh I feel like I would have
to see the new area I'm at like 950 I feel like okay I don't I don't feel like the game has too
many surprises left will you start getting grappling hooks and your wing-a-dings and maybe
yep I think it's like it's like most games these days it's front-loaded with so much
bullshit even if the rest of it is fun and it's hard to recommend to anyone you're like oh yeah
if you watch like the first season like season two is pretty good skip three yeah and then like like
four is all right yeah that does tend to happen nowadays yeah I think it's good I felt that way
about dying light one though too that if if you just had all your stuff unlocked and it really
was like sandbox world the game probably would have been a lot more fun I could see that I will
say I give it a I give it like a 9.8 be like a 9.8 and a half that's very high does your scale
will go up to like 20 or I was just waiting for you to be like you're a fucking idiot so then I
could prove to you that I could prove to you the point you made earlier that like no because I
know that you're joking yeah I was waiting for you to call me dumb is this really okay like
bloodborne's a 10 this is a 9.8 no this is a solid this is a solid game I'm doing a jump joke are
you let me see other players are waiting for you where are you oh you're here all right yeah maybe
I mean if you want to play it again we could obviously play again if you wanted to how do you
feel how are you what's your schedule like stir oh my schedule is uh panic panic stress uh saturday
myriad wipe my wipe my brow uh which by the way right panic panic that's in the middle of it
episode four just happened right yeah yeah what is the what is the myriad by the way
curious oh I mean the myriad is uh basically like a dnd campaign that I run every week on my
channel on saturdays we've got a couple of fun uh gamer streamers and in the future germa is
going to be a part of it uh because it's a whole system I programmed and you don't you you can
have streamer brain rot and play it because it's all automated and I am I am the dungeon
production man of the show right and where can we find you on twitch.tv slash stir anywhere
any more that's s t e r I feel like I'm I'm killing this yes s t e r yeah it's dnd without
the dnd that it's dnd without like all the stuff that makes dnd slow yeah yeah pretty cool I think
it's a really cool thing all right you can just wait till germa plays it because one day he's
gonna play it one day yeah whenever we decide to do that uh but yeah indeed uh if you if you
actually do want to play this again at some point like this week or whatever let me know
we can get to the non-tutorial island well what's what's your schedule like I was gonna do like
some just chatting stuff but tomorrow's valentine's day and I want to spend it with my girlfriend so
um I was thinking about I don't know maybe like do you want to play on like Wednesday
uh I mean I was just curious your general overall I mean I'd even be like like like if I was like
hey like what about this other game we're like oh cool new thing then we do we do the new thing
um I would say I mean Wednesday I was probably going to stream like IRL just like just chatting
for like an hour or two okay we'll figure it out we can play on Wednesday sounds good thanks for
playing stir appreciate it okay yeah yeah take care and uh you know um yeah bye and we'll see
we'll see on probably Wednesday all right all right it's a date uh I will see you guys but
we'll do it on Wednesday seems like a good time to do it let me try to gift 100 community subs again
for like the 10th time uh let's see I'm gonna run the credits thanks for watching everybody
I don't want to go too too late here into eastern time I wonder if my cards are gonna get declined
again yeah on Wednesday we'll I was gonna do two days in a row but that it's valentine's day I
want to spend it with Oli so I'm gonna spend it with Oli I'm gonna have a plan it's gonna be fun
aced yeah we'll uh me and stir will play probably again on Wednesday we'll do the
browser game stuff on Wednesday too because I honestly I'll be really honest I don't think
I would be playing this on stream for like another like eight hours so oh the game master he is a
game master see he proved it right there game master has disconnected you and you're gonna
return to your game uh a couple things I do want to talk about real quick today is the last day
for you to nominate people for the streamer awards it ends I believe tonight at midnight so
if you had I was gonna take it on stream but I looked at the list and I realized that I don't
think I would reliably be able to answer too many of these just because I don't really watch a ton
of like some of the content that's here yeah I'll link it hold on it is alone it is the streamer
awards.com here it is there are a shitload of categories you guys know uh cutie cinderella
and maya they are running this there's a ton of people involved um it seems like a pretty cool
idea it's sort of like a twitch awards show uh if I could give you the ones I've if you want
me to do some nominations here I could probably give you some if I'm scrolling down the list but
like stuff like league streamer roleplay streamer battle royale streamer I don't really watch too
much of that uh so I don't really know but let's see here I'll give you some some examples the
did it no it didn't did it it should be until midnight right it's ended it didn't it did it
did it oh shit did I miss it I don't know it doesn't I can I can see it still you don't have
to enter a name for each yeah you can you can skip categories it says February 13th they end yeah
tonight it yeah today tonight at midnight that's what I said but yeah let me go through some of
these real quick I'll give you some of my opinions I mean uh I'll start with I guess vtuber streamer
that's that's I'm gonna say neanderth I don't really know that many other vtuber streamers if
I would keep going uh uh best like smash brothers I don't really know sports game I don't really know
I don't really know who else best okay best variety streamer I would say lidwig
lidwig absolutely is best variety streamer of the year without a doubt best streamed event I would
say you know you know whatever whatever I don't know you know there's things that happened this
year or it's supposed to be 2021 so stream game of the year is what would be a stream game of the
year stream game of the year because this is all across all of shit you can't hold on this across
all the platforms right because it's not just like oh a game that I played on my channel it's
like just across all of twitch all of youtube everywhere I mean I among us I would probably
say I mean that's like one of the biggest things that happened last year right I mean I didn't play
it I don't know it's my vote yeah it is it is I don't know I would probably say among us even
though I don't even like play it best content organization esports or content organization
that has created the best content during the past year but I think I probably put the production
company that I've worked with every time community jakes company what I was gonna put
is that I don't know if that's like an esport like content organization that has created the
best content if that fits I mean I don't know if it does but that's jk productions I don't know if
that's accurate but uh if I keep going I don't know I can't some of these it's hard like rising
star award for instance I'd like who's like somebody that I didn't really notice before but
they're like really kind of blown up um it's hard to put somebody here because are we talking brand
up-and-coming streamer that's had tremendous growth over the past year and has the potential
to be a top streamer I mean I I would say I mean Connor's been pretty popular for a while though
maybe like atriarch but he's been popular too for a while how popular are they gonna be
is popular is popular like five to ten like I don't know I'm not sure because all the people
that I would put in this list are already pretty popular like they already have like a large
following I don't know I don't know who would put their legacy award a legend who's contributed
a great deal and has shaped the industry career achievement award I don't know I don't know who
would even say for them gamer of the year I gotta give that to xqc are you serious streamer that
has extraordinary gaming abilities and as excelled at games over the past year and then streamer of
the year streamer of the year I mean I think you gotta I think I have to nominate Ludwig for this
I think Ludwig did a ton of shit he did so many things he I think he's probably one of the
few people that is doing interesting content on every platform yeah but I'm not gonna vote
for myself I don't I'm not gonna go into the presidential booth and be like that's right
that's me oh I'm giving you my opinions right this is not just for twitch this is for everywhere
this is youtube this is twitch this is facebook I don't know residents do do that though yeah but
if I'm if I'm not talking about like being an ego Andy I would say probably Ludwig that's what
I would say he's done a lot of stuff yeah he's also done a lot of stuff for this channel I mean
a lot of things uh I got a lot of help from him over the last year or two for tons of different
things so he's a he he's a really really great dude and I really do genuinely think that like
he does interesting stuff either that or I'm gonna put xqc like I'm just gonna put xqc here
if it's not Ludwig that's what I'm gonna do also like league of their own the streamer is a pioneer
that creates one-of-a-kind content with their creativity out of the box thinking they're a
trailblazer in the streaming industry someone who relies on themselves for their content and
genuinely is in a league of their own I mean I would probably put xqc here too like xqc just
does his own shit he doesn't like rely on anything or anybody else he kind of just does his thing he's
in his own lane yeah but I'm not we're not talking about me right now we're not talking
about me you can vote for whoever you want and that's cool all right okay you can vote
wherever you want but I'm just okay I'm taking myself out of the equation I can't what am I
gonna be here be like oh let me tell you how I think about me I belong here I belong here I
belong here I belong here yeah best valorant streamer that's me baby yep uh yeah I think I
think that's accurate I'm gonna say Ludwig I think that's accurate all the others it's hard
for me to do because I don't watch too many streamers we're the oldest juicer couple oh god
oh no all right I'll see you guys on Wednesday take care of yourselves let me try to give 100
community subs I hope it works okay here we go are you ready does it go through huh come on
oh wait I have to actually get my credit card again it's not saved why is it not saved 100 subs
let's go oh I got it I got it it's in there here we go please work please work please work please
work payment processing what the fuck purchase could not be completed there was an error during
the order why can I not buy community subs I literally used this credit card like 10 like
12 hours ago why does this keep happening I have to I gotta have to talk to twitch why is this
happening why I can't every option doesn't work I used this card I'm not kidding like less than 12
12 hours ago okay I gotta I gotta I gotta talk to twitch and be like why can I not give subs
try buying one okay I'm gonna buy let's let's see if I can do like 10 let's do 10 subs complete
purchase okay payment processing your gift order will be completed soon purchase could not be
completed there was an error during the order I don't get it uh I'm I'm gonna try to get to the
bottom of this and I'm gonna try again because I've tried three different payment methods
can we try Holly can you gift 100 subs and then I'll just send transfer the money to you
okay can you can you try hold on hold on let me let me let me see if I can get this to work
all right hold on wait a minute wait hold on let me try using my card yeah wait wait wait
here use my card okay she's gonna try to use my card but if that goes through that's fucking
weird why was it happening I wonder if it's gonna work you have to put the numbers on the back
I I did honestly if this works I I'm gonna have to actually talk to twitch and be like why am I
banned from community subs I thought that that was just her only do 500 no only do 100 did it work
oh she she's like bank info hold on sending bank info no don't do a thousand okay here we go
did it work I don't think it worked no nothing no I didn't accidentally use a Dave and Buster's gift
card you got an error yeah what's going on here all right I don't know what's going on I gotta call
my bank all right well I'll see you guys on Wednesday hopefully I got this figured out
it didn't work I'll see you guys later have a wonderful rest of your day thank you I'm not
broke I just my car doesn't work in twitch but I've worked everywhere else that's so weird
happy Valentine's Day all of you you know just have a good day you know you want to raid some
all right let's raid somebody I mean I this raid is gonna be like 100 people I've been sitting
here dilly dallying who's live let me take a look okay what do we got what do we got what do we got
what we got what we got Vinny's doing weird AI shit all right let's go I will see you guys on
Wednesday have a great night go say hello to me take care of yourselves goodbye good night
I'll see you soon bye why did I wait so long to say to that last part I waited way too long
yeah and no all right I'm being serious dead serious Andy right now no more the raid song
shit don't no more of that like raiding people when they get raided and they just have to look
over and they get being forced to have to do something don't no more of that shit no more
no more raid songs no more raid songs no more raid songs stop it stop it stop it stop it I demand
it I command it I'm telling you I demand you don't do this I command it I'll see you tomorrow no
Wednesday no Wednesday Wednesday Wednesday are we grounded again
we'll find out have a great night guys see you later goodbye