Press enter to select Sexy Layla, Tough John, or Sleazy Estelle.
There you are, hurry up, we have a passenger to pick up. He's waiting for us at the El Banana Bar.
Alright, fine. He's waiting for us at the Banana Bar.
So you're the new guy, I'm Hank. I'll show you around and teach you how to drive.
Thanks a lot, Hank. I appreciate that.
Get there as fast as possible. If you're too late, the competition will have your passengers.
So, we're fighting over taxi passengers? Is that what's going on?
Take shortcuts whenever you can.
Wait, what? The faster and safer you jump just driving into stuff.
That wasn't safe at all.
So these are the passengers.
Alright, hey, where are they going? No, it's a setup. Ah, we have to get out of here.
What's a setup?
What is a setup?
What do you mean it's a setup?
Wait, how do I drive the car?
I don't understand. Why would a taxi company set you up?
Is there a reason for this?
A rival taxi company? What?
I just, I just don't get it.
I just don't get it.
Why do these guys want to have a taxi battle?
You know what I mean? What the, what?
Where did that car even go?
I'll show you a taxi battle.
See you later, Frank.
This is my pickup.
Get in the car.
Ow, my, my head.
Oh my god, guys, I'm gonna die.
Oh, hold on.
How do I steal the passenger back?
How do I steal this guy back?
150 bucks? That's easy, buddy.
Come on in, honey. Let's move.
So, that's never gonna get old.
The car boogers coming out of the giant's sneezing nose is never gonna get old, ever.
That's what that is.
What kind of force is that? Like, seriously, why would that ever happen to a car?
Unless it was coming out of a giant's nose during a sneeze.
Watch this, ready?
Out of the way. Out of the way.
This passenger's mine.
Sorry, Jerry.
Maybe next time, Jerry.
Thank you very much.
No, get away. Get away from me.
Please, get away from me, Jerry.
Here it is, around this corner.
Just be careful.
Don't get knocked off the edge.
Okay, secret. I found the secret.
This is no secret.
Bad driver.
It seriously took you that fucking long to figure that out?
He's right behind me.
Can I lure him off the side of the road here?
Nope. He's too quick.
Where the hell did I just go?
Oh, great. Oh, great.
I'm going to bait you into this gas station and you're going to explode.
Whether you want to or not, it's gonna happen.
Here you come.
Yeah, good for you.
Good for you.
Come this way. Drive straight into this.
Now he's stuck.
I got him. I got him right where I want him.
Yeah, that was not the correct thing to do.
I'm not sure you know this, but that was really stupid for you to do that.
And your head is coming through the top.
I don't think you're alive anymore, but to tell you the truth,
I don't think you ever were to begin with.
So we're just going to keep going.
Man, that's not a good place to be standing.
If you want a taxi ride, I understand.
But you're going to have to be safer, buddy. You're going to have to get...
Would this person really be doing this for like an extra 15 bucks?
No, he wouldn't.
I win the taxi battle.
Jesus, Harry.
Let me just drop the passenger off.
Well, I lost the game.
Game's over.
I have no more taxi.
We're raining taxis from the sky now.
That's what we're doing now?
That's where we're going with this game?
You got to be fucking kidding me.