Hey, sorry everybody. My cat rolled all over my Twitch computer.
And my cat, I have a piano that's over here that's hooked up to the screen,
and my computer cat walked over the piano. I didn't mean to turn the stream on.
Good morning, how are you? So yeah, it's early. I'm, I was up late last night,
uh, preparing for this exact moment. Um, I know a lot of you probably really
confused as to why there's a stream right now. Uh, I'm participating in Ludwig's
Super Auto Pets Tournament. That's right. In a game that I have a collective
hour and 12 minutes in the game. I'm gonna get fucking annihilated.
I was cramming for an exam. Yeah, I was up late last night because it's like,
oh man, that game looks really cute and really fun. It's what a cool looking game.
I saw Ludwig play it and I saw other people playing it too. Uh, and then late last night,
I found myself saying, you know what? Yeah, I think it's time to cram for that exam that I
told Ludwig I would be in like a week ago. So I watched the Northern Lion Tier List.
You know, just trying to get an idea. I played for a little while. I actually,
this is not a joke. I'm making the, this is not me making something up. This is for real.
I fell asleep last night with Northern Lion telling me how good and bad things were
the different animals while I was sleeping with the iPad on my chest. I was just sitting there
with iPad on chest listening to him. My eyes are closed and I open it up. I think the videos,
it's like a two and a half hour video. I started the video. It was just like, fuck, I'm tired.
This, I gotta, I gotta know though. I need to know. And I closed my eyes and I kind of woke up.
It was, I think like an hour had gone by and he was still going through the list.
Well, I think I absorbed some info, but yeah, I'm very prepared to just be the,
the first enemy of level one for all the people playing in the tournament today.
His voice sounds so sleepy. Well, it's because I woke up 20 minutes ago. I literally rolled out
and got out here. I told you I was up all night studying. The reason why I'm live like 20 minutes
early is because I want to play around and everyone's, I look, I don't even care how bad
it from what he thinks I'm playing. I'm not, I can't even look at the chat because people are
going to be like, holy shit dude, you suck. You got, how fucking dumb are you? I think I just
barely learned what the, what the alligator did. That was about 15 minutes ago. Let me tweet this.
Okay. Yeah, this is, this is, and this stream is only going to be as long as the tournament is.
You know, I actually kind of like the voice. I like having this voice. You know, you know,
you know how you wonder how does the guy on the radio sound like this?
Well, it's because the guy on the radio is, it's about seven or eight AM and they, they have wake
up voice and they use wake up voice to their advantage. See by noon, 12 o'clock Eastern,
by the way, this is gone. And those guys talk normally for the rest of the day. Sonic is the
funniest movie of the year. That's funny. That's like my favorite joke of 20 of 2020
and nobody even voted for it. A nice hot voice, Andy.
Howard Stern hates me. Howard Stern. No, it's, it's, it's just being really close to a microphone
with a deep voice in a compressor. When you get really close to a microphone and you have a
compressor on, what it does is it, it takes your voice in it and it just transports it into
everybody's minds. It's crazy what radio's done. You know, what's the next question? Uh, Phil.
All right. No, I don't, no, I don't want to run a virus scan. I have to warm up. I'm not,
I actually don't even know how this is going to work, but we'll figure it out.
What is this exactly? All right. Let me show you what this is. It's a game we're going to learn
together before the tournament. Why is my chat not even in dark mode? What? Okay. Here we go.
I don't know. It's not, it's not back of me. I should, maybe I should. All right. Here we go.
So this is super autopets. Yeah. Yes. You can see, you can see my name. My name. I know at this,
I'm not going to be able to play on this fucking account ever again, probably. Yeah. My name is
Bert Ernie. Bert Ernie. This over here. All right. So this is, it's okay. You don't, uh,
you ever play like auto chess? I haven't, but I played battlegrounds. Uh, Hearthstone
Battlegrounds is apparently very similar to this. And it is very similar, which if Hearthstone
Battlegrounds is just, uh, uh, team fight tactics, whatever it is, that how it works. You get in the
game, you started with them. And by the way, I've got, I've got hats on his hats. It's gotta,
I gotta just make sure I keep an eye on this discord over here because I don't want to miss
the call time. It's very cute. And it's okay. It's just like Hearthstone Battlegrounds, just like
probably team fight tactics. I saw, I was, you know, I'm, I'm, I'm like a reviewer. I check out,
you know, games that have come out that are new. And by that, I mean, I watched Ludwig play this
and then I said, wow, that looks cool. And he said, Hey, do you want to play in a tournament?
And I was like, sure. And then I realized that it was today. Okay. Uh, so it's just like,
this is the attack. This is the heart of health. What did you study? I told you I fell asleep with
Northern lions tier list. I was on my own, my chest. No, I wasn't on my chest. Okay. All right.
I'm going to try. I just spilled coffee all over me. I'm not even fucking ready. Oh, all right.
All right. Um, no, I'm not. I'm tired. I just woke up. Everybody relax. I'm laughing. I'm very
disheveled right now because I just dropped the hot coffee on my chest and I don't have any clothes
on. I don't have clothes on. So I just burnt my chest. Okay. So you really want to get like a,
the pig sucks from what I hear, but they fight on their own. It's automatically right. So I'm
going to let's just go with cricket. Everything costs three gold. That includes the food, which
is the sometimes give permanent buffs. Sometimes it gives something temporary. It's sometimes it
might give, uh, health and I'm saying mana, but health and attack. So we've got a cricket, uh,
and rolling. You can roll is what she gets you other ones to choose from using the pay to lose
pack. Why? I didn't know what the rules were. So I just got to get, you got to get stuff up there
as, as, I mean, as Northern lion says, forget about being the big brain tech guy and go for wins.
Like, you don't, you don't tech into something, right? Like this is what I've been taught
by the best, by the way. All right. So let's, uh, beaver's good beavers. All right. It's two, two.
Let's get another, uh, well, I've mosquitoes. Pretty good. Mosquito throws a mosquito dust at
somebody to start and you'll see how this works. Are you ready? Here we go. Uh, name your team. The
fishy lawnmowers. That's fine. No face cam. No way. So then I don't, I don't, I don't know how
this works. I don't, I don't understand how the matchmaking works, but there's no time limit
like there is in Hearthstone. I killed that guy, got the hit there. That summons another cricket
and then there you go. Automatically does it. And there's your first win. There's no audio.
Oh, okay. Well, this should be no audio is broken. I got it. I got it. Okay. So you, if you lose,
you lose a heart and after turn three, if you lose, you lose three hearts. And I know what
you're thinking. I know what you look over time, over the course of like a few days, you get,
you get these back. Um, you can all, I'm just kidding. So the cool part about this is the reason
why I think it's cool. I like it. No, that's, it's just, that was a lie. Don't believe that.
That's literally that this game does not have, could not connect to server, but it's all right.
Are you sick? Yeah. Let's just say yes. So if I have a cricket, I can upgrade this cricket by,
oh, um, what happened? Did I get like banned? Oh, there we go. All right. Sick. Yeah. All right. So
I got a beaver. So, okay. So everybody has a certain thing that can happen, right? So when I
sell beaver, I do sound like fucked right now. So if I sell the beaver, he's going to give two
random people one health, but permanently, which is a big deal. Servers are bad. That's all right.
So I'm going to go, I, you know, I'm just going to fish. Win early, win early, win early, win early.
That's what I've been told. Win early. I'm going to upgrade the beaver because if you do two,
if you take a copy, put it on top of what you have there twice, bang, level it up.
Sell the beaver right now? Um, I don't know. And I'm going to lose the tournament. So don't
worry. But this is really fun. The game's actually really fun. Um, I feel like that's a waste.
Oops. Well, it did it anyways, I guess. Okay. Uh, let's roll. Should I buy the food? No,
we're just going to fish. Going fish at the back. I can combine this after. Oh, you can free stuff
too. I probably should have froze the ant. Yeah. I have maybe an hour or two in this game
and I'm going, I'm going up against like literally like the Galileo's of this game.
No, it's not a drill. Oh, well you studied though. Yeah, I did. All right. So some of these are
really, really cool. Like peacock, right? When a peacock gets hurt, it gets to attack. With
porcupine dies, it does two damage to everybody. And the, uh, the dromedary.
What am I doing here? What am I doing here? What am I doing here? I can't be in this. I
can't do this. I'm going to get fucking beat the first round and I'm going to like burp at somebody.
Okay. So, uh, stay calm, stay calm. All right. I'm going to stay calm. I'm relaxed. Yeah,
I'm relaxing. I'm fine. I'm, I got confidence. I should be just fine. Okay. I think we're about
to start. Oh no. I thought I was going to have at least like 20 minutes. Oh shit. They said, hey,
jump in the, jump in the general. Oh, okay. All right. I got to pretend like I'm not freaking out
about this. You know what I mean? Like the battleship tournament was, I knew what I was doing.
I know the game very well. It was like, oh, German, look, we're going to do a battleship thing.
I have no idea what's going on right now. And I like have to, I have to put out the air
that I, that I'm, I got it completely together here. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello.
I'm so tired. When are we starting? What are you? Lud said we can be 10 minutes late. So I'm assuming
we're starting in 10 minutes. Okay. Cool. That's a freaking out. I just muted and deafened. I'm
freaking out. All right. All right. Um, let's go. I got to finish at least this thing here. Everybody,
everybody is stoned. Okay. Let's go back to what I was doing. No more fucking around. All right. So
when you combine, when you get to fish level two, they give everybody one, one, which is pretty good.
So, um, but I don't know if I want to do that right now. This will kill. Well, the word is faint,
right? You don't mute it. Just say it. Sell the beaver now. Yeah, that's actually a good idea.
But I, I can't get a over 10 gold, right? My mic is not, I, my mic is muted. Okay. I can see it
over here. No, not muted to you guys. Muted to everybody else. It's in that call. Okay. Uh,
can I, what if I do this? Hear me out. So let's combine the fish and then do I want peacock?
I would anyone ever not put the hedgehog first because that hurts everybody. They're talking
about me. No, they're not. Ludwig is literally muted in here. I can see people. Should I pull
the head? You want to try it? Um, I don't even know what I'm looking for here. What do I want
to even try to do? Let's go peacock. When the peacock gets hurt, then you get, it's like a frenzy
mode. All right. So let's keep the peacock back here. Unless I can get some food, which let's
roll for it. Hmm. Should I give her the cricket? Spider, spider is good. I think spider is just a
better cricket at this point. All right. So do I get, okay, do I get two spiders? Sell the beaver
or should I just level up the spider or should I, uh, cupcake the, uh, peacock?
Sell the otter. Yeah, I'm going to, I'll do that. Let's do that. That's what I wanted.
All right. We get two spiders. I don't want the shrimp. I do want this though,
because this just adds, this is a, one of the buffs. Okay. It looks like every people are
trickling in. Ludwig's watching you. Yeah. But I mean, uh, honey. Okay. I want the honey as well.
Having honey at the last person, the first like five rounds is incredibly important.
Spider only, that's not how it works. Why do they have little hats on? I put them on.
Called me profoundly new, but no, you have no idea. I was up all night last night preparing
for this. I'm going, I'm going peacock, whale, cheetah. And it's going to, it's going to,
everyone's going to be in a lot of trouble. I just want a game. Oh, I like this one. Okay.
Bat is S tier. I know that for a fact. I know it for a fact. So I got, I got to, okay. I need
to roll for a fish. I want bat. I want bat, but I want spider to have this because it's just five
more damage just permanently. And let's, it's taken off of course. All right. Let's give this
to you because that's just a win. Now what are we looking for? Excuse me. What are we looking for?
I actually don't remember, but we're going to combine the spider. So now at the start of battle,
this makes somebody weak and all week is, it took me a while. It took me about a couple hours to
figure this out. So weak is just a, like an equipment slot. You see on the right, it's a
bone attack, attack for five more damage. Honey bee, summon a one, one bee after fainting, right?
It replaces that on anybody that it hits. They're starting. That's literally last night entry.
Jerma, why are people coming in my chat saying he's blazed? Who's saying that? I'm having like
people come in here talking about how you have ancient peyote that the lions used.
Can I get some of that? I do not. I do not. I've just.
That was very convincing. Well, look, the game, we have some beginners. Can you explain the rules,
please? Like, I don't even know how the game works. I just installed it 15 minutes ago.
So the game, very simply, is an auto battler. You form a team of five, the best team you possibly
can. And the team will battle against a random person. So we're going to enter a 16 person lobby.
Everybody in this call will be playing. And then the top eight people from that,
from that giant group will go to a single elimination bracket. Just the sweaty people,
just the stans of the worlds. Okay. Let's relax. Let's relax. I'm here to have fun.
We'll go to a different bracket. All right. A less sweaty one, the me youngs. Okay.
Aren't so good at games. I want to get rolled. I have a chance.
Why is that called that? Everybody gets. So the winner of each one will get their own award.
If you win the champion bracket, you get your own custom hat in game. It's a trophy hat.
So you're the only person in the world who has it. If you win the losers bracket,
you get a joker hat. And then also four K for winner of champion two K for winner of losers.
Is that all? That's pretty cool. What? I just want a hat. I just wanted a hat.
Yeah. The hat sounds amazing. So that's, that's pretty much it. That's pretty much it. This is
not sponsored by the people keep saying I'm sponsored because I keep playing this game.
It's mostly because there's this bald guy on Twitch that I've watched a decent amount lately.
Hello. Oh, northern lion. Oh, I fell asleep to him last night.
To help out, by the way, I have a discord channel for all of you
because it doesn't make a lot of sense for all 16 of us to talk on a discord.
Uh, wait, that sounds fucking mean. That's not what I mean. Like, oh, hey,
I fall asleep to you all the time, dude. No, no, no, no. I mean, like I was,
I got to fucking correct that. I got to correct the record like right now,
but I can't like interrupt, right? Uh, and I, I predict if you win this,
it'll go max like three, four hours. And if you lose right away, it'll go like 90 minutes to two
hours. How do I jump in and correct this? I didn't know I did. That was not like a,
Hey dude, like I fall asleep. I fell asleep to your stream last night. No, no, no, no, no, no,
no. God, how do I, it's, it's too much time has passed. Nobody's talking. Uh, I caught the,
I didn't catch the last part. Uh, I said, okay, I didn't, this is going to be like a fun stream,
but I'm like having a great time right now. Like I thought this is going to be like a game or
stream where like, I got to focus. I got to really pay attention and no, no fun right now. I'm going
to, I'm trying to win. Point. Yeah. I should have, I should have clarified. I did forget about that
fact. Um, hold up, actually let me abandon this. Uh, so for this one, uh, everyone use the free pack
just for the large group. That makes sense. Whatever you want. If you duckstrap your lame,
just calling it out right now. I'm not going to do it. This is good. Call it duckstrap.
Do it. Don't do it. That's the duckstrap. My ducks for five turns and don't really use the DLC.
Don't leak my strats, bro. Well, I think, you know, there's no gift in the ducks. I've never
played this game and I'm probably going to get rolled because I don't even know what I'm looking
at here. Is there like a tutorial that I can look at? I just, I just picked the cutest ones.
Guys, I have no idea what I'm looking at here, man. I need like a tutorial or like a breakdown
video. Kind of a little too late for that. Northern lion as we time to have a three hour long tutorial
video. If you watch it on like 15 X, you might be able to digest it. Just go to Northern lion
tierless super autopets, go to the very end and then just look at that and then buy the S tier.
That's what I started. That's what I fell asleep to last night. I was lying there with the iPad
on my chest just trying to cram for the exam and I got, I got to the, I was on the Northern lion
video. I was like three, four o'clock in the morning. I put the playlist on and tried to
absorb it while I slept. I don't, by the way, I think scientifically that doesn't work, Dan.
Well, it looks like you're going to try again tonight and I'll put some more mid rolls in that.
Good for the next week. See if it works. Oh, the lobby's up. All right. No, do lobby. Oh,
yeah. I'm adding. Was there any rules that I needed to know when I missed or
go for it? No, you're good. All right. Just pack one. Yeah. Flat pack one for the first round.
So pack. So we all jump. We're just doing the same. Yeah. Everybody can just kind of hop in.
Wait, how do I join? So you go to a private game join and then you type in the code I put in chat.
It's because I didn't start at me. I kind of, I kind of reject. Make sure you don't leak. It's
very easy to do it. Is it easy to leak? Yeah. Yeah. Join private and enter game name. Okay.
Me young wins. She gets pretty good subs. Yeah. Don't say that. It's a rule. Okay.
Should I join or am I just going to like capture your stream or like screen share or? Yeah. My idea
was everyone will enter their own call and then screen share. So you can easily bounce around
watching POVs. Makes sense. Let me see how many people are in this. Ray is not streaming. I'm
going to get there in a second. He's like a spectator. Why is there 17? Oh, wow. This really
is super easy to leak. Yeah. It just shows that it's just there until it starts. So just say,
no, I did not leak. No, I did not 14. All right. So I think we're just missing
Saikuno and mango and then we're set. Uh, and I think one person in this call hasn't joined.
Is that right? Um, I haven't joined, but one extra person in addition to you. Okay. Okay.
You know, there's a chance Northern line. I don't know how much you want to risk it.
I don't think it'll go that long if you want to hop in and play. Here's the thing. Okay. I'm
there's two things. One is I already have a one of one hat in the game, so I wouldn't want to take
both of the one of ones. That's rude. And then the other one is I think my chat really has high
expectations. They expect me to win. And that's a lot of pressure because there's a lot of good
players, a lot of good analytical thinkers here. So I would rather just sidestep the entire
issue there and just commentate instead and act superior from an ivory tower. And then you
won the champion, like in the end of Pokemon elite four. Hey, that could work. Whoever wins
plays Northern line at the very end. That would be, it's like Pokemon. If every time that someone
loses, you just say, Oh, they should have watched my tier list. I actually, the tier list is out
of date with the new patch. Uh, I need to do a retcon, but I digress. Uh, Saikuno code is in
general. Yep. I'm already in it. Does, does this code leak after the lobby? Is there some way to
hide on the screen? Once you go into the game, you're good. Once we're live, I think we're good.
Yep. Uh, I think, is this everyone? I'm missing three people. Unless I'm terrible at math. I
feel like everybody in this call, if they joined, we would be at 16. I heard a distant whisper from
five up. I did not know what he said though. I can mute. What are you saying? Wicked rude.
What? Who me? I haven't even talked. Why am I wicked rude? I think I need another, I need
another coffee though, for sure. Yeah. The best part about like having, being a streamer that's
in a call with a bunch of other streamers is like, I, I can just leave. I'll be back in like two,
three minutes. I think he was in the bathroom. I think he's going there. Okay. Okay. I'm sorry.
I grabbed it. Do I have time to grab a copy? Yeah, go for it. Anthony, you're in. Uh, yes, sir.
Yeah. Perfect. All right. Love that. Are you Alex? You're in. Yes, I am. Wonderful Buddha. Oh,
there's 16. Oh, it was the pooping man. Uh, can you just join and then, um, do the old, uh,
just drop from it. Oh, sure. Yeah. Yeah. No problem. Then it'll, it'll start when he joins.
I guess we should wait a moment. Uh, so after it starts, just hop in your own discord and then
just discord screen share. You can just mute or deafen. I'm sure. Oh, discord screen share.
And then that's just an easier way to spectate. Oh, I might've boned Jerma right there. All right.
We're in. Oh, yeah. Let's get it. Do we restart? We might need a class restart because I did tell
them to go get coffee and then I forgot it. Yeah, I didn't even. Yeah, back out. Yeah, back out.
Yeah. More chances for ducks. Good thing I got bad RNG. I had three ducks, man. I had three.
I'm actually not playing ducks because I hate them. We were abandoning, right?
It's on principle. Yep. I respect that. Everyone's on the standard. Plus I get three.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. We're leaving, right? Same. Good. Good. Wait, are we leaving? I love that.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Because Jerma's going to get coffee, right? Okay. Are we going to do some code?
It's going to do same code, but everyone can't join at once because if it starts again,
we'll have the same problem. Right. So everybody's got to leave first.
It's not letting me join the same code. Well, let's see. Well, yeah, I can't join either.
No, we're just we're just waiting, I think. Yeah, you're good. So I've never played this before.
Am I allowed to get help from chat or like, or is that like a no go? No, no, absolutely. Please do.
Okay. All right, cool. Yeah, because I'm going to this blind man. I have no idea what I'm looking
at. I think a few people are going in blind and I think that's why we have the bottom bracket.
So it's going to be it's going to be hilarious. It's going to be funny. It'll be good content.
I know we're going into you guys and it's going to be fine. We're going to get absolutely rolled
by the pros, but that's okay. All right. New lobby code. Normal line. I don't need to join this one.
We'll commentate together and hop through. Understood. All right. So 11 a.m. is early.
Is this what I'm understanding? Yes. It's late for me. It's late for you.
No, it's a joke, but I do wake up at like 9 a.m. right now.
Well, this guy's up at 4 a.m. in Japan.
Just know that after last night and he's like, what time is it? I was like 11 hours from now.
He's like, yeah, I'll just stay up. No, actually, I went to sleep for like four hours. Yeah, I had
to. Wendy and I were awake at 7 a.m. and we're like, we shouldn't go to sleep. We're not going
to wake up. Dude, I got two. I woke up to two flake messages from me, Young and Mango, both going
like, hey, don't hate me, but I might not be there. I'm back. Sorry. I feel like I'm holding
everybody up. I gave you my word. I didn't cook for the house to be here. I appreciate that.
It's a nice afternoon here in New York. That's all I'm saying.
Okay. Bad news. I think me on stream. Oh, she's back. Oh, I already lost a match.
Maybe your internet. No, no, no. We had to we backed out for you so you can back out.
Oh, okay. New code. It's in general. We have three more people who need to join. We're good.
Okay. Apparently Mango, because he's not on the call, was playing against bots.
He's like, wow, dude, so good. He literally said I was on a run.
So this is what happens when you win. Hello. Hello. Well, all right. I think we almost have
everyone. We just need two more. Yeah. What's the win condition? Is it collecting a bunch of
trophies like all the trophies? I think it's me young one and I don't know if there's mango
for sure. So if you get all the trophies, that's like a win condition. Like what would you consider
a win? So the way trophies in versus is it's lives and you will die and run out of lives.
So you just need to live longer than the other people in this call. Okay, I see. I don't know
exactly how they calculate how many lives you get because I feel like it varies sometimes
in the regular game mode. Would you guys consider up around one part, seven rounds to be good,
like eight crowns to be good. What's, what's like, all right, that was a good, that was a good run.
Yeah. Seven. It's good. Yeah. Seven. It's great. Yeah. So when I get like four under 10 personally,
but I can appreciate seven. What about, what about between like three and five? Is that considered
okay? Well, I should get at least five. I'm sorry. Did you hit it with a higher number
and then count where you're at? I think one to four is the only bad ones because you should just
play for, you should swing for the fences, right? Zero is better than four. So do you guys just
leave game? Like do you just abandon game if you have? No, no, because then you get a dunce hat
nowadays. They patch it. Oh. Yeah. The game makes fun of you if you abandon. So you have to play it
out like a hero. Wait, do I get a dunce hat if I already abandon them? No, if you abandon a bunch,
only pubs or something. All right. Yeah. The arena resetting for that perfect to triple fish.
Damn, so knowledgeable. I think it's just me young. I think she's having some audio
and stream problems. It just F. Yeah. I'm also just downloading steam. So I need to say, yeah.
I just said at least we know he has friends. Yeah. You're already wearing a dunce hat. I've
been wearing a dunce hat since at least 10 years ago. Okay. She played, see if they'll play among
us after this. Absolutely not. Only play Super Auto Pets on team. No, you can play on browser.
Right. It's better to play on browser in my opinion. There's a browser. Yeah, there's a
browser version. If you go to Teamwood games or whatever. The browser version. Hell yeah.
Where is that? I think it's teamwoodgames.com or just Google Super Auto Pets. Oh hell. They said,
I don't know. Wait, what? Among us, among us. No. Play Farmville. Ask Ludwig to the winter formal.
I can't tell if they're ignoring you. No, no, I'm muted. I'm unmuting when I have to ask
somebody something. I'm not just talking over everybody right now. Will, is it just you at
this moment? I have it. How do I join the game? Versus and then there's a code that Ludwig posted.
Yeah. In Discord. Versus and then join private. Okay, got it. Yeah. And then just the name.
Oh, yeah. Don't say it out loud because people can just snipe it. Yeah. I'm definitely leaked.
Go, Will. Go. It should be fine as long as Will joins in the next 13 seconds.
Oh, are you in? Is that you, Will? I'm in. Okay, that's us. Perfect. All right. Everybody off to
your own Discords. Okay. Own Discords. And then go live on Discord showing your perspective.
Yo, good luck, guys. Good luck. Oh, you might have to pull me from my stream. You guys are
going to need it, man. You're going to need it. Because they're about to get smacked, man. Okay.
I can't do that. I'm on my phone. You're good. I'm not sure I can do that. And I have, like,
program authority problems doing that for some reason. All right. Here we go. I'm ready. Are
you guys ready? We're not on, like, a time limit or anything, but I don't want to be slow. So,
hold on. Let me turn this up. All right. So, turn one. I, uh, all right. There is a timer.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What do you see? Don't say that. Stop lying to me.
Oh, did I do it? I didn't know there was a timer. What the fuck? This looks, I look so stupid.
This is somebody that's never installed the game once. I can't fucking believe it.
I didn't know there was a timer. Oh, God damn it. That's, uh, it's oh, it's over. Like, I've,
I've fucked up everything. This is bad. This is really bad. Okay. Um, I didn't have a chance.
Okay, sell. Give two random friends one health. All right. I have to have at least two people for
this. Let's do bird again. And, um, beaver. Fuck. I'm so, I'm so thrown off. It's over.
I'm on the wrong pack. Oh, Jesus. Oh, no. How am I able to play in the game?
Okay. Why I have the wrong pack. This is, oh my God. I thought once we got into the game,
it would be all right, but like I'm in the wrong pack. I may as well just fucking lose and just
watch YouTube videos. Okay. So I don't know how I'm going to salvage this. I thought I was going
to do okay, but this whole thing started like as such a disaster. All right, here we go. Um,
I mean, does this really matter anymore? This is the worst team that's ever been put ever.
What do I want? All right. We have, I have to at least go. I have to get something on somebody
now. He's going to do seven damage. Uh, not the cat spider. I take so long to do these decisions.
That's why I'm not used to the timer. Did you lose? Oh, absolutely. Like literally the first two,
three turns. Like this is turn three and I live on discord. I don't think I can
the way that, uh, after through OBS, it always screws up. Let me see if I can get it to work.
Is this going to work? Oh, not the webcam. Yeah. I can't, I can't get it to do my video.
I've tried, I've tried this before. I'm going to be the first to be eliminated after this.
I just have to take this loss completely. Why am I throwing? I'm really not even trying to.
I just like have the wrong pack and the missed the first two rounds. All right, here we go.
I need another. No, I don't think I can do the rat right now. Let me do this.
So I get two peacocks. I think so. Okay. Well, this fish freeze fish and I got to move this.
So this is all right that I needed to be here. What do I want to have that attack you? Okay.
All right. Let me see. Share my, let me try to, let me see if I can get it to work.
Bind the fish. Yeah, I got a freezer mill. That first round just,
Oh, that's actually really good. That's really good. That might be the save right there. No,
definitely not. Unless I don't think so. No, too bad. I'm, I'm guaranteed to be the first person
up. All right. Can I salvage this somehow? I'm sitting there talking like a dickhead and I'm,
I wouldn't, I wouldn't pay any attention to this. Oh, should I give? Okay. If I, okay. If I find
another fish, then this is potentially salvaged. I'm going to give this to the peacock because
garlic on the peacock is great because you want the peacock to get hit. All right. Give me fish.
This is good though. This, this is, this is really good. I'm going to, I have to get rid of somebody.
I have to get rid of somebody, the spider, I think. I don't, I gotta get rid of the spider
and I have to put this on behind the peacock. Well, the bird, the bird has the meat. Okay. All
right. Come on. I got to pull this back. I'm gonna, I'm dead. It's not enough. That turn one, turn one
just killed me so bad. I can't. Well, okay. Now we're doing another one. We're doing more than one.
This is like, I'm going to fail the first one, obviously. All right. Here we go. Finally. All
right. All right. This is important. I want to freeze you. I want to give the meat to somebody.
All right. This is going to give one, one to everyone here. I'm going to, I gotta roll. I
gotta roll for something, for another peacock. Okay. Okay. All right. Look at that llama. If you
have four or less pets, that's not going to work, but we're going to do this. Oh shit. Okay. I,
I gotta get rid of somebody. Who do I get rid of? Probably the, the fish at this point needs to go
and I'll replace fish with rooster. I think that's a play. And I'm going to give rooster the meat
bone. Oh, okay. Or the chicken, maybe. Chick behind the rooster. I, all right. I, I, who do I sell
though? Who do I sell? Who do I sell the fish? Probably. Fuck. I don't have enough time to think
about this. I have to sell the fish, put the rooster up, and then I don't want to save any
of these people. Okay. All right. All right. Hold on. Freeze you. And then, oh God. Oh my God. Oh
my God. Oh my God. Oh my God. Where do I go? Here. Here. Like that. Okay. Cause this, yep. All
right. We're good. Everything's fine. Cause he gets the buff from the bird. All right. All right.
Come on, Gwen. Let's go. He's got the garlic armor. Garlic armor means take two less damage.
This is going to be a win. No, it's not. That was so much overconfidence, but nothing.
I actually think I'm okay. Well, I didn't lose. Oh, that's right. He, he summons the chick. Okay.
Wowee. Ho wowee. Let's do this. This sucks. If you buy a tier one pet, give current and future pets
one, one. I don't. Bison is, seems pretty good if you have a level three. I like this game,
but I'm not very good. All right. I need to figure this out. Um, I don't want any of these.
The dog might be all right. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No, he's not. No. Uh, let's just feed
some people cause he gets buff from food and, um, uh, worm is actually kind of good. I don't
know if I want to keep the worm over the potential, uh, okay. All right. I just need
to warm up round. That's fine. That's that, that shark is going to be a big problem though.
This is a problem, but I, if the, I can last a pretty long time here with that garlic armor.
That's fun to say when you've been fucking lost it, isn't it? That's all right. I can handle it.
God damn it. What is this? All right. If you're watching my perspective, I didn't play the first
two rounds. I didn't know there was a timer. I was talking to Chad about pancakes and waffles
and shit. I didn't know there was a timer and I'm using the wrong pack anyway, so I'm disqualified.
So I'm, I'm out. Is anybody else out? Oh, okay. Other people were out. It wasn't just me. I wasn't
the first one out. All right. Let me get in there with the right pack, with the right mindset,
with the right everything. You know what I mean? Let me get back in there. Oh my God. He gave 35
subs Tommy B. Thanks a lot. I'm going to come back. Yeah. Lower bracket legend. Well, I, I'm
finished the tier list. Yeah. I have to go here. All right. This game is really fun, but
all right, we need to change the hat. Let's put the flower hat on. Okay. I'm ready now.
He cheated and he lost. I feel like people are just like clapping for me because I'm the old guy.
You know what I mean? Like, oh, German. Yeah. Come on. Come on over to the,
to the tournament we're going to do. Oh yeah. There you are. Hi. Yep. Your seat's right there.
Grandpa. Right at the end of the table. I clicked a click to use a different pack
that everybody else is using. Yep. Grandpa. Hi. I don't even play the first three rounds.
Oh, do you see grandpa just took just, just, I have to pay $2. I landed on park place for grandpa.
What time is dinner?
You're not. I know. I'm just kidding. I was kidding. Don't worry. Uh, so who's, who's actually
winning? I just watched one of the other perspectives or should I just do some practice
practice? Well, uh, good luck and congratulations to all the winners.
Let's do some practice. All right. And if I had a second, you know what I mean? Like I would have
already done this shit, like horses, bottom tier, absolute zero. And there you are. And there it is.
And there it is. That's a great starter. We're going to be the shy. We're going to be the shy
feet. The frigid legs. I like that one too. Yeah. I like this one. So now we got a team, right?
Rigid legs. Okay. It's fine. Mosquito is good. All right. Now this is important. We're going to
give this to, who do I want to give this to? We'll get a beaver and maybe a mosquito just to round
it out. And then we're going to give the, let's roll. Okay. This is good. This is really good.
I do this now though, or should I wait as technically you get tier two and then you can
go to tier three, right? Cause when you, when you get to three of the same, right? As if you,
when you see me combine stuff, when it's a leveling up the creature, when you do that,
it gives you the next tier. It pulls from the next tier of animals for you to play with. So
shouldn't I wait for that to happen for us to go to tier two? So then I can just get a tier three
kind of next turn. Yeah. From my understanding. So then I'm going to freeze you and give this just
to the person in the back, which is by the way, a guaranteed win early on. If you honey the back
line here, this person here, it's pretty much a guaranteed win. Cause nobody does that. This
should be a pretty, this should be it. I think it's going to be all right. Everybody does that. I
know they're all going to lose. Okay. So now I have tier two. This is where combine this. I want
somebody else up here though. And I don't want it to be a cricket or start summoning. I don't have
anything that is synergy synergizes. I don't have anything that synergizes with the dog is the worst
stream of the year. Well, yeah. Right. I actually, I don't think so. I don't know. I feel like this
is going to get good buying the fish. Yeah. But I want another person to get the one one. Hmm. Okay.
Well, I know I'm doing this because it's just so good early. Maybe beaver. Hmm. Copy health from
friend ahead. Uh, every time he attacks, he hurts the person behind him. So you need somebody that
takes like a hurt does this. Hmm. It's really funny watching you fail. It's probably why you
got invited. Hey, now I can't afford the fish. Oh, shit in my pants. You're right. I'll do it next
turn. Hmm. Spider, I guess I should be upfront too. This is annoying. And then this will kill.
And then, yeah, that's fine. Remember you suck at this game. Yeah. Well, you know,
that's fine. I think this is a win. Hey, I still, I still think I got this. Wow. Um, nevermind.
No, no, I do. Yeah, I got it. Why does he only read from the room chats? Because I have, uh,
I have this, uh, third party app that just shows only specific keyword, uh, users and stuff. So,
um, loser, stupid, idiot, dumb, um, slow, uh, hurry up, too slow, speed, uh, brain. Brain's a big one
that I look for. Yeah. I take my time. Sorry. I take my fucking time. Holy shit. Okay. So let's
go with, I want the swan. The swan is very good. So I'm going to get rid of the mosquito
before I do that. This is no, no, I'm going to do a big brain play. If I kill this, it'll give
it's two, one to you. Put up the goose, do the level up. And then here we go. One, one. There's
the giraffe. End turn. Give friend a head. One, one. Ooh. Uh, is that better? Should I get rid
of the beaver now? I think so. Nice. Okay. Let's put the giraffe up. Fuck it. Why did it say that?
That's the only time it's ever said the name of any animal. Oh, that's good. The dodo bird.
I like the dodo bird. Um, okay. New germa frog. Cause you can call a germa a dumb ass. Yeah,
that's fine. The giraffe to spider. So this, the spider is going to start to get a little bit,
a little beefed up. Oh, maybe not. We'll see what happens next turn. I want this though,
cause I want it for the spider. All right. Let's go. I got like frozen halfway through that one.
It's too early. Too bad. It's the giraffe that's going to get the melon armor,
which you get one hit for free. And he's going to just buff up this guy. Um, just barely,
just barely. We get to have a draw. Badger when it dies, deal attack damage to adjacent pets.
That kind of sucks though, doesn't it? Shit. Ooh. The ox is good too. I'm keeping the ox.
And should I replace, um, who should I replace with this? I'm freezing everything in a peacock.
Don't want the peacock. All right. This should be good next round. Yeah. I'll get rid of the
mosquito. I, the spider will start to carry this when the spider starts to carry, that's where it's
going to get good. Right? So I can get over, I'll get rid of three of his first three characters.
I have enough to kill his Dodo. Oh God. I, it's going to be, yeah, I do. I went,
that's why you always put the B in the back. Give something to the giraffe. Yeah. I think
mosquito goes away. All right. Who am I going to give the garlic to? Swan. I think Swan gets
the garlic. He's got the most health besides spider. I'm going to sell the mosquito. I'm going
to buy the ox. So now the ox, when this thing dies, it summons something, which when that dies,
he, so he's going to get this twice and melon armor and he's going to get hit with one ones.
So he's going to be buffing the ox. The ox now needs the garlic armor. And then we round it out
with, uh, leveling up the spider. I think, I think that's all right. Let's see what happens.
So the tournament, I think it's, I think they're still doing it. They have players here that are
real. Oh my God. That was 30 damage. So it just ended. All right. Well, we'll get into it.
See what's happening here. Every time somebody dies in front of him, he gets to get two more
health. I mean, two more damage that worked out, but I, I think this is a win. This is,
Oh no, it's not. Damn it. They're waiting for you. Let me find out. Hey, you think, well,
it's unfortunate you did make it through because you slightly cheated there by using the payday.
Listen, I was told I could use whatever pack I wanted to. I did the same thing. You were told
that yes. Uh, this was the common conception among the pro circuit. I'm glad I wasn't the only one
I got. I'm sweating. I was, I was here and prepared like yesterday too. And it's like,
Oh yeah, I don't even know what I did. What did I do? You used the pay to win pack and I said it
was free to, uh, free to win only for this one. And then I said, uh, the main lobby, my bad. I
didn't even know I was using a browser version. Yeah. You know, I think we'll, we'll, we'll let
it slide. I honestly don't think it's like, um, a big difference maker. I mean, if you don't expect
that it can be a little weird, but I don't think pay to win is better than free to win even.
Uh, I have no idea which bracket I'm in. Was I the only one who didn't buy pets on the first round?
No, I didn't. I'm sitting there. I'm sitting there. I'm not knowing like what I'm looking at,
right? I'm thinking I'm looking at the fucking starting screen, which I was I go into battle.
My chat's like, you didn't buy any pets. I'm like, what do you mean? I literally get rolled.
And then the second round, I finally have pets. And then the people have more pets than me.
It's got to absolutely demolish. I just, I just didn't know that I didn't know there was a timer.
I said it to the normal pets. Now I was quite confused. You can play whatever you want. Now
I was against the lady bug. And then the second round, there was a person with one pet.
You can play any deck in the second will might be in a one V one against me though,
for the eighth spot. So, oh, well, no, no, I believe you guys are both, uh, in top eight.
You guys didn't draw, but you drew. So I think it's logic stands five up Abe,
Yeti, Ray, Dan, and Will. Uh, and then the other bracket is, uh, Wendy,
Jerma, Saikuno, Mango, Buddha, Anthony, Otto, Alex. Very cool. Uh, I believe is the seating for each
or not the seating with the people on each. Um, and then give me just like a couple of minutes.
I'll get the seating up and then we'll start the tournament and everyone can just play one
V one at once. Sounds good. Let's do it. All right. Did you say any pack this time? Does it matter
on this any pack? Yeah. Any pack's fine. Any pack. I would just recommend buying.
I'm going to play Anthony in the first round, please. Just don't buy pets again, please.
No problem. You know what, man? I got, I got a nasty little strat.
It's a lot. You can go ahead and see that one. We've agreed to it is really fun. It is a great
game. I've been so addicted to him. Oh, he played it so bad. I feel all right. I'm muted over there.
All right. So let me, let me see if I can play this out because I feel like this is going to get
all right. So the shark is one versus one. I'm around for the other brackets or is it just like
the rest of it is all white. I believe so. Yeah. I think I get rid of the night. No one from the
winter black bracket plays somewhere to the draft bracket. No, no, it's two groups of eight.
That would be so important. Number eight winner that and then it goes up to the end.
Oh, simultaneous matches, right? Yeah. I feel like I need to replace somebody, probably the fish.
So it's like first and eight seeds or some shit. I would assume so. I don't know how they roll me.
Is that what's going on? It's way better if they randomize it though. Yeah, they should randomize
it. Well, I just have a stream. He had the bracket two, seven, one, eight. Oh, no. I mean,
will and logic means I don't know. Me versus Aiden. Do I have time to use the bathroom?
All right. I think we've got like a minute or two here. What? He killed it. What? What happened?
How did he kill that? Oh, that's that's actually pretty good. I'm happy about this.
Did we all take a few hits? Come on. Well, that sucks. The whole reason I bought the
shark and he died instantly. They should better at this game than Mario Kart.
Now, that's the first round. I really I swear to God it was I just wasn't prepared. I was.
But you know what I mean? Like it just I was all fucked up. I missed the first two rounds.
And then it was like at that point I was just buying. I just bought the first three random
things I could find. This one will be better. I promise. Skunk is good. Oh, OK. Wait,
I need stuff that dies and comes back. Spiders like let's get the I need stuff that like dies
and comes back like another spider, I guess. Another giraffe. This is good.
All right. All right. All right. Check back and make sure what should just played better.
Predict the bet. Yeah, that's my fault. I should I chose the wrong pack. I think we're good.
I'm still got time. All right. We want that spider. I want this pair. And now this if I get this to
a two, that means he'll give something in front of him to two, which is huge. All right, let's go.
This time, don't die. Can you say hello? Hello to my friend, Ben Dover.
Come on, Ben. Hope the Dover family is doing well. Oh, there we go. All right.
Feed the hell out of that shark. Stop that. This might be a victory.
No, maybe not. Do I have enough to get through both of them? I think I do.
No, it's going to be. Yeah, I do. No, you probably have some friendly banter.
I don't see a problem. You could have friendly banter. There's no problem with that. It's more
so for me to spectate and chat when you when you join. Yeah, we'll just meet up. Yeah. Yeah.
We'll just hop in. I guess if we're not in there, it's totally fine,
because most people we won't be in there for. That's not perfect entertainment for our own
stream. Yeah. How do we know who we're going to get? It's in the bracket. OK. OK. OK.
Do we make the games now? Yeah, we'll just you're going to hop in the call. Yeah, make the game
against each other to make the game, by the way, if you guys don't know, all you need to do is to
create private game, hit Max players to make the name and then just put it in general chat and at
the person. All right. So who are we out here? Well, I should be good makers. All right, logic.
I'll jump in your little thingamabob in discord. Sounds good. By the way, this is a best of one.
You can use any pack. OK. And we get eliminated. You're out. Should we be in the same
call as our opponent? Yes. OK. And then are we streaming our perspective on discord? Yeah. I
mean, only one you really know. I guess it'd be a bit cool. Both of you did. Yeah. It is stream your
POV. OK. Yeah. Something about the way that my stuff hooks in through OBS, it like it always shuts
off. Yeah, I know you're shit. Fucked. That's good. You're good. Sorry about that. And also,
if you don't start round two is the only other thing. Oh, OK. So wait until everyone's done.
Yeah. All right. We we good. Can we just kind of just stand and go off? Go off. Go off. All right.
Just enter your group or just enter wherever. Good luck, everybody. Where am I going? What's
up with all the licks in your chat? I don't I don't know. I mean, they like licking. How did you have
my chat open? I am streaming your stream and then putting my face over your face so people don't
notice that there's an audio to video delay. Appreciate you telling me. All right. Where am
I going? Round one, group four. Jerma, you are up against Wendy. Wendy. Yeah. So just any call
of Wendy. You can enter. Yeah. You know, people didn't really, you know, heed to the to the group
location. I see. I see. They're going to pick a random one of these rooms. You could just pick
any room. OK. How about round one, group one? That sounds good. Oh, there was another round
one group one. Oh, is there two of them? Yeah, there's a constellation, which is the one where
well, I did not do very well last round. Good. I'll be very honest. I made the pass already. It's
a woohoo yay. If you check the general channel, I added you. Oh, is that the name of the game?
Because I think that I may have just screamed you saying that when we get in. It's so easy.
OK, so versus mode, join private. That is the new pass for us. Very cool. All right. I don't
want to leak it. Don't think I should be in. All right. So this is don't do don't do around
two. We're just doing this once. Yeah. All right. Well, good luck. So how much how much experience
you have with the game? I play like a decent amount, but I'm not that good at it. OK. Yeah,
because I've been playing for about an hour or two, maybe. I'm going to try though. Yeah.
There's a timer, right? Timer. Illegal sausages. That's me. I need a name, too.
Did that in the wrong order. But, you know, get everything correct every time.
I need a team name, too. It took so long.
The talkative piggies. How does that sound? Well, I've got some piggies on my team. OK,
you don't got any on yours. No, I think I'm going otter strat. Otter strat.
Fifteen health. Oh, wow. This is going to be interesting. This will get interesting.
So I can't we can't really talk strategy because you're right here. That's right. We can't.
Well, I got the mute button. All right. What do I do? Why this game? This game has a way of
doing weird things. Yeah, it's the servers get kind of hammered, don't they?
All right. I think I ran out of time. I'm muted. Don't worry. God damn it.
Nice. Very nice. I'm definitely going to go. I guess I'm going to switch it up a little. Let's
see. Does the buff work? I don't know. I'm very I'm very curious. We'll find out.
Timer gets me like every time. Yeah, I actually didn't know there was a timer in the first in
the seating. So I like totally messed up one of my rounds and I was like, no.
Yeah, I didn't play pets on the first two rounds, I don't think, because I was just talking. Oh,
my God. I know I was so distracted. I'm just so distractible. Oh, yeah. I got to try to try
to beef that dodo up. Oh, it's gonna be close. Guys, I think it's time for ant. Do you think so?
Get rid of cricket. Go for ant. No, wait, get rid of cricket. Go for ant. That's I just said
the exact same thing. Nothing that I said changed. OK, is that it? The dodo needs. Oh,
shit. Thirty seconds. The dodo needs the buff. Hmm. OK. Oh, I realize we should be streaming
our stuff. Yeah. For some reason, when I try to hook through to do both, it doesn't capture
one of them. And usually the one it doesn't capture is the stream I'm streaming to.
I don't know why. I think I got a big play next turn. I'll see. Crab. What does the crab do?
Poppies. Dodo is so good. Oh, no. I do that wrong. I may have just done that completely wrong. Oh,
well, that's a beefed up pig. Oh, OK. All right. All right. All right. OK. I got a minute. I'm
sitting there freaking out. I thought I had like 10 seconds left. I'm also trying to think about
my life choices over here, man. Yeah. Hmm. OK. OK. I don't think it's going to be enough
until maybe next round. Oh, that crab, that crab getting beefy. I'm not throwing. I'm not throwing.
I have to mute. I don't want to sound like a weirdo, like like I'm screaming at people.
I'm not throwing. He sucks. You know, I'm not going to say you. I'm going to say no.
Leave me alone. OK. The play is give the meat to the deer because the deer is going to do five,
six damage and it's going to do five damage to splash damage. And then the play after that is
going to be mosquito. No, sell. I'm going to sell the mosquito and put the kangaroo in and then put
the kangaroo behind here. I don't know. Who am I selling here? Oh, my God. I have 20 seconds. Oh,
my God. OK. Play. I usually like take forever to think. So this timer is freaking me out. Yeah.
The only experience I have with the game is with no time or just sitting there,
just going, hmm, no, I wonder what that would do. Yeah. Well, I think I'm in trouble here.
I think that's what one or two more or no, two, three more. And then that's it. If you win.
How much else do you have? I have five. I think like two more. And it looks good.
He was saying, why do I still have the otter? It's cute. He's got a cute hat on.
Oh, you have hats. Oh, I have little bear hats. That's a lot of damage.
Oh, the monkey monkey's amazing. All right. Well, see what happens. This is my last attempt here.
See if I can pull through. Hmm. Your dual core CPU brain is overheating.
I have at least a Pentium three. OK. Oh, shit. That's they just gave me like every
big top tiered pet in the whole game right now. OK, pivot angle. Hmm. Oh, oh, you got the turkey
and the cow. Yeah, I think it might be it might be too little too late, though.
That is a GG. I wish you luck in the remainder of the tournament. Thanks. It's going to take for
to go through the winners finish and then the losers bracket. And then I have a feeling it's
going to go back and forth a lot in those higher. I'm like curious as how it's going to play out.
I need some more practice. Yeah, me too. Isn't that why we're here?
Yeah, well, Ludwig was like, hey, you want to play in the tournament?
I'm doing super autopets tournament and I'm like, sure, I'll give it a whirl.
It's really fun. It's actually like a really fun game. It is really fun. It's also really
infuriating. Mm hmm. Tournament loser speed run. Did I lose? Did I lose the fastest?
I have no idea. I think we have to report the winner or loser, right?
Uh, yeah, we just put it in general. I would assume so.
Okay. Have you played the DLC pack? I have, yeah. Do you like it more or?
I really can't even tell because I like the bugs. The bugs are cool. But besides the bugs,
it kind of gets messy. Let me wait. Let me take a look. Yeah, the Beatles are cool.
The what else we got? Is it bad in the main game? Because that's incredible.
Sorry, what did you say? Is the bad in the base game? Oh, sure. Because that's probably one of
the best abilities in the game to give somebody weak. I don't think it's in the base game.
Yeah, the bat replaces whatever you have for a buff with weakness. Oh, okay. Yeah,
it's not in the base game. Yeah, that character is insane. What else is in here? It's happy cats
new too. I mean, everything is kind of new to still people in the base game. I have no idea
how to play with a lobster poodle. Yeah, I haven't played with any of them.
Talk about you being the sus guy. What are you talking about? What are you doing? I'm hey,
I'll buy the link. It's just case you do not. I'm the sus guy. I think that would be like a okay,
like who cares? What are you talking about? Well, I lost the tournament, but I'm the sus guy. I get
to keep that. That's what I get to keep with me. That's like a double loss. Do you get points?
It's 5000 points to buy a new background. Yeah, I think so. Let me see. Or you can just purchase
it around. Oh, yeah, I guess so. Oh, actually, no, there's some with like 500 points and like
1000 points or something. I don't really care about the background. So I feel like the hats
are way better. Oh, yeah. I would definitely spend that money here. There's a lot of hats too.
A lot of cute hats. Yeah. I love how the 5000 point one is a golden poop as if that's the thing
that like shows that you're a true winner. How long does it take to get to 5000 points?
I don't know. I feel like it comes pretty quickly. Hey, what's up? Oh, wait, he's just,
I guess was spying on us and then left. Yep. I think people made new channels. Yeah,
I think people to move into the general, I think temporarily or new stuff. Let's see.
I need a sus hat. I don't need a sus hat. Why would I have a sus hat? I thought I was muted
when I just said that. Thanks a lot. That just, that makes it sound like that's all I talk about.
Oh no, Chad, there's no sus hat for me. Golden poop. Yeah. Early adopter hat too. This one looks
kind of cool. Only five bucks, right? For the expansion. The game's free. Yes. It's very,
very, very affordable for the kind of the word you get to play. Yeah. And you can also play it
on your phone if you have Android. Are you serious? Yeah. Oh, playing it on my phone. Oh my god.
I want, I have, I have iPhone, which sucks. Oh, you have an iPhone. Yeah. I want to play it.
I was going to switch to Android, but I just know Apple too. It's all I've used,
even though I don't like it. Yeah. I've also only used like Android, mostly except for like,
I don't know, like iPods and stuff. Yeah, iPad. It's funny because I was so against the Mac
computers. I was like, I'm never going to buy one of those overpriced pieces of shit. And then I
just bought all their other products. Okay. It says we can move to general. Okay. Okay. I want
to move over to general. Yeah. Good to do. GG's. GG. Good luck. I play among us on iOS. You guys
have fucking, okay. Yeah. Good luck. She, she was good. You're awkward. We're just have fucking
what are you talking about? You guys need to relax. Sounds good to me. All right. Uh, let's
get it started. You can just join semi-groups one. That's Psycho. No, I'm trying to think. No,
no. Excuse me. That's auto mango. No, it's Dan Ray. I'm looking reefer Dan Ray, your auto,
your group one, and then auto mango, your group two and auto, you just set it up and put the code
in general. Mango will join. Let me, let me just make sure I'm very clear. If I lost that last game,
that means I'm out of the tournament. It is single limb. Yeah. You're out from here. Okay.
Well, thanks for playing Jerma. I actually had a great time. It was like, actually it was like
really fun. It feels like a bit of a Jerma game. It's a great game. I love it. Some people have
called it the next battleship. I mean, I don't know if I'd go that far, but it's so addicting
to it's good battleship was pretty fun. It was really fun. Good gun here. Northern line. I mean,
it's not that big. All right, let's get it started. If you guys are, want to spectate,
or if you're like waiting, you can hop in just like mute. Okay. And so where, where do I go?
I go to Sammy's group one or number two. We're going to hold your match because we're just doing
two right now. I'll play for a little bit longer. I'm not going to end the screen. And then auto
mango. Oh, so I watch Ray's game. You just watch Ray's game. Yeah. Okay. Thanks for having me by
the way. Thanks Alex so much for playing brother. Yeah. I'll, I'll see you guys later. Bye guys.
Good luck to everybody else. All right, hop in, get it started. You two for you four. Uh,
and we're going to occasionally hop. Hmm. Yeah. Have a great time. Everybody. I wish everybody
really good luck on all the rest of the games for the rest of the day. And I will see you later.
It was a lot of fun. I was muted. Don't worry. I'm not a fucking weirdo. Yeah. The stream was
going to be small. That was fun. I look, I'm just, it was fun. What time is it? Yeah. This is going
to be a short stream. I'll play a couple of rounds. I am the sus guy by the way. No, I did. I did.
Okay. My biggest mistake with making like, um, just kind of like talk to small talk with it,
but just anybody is if I do like the funny voice, that's when it's like, okay, I gotta,
I gotta slow down. This is not like, this is not small talk anymore. I'm like, I'm,
I'm being like a funny guy. You know what I mean? Like, oh, the Mac, ah, piece of shit Macintosh.
Like I, that's slow down. That bit was so bad. I'm not even, it wasn't even making a bit. It was
just, you were so normal. I've told you guys this million times before. Okay. Like I, I,
we can be a weirdo in our own house, right? But we'll go to somebody else's house. If you get
invited to somebody else's house, you don't just grab a microphone in their home and just walk
around and just yell stuff. They're not prepared for that. They're not, they don't want to hear
that. You know what I mean? That's the quickest way to get disinvited to anything else in the
future is being in that general chat with like 15 people and being like, hey, once I picked
the beaver and, oh, that's kind of the, the beaver goes and makes that sound and then he goes na na na
na na na naas on the corn. And then I put the horse in there and they'd be like, all right,
Jeremy, we get fucking can you stop? Like, can you leave the call? Like, stop, we're trying to like
set this up. You can't be a weirdo in somebody. You could be a weirdo in your own home. Right.
You held that all in. I heard duck is bad, but that was fun though, that was really cool. You
You held, you were holding that in the whole time.
Host your own tournament where you're in charge.
Yeah, but that's the thing.
I could host a tournament and be in charge, but guess what?
When I send those invites out,
people are gonna know that I'm the one in charge,
and they're gonna be like,
I don't know if I wanna hear this dude nay like 20 times.
I might get, okay, I might get two people
to come to that party,
but it's people I don't necessarily want to be there.
You know what I'm saying?
Like, if you know like the weird guys having the party,
you might attract like the weird other guy,
and then you have to out weird that person.
It then becomes a competition between who's weirder.
No, all jokes aside, I wish them everybody else luck.
It was fun, I'm glad to have been invited.
It was very entertaining.
So now what's gonna happen is I'm gonna go pee,
and I'll be right back.
I'll play a couple more rounds,
and then I'm probably gonna stop
after like another 30 minutes, so I'll be right back.
We'll just chill.
All right, I'm back.
Sorry about that.
That was one of those really, really weird pees.
I was peeing, and it like felt like I still had to go.
Like I hadn't even gone yet, mid-pee.
You know what I'm saying?
Like after like a full 20 seconds,
it was like I still hadn't gone pee yet.
It was like, what's going on?
It was like at the brim for some reason.
No, I don't have a UTI.
And then it felt like it was going.
Okay, all right, let's do this a little bit.
We can take our time.
This game is actually pretty fun.
I don't think I'm gonna stream this again,
but I mean, I did say this is a short stream,
but I think two hours is too short,
and four hours is too long to be a short stream.
So let's see if we can round it out in the next 30 minutes.
Okay, the horse is, I don't like the horse very much.
I'm not joking, that's a UTI.
I'll be all right.
I don't have a UTI, okay?
A beaver is just good, early.
I keep hearing about this duck meta,
and I don't really wanna listen to it,
but I feel like give shop pets one-one.
Is that permanent?
Or is it only the pets that are down here in the shop?
Or is it a permanent thing to everybody?
Just those, huh.
I feel like that's not that good.
Maybe like really early, you just sell them immediately.
Like next round, just sell it.
I'll try it.
I don't want the horse though.
Here we go, okay.
I could do two beavers, and just buff somebody up.
Or fish is just a good, it's a two-three.
I'll go with fish.
All right, the confused teabags, the full scouts,
precious teabags, the precious bikers.
What about the precious teabags?
About buying bees?
I feel like early, the bees are really good.
And I wouldn't listen to anything I say,
because obviously I came in last place in the tournament.
But they just, they seem really useful.
Bee is ass most of the time.
Well, this is good, okay.
I feel like I know people are gonna,
people are telling me don't do bee,
but I'm gonna do the bee.
It's my strategy.
All right, do I just want a second two-three,
or should I get a cricket?
So that would be a one-one, maybe a second fish,
and I can combine them later.
That looks good.
Didn't I just buy?
You have a random friend, one-one.
That didn't happen.
Did it happen?
Happens when you buy the otter.
Only the otter?
Oh, I thought it was when you buy, oh, buy any, oh, okay.
Well, shit, all right, that's fine.
I think this is a winning team right now.
This looks like a win.
I'm convinced that you're me from another universe.
Not even a win, it's just a draw.
Only three-man, a one-one value is terrible.
Yeah, you're probably right.
No rat.
Ant is really good.
I think we combine fish and get ant.
I think you Leon for the 10 community subs, community subs.
Can we have a face cam?
No, I'm not kidding.
I don't have a t-shirt on.
I rolled out of bed and turned on the stream
like 30 minutes later.
I was up all night studying.
Do I just buff this guy up like crazy to make sure I win?
Well, that's easy.
I think I sell the duck next turn.
If there's a fish, I sell duck.
You sound tired.
Well, this is okay, so for everybody that's asking,
how come, dude, come on, how come you don't start
at like 10, 11 o'clock in the morning?
More people would be able to watch your streams.
What about EU?
I cannot function before noon.
I can't.
Even if I wake up at eight o'clock in the morning,
doesn't matter.
I don't function until at least one, two or three p.m.
Doesn't matter when I go to sleep.
Doesn't matter when I wake up.
So reliably getting up in the morning
and doing a live stream at 10 o'clock,
11 o'clock in the morning, which means that, okay,
so that means I have to get up around eight or nine, right?
So get up at eight a.m. and I'm just not a morning person.
I've tried a million times.
It's not gonna happen.
All right, well, let's do this.
Hold on.
I don't want to do this to the duck.
Oh, God damn it.
Can I do a second, should I do level two duck?
Is duck bad?
Should I just not do duck?
Oh, what else we got?
I like swan.
All right, I'm selling duck and I'm getting swan.
Here we go.
Nice.
Here comes the swan and then here comes otter.
Not bad.
Shrimp.
When you sell a friend, give somebody random one health.
This is the only other thing I'd be selling.
Although I could just, okay,
I could kill the ant, give the buff to somebody
and put the shrimp up there.
Because then I'm gonna end up selling the beaver.
I think that's not a bad idea.
Because if I kill the ant,
he'll give the two one to somebody back here
and then I can put the shrimp up.
It's the same stats.
And then eventually I'll get the one health
for selling the beaver.
Shrimp sucks though.
I'm gonna go for it, okay?
I mean, this is gonna be the beefy guy.
What?
Oh, it doesn't sell it.
It just deletes it.
Oh, no.
I thought it sold it too.
Oh, okay.
I thought I was gonna get one gold.
Shit.
No, well, that plan is gone.
No, what's the reason to just roll the shrimp?
Oh, fuck.
And you can control Z?
No, you can't.
Copy the health from the friend in front.
Damn it.
Oh, that's not good.
I like the peacock.
Maybe I'll hold onto the peacock.
Shit.
Well, did you get a spider?
I actually might not lose this.
I only have four as well.
I might actually win this.
Yeah, okay.
Is this a bot?
No.
Please make a joke or do a bit.
I don't think I need to do that
considering the first two hours of the stream
was like a joke.
Honestly, that whole tournament really did feel
like I was in a Mr. Bean movie, just in a video game.
I just was sitting there.
I made every single mistake.
I didn't know there was a timer.
I fucked up the first like three turns.
I'm playing checkers while somebody else is playing chess.
I'm trying to stay in the lines in the coloring book
and they're playing with chess.
I was not, I got thrown off so bad.
Sheep is really good.
We're gonna do sheep.
Wait, hold on.
Sell, give two friends one one.
All right, we're gonna buy the sheep.
We're gonna do the fish.
This would be really good.
Squirrel, buy, clear and fill.
She clears everything and fills the shop with food.
Interesting, okay.
All right, so now that I have a second,
like I can barely kind of explain to people
like what is even going on, I have no idea.
So this game is kind of like auto chess
or like Hearthstone Battlegrounds
or whatever other auto battler.
You have a set of 10 gold at the end
of the beginning of every round,
which everything costs three gold.
It's three gold for me to buy this.
I get 10 gold every round and your goal is to try to,
they all have little things, they're like little perks
and little, if this, then why?
If X, then why?
And you have to try to build up a team eventually
that's strong enough to take you to the end.
They fight on their own just by in order,
one, two, three, four, five.
You can only have five and there's no undo
and you're playing against other players.
Is this like team fight tactics?
I've never played team fight tactics,
but I'm gonna say yes, I'm gonna say yes.
It's like a StarCraft custom map.
Yes, but I don't know if I should buy the squirrel.
Is it time to buy squirrel and just feed somebody?
I don't think so.
What about the peacock?
Hope you're doing great.
I'm doing pretty good, I am.
I think I just re-roll the whole thing.
All right, now we're talking.
Now we're talking, now we've got some synergy.
So the whale swallows something at the beginning of battle,
which is technically killing it.
And then after the whale dies, it spits it out
and it gets to come back as a level one.
So look at that, we have a sheep.
It's going to eat the sheep and summon two rams.
And then when the whale dies, it gets to happen again.
Now we need somebody, we need the dog.
All right, this whole thing has to be redone,
this whole thing.
So I need to get rid of this, everybody pretty much.
Let's get rid of the beaver.
I get it in the right order.
Oh, fish can go, fish, can I buy everybody with the,
let's see, this is two gold, four, five, six.
Okay, I can afford both.
I think the fish, if the fish goes,
which then allows me to get the,
all right, I have to buy the dog first.
So maybe the swan, replace the swan or replace the otter.
Cause the beaver, I mean, five, five versus six, six,
get rid of the otter first.
Yeah, cause then I'm going to do,
okay, we'll get rid of otter.
Now the dog goes up.
Okay, and now the whale comes up,
which will get a benefit from the dog.
There we go.
So I have to make sure this is going to,
so I have to do this, right?
Cause technically you can only have five people up.
So I don't want to have to just be wasted.
Oh, wait a minute, fuck.
Oh wait, this is wrong.
This is wrong.
He does it at the start of the fight.
So he's going to just spit out a two, two ram.
Oh, oh well.
I think it's still going to be all right.
Okay, well we'll do it like this.
Dog is going to start getting buffed.
Okay, well we'll see how it goes.
Still greater in the numbers game, that's true.
This game's really fun.
I'm probably not going to play this that much on stream,
but when I saw Liberty play this,
I was like, that looks cute.
All right, so there it is.
Is he going to get the buff?
Yep.
Where's my second?
Oh, okay, I was like, what?
The dog is just a huge pain in the ass if you have summons,
but I didn't make it.
You know, he can speed it up.
Yeah, but I like to watch.
Another swan.
I could put this guy behind.
Hmm, money on the dog.
Might be time to sell a beaver.
All right, I think I'm going to sell beaver,
upgrade swan, sneeze directly into the microphone.
Ah!
After that, probably, did I even freeze the turtle?
Well, I know I'm doing this,
but I don't want to, hold on.
Let's do this first.
The dog gets a benefit from this,
so it has to be on the swan, maybe.
Okay, good.
Now, this can really start to stack up,
especially behind here or behind him.
Ox behind whale,
because anytime somebody ahead of the ox dies,
he gets a divine shield and two attack.
I feel like that's really good.
Or should I not do that and try to find more summons?
It only applies to the person directly in front of them.
Oh, that's right.
Swan will, I think behind here.
I'm going to, let me, hold on.
Let me see if there's anything else.
I know I'm doing this.
Just a constant stream of money,
especially if it's too gold around, that's a big deal.
Let me freeze this.
Let's just go for something else.
I don't know if I even want the turtle.
Ox and salad.
Yeah, it's too late.
Let's try this.
Let's see if this works.
Herman hates Elden Ring.
I was going to just go off
and I'm going to fake elaborate story
of why I think it's the worst souls game,
but why would I do that?
Okay, here we go.
This is where this makes sense here.
He dies, so he's going to get the buff.
This sheep dies, two sheep come out.
Perfect.
Yeah, all right.
This is going to work out,
as long as I level them up and beef them up a little bit.
I think he might have better stuff though.
I'll kill the first two.
No, this is a win.
Shit, no, it's not.
Damn it, come on.
He had garlic armor on.
Ah, no, it's still, it's a draw.
Ooh, monkey is so good.
Give the rightmost friend two, two every time you,
and every time you like go to a battle.
I think it's time to get rid of the, I don't know.
Who does this replace?
The dog?
The dog's kind of fallen off, or the swan maybe.
What does the one for do?
So every time some,
the character directly in front of the ox,
when it dies, he gets plus two attack and melon armor,
which means you can take at least 20 damage one time.
It's like a shield, like divine shield.
We need to buff this guy.
All right, let's see.
Okay, we're going to make a decision based on this.
All right, nice.
That's exactly what I wanted.
I think it's time to get rid of this one.
Yeah.
Okay, now I need garlic armor or something.
Ooh, ooh, here we go.
Okay.
The hippo is actually really good.
When you, if you kill somebody with the hippo,
you just get two, two.
You just keep doing over and over and over
and over and over again.
Monkey buff's going to get wasted on the sheep.
Should I have the monkey just give it to himself?
Cause I want the hippo eventually to be here.
I think we, I think I'm actually just probably
going to get rid of the sheep and the dog maybe.
Well, let's just roll.
Yeah, I mean, the dog is good.
It's the ox for the hippo.
Yeah, that's probably the play.
We'll do that next time.
Cause I want the monkey to buff the hippo.
Oh my God, I'm going to lose.
Holy fucking shit.
Are you kidding me?
This is a disaster.
What episode of the let's play is this?
I don't know, 200?
What's the title mean?
What does it say?
Oh, free space bingo perspective.
Yeah, but that means I'm the free space.
Whoever is playing against me in the tournament,
I'm the free space.
Like you're just pretty much guaranteed to win.
All right, let me get this right.
We're going dog.
I'm keeping the dog.
Getting rid of the ox, right?
Yes, yes.
Get rid of the ox.
Hippo going in front.
And then we're going to garlic the hippo.
And then we're going to go like this.
And that's a leveled up dog.
Next round.
Oh wait, I have to live.
I actually have to survive otherwise.
Why are you commentating like it's a grand strategy?
You know what?
I'm a nice guy.
I'm a nice person.
But when somebody comes in here
and I'm a good guy, right?
I'm a nice guy.
But if you come in and just kind of talk shit to me,
nice guy drops.
And then you will watch out, here comes the mad guy.
Here comes, you know what I mean?
Like I'm a good guy, I'm a nice guy.
Do I want to say anything else?
No, roll.
All right, come on, please survive this round.
Come on Hippo, please survive.
I don't think the hippo is going to survive.
Maybe because of the two, two.
Look, this is going to take off if I live the next round.
Okay, come on, let's go.
Don't get on my bad side.
Yeah, look, chat.
I'm a nice guy.
But don't like, you know, you get me riled up
and you get me pissed off.
Like, you know, don't get me fucking mad and everything.
You know what I mean?
I'm a nice guy.
I'm nice to people.
I'm not a fucking dick.
I'm not a bad guy.
I'm a nice person.
I actually might survive.
Oh, no, come on.
No, I don't live.
He's got a 21, 16 dog.
Dog's level two.
God damn it.
Oh well.
No, I'm a nice person.
Okay.
I do nice things for people.
It's like, okay.
All right.
So what's your point?
What are you talking about?
You're doing an extended bit here.
This is not a bit.
All right, parasocial Andy.
Don't let it get under your skin.
How dare you?
How dare you say something like that to me?
You're lucky I'm a fucking nice guy, okay.
I, how did I lose the first round?
What?
Oh, God damn it.
I need to, okay.
I'm just gonna, I'm being a weirdo.
This should work.
Do I level up one of these two or do I just feed someone?
Probably just level up the beaver.
Come on.
No, I think I still, yeah, I still got it.
Are you this bad?
I just won the match.
Okay, okay, okay, okay.
No, I don't want the dog.
Do I kill ant?
Maybe.
Oh God, okay.
So the play here is I'm gonna make a level three ant,
sell this ant, like just get the,
okay, let's combine the ant, one of them,
get another one.
Ooh, yeah, all right.
That's really good.
Play kangaroo, kill ant,
or play kangaroo, kill ant next turn
and give food to kangaroo.
Yeah, I'll do it next turn.
No, I, no, whoa.
No, I wanted to move him.
I wanted to move him to the front.
Oh, yeah.
I want, whatever.
Come on.
I was trying to move him.
I think I'm all right.
That's a crock of shit right there if I've ever seen one.
Oh my God, he got melon armor.
That just made you win unironically.
Oh, look, it doesn't even matter
because I can just buy this and kill it.
We're not doing that right now though, hold on.
Ah, interesting.
Come on, the worst one,
the worst tier three pet that you could have given me.
The worst one.
All right, I'm a nice guy.
But when I see shit like this that I don't like,
it really, it gets me fucking a little pissed off
and it makes me, I'll talk about it for a little while.
I hate to say this kind of shit
to somebody that like, I like to call myself
like a good person, but everybody hates me.
No, these suck.
I can't use the dog right now.
Oh, listen, he's a nice guy.
There we go, dodo, freeze.
Nice guys can get pissed off too, relax.
Because of boomer rant?
What do you, what?
Dodo, guys, I'm gonna sell the beaver
and the dodo is gonna get extra points.
That's a swan meadow, look at that.
Wow, I didn't even know how you did this.
Like how?
I think that's a win it is.
Okay, if I sell, oh shit.
Okay, it's random friends up here.
All right, this is where we do the thing that I wanted to do.
We're gonna sell, we're gonna kill the ant.
Give it to the kangaroo.
Mosquito is worthless now too.
All right, who do I replace?
I know I got to buff up the dodo.
So we're definitely gonna buy the dodo.
And I'm just gonna do this too.
Wait, no, hold on.
Get rid of the mosquito for maybe even the beaver.
The giraffe will buff the dodo.
Okay, let's do that.
The giraffe is gonna buff the dodo
who in turn is gonna buff the kangaroo
who in turn is going to, all right, that's fine.
I think everyone needs to move up a little bit though.
In turn, give one start of battle, give it to, okay.
And I'm gonna do this.
That's what I would like to call a pogchamp.
But if I don't see at least 500 pogchamps
in the chat right now, I'm gonna scream.
This is loud as I fucking can.
Sell the fucking beaver.
Next round, boom, boom.
Oh, this person has a background.
I know what they're doing.
All right, come on.
Not bad so far.
This dog is really scary.
I'll make it to the dog.
All right, we're good.
Very nice.
Okay, I gotta do this in the right order.
Sell the beaver.
Don't sell the beaver yet
because I need to give garlic to the kangaroo.
And that means now I can sell the beaver,
which will give two health to two people.
I'm really hoping it hits the kangaroo.
That's perfect.
That's almost precisely what I wanted.
Rabbit now, if a friend eats a shop food,
they get plus one health.
I wonder, that's probably good.
I need to feed somebody something.
I'm gonna feed the dodo the garlic
and that should be plus one health as well.
Let me try to get some.
All right, I have to do this
because it's a sure thing.
Okay, good.
Freeze that.
Get another roll.
That's another bunny.
And I'm gonna freeze the snail too
because if I lose the next battle,
then I just have to put him up there
and he gives two, one to everybody
and then you just sell them.
All right, this is looking good.
All right, let's go.
I think this should be all right.
Is this the guy that wore the snuggie?
This is a loss probably, we'll see.
Garlic armor is on the crabs.
Although I think the kangaroo is gonna carry.
Yep, that's a kangaroo carry right there.
Bingo.
Do I have enough to kill the next two?
Yeah.
Oh shit.
That was actually closer than it could, wow.
I won that.
So unfortunately, I'm gonna hold on to the snail though.
Give me another bunny.
Okay, so if somebody eats food, they get plus one.
So this is just gonna give them two people plus one plus one.
So it's gonna be just doubled up on the health.
Oh, oh my God, couldn't have been better than that.
You could not have even given me a better one.
What do you think?
Should I just get the ant, level up the ant?
What's my favorite soda?
It varies, seven up.
And then roll it.
All right, so in case I lose, I have an opportunity here.
So I think this is gonna start to stack.
Kill the dodo, why would I do that?
That's a level three ant, which is awesome.
Watching any new shows?
Not really, not really.
Give it to the kangaroo.
Ah, it's all right, spread it out a little bit.
That's a loss.
That's okay, that's fine.
I got a big, oh yeah, this is a big play here.
So I lost, let me think this through.
Okay, hear me out for a second.
What if I get the ant to level three, kill the ant,
do the snail, and then give food to kangaroo?
What do you think?
Sell the giraffe first?
Do not do the snail, sell the giraffe.
All right, well, I know for a fact
I'm gonna do this at least, like this is a fact.
I want him to have more health.
So now sell the giraffe, I sell giraffe,
then the ant up here, then put the snail up there.
Well, let's see what we get for the triple.
That's a fucking Thanksgiving turkey.
That's too bad that I don't have anything to summon.
Otherwise, cause this is one of the best,
this is one of the best cards in the game.
And I say that cause all I play is Hearthstone,
it's the only thing I know.
Summon, there's one here I know,
but like I'd have to throw away this whole party
and I like what's going on right now.
So what's more valuable?
Giving everybody right now on this whole team to one,
everyone, or throw away the rabbit,
get the turkey and the sheep.
I think snail is, I think it's snail.
And then I can sell the snail and put the sheep up.
Or should I do the deer, put the turkey up?
I think I like that.
Yeah, cause the bus has splash damage.
All right, so now the ant go first
cause the ant could give the six, three to the deer.
No, all right.
Now this is a big deal
cause he's going to give him seven attack.
This is huge.
The Dodo is huge.
All right, what's it going to go?
I freeze these both.
Hmm, I don't even,
I don't think I'm doing the summon thing right now.
I'll think about it.
Is this game actually fun?
Yeah, this is not like sponsored or anything.
Ludwig just said,
he was wondering if I wanted just to play in the tournament.
I was like, sure, why not?
This is a big deal cause he's going to knock this armor off.
This is huge.
That's a huge deal.
Now we need the kangaroo to carry.
All right, this is a win.
You ever going to play this again after this stream?
I mean, I don't know.
Oh shit.
All right, it's decision time.
Is it time to sell the ant,
give somebody a six, three permanently,
hopefully not the bunny.
Okay, do I sell bunny first, put turkey up,
get rid of ant.
But unfortunately I can't go over 10 gold, can I?
Oh, you can go over 10.
I thought you couldn't go over 10 unless, okay.
All right, turkey goes up, build the ant.
All right, I need something good here.
I want this to go on the kangaroo so bad.
Oh, right.
I did that in wrong order, you're right.
Oh no, okay.
Well, it's still a one out of three.
It was a 50, 50.
Fuck, it's all right.
Shit, it's all right.
Yeah.
Now we put the sheep up here.
Now we're in business.
We are in big business now.
Because this is gonna give, to anything summoned,
that includes the car.
So anybody that's summoned gets three, three.
This is gonna be okay.
I still have money.
What do I wanna do with my last bit of money?
Let's see, let's roll.
All right, this is, okay.
Really, really good.
Very good for me.
I'm gonna freeze.
Do I just use the dodo now or use the food?
Yeah, buy the dodo now.
I'm gonna hold onto these
because I wanna give it to, I don't know, maybe somebody.
All right, nice.
Level the deer up.
I don't think I'm doing the turtle.
What does freezing do?
Freezing means that you're guaranteeing
that that will show up next turn.
So it doesn't go away.
It doesn't get rolled out.
That is a monster back there, that kangaroo.
Beautiful, beautiful.
More splash damage, beautiful.
Four, beautiful.
Oh shit, but this thing is murdering people.
What was going on there?
I still win.
What the hell?
That thing was doing so much damage.
Is it gonna unhurt?
Can't do that.
I guess I could.
Is it time to get rid of the dodo?
No.
I'm really looking for another deer
or another dodo.
The sheep or the rooster?
That's actually a pretty good play.
Now we just use, let me roll because I can do it.
Copy ability from pet ahead as a level one until the best.
So this copies whatever the person in front does.
Parrot could copy dodo.
So would that mean that the parrot
would give the dodo three attack?
Yeah.
Does the parrot copy the bus?
The parrot would, yeah, the parrot would copy the deer.
Parrot is trash.
Well, I don't know.
Copy the turkey.
Oh shit.
Copy the turkey so then anything they could summon
gets a six, six.
That's not bad.
That's kind of cool.
But what would I get rid of?
Like everyone up here is way too important right now.
It would be an 11, 11 bus.
I don't have space for it.
I don't.
Eat shop food, give two random friends one, one.
Good.
That's really good.
I'm not gonna give that to anybody else.
All right, come on.
Let's go.
How many vitamin gummies can you eat in one sitting?
Why would you eat that many vitamin gummies?
That's like bad for you.
This is an instant kill.
Thankfully, he's not gonna be able to go through it.
It's gonna kill.
Thank God.
This motherfucker though.
Die.
Damn it.
Oh yes.
The turkey saved it.
Oh shit.
This is gonna be rough.
No.
No, he's had so much.
Damn it.
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah.
This is where it gets weird.
All right.
Gorilla, when it gets hurt, gains a coconut shield.
Works one time per turn.
It ignores all damage once.
This is a snake.
Okay, so friend, when the person ahead of you attacks,
deal five damage to a random person.
These two seem like a no-brainer,
but I don't know which one's better.
Behind the, I feel like it would be better behind somebody
that can, probably the kangaroo, right?
Because the kangaroo is gonna be able to swing
the most amount of times.
Put the dodo on the rooster now.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Or I could use the deer, but ah.
All right, hold on.
Let's do this.
If I find chocolate, then the deer is gonna stay.
I need to try it real once.
Fuck that splash damage.
That's good.
I feel like somebody should have this.
Food with health and attack effects
are doubled.
Splash on the kangaroo, that's probably the play,
but that would get rid of the garlic armor.
I'm gonna roll one more time.
Give it to the deer.
Yeah, because it's always five damage,
so it's gonna do five splash regardless.
Yeah, that's a good idea.
Let's do another roll.
Fly, when a friend faints,
summon a two-two fly in its place?
I feel like that would be better than the turkey.
No, I see the tier six and I go better.
Turkey and the fly.
So is it time to get rid of the dodo or the rooster?
Turkey and fly is big, big, big.
Dodo sucks.
Dodo or kangaroo, but this is the only reason
why it can even hurt anything right at this stage.
I think sell dodo, but that's a hard call.
Yeah, I don't know.
Yeah, all right.
We're gonna replace dodo with the fly.
And then, hold on.
I have another rooster.
Fly, rooster.
When a summon a two-two fly in its place.
Okay, I ruined it, how?
Okay, so I'm gonna do, yeah, okay.
But now, but there's not enough room.
Does the kangaroo need to go first?
Because this is gonna summon a bus
and it's not gonna be able to summon the two-two fly.
So I feel like this needs to be first
because this has to die,
then there's enough room for all the summons.
Is that wrong?
No?
Yeah, isn't that correct?
It's fine, you just miss one fly.
Turkey won't buff it.
Don't put kangaroo first, it will not use its ability.
Let's, yeah, okay, that's true.
Well, let's just see how this goes.
Maybe like this?
I think that's the fly.
All right, yeah, let's go.
Because I'm just imagining it won't summon all the flies.
Well, we lost anyways.
I don't think we're getting through this one.
Maybe, that's so good, but it's too late.
It's too late.
Is it too late?
Maybe, no, maybe not.
I think this might be, no, it's not.
This might be a win.
Is it?
I can't tell.
21, 10, this is a win.
Holy shit.
All right, well, that's really good.
I need to level up one of these guys,
especially the fly or the turkey.
Scorpion's so good though, it's an instant kill.
It kills anything one hit.
Do I stick with the plan and just keep this team going
and try to buff this team?
Or do I replace somebody with the instant kill Scorpion?
Just stick with it?
What about the food?
The canned food is usually really good, right?
Or are we just skipping everything
and just trying to buff these guys only?
Buff, buff, buff, just only roll for food
and buff this team, food.
Buff only the current team.
All right, let's go.
Oh, that's cheese pizza.
Okay, if the cheese pizza goes to,
oh, that's a cheese pizza.
Bingo, exactly who I wanted it on.
Give me another rooster or another deer, come on.
Or two turkeys, I want two turkeys.
Give other level two and three friends one, one.
I don't have any.
I guess I could just do this on the kangaroo.
Let's hold that for a second.
I can't sell anybody, we gotta run this to the end.
Back for 20 more damage once.
Oh, the shark, friend faints two, one.
That's a lot of fainting.
But the stake on the deer, is the shark a trap?
Fly is better.
Yeah, the fly I think might be actually better.
Freeze the shark at least, okay.
Well, if I can't lose, if I lose it's over.
Put the stake on the deer,
because it's a guaranteed more than 20 damage.
I'm either gonna do that
or I'm gonna do the three, three on the kangaroo.
I can roll again, but do I,
I think I need to save the stake.
Let's roll.
Oh my God, oh my God, oh my God, oh my God.
Why can this not be like a turn ago?
Oh my God, this would be insane.
Because that means he would be doing four, four.
Stake on the deer, freeze everybody,
because the cow is crazy too,
but I can't replace anybody.
All right, we'll go and stake in the front.
This is, I have to play for the win, right?
He'll kill the first thing.
Next round we get a level, okay, here we go.
I should freeze the cow, because then I could sell,
mm, shark better than kangaroo.
I don't know, not at this stage.
Especially if I can get him to like a 30, 30.
Yeah, no, no, I'm sticking with the plan.
If we live, we live.
I'm going, let's go.
Because there's nobody I can really replace.
The dog is terrifying, but I think, oh, yeah.
Oh man, okay, hold on.
All right, what we got?
That dog is terrifying, but I should be all right.
I think I'm going to be okay.
21, two, 18.
All right, come on, come on.
No, damn it, no.
He was just too strong.
He's just had too much attack and too much health.
Not well, double monkey.
I'm not sure I was going to get over that one.
Damn it, it's that kangaroo pole
couldn't happen last turn.
Oh well, that's fun, this game's fun.
All right, we're going beaver, cricket.
I mean, the horse sucks, but I can just sell him.
I should just roll.
Cricket sucks too, the horse is worse.
Just to go for the stats, mosquito.
Try to get ant, yeah.
I think ant's the best tier one person.
This is just a trade, so it's, oh no, it's not.
Oh no, this is a loss.
Remember the timer, it's been two hours
since you said 30 minutes.
Yeah, but what else am I doing right now?
I'm fine.
Fuck it, has more stats right now,
but it summons the one, one rap of the other team.
You know, yeah, let's just go for it.
Cricket first, oh no, he should probably be first.
Didn't you say this is going to be like 30 more minutes?
Yeah, I'm having fun though, but the rat last.
Nice, why last?
I don't know, because he has the most health,
but I kind of want him to tank.
Turns out it didn't matter.
Well, that cricket upgrade seemed like now a good idea,
although this is going to be tricky.
No, this is a loss.
Do I have to give this homework?
Don't remind him, oh, they're reminding me
to turn the stream off.
Well, I'll be back on Sunday.
This is just going to be a little thing
just to kind of jump in and play around with them.
The tournament, that looks good.
That looks good too.
I like the swan.
I like the spider as well.
Do a bug tier list.
Every single bug at F, honey bees at S,
praying mantis at S, a big stag beetle at A,
and that's it.
What about butterfly?
Ah, B, A, not A.
What about a worm?
A worm's not a bug.
A worm is a bug?
Worm is, no, that doesn't classify as an insecto,
whatever they're called.
A worm is a bug?
I thought a worm was something else.
It's not an insect.
Yeah, I thought that's not an insect.
Is it, okay, worm, bug?
Isn't it like a nematode or something?
No, worms are not insects.
Both worms and insects are classified
under the kingdom animalia?
Vertebrae, animals with a backbone,
and invertebrae, animals without a backbone.
Are worms insects or animals?
Are worms considered a bug?
What is an, no, it's not a bug.
It's like an invertebrate worm thing.
They're like nematodes or something.
Okay, although they are indeed invertebrate insects,
worms definitely are not insects.
Even segmented worms are not classified as an insect.
They're just called an invertebrate worm.
Okay, well, there's a post on MMO Champion
from like 10 years ago.
Somebody please settle a debate with me.
Are worms bugs?
It looks like this has been a battle for a century.
I disagree, I don't think that worms are bugs.
They're like an inanimate, not inanimate object.
They're an invertebrate object.
Whoa.
Okay, I'm gonna sell the beaver.
They didn't want it to go on either one of these two.
Not really, but you know, we kinda have to do this now.
All right, what does a level two rat do?
Does it just get rid of the dirty one, one rat?
I don't think I really want the spider.
Let's just get something else.
Oh boy, oh boy.
Well, okay, I'm gonna kill that next turn.
Forget about the dog.
Why isn't the rat last?
So it summons a one, one for your opponent
that betrays them.
What does that even mean?
Friend to head deal.
So you deal one damage to the friend to head?
What?
What the fuck?
Well, let's do this.
Okay, all right.
It's time to get rid of the ant and the mosquito.
Or should I roll for a level two ant?
Let's get rid of the mosquito.
Put up the penguin.
Wait, let me get this in the right order.
Put up the penguin, sell the ant.
Sell the ant now probably,
because I don't really want it to go on the penguin, do I?
I'd rather it go on somebody else.
Okay, that's fine.
Get you up there, upgrade the rat.
No, not yet, hold on.
Let's do another roll.
I just do two rats.
Don't upgrade, just have two rats.
It's gonna, I think, screw me over later.
I can roll one more time.
Get the sheep.
I think I'm just gonna do the rat.
He's gonna give one, one to everybody here.
Worm is a worm.
All right, this is kind of a shitty team, but whatever.
The rat is the worst unit in the game.
Well, sorry.
You want me to read that so bad.
I've seen you write that twice, at least.
You want me to say that so bad.
I've seen you write that more than two times.
I'm not gonna read it.
You wrote it 10 times.
Okay, well, whatever.
Let's go.
I feel like this is not that bad.
I should be able to get through the first two
with the cricket.
Yeah, the first three with the cricket, actually.
This is good, because the cricket's a two-two,
because he's, oh, nevermind.
Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
No, they're gonna win.
The rat's the worst unit in the game.
But I'm kind of stuck with the rat.
Look at his roll.
It's good, but not really.
Rab, copy the health.
Whale, rat, why would I do that?
Oh, I mean, I could do rabbit salad bowl.
Kill the rat, the whale behind the rat.
Why would I do that?
Ox and otter.
I'm going rabbit salad,
just in case I get something good.
Hold on, not really.
Actually really good that it hit those two.
I'll hold on to the dodo, maybe.
No, actually, it's probably too late for the dodo.
Yeah, let's just go.
Hailing the rat would just give me a one-one.
I don't know how that even works.
That's a wash, but he comes back.
This is gonna be tough.
Yeah, I'm in trouble.
I just didn't scale that well.
That's not bad.
That's actually really pretty good.
Deal five damage to the lowest enemy with the lowest health.
I think it's dolphin in the back, or even in the front.
Wait, snail first.
Wait, I think I want the dolphin
to get the buff from the snail.
Can I get rid of the rabbit?
Oh, what happened?
No!
I was trying.
I apparently had this selected, and I clicked what?
Oh, fuck.
Okay, well, whatever, goodbye.
That kinda sucks.
Put him first, because he only does that once.
Elephant would be good if I don't have anybody
that can benefit.
Yeah, we'll put him first, or rat first.
This game free, this game is free.
I believe this is $5 to buy the extra animals.
So, I believe this is free.
That rat sucks, but I think I win this.
It's not that good, actually.
That kind of is really bad.
That's not good.
I just gave him free buffs to everybody.
I think I still might win this, though.
Only one win, oh my God.
I know, I gotta get rid of the bunny.
Maybe the penguin, too.
Penguin's not doing anything right now.
Crab behind rat is not bad.
Then just feed the crab.
Hippo is amazing as well.
Think it's time to get rid of the penguin,
because the rabbit, I can feed the hippo,
and he'll get extra health from that.
I think that's what I'm doing.
Very good, roll again.
Really wanted something else besides this.
These two, it could have been anything else.
It could have been anything else but these two.
But, I mean, I have to use it,
because he's gonna get the health.
I feel like I should put him behind,
still put him behind.
I don't think he has enough damage to kill anything.
Well, I'm dead anyways, so let's go.
This is a dead rat run.
Oh, hold on, hold on.
Ooh, that's good.
What'd he just kill?
This is okay.
I think this is all right.
It is.
We live another day.
The bunny, yeah.
14 damage, holy shit.
Splash damage on, these are all good,
but it's almost like I can't even do it.
It's too late.
The shark with all the bees, yeah.
It's, okay, I gotta get rid of the rabbit,
and we're gonna do shark,
and we're gonna do bee on everybody.
Yeah, I'm gonna put bee on the dolphin.
Bee on dolphin or bee on, okay.
Splash damage for, oh, let's roll.
This emote is vile, I don't even know what I'm looking at.
Couldn't give me anything that could work with me here.
I could just do, roll again.
Heal seven damage to the last enemy?
I could just be the cricket.
Yeah, this is really like kind of a last ditch ever here.
Let's just try to, let's just smoke this guy up.
That's the best thing I got.
Let's hope I don't lose.
Are you streaming on a Tuesday?
I wasn't planning on streaming,
but I was like, you know what, let's go,
because I was playing in the Ludwig's Auto Pets Tournament,
which I did okay.
I did all right.
I came in last place.
I lost every game I played in a row,
and I forgot the rules the first three matches,
but it was not, it wasn't bad.
It was okay.
I think this actually might work out.
The shark's gonna get just so fed.
It really depends on what happens here.
I think this is a win.
Yeah, he's gonna be too fed.
Bee shark strategy seems to be pretty good,
because here we go.
All right, he's got 11.
He'll have, how much will he have?
13, oh, fuck no.
Nevermind, it's over.
Oh well, that was never great.
All right, I have to pee again.
What's wrong with me?
Is he not in the tournament anymore?
No, I lost.
I'll play another one.
I'll play one more, maybe.
We'll do one more.
But I have to pee again,
because I don't know, my body,
I don't know what's wrong with me.
I'll be right back.
One more.
Oh, it's Jebaited, but it's a turkey.
Okay, I get it.
I was trying, I thought it was a flying skull.
Flames behind it.
He was going really fast, I don't know.
Hey, let's go back, okay.
Very nice.
It's just time to continue.
All right, last one.
All right off the bat, this is a great one.
Already, right off the bat.
Beautiful.
Oh, yuck.
Oh, it's, ah, I didn't want to do that.
I wanted to move him.
Fuck, come on.
Okay, it's, oh, listen to me.
It's right, you hold right click to move.
You don't hold left click to move.
Don't make the mistake I keep making.
Shit, it's right click.
It's okay, I think this is still a win.
Or it's a draw?
No, it's a win.
Because my brain just wants to move,
like move you this way, move you that way,
but I got to burn that in my brain.
It's right click, right click, right click.
I like the fish on low levels.
Ooh, okay, nice.
I like it, looks good.
You have to pee?
We just went pee.
Go to the fish behind you, nice, perfect.
I'll just clean the rest of this up.
I have mine, why are you saying we?
Well, we as in collectively,
we all went to the bathroom five minutes ago.
Oh, beautiful.
It's like the game wants me to win.
It actually really wants me to win.
I mean, it's just good for now.
How come, does it just say giraffe?
How come it doesn't say that for anybody else?
That's the only person that says that.
Did I bring that up earlier?
That's weird.
Nice, nice, oh, nice.
All right, I think I'm gonna hold that sheep.
I'm gonna hold the meat.
I'm gonna give this to you
because I want you to have more health.
Yeah, well, they don't make noise.
Oh, okay, that's cute.
Hold the sheep, hold the meat.
I think so.
I get another fish, then the whole thing changes.
Whoa, he did way more than I thought he was gonna do.
What was up with that?
He just did so much damage.
Oh, why did he do that much damage?
Oh, because he has meat on, shit, okay.
Well, first loss, that's the plan.
Go in, all right, I'm combining fish
and I'm going to go with sheep and dog.
Or do I go sheep, tell the otter, that dog now,
then sheep instead of,
I feel like the otter, this two, two is so good though.
Maybe the giraffe, maybe, only when you buy otters.
That's true, but giving somebody a two, two permanently
right now is a pretty big deal.
Well, let's put the meat bone on the dog
or meat bone on the fish or ant.
I like that, cause that's 10 damage right up front.
Let's roll, I got some more rolls to do it.
Let's see exactly what I'm talking about.
That's why I held onto him.
Cause this is, I mean, that's, I can't do it twice.
I can put the sheep out there and I'm gonna freeze the otter.
We'll put out the sheep and we'll roll.
All right, whatever, let's go.
Correct order, dog champ, please say dog
with a Boston accent, dog, dog, dog.
I don't know what you mean.
Now we're gonna play the otter
and then we can just probably sell the otter
after that maybe, it depends.
If I get another otter, that's a big deal.
That's annoying.
Say with a British accent, dog.
I needed fish too, fish would be a big deal as well.
All right, let's roll.
I like the dog probably.
I don't want the bone anymore.
Maybe get the bone to the fish.
I want fish, fish or dog again.
I'll take the sheep maybe.
Yeah, do this now, fuck.
Okay, say with a shpee accent, dog, dog.
If I can last a little bit longer,
I can level up a bunch of stuff.
Now let's go.
You have to have summons for the dog.
Yeah, but that fish gives one, one to everybody.
I really wanna, and he's nine, 10.
That's like the only thing
that's hurting anything right now.
Oh, come on now, really?
That actually just happened.
I'm gonna be close, but I've still got it.
Do I though?
I don't.
Shit, no, I do.
All right, I was gonna be really upset about that one.
No, no, accents.
I'm not doing any more accents.
I could pill ant,
and then I need some more summon stuff.
Cricket is a summon, but meh.
All right, all right, all right.
Now we're talking a little bit here.
Okay, okay, if I get a level two dog,
then this thing's gonna get fed and it's gonna be amazing.
I know I'm gonna do that, so just do it.
Do I just do this now?
Roll for another dog.
Yes, bingo, bingo.
Absolute bingo right here.
Hell yeah, all right.
Now, this is good too.
I'm gonna hold onto this.
Next round, we're gonna make a bunch of moves.
Okay, next round is a bunch of moves.
Dog is gonna get two two for every single person
that is summoned, which should be all right.
That should probably take us through
at least the next round or two.
Say that what you just said in a Brooklyn accent.
So I got the dog, I got a dog at level two,
and when the penguin comes up here,
I'll be drinking my coffee
and the penguin will fucking just annihilate everybody.
That's in a row, you know what I mean?
They can take people out in a row, it's pretty good.
I've only had two coffees, so I don't know.
Probably gonna have to have a third.
Say that again, but in a dog accent.
Okay, I think I lose.
Oh, it depends how, if I can get past this fish,
then it's over.
Nine, fuck, no.
Does Jerma do literally everything Chat asks him to?
Not everything, just a majority.
Okay, now I gotta sit here for a second
because this gives everybody one one.
I wanna make sure the right people are up there.
This is gonna give somebody a two two.
This one I sell, it gives somebody a four two.
So I need, what do I do first?
Because I'm selling you, so I'm gonna have to do that first.
Let's do that, because I know I'm doing that.
That's the best person it could have just happened to.
Now we bring the otter in, right?
Otter is in.
Oh my, you, okay, come on.
Keep this fish, do I keep the penguin?
I don't know if I keep the penguin, I need more summons.
I need some bees and shit.
Or do I just do fish and then put the penguin up?
Because everybody, I have three level twos.
All right, I'm gonna go for it.
Let's do penguin first, and then let's go with the fish.
Stupid ass parrot, really.
Everyone's gonna get one one, except for the sheep,
but that's okay.
Dog needs to go last, right?
Well, all right, I have another chance after this.
That's too bad, a level tier five, that sucks.
Parrot and dog maybe, wait, I'll try it.
Sheep can't be in the front, that looks good.
I think I'm okay, looks okay.
He's a lot of buffs, I need more summons, bad.
Otherwise that dog is not gonna, shit, this is bad.
Very bad, very bad, I need more summons.
Damn it, this like turned out, this started so well.
I gotta get rid of the otter and the penguin probably.
No, I need somebody that summons shit.
Parrot the sheep, could parrot the sheep,
but let's do, I mean, this is just a no-brainer.
Let's roll for another sheep, and we got it.
And okay, this is good, this is perfect.
We're gonna parrot the sheep,
unless something crazy comes up.
That's not crazy, so here we go.
Let's get rid of the otter.
Should I get rid of the otter or the penguin?
Probably the otter, okay.
So now I get double the summons, it's gonna be two, four,
four rams, I'm gonna hold onto this food.
Hold onto both foods actually,
and see if I can get something good for the next round.
I have to survive this round.
No, I can't, why would I freeze that if I die, it's over.
Okay, well, this is it.
I think everyone's in the place that it possibly can be in.
We just hope that, I have to hope
that the dog can get buffed up.
There won't be enough room for the rams.
Should I move them back, like this?
I think that's the play, otherwise, yeah, I won't fit.
Okay, good luck, cute, darkest dungeon.
This is a victory, I get to go another time.
Oof, yes, I can, I think, unless that ox causes a problem,
which I think I'm fine, because here it comes again.
Nice, okay, we're good.
Darkest dungeon for kids.
I think I just throw this whole thing away.
I think it's, who am I gonna replace, the penguin?
It's too late, yeah, it's way too late.
Okay, the penguin gives three people one-one.
This is him giving himself one-one if he eats food.
It's just spread out more.
No, I gotta throw the whole thing away.
The whale could eat the parrot after he copies this, right?
So then we'd get, okay, whale the parrot,
because the parrot copies this.
This is gonna happen first.
Yeah, this is start of battle, swallow friend.
This is end turn, so he does this first.
Parrot does it first.
Use the can first, yeah, absolutely.
So if I get rid of the penguin, will this actually work?
I'm kinda curious, let's find out.
Because you're gonna copy your moves.
You're gonna die, become two.
He's gonna spit you out, you're gonna die and become two.
Wait, the whale goes first.
Oh, wait a minute, yeah.
That's at the start of the battle,
so he's gonna eat him, he's gonna turn.
I think it still is more.
Okay, well, let's just go.
Jesus, am I actually gonna, I have to survive.
I think we just do sushi and just hope for the best.
Oh, I could put parrot in too.
Sushi gives three one ones.
This will give the parrot up to what?
Like a seven something, eight something?
I think that's actually better, yeah.
Eight seven's better.
We can save this next turn.
All right, if I survive,
then this is gonna be a pretty good turn.
Oh, hold on, I could've got rid of the whale.
The parrot copies the other parrot.
Does that work?
If I had put the parrot here, a second parrot,
would that have been he copies this person
or would he copy nothing?
Would the parrot copy nothing
and then this parrot copy something?
Oh well, let's just go.
It actually does work, oh,
because it goes right to left.
This might not be a loss.
I think I still win, possible.
Yeah, I definitely win.
Although this elephant's gotta fucking die right now
because he's puffing these things up like crazy.
Kill this thing.
Come on, there it is.
All right, here it comes, the two.
Hey, hey, whoa, whoa, whoa, wait a minute.
Wait just a second.
Wait just a second, what's going on here?
Why did he copy, why did that happen for?
It turns it into a normal parrot?
So when he eats something,
he just removes anything that was on it before?
Oh man, it makes an entirely new animal.
So it's all, okay, it's death was triggered,
which means it's a new parrot that comes out
that did not copy anything, please.
All right, last one, one more, I'm done.
Last one, this is it, this game's fun.
And you know what the best part about this game is?
I know that like, okay, Hearthstone Battlegrounds I love.
I used to play it all the time.
Obviously I haven't really played it recently at all.
But I like the fact that,
I don't know how this matchmaking works,
but the fact that I can just sit here for an hour
and not even do anything.
I don't understand how the matchmaking works.
All right, well, I think we're just gonna pick this team.
Skeeto's fine early.
I think I'm gonna roll, good thing I did.
How about the obese posers, the obese feet,
the skilled feet, the skilled posers,
obese posers, that's so stupid.
The fussy piggies, you already buffed that, how?
Ooh, that's huge, that's bad.
Game's results are predetermined from the start.
You just watch it unfold before your eyes.
How is it matchmaking people?
Is it just based on how many trophies
and how many hearts you have
and it just finds somebody else
that has that amount of hearts and trophies?
That's a really cool way to do this.
It's by turn, if you're on the same turn.
That's kind of cool,
because it really doesn't even matter
when you press the button.
These are old teams from the past that are saved.
These aren't live, really?
So they're ghosts of other teams
that would explain the lack of timer.
That's really, really actually, that's really cool.
There's always like a saved team somewhere.
Someone is losing to you right now
or beating you from like yesterday or like an hour ago.
That's some pretty big brain game development right there.
What do I wanna do?
I think I'm throwing this whole hand away, good.
Excuse me, hold on a second.
I've right-clicked and dragged.
I swear to God, I swear on everything.
You even saw me hesitate.
I hesitated and I was like,
wait, I wanna make sure I'm right-clicking
and I right-clicked and dragged.
It's not, it doesn't matter.
Oh yeah, okay, well, let's, now I have to buy a beaver.
I need, I need stats.
I just, I have to buy the duck too.
Like I need stats now, I'm screwed.
Single click and move them
if you're worried about them mixing.
This team is awful.
Well, it's about to be pretty good
because I'm gonna sell the duck immediately.
God damn it, I think I still would have lost.
We're doing that for sure, because I want the peacock.
Peacock, I'm gonna combine the beaver, I think,
or just sell, see what I get.
Very nice, all is not lost.
Yes, it is.
Heal attack damage to adjacent pets.
That sucks, it needs to be last.
The badger in the back?
Combine the beavers, put the badger in the back.
No, did you fart?
Worst voice.
Speaking of worst voice, the nominees are gonna open up
probably in like a week or two, maybe like two weeks.
For you to nominate things for worst and best of the year,
you'll have some categories to look through.
Categories will be known in advance.
I'm hoping for the first week of December.
Finally, victory, crying out loud.
I didn't see the last part, apparently.
Kill the ant, hopefully it goes to, all right.
I'm gonna sell the mosquito.
Let me roll.
Sell the mosquito, kill the ant,
hope it lands on the peacock.
Sell the mosquito, sell the beaver.
But then I'm killing everybody.
All right, I know I'm selling the mosquito.
I sell the beaver, hopefully it gives it the health to him.
Sell your kidneys.
This sucks, but I kinda have to do it.
Shit, no more crabs.
Oh, the elephant, shit, you're right.
All right, we're good.
Okay, sell the beaver.
That sucks, but whatever.
Okay, now, I'm gonna have to pick, oh shit, okay.
Is this stupid, what I'm doing?
Do I just buy the swan?
Or should I roll for something better?
Crab on the peacock, swan it up.
It would be an eight health crab.
Yeah, that's probably better for right now.
I am gonna, no I'm not.
I could just, okay, I got an idea.
Why do I have a sus command?
Because I've, okay, I've been around,
it's not Among Us.
Before Among Us, I did a thing like five years ago.
I don't even know how to explain this.
It's part of a game, it's part of a game called Sorcery.
Steve, okay, well, it's, I have not lost or won anything.
What do we got?
I know that's gonna happen.
Wait, okay, so if I give this to the peacock,
if he doesn't actually take the damage,
that means he doesn't get the buff, right?
If I garlic the peacock,
it's not technically gonna get hurt.
Needs to be hurt, right?
So wouldn't it go to zero,
because he does one damage.
It doesn't any hurt, it has to be a minimum of one damage.
Garlic blocks to a minimum of one damage, not to zero.
That's not what it says.
Will always do at least one, even with garlic.
Okay, now the question is,
I don't really want the rabbit.
Do I want the food?
All right, let's see what happens.
Okay, I need another unit though, don't I?
That will make him a eight.
It doesn't, makes him an eight, eight.
I think I got this one.
That's wonderful, actually, what just happened.
That was unbelievable what just happened.
All right, well, he's gonna die regardless,
but at least he'll kill the whale.
Shit, it's okay though.
Turns out the crab was a great, oh, that's bad.
Ooh, oh, that's actually pretty good,
because it does its attack damage to,
now it makes sense as to why you use this.
I thought this thing was terrible.
All right, puffer fish.
Okay, if this guy gets to level two,
he does one damage to two things behind him.
So the puffer fish would make sense,
but I need another elephant to be on the badger.
I'm gonna stop freezing this guy.
I need an elephant or a honey, but I'm out of money.
So I think I'm just gonna have to, I'm not sure.
Should I just feed the badger and put the puffer up?
But he's only gonna hit one behind,
and the crab needs to copy the peacock.
The peacock is the one that gets the most benefit
from getting hit by this.
Okay, if I do this, I just have to really hope
that I get a second elephant.
That's what this whole thing is based around.
All right, well, I'm gonna feed the badger,
because that's six damage,
and I'm just gonna have to see if this works.
Put the puffer in the front.
I feel like he's just gonna die instantly,
because you have to get hurt and stay alive.
If you die, you don't get to do it.
Yeah, it has to be like this.
All right, well, hopefully I get a,
I have nine health.
I just have to hope that I get another elephant.
Another elephant, this is much better.
It looks really good, actually.
Well, at least that dies.
Very good, very good.
But is it good enough?
Is it good enough?
It is.
Give me an elephant, give me another elephant.
Give me another elephant or another puffer.
I should garlic the puffer.
Elephant, elephant.
Shit, damn it.
No, crab?
Would this potentially triple?
What happens if this does not upgrade
when leveling, nevermind, okay.
I think it's just be the badger,
because that's gonna do seven damage.
I'm just trying to win attrition here.
I'm trying just to stay alive,
so I can really level up the elephant.
So if everything dies,
but at least it kills the last thing,
I wanna make sure it can.
Well, kill that monkey in the back, come on.
Again, shit, sorry.
Brutal, that's bad, but it's okay.
I think it's still, yep, I'm good.
Badger stays alive.
Nice, very nice.
Finally, elephant.
Then he'll be doing damage to two people behind him.
Turkey, I don't have anything.
I just don't have anything that's good enough for it.
All right, I have no summons really.
I'll take it.
Place the crab with the turkey.
I don't think so, nothing's summoned.
I don't have any summons.
Oh, there's honey for the badger, right?
Do I wanna do that?
I think that's what I wanna do,
because then, ooh, I want that too.
Who do I replace?
I don't think I can even take the monkey.
I like this team.
Well, we'll find out.
Now this is gonna get very interesting.
I need to start scaling.
Yeah, that's true, nice.
At least you gotta do it once, bad.
Crab has been carrying.
Look at what the crab's been doing here.
Oh, come on.
No, shit, it hit the wrong person.
Oh no.
Oh well.
I think I have to replace the badger.
Crab has been doing so well.
He's a nine, 10.
Crab's gonna start to fall off.
It's the badger and crab for the monkey and the elephant.
Really start growing your front three.
Maybe it is time to get rid of the crab
and just put the monkey out.
Yeah, it's probably the play.
So then he'll be constantly giving the elephant tutu.
Keep you in the back.
All right, let's feed the elephant.
No, actually, not yet.
They might be better food.
I, okay.
I don't know if I wanna do this right now,
because I think I wanna give the cupcake to the elephant.
I don't wanna lose.
The elephant has to survive
with the peacock upgrade to even matter.
Camel might be a good replacement with the...
All right, wait a minute.
Camel gets hit.
It gives one, two to the person behind,
which is the peacock, which gets two.
So it would be giving every time the elephant attacks,
the peacock would be getting three, two
every time the elephant attacks,
which that's kind of insane.
I'm gonna go for it.
Two gold.
Do I freeze the cupcake?
All right, we got something else to hold on to.
Really?
Oh, it's too late for the scorpion,
unless I wanna get rid of the monkey.
The cupcake is temporary,
but at this stage, I probably need it to scale.
Actually, the salad does kind of suck right now.
It's never too late for the scorpion.
Yeah, but who do I replace?
The monkey?
I feel like the monkey needs to be here for a few turns
for him to be worth even buying in the first place.
Yeah, I don't think I even care about this.
It's too late now.
I'm going with this as this meta here.
I have to hope that the peacock just goes absolutely crazy.
All right, there we go.
It should see at least a few hits.
Here it is.
Boom, boom.
It's gonna kill the...
All right, nice, perfect.
That counts though, cause it was alive.
Does it not count?
It was alive when it happened though, right?
Oh, this is perfect.
Am I gonna be able to kill the dog because of this?
Oh, come on, no.
Damn it.
Get that shit out of here.
Oh well, I think I still lost anyways.
Well, I can't die again.
Aye, aye, aye.
Oh, this is a certain play here.
Gain four attack.
Why a tier one pet give all friends one one?
Elephant, elephant.
Maybe get rid of the badger.
Freeze the dragon maybe.
All right, elephant, cupcake on elephant.
Do double elephant?
Get rid of a badger.
Go with just double elephant.
I think so.
Go for a camel upgrade.
Wait, wouldn't double elephant not make any sense?
Because it has to attack.
So wouldn't I just be hitting my own elephant?
I don't think that's a good idea.
I mean, I could upgrade the elephant again.
That uses all my money.
I don't know, I almost kind of want to look for the camel.
I wonder if I should try to upgrade the elephant
or should I just roll everything and look for the camel?
Where is it to level the elephant?
I have to survive though.
Whatever.
Okay, all right.
All right, we're going to do this
and just hope for the best.
Is it enough?
Hey, it's at least enough to do it twice and go.
Come on, get that shit out of here.
Do I lose?
I think it's still, let's see, seven, seven times.
Damn it.
No, I only had two wins.
All right, one more.
This is actually the last one, I promise.
Last one.
I'm going with this.
The leaking soup, the inedible bush.
Inedible bushes, inedible soup.
Leaking package, leaking packages.
That's okay.
Let chat play.
It's a games free, you can play right now.
I was going to say if I didn't win this,
or if I didn't turn this into a draw,
this is going to, I don't know, I'm not happy.
Here we go.
Okay, hold on a minute here.
Remember, stop losing.
I'm still learning.
Why do you have a four, five duck?
What happened?
You have a four, five duck?
Okay, and then maybe a spider.
Spider in front, probably of the kangaroo.
And I can't wait to get rid of this duck.
Okay, good, let's go.
Nice, very nice.
Don't talk with food in your mouth.
All right, can't wait for the next six
super auto pet streams.
I mean, this game is just, passes time very, very easily.
It takes 15 seconds to open this and get in a game.
It's not like I wouldn't ever play it again,
but I don't know.
I think it's fun.
Very good.
Let's go ahead and get this out of the way.
All right, turtle is, okay.
Sell the duck, turtle going up.
And I want turtle to go in front of the kangaroo.
No, I don't.
Who do I want the turtle to go in front of?
I think I want to do, okay, hold on.
In front of the spider, but I think I need to, I don't know.
Sell the cricket or, and crab.
Yeah, but he has the five damage on him though.
Is he even being funny?
Dude, yeah, the reason why I'm so tired is I just,
I did a, I just did a three hour nonstop standup routine.
Just like kind of chilling now.
I'm exhausted.
Kangaroo has to see somebody in front of him attack.
Turtle, when it dies,
it gives melon armor to the person behind it.
I guess it'd have to be here.
And then I want to do this.
This is stupid, probably, but maybe.
This is stupid, but whatever.
Melon, oh, that's right.
Melon armor, it cancels because it's its own thing.
Well, I'm kind of screwed now.
I think I have to do this or do this.
Then the kangaroo doesn't give very much benefit.
Yeah, I messed this up a little bit.
Okay, so then he can hit.
Yeah, that makes more sense.
All right, let's go.
The spider will get to hit at least,
I'm going to lose the bee,
but it's being replaced by swinging at least twice.
I've been streaming for four and a half hours.
What the fuck is going on here?
I was supposed to be live for like 45 minutes.
Yeah, that's, that's good.
All right, that's two wins.
Okay, thinking about, let's upgrade the spider,
sell the ant, sell the ant, upgrade spider.
I don't think anyone's leaving right now,
although hold on.
Let me just make sure no one else is leaving.
Or I could pill the turtle
and then they get permanent melon armor.
That's not bad.
That works, right?
And then the spider will have a melon armor forever.
I can pill the ant later, the pill will show up again.
You'll sell the spider in not too long from now though.
Will I, even if I upgrade them,
pill the turtle on the kangaroo?
That's not a bad idea.
I like that idea.
Want to do this or do I?
Let's roll.
Hold on to this in case I lose.
What do I want to do here?
Swan, I could do Swan and level up.
Interesting, nice.
Very, very nice.
I'm really happy about that.
All right, let's go.
This is going to be bad.
I should have had the cricket go first.
Hey, very nice.
It's not going to be enough, I don't think.
Let's see, it is not.
Okay, so I'm going to pill the ant,
play the snail, sell the snail.
Go ahead and do that.
Pill the ant.
I didn't want you to get that, but whatever.
Snail, sell the snail, meet the swan.
I mean, maybe the badger.
I think that's the play.
I roll the whole thing in case,
because I'm going to sell something next turn anyways.
These are not good right now.
All right.
I think this is okay to me.
I really need splash damage.
I think this is okay.
That dog's not going to be a problem.
Yeah.
When are you going to play Destiny 2 PVP?
I already did.
I just deleted the VOD because I was embarrassed about it.
I just turned off notifications to subs and stuff
and followers and I just played like three or four hours
of it and I was just like, I'm not into this.
I mean, it's all right.
I just deleted the VOD and shit
because I don't want anyone to see it.
I remember that.
Yeah.
It was like fucking, yeah.
Well, I won.
So we're going to keep the snail frozen.
Oh, honey on the badger.
Honey on the badger.
What am I doing?
Oh, that stream was so bad.
It was so sad.
I know.
Honey on the badger.
All right.
I really, really want a spider or kangaroo upgrade.
No, no.
Okay.
We'll do meat.
No, we won't.
The swan.
Yeah, that's the only thing I can really do.
Okay.
Probably going to lose, but I'll get a good next turn.
It's a phone game.
It's not a phone game.
It looks pretty safe.
Literally a phone game.
This game is on Steam right now.
Is Clash of Clans on Steam?
No.
That's a phone game.
I won again.
Okay.
Well, we need to roll for some upgrades.
No.
This has to replace somebody with who?
I feel like I need both of these.
He has, and the rooster has to go in the front.
I get rid of the cricket.
I think the, or the spider.
What gets me more value here?
The spider, I think.
Cricket currently does more damage than the spider,
but the spider makes the kangaroo better.
And I'm almost about to level them up.
All right.
This is bad, but we have to do it.
Cause then this will get really, really good.
I wonder if I can, should I move the?
No, I think it stays there.
But the swan might move.
Hold on.
Let's just see what we get here.
Right?
I have a roll and I'm not going to buy any of these.
So let's say, you know what I mean?
Let's just roll.
Let's see if we get something good.
All right.
That's, this is going here.
Okay.
This is big.
Take a look at this shit.
Perfect.
Roll again.
Okay.
All right.
I just have to survive to another turn.
And this is big.
This is bingo.
Even if I lose, I can't sell anything.
I don't think this snow might have to go.
Find out.
At least get rid of the elephant.
That hippo is really dangerous.
Swan should kill not both of them, but it's all right.
Ooh.
Scary.
I think I had the melon armor.
That would have been very scary.
Oh!
What happened?
What?
What the hell?
Oh man.
That sucked.
Oh, come on.
Oh, but look at what it gave me.
It gave me triple.
All right.
Oh shit.
So I think the play is sell the swan,
get rid of the swan, upgrade the monkey,
put the snail up, sell the snail for the sheep.
Maybe.
Well, I know I'm doing this.
This is certain.
Like this is just certainty.
So just do it.
Four, four.
Gorilla in front.
Get rid of the swan.
Okay.
Gorilla's going in the front, but not yet.
Come on.
Okay.
Let's go.
This should be a winning hand.
Would have been awesome to get another gorilla.
I like the way this is set up.
Hopefully it works out.
12, 12 gorilla with the coconut shield.
It has to activate it though, which is scary.
Okay.
I will.
Took off the melon armor.
Oh, you son of a gun.
We recorded stream.
Sag.
Okay.
Oh!
But wait.
I don't know what to do at this point.
I can upgrade gorilla and then feed gorilla.
The spider sucks.
Put in two.
Okay.
Is it time to get rid of the kangaroo or the spider?
Because the kangaroo is really awful
without the spider in front of them.
Kangaroo is better with the spider.
Okay.
So what's better though,
is this is just a free 22 damage, right?
But the rooster in front of the kangaroo.
So that works still.
Sell the spider, upgrade the gorilla
and have double monkey.
Like you're talking two slots, right?
So the gorilla gets a six, six.
All right, we're going for it.
That's cool.
So this is gonna go here
and then upgrade the gorilla and then feed the gorilla.
All right, let's go.
This is gonna be a huge deal.
All right, let's do it.
21, 21.
That's a big boy.
Oh, but that's an even, that's a bigger one.
That one's bigger though.
Oh God, that's not good.
I think I still do it though.
Cause this is the strongest thing he has.
Is it okay?
No, it's not.
Aye.
It's all right.
No, it's not all right.
That's loud.
I wanted to get an upgraded gorilla so bad.
I don't want the fever.
Thank you.
How about the flooded ears?
This is it.
Yo, I'm streaming again on Sunday.
I'll be back.
This is too fun.
What about Friday?
Oh yeah, maybe it is Friday.
I'll figure it out.
I gotta talk to italics cause we're gonna play,
we're gonna play Resident Evil 6.
So it's either gonna be Friday or Sunday.
But we'll look out for Sunday.
All right, next turn, selling both ducks.
And I'm gonna try to replace the two ducks.
Is this a win?
Five, three.
I've ever played six before?
For about 30 minutes.
Okay, here's the, oh no, this sucks.
I screwed, okay, I need to do,
should I just do a weirdo porcupine build?
Yeah, let's go.
Watch this.
Okay, sell, give shop pets one, one.
Okay, all right.
Then I'm gonna roll.
Oh hell yeah.
All right, sell the beaver
and then put another hedgehog up here.
And then combine the fish.
Take a look at that.
Wowee.
I want that turtle.
Oh wait, they have to die.
So they have to die for that to trigger.
This is a win because this is guaranteed.
I'm guaranteed to win.
Cause even if they die, they will kill.
All right, interesting.
Maybe I should combine them.
Yeah, this has to be in the front cause that will die.
And then do I, I could just make one
that does four damage to everybody.
DLC pack, yeah, I switched it to the normal pack
because we were playing on the normal pack
and I accidentally switched the expansion one
and I didn't, I never switched back.
They're just gonna kill the fish.
That's true.
So why don't we do this?
And then this will just play out.
All right, what if Peacock the hedgehog?
They do too much damage.
They'll just kill it.
It does two damage, Peacock has five, right?
All right, how bad is this gonna go?
We'll find out.
Okay, ow, shit.
Hey, it's not a loss.
Okay, this is give everybody two, two.
Do I just build for that?
Yeah, let's do it, who cares?
What's wrong?
Move the turtle?
Well, this is a disaster for this guy.
Here we go.
Oh, kill it all.
Okay, oh, hell yeah.
Everybody loses.
So I guess you have to, you garlic the hedgehogs.
That sounds like a shitty new Sonic character
because they'll only take one damage now from this.
I want a fish, bad, really bad, please.
No, oh, shit.
No, fish, move the turtle?
I like the fact that this does damage with the,
oh no, you're right, you're right,
because you can only have one buff at a time.
You're right, you're right, okay.
It'll work out though, it's fine.
Now it's over, check this out.
Yep, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful.
Nobody gets to win, draws only, oh no.
God damn it, okay, well, what does this do now?
Just four damage to everybody?
How am I gonna, this is gonna be fucking horrible.
I'm just gonna lose.
Why the front one?
This one needs to go all the way to the back.
Do not do that, how do I move this to the back?
How do I move this without it combining?
Very good, so I'm gonna do this, that makes sense.
I don't have any money for garlic.
This is a huge pain in the ass for anybody that fights me
even though it's not that great.
This is a huge pain in the ass.
Okay, that's fine, all right, again.
Oh shit, come on, turtle, turtle, I need the turtle.
Nice, very good, okay, oh, come on.
Wait, before I do anything stupid,
level two turtle will give two armors.
That doesn't really help me in this stupid build.
All right, here's what I'm gonna do.
I think I'm gonna combine hedgehogs
and have two level two hedgehogs
because that's probably better.
Don't do it yet, do it in one more turn.
They'll kill you, you need honey.
I actually do need honey, you're right,
because they're gonna kill everybody.
I need to roll for honey.
The monkey's cool, but not for this build.
Oh, wait a second, wait a second.
Excuse me, that's a big deal.
Oh shit, okay, are we ready?
I think we're ready.
Oh, should the turtle go in the front to hit?
Who should the turtle give it to?
Ellen will cancel the garlic, so I need to give it to you.
I want the fish to be in the back.
The fish is gonna die, I think that's all right.
All right, let's go.
Can you do the Elmo voice?
Hello, hi Mr. Noodle.
I woke up too early, I can't do it.
Kill this guy in the front.
I hit Melanon, oh, it's 20 damage, no.
It only blocks 20, that's right.
All right, this shithead build
is not working out very well.
I could just do two level two hedgehogs.
What is that?
Oh, Douglas, it's me, Mr. Dink.
That's definitely going on, one of these guys.
End the stream now, no.
This is just so stupid, it's gonna do eight damage
and kill everybody, who cares?
It's funny, this is the last one anyways.
It should be like this.
I do have a reroll, that's right.
Not enough to do anything interesting.
I'm gonna garlic, who do I do?
Maybe just health on the turtle or something.
Health on the tiger so he stays alive long enough
to at least have this happen once.
Or garlic on the tiger, otherwise he'll just die.
But then he'll take two from that, all right.
Well, this is gonna be stupid.
I get to do this one more time.
Wap the hedgehogs, all right, let's go.
No, the German tiger will die.
Can you combine it for a level three?
Do two level twos turn into a level three?
I don't know, I'm unaware of how that works.
I mean, if it goes off, it kills everybody.
Literally everybody dies.
Oh man, it's gonna happen.
Yeah, that's it.
No, stupid boss, oh shit.
All right, okay, please confirm with me.
If I combine these two, does it make a level three?
Because doing six damage,
doing 12 damage to everyone is kind of funny.
I didn't get a, oh, this is gonna do six damage to everybody.
I have to keep the tiger alive.
12 with tiger, yeah, this is gonna be insane.
Do another one?
No, I don't think I want to.
All right, I gotta roll for like a melon
or something for the tiger, yeah.
I need something else just to stand in the way.
This has to hit two people.
Put the turtle in front of the hog
so it'll protect the both of them, I guess, I don't know.
Puffer fish could be interesting, really late for it.
It's just too late for it.
Hog two is dumb, all right.
I mean, it's just, I could buff up the tiger.
Do the rooster, they just die.
And rooster in the back.
I don't think the rooster's gonna survive.
It's 12 damage, guys.
If this thing goes, everyone goes.
Oh, we're hoping for worries.
It kills everything and then the chick pops up.
Okay, right, that makes sense.
Well, how is this for placement?
I think that's as good as it's gonna get.
This is stupid.
Is this stupid enough to just ruin everybody's game
and have me win games?
Make sure the rooster's in front of the turtle.
I know, I want him to die after this.
We'll see.
No, I think this is fine like this.
Rooster needs to be last, yeah.
This is fine.
Here we go, good luck.
Let's see how this works.
Okay, well, this is gonna be an interesting scenario.
Okay, fine, 12 damage.
Oh no, come on.
Oh shit, oh shit.
Did I win?
Oh, you have a dumb ass porcupine.
Okay, we're good.
What's the deal here?
Do I just keep giving food to the rooster?
Just keep buffing the chicken like crazy?
Rooster needs honey.
Yeah, yeah, we need to roll for either another rooster.
Cat is better than the fish.
It is, okay.
The fish just has garlic on it.
So we can put cat instead of fish
and then feed the cat a bunch.
Does the cat get the benefit from this?
We have all current and future shop heads too too.
Does that mean he's a 4-4?
And before cat, you can feed anything.
Okay, so that should be 4-4 added.
Well, that was wrong apparently
because that's only a 10-11.
It has to be purchased first.
Well, we know we're doing this.
That's so cute.
Steak, all right, it's like this is six-six.
Do this and make the cat a 16-17?
Or do I cupcake the rooster instead
to make sure that there'll be at least 11 or 12 damage?
Do the cow instead of who?
Who do I get rid of?
I mean, freeze the cow is a good idea,
but remember, this is over if I die.
Get rid of the turtle at this point
and just buy the food from the cow
and just give it to the cat twice.
So it'll be like a 20-20.
Ludwig is stealing your strats.
I think we feed, yeah, I think we get rid of the turtle.
We either give it to the cat
or just stuff the rooster full of milk.
Well, let's do it.
Let's go for it.
Okay, cow coming in.
Cupcake, wait, cupcake.
Cupcake to rooster?
No, what do I do?
Cupcake to cat and then all milk to cat.
This would be like a 30-30
because it clears the items.
Cupcake to cat, that means 16-17.
Two milks is eight-eight.
17 plus eight is like 25 or something.
And it's not gonna be like, that's gonna be like 25-25.
It's free, the milk is free.
I don't have enough money.
Oh, okay.
All right, so what I'm doing is I'm putting the cow up.
Cow's gonna get the milk.
Milk is going to the cat or to the rooster?
Probably the rooster, right?
And then the cow is just gonna die.
Everyone's gonna die, who cares?
Cat or rooster?
I think the safe play is rooster
because then he'll come back with another,
be able to kill it.
I mean, we'll have a really beefy cat,
but I don't know if that's good enough.
Boost the rooster.
That'd be four-four or eight-eight to the cat.
I don't know, I kind of want to see it to the cat.
But hold on, here's the thing.
If I give it to the rooster,
the rooster will survive the apocalypse
because this is 12 damage.
I think it has to be the rooster.
Yeah, it has to be.
The rooster now survives the apocalypse.
In fact, I'm doing it again.
Here we go.
Last chance, let's just roll.
Oh, and you're gonna show me your chocolate right now?
Is that what you're gonna do, really?
Well, fuck it, here we go.
Curious.
Look at all these, oh, you got a level,
17, 19 damage, 19 health, that's fine.
No one's surviving the apocalypse.
Oh, fuck, this is not good.
It is good, I win.
Do I win or is it a draw?
Oh, it's a draw.
Oh, well, this looks so bad, but this is fun.
Okay, damn it.
This is, I win every game now.
I win every game.
There's no way I lose another game after this.
Mushroom on the rooster is,
I've guaranteed to win every single game
no matter what happens.
Wait a minute, should it be on the hedgehog?
Because then the hedgehog would come back
and do 12, six damage again?
Does it come back as a level one?
No, it just comes back as a one, one.
Okay, so that would be bad.
Chocolate the cat.
One up the hedgehog.
It would still be level three,
so nobody will ever win.
This would be horrible.
Just do it for the nuke build.
That's 18 damage.
Somebody said feed the chocolate to the cat, okay?
Do it to the rooster.
Do it with, yeah, I need to make sure there's no survivors.
Chocolate the rooster.
Wait, so this is not just for the cat,
this is for everybody up here.
So if I give it to the rooster,
it'll be level two, rooster.
And the rooster will make two.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, that's good.
That's, no one will ever win.
I win every game.
Don't do it?
No, no, no, don't do it.
Only works for one?
It doesn't affect chocolate?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Roll first.
Wait, what do you mean?
It doesn't work?
It's health and attack only.
Oh.
All right, well, I'm giving the mushroom to the hedgehog
because who cares?
It's over.
Who gives a shit?
So now I'm looking for another cow.
Does fly help me?
I don't think so.
Not at this stage.
Unless I put him behind the rooster.
Sushi's not bad here.
No, just use the sushi.
Fly is just gonna die.
That's true.
I would love another cow.
Sell cow and get the bison.
Yeah, that's not a bad idea either.
Do two every time.
All right, I'm gonna roll once.
I'm gonna freeze this guy
because I think that's a good idea.
So we get one roll and we can sell.
Let's see what happens.
Okay, so this is level three.
I really need, there's no defense back here.
All right, let's do it.
This time, this is gonna be stupid.
Defense is unnecessary because of the nuke, yeah.
Well, I can tell you right now,
this could be really bad.
Okay, here we go.
Okay, do it again.
That's a win.
When am I gonna lose another game again?
You just have to lose every time
until you get level three hedgehog and a mushroom.
The goal now is to try to get these upgraded.
Okay, so I could do cupcake on the cat,
broccoli on the tiger, that doesn't do anything.
Upgrade the rooster, fuck the tiger.
Upgrades don't do anything on the tiger.
We're looking for a rooster.
So I'm gonna use chocolate on the rooster
and then we need to find a rooster.
It's so important to find a rooster right now.
I'm just gonna roll till I find one.
It's not a rooster.
It is a bison though.
Shit, can I do this twice?
Wait, hold on.
What if I mushroomed the tiger?
So then it would be 12 damage again.
This is literally impossible to beat.
I don't think there's a meta in this game
that could beat level three hedgehog,
mushroomed, mushroomed tiger.
I will always at least have one character left
unless they have something in the back.
It won't work, why not?
It will be dead.
Well, this blows up, this does 12 damage.
It comes back and then it does it again
because it has to die, because this has to die.
So when it comes back, it'll die
and then this will come back and then do it.
It, yeah, this should work.
Let's just do it, who cares?
And then we're gonna give splash damage to the bison.
Okay, good luck.
I have no idea what's gonna happen,
but it might be funny.
You're gonna get wiped out, buddy.
You're gonna get wiped out.
You have no idea, you're gonna get wiped out.
Oh, oh no, what happened?
What am I gonna do now?
It's gonna work, it's gonna work.
Oh God, wait, it didn't work?
Wait, why did that not work?
Why not?
Come on, are you kidding me?
Oh, rooster.
I win, oh my God.
No, that's what I didn't, don't relax, it's fine.
So I think it's just pizza.
Tiger doesn't really do anything.
B and pizza, B on the rooster?
Rooster, honey?
Rooster, honey, yeah, because then it would be,
yeah, it's over.
Honey on the rooster for sure.
Then we get a pizza.
Oh man, oh man, it's over.
I am, I'm gonna come back from the dead here.
I was at one heart.
I'm gonna win all eight of these games in a row.
I don't think there's anything else I do.
I think there's real for food,
which that's a pretty good, that's pretty good.
I'll keep this one.
This is just crazy enough, I think,
to carry us the whole way.
As long as I can keep that rooster alive.
Oh boy, that's very bad.
I don't think this is gonna play out.
Now I'm actually kind of scared.
It's not enough.
Is it not enough?
Shit, it's not enough.
Oh, it's just not enough.
He's gonna kill everybody.
No.
Oh, what the hell?
That was fun.
Now it's over.
How do you get a 50-50 goose?
That doesn't make any sense.
How does that happen?
All right, no, that's it, that's it.
This is only supposed to be like a stream
that was like an hour long.
I'll see you guys this weekend.
It was fun playing into it.
If anything, this tournament,
even though I lost like every game
and I didn't know what the hell I was doing,
this is really fun.
I like this a lot.
Thanks Ludwig for the invite.
I'll do better next time.
I'll see you guys this weekend,
either Friday or Sunday.
Let's see what Alex is up to.
See what day probably works better.
So I'll see you soon.
That was super AutoPets.
And that was a lot of fun.
Take care of yourselves.
We can run the credits though.
How long?
This stream is way longer than I thought it was.
Is Ludwig still streaming?
Like what the fuck just happened?
Let me see.
Yeah, we'll go raid Ludwig.
Playing AutoPets, right?
Go say hello.
Say thanks for the invite.
And I will see you guys later.
Thanks for coming.
Thanks to all the subs.
See you guys this weekend.
We can start the raid.
Raid.
I don't even know how many people are here.
I haven't even looked the whole time.
Was that fun to watch?
Cause it was like fun to play.
All right, I'll see you guys later.
Take care.
By the way, the game is free.
It's $5 to get the like DLC pets,
which I mean like really,
it's like $4.99 or something.
Take care of yourselves.
See you guys soon.
Have a great rest of your night and goodbye.