I'm already just so exhausted from even trying to put this together. There hasn't
been an ounce of enthusiasm in my voice since we started talking about this, but
now we're ready. I sent you the info. Let's do this. You like do not want to do this at
all. I almost like threw up. Did you hear that? A little bit, yeah. So here's
what the deal is, right? So here's Ster. He's a soldier right here. He's on
red team. I'm on blue team. This is upward. We are going to both have a team
of easy mode bots. That means our bots are at the lowest difficulty they could
possibly be at. And why is there a tank? This feels familiar. So no, no, don't
break your own fucking server. Can you give me one second to explain what's
happening?
I can't believe you made like a trail to yourself. Okay. Yeah, I really didn't
think you were ever going to be able to do this. You brought the truck punch
line over into Team Fortress 2 and your server is going to crash. There's no way
we're making out of this one. This place is shutting down. Shit's like flying by
my screen. Oh, no, we invested our money poorly. We didn't put it into a 401k.
It's disappearing. All of our money is disappearing. You wanted to invest in a
lollipop company. It's all gone. All right, come on out. Um, they're they are
not leaving. Oh, yeah, they have one person. It seems two of them has left.
They're a little bit delayed. They're making some progress. Don't worry. We
have a we have our sentry set up in a very optimal situation with a scout not
moving standing next to it. Oh, I think I think my guys are pushing in. We got
it. We got a heavy medic combination coming in through the front control
point here. Pyro coming out here. Looks like you see your spy. No, I'm watching
the action. There is no, what are they doing? What is he still doing? He's out
of bullets, I think. Oh, okay. I'm going to, I'm going to pay attention to
something else. Why is they doing a melee fight? Are you kidding me right
now? What the fuck? Did you seriously make every single person a spy? Yes. Oh,
my God. What are they doing? What is your team doing? What? Why are they
freaking out in the corner over here? That's just what spies do. This is what
you should be aiming for. Oh, make sure you're disguised. Make sure he doesn't
see you. I just heard like 10 seconds. I wonder if one. Why are they trying to
jump through the boards? That doesn't work like that. You're not like made out
of taffy. Here we go. Um, here they go. I'm unstoppable. Don't even tell it.
Please don't tell me they're all gonna keep coming out of this door. Where else
would they go? I don't know. One option. I just, I go out this door. Oh, you're
spies. I think you like broke them. Hold on. Let me see where they are. Are they
done? No, they're all going out the front door. This is stupid. No, they're
going after each other. There was one too many of them. No one's gonna go
for the point. This is gonna last exactly three minutes and 32 seconds
because there's absolutely no way any of these brainless son of a bitches are
gonna go for that point. Okay, this one engineer is really just going for gold.
We actually capped it. Really? How the hell did that happen? I don't know. Maybe
had something to do with the tank.
It's just going through. They're all gonna get stuck on it. They're all just shooting it like what the hell is this block of the door?
This guy's freaking out. I'm about to get trick stabbed. No, no, no. Is it actually making its way in?
No, it's not. Is it? Please crush them. Please crush. You go for like crushing them. No, it didn't kill them. They got it in. They got it in.
I'm gonna die. This should not be happening. Drive up. They're actually doing enough damage to it.
Engineers on the back of the tank? Yes. Oh my god. Oh, you didn't think this could get even dumber. It's genetic. They just keep getting right over.
Alright, redo. Retake. I need like a second before I throw up. Why are they all taunting?
They don't even know where to shoot yet. Why are they not shooting you? Because the round doesn't start. I'm not supposed to be out here.
Oh, they're that confused about the round not being started yet. That they refuse to shoot you. What are they?
This doesn't make any... Wait, I want to see what happens in one second.
How is anybody on blue team gonna get anything done? You have such a huge advantage.
Because you're allowed to build your sentries first. My guys are being like dumbasses trying to do like leapfrog in the spawn.
Hey, you could be a little bit more respectful. Just wait. Wait till this 12 seconds counts down.
I bet you every single one of these guys just walks out and just gets eaten alive.
Eaten alive by what? We barely have a defense. The sentry mosquitoes.
Alright, here we go. You need a catchphrase for everything. Here we go. Let's see what happens.
Oh, this is gonna work. This is gonna work. They all backed up instantly.
Nah, let's just build them back here. Let's start getting these teleporters up.
They're so confused. You're still prioritizing the teleporters over sentries.
Yeah, they'd rather build teleporters than sentries.
No, seriously, this was done. The joke was over.
That joke ended so long ago.
Why do you have to fucking ruin everything?