It's been a long time coming. We've been waiting for this one.
Desperados 3. Launched on Steam. And I'm gonna play it the day that it launches.
I've been talking about this shit for like at least a week or two.
Man, it's not like I've ever done that before. Talking about Half-Life Alyx for about six months.
We've been waiting for this one though, except not really at all.
I played Desperados 2 and I made a video on Desperados 2 for those that do not know.
It's pretty fun. It's pretty crazy. They made another one.
So I'm gonna play it. Zero viewers. No viewers. Omega Low. Yeah, all right.
Well, uh, whatever. I'm okay with zero viewers. You know why?
Because that's an fucking infinite number. It's a never-ending circle.
There is an infinite amount of you here. Zero is infinity.
Oh wait, no. Infinity is like eight, right? All right.
Let's have eight viewers because that's like the infinity symbol.
Let's have eight. Zero is infinity. No, zero is. That means no one.
What does the infinite symbol look like? It's like an eight, right?
The infinity symbol. What is it? Why is this not the first?
Yeah, it's a sideways. Okay. It's like a pair of goggles.
It's an eight. That's an eight. That's an eight sideways.
It's an eight lined out. That's fine. Hey, thank you Game Watch.
The 10 community subs. Appreciate it. Thank you Game Watch.
10 fucking subs just came in. A lot of money. Thank you.
You're playing Doritos 3. That would be weird if this was Doritos characters.
Doritos doesn't even have characters. They never did that. They never tried that.
All Doritos characters were just way too enthusiastic adults giving their children
junk food or stealing the junk food from their children. That's pretty much all they've done.
The Doritos bag is the character. Oh yeah. Didn't it like tilt around?
It wasn't like, hey kids, it's been a while. Doritos. They moved around, right?
They did that. The Doritos bag like tilted and it didn't have a mouth, but it talked, right?
In like one commercial? No, really? No, it definitely did.
Somebody said that in chat. I distinctly remember it happening.
I never said anything like that. Creep. Why are you calling me a creep?
Because I misplaced a Doritos ad. Therefore, I'm a creep.
What was that Doritos commercial? Oh yeah. It was like a Doritos bag.
Yeah. Doritos are really just tasty. You creep. Get away from me. Don't look at him.
Go this way everybody. Dairy. We only eat, we only eat Teddy's natural corn chips.
You fucking disgusting creepy. All right. We have a game to play. We're
going to play Desperados 3. We only drink peanut butter oil. I'm, I can't, I'm,
I'm still angry about that. Ask pre stream chat. I was still angry about that today.
I was being told that peanut butter was unhealthy and I gave everybody detention in pre stream chat.
Because if you think that peanut butter is an unhealthy snack, then your teachers are
fucking aliens and they're giving you an alien learning book. It's not, it is not,
it's unbelievable to hear that. You guys need a nutrition lesson. Okay. Real peanut butter,
not like the shit with like 30 grams of Coca-Cola sugar soda put in it. I'm talking about real
peanut butter. It's no sugar added. It's got so many delicious, healthy fats. It's got fiber.
It's got protein. You know, if you got like locked in a basement, like let's say, let's say,
let's say there's like an absolute destruction of the earth and you're downstairs in somebody's
bunker and it's walls of peanut butter, you can stay alive until while that peanut butter is gone.
It's a goddamn complete food. It's got your protein. It's got your fat. It's got your
carbohydrates. It's got your fiber. You could live if peanut butter is a superfood, you could
live out of it. It's true. Thank you. I want to VIP that person for an hour. For some reason,
when I bring up the word peanut butter, people think I'm like eating cotton candy out of the
bag before you turn it into cotton candy. Like I'm just eating cotton candy sugar. That's like
what I'm telling people apparently. Holy shit, dude. You eat like a whole tub of ice cream.
No, I like peanut butter. That's the same thing. I mean, I like cookies and cream. Ben and Jerry's
like the rest of us, man, but I don't, you eat the whole, the whole tub. No, I like peanut butter.
I love peanut butter. It's like my favorite thing ever. Do a peanut butter stream right now. I'll
tell you. You go, if you guys have like a Whole Foods around you, it's so simple. It's basic. It's
so easy. The 365, just default Whole Foods brand 365 creamy peanut butter on the shelf. Go get it.
You can always tell because it's the one with the, it's the one with the oil on top. Get that one.
Get that one and just do, just do it and just eat it a little bit. Just put some, put it on a
fucking piece of celery. Dip your pretzels in it. Put it on like a toast and just please trust me
on this. You have to trust me. Not as healthy as, yeah, we went by too fast. I don't even know what
you said. He's the peanut butter guy. Pure peanut oil is not good for you. I don't know why you guys
get this misconception that I'm telling you to like put it in an IV bag and put it in, drain peanut
oil into your veins. But it's, peanut butter is a good snack. All right, let's play. I'm going to,
at some point during this stream, remind me, we're going to go over my food pyramid.
I'm making a food pyramid for you guys because I think a lot of you guys might have a little bit
of unhealthy, unhealthy, non-nutritional shit in your life. I'm not doing hard. I'm so glad
he can't even pick anything other than normal. He's got a nut addiction. He nuts are great.
Sunflower seeds, peanuts, walnuts, almonds. If you're not allergic to them, eat them. I got so many
good things in them. All right. I, I, I'm just, I'm not going to do, what is it? Beginner or this
one's on fire. I don't like this one. There's a hard and then there's a super hard. It requires
perfect planning and execution. Enemies have lightning reflexes. Characters have almost no
health and ammo. This is not recommended for a first playthrough, regardless of player skill.
Recommended for veterans of the real time tactic genre, not me. We're going to stay on normal.
Thank you. I'm not doing super hard. I've learned my lesson. I can't do that anymore.
I can't just fucking pick the hardest difficulty for a joke for 10 minutes and then we have to
restart the stream. I don't want to, I'm not doing that. I'm not that guy anymore.
That's all you guys want. You want me to get destroyed for like 30 minutes and then, you know,
I'm going to turn it off and turn it back on again on normal. We're skipping that part.
Fod watchers, you don't have to do anything. Stay here. It's really low. This is a lot of audio.
So low. He chugged peanut. Guys, I would, I will eat at least five or six full spoonfuls of
peanut butter on stream. That's normal to me. That's not abnormal. That's not like, oh, I will
do that and it'll be fine. That's like a routine. Johnny, you're straggling. Come on. Right behind
you, pa. Eat a whole jar. No, that's now you're good. Now that's unhealthy. Now that's not good
for you. I'm going on ahead. You follow and keep your head down. Let's get like a top down red dead
redemption too. Yes, sir. Which one am I? Wait, that's me. That's, that's the guy from the second
game, right? Sly Cooper. Come on. Somebody said it in pre-stream. Somebody said Sly Cooper in
pre-stream chat and it's stuck in my brain. All right. Move. I got this. All right. That's pretty
responsive. Move camera mouse. Right. W A S D does not move the camera. Okay. I can hold middle mouse
button just like every RTS. Okay. Right on my way. Where am I going? Drink out of the water.
Ooh, wait. Is there a, there's a super zoom and I tilt. Ooh. Cool. Sure thing. I'm going to get so
fucking killed. All right. Crouch. Son man. Okay. Crouch. It's now or never. Use. Use control.
Am I using? Control. I'm ready this time. Use control. On my way. Display view come.
Display view come. They found us. Stop. What the hell happened? Sorry. I slipped up.
Thank God. Thank God I'm here with my friend. Okay. Why does it say use control? What does it
for? What control? I can't use anything. Oh, you have to hold it and then grab. Okay.
He came in and threw a knife at the guy's neck. If an enemy sees you in their view cone,
if the enemy sees you, the view cone fills with yellow, right? It's like metal gear solid.
If the yellow reaches you, the enemy detects you start attacking and sounding alarms. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. So just like it's metal gear solid too. There it is. Like, which there he is. Right. Okay.
There's the first guard. I need to be sneaky about this. Leave it to me. Okay. First guard.
Can I loot this guy? Is it time? Sure. Let's go. All right. Let's go. Crouch. On my way.
Okay. Quick save. Thank God. There's a quick save. You can save the game at any time.
I'm pressing F5. Quick load by pressing F8. F8. Okay. I'm going to be using this all the time.
F5 and F8. Hey, thank you. Sly Cuper for the 10 subs. Thanks for the 10 subs. Sly Cuper.
Use it often. Failing and retrying is intended and part of the game. F5 and F8. Okay. F5.
All right. Good. Last save one. Is that going to keep, is that going to stay there? Sure.
Sure. Let's go. Copper can throw a coin to distract enemies with the blue radius.
Press E then press L and mouse. Sure. I'll throw one of my coins. Good idea.
Get him to turn his head. I'll do the rest. Okay. If eventually this is a brick,
then I think a lot of you guys need to pay more attention.
Need some change? You hear that? Let's go. I'll get it done.
Wait. Hey. Why are you so much better than me? Remember. Think slow. Act fast.
Last save thing? You always hide the body. Why do I have to constantly count things up?
Right. On my way. To hide the body? All right. Now what? Follow me. Keep your head down.
Catch up to your father. Oh, he's my dad. Okay. It's now or never.
Shout out. Showdown mode. Shift. I got this. This might be fun. Incoming dead dad.
No, they're not going to do that in this game. Showdown mode pauses the game and lets you plan
one action per character. Okay. You can execute actions right away or save them for a later time
for a shift into showdown mode. So it's a pause. Then you can just go, all right,
I want to do this. I'm going to do that. I'll do that. Okay. Let's do showdown mode.
Don't come to me. I'm just standing. Showdown. Throw coin at horse.
E. One fake coin. Leave it to me. Coin at horse. Continue. Execute order.
All right. Do it again. She wants to still have plenty of money on my way. Execute.
Okay. Why don't you just throw knives at people, dude? You just like, I don't get it. Sure thing.
Wait, is this person unconscious? Hey, pa. Yeah. How many men does Frank have?
Doesn't matter, boy. What are you doing? One on one. You always got a chance.
You just got to thin out the pack. Okay. Safe. Sure. Let's go. Knife camera.
Locked. No surprise there. Distract the guard. Anger the horse.
All right, son. Time for a challenge. See that ladder up there? I need you to throw it down for
me. Okay. Mouse wheel zoom and get it. Sure. No problem. Oh, thank God. He knows where to go.
I would have walked around in circles and everyone would have been like, oh my God,
he's pretty, he doesn't know what he's pretending. I don't even have to pretend.
I can just play. Oh, you'd have a double tap. Cool. I got this. I knock it down.
It's going to be an acting screen. Good job. That's my boy. It was easy.
Somebody's getting $50. All right. Him times gave 5,000 bits. Thanks to the $50 and they do
the, they say, mwah, the French champagne. Always been celebrated for its excellence.
Leave it in your head. They start with the interruptions. Stay cool. Hey, thank you for
the, that's a $50 interruption. Thank you. Well, crouched space. You can safely move through the
dark striped area of enemy's view cans while scrouched on a roof. I can't even read anymore.
What's going on? I'm only 34. What's happening? This doesn't, this is stupid. Why? I used to be
able to read anything. Why did I add an S? You're always hit into guards as long as you stay in the
darker area. Okay. Yeah, I know. Quick save. He's only 34 and he's like, you can't even read anymore.
You've got to find a way to sneak through. Oh yeah. He was crushed. Okay. You cone.
All right. We've got an area here. We've got to go this way. I'll get it done.
That explains why the old bastard has it in for her. It's now or never. You're a view cone.
I've got to go down here. Wait, can I just walk across? It's not going to, it has to turn yellow,
right? I should go this way. I can climb up this. I'm going to go for it. Here we go.
Her only friend is his bottle. Sure. Let's go. This dude's face is way too small for his skull.
Right on my way. Oh, stop. Stop. My money'd be on Hutch. How can I get up there? Quick too.
Leave it to me. Something. Ah, I found you. Fuck.
Dad, dad. All right. Let's go. So what have to go? How do I go around that then? Sure.
Roach. You've got to find a way to sneak through. Okay. So did this person turn?
Wait, I forgot the coin. I have the coin. Here we go. Ready?
There was something on my way. All right. Can they see that? Can they look above?
Save, save, save, save, save. They can't look.
And nowhere. Where are they going? Are they going up the stairs?
I don't know. We're good. Oh, you want to go up there? Okay. Let's go up there together.
See the one in the back near the cliff? Find a way to distract him with your coming.
Then I can take them both out. Okay. One fake coin coming up.
The other one, John. We'll get him. He's not looking. How far can I throw? Still got plenty left.
How far can I throw this? Leave it to me. Oh, shit. I knock him out. Hey. On my way. One fake coin
coming up. What's that noise? Sure. The other one, John. I'm working on it. Hold on. I don't think
he's going to be able to get down here. Oh, sure thing. Still got plenty left. Need some change.
All right. Go get him, dad. He's still breathing. Tie him up and quick before he comes to.
What? What do you mean tie him up? How do I tie him up? Oh, shit. There's a tutorial. He left a note
for me to tell me how. You can hide bodies in bushes. Houses and other places. Hold control
then press left mouse to pick up a body. Hold control and press left mouse to drop a body.
Okay. Don't mind me. Good job. Now hide him in the bushes. Am I too weak to pick him up?
Look at this. Atta boy. Let's go. Sure. No problem. Right. On my way. Where is he? Where'd he go?
He did a full swan dive. It's now or never. We got to get moving.
Rotate camera. Hold on. Yes. I will. On my way. That was fucking crazy. Holy shit. I don't know
that was going to happen. How am I still? Okay. I did good. Browse. Where'd they all come from?
You got her. See that crane up there? Yeah. How about you go over there and make a delivery?
Coming right up, sir. I have to stand up and be like I have to wait. How do I do that?
They're looking in every direction. Sure. Let's go. The hell? How do I get up there?
Glad I picked up these. Forget it. That's nothing. Sure thing. Son of a bitch.
Transmit. I got you. Spread out. Let's take him down. Why would he run up there?
Dad died. Dad died. How about you go over there and make a delivery?
Coming right up, sir. Forget it. That's nothing. Oh shit. There's bushes on my way. Excuse me,
dad. Leave it to me. Glad I picked up these. Son of a bitch. Stop. Let's take him down, boys.
All right, guys. Let's smoke him out. If I make a mistake and try to run away,
dad just goes, oh no, son. I'm going to run into all of them and die. No. That crane up there?
Yeah. How about you go over there and make a delivery? No, my son. Coming right up, sir.
Dad died. All right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. We get it. Glad I picked up these. Yeah,
the dad died. Sure thing. Okay. I'm hidden in the bush. I'm going to climb up that.
One fake coin. Coming up. This way. Come on. Turn around. I got this. Good. Nice. All right.
Nobody up here? Leave it to me. Is it time? Okay. You can highlight all interactable objects
if you press H. Wow. That's really useful. Okay. Cool. I have to go over there and drop
that on those guys. This is a bird's nest. It's now or never. It's in there. Oh, okay.
So if I drop down here. Hitman looks a lot different than I remember. It does. Sure.
Let's go. What's that? Oh, that's going in here. I don't want to do that.
Holy shit. That was kind of brutal. Nice job, son. Now stay right there. I'll come to you.
Come on up here, dad. Non-descript civilian, 10 subs. There's a lot of fucking subs today.
It's like 40. Jesus. Good job, boy. You know the drill. You wait till I'm back. Here he comes.
Here comes the dad. I don't hear it.
So the same thing last time. Why can't I come with you? Just give me a gun.
A gun, huh? By the way, I want to tell you something. I got something real important to
tell you when I get back. I want to see the main part of the story. 15 paces.
Hit this? What? Oh, you get guns in this game? NA aim. Sorry, sorry, son. I've spent too much
time online. When you pull that off, you're ready for a gun. See you later, Johnny.
Do I have to sit here and practice until I get it? I'm aiming at it. We're going to get a
transition into him having a beard and being like presumably 20 years older.
Because anytime you get a beard, it means you aged at least 25 years.
He's gonna get it right when they pull all the way back. Oh, if only the characters could do a
backflip. All right. Okay. Loading. Look at these loading times. Oh, yeah. A broadcaster.
Nice. This grenades. This is probably grenades.
Big Ann. It's like a shootout. Do I get to actually use a gun?
Come on. Let's show them who's boss. Yeah. Take cover. Brain robbery. Come this way. Let's flank
him. Holy shit. Who's doing that? That's insane aim. Don't let him get away. Is this me? No.
These people even have weapons? Well, this is not good. Another notch for Big Ann.
Hey, Lisa for me. This is a huge train. This is the biggest train I've ever seen in my life.
Rocky Mountains, Colorado. You're a city slicker. Am I? It's both huge. I wonder what's in here.
The train was so long that I feel like if the train crashed, it would take like
four hours before we even figured it out back here. Something tells me you ain't here punching
tickets. There he is. Is he a beard? Kinda. Seems like we made an unplanned stop. Kinda.
I'd better go find out what's holding this up. OK. I have a weapon. This game's kind of fun.
I have to sneak my way up to the front of the train. I have a knife? Holy shit. I can stab people.
All right. Hold on. This game's fun. OK. Anything else over here? Wait, what about you?
And up on my way. Hurry up. I'm so glad you could do that.
OK, here we go. Knife knockout. You can take down enemies up close using your knife.
We'll knock them out. Press Q to select the knife, then L to attack. For a knockout,
swap out the skill in the skill bar. I mean, a knockout. Let's make it quick. You fucking serious?
No, I'm not knocking him out. He's got a gun. Can I pick up that gun? OK. Nice knockout.
Why would I knock him out? I'm fucking desperado. Throwing knife. Koopa can throw his knife to take
down enemies from afar. He needs to retrieve it afterwards. This is awesome. Press W to select
throwing knife and throw it with L. I have to get the knife. Oh shit. Let's knock this guy out.
Oh shit. That guy had a shovel. That guy had a shovel. All right. That guy was always going to
give me the shovel. Got to go. Got to go. Got to go. Got to go. This guy's going to wake up. Throw
him. OK, he's dead. Give me the knife. You're ignoring that. Put a face cam on the portrait.
No, I'm naked. I can't do that. David.
Shall we? No, I'm not going to put casino ink on the portrait. No, no. Hold on. Hold on.
You said you bought a cowboy costume. Do you really think I did that?
Jesus, you scared me. Don't hurt him. Let's get going. Here, have a coin. I just need a few
seconds. Fuck. You say what the fuck? Because I gave him a coin. Koopa can use his revolvers to
take down guards. Guns are loud and will alarm guards not hear them? Oh shit. OK, what? I have
two different kinds of guns. Here he comes. I'm doing tricks. Shoot him. I did a trick and he
didn't shoot him. First the trick button. There's got to be another way. No, I don't have a cowboy
costume. I made that up. Jesus, you scared me. Can you help us? Where's he looking? Over there.
He doesn't see you over here. Let's take out the new model army. Remington model. Or the old 51.
Did you get him? Oh shit. He sees me. Give me more time. How many bullets can this thing hold?
What's that? Don't look for you. I just used the other gun. Thank you, stranger. Give me money to
hide. I don't want to shoot them. How do I put this away? Come on. OK, that's good. Who cares
about lifting them up? Where'd they go? Where'd they go? Did they jump off? It's now or never.
Next time I better thin down the pack before I get loud. I fell. And no, I'm going to play this like
I play every game that's like Hitman. Try to sneak in, get stopped at the front door,
and then just shoot them all. Anything we might regret was this. Well, now maybe throw a grenade
or two. So should I sneak over here? I feel like this is a character I want to keep. Not a problem.
Dual shot. You can fire both guns at the same time. You can now choose two targets for Cooper's
guns. Oh, that's really odd. That's actually really cool. I'll take them both down at the same
time. One, two, execute. Nice. A two headed boy, thanks to the five subs. I'd say you owe me one.
Hey, now, are you kidding me? All right. I'd say we're even now. Identify this. Now I suggest you
return to your wagon. I'll handle things from here like you handled those two.
Listen, Mr. Cooper, you would recognize your own dad. Mr. Cooper, I've been hired to make
sure this train gets to Flagstone. I'd appreciate it if you don't get in my way. Well, now, Mr.
We go like four hours into the game. And he finally talks about how he's like Mr. Cooper.
Oh, shit. Yeah, dad, it is you. Fuck. In a while. How did I not know?
You don't typically wear purple. That's a very simple joke.
The train stopped. He's going to take some work to clear those rocks.
Me a dynamite. You're going to give me dynamite? Yes, you are. Good thing they have a stash of
dynamite up on that plateau. Yeah, grab it and clear the tunnel. Not such a bad plan.
I don't do bad plans. Fair enough. Let's get to it then. All right. Sure thing.
I don't understand why people just put this huge stuff like stuffed peppers worth of dynamite.
Why would you do that? Why can't you have like five different barrels? Why does it have to be
stuffed that much shit in it? I don't know. You can throw your bag. Yeah. OK. He has to retrieve
it again. A gas trap blinds enemies who opened the bag. Oh, shit. I have more than one character
now. What is this one syringe? Well, the game just got way better.
Only temporary. Throw the bag. First enemy to spot it will come for it. If opened, it briefly
blinds the target with gas. All right, so we're going to go up here. Wait, we can go two different
ways. All right, you go this way. Let's keep moving. You walk across this. Don't get in the way. I'm
going to use my bag. You get over there. You just hide and learn something. OK, you go this way.
Here it goes. Jump over to the other cart. We're going to do this at the same time. It's going to
be awesome. Oh, I can't. This is a tutorial. Never mind. Someone call for a doctor. Here we go.
Gas bag E. Let me take care of that. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I need a coin. I can't throw it. Saved me dozens of time. Who wants to have a look? Hey, OK, then.
Bag came out of the bush. It looks like a gas trap. Huh? Not bad. Wait, is he blind?
You don't, Mr. Cooper, unless you're me. But can he kill him? Gotta love bandits.
Leave their boss to me. I smell trouble. This is our train now. I can handle that. Thank you.
You wasted. Oh, I got it right here. Hold on. Let's throw. OK, we're going to do this.
You get it. Then you stab him. No, I'm looking at this. That wasn't there before.
Is this guy going to do it again? This guy's got like the mind of a mouse. OK, let's go. Ready?
Got him. Fucking teamwork. Perfect.
Let's move. Get that bag back. You get it? I just have to walk over it. OK.
They work together. Do they walk together or do I have to control them both independently?
Bunt line. McCoy can use his bunt line to take down enemies from a long distance if he needs
this skill for him. Holy shit. OK, if he needs this skill for a mission, he will carry a final
golden bullet. There's a lookout up on the cliff. I'll take him from here. That I want to see. Well,
I'll be damned. Give him a chance. Bunt line special. Custom stock. Go that far with a weapon
like that. Hurry up. Isn't that a pistol? I'll take him up. Where can I put him? On my way.
Whatever. Who cares? Put him over here. This is the tutorial mission. Who cares?
Let's go. I've got a group of three up here. It's now or never. Can't climb that shit.
Can he do anything about this? For the job straight through hell. Right. I'll follow.
Can he shoot that path is blocked? Understood. Oh, I thought that. Hey, I had a John H was
activated. It was fucking me up. Well, we'll figure something out. He can't climb. Let's keep our
distance. Oh, wait, he was too old to climb it. See, save that game. You can highlight both
characters. No, I beg your pardon. Oh, that's so much better. OK, cool. All right. Nice path is
blocked this way. The path is blocked. I refuse. No, you can manage this rope ladder, Mr.
McCoy. I prefer Dr. McCoy. I'm sure you do. Why do we do that? OK, then. I refuse.
How are we going to tackle this, man? We got a campfire over here. You've guns, right? I know
I'm supposed to be tactical about this, but is that really going to be a thing? I could do
the showstopper and we could both do something. I could throw a knife at this guy right now. I'm
going to throw a knife at this guy right now. OK, he's dead. All right, now go get him. Go get him.
Go get him. Go get him. Go get him. Go get him. Go get him. Go get him. Go get him. Go get him quick.
His friend's going to be looking for him. Here goes. Yeah, that worked. All right, let's do it
again. Someone's about to lose a few teeth. Got it. Let's go. That worked. OK, now what?
Here goes. What are they? Where's the site? All right, stay behind the rock.
OK, so I can coin. I'm going to coin him and then the doctor's going to get the doctor's going to.
Do I get more? OK, I have a question. Do I get more points for doing things
a good way? Or can I just shoot all the matter? It's just fishing. Wait, give me that back. He's
not going to see it. All right, give me that back. He's not going to see it. Just what I had in mind.
Do you see this? All right, he'll see it if I throw it over here.
All right, so I'm going to gas him and then syringe him. It saved me. Let's throw out the door.
It works very fast. Here they come. Objection's here.
I love how you can syringe people in this game. OK, he's gone, too. We only have one more person
to deal with, and I know exactly how I'm going to do it. Still warming up shoes.
OK, good. What's the next tutorial?
Guards wearing ponchos don't get fooled easily. They don't leave their posts
and distractions are shorter. Oh, that doesn't matter.
He ain't going to move if it ain't necessary. And you know that because trust me, I know the time.
Who cares? Just kill him. Just kill him and then punch this guy in the face and throw him over the overboard.
Oh, no, that guy is wearing a poncho. Does that mean he can't die?
No, he actually can die very easily like every other human. OK, kill him.
Oh, that was not good. Is he still unconscious? Showdown mode advanced. OK,
showdown mode. Pause the game unless you plan one action per character.
That's important. Press enter to instantly execute all the actions for a shift.
You want to execute planned actions later. Oh, nice. OK, we can do it together.
We can do one and two. Give me that knife. OK, let's go back in business.
Well, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. This is a guardhouse. Hey, ambush right on schedule.
Well, I forget what this guy's name is. It'll cost you our hide here.
I'm going to get extra points. We're going to kill all these people in here. All right.
Hide here. You hide here. Damn, that train's long. Right. I'm going to gas them.
Here we go. Anyway, I got a few tricks who wants to have a look.
One out straight through hell. Never mind. I can handle that. Thank you.
Let's go. So we're going to I'm going to do advanced mode. Let's see how this works.
That's sweet. Sweet. Come on. Let's go about this quiet.
All right. Showdown. You take the other. All right. Showdown. I have a timer on this.
I don't. OK, good. Let's catch a few bandits.
I'm going to stab this person in the back and then you're going to syringe this person
who needs a shot in the next trouble. Oh, come on. Nice. See you in hell.
OK, that was fun. That was really fun. OK, cool. Now what? Oh, shit. On show.
Let me take care of that on my way. I would rather stay out of this.
Selecting multiple characters. You guys already told me that you're sure could use our health.
I waste time. Let's keep going. Side quest. I hate fancy folk like you.
All right. We have a side quest. Especially you.
All right. We're going to throw a guy in the fire because I have to.
All right. Showdown mode. Right. How do I do this without losing?
We have moral choices to make. OK, there's a guy right here.
Three, one, two, three. OK, I'm going to throw. Here we go. This is what we're going to do.
We're going to throw a knife at this guy, syringe this guy. Here we go. Syringe you.
OK, then I'm going to switch over here and throw a knife at you. Watch and hurry up.
And we're going to go.
All right. He got it. He's good. He's good. He's good. All right. Now shoot him.
All right. You're all safe. Wait, there's one more. There's one more. There's one more.
I didn't see that last guy. All right. That didn't work. I waste time. Let's keep going.
Stop collisioning each other. All right. There's one, two. This is the guy I thought. OK,
they're all like kneeling down. I thought he was one of them. All right. Eyes open.
Cooper. Here it goes. I didn't hear. Well, that's what you get.
Whatever your name is over here. Get a spot right here. Go.
Shoot two people in showdown. That's right. Oh, yeah. OK. Bag. I think I can just kill this guy.
I don't need anybody knowing. No, maybe. Yeah, maybe I can. If I just get OK,
if I just get over there, save it right here. If I just get over here because he can't see.
All right. He's in a good spot. OK, new plan. What's up?
You better give us everything. We're going to search your body.
You hear that? Who needs a good killing? Oh, look. Oh, look. Wait, shit. OK, where are you?
Ready? I got lots of you going to be big. All right. Stay distracted. Hurry up. Hurry up. Hurry
up. Hurry up. Get down. Get down. Get down. Get down. Get down. Get down. Get down. Get down. Get
down. Get down. Get down. Get down. I'm fine. All right. OK. Now. I hate fancy folk like you.
Now I'm going to stab. We're going to bag this guy or bag this guy or OK, we don't walk anyway.
Let's throw out the lower. That's what you get. Oh, no, no, no. I don't want you to look at it.
No, no, no, no, no. You don't. I don't want him to look at it. OK, let's go. Let's raise some hell.
Got a load. It's only let me take care of that. Execute.
Straight through hell. Did he miss? What just happened? How come he didn't shoot this guy?
Why didn't he not shoot this guy? Keep it cool. Watch and learn. I'll get close and personal.
That was a civilian. Thank you. I'll send you the check. Where are they? What's the big idea?
I didn't kill a civilian, though. Are you kidding me? Wait. I'll follow. No more surprises.
I know I did not. I didn't kill anybody. It'll cost you.
It burned bodies. Throw him in the fire. I know, but I don't want to get spotted. Look, you got this
time. What's he doing? Burn them. But I'm going. I'm going. I just I don't know if this guy's going
to swap me. How's it going? Hurry up. I just want to. Where's the bad guys? You're heavy on my way.
And up. I can't. You are the bad guy. I'm not the bad guy. The guy's the guy with the poncho.
No, forget it. I got a bullet for him. Shoot him. Shoot him. Why can't I shoot him?
We need to be moving on. This is an obstruction. All right. Oh, God damn it. Um, I think we may
have a problem. I did. Darren, you're going to have to do the rest of the game because I can't move.
Now's the time. OK, Darren here. Take a few coins to buy some potions. OK, I have to do
the rest of the game with him. Just yet. Sure. OK, cool. Let's go. Just load. I think I could
probably do it. Well, that was a waste of time. See, I knew you had a heart in there somewhere
anatomically. Maybe someone call for a doctor. How far away is the load? Oh, OK, we're good. We're
fine. OK, then don't get anywhere. I knew you had a heart in there somewhere. All right, slow down,
slow down, slow down. Maybe. Wait, there's a there's a treasure chest over there. Understood. I can't
wait till I get grenades. Seriously. One of the train looks like we made it. We still need the
dynamite to clear the tunnel. That's easy. Come on, let's make our way up on my way. Shall I get
out of here? Go run. Keep your heads down and stay out of my way. Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa. Thank you so
much. You think you're. I see you asshole. I didn't. Let's keep our distance. It's fun.
I actually like this. This is actually fun. This is like a strategy game, but for fucking moron
psychos like me. OK, do you like like strategy games with top down like kind of real time?
Yes. Are you also fucking psycho? Yeah. Oh, you're going to love this. Cool. Thanks. I've always
wanted to be the psycho RTS guy. Just what I had in mind. Let me take care of that. Where are you
going? Where are you going? Where are you going? Where are you going? Where are you going? Where are
you going? Where are you going? Where are you going? Where are you going? Where are you going? Where
are you going? Come on, let's make our way up. Understood. Get down. Don't get in the way. I'm
trying to read this. The view cone marker shows that the spot is watched by guards. Hold what?
Hold the L to place in a location or a guard. Not a problem. Something. Well, who do we have here?
I'm trying to figure out the tutorial. You know, I got to stop clicking everywhere.
I'm playing this like I'm playing League or like Dota.
But don't click that often. Why am I like, well, like, slow the fuck down. Shall we?
You click more often than you click in Diablo. All right. I have to get this treasure. I'm not
going to. OK, so what was it was hold L. I can see where they're looking or how does that work?
Let's see. It's kind of like a location of what they're looking at or something.
Let's see if an area is being watched or not. Looks like we made it.
I still need the dynamite to clear the tunnel. That's easy. Come on, let's make our way up.
OK, so leave it on this guy. Not a problem. OK, can I kill this guy and get this stuff
without anybody seeing me do it in this bush? No, motherfucker. I swear to God. It's OK. Stay right
there. Let's make it quick. Get him. We'll take care of the bandits. Thank you. Thank you so much.
All right. Hold on. Is he going to notice that this guy's gone?
I guess time's a changing. I can't put him down here. Can I? All right. Hold on. Here comes another
guy with a shovel. Now I want you. I want your eyes. Where are your eyes? There we go. All right.
There's three of what in here? Someone call for a doctor. I can reload this. Let me take care of
that. There we go. All right. It's a reload. Nice. Nice. I get the dynamite.
The safe. I swear. Good time. They think they can hide. Thank you. Thank you so much.
Somewhere. Drag you out of there.
Oh, man. There's a sniper. Quick. Hey, stick your neck out as far as it can go, Terry.
There's a sharpshooter. No more surprises. Got to find them.
Whoever finds them gets their stuff. What? That sucks. I know they're here. Whoever finds them
gets their stuff. Okay. Not like not a thousand gold or something. Just get this stuff.
We got to smoke them out. Someone hiding in there. Shit. Don't let them get away.
Okay. Let's go reload that again. It'll cost you. I'll take that. Thank you. I hope I don't need
this. Okay. So we're going to distract. Okay. They're going to go in here, not out here. Yes.
They're all going back into the train. We're fine. Oh, what about this guy? I beg your pardon.
Can't get him. It's an obstruction. I'm sorry. Sorry, you two. I can't do anything about it.
If they make choices. I got a feeling about this. I'm going to throw a coin right here and we're
going to go do a showdown. These two. Let's see what's happening here. Not yet though.
Oh, God damn it. Really? Hey, coin. What oldest trick in the book. If we can grab
all three of these guys, heads or tails, distract three bandits at the same time.
Uh, I got lots of these need some change. I don't, they're not going to look over here. Go.
That big rock there is looking like it wants to fall. Wait, I can fit a big
wave. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
hold on a big rock. It was like 10 people right here. Oh no. Okay. Let's just, let's get them.
All right. Who's going to do it? Somebody has to push it. Push the rock, push the rock, push the
rock. Excuse me. Go to push the rock. Oh shit. I thought it was going to roll at least a little
bit. Can I get on a horse? This is wild. Okay. There's one guy here. All right. We're going to
distract this guy and then you're going to knock yourself out. Oh, together, together, together,
together at once. Sure thing. Got it. On the horse. We get on the horse. Now's the time. Get on
the horse. Well, now let's see. I wouldn't worry just yet. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit. Showdown
mode. We have to, I, we have to, we have to just kill this guy. Double team him or something.
Here, go to the gas. I understood. It's just fishing. Hey, that's going to pay for it. Here
they come. It works very fast. See you in hell. I'm here. What do I do with these?
What do I do with these? I don't think I can do anything with those guys. Oh shit. Save it.
You can't see shit. Okay. All right. We almost did the dynamite. I'm almost got it. Somebody's
about to lose a lot of money betting that I wasn't going to get past the first mission of the game.
Um, what are you doing? What are you doing? You're about to. Let's go fuse. Trying to touch the
tutorial. Pick up dynamite from the barrel and throw it. Oh, come on. Yes. Okay. The game just
increased in value. Aim with Q and throw with it using left mouse. Be careful. It'll explode in
your hand. Oh no. All right. Oh, only one of us is going to do this. Pick up the dynamite,
not the guy on the ground. That's a very, very short fuse. It's not, that's a really short fuse.
By the, I had so many people are just dead up here. All right. Who needs this? I object
back in business. You better have a fuse. Better throw it fast.
Wait, it's already lit. Oh shit. The horse. All right. We're good. We're good. We're good.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. Do I need to show down time for dying? All right. I'm going to
move him out of the way. Here it goes. We have these, this guy, let's take these guys out first.
I'm not fucking around anymore. Let's go. These guys all got to die. What are you looking at?
Us. All right. Get the bag out. Hide in the bush and then we're going to go. This guy's dead.
Okay. Throw it out there now. What the fuck was that? What was that? I was trying to throw the
briefcase. Who needs the fucking briefcase? Just stab him in the head. All right. Pick this up.
Gotta love bits. Are we killing bandits? Why would they love bandits? Okay. Does that guy dead?
I smell trouble. I hear for a second. Where's his eyesight? All right. We'll go over here.
This is only temporary. Something on that I don't like. Get in there. Safe up here. Safe. Only one
at a time though, please. Shall we continue? You stay in the bush. Let's see what's happening here.
Okay. I'm going to throw. We're going to throw a coin right here.
You hear that? Watch and learn. Okay. He's dead. Anybody else? We're good. All right.
Let's go. Not sure where this is going. Let's keep our distance. Back in business. Now, only one of
you go down here to the dynamite, except you need this shit. Here, come here. Looks like we're past
Denver. You go up here and hide in a bush. You come down here and you refill your ammo and then
get the dynamite. Got it. Okay. I'm ready. I'm going to throw this. Oh, but there's a guy I could
like punch. It's now or never. I've missed the fuse. Now run. I'm in the bush.
Good thing we got more dynamite.
Hey, now we're good. Right? He's in a bush. He's in a bush. Why do they know what bush he's in?
Fuck you. Okay. I've missed the fuse. Better throw it fast.
Oh, wait, wait, wait. Oh my goodness. Did you see that? Holy shit. I killed everybody. I killed
everybody freaking out. Let's find a safe spot. Good thing we got more dynamite. Okay.
You better have a plan. All right. Now what? Play the tunnel. Meet up at the meeting spot.
I got a feeling about. Oh, I can save these people. Oh, you're both going different ways.
Just what I had in mind. Don't get in the way. This guy has a shovel. He's not going to threat.
This is the guy that's the threat. My thoughts exactly.
Bring it on. Here it goes. Edit and then save the civilians.
I'll take that. Let's make it quick. All right. You're free. Don't take it personal.
Keep your hands down. Nice. We'll take care of the pain. That's what I did it. That's a
secondary objective. Not a problem. Meeting point. Let's go. All right.
All right. Here it is. Let's deal with the rest of them. My thoughts exactly.
What is this game? This is Desperado's three. And so far, this is actually pretty fun.
Guess you made the David company happy today. How much do you get for a job like this?
Hope you're not expecting a cut. Relax. I got what I need. This counts as a plus
full letter grade, by the way, if I can drive the car, which is a horse got to make good on time.
Like I said, please, I got an appointment. I'd like to keep suits yourself.
Right. I mean, if I can fall sprint the horse into bad guys, you McCoy have to give it a full
letter. Sure. If you need a professional, you know who to send for. Good day, Mr. Cooper.
Wait, we're losing them. That guy was so useful.
Owen Wilson team up. Oh, I didn't get this one. Don't save during the mission. Don't use fire
arms. Complete the mission in under five minutes. The mission on hard. Well, I got two out of three.
This always is the most obnoxious thing. And I hate seeing this in every iPad game.
Two stars is like, holy shit, dude, come on. You were so close to the three.
One star means you don't care. And you don't have any fucking in game currency shit.
Two is you probably bought in game currency shit, but you used it so poorly that you still couldn't
get to three stars. That pisses me off seeing that. Wait a minute. Hold on. What you can
tells you everything you did. This is awesome. All right. Where do we go from here? Why is this
money explosions? You're going to see when I compulsively had to throw somebody off the cliff.
Does this take into account all the saves? Save one save number three. Wait, what happened up there?
What? What exploded? I feel like I'm playing like a Gario. Holy shit. That was awesome. Nice.
Let's see. That's so cool. Eight saves. Twenty two. What's that? Twenty two. What was he on fire?
Does that mean he did better if he was the better teammate? OK,
let's save in the replay. Twenty two saves, eight loads. Oh, that's cool. Thirty three minutes,
seven shots, three dynamites and stabs kills thirty alarm. Enemies killed. There's only two
people left on the whole map alive. That kind of bad. The star is five minutes. Yeah, no way.
All right, we got Devil's Canyon. Yes, pass and then Flagstone. Do you feel the game is too hard?
No, I don't want to adjust. John Cooper has come to Flagstone to meet an old friend. Doesn't take
long for trouble to arrive. I just beat the first level in thirty three minutes. Do you think I'm
having not that much trouble? Troublemakers in Flagstone. Nestled between the peaks of the
Colorado Rockies lies the small town of Flagstone. Store owners, farmers, blacksmiths and barkeepers
all go about their daily business. Workers of the David Company mingle with the locals as they
continue to build the new railroad through town. As Cooper arrives in Flagstone, he heads straight
for the saloon, which is empty except for a few regulars. The barmaid pours a glass of whiskey in
the nurse. The nurse, he nurses it while he waits for an old friend. Can't fucking read anymore.
They tore down old Williams House the other day. Call the sheriff. Now, why do they have to do that?
Can't they lay their tracks between our homes? Actually bad. Stick to the game, will you? Yeah,
I'm just saying they ever come to my house. I'll show these railroad thugs whose balls. Oh, shit.
Well, what can I do for you, gentlemen? Oh, we'll get to you in a minute. You know the drill.
Everybody out. Yes, sir. Game of cards. It always looks like this. Oh, you keep fucking track of
who's who. Something in your ears. Just finishing my drink. Better dealer, man. You gotta go to a
better banker in Monopoly. We own this town now. So when he says out. Look at me. We don't like
troublemakers around here. Who do we have here? Well, you got double trouble now.
What the hell? You again? Is the doctor. Wait, he's on my team.
They're running away. I can't blame them. Poor guys had to look at your ugly mug.
Oh, you're welcome. You need a drink. Is it like a giant sword? A bow and arrow?
Yours is on the house. The big axle for a car. You really shouldn't. They'll kill you next time.
They can try. I guess you've been here a while. Spent your time pissing off the wrong people,
huh? I'm the one that pissed off. But as you're here, maybe we can work together.
Oh, no, you're not dragging me into this. He shot that guy. I'm here for Frank.
Surround the place. Don't let them get away. Amigo, you're already in it. And besides,
you owe me one. All right, let's get out of here. Come on out the back. The guy's dabbing. Of
course you would say that. That's okay. I mean, of course that that's what's happening.
It's a bloodborne weapon. That's so funny. All right, let's go. What's his special power?
They're here somewhere. And we got all the time in the world. Well, these guys are out for blood.
The Monster Hunter. Part of the David company. I've scores to settle with a few of them.
Cooper, find any green teeth. I need it. I'm trying to turn this into a poison weapon. Sure.
Let's head for the street. Nobody will bother us if we stay among the townsfolk. So we got room to
breathe. So far so good. But whose heads are we bashing in? First, we got Jarvis here. We're tough
guys. Right now he's in that backyard trying to ride that just kill him. That's just gonna kill
him anyway. Next is Wilde March. She's on the first floor of the flagstone brothel. Oh, this is
awesome. Whiskey and watching the girls. This is gonna be so awesome. I can't wait. Then there's
the Duke. He's making rounds with his bootlickers up and down Church Street. And last is the former
people don't have to kill. He's a real asshole had his men tear down half the towns that he
doesn't have to plan around it. So we get rid of them. Head back to the saloon and finish our
drinks. That ain't much of a plan. Hector. Why do you think I've waited for you? All right.
Let's get it over with. I have to sneak around. Am I allowed to be in this town? What's the matter
with these guys? Well, now I don't have to sneak. Right. I guys live here. Hector can whistle to
lure guards towards his current location. It's a trap. He can place Bianca, a giant but surprisingly
stealthy bear trap. Hector is smart. So Hector likes to combine his skills. That seems really,
really morbid. Just unnecessary and completely inappropriate. Why don't you just learn how to
fucking shoot a gun? I say it's time to use Bianca. You still carry that thing around. I have a
reputation to keep. Time to use Bianca. Let's lure someone into your embrace. Get your shit
together. Hector, it don't work. Can we get this over with? We're not done yet, amigo. I'll use my
singing voice. I do it. You got it, amigo. Sing. Sing. Is he even gonna step in it? Don't think
you can hide. Who needs a haircut? Yeah, I got it. You better leave Blackstone before I find you.
Super, the trap didn't work. Trust me, it doesn't usually go like this.
Wait, isn't that the main bad guy? Oh, come on. What? That's the main bad guy.
I just need a few seconds. Don't let them get away. We gotta smoke them out. Let's make it quick.
Who needs no bloody? I knew I was right to bring you along.
Sure glad I'm meeting your expectations. We got troublemakers here. Keep your eyes to you.
I need this back. Where are they? Keep looking. Gotta find them. Fucking three-head. What?
Fuckers. Whoever finds them gets their stuff. It's so lame. What about T? What's T do?
Good stuff. Oh, I can heal Hector. I'm in the mood for some chopping. They gotta be around here
somewhere. Yeah, that's right. You run home to mama. Give me this back. On my way. She looks ready for
more. I see you. Fuck. Why does this keep happening? Hiding in there. It's the two chokers.
What is he saying? Drink, drink, drink, drink. I think you're clever. I found you.
Whoa. What? He's Estus chugging. Can't even say it. It's so stupid.
We already know what happens here. What's wrong with my voice? Okay, this is what I'm talking about.
Nobody move. Nobody talk. Nobody say anything. This is permanently... I've turned into Tom Hanks.
Somehow I just turned into Tom Hanks because my voice has changed a little because I was drinking
water. Let me tell you, I loved working on Toy Story. It was one of my favorite movies working
on. Favorite film. I love being Woody. He's the best character I've ever done work with.
And I'll tell you, Tim Allen with Buzzkill, he was great. He was great. He was great, Tom.
I'll never get that again. Hiding here. He was never really here to begin with. All right,
let me get this right. How would you not see a gigantic bear trap on the ground? Okay,
put it like right there. It wants me to seriously learn how to do this.
Okay, we're still here?
Time to make some noise.
Yeah, still fresh. All right, get it back. We're good. Save it.
Let's take a look at the plan here. Okay, we got two guys here.
He can't hide forever. Make it this way. Let's check and see. Let's take a look at what he's
looking at. All right, he's got a big radius. Where's he go? All right, he goes, he turns his
back. How's our opportunity? Go. Remember, leave the big guy to me. He got you once already.
He's all yours. Where do you look? Are we safer? We have to be, right? Long coats. Yeah, the most
dangerous enemies. Hector is the only one that can take them down by himself with his axe or his
bare fists. That's good to know. That's why he didn't step in the trap. I'm going to show down
this. I'm going to wait. Can we get this? He's going to stab this guy in the back. He's going
to go for him and have the axe. Yeah, they couldn't have slipped through. Let's get going.
Go down mode. Is he immune to guns? I mean, he has to be right. All right, time for a showdown.
You are going to go stab him in the back. Come on. Hector, you are going to go over here.
Nobody messes with Hector. What are you going to do? What is he going to do?
Whistle? Hector, you're going to whistle. I'll use my singing voice. Yep. And then you're going to
hide. Whistle. Let's go. Oh, my God. You fucking did it. Just a scratch.
It's so quick. How come we didn't whistle? I have to click it? I thought it was like,
OK, I'm so I'm in showstopper mode. You're ready. So like whistles my singing whistle. OK,
I get it. You have to actually do it. You're going to go over there and you're stabbing the
knife. And then you are going to just like the Sims. If I haven't do something else,
we do it. Time for the X. Let's lure someone in. Is this place just a scratch? Why is he a bear?
What's going on? Are you behind this door, Sonny? Don't move an inch.
Who needs a haircut? Hey, it's the two jokers. Who the fuck are you?
OK, I have to I got to lower him again. This strategy is not going to work. OK. I mean,
we could turn him around and go this way. Come on. It'll be fun. Keep your head down. I just need a
few seconds. Throw it over there. Put a cork in it. What the fuck? And then wrap around this way.
I can't kill him. Turn up the long coat. Isn't that going to make a huge bunch of noise?
Stop being bad. I've been that guy for 10 minutes. Come on, amigo. No, I need to. OK, I know. I have
to coin him and then kill him. All day. We go. Ready? Lots of these point him heads or tails.
Kill him. Not worth it. I do it again later. Oh, you can kill people, too. That's good. Well,
I'm getting thirsty, Murdoch. I can't hide forever, Sam. Let's do this. Get your shit together.
How's it going? Shall we? Let's do this again. Go time. Ready? What? Oh, you son of a bitch.
Fucking restart the goddamn thing. Just use the axe. He's going to but he's going to see that.
I got lots of that over here. Come on. You come over here and use the axe on these guys.
I like it. Oh, sure. Knock yourself.
All right. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. This is perfect. Perfect. Perfect. Perfect. Perfect.
Perfect. Perfect. Perfect. Perfect. You're going to go. You're going to go this way.
You're going to go. Actors here. Act them right in the head. I'm in this way, amigo.
And then you're going to distract them. Throw a coin right behind all this trick in the book.
Okay. Check this shit out. Go. Let's go.
Fucking idiot.
Not your lucky day. Don't let them get away. You got it, amigo. Anybody find anything?
Time for the axe. Time to go.
True. I was ready to bring it along. Sure. Glad I'll meet your expectations.
It's like slaughtering people. All right. We have to stop doing this.
Why do they keep reviving him? I put the bear trap down right here and then you're
going to do it. I didn't pick the knife up. I'll get close and personal.
All right. Just no, no, no. Just put it down. Who do we have here? I'll run.
What's he doing? Run. Run. You fucking moron. Someone's about to lose a few teeth.
All right. Kill him. I have to kill this guy.
Someone needs to get things done. Oh shit. Time for the axe. Okay. I'm good. We did it.
I made it. All right. She looks ready for more. How do I hide all these guys?
I don't think I can throw them down the well. Yeah, I'm ready. This is nothing over there.
No problem. Can't do it. Can't throw them in the well. Why? Look, I killed everybody that would
be showing up over here anyway. Does it really matter? Forget it. I can do this all day.
It does. Yes. Okay. All right. I'm doing it. This bush is going to stink after a few days,
by the way. This is going to be the smelliest bush ever. People are going to be like,
holy shit, someone's going to pull that up. What's wrong with that bush? It smells so bad.
That's a problem. I can handle it. Let's light this up. Okay. The game is saved. We're good.
And that was tricky. Yeah. How many people? All right. So now I can be in the town with it.
Civil zones. Characters can move through civil zones undetected. As long as they don't act
suspicious, the red marker will indicate when you're about to leave or enter a civil zone.
Here we go. Look, it's now we're just normal people. Hey, look at that. Civil first on your
list. How about we just kill them in the order we like. Great plan. You have there. You heard
what happened with the church bell the other day. So who's on the list?
Okay. Kill the company thugs. Where's Jarvis? Guy over there. Wild Marge. McBain and the Duke.
All right. Let's let's head up that way. Follow this guy around.
Dang. I thought all this would be good for the town. We were so,
so happy when the mayor told us that the railroad would come. That's the Duke right there.
Oh, you take a good look. It's the guy running the company. Yeah, he wants to see his
dog. Doesn't give a doesn't give a shit about it. Yeah, we're just talking.
Okay. We know friends won't take long. This is outrageous. You can't just
tear down my house. I'm not going to just do that. I need to have at least somewhat of a plan.
Where does he go? I want to see. Does he leave a civil zone?
Okay. Now what if I put a trap right when he comes over here? Will this guy see?
We, uh, all right, here we go. We're going to try this here because our good friend,
I think I can get that to work. I really do.
He's trying to catch a bear. They're walking around it.
How many of these people are going to look around? What are you looking?
You're looking straight ahead. You're just a civilian. What? Who cares?
If you see, you gotta put a bear trap down and get out of here.
Wait, what's this? What's this bell?
Wait, I can throw somebody in a coffin.
I can get over here. This is still a civil zone. I'm allowed to be here.
This is going to kill anybody that's right there.
There's so many ways to kill people. Is that going to kill this guy too, right?
Is he going to walk over here and I'm going to looney tune this guy?
And I said, shut the fuck up. Yeah, I can. All right. I'm going to.
Cooper, you go over there. You too. This is a civil zone, right?
No, it's not. It's not a civil zone anymore. When you go through there,
is he going to walk through here? Okay. This is not a civil zone anymore. Not yet. Now I want you
time to go get over here. You don't mind this, right? Only Cooper can climb fucking trees.
All right. We'll switch. Things are quiet. It's like this. Sure thing. This is outrageous.
You can't just tear down my house. I'm obviously going to squash this guy.
Get everybody in the right position. Save the game. All right. I'm going to squash the guy first.
Relax, amigo. I'm going to sneak over here. Only got one guy right there.
You're looking this way. You're safe all the way until right here.
All right. This is where they're laying the tracks.
McBain's the foreman and doesn't let anyone on site. Let's keep it quiet when we head in.
He's too talking. I could probably trap this guy if I wanted to.
What happened? Has this guy walked over here?
Shit. What? Oh no. God damn it. All right. I got to take these guys out one by one then.
I'm going to trap right here and I'm going to whistle somebody and someone's going to die.
Hurry up. Hey there, you. You're enjoying yourself yet, Cooper? This way, amigo.
This is where they're laying the tracks. McBain's the foreman and doesn't let anyone on site.
Let's keep it quiet when we head in. Where? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I can't help but have the fucking wood. They heard that?
They can see me. Girl, this wood. I have to distract everybody. Okay.
I can't go through there. You're going up here. Changing you.
Does anybody care that I'm doing this? I don't think so, right?
All right. Let's take a look. I got to get up there.
This guy's looking straight ahead. Who cares? I care about this guy.
I think I can just knife him right now.
This guy's fucking dead. Let's go. Nobody else, right?
This dude is looking straight ahead that way.
Wait, am I just going to throw the bell at him? What do I do with the bell?
Oh, I'm going to kill this guy. Here he comes. This guy's dead.
One down, three to go. What about the coffin?
These guys didn't even care. Can I throw them in the coffin?
Why does this coffin exist? Doesn't that seem weird, right?
What do I do? All right. I'm jumping down. Wait.
Okay. Now, wait, wait, wait. Are these guys coming?
Now he's going to check the roof.
I'm really going to have to sneak through here, aren't I? I might have to go a different way.
Okay. Now I'm going to get, this is the only guy that stays down here. That was my fault.
Yeah. Well, just hold on and watch. Let's get going. Can't you jump off the roof?
And I'm going to sneak behind this guy, knock him out and I'm going to bury him.
A lot of people can fit in here, apparently. Okay. Anything else?
I have to actually be careful here. There's one guy pointing this way. I'm just going to
hide. I'm going to climb back around. Clown coffin. What are you doing? All right. That's
one dead. We need three more. Do they know? Go over there and distract them. Do something.
Okay. Now come down. We're good. All right. That's one down.
Here we go. Maybe we can't do that one yet. Maybe I have to wait.
Climb up there. All right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
I thought all this would be good for the town. We were so, so happy when the mayor told us.
German doesn't read this message. I will eat my barbecue chicken. Well, now you've got to figure
out something else to eat. It's the guy running the company. Wait, wait, if German doesn't read
this message, I will eat. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Okay. This is the, we got to probably have to like
poison this guy or something. I mean, I could, I could just throw an axe at him, right?
Is there a place to hide? Is there a bush right here somewhere? I could just throw something at
him. Oh, these are a little, okay. These are little helpers.
Tom's up there. All right. Let's go. What do I do about this guy? Just kill him and run. Sniping
spot. I don't think I can shoot that far. Sure thing. I'm down here. Who's this? All right. Let's
go check this guy out. We're probably going to be able to knock him off the thing and kill him.
Right. Understood. You got it, amigo. Too many guards for some backyard corral. Jarvis and his
man hang around here. Only one guy. What do you mean? One person. All right. Time for distractions.
We're in. Point. Heads or tails. Come on. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh.
Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Show stop. I got a plan. Okay.
I'm here. Put this shit down right here. Bianca. And then you're going to roll a coin. I just need
a few seconds. Right here. Just for a second so we can get some time to figure this out.
And you and I. Wait. Show stop. Show town. Whatever. Just stop it again.
I don't know. I need another coin. Ready? Oldest year goes.
Get in.
Okay. Now what?
I can just go over there. I think I can just kill him.
No one's going to even step on that. Piss off the bull. Yeah. I mean how?
Do I just fire a gun? Okay. I'm going to fire a gun. Just shoot and the bull's going to freak out.
Throw a coin at the bull. I'm not going to shoot the bull. I'm going to just shoot it in the air.
You're not going to walk in it? God damn it.
I know they're here. We're like every time at El Paso. I have to go get this dumb thing.
I just need a few seconds. We have to get. I have to get up here and then throw a coin from here.
It's possible that I could hit it from here though. Let's see. When it gets on, I'll try it.
Why would a bull give a shit about a coin sound? Do it now? Doesn't he have to be riding it?
Doesn't he ride it? I'm trying to like have him break his neck, right?
I'm just getting warm. You hear me? Next time I'll have you watch heads or tails.
That didn't work. Let's raise some hell. Okay. Then we're ready for it.
It's not scaring them. It's not scary. The bull's not scared. You guys that have
everybody was telling me to throw a coin at the bull. Shoot them. I we're like every time
at El Paso. All right. Well, that's not going to work. We have to find something else that has to
happen. Hit the bull. So I got to sneak back there. So this guy has to die. Okay. I'm ready.
It's now or never. I just need a few seconds. Not worth my time. Hey, it's the two chokers.
Here it goes. The coin. No, I have to sneak around and hit the bull. What's up? I just need a few
seconds. Let's get going in it. He's so slow. That's the problem. All right. Let's go save
kill these two. I can't just run and shoot them. The whole game attacks you. All right. Hold on.
That's good moving amigo. I'll use my singing voice.
Don't let him get you boss. You know, I'm going to walk over here.
Okay. Come on. What? Oh, it's he's got a poncho on. I have. He has to just die.
Can we get this over with? Let's lure someone in.
Get on with it. This guy's going to walk over getting a bit crowded. Sure thing.
Get over here. What? Nobody messes with that. Make some noise. I like it. I heard that
the more the merrier. Why won't he walk over here? This guy doesn't have a poncho on.
This guy has a poncho on. This guy doesn't have a poncho on. Why is he not listening?
Throw a coin at the trap. That's not going to do anything. Lots of these.
Okay. Here's the chance. Here's here. Keep your eyes. I'll use my singing voice.
What? Still got it. Let's do this. David, why don't you go get him?
Had to drag me into this. All right. Yeah, I'll get that. I need that. There she is.
All right. Let's fucking kill this asshole right here. Right now. Time to use Bianca.
Might have a poncho, but that doesn't particularly fucking hike in the head.
Okay. Now I can safely go get you. The other guy's not walking around. Let's go.
And up. No problem. Let's see.
Crap again. What do you think? Yeah. Oh yeah. Just like old time,
that'd be all guys ready. Check this shit out. Once this guy turns around,
this guy has this patrol. I'm going to, I'm going to whistle him over here. Get out of here. Move.
Leave. Leave. I just need a few seconds. They won't see us. Let's go. Looks like a job.
Oh, I heard that. No, I don't want you to come over here. I want you.
You show that bull who's boss boss. Well, I'll break that.
There we go. All right. If it doesn't work out, just fucking throw a knife at him.
Watch and learn. Don't think you can hide. God damn it. Nobody move. Nobody move. Nobody move.
Just don't move.
Like I'm making like a fucked up YouTube video proving that he could
withstand a bear trap. Why would he? Why would you do that? Well, okay.
We're going to go this way and I got a feeling we'll be able to knock this guy out. I'm going
to throw a knife at him. This trick in the book and the knife.
Oh, fuck. Duck. Duck. Get the fuck in there, dude. Hurry up. Oh, no. He's going to see him.
Hey, if you see him, shoot to kill. No one's going to check.
Stay in here. You got to find him. Anybody find him? I'll smoke him out. I'll be fine.
Stay the hell stay away from here somewhere. Where are they?
It's not going to be a soft lock. This is just they're going to go back to normal.
I know they're here. Sneaky motherfuckers. They got to be around here somewhere.
Okay. Good. Save it. We got I'm going to pick him up. Do they care? Are they going to come back and be like, oh, shit, I bought it.
Or does it not matter anymore? Oh, you're damn right. I need that knife. I'm the best.
Well, now let's see. Back in business. Yeah. Who needs a good killing?
We're going to do this quick. Knife will do. Okay. All right. You get up there and act.
Let's go. We're going to hear this right there. What the fuck?
No more surprises. These guys are hiding good here. Whoever finds them gets their stuff.
I'm here, amigo. It's like a job. Don't let them get away.
Search everywhere. I got it. Look. Oh, they didn't see me. He didn't see. He didn't see.
It's okay. And look, it doesn't matter. I'm going to show time. We're going to kill all three of them.
Okay. Good. Good. Now show. Show. Stop. We're going to go coin on you.
Okay. You're going to get up and you're going to hit the guy in the next. Go for it.
Drink, drink, drink, drink, drink, drink. Use your guns. I got it. Wait,
why am I? Okay. What's fine? You can shoot
once. Yeah. But then like the whole town gets alerted. Not a problem. Son of a bitch.
We're fine. That's an overreaction. The old and the new. Sure. Thank
I
Have to be patient I have to be patient
Don't even kill these guys. It's not even worth it. This does nothing for me
They'd go all they're gonna go up here and then we're gonna go into the bush
This guy is a pain in the ass. We can make it into this bush. That's it
What the fuck are you doing Jeremy? What is wrong with you? What's wrong with you? Why would you move? Why would you do that?
What's wrong with you? You insane?
Fuck let's I just need a few seconds
It in there get in the bush, okay good perfect perfect now we have an opportunity here
He's this town I can kill him watch and learn nobody's around, right? Oh
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
They're not gonna look over here though
I got the master
Ended up killing every single guard here somehow and this is the last guy and I'm just gonna be able to shoot him
No, we're not gonna be able to do the fun hitman mission completion thing with the bull kicking him in the head
I'm just gonna walk up and stab him
There you are, what do you mean there you are wait, okay
Opportunity coming in about five seconds five four three two. I like it
Okay, but done pretty much done these guys leave
Let's do this. So who should do this? Should I do it with a Cooper? Hey, wait, but um, uh
I don't know. I don't know what to do right now
Be our guys ready
Somebody has to sneak around
Eyes open can't see back here. This guy's gonna die
Hmm. I mean I could whistle this guy over with trap, right? Let's try that
These guys gonna come around the phone will be gone and I'll put the trap down here with this guy over said
Boy in the cold. All right, this should be good ready
do
Hey, I heard that get on with it
Hide him quick
Yep, um now this guy's fucked now I can we get okay. So let's do the fun thing
Keeps me waiting, huh?
This town's got her breath on my way. I won't see us coming. They're not gonna see this and be suspicious, right?
Let's go
She looks ready for more. You ready? I mean sure thing. Well, this guy go back to normal. I
Could die from right now, but that's not fun
new hint
Not so gifted worker build the sign. Oh
No, I don't just want to knife him that sucks. I want to like kill him fun in like a crazy way, right?
Let's go. I got lots of these
Looks like Jarvis wasn't such a big shot. I do. All right. What did I do? I didn't do anything
At least we're halfway down
The coin
But I threw the coin it I threw the coin at him before I didn't do anything. They won't see us coming
Let's do this
Be hungry third. Come on. Let's move it. Yeah, I did now or never
I did when I was standing back here and I threw it right there
You threw it and wait, you have to throw it. It has to hit the ball. So
Okay, he's not ready to go back yet. I mean I threw the coin right here and it was like the in the circle
I didn't know I had to throw it and hit the ball with it
Come on. I got lots of these
Looks like Jarvis wasn't such a guy. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it
All right, that's two down. Yeah, at least we're halfway done wild Marge is in here. We're gonna go. We're just gonna go in there
We're not done yet. I mean go wait to them. Hold on
Fuck making a move safe, but it's just a saloon right happened the whorehouse
Townsville can't go in since while Marge took over why not the front door then? All right, keep it low
We cannot find another way in
Okay. Well, we obviously have to go around here through the back
All right, just make me crazy part of me just wants to pack up and
Wait, nice house. Let's light this up. Hey, okay. Okay. Hey now
What I think that was gonna work? Why would that work in any video game? I've had any mechanics like this
What I think I got to get the whole thing and run
Keep your head down. I just need a few seconds. Well, shall we?
In the bush in the bush Cooper, please. Okay. This is the I have that tactics have to work out here. Okay, ready trouble
throw coin right here
All right, these company assholes or I'll get
Let's get going
Even if he wakes up the guys tied up doesn't matter save that shit and this is huge. Okay, let's go here. Let's see
It's a good climb up. All right, I'm gonna cut I'm gonna try to go off that ladder on my way
God damn it. It's never that easy. Now. It is your thing. Wait, what are these chickens? I'm old this trick in the book
That do I just need a few seconds
Get him
Yeah, not you're lucky. This is nothing. What's that?
Nothing stay over there
Actually come over here. No, no nowhere. Yeah over here. I'm right. I'll use my singing
How are you not in the bush just like I wish I had a goddamn knife I
Got lots of these
The hell time for the
Okay, I got it I got it I got it I went where are we let's get going
All right. Here we go. This town's going to shit's oldest trick in the book
Hey
But yeah, okay. He's clearly in the bush. You see that that's stupid
All right, let me think about this
Pre-recorded it'd be really weird if it was me not am I not reading chat anymore? It's actually soft-locked. It's soft-locked if you
I'm trying to pay attention. I have to go get the knife
Shit do I need it? I don't think I need it
My singing voice
Keep it cool. I just need a few seconds
Why do they not care about this?
Shall we I'm just getting I'll use my singing voice
All right, here we go. This is it. This is it. This is it. This is it. This is it. Get in the bush
Then I'll get back there and I'm gonna coin them
Yeah, I got it come on it'll be fun use my singing voice
All right show stop this shit right now ready they come
Okay, okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay show stop. No need to get bloody. They won't who needs a haircut sure thing. I may go
I'd hide hide. I'm up time up time up. What do you do it? You got it pick him up do pick him up
Up
Dump him right here. Oh my god that two people
Dump him
Dump him. Why would you take I've been by the spam clicking?
Here they come so shall we just like old time who needs a haircut? All right
Hector you got are you gonna take her in here with the axe?
Got two jokers. No, I did not select the same person. It'll be fun. Use my singing voice
Okay, all right, this is the one right now
Let's finish these guys. All right show stopper. Keep it cool. No need to Hector
Get the guy in the front
No need to Hector get the guy in the front I'm gonna get the guy in the back Hector's gonna kill the guy in the front
see
This guy up nobody can see us make you good and cozy
No one's gonna come back here
Don't even hide them. Save it. Let's go
I have plenty of bullets the time
Now what?
Go right there. We could probably all right. I'm gonna trap this guy to go
Little or no work. I got lots of these don't do that
Get out of here. Sure thing. Let's keep moving around the side
Like this. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Go up here
Ah, this is just another way to get over here. All right, cool
Multiple ways to do the level. That's cool
This guy's not gonna see it. We can just move I killed the other two guys
Yeah, listen bod watchers
He refuses to get the knife for another 40 minutes to preserve his pride and then pretends it was his idea to get it
It's now i'm gonna pay bod watchers. Don't listen to that guy
I know that I need to go get the knife and like i'm it's not my idea somebody in chat said dude
Get the fucking knife. So i'm gonna go get it
I have this is not me saying that this somebody in chat told me to get that
I want to correct that person ban that person for five minutes
Save it here
Dude, skip this part don't why would you skip this part?
Okay, here we go. I need to get in here
This is such a pain in the ass
Like why can't I just up eat this guy or absorb this guy and take his stuff?
What two people is too hard this guy's got a clean look this way we have to pull this guy
Who's i'm gonna set the trap down here looks like a job for bianca
Right here. Keep your eyes peeled. You're not gonna see this, right?
Just
I'm gonna whistle him over she's ready. Let's lure someone in
Making them more hungry
You didn't hear it. I had to make some noise
Hey, will he hear this?
Shit, you're not gonna hear this
All right, pack it up get it again pick it up. Let's do this. I pick it up
She looks ready for more the hell. Where's the fast forward button?
um
Okay, there is a fast forward button. Let's go. I don't like this something this way amigo put the trap down
Here I can get it there
What bianca is ready?
You got right there
Let's lure someone in
Still got it
Wait, wait, what do I do? I have to show stop because now there's a guy coming just shoot him. I just shoot him
I think i'm just gonna shoot him
Maybe I shouldn't even kill this guy
Yeah, I got it
I gotta go get the knife. Okay, fine. Fine. He's going on an expedition to get his knife. All right
Are you happy? He's gonna go get his knife. Let's get going here. Are we happy now?
Got it and reload. I'll take that. Okay, let's go
That's all right. I mean that's not right. What oh because I jumped
Who needs a good kill? No, I can't kill this guy. No, I have the knife. I didn't save it
I'm fine. I'm not soft-locked. We're good
Shall we i'm no longer illegal. So
Why does he care?
Won't take long
All right. Here we go
Not a problem, but he cares. Let's move
Is this one guy here? I'm gonna knife him
Do the food pyramid food pyramid. All right, hold on. Let me at least beat this level
I got two more people to kill
I'll do my i'll do my food pyramid soon. Hold on. I just gotta kill this guy
Sure thing. I just wanted the worst possible time
All right, i'm gonna save it here
good
And go this now or never
Hi, i'm back. I have my knife. You're ready to fucking play the game. Sure. Sounds like a lot of fun
Why don't you whisper this guy over here? Come on. Why don't you whistle just whistle at him?
And like he'll walk over here
There and then i'll knife him in the head
That sounds like a lot of fun
Is he plays this would you look at that?
Now go get him pick up that you didn't buy tonight and I tell you stay over here
Okay, now go get him
Stuff them in there
Save the game and we're cool. I'm just getting started. We're good
Good. All right. Now I can go this way
ah
Yeah, I feel good. Your voice sounds like he's crying
Kind of a weird observation, but all right. I like it
Dude, this dude's come on. I'm fine. Do you hear this guy?
Dude on stream just fucking bawling his eyes out. Ah, check out this whorehouse
We're just building in town. This place reminds me of the one in deadwood. There's three dudes here
Some deadwood, you know the one where they kicked me out that doesn't hide the chair
Good to see you amigo
All right, put this down bianca is ready
I feel like bianca. This is
This item's stupid
But we'll just knife a guy picket the knife up and do
They won't see us let's lure someone in let's light this up you yourself
I'm here
I feel like this this thing is stupid takes so long and I can just knife a guy bianca returns we got all day
Okay, all right. This is the last guy
And we're going in the house and i'm i'm gonna i'm just gonna get up there and i'm gonna shoot her
Keep using it. Yeah, I know
Um time to make some noise
Let's go over here
What's up?
It's the best tactic
Just whistle and then knifey it works every time
There goes he's gonna go in the front door
Hey
One no, I didn't okay. I wanted to use the knife but that works too. There goes another come on. Let's move it on my way
Oh shit, it'll be tight getting new march. She's on the top floor
Where's the guy wait, where is he where's cooper where's cooper where's cooper oh god run
Somewhere
There's always a way she's still up there. Wait, did I kill her?
Wait a minute. Oh, no, okay
That's wild march. All right. All right
Back in there
Fuck out. This guy's gonna come back in. Okay. No one no one's coming in here. We're fine
What what's this?
Maybe we could put something in the whiskey. Hey amigo think we could do something to the whiskey. Um
I guess
Okay, then put something fucked up in the whiskey. Where can I get that?
Nah
Nah, nah, nah
This is killer. I'm not gonna go find the poison. No, i'm not gonna go find let's go cook. Let's just go killer
Pretty good sims game. This is like this is the best sims mod I think I've ever played
These company assholes are everywhere. I'm gonna kill this guy right here. I'm gonna knife him. I just need a few seconds
You're enjoying yourself. Yeah
That's not what I wanted to do
Right before the ninja throws the smoke bomb down and disappears about if you don't get it off
You can't do your magic trick
Just die
You're just dead
This is the guy that has to die
It's now or never
This town's going to shit
You
Get him get him get him get him both the two guys two guys two guys two guys two guys two guys two guys
Move I can handle it. Let's go. They don't go in here, right? Oh they do go but he's leaning he's under the desk though
Do they care?
Sure, then shit
Amnesia the next guy that comes in here is gonna get jumped
Keep your eyes
Okay, how many of you guys have played this game with your dog?
Hey auto and then you like hide under covers
And see if you can find you in the room
You hide like in your closet you like yell for your dog and see what he does
He's looking for you like where is he?
And he like sniffs right where you are and you're like
And then he gets really excited. You're like
Okay, can we
We move on
I don't want to sit here all day. I don't want to sit in this all day
See ya
Okay
So now it's safe to jump this guy
I'm in the mood. All right, get on with it
Come on get him
Okay, I think it I think it actually might be safe to go in this room
Well now let's see
That knife back i'll take that. Okay, let me get this guy this guy's dead
Stay here
Let's finish these guys. I'm gonna stab this guy in the back. I'm gonna drag him in here
Is these I don't think these guys come in this room?
They walk around it
Not a problem
All right, let's do it quick now right now go close and personal where's my knife get the knife get the knife
Let's make it quick
No, no, we have to leave come on george what's your name is
Get it
Wait, why are we alive
Make some noise I can't do any actions
Had to drag me into this sure you just stay back here and just get in there and don't move
Fucking kill this guy
Pick his ass up here goes and bring him back here
Okay, just put him down. Nobody cares. Just put him down here. Just like old times. Hey amigo
We're gonna be able to double team these guys right now ready
Zit show time time for the axe
Not a chance
Hurry up. See you later
George get one. Yeah
All right, put him down put him down put him down we've cleared this whole entire area. We're fine
I think I heard a few bones creek you wish amigo. I'm as fit as if I was 20
Only two guys left
Let's get going
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, where's he go?
Come on wait, what do I have? Why am I carrying two people in my hands?
Uh
I tried to put one down
Well, now let's see
Let's light this up
Busy place this town. I just need a few seconds
Can we get this over with?
Time to make some noise cool
Oh
It's like you walked in the bathroom
And right when you open the door, it's like no no, dude. I'm in here. Oh shit. I'm so sorry, dude. Fuck
That's all right. All right. Sorry. I'm sorry
Let's go. Let's go. There she is. What's this?
um
Let's get her. All right, what's I'm just gonna get her
Come on. Let's move it
Not for do on my way. I thought that was shooting march. That's three down
How come you pick a fight with every big shot asshole in town, maybe I can't stand the big shot assholes
Hey remind me why we're doing this. I haven't got all day
It's now or never
and up
On my way. Hey
She's making me cry you hear that hey quick
Found you just
Try to throw her over the balcony, but nope, okay, can't do that
All right. Only one guy left. It's mcbain
Oh, right this guy
All right. I here we go. I know the plan making a move. Let's do this
That's a good I got lots of these
Sure thing meet you there. Nice. All right. We're good almost done
Dang, I thought all this where is he good for the town right there. Okay, let's get going
Let's think about the way to do this. Okay. These guys are gonna see me do that
Hmm
Are they idiots? I think you guys are just idiots. I don't think this matters
Nothing to it. Fuck what's going on in there? This is where they're laying the tracks
That doesn't matter. I'm gonna suffer. He's the foreman and doesn't let anyone on site and then let's keep it quiet when we head in
And it's now or never
Wait, what's that?
What happened to this kind of like legs off? Oh
Well, now let's see
What's the matter with these guys?
I need to move this guy
This place is the foreman and doesn't let anyone on site
This guy let me see
Lots of patrol over here. I gotta get in here. Oh, no, I'm sending one person over here. I'm cooper's the only one moving
It's just gonna be cooper only this guy's gonna hang out up here. All right
Meet you there
Okay, okay. You just stay here cooper. Let's go. I'm ready
Just cooper only
All right, they'll run away in a minute
They're here
These guys are staying here good these guys are hiding good dying. Why's he lying down? No more surprise
They gotta be far away by now cooper is now or never
At that night
Do your thing only you?
I don't need that other guy for any reason right now
Not at all
Your who's looking at you?
What do you got? You got a guy looking over here at you this dude right here?
All right. This guy's a problem
I can
He's got a whistle. I need the whistle. It's like old times a whistler. You're gonna come down here just to hang out in here
Just a whistle
Let's lure someone in I don't I want only one who lured this guy
This way
Dammit show time show time show time show time show time show time problem need sharpening. I'm in the mood for some chopping
Who do we have here?
I just need to use my singing voice
Maybe he goes this way. All right. Hold on. I got an idea
You're gonna sneak over here. You're gonna whistle the skyway
He's gonna whistle this dude over here. He's gonna kill him
Let's go
Where does this guy go? What's that?
What do you mean? What's that eyes open?
Yeah, get away from me
Well now let's see
Everybody's looking at this dude. Everyone's staring at him. He was builder parts
I drink something too, man
I like it
I whistle now someone I should get him not only him
Keep your eyes peeled
Oh my god
He's just seeing me through the wall
All right. I'm not doing this right. I'm doing I i'm doing it right, but i'm not doing this right
How do I do this hurry up?
We both have to sneak over here. I think we both have to go over there. I hate these guys
Keep your eyes peeled
Use builder parts. What does that even mean?
He hates these guys. He hates them
The box the box the box this is guns
I already have full ammo
Eight out of eight time
Gotta get rid of this guy. Okay, what if I throw a coin?
Okay, I have to I just need a few seconds
Need some change
Dick
Wait, okay. Now i'll use my singing voice
Don't get anybody else
Come on
Okay, I don't know what to do. I don't know what to do. I don't know what to do. Okay kill him
Get on with it. Let's make it cool
He's leaving here scratch one i'm just getting started. Oh my god, can they see through can they see him? No, they can't right?
Let's go. They're not gonna be able to see him
Get in this building who's looking at you
Nobody's got eyes on you
I think I could probably I could probably knife him save the game right here. Ready? Watch this one two
Three we're gonna go for it in one
Two no
Go to these guys on patrol one two three kill this guy go in the bush dump in the bush
I have to throw it at him and sprint at him. I'm playing for tonight with like 10k viewers, whatever
He's not yeah, he's not actually
Okay, can I go wait? We might be able to go now? Okay. Yeah
I got you
What am I doing? I got a bullet for you
Oh my god, that's a horrible save
My plan is gonna work. It's gonna work. I'm just gonna use cooper. Watch this ready
sneak
This guy's gonna see me in one second. It's okay kill
You dumb motherfucker. You saw me
It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. Only this guy saw me. Oh no. No, they all did
That guy is gonna die. Okay. I think I can kill him first. Don't ask me why you're doing that save it here
All right, you need to die you do
You both need to die. I gotta throw a knife at you and then kill you
How the fuck okay coin keep your head down I got lots of these out there and throw a coin
then
I didn't even know that existed. But okay, we're okay. These company assholes are everywhere. Who's next?
Something do we have here?
All right, I get it I get it I just have to go over there not a problem
Yeah, oldest trick in the book
Stop a cork in it
Let's finish
Okay, bingo, let's go
Come get in here. We just sneak in who has eyes on this
Nobody does this thing only guy that has any eyes at all and he can't see right here
No one's paying attention. This guy's barely paying attention
Imagine playing desperate three instead of desperate four
Let's go
He was like trying to run away what am I doing I was looking at chat and somebody was talking let's go
What did I think that was gonna work let's go i'll get close and personal
Okay now this is perfect
Don't let luigi die
Keep looking
We gotta find them out
They gotta be around here somewhere
I know they're here
Some
Let's go stop fast forward that's what this is for
Should you imbecile built this?
Do you mean you're
Going what are you doing?
What are you doing?
What's wrong with quick?
Well now let's see. I don't know what that guy was doing, but he's dead. Whatever we go opportunity coming up
opportunity
No, come on. So this is why the train had to stop out of town. You'd think the railroad would be good for the folks here
But then they tore half the place down
Whoever ordered this wants these people gone. You mean vincent devitt railroad boss if you say so
Men like him are the reason everything's shit
Stop doing like frostbite and get down here move with him. You know, I see place this town
Knock it over my way
Knock it down. Why can't I knock this down?
Yeah, I got it I can't kick it down on my way, okay, let's go
You up for the saloon later?
Clearly it was the two guys in the room
Isn't it so clear that it was the guys that were just in the room
Well, that's our cover
You know what? Okay moving George get out of here or just leave
I need to sneak george back out
Can do
All right, he's safe
George's out just tear down my house company orders trek's got to go through you. Okay. So how do I do this?
without
Huge problem
I just jump over down or whatever afterwards
You hear that shifts over mcbain
That's it
All done satisfied now. You'll be able to sleep at night. I'm fine cooper
Let's head back to the saloon. Our drinks are still waiting
Okay, tilt the camera
Hurry up
They all see me
Shifts over mcbain. Hey, that's it all done satisfied now
I'm fine cooper. Let's head back to the saloon. Our drinks are still waiting
here goes
All right. Hi, we're good. I'm going back to the saloon
You got the amigo coming through
Dang, I thought all this would be good for the town
Awesome. I did it. We were so so happy. I did it
I beat the mission. Everyone thought I wasn't gonna be able to do it
Gentlemen, I saved your whiskey for you
I'll make my food here a bit after this. I'm gonna go take care about those men anymore after we save
I want to see
We sure could use a little more quiet around here
Well fellas, I have to step out. Would you mind keeping an eye on the place leave it to us help yourselves?
I'll be back in a few
so
How long you've been here?
A couple of days. Why are you asking? Did you find him?
You know where he is. You have to bring this up now. What the hell hector just saying we just had a good time
So why ruin it, huh? Look i'm not here to play the good samaritan. We both know he's working for david
So just tell me where he is
So there's no first person to go
Last person the last one that was really fun. He's at the mayor's house, although everybody hated it right right up the mountain
No reason to waste any more time then you sure this is a good idea
It's getting late
I put this off long enough
What difference is one more day?
Where I know frank he'll still be there tomorrow
all right
Tomorrow then that's right amigo
now
Tell me what you've been up to. That's a really detailed message. I don't even know what it means. So i'm not going to answer it
Okay
Make the deaths look like accidents
What was the oh the girl?
Don't kill or knock out anyone in the train track area that didn't happen. Don't touch any bushes or haystacks. How would you do that?
Kill three mission targets at the same time
What do you poison her drink?
obviously
You then split them up and knock him down with a show stopper and do the coin in the bowl
See what happened
But we started here. Okay, we'll do times uh times 16
I remember this part being really really hard for no reason. I don't know why
Circled do not do not
Please do not make
Thank you. We came all the way back down here
It's the bull part. Yeah, I didn't do this right
It's gonna be a lot of saves
Okay. Now the real four hour long joke here
Would be if I made sure that i've walked on the map in a way that I've spelled out. Fuck you
Now that's the real four hour joke
I'm not sure i'm willing to do it
And I just play the game and i'm playing terribly
And everyone's like why is he playing like such shit? This is terrible. Like why is he doing it like this?
This is like absolutely brainless
And then at the end you see that I just spelled out. Fuck you
Maybe too long how many saves 32 reloads or two saves where are they right here?
All right, hold on because I went is this when I was the one I went back to get the knife
Right. It's so inefficient
The life of a camper this would just be embarrassing if you showed this back to me
If I was playing like call of duty or something
Did you ever eat it's you need to eat human meat. It's human meat
I'm not gonna eat. I would never eat human meat. What the fuck are you talking about?
Not even a little no never not once ever. Hey, we did it
53 minutes
65 loads
That's a lot. Okay
65 saves. Okay. I seem to like to play as cooper more than any other character, I guess
What civilian died?
One civilian died. Who was it?
I don't know who that is. What if a human was prepared by a master chef?
No, it's not gonna happen
All right. I gotta pee when I come back. We're gonna do my food pyramid
I'm gonna show because everyone was talking shit about what I eat
Do my food pyramid
Be right back. So people ask in the pre-streams
Whatever the thing that happened before I turned on the live stream. We're talking about food
I was trying to talk my case about how I eat peanut butter
That's insane. Apparently eating peanut butter is fucking crazy
Eating peanut butter is like eating humans
To a lot of you
But we'll go over we'll talk about it. So I have over here
Is down you don't hear this fucking music right now
Okay, let's go. So what do you have in front of you?
is
It is a pyramid
now most
Really long long time ago
The pyramid used to be
Like this, you know, this is back in like the fucking 30s. It was like
Like this. Well, why is it the weird color?
This was essentially the food pyramid back in like fucking 1938 or like 1940. Whatever 1950
I'm gonna select it. Okay. You had bread and beer
I think my computer crashed
Fuck
No, wait, hold on. What the fuck is going on my computer?
What stop how do I get rid of this?
Where's the brushes?
Okay, honestly
Where's the brush? How do I get rid of this? Holy shit. What the hell was that?
All right. Anyways, here we go
What do I eat the least of the thing that I eat the least of let's put it up here
This is because you a pyramid supposed to be this is what you eat the least of all right, and this is dead serious
I do not eat anymore really at all. I don't have dairy ever
Literally ever not ass
Dairy like milk. I don't eat drink. I don't eat milk. I don't have it fucks me up. I have
It has now I have intestinal diarrhea problems. So milk does not really do well for me anymore. So up here is milk
This is this is like milk
And can we not make it like 600 font, please?
milk
Okay
Milk that's way too fucking small there milk dairy cheese
I don't eat any of these things really at all anymore. Not good for me. It doesn't do it for me. I can't do it
That's probably what I eat the least. What about pizza? I don't eat pizza anymore. I don't I really just don't I swear to god
I promise. All right. What do I eat the most of what I here's what I eat the most of
I most of my food comes from shit. This is kind of weird like the biggest
It's not bread bread's like here. This is i'm gonna make this would be bread
I don't really eat bread. I try to always stay away from white bread wheat bread. That doesn't sit well with me either
Also all these medical problems. I've been trying to have a better diet, but I never really ate that much bread anyways
It's chocolate milk. No, not milk. I don't drink milk. So this would be bread
and flour
Bread and flour what bread flour pasta?
I don't eat. I don't eat it. And then the next thing
Okay, what I eat the most probably turkey. Yeah, it's definitely tur I eat turkeys number one turkey
Uh, yeah, definitely turkey. I have turkey for four times a week
Four three or four times a week. I will eat turkey but also turkey and chicken I think are on this list here
No, no, it's not even true. That's really not it. That's a lie turkey. I eat the most turkeys all turkey
I'm a huge turkey guy. All right. Well, I can't move this but whatever you get the idea the poultry
Yeah, but I eat turkey way more than chicken just because turkey's a lot leaner doesn't have a lot of fat in it
It's just much better for you. It's I like it. I love it a whisk captain crunch
Okay, i'm gonna show you guys what I might what it used to be. This is what it is now healthy
I'm trying to be a healthy person. I will show you what my food pyramid used to be I promise up here
You've got probably fish salmon tuna. Let's do that
Salmon's pink. So I eat a shitload of salmon. I'd eat a shitload of tuna
I eat a lot of it. I eat more turkey than I eat tuna. You know, i'm gonna write fish
there fish
Turkey number one
My main source of food is turkey and then fish and then right here underneath that you got your vegetables. This is green vegetables kale
Broccoli spinach. I'm a huge baby kale fan. Let's do that. So that's like about right here fill that in
I'm trying to i'm really trying to be accurate with this
Greens there green. Yeah, there's a lot of greens
And then there's a whole lot of shit in here that it kind of doesn't exist
I do really eat just like a bunch of green vegetables fish and turkey
And then also very important right underneath this is nuts and seeds
I want to change this color because I like this. This is more of like a bread and pasta color
Yeah, like that's better
Up next you got probably fruits. I eat a shitload of bananas
I shoot a little blueberries bananas are my favorite thing in the world. You're eating a there's a bird diet
Not it was not a bird diet yet bird diet would be seeds down here. I eat turkey. I eat the birds
I mean it is a bird diet because I eat mostly birds. So is that if that's what you meant then that's fine
Why am I getting to like the scared face?
You guys probably eat like a six piece chicken nugget three times a week
What are you talking about? Because I used to do that. I'm telling you we're gonna do my neck. We're gonna do my
Before pyramid, this is the after pyramid. Okay, so up here you have
Next is this is fruits. No, that's a fucking lie
That is such a lie. I'm just that's that's absolutely pretending. I eat maybe like one or two bananas
A week or something. It's probably up here. That's a lie. I'm gonna i'm just lying to you. Is it gonna be fruits?
All right, this is fruits
And then I gotta think of like servings a day, right?
Because why is that so powerful looking?
Okay. All right. There you go. Then you got greens your fish your turkey your fruit your bread your flour your milk
Your nuts and your seeds
Okay nuts and seeds, but probably go right above fruit. That's the nuts and seeds right there. Okay, here we go
By the way, this is almonds
No, fuck that's a lie. Oh, no, wait a minute is is it I think I think it's above greens
It is it definitely is I eat so much peanut butter all the time. Like it's definitely it's definitely peanut butter up here
It has to be this is fake. This is peanut butter. It's not greens. It's peanut butter. How do I this is
peanut butter
Sunflower seeds nuts and seeds and you know what?
90% of this is peanut butter. I love it. I love it so much. All right, you get the point
Well, it's not all peanut butter it's mostly peanut butter i'm just gonna say nuts and seeds
Okay, then it's vegetables. All right, there we go. Now I got it. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Yeah, we're good. We're good. We're good and it's greens. Wait, do I eat anything else weird? What do I drink for liquids?
It's it's probably coffee
But i'm trying not to drink coffee anymore. So this is the lie. It's crap. No, it's grains
I eat shit little kale and spinach. You guys know that i've talked about that for years
Drink liquid. Where is weed?
Don't I don't what are you talking about? Okay greens
Because I don't wait greens and radishes
Okay
Because I don't eat vegetables. I don't like them. I hate them. I'm just being completely honest
If it's not a green vegetable, I don't want it. I don't like it. I'm sorry. I'm just being honest. I love broccoli
spinach kale
And that's it. I don't like any of that. I don't the carrots are gross. I don't like them. I'm sorry
I don't like them. I like radishes a lot. I like
Regular radishes red radishes daikon radishes. I love radishes but onions no fucking no onions and garlic essentially is a condiment
Okay, i'm gonna put that in condiments. I love radishes. They like the best red radishes are like my favorite
I love radishes. Okay, the greens and radishes coming up next you got condiments. I eat. Okay
This is not even a lie either. I think I mean a lot of my diet is like mayonnaise
I probably eat as much mayonnaise as I do green vegetables. Do I I think I might okay
I'm gonna write mayonnaise slash condiments. No, that's fucked up. I don't eat that much mayonnaise. Do I?
Okay, here's the thing. I have to ask do I eat more mayonnaise than I do fruit? Yes
I am certain of that. I'm telling you right now. That's 100 certain. I absolutely eat more mayonnaise than fruit
I eat a banana like maybe two or three times a week
I put mayonnaise on everything in my tuna my fish I mayonnaise on my turkey sandwiches mayonnaise
In my aiolis mayonnaise all every day mayonnaise plus i'm gonna write mayonnaise plus
It could be like it'd be like I don't but mustard sucks mayonnaise is the best
What about peanut butter that goes over here? That's in the nuts and seeds. It's no no wonder you're so sick
No, I definitely just eat way I eat more. I eat more mayonnaise than fruit. I eat more mayonnaise than dairy
I eat more mayonnaise than flour and bread
I don't eat all these other things
I eat mayonnaise
More than I do bread. I've had mayonnaise more times in the last week than a piece of bread
That's a fact and plus who gives it's just whipped up eggs and fucking oil. It's good for you. Just don't eat it every day
Don't have it in your pyramid. Okay
Listen that leaves us with I don't know. What else is what else do you eat?
What what hey what is here what drinks potatoes
I don't eat I don't eat them. I don't eat potatoes. What about sugar and sweets?
That's changed recently too. I'm gonna make it like cotton candy color
I don't I barely eat any like zero
You want to know where I get my sugar content from at the point at this point right now?
This is gonna be like I know people are gonna go. Haha
Yeah from from like whatever is in the marijuana edible that I have I'm sorry, but I have to tell you the truth
I have to tell you the truth
There okay
It's it's right at the top. It did it it won it won the game
All right. Now what what else do I eat?
Lots of turkey lots of fish and remember when I write turkey here
Let's let's I gotta clarify this because people are gonna think i'm fucking psycho
I will clarify this turkey
slash poultry
Oh, how do you spell poultry?
Because people are gonna be like what the fuck dude eat and you eat you only eat four things. No, no, no, no, this is
You understand it's mostly turkey deal mostly turkey and poultry like chicken turkey
I would just write poultry, but I don't want to because 90% of it's turkey. Do you understand? What about rice?
Oh, uh
No rice is probably okay. I'm gonna split this this is getting split in half. Oh, no, it's gonna split. Yeah, let's go like this
This is probably rice
Uh, what should rice be?
Let's just do like a like a dark
Like here, I don't know it's the color of the background shit, um was a good I need about a cup of milk
God damn it. What the fuck are you doing? Stop? You're ruining everything. Okay. What is pot? What color is pasta?
Like I want to just do this one. Whatever
Okay, that's fine. Who cares
So through what was I doing? Oh, yeah, I was splitting this into thirds because this is rice rice is right here
Well, I eat more rice than mayonnaise
I mean, I don't know
I really don't know
maybe
You put mayo on rice
No, I don't I just know I use it more often
All right rice is right there
and
I definitely eat more
How do you consume that much mayonnaise?
This is my weekly pyramid. This is not my daily pyramid
This is like my like my weekly fuck. That's a lot of mayonnaise. Um
I'm trying to think about okay. When do I eat mayonnaise in the morning?
No, where eggs?
Where eggs?
Eggs are up here
I eat eggs
I don't eat pork at all. I don't eat red meat either
What does that go? All right, it has to go above sugar. No red meat fell off the fucking cliff. Okay red meats
I don't eat it any I don't I don't eat it at all
Like literally i'm gonna throw like fucking throw lines like it fell off the goddamn mountain
Yeah, like sugar threw red meat and it buried it in the ocean
Okay, no, I don't eat nobody better. I don't eat any red meat anymore at all. What about steak?
It's not anymore that was just for a stream gag
Not anymore. Wait, this is my we're gonna do my other pyramid after this. I promise
I will show you what I used to eat like
Up until about like a year ago the mayonnaise. I'm not the the I always have mayonnaise on the brain
The red meat thing was just a gag for the stream. I don't eat red meat
Although I I I shouted that out all the time. I said how much I loved it. I did but not anymore
Okay, let's put eggs in here eggs
That makes sense to me
If I want I really do wonder if this belongs here
I don't know if this belongs. I think it belongs above mayonnaise
I don't eat eggs at every meal. I eat mayonnaise at every meal
besides at breakfast
That's is that true though?
All right. What about um
Mayo is eggs. What about the legs?
Eggs are dairy. Um
Uh, no, they're not
Like they are not dairy eggs are not dairy. I know that
No, what about easy baked oven meals? They are eggs are not dairy. They come from a chicken's ass. What are you talking about?
Is a chicken a cow cows don't lay eggs
They do live birth. Yeah, it's not from a cow. It's not dairy means from a dairy means
Milk-based prove it. Okay, you would like to go for on a tour at a farm. I'm going to ask the farmer
Hey, are eggs dairy? No, they're not
I thought you learned that in the third grade when you went with your class
To the look at how old everything is exhibit on the field trip when you were like eight
And they were all the actors and they all pretended to be from like the pilgrim times. You don't remember that apparently
What goes here though? What else do I eat? I definitely eat eggs more than no. I don't I think I do
I eat rice eggs and uh, what else what about beans? There you go. Bingo. Yep. That's right
Why does this keep happening? I swear to god this thing has a mind of its own
beans
All right. There you go. There is my food pyramid. That is currently how I live my life at the moment
Mayonnaise may be below fruit. I may have overdone it a little onions and garlic are in there too, by the way
This is mayonnaise plus this mayonnaise onions and garlic. What about what about drinks? Okay. I'll make another drink pyramid
Here's here is it. Here it is. Here is my drink pyramid
Is it only two things that I consume as of I literally have been trying to switch to tea
I don't that's it. What about wine? I haven't guys I haven't drank
in a very long time
Wine would be on here, but I haven't I have not drank alcohol in quite a while. It's been months
What about tea? Yeah water and coffee, you know, and I you have to if I drink one coffee I do
I it's a diuretic. I gotta be careful. I'm trying to go to uh, black tea and green tea now
There you go. There there it is. I made it
Now tell me what's wrong with this besides the mayonnaise plus
I don't need any red meat. I don't need any sugar milk and dairy. I don't eat very off
No bread really that no no fruits a little bit
Rice eggs and beans sometimes mayonnaise plus onions and garlic all the time greens radishes all the time nuts and seeds
Almonds peanut butter peanuts walnuts cashews. Eh, not really throw those in the trash
Don't throw those in the trash. If you don't want them donate them. Don't be an idiot fish. We're talking tuna
Salmon, we're talking
Sushi. Yep. I love it turkey poultry chicken. We're talking chicken fingers
We're talking turkey bird patties
Turkey ground turkey on top of look at this check at this
I'll show you some fucking combos you can do with this pyramid. You got your turkey patty
Combo that on top of the rice. That's brown rice
Turkey just fucking sprinkle a little bit of spinach on there. There you go
Done there's a full meal. You're ready. I don't need any of this shit. I'm kidding. That's gross
What's gross about having like a like a little some like a turkey like some like a nice pan
Seared turkey patty on top of a thing of brown rice with some kale on top with some chopped mayonnaise plus on it
We're talking garlic. What's wrong with that? You put your mayo in your drinks. No, I don't put mayo in it
Why would I do that? There's another one for you. You got a nice you toast up some you got some nice toasted almonds
You have a nice nice piece of salmon. Okay, chop up those almonds throw that away. That's not a real recipe
I'm just trying to make up stuff. All right, so you take the radishes. No, how do you do this?
How do I eat fish? All right, take hold on. I need to add something
I have to add something mayonnaise plus includes olive oil. I love olive oil. I eat it every single day mayonnaise plus includes olive oil
Olive oil around here salmon put it in the pan salt pepper. Don't touch don't do anything else to it
Please for the love god a little bit of olive oil. I'll just a little bit of salt pepper
Don't touch it put it skin side down in the pan into the oven 450 degrees
It's 12 minutes take it out. Don't fucking touch it. Let it sit there for a second
It's gonna be the best piece of salmon you've ever had in your whole life greens take some mayonnaise plus which is take a little bit
Of olive oil garlic only don't put an onions in there olive oil and garlic in a pan
Okay, cook it down really toast to roast up that garlic in that pan take your greens
Grab some kale throw the greens in there when it's hot shake it around 10 seconds
Get that thing out of there lay it next to the salmon after it comes out bingo
You've got yourself a salmon and kale garlic dinner burn the garlic. That's not what you've done in burn the garlic
I got it nice and roasted. Yeah sunflower seeds
Take a take take a half take a quarter pound of turkey dump sunflower seeds on it roasted toasted put it in the oven
125 degrees for 10 minutes dump mayonnaise on top of when it comes out eat a bowl of rice while you wait
Didn't know about that little fucking secret snack. Did you once that's done pull it out of the oven?
Uh squeeze lemon juice in your eyes and throw flour in your face and eat this as fast as you can
I've got a perfect pyramid doing clown makeup. Well, this is like a clown pyramid. Look, okay, that's this is it
It really is it I don't eat red meat. I don't eat that much sugar anymore
I don't take in that much milk or dairy
I don't mean I okay
Let's do you want to say what it used to be years ago before like by years ago
I mean like four years ago not that long ago. Let's do what it used to be
This is what it is now ready for this doesn't go back that far
Okay. Well, whatever i'm just gonna erase it
How would you erase yellow that it makes no sense?
Why perfect? He says you already took a screenshot
Just do the triangle tool
If I hold I don't want to I like this. I like the setup already
I thought I was gonna do new whatever how do I do like? Oh, what's the what's the command keyboard to do a new product?
Control what I need to know this for later control n control w file new
I know I know what it is, but I want to get like the real one. It's not control w. It's control n
No, I don't want to save
Okay, this is what it used to be
Uh, I am going to show you
Why you really need to take a look at your diet. It's really important shit. It really is
This is i'm not gonna pretend i'm not gonna lie. I'm not gonna lie to you guys. This is gonna be for real
No fucking around this is you're gonna see right through me, okay
I'm going to go with this is probably like about like maybe like a year or two ago
This is a shitty triangle. What's wrong with it? This is it's fine. What?
That's fine
Okay, so down here. This is what I ate the most of
And it's embarrassing
It is it it actually is it's more than that
This is what my what do you think my number one source of food was for a long time?
Chicken, yep, what but very specific
No, not I know. No, no, no
fried chicken
Whether that's chicken sandwich whether that's chicken strips whether that's just chicken that's been fried it like just fried up chicken
I'm not kidding. Maybe this is not a year ago. Maybe this is probably like a probably like three or four years ago
But it used to be like this
This is not a joke
Spaghetti that's pasta, which is don't worry that you it's going it's coming right next to that
All right. Well fried chicken is gonna be yeah, that makes sense
Gotta be bigger than that too. Let's do like I don't know a hundred
And it's gone. Okay, cool. Wait, what is he? What are you doing? Where's my cursor?
Whatever. That's fine fried chicken
Fuck mom. Don't watch she's gonna be like what I raised him on a mayonnaise diet. Why is he doing this?
Uh, and i'm gonna clarify underneath because people are gonna be like what the fuck is he talking about i'm gonna clarify
this is like
Sandwiches, why just write it. It's so much faster
sandwiches
strips
this is uh
Nuggets, this is uh
Yeah
That's chicken sandwiches chicken strips chicken nuggets
Oh man, I want it right now, but no
Not part of my current pyramid
Can't be included coming up next. We have what do you think?
This is bread and pasta. This is bread pasta flour
Okay
bread pasta flour
Because the flour and the bread on the chicken makes fried chicken
And i've had a lot of it all the time
No, no flour like flour tortillas flour like white flour wheat flour like i'm talking like it's in everything
I used to eat a ton of it and this sucks looking at this. Okay now after this
okay, um
After that, it's probably
Probably like ground beef
like meat
Yeah, it's like specifically ground beef just just like red meat. It's not good
It's too much. Look at it. Look at how just how sad this looks too
What's all the color?
This diet isn't bad though
Okay, I really need you to think if
consuming
fried chicken
As a majority of your diet is a good idea
You have to think about that
If here's the worst part about this if you put a plate of perfect fried chicken in front of me right now
I would break everything and just eat it because I would be like, I don't care. I love this so much
I don't even give a shit. I don't care. Give it to me
Okay above that
We're gonna do okay. So
uh
Probably onions like specifically onions
I would do a vegetable one, but I can't even do a green one
So we're gonna have to do like a puke one because it was onions only. Okay onions
No, I want to pick it up
Whatever
What are steakums?
They fit in here right there
Lavender is not a puke color. Well, I already used the puke color. Didn't I?
Oh, no, I didn't but that looks good onions are like this. Yeah, that's a good onions color
All right, and then after that
Hmm. Yeah, I know it's like a gray but the background is gray. What do you what do you want me to do?
Look, i'm ruining everything
I i've got to use white for milk
Because that's right here. How big is it though?
Yeah, it's pretty big
Weird, you know, what's really funny about this diet
That we'll talk about in a minute and this is just the total just liar hypocrisy dog shit
That a lot of us have a problem with and i'm like i'm guilty of it too. I'll tell you in a second
so up here
Is i'm gonna put it in the same spot
Right there
Here it is
This is sugar sweets and candy
And I remember telling everybody and telling friends and family like oh do you want like to get dessert? No, no
No, of course not. I mean sugar kills you sugar's so like bad for you. You're taking in sugar
No, not me. You see not me not this guy not me and little do I know on my own that I was eating like
Pasta and like red meat and sauce and onions and fried chicken sandwiches three four times a week
No, no, I don't drink soda
Hey, german, would you like a soda?
Okay
Would I like a
Here would you hear what he's saying? This guy's saying this would I like a soda?
Okay, are you disgusting?
You know that like that's like that you that like rots your teeth and stuff and it's like we're it's like smoking a cigarette every
Time you drink a soda. Okay, this guy wants a soda. No, i'll take a lemon with i'll take a water with lemon, please
Fucking idiot. Uh, what's your entree gonna be?
I'll have flour bread pasta and meat fried inside of the thing that has a bunch of fucking oil in it. Okay
Yum, are you disgusting? Yes. Look
That's all you need to see. All right. So this is milk dairy. Actually, you know what eggs probably no, this is dairy
There's your dairy. I got it
Okay. Yeah, I definitely eat more I ate more onions than dairy. Wait, I didn't put sugar up here. Did I write it?
You can't even see that but whatever it doesn't matter sugar you're making us sad
Why is this all your diets?
Is this what you guys used to eat?
Did you eat this now?
You were just like me. You're just like me until I found until I got on team turkey
and team nuts
Join me
Join the turkey eaters the nut eaters the peanut butter eaters
The the the tuna fish eaters the salmon eaters join us. Don't eat this stuff that often
It's not good for you. It's not as bad. All right after dairy we got
I did eat vegetables. I wasn't like a total fucking psycho
I did but I ate a lot of yogurt and I thought that was really healthy of me
I would eat one
Just unsweetened greek yogurt and thought I was a god for the rest of the day turkey shrinks your dick
Well, that would be weird. It does not oh my god
Turkey doesn't shrink your dick
That's absurd. That's insane. And I refuse to even acknowledge that that's a real opinion
So we're gonna move on we prove it. Look it up
Um, I don't want the last thing in my search history to be does turkey shrink your dick
I'm feeling i'll forget about that one and someone will use this computer and be like, okay
Something's going on with this dude. I did eat vegetables. I really did
I still was a big fan of green vegetables, even though this is like the end of the pyramid
No, you know, i'm gonna at least do myself a favor i'm gonna put this this belongs onions get that
I mean who eats just onions. I mean I did eat a lot of them, but still holy shit
It actually shrinks your dick
Shut the fuck up
I refuse i'm not gonna believe it
Turkey does not shrink your dick. I'm not even gonna look it up
The final thing would be like condiments
So we'll do this
Just look at this diet
You want to know the sad part about this diet?
So, okay screenshot screenshot this in a second because this is actually really bad
This is like oil oil and condiments. That's pretty much my diet what it was so essentially this
Leveled up and knocked out all these other ones and got down to here green vegetables like green greens greens greens greens greens
And like condiments this dude's a keto streamer. This dude's got a turkey dick
Okay, this is I don't think I can even say this but when you say that I imagine like
Okay
You know the turkey's neck
That's all i'm gonna that's all i'm not gonna say any more words
I didn't say any more words. I said do you guys know a turkey's neck?
It's like oh, I know what the turkey's neck is. Yes. I'm done talking. I'm not why do I need to continue to speak?
No neck
N e c k do you guys know a turkey's neck?
What about baby food? Yeah, but that was just like a little snack that goes like up here
Gizzard dick
All right. Yeah, that's right. That's me
Why did you say that? What do you mean? Why did I say that? Why did you type that?
Why did a thousand of you why did a thousand of you type that?
Is it bad that I said it or is it bad that over a thousand of you wrote it first?
All right. There you go. There's my food pyramids. I hope you enjoyed it, but here's the sad thing
I'm going to show you something because this is actually bad and it's I was thinking this as I was making this pyramid
Let's look at the actual food pyramid the one that everyone thought was the good one for like five decades
It is not that different to the one I just showed you food pyramid. Here it is. Okay healthy food pyramid
It's it's all bread
Okay, it's a bunch of bread and and vegetables and fruits and then milk. Let's see how different mine
This is so coolly made too. Look at this
Log in to see more. Oh my god
Don't give me that fucking bullshit
I can't even get away from this website
This is linked me to pinterest and i'm trapped on pinterest and begging me to make an account. Okay. Here we go
save image as
Here's the this is the original usda
image
usda
Okay, let's go over this real quick
This is what?
Your this is what you were supposed to eat
So you got bread
Bread cereal rice pasta should be at this was 40 percent of your entire diet
It was that was my diet
I didn't although I did vegetables were not up here and neither with fruits
This came down here
Milk yogurt cheese meat poultry. It was a bunch of bread and corn
This makes me want to puke. Is there no there's no turkey inside here, but I mean they do have peanut butter
I will give them that
Although this belongs here mayo is at the top
Mayo is apparently worse than cookies candy and chips
It's the worst thing in history of eating
You're not supposed to eat it
You're supposed to have mayo less than you have cookies
Now imagine if I ate like 30 cookies a day worse than sugar. That's not even accurate
Oil is good for you. This is old shit
This is back when they this is back when the cavemen were trading teeth with each other. All right
This is not even a real good list. This is the you want bread. You want to eat loads of bread every day
You want all of your food to come from bread?
Oh, yeah, this is pretty good diet 40% of donuts bread pasta and cereal and some tacos
They didn't know shit about mayonnaise. They didn't understand. They didn't know anything
They didn't know that had this fucking polyunsaturated fat in it
Yeah, that's a big word. I know it they didn't know anything about peanut butter
They're having all like the good fats fat was bad back in the day guys back then fat was bad
All fat was bad, but new science
Has put mayonnaise way back way down to here because it's a healthy fat. There's been so much more science on fat
That's why peanut butter everybody loves it. It's so good for you olive oil mayonnaise
Mayonnaise good real mayonnaise is healthy
Marshmallows marshmallow fluff is like zero. It's like 12 calories. They didn't know this shit back in the day
No, it's not it's not hold on is mayonnaise good for you real mayonnaise
Here we go, this is from very well fit
Dot com you think there's a website that doesn't tell you the what is good and fit for your fucking body
You don't think it's that website get out of here depending on the type of diet you follow mayo can be considered good
Or bad for you. Okay. Well, let me I gotta read the whole article
I'm actually gonna read the fucking reddit thread and make my opinion on it the reddit like height like the title
It's mainly hey
Americans seem to have a love-hate relationship with mayonnaise. It is the best-selling condiment in north america
Thank you
And it is a lot popular and it is in a lot of popular american foods from sandwiches. Thank you tuna salad
Love it deviled eggs egg salad. Oh tartar sauce. Love it part of my fish diet
But mayonnaise has seemed to have acquired a bad reputation
Hmm, maybe it's for much fucking internet dickheads that talk about how mayonnaise is fat instead
Oh, and I don't like it because it's like white and gross a high fat food mayonnaise is often thought to be unhealthy
It is mostly fat and as a result, it's calorie dense
In case you know, you gotta get put some weight on if you want
It's easy for calories and fat to quickly add up when you're not paying attention to portion sizes
Maybe you just shouldn't eat the whole can in addition
Some people steer clear of the popular condiment due to concerns that improperly stored mayonnaise would be hotbed for bacteria store it correctly
Thank you very well fit.com the safety of potato salad left outdoors during a fourth of july barbecue or a tuna salad sandwich from a food truck
May be questionable what that real is that actually a real thing?
The truth is with careful selection proper preparation and storage and moderate use
Mayonnaise can be a delicious and healthy addition to a low carb diet. Thank you
Let's see. Okay. Now let's get to let's get to the real meat here
Depending on the type of diet you follow mayo can be considered good or bad for you. Mayonnaise is mostly oil
So it is a high fat and calorie dense condiment with 100 calories per tablespoon
That's a lot
If you're on a low fat or low calorie diet
You want to exercise portion control and measure out the amount of mayo you use for people on a low carb or ketogenic diet mayonnaise
Can be endured more liberally while mayo is made almost entirely of fat. It mostly is unsaturated fat, which is a healthier fat
Okay
This is how this is how I determine how much mayonnaise i'm using so when I make tuna salad
It's one of my favorite things since even since I was a toddler since I was like seven years old
You take a nice good can of tuna fish a good one
Sustainable get a sustainable good sustainable tuna brand open it up. No, what do you mean?
No, put it in a bowl
Mush it up with your fork stir it around and then put a bunch of mayonnaise in there until it becomes a paste
Is that too much? I don't know. Is it too little? I don't know, but it becomes a like tuna paste
It's not thin. It's not like too much mayonnaise. It's just like enough to keep it all together. It was one time
Where okay, this is incoming disgusting statement. Hope you all know what we're talking about
Like how gross this pyramid is that we're looking at? All right. Anyways
One time I was really hungry
And I did a big thing of tuna right just right out of the can put it in there
Okay, i'm ready for the mayonnaise and I just I my my eyes went I saw red
I don't know why and I took a big tablespoon of the mayonnaise and I was like, all right, there's one
I'm gonna do another one. That's not enough
I did another full fucking huge tablespoon of mayonnaise and I started to stir it up and I went boom boom boom boom
Okay, and it's looking a little that looks fine. Not enough and I did a third gigantic disgusting
Slop of mayonnaise into it and there was probably more mayonnaise than tuna in this and I immediately regretted my mistake
I took a bite of it just just to check because I didn't want to waste it or anything and it was
It was I was and I ate it. I ate the whole thing. I ate the whole thing. He still ate it
That's not moderate no, but that that's all right though because listen why the oil matters is important
The good news is that almost all any edible oil can be used to make mayonnaise
But get all that other shit out of here. I want it with good
100 straight from italy olive oil. That's how I make mine
You can make your own mayonnaise cheaper the oil itself is the biggest factor in the healthfulness of the recipe
In the united states most commercial mayonnaise is made with soy oil. Yuck. That's problematic due to its high levels of omega-6
Get that out of here. No, you want the reels the good stuff
The best selling commercial mayonnaise in the u.s
Is helman's brand in the east and best foods in the west
Those companies sell mayo made from soy oil in the u.s
And canola oil in canada canola oil has a lower omega-6 content than soy oil
Nope, no, no, no
If you make the mayonnaise yourself, you can use any kind of oil including olive or avocado oil
Uh-huh. What did I just tell you you get a and plus this is I don't know how when this article is made
A lot of a lot of mayonnaise that you buy at like good stores at the grocery store have
olive oil
If I turn it in says soy oil, I turn it around immediately and I put it back
I put it immediately back on the shelf
But I don't need to do that anymore because I know exactly what I like in my brand
I either I either make it myself as i've never made mayonnaise of my own by myself ever
It's just a way to make the streamer make the audience think that he's way more talented and smarter than he is
When in reality it was all made up from the very beginning
I've never made my own mayonnaise ever. I buy a good brand. Anyways, you get it. It's olive oil olive oil and eggs
Listen, man, you aren't healthy little mayonnaise
Almond is the best
I don't I wish I could agree with you there. I cannot agree with you
I'm gonna have to go with 365 original organic mayonnaise. I'm sorry you lose you lost out on that one
It's smooth. It's fucking creamy. It's perfect. It's thick enough. You can get it right on a sandwich
Do a mayonnaise asmr you make me sick. Don't wait. There's one thing one thing one thing
365 is the good my favorite like store brand. It's not olive oil. It's canola oil. Okay, just so everybody's and freak out that like
He said he doesn't like what it's it's soy oil. I don't want olive oil and canola. That's fine
It's a bougie rich. You're a bougie rich bitch
All right time that guy over 10 seconds at least
Oh
Why because I buy like
365 wait, I did say 365 for something else too
Today
What was it?
Well, what is that? What did I say peanut butter? Oh shit. Oh now you guys know where I like to shop for my like peanut butter
oh
He likes the stuff at whole foods
Look, I okay. Listen, I like I go I just I don't just go to whole foods every fucking day
Okay, I buy my shelf stable stuff from whole foods because I like it better. I think it's a higher quality
It is the peanut butter mayonnaise
Uh, like tuna condiments. It's that's all better from whole foods. I'm sorry. It is. I'm just telling I'm just telling it is
It just is i'm sorry. That's it. That's true. That's real. That's for real
It's not just like a hundred rows of like hinds tomato ketchup
There's like a bunch of different ketchups that buy a bunch of different like local companies or brands or or a healthier it
He's a capitalist
I just don't want I don't want helmans and they have helmans
And okay, they have helmans and grocery store brand
And I don't I don't want to buy grocery store brand
I'll eat I want helmans instead of grocery store brand. Is he still on this? Holy it's been a long time
What about what about the somebody said it that mayonnaise is fucking incredible
What it was? Uh,
Cupid pie. Yep
Cupid mayonnaise is insane. It's it's a japanese mayonnaise. It's the best mayonnaise i've ever had in my life
cupi mayonnaise
I don't know why the pie was in there somebody said pie at the end of it. That's why I said it
But cupi is incredible. It's the best mayo ever. It's a japanese mayo and holy shit
It's the most like a handcrafted delicious thing i've ever had in my life
That all 365 is good too. It's good 365 anything is good
If you open up my fridge or you open up my fucking
Look in my like pantry or whatever you open up like any of my storage for food
You're gonna see the number 365 a thousand times xbox 365 right just write a five in front of it
I'll wait i'll try it out. You're still gross for all your mayo consuming. I don't know and that it's like that's gross
It's gross to like mayonnaise. I know I get it
Just one day when no when none of your friends are looking
If they have mayonnaise at the counter wherever even if you it doesn't matter if you're like mcdonald's
It doesn't matter what the fuck you are. Just take your french fries and just tell it like hey guys
Anyway, you guys have to go to the bathroom. Like I really had to go to the bathroom
Don't you all don't all four of you have to go to the bathroom. Oh, yeah. I got a fish. Yeah
All their chairs will live. Yeah, that's right
They all leave and then you can sit down you can open up the mayonnaise
Pack it dunk your french fry in the mayonnaise enough where you could not like a little tiny little pin
No, go in there and get it and take a bite with french fries
Nobody even has to see you doing it and then either say wow that was horrible
And you've nobody cares and nobody sees it or go. Holy shit. I'm I I just I literally just ate
I just ate the mayonnaise and it was delicious. It's the worst. No, it's i'm telling you where where am I?
Where are my english friends here? Where are my english friends here?
I know there's at least a few of these guys somebody two people at least have to be from britain europe
Somebody from europe, please bail me out here mayonnaise and french fries. Come on bail me out here
Where am I that's a quebec thing? Where are all my where are all my quebec friends?
We're all my canadians
Come on, you do so you guys do like the gravy and cheese thing you do poutine you guys like the mayonnaise on there
Too, don't you? Yeah guys, you got to expand your horizons. Is william is william
Do you say defoe or you say was that a they love mayonnaise in germany cheese and gravy? Yeah, that's awesome
I'm canadian and I like mayo and fries. You're right. Thank you
Belgians love it germans are insane. No, they know what are you talking about? Nobody said that
All right, we're done we did it we that was about a full hour of absolutely nothing
I don't think i've ever burned an hour like that before and I don't think I stopped talking
I feel like those people that go to like the local like town hall meetings
And they get up there with a big presentation like an old science fair thing behind them with the boards
With pictures on it like they're fucking 11. I just did one of those
I just did a science fair presentation to you guys
I just wouldn't stop talking and even when people told me like that's your time and I just keep talking
Until somebody like removes me mayo filibuster pog. Okay
Um, shall we shall we go back to playing the video game? I don't even know what the hell is going on
No, that's it. Is this the stream just end? I mean, it's been four hours
I'm only gonna go for like probably another hour. Is the end of the stream?
Now, what are we doing tomorrow tomorrow might be viewers choice. I think
I have a lot of things you can choose from
We got game cube
Neficent and another I think this side is just gonna be sad, but that took so long. I forget how to play the game
How do you like the new dress sweet pea?
It's a lovely darling
Excellent. I want everyone talking about this day for you
It was an hour of mayo discourse
This is something I really have to take care of
I mean if I get that passionate
About mayonnaise
If I ever became a politician
Holy shit, I think I would be unstoppable
If I just did a one hour full talking like mayonnaise rant
I could just be one of those guys that just I could be one of those old guys. Hey
I just I want to be noticed by the speaker if I could have a speaker's attention here
And did you just talk you could be talking about mayonnaise for like an hour straight with like papers in your hand
You just shuffle them sometimes
And the thing about that mayonnaise is only soybean oil
Should be allowed in that mayonnaise. I'm just saying I think that's the most delicious kind
And my friend my friend from across the aisle my friend. They all call him my friend
You know friends you guys hate each other. Stop saying that you're doing that like to like be in jest and kind of annoying
Well, you see my friend from across the aisle and now he's like i'm not your friend like fuck you now
I'm not going to sign that bill
I just can't understand why my friends from across the aisle over there won't put their name on that bill
It's like now i'm not going to put it on now not putting it on i'm not your friend
You're a fucking asshole not putting it on and everybody does that all of them do it
Well, you know our friends from across, you know, they always like put like quotes in sometimes too. What does it play the fucking game?
I just
Hold on
Wedding gown
Who the fuck are you? Um, isn't you at my wedding? Aren't you like security at the wedding? I'm the bride mother fucker
Holy shit
Wait am I not is this not a not husband and wife? I thought this was like photos for a wedding
Now
I just grabbed this guy and need him. This is something I really have to take here's the photographer
I did not like that photo deleted
And on my registry buy the mixer game's too low
Get what I need and leave before I get dragged to the altar fucking delete delete what I need a key to the upper floor
I think she carries a spare
Is low you're right. There we go
Bet you won't mind if I borrow it believe this game the guards won't bother me so long as I don't
I gotta pay attention. Don't misbehave. That's it. Just walk around. I'm the bride
As soon as I get it i'll sneak in through the library door the upper floor is off limits
I'll have to avoid the guards until I reach the office
Bodwashers mayo turkey dick rant is over. You can skip now i'm here for no stay
Stay and don't leave
I need to get out of here before the groom decides to check in on his bride
Fuck are you?
I can't get over that
Fuck I need the small I need the okay get in through the library door. You'll need a key
I have to give him one thing the dress is beautiful object this union
Am I not allowed to go up here?
No, this is like my house
I doubt I could climb that why would I need to climb the vines in my own estate before he comes back?
Oh shit ruining it
What am I ruining? Let's put him down. What's that?
I got you now
What happened I i'm looking it up once and for all i'm i'm looking it up once and for all
I i'm gonna have to clear my browser history. Does turkey shrink?
your
eating
Chicken may lead to a smaller penis
Okay, you have one article from 2011
That's on a website called nutrition facts. I don't know. Is this a fact? Can you penis shrink? Can you penis shrink?
dirty foods that surprising causes a permanent penis
Shrinking what?
No, no, there's only one article
There's proof permanent. Let me see
eating chicken
Okay, don't click this
Yeah, according to available science three quarters of women find. Yeah. Okay. Sure. Sure. Sure. They find whatever
What does this have to do with the diet?
fletalalates
phytalates p h
t a l a t what it spell is
fletalates
fletalates are chemical compounds used in a wide range of consumer products including pesticides paints and pvc plastic
Okay, the contribution of dietary intake of fletal site
Well, it's late. I was just I tried to say malice site from like warcraft
It was not well defined until a landmark study published last year in the journal of u.s national institute of environmental health sciences
Malice site has known to affect the genital development of lab rats
But human studies have also shown adverse effects on this on on that
The most important finding today to come from the study for future families a multi-center study for prenatal clinics in california minnesota and missouri
It was a simple study
researchers measure the levels of fletalates following flowing through the bodies of pregnant women and then later measure the sizing
characters of their
What did you do of their?
They measured the size and characteristics of their you did why?
You did what?
Why?
What the fuck you after they were born? This is that's unbelievable. Why would you do that?
Why would you do that?
That's I can't all right. I'm gonna that's unbelievable
So the kids were born and then okay. Goodbye
He's changed his social exposure to some of the same. There's okay
What what?
So, okay
They did a study not on adults. I don't
Pregnant women should avoid poultry to protect their son's normal development. Okay
Well, I know for a fact
that my mother
Ate chicken all the goddamn time all the fucking time all the time every almost every day
I turned out just fine. Thank you. It turned out just fine. I'm fine. Nothing wrong with me
Can I even play this game right now?
It's like one fucked up stupid ass study
guard dog
This dog hates me
The feeling's mutual it's because all the mayo cancelled it out
Oh, it's gonna be wonderful. He's been waiting so long for her to grow up. I wish I was married to him
That deal with a turtle dick made him he's a turkey dick. Well, oh this one's off the rails. It's gone
Are you jealous or envious?
Envious
Okay, we're getting the intel I need a key fuck. I should have listened
Hey
This person's a key
Quick before he comes back
Climbing a ladder in a dress. I double dare you kate. Here comes the runaway bride
All right, save here
Crouch, she's gone
Do I get married up there? Why do I have to sneak? I object this union
Words fail me I am the bride
In certain missions kate can pickpocket enemies
Don't get spotted
Okay, let's get it. What do I do about this guy?
Here comes the run. I'm gonna knock this guy out. He's can I distract him a little touching up? Yes
Now aren't you? I'm crying
what
What's that don't mind me am I allowed to be here? Oh i'm allowed i'm actually allowed to be here
The guy on the balcony seems a little too fixated on her. Let's blind him a little with this perfume
I'm gonna spray him on the eyes in this wedding for years never could keep his eyes off of me
All right, i'm gonna spray him in the eyes. We have to be fast
Not like this. No
Bless your heart
I got the key
Now up the stairs and through the door to the library
What are you guys doing? Omega loli's blind. I just did it
I just did it
Not you the dude. Oh, okay
Let's go up here drop somewhere. There's the door slip inside when no one's watching strap in
Oh shit, he has turkey in his eyes. I can't wait to eat some turkey quick before he comes back
There's the door
slip inside when no one's turkey
Uh, what does this want me to do?
Knock out
Kate only knocks out guards and has no lethal takedown doesn't carry in a rope to tie them up. So be careful. They'll wake up again
Time to make an impression
Open come on. He probably uh
All right. No, stop. Stop. Stop. Stop. Stop
Stop stop
I got good aim
I think you should lay down quick. Sorry in advance darling
That should knock him out good. Okay. Hurry up get the brighter space
Check this out ready
Just the door. Oh, I gotta move it. Go for it. Here comes the runaway. Hey get in get in get in
Almost there and now to find these papers
Okay, what the fuck just happened?
How do I get in here?
Over here
Killing us wait, um, did they shot me object this union? Oh fucking god. Damn it
Almost there and now to find these papers. They are quick before he comes back
He must be here somewhere
Oh shit turkey
I left turkey
Yeah, you know i've been watching just in bed. I've been watching old commercials from like the 50s
Just hours of them just bored lying there in bed
Something that I I wish I could have and try and drink
Is coffee from 1950 it always looked so good
On these commercials. I don't know why it was always just a tiny little cup of just black coffee
I just want like 1940s coffee
Frank I see you found my office
You should keep your friends waiting hanging. Yeah. Well, sorry about that
The wedding you understand what are you watching that has commercials from the 50s?
I'm watching
1950s commercial compilations
That's the content
of course
Just give me a moment
Did I hear correctly that there was trouble in flagstone yesterday?
The usual doing drugs I can imagine. Mr. DeVitt isn't too happy about that. That's like a big snort
DeVitt isn't here. I wonder if he'd want you to leave things unfinished here
Or is there something more important in New Orleans?
Maybe you should just get back to your wedding eggins
Maybe you're right. They're under commercial compilations are underrated. Yeah. Well, she has every reason to be
pardon
Long time ago. He's just eat like king-size Reese's until I couldn't anymore while watching like old 90s commercials
Like 30 to 40 minutes each. I probably had like seven king-size Reese's bar to find out until after the wedding, right?
There's a lot not recently this is like at least five years ago
Wait a second, I need a drink
Hmm, can I just stay in here? Let me ride the horse, please the only thing I want
This ain't a discussion
So what's your plan?
Get in find frank do what I came for
This is not the same mission
March to the front gate. Yeah, there's a path down those cliffs
Bernie is a bernie voice. Just follow that and climb up those vines from there. I'll wing it. That's no plan
Amigo, I pulled all flimsier once I think something's up
I'll come and get you. No, you stay put and not really
I kind of maybe you say
Not even else not even close
Okay, where I need to go I need to go to enter the main lodge
Okay
I just want to try I thought maybe I could like speedrun just run through it somehow
Here we go. All right time to do the mission. Hello, sir. Everyone sounds tired
Um, no, i'm all right
This is what I have turkey on the brain, which means that i've seen my whole life. We're looking at you
Okay
I'm fine
I have full ammo
Look that way, please look
Heads or tails, let's get going
Who the fuck is
Turkey releases chemicals that make you tired. That's a myth. It's not real you're talking about tryptophan. That's not real
Tryptophan doesn't do anything
You think I ever have one of those okay, let's go hold this trick in the book
No
Why not?
Can't be that expensive how much is like, uh, okay, how much is a statue made out of a metal like that
It's now or never not gold not bronze. I'm sorry. What's like a cheap metal?
Okay, what if I had a statue of me made out of stainless steel? Why did this guy see me?
Make it out of stainless steel. We're just like
steel
500k I just need a few seconds. You hear that shall we stainless steel is not cheap
Yeah, but it's cheaper than bronze, isn't it?
I got lots of these
Oldest trick in the book throw it need some change
Not a problem
No, okay aluminum. Yeah. Okay. What if I had a statue made out of aluminum?
How much would it realistically cost?
what size
Uh like eight feet tall
If you are aluminum is expensive
All right, but what if we're talking about like aluminum can
a statue made out of the
Not crushed before it gets crushed
And I know dude somebody's gonna walk up to that statue made out of aluminum can
And it's just gonna go up to my face. They're not gonna damage anything else
They're gonna press and squish the fist into my face. So I have a permanent like deformed crushed in face
That's the only damage they're gonna do to it. So I look horrible
I'm gonna have to run one two three go. Okay
That doesn't ten thousand dollars not counting the payment for the artist
So that's I cannot hide there. Don't move. Yeah, that's a bush
We will protect it
It's minimum 15k
That you will be gone
in an hour
That would be on local news
Oh local funny man thought it would be interesting to make a fifteen thousand dollar statue of himself and
Put on his front lawn
By the time the reporter was done talking about it. It would be gone or destroyed
You hear that
down local funny man
Eight people have beat up a statue to pieces
Is
I I would never want a statue of myself
To me, I don't I don't think I would want that to happen to me
Unless I could if it could be a statue of me
On the toilet with a newspaper in my hand just looking at the newspaper
I don't want to be like pointing in the distance with a book in my other hand and like a big overcoat
No, I don't I don't want that oldest trick in the book. Let's make it quick
New toilet statue
And I have I am straining
My face is like just straining. All right. Am I allowed in here yet?
Have it be you on the toilet reading with the computer
No, can I hide anywhere else?
uh
There okay. I'm gonna go up here
I'm gonna
Oh, it's gonna be wonderful. Have it be a diablo toilet statue so long for her to grow up
I wish I was married to him
That deal with the davit company made him rich
Well, we can't all be as lucky as miss o'hara
Are you jealous off these chairs by the way? I'm convinced that there's never one of these is ever clean
I think they've been using the same ones for like a hundred years
These come brand new with a bunch of scuff barks and dirt and like footprints all over it. I hate these things
Shall we get in? All right, I gotta get in here
Wait, I have to get in enter the main lodge. Yeah. All right, I gotta get up there
So can I climb that I have to go through?
This all right, they're distracted a little bit
Does this person care that i'm here?
Or is it just the guards?
Come on
I didn't see that guy give us a joke. You got it
Get it get it get it run run run run duck this game is sick
All right, you can't rush me. Don't rush me. Do not rush me
I can go I can crouch up until
These guys are just talking to each other
I can go up to here and crouch
I can cross the whole thing
Point these guys like frank to just right off like that. What's that noise?
Sure, and we're gonna kill this dude quickly quietly
And dump him
Just a scratch
You aren't hiding man, i'm trying to dump him please stop playing and talk about mayo again, let's get going
Please we want more mayo, please just right off. Oh, you like mayo now, huh?
What are you doing why would you i'm trying to throw him fucking just run I just that's not like frank to just
Finally we're good
Emotion andy is it that's a mayonnaise reference, I think here goes you know decency you're saving
A bit excuse for a man
Sweet pea, please. I only want what's best for you
Okay
It's now it's pretty cozy in here
Looks like the mayor's doing all right for himself. Something's going on in that room
Let's have a look
Hurry up. Oh, no, don't come watch tv. Don't come watch tv. Don't come watch it
Please okay, this is not the time nor place
Eyes on the
Bloody
Sweet pea, please. I only want what's best for you tv in the 80s. No, I mean whatever that's where tv would go
Fireplace was the tv of the 1700s
Bring you more than your uncle could ever give you what?
Fuck
A guy speaking the corner garage with a knife because viewers dropping talk about turkey mayo. No, I don't whatever
I'm one of I want to at least beat this level
Sweet pea, please. I only want what's best for you. Let's get going
How far does he walk down?
I'm offering you more than your uncle could ever give out to lose a few teeth pick him up. Got it
Do I go kill this dude? Am I gonna go kill her dad?
Of course, you'll marry me you just need to calm down a bit
I did it
It's done
Nothing. I can do now
Call him back
Kate, please
We have a wedding ahead of us
You really still think I was going to marry you
I can't get over it. It was so stupid. No idea how much i've invested in this you will
Marry me today
You're going to play the good little wife
I bet you'll forget all about your old life after you pop out a few children
Tempting but I must decline. You had that the whole time. What are you doing? Kate? Just trying to be convincing. Oh
Yeah
Well, i'm gonna show you your place in this world you stupid
Oh, no, he's dead
I think I know my place
I reckon he deserved that who the hell are you? I could ask you the same
I don't have time step aside
Really?
Are you sure you want to go this way?
So now what do we is this a whip to get out escape open fire take this
New weapon unlocked case closed
Okay, what now what balcony door works for me? Why would you leave that there?
There
Oh is a shotgun go go get the shotgun. What are you doing? Don't he doesn't need that money anymore money, huh?
New weapon unlocked give the new weapon locked the door. Yes
new weapon locked right
Close call they're gonna search everywhere now. I have to warn my uncle
Let's get out of here. Well, tell me something first
You ever heard of a guy called frank? Yeah
Let's discuss it on the way if you don't mind. No chance we'll get through there
Not without some serious firepower
You know how to pull the trigger of a gatling gun. I sure do but um, why does it have a pink ribbon?
It's a wedding present
Don't ask who omega low. What are you talking about?
I don't think i'll get very far in this bloody dress. Let's visit that maid up on the stage
I can steal her clothes and use them to blend in sure
Still the maids well, I don't see a gal like you blending in anywhere miss
Ohera, why don't we just change clothes?
I'll take that as a compliment. Mr
Cooper, you know like very clearly i'm not the one they're looking for but i'm in the i'm in the gown
And I'd be like, i'm they'll grab me be like I swear to god. I swear to god about this on ebay
I got this on ebay. It's an ebay dress
And she's just in my clothes doing whatever she needs to do. I'm just like the guy in the wedding gown
It's not like there she is it's like wait, there's a there's a guy in a wedding dress over there. What let's talk to him
If there's only one wedding dress, but I would confuse the fuck out of everybody because they're looking for her
Just wow, i'm gonna switch clothes
We're at the right wedding. Where are we? Where are we? I suggest we get moving. Can I take the shotgun?
That's a problem. Forget it. What can I do you for? I can't put them in there. Where to?
Oh, right. He doesn't who cares. Let's just leave
Okay, what's that?
Stop crouch how far can you throw? Let's give him some trouble just a harmless sneeze
Damn, all right. We're gonna go this way
I'm gonna take care of this I guess in this bush
lots of these
Let's make it quick take you for a man who throws away money. It's just pennies every penny counts. Mr
Cooper not if they're fake just clearly watch watch me do that
All right, we're good somehow need to stop him
Eyes, oh, how am I gonna stop him for potions trick in the book? Okay. See how far can I go?
I've had enough of weddings
What's that tear gas perfume from my late suitor this is not a hider he said his guess love is blinding after all
Oh shame. They crouch. Mr. Cooper
Let's leave quietly
Why does this keep happening
He's choking on one of the peanuts oh shit, I told you we should have got the peanuts
We should have got the bigger ones in the shells
Let's pick him in the groin
Did I grab cooper and just boot him?
Sure
Love is blinding after all oh shame on you. Mr. Cooper keep it cool
Fucking god damn it. All right
Was that made
Don't let them get away
I have to beat this. I have to beat this
I need a big picture. There's tons of places to hide
What can I do? This guy comes down eyes on this guy. All right
Do it up here in the front
We could I wonder we're going we're going left and wrap left
We need to go around here
Here
Don't run do not run
I guess love is blinding after all stay here. Don't go anywhere
Okay. Now you can go
Get in here
Let's destroy this guy
Wait, but he's gonna do a full rotation. He's gonna go back
This guy comes over here
Slit you know what I mean done easy
Wait, was that that these violent delights have violent ends that was supposed to be
Who the fuck was that? I don't know. All right, i'm almost done
We go around here. Where's the the maid? They're made up here
Wrap wrap wrap wrapper wrap
Okay, what would you like me to do about it?
What would you like me to do about that? I don't know what you'd like me to do
About to lose his teeth. He said it somebody said please snap
What the hell?
Where's she what is okay?
He's gonna turn around i'm gonna throw the smoke at him
Okay
Hit the lady kill her and then take off
How long is this last i'll do it right now
But okay five shall we never stop gaming
I'm not gonna
All right. Can I kill her without anybody seeing?
Oh goes on don't worry. It's harmless. Here we go. This is gonna try we try to work this out
freeze frame
Then i'm gonna stand up with you
Let's make it quick stab
stab
Execute
We have to do a double
Can I
Can we just kill her from here?
What's the real game plan here?
This guy comes up
Maybe I had to take care of this guy first
Yeah, I gotta kill this guy hooper get back there and go kill this guy
Milk miracle whip is cool with but only better milk miracle is disgusting
Shot him down. Holy shit if you think miracle whip is better than mayonnaise
That's unbelievable thing to think
Miracle whip is just somebody that made fake mayonnaise. It's like it's like they just made a fake mayonnaise
Why don't you just get the real one?
Why do you have to get the fake one?
What's that noise? What can I do you for here? We go ready show time show time show time shift
Does he know
Is it miracle whip whipped cream and not made up? They I don't know. That's not gross. It tastes like vinegar
I think we have to incapacitate, but they'll hear it. Okay. Here's the plan. The plan is you gotta throw one
Throw it out there
And then show time
Pick stab
Teamwork beautiful
Okay, you have to tie him up
Already before she turns around she's gonna turn around
Oh stand up and drag him
Why are you riding him like a surfboard pick him up
Guy comes near me
No, okay, I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it
What can I do you for have to be fast? Hey cue stab kick
Execute
Did you not throw it?
Okay
Pick him up. I'm not sure which would hurt more hurry
hurry
Crouch, it's just her now. Let's go get it
Let's make it quick
Quick, okay. Let's get going. Let's try this on for sad. Okay, good
Not gonna have no can do
Kate's disguises once Kate has picked up a disguise. She can put it on by pressing t
While disguised she can traverse enemy territory almost undetected dogs and long coats will see through the disguise
Let's freeze them
t now
What do you think if you look like a wolf and maid's clothing, I think it's enough to fool them only way to find out
All right. Now we have to this guards know you're here escape from the compound
Suggest we get moving
But she's allowed here, but i'm not allowed here
Let's leave quietly enough dilly dallying e
alert
Alert with an enemy to keep their eyes on you
That didn't work
It was supposed to work
I still work
Yeah, they're not they're not cupping both of their hands over their eyes like they're looking into the distance
And leaning forward and staring into her face
god
Where are we? All right, let's go
We have to go around here
Down here. Here we go. I suggest we get moving
so
Gasps in his face. Keep your head down and then stand up and go talk to him
I say good riddance. I'll ask again
In any of you
Oh, come on
Oh fuck
Wait, I thought this is supposed to be
What can I do you for sorry in advance darling
Wrong with you i'm trying to I don't know
So how am I I guess I could distract him and climb
Let's leave this mess of a party
We'll just distract this guy that doesn't work on him though. He's a he's a long coat, right?
No, that does work on him or here we go ready
I thought I could sneak around there was a edges were there exit stage left
You saw the the edge. Yeah, I could I could have he just bumped into him
All right, let's go
We're good right now while he's looking the other way time for my entrance
Quick quick dump them dump them
Wait aren't they gonna this is nothing darling. How am I gonna distract these people? I'm all ears just a harmless sneeze
Get out of here
Instead I was gonna be starting and stopping all the time. Okay, it's now or never
Okay, I got you hurry up I'm talking to you all right fine come over here shut that mouth
The mayor was killed aren't you handsome? Yeah, baby. I got what you need. It's not got lots of these
Heads or tails, what the fuck don't you think coins on the ground are interesting see anything you'd like
I'll work my charms wait
You can do to anybody
What he's pissed
Okay, then
I'm just i'm gonna kill him. I'm just gonna i'm just gonna shoot him. Hurry up. Just need a few seconds. You're giving me
No problem
Okay, fine good yes
You know, whatever you say gorgeous put the gun down, okay now distract
Oh my god, there's a guy with a gun
Let's get going skip nice. Okay. Now you come over here
This again
Yeah
I already knew that
And the vic company's gonna attack my uncle's ranch tonight. I gotta get word to him
I can distract you
Work my charm let me ask you something. I'm gonna double I can double you guys up. No, I can't
Oldest trick in the book shit. Okay, i'm gonna have to jump down though like this
Come on
I never wait for the distraction way out of here
So what was that back there about warning your uncle and the vic company's gonna attack my uncle's ranch tonight
I gotta get word to him. I gotta get we don't have to go from here. Have a nice day
Oh fair
Okay, you're a beauty
Not a problem. What I why are you looking over here?
You don't even know i'm here
Damn it like that to a lady eyes open hold this trick in the book. Okay, save it. This is gonna kill her
Yes
Wait, two of them come by here
I'm here if you need me
All right two guys come over there what are you doing man? I thought he was in the bush son of a gun
Halfway out of here
So what was that back there about warning your uncle and the vic company's gonna attack my uncle's ranch tonight
I gotta get word to him run him this way later. Maybe
There we are
We were all working outside when it happened we go
Okay, just need a few seconds
This is it opportunity now now now now now knock it over quick quick quick kill kill kill kill kill kill kill
That scream that
It's a i've heard it a million times before where who's calling me now
Warcraft 3. Yep. Perfect. Thank you. Holy shit. That was gonna drive me nuts all day
Oldest trick in the book
Okay, did I save it? Let's go
I'm listening
Did I hang up on mom? No, it's not mom whatever you need easy
easy
Uh-huh. I hope I don't need that knife anymore
Someone's about to lose a few teeth. Um
Run just run out run run out of the level son of a bitch
I always made it
Yeah, what's funny your peepee or poo poo definitely peepee. I think let's get on that second. You're a capable hand. Mr. Cooper
My uncle could use your help at the ranch. Sorry to any of the mayo screamers
Dogs can sniff out characters when they're hiding
Well good to know careful as a guard dog up there staying in here. All right, I gotta get him in here
She hates me
Hold on this guy knows where I am
Wow
I got lots of these
All right, I just ain't ready yet throw the fucking coin mate
Let's get going
Oldest trick in the book you didn't see shit. What's he doing there?
Give me my knife. Give me my knife. Give me give me give me give me give me
I'm up
Are you still the same stage?
uh
Well, you may not have you met when you left we kind of went on a food pyramid rant
And it wasn't a regular one that lasts usually like 10 50. This was about an hour and 20 minutes
It was a very long one
Okay
Almost there
got a dog
Gotta go out this door and stand right there
Did it go this way? It's now or never can you get sniffed in the bush of us has to take a shit?
Oh, I'm thinking why am I sneaking around?
Let's give this wedding present a spin y'all ready
I can shoot this thing
Our players my wedding present mind if I get to know that catling be my guest. Mr. Cooper
Tell this guy right because he's gonna need some change
I almost got hit in the head
Is
Gonna see through I need to get on that gatling gun
Put him down ever gets old I gotta move fast I gotta move fast shall we
Get on the gun get on the machine gun quick
Stop i'm almost done. I have to beat this
Goes on
I'm not very good at these games. I don't i'm not very good at these. I this is fun
I like this, but i'm not very good. This isn't gonna be i'm not gonna be able to do it
Holy shit, I did it
I'm gonna distract this one to turn him this way
Aren't you handsome who's looking at him I can help you you but what's the view?
Are you the one that's what what what does this guy do? He turns around?
There's more where that came from you got a lovely voice
Keep it cool. What can I do? Let's do this fucking dog away from me
This dog away from me get the get away get away get away
I suggest we get moving
I've had enough and now what?
Now we gotta go like this
I just distract this guy now
So this dude get on the gatling gun it's now or never this is nothing darling
I'm here all day, honey. What's that? Oh found you. Do you fire?
I got you
How do you fire the gun
Oldest trick in the book see anything you'd like
Let's get going no problem
All the way down there really, you know what okay
Let's get going
Listen
Did you make it you can't be in combat damn it
All right. Hurry up. That's speed speed speed speed. Go go go go go go
Dogs gonna see through
Oh, I can't do these
Charmer
Fuck you. Oh, I can't even handle it. I'm gonna have to quit. I can't do it
Run quick, i'll play the charmer. I was wondering keep your head. Oh, you know, okay. What happens?
Holy shit, I didn't even
Quite the exciting let's dazzle him. I was wondering eyes open. How can I help you in the book?
Hurry up. I still can't believe you would gift her a gatling gun of all things. What?
I don't know what to do. I don't know. I don't know. I don't get it
I think I think okay just I got a better idea
I got good aim sweet dreams
Keep your head down
Around here
Wait, did I kill her?
Well, holy shit. Okay, that's I get it. I get it. I said she can just do it. All right, um
Run, hey, meet me meet me over there. Meet me over there. Mr. Cooper. If you help us defend the ranch
I'll tell you where frank went
You drive a hard bargain miss o'hara. I simply know
Yes
Sorry, I'm awake. I'm awake. So you must be mr. Cooper's friend
Ah, yeah, and you are kato hara pleasure to meet you. Yeah, was it hard? No, it wasn't
I don't know why I just thought
It says she didn't have any weapons and she didn't have any guns or anything
So I was like, oh she doesn't have weapons. Listen, I got someone that could help us. She can't use weapons
I was like, okay what thing is?
He doesn't work for free i'm sure higgins has no objection to this investment
All right, hector you go with miss o'hara
I think we have until sundown before the devit men come for the ranch
Yeah, i'm gonna call it here, by the way
I'll see you guys tomorrow. Mr. Cooper. I'm actually really hungry to thank me
We have a deal don't we this frank must be a hell of a guy if you risk your life like this to find him
Wouldn't be the first time
Well, you better hurry. We'll be ready for you at the ranch
We're gonna go. I want to see the end of this stuff here, though
I'll see you tomorrow
Why are we defending a ranch now?
Well, it's a long story. We're not gonna play desperados tomorrow. I'll explain on the way
Sure, i'm gonna give you guys a list of things to play
Tomorrow in pre-stream chat if you're there
Only about 30 to 40 minutes before stream I pop in
Sometimes a little more than that
Don't use disguise. How would you even do that?
Take a photo of the dead groom
Where did I get a camera?
Oh, you can bring him all the way out there
And lay him on the ground and take a picture
But you have to take him all the way to the beginning of the level
Uh, yeah, there'll be a poll tomorrow because I need to figure out what it's gonna be. It'll be probably three or four different games
I did that
Don't use the gatling gun kill everyone except for civilians. I didn't do that
Here we go
Brassatui?
Making a pretty good statue though
This is a big muscly guy
Come on, go down here and complete it. No, Jeremy. You messed it up. You idiot. You had an opportunity
Uh, no, not vr
Not vr
Sorry
What should I play though? It's gonna be either game cube
It might even be 3do
I might finally bust that thing out and actually play the damn thing
I have like 10 games for it, too
I only bought the 3do for one reason because I wanted to play this game. I'll tell you exactly what it is
Give you the exact name
It's called twisted
the game show
It's an fmv game show game
And it looks just it looks you know how they all look could be terrible. That's the only reason why I bought it
Not symmetrical. I'm annoyed
I always killed one person accidentally somehow zero bodies discovered though
How did cape kill oh right right because she went absolutely nuts
God I was gonna say that doesn't make any sense. She can't kill people a maid was a civilian. Oh, that's right. Yeah
This game is pretty good
How many levels are in the game?
Was it like three chapters four chapters?
One two, three, four five six twelve what 18 levels?
20 30
Oh, I can see why people like it
If you if you're good at video games and you like planning stuff, you can do a lot of that stuff very very quickly
Simultaneously, but yeah, we're not gonna play tomorrow. We're gonna do either radio game cube
Or something else i'll give you pull tomorrow
Thanks for watching
Uh, sorry, we kind of the whole stream derailed for a full hour
We did the podcast episode where I talk about mayonnaise
Sorry about that
Uh, but I have a lot of fun
There was also fifty dollars. There was five thousand bits from
zombie eater
Thank you zombie eater
Say next time you go to the doctor regarding the mystery illness show them the food pyramid to see how wrong you are
It's not a bad diet
The mayonnaise I don't eat that much mayonnaise. It's like two rungs down
I'm a liar. I'm kidding. It's a i'm a i'm a funny guy
Right. I don't eat that much mayonnaise. What is mayonnaise is gross
You need vegetables dude vegetables. It's like numbers. It's like the third most thing I eat
I eat a shitload of greens. I eat a shitload of radishes
broccoli spinach kale
radishes daikon radish
That's like a almost a third of everything I eat
And then a shitload of beans a bunch of a bunch of uh
nuts seeds
He's a rodent
He eats beans. No, don't stop eating so much bread
So you guys are talking like that because you have too much you have too much bread in your mind slow down on the bread
Take it from me
Anyways, thank you zombie eater for the fifty dollars and thank you all for watching
I will see you
Tomorrow and I will see you
For the mystery game see if this works
Hey, look at that
Here are tonight subs and resubs. Thank you guys
My computer sucks. So it's at 60 fps
But my computer sucks
More than one person. Yep
Tomorrow we'll start at probably 11 o'clock pacific tomorrow 11 a.m pacific
But we'll see tomorrow. Thanks for joining me. Thanks for sticking around. I know
Maybe some of you guys more than your favorite game in the world, but I still had a lot of fun
I think it's still it's a good game
Maybe you liked it. Maybe you might buy it. Maybe you like
No, I had fun. Take it easy turkey dick. Hey, thanks a lot
Uh, all three balls. I don't know. What's your name?
When it's green screen, that's the green screen movie night encore dlc is this weekend
Are you ready?
Gonna be probably part one of two because there's a ton of videos depends. Maybe we might do it all in one night
I don't know. I'll find out it's a lot of them. This is alphabetical order, too
Genuinely cannot wait. Neither can I
There's so much more material
To just put in random places now
And i've been gone for months
There's been a lot of time for people to refine
A lot of their submissions
I'm looking forward to it, but that's it. I'll see you guys tomorrow. Thanks for watching
11 a.m pacific
Goodbye and good night