Hey, phone call is good. I just, I had to take care of something. Something I didn't know that
I had to take care of, but I did have to take care of it, so I took care of it.
Welcome to Dreamcast Day 2 of the Dreamcast Stream Central.
Taking care of it. Give me one second, I gotta uh, I gotta tweet that. I'll see you guys in a
moment. All right, good afternoon. Good evening. All those things. I remember this screen. I
don't know why we're getting this screen again, but it's a good place for us to test the audio,
because I know a lot of people said last last or day night that it was out of sync.
So let's go ahead and see if we can get it in sync. Are you ready?
Here we go. You should be hearing my voice and the sound at the same time.
And here we one two three four one two three four five one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten eleven twelve one. Voice is behind. Okay. So the voice is behind. Really? What if
I give you one of these? One two three four eight eight eight eight eight eight eight eight.
There. Voice is still behind. The voice is too early now. No, no way. Hold on.
Do a little thing like this. One two three four one two three four five six seven eight nine
ten eleven twelve. All right. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good.
The game is a bit behind. Well, I can fix that too. Check this out. I have a ton of magic
tricks here. You ready? How about this one? One two three four five. Welcome to the
troubleshooting stream. Five six eight nine ten eleven twelve one two three. Oh the first
game by the way is the worst one. I need to get it out of the way as fast as I can. I saw
it on the table and I said I don't want to play this. I don't know why did I buy this?
It's not the evolution game. It's the fucking worst game ever. It was just a Dreamcast
exclusive. That's the only reason why I bought it. Never mind. I take back everything I just
said. Uh his mouth is even doing. You know I'm glad we got to see at least this part here.
This is Toy Commander. Who gave that little kid explosives? That's it's supposed to be a
it's him imagining things. Run around in his house. All right so I don't know.
No. Evil? The evil crew? Andy the time has come we toys are sick and tired of how you are.
How you use us then toss us aside. So prepare for the mutiny as I Huggy Bear claim the title
of Toy Commander. So this is Toy Story 5. This is the toys rise up and like strangle
old Andy. Well he's in his sleep or something. Yeah it's the trip to the nursing home to find
Andy. W6Y. I don't I don't know what the fuck I'm doing. It's three letters.
I don't care. Well that's boy that's Andy. A lot of uh don't give a shit about copyright
in some of these Dreamcast games. Not even copyright but like referencing
other like western media for some reason right? Copyright? No my point is is like
we had the whole family guy cast in the last game for some reason and now it's like Andy
toy game Andy. Okay so let's do 16 by 9. I'm not sure this is going to do anything. Is
this game older than Toy Story? No no way. Dude you don't have a game about toys. This
looks awful now. It just looks like I stretched it up or whatever. Who cares? Kitchen and dining
room. The rest of the house is coming soon. All we have is the dining room in our shelf.
Open the draw house. Okay kitchen and dining room. Training. Boiling rage. I am cyclone
and I am the boss of the kitchen. Each room in this house has its own boss. If you can
beat our records in at least four missions you'll be tested against us. If you defeat us
we'll become your allies. Then you can pilot us in the final duel against the Toy Commander.
Land the plane on the runway then use the helicopter to drop two sugar lumps into the
cup of hot cocoa. Finally use the pickup truck to find the chocolate bar. I'm liking the
Pee Wee Herman quests. Holy shit, Jerma, this game is my whole childhood. I never could
remember its name. Well it is Toy Commander. I'm glad you can see it and figure it out.
How do you fly? Okay right triggers fly. That's what I have to do. Grab the sugar.
Open world. This is the kitchen from Rat Movie.
It kind of is. All right grab the sugar. No land on the runway. Land on the runway. Okay.
Oh I didn't get it. Stop. How am I not on the runway? Land on the runway. This is the
runway right? Did I not land on the runway? Okay well let's go ahead and get the sugar.
How do I open it? How does it want me to open the sugar thing? I'm gonna throw up
play this for more than two minutes I think. Oh wait what was that? Switch planes. All right
land in the cup. How do I switch planes? How do I change vehicles? Okay how do I get out?
Okay it's apparently X. Come on you're not gonna tell me the controls of the game?
All right I gotta lift up this thing. What button is that? What button is like lift up sugar
thing? The sugar isn't there. What? Look at the mini map. That's not the sugar? The grid. I'm
no I'm supposed to put the sugar into the cocoa. There's no where's the sugar? Wait so
what the hell is the other? Look at the mini map. What's that for? What is that even for?
Look at the other mini map. Why is it on the sugar bowl? That's inverted fucking throw up
controls by the way. Name of song. You really care about the song? Okay got it. It's a
chocolate candy. It's harder to fly this than I think it is to fly a helicopter in GTA 4
with the mouse and keyboard. I gotta change to the truck? I'm about to run out of time.
That how do I just change to the truck? Time is gas. Land on chocolate. Yeah I don't like I can't
change off the helicopter. Go pick up the pickup truck. This is supposed to be tutorial which
but in my mind is this is how you control the game. There is no explanation as to how
to change vehicles. It said go pick up the sugar and then pick up the cocoa and pick up the
cat poo. I don't have it. There's no I don't have a manual. Read the manual. I bought this used and
it came in a black fucking box. All right I pressed x last time and it didn't do that.
Where the fuck am I supposed to go from here? I'm just on the table. Sorry I'm even distracted.
Does the cat do anything? Okay why why the truck is definitely more fun than the helicopter.
So do I have to pick up the truck? Because the only other indicator on the minimap is up there.
So do I pick up truck and put the entire game is this level? No it's not.
The food grinder? I would have loved this as a kid. So probably I would have too.
Cat box? The yellow ramp against the wall. What? Where's the yellow ramp?
Am I actually blind? There's a yellow ramp against the wall.
No you guys this is you guys are horseshitting me here. Yellow ramp that goes up against the
wall. You guys are shitting at me right now. No way. Which wall is there a yellow ramp?
No that's not a ramp. That's a half pipe. Not even. What's this is not going to do anything.
Why does this work? How would you ever know this was going to work? There's no laws of
physics that's to explain why I'd be able to drive up the wall and stay on here.
There's no fucking way. Somebody in chat looked up the guide and figured it out.
Go up the little tiny half track and drive up the wall and drive on the ceiling.
Oh my god I'm looking at chat. I did it. I went. Kids logic. No one would ever do that.
No kids are gonna do that. When you guys are saying ramp I thought you were talking about
an actual ramp that could take me driving on a regular plane with real physics.
Not go up the small yellow McDonald's symbol. Drive up the wall. I'm glad my kid wouldn't
fucking understand that because he would be he'd be he'd be logic about it. He'd be asking me
dad I don't see a ramp that an actual you know in real life that you'd bet I'd be like
me either. I'd pat him on the head. I didn't even read the instructions.
You've managed thus far but you're nothing unless you can cook. Drop the eggs into the water and
don't forget to light the stove. Okay I'm ready. I need to pick up eggs. All right hold on.
Where are the eggs? Does it say where they are? Drop the eggs in the water. That's all we
get. I don't think that's an egg. That's a lighter though. I feel like I have to get the
other tank up there. That's fuel. All right eggs. Fridge. If I were a bunch of eggs I'd be in
the fridge. No there's eggs right here. All right so I need to switch because unless I go
and land and push them into the water from this side this level is not going to take
12 minutes. Got it. Okay they got one. Time to beat is one minute and 30. Yeah but you're
not expected to do that first try. It takes a minute to figure out where the eggs even are.
Throw up controls. I need like a joystick. It's a toy commander if you're wondering.
And it sucks. All right now it's gonna light the fuse. Stop stop stop stop.
Do I need to land on a special children's runway? Is that what this is?
All right do I have to find the one spot where I'm allowed to land? Guys.
Ah stop. Inverted stop please.
Can I change that shit? I forgot that game companies didn't realize how terrible it was
until like 2006. Plane altitude reverse. Is this is this it? No that's not it.
No it is for the plane. What I'd want is I'd want inverted before the plane.
Toy commander. I thought I was gonna break this desk on spring.
I think I might. This is still it still wants me to put an egg in here.
How am I gonna do that? It's destroyed. I'm gonna have to just reset the game.
That's not gonna start a fire. I thought I was supposed to be using kid logic.
Kids don't know how to use the stove. I do. Okay it's on. I'm burning the
fucking house down. So what was the point of giving me the tank in the first place?
I thought I had to change to it. Is that just a different way to go?
All right well here's this one. It's called rings of fire. Okay.
If you're a speed runner you go plane only. Okay this is a race.
Let's just fly through the ring.
Everything is bullshit. Everything is bullshit.
Okay who's increasing my speed? What's with the frame rate?
Where are you even trying to tell me to go?
What? God. This is horrible.
Superman 64. I have to beat this one. Wait I can kill the other competitors here?
Well immediately. What is it? What? I don't understand. Hold on. It's right next. It's the same ring?
Now I'm of the opinion that video games were terrible.
But as children we were forced to play them because it's the only thing we had in the house
there. You couldn't just go and get a game on Steam. You couldn't go buy a game where
you're gonna go to GameStop. Mom you're gonna drive me to GameStop. No there was
no free to play Fortnite. There was no free to play TF2. If your mom got you a game at the grocery
store you had to play it and you played it all fucking day because it's all that you couldn't
go. It was all you had. I wonder how many games that I actually because like I'm sitting here
right now as an adult and going like man this is horrible. This sucks. Why would I ever play
this? If I got this as a kid I would have 100% at every single level and I would have been
like this game's awesome because that's all my mom got me. Like this is all like I can't get
anything else. They didn't have video games when you were a kid? Yes they did because they
also weren't jaded. Yeah and like there's been too many. Like GTA 5 exists. You know what I
mean? With two spoiled as gamers. Okay take down the enemy bombers. But regardless of
what you think about GTA 5 these are like technically speaking this is just flying around
the living room shooting at radical v2 sets. The game that I played that was just painful
but it wasn't painful to me because I played it and I loved it. I'm trying to think which game
it would be. I'm about to scream like mom go get me something else. I played Mario Golf at
Anthony's and I want it too. Mario Golf came out good. What a game that was. No one had
played golf before on a computer but they're all above. Are we on different teams?
How do I keep missing this guy? All right that was quite demanding. This is your base.
I know but I can't. There. Okay I Mario golfed that guy. Hole in one. Just sit here.
I am using the radar. What does this have on IGN? It hurts. That was Toy Commander. I can't do the
controls anymore. Let's move on to a good one. God I'm gonna nostalgia's gonna hit me in the
face here. This is not even gonna be fun. Let's do Power Stone. We've been so that was a nine
on IGN but it probably makes sense though. That was like so long ago. All jokes aside
this game is actually really really awesome. Highly recommend. This is Power Stone.
Rage quit this one. No! Did I rage quit Dynamite Cop? No I beat it three times. I thought it was
great. Then it was a fun game. One of my favorites. I'm not gonna rage quit. Power Stone!
Here it comes.
Here it comes. Falcon. Wang. Gun Rock. There's Power Stone 2 as well.
Fuck it didn't do it the way that I said. Still good. So how the game works.
It's a fighting game. Uh kind of. It's a fighting game. The whole point is there are
Smash Balls. Wait I think they got that idea. So there are three Smash Balls that
will uh show up. What you gotta do is you gotta collect them and you get three Smash Balls.
Three Power Stones. Your character turns into the Power Stone version of their character.
So I wonder. Let's play Jack. All right I don't really remember the controls or anything
but it's very fun. Jack versus Jack.
One two. Got them both. Got them all. Here I am.
Essentially you have to avoid them. It's two stones. Don't let them get the other one.
Knock them out.
Oh yeah knocked it out of the hem. I'm gonna uh where's it this way. One more.
I am the green Jack.
Now take two of your stones.
You gotta just bully in the very beginning and get three stones as soon as possible.
We jumped over it.
No wowies. Okay that's all right. That's all right. That's okay.
Uh oh. Not okay. Where's the yellow one?
Give me. Give me. Give me. Give me. Where'd it go? Where'd it go? Over here.
Ah. Got him with the bump. This game is so much fun. Let's just go ahead and beat the
whole game first right. In Lundo. Lundo. He's like kind of the red Power Ranger.
Uh oh. That's not good. Can't take this much damage.
Got it. Gotta get a good hit. Got it. Got it. One more. Got it. One more. That's okay. We're good.
He's not paying attention to any of the gems. This is a mistake.
Uh oh. No, no, no, no, no. He's gonna get blue. I'm gonna get yellow.
Okay. Soft screen. Holy shit he just tailed me.
I know there's like a block or a dodge I think. From what I remember.
Reverse or I know there is.
Oops. Lost the other gem, didn't you?
Take it. Let's go. Damn it. Oh man. He's smart. I'm getting kind of beat here.
Oh that was bad. I need to go and like practice and learn to do those blocks and stuff.
Grab two.
Are you smarter than a dream cat? Maybe that's you. No, just get the stones. Just get the stones.
I'll take it.
No. See there it is. There's the dodge. How do you do that? There's that like dash. How do you do that? Trigger?
What block is? I'm so like. Got it.
Holy shit if he kills me in power stone form it'll be so embarrassing.
Thank you. Freudian weapon for five community subs. Play with italics. I don't have another
controller. I don't have two dreamcast controllers unfortunately. Go back to toy commander.
Why would you want me to do that? Hold on. Is it okay? Button config. Here we go. All right.
Jump. Grab. Punch. So what's the dash? Power fusion one. Power fusion two.
Yeah you get a special move. Two of them. Maybe saw falcon do it. But then you lose your power
stone. So let's grab. Dash with that maybe. That's not good. Damn it she got it.
No what's that? Sorry I only get hit by one thing.
Oh a direct hit right in her head. Let me try those one of the fusion.
Let's see what happens. Oh exactly that's awesome. So I get in close and do the cyclone.
Look at the jumping. Can blow. Didn't get her. See ya.
I don't know how to do that with it.
This game is cool. This game is very cool.
Fine you want to play that game? Get you right at the wake up.
Thank you. Very cool. What's the other special move?
The jump above you. You do right trigger and that's the other special.
I also can't understand why Capcom has not made a new one of these. They only came up
for Dreamcast. They were only available for Dream. One and two that's it. It's such a cool
franchise that even it's a very simple combo concept. But they could turn it into something
so much bigger. But the popularity of games like Smash right now. You wouldn't want to
have like your own kind of version of this.
And then you're the other one.
That's not a good place to be. Especially right now.
Into the meat grinder. Oh he's a fan. I got it.
There's a lot of dynamic with who has one, who has two. It's really fun just to try to
dance around the fact that even when you have three, this could be a waste of time.
Somebody put, there was a lot of people who played this game that didn't even give a shit
about the gameplay. Just went for the, just went for the kill. That's it.
Because it was too much of a distraction. So oh what? Randomly spawned.
Oh now let me, let me two stalk him. Come on. He's gonna get all three. He is. He turns
into the thing.
Fucked.
That kind of sucked. I'm not gonna lie.
And we keep going back. I'm not gonna get it.
Dominoes of Pizza Hut, Pizza Hut. I'm gonna, I'll tell you first try I'm gonna get to the end.
Or lose. Did you say wrong? Pizza Hut has stuffed crust. I don't really like to order
either of them. I like local places. I like local places. But if I'm gonna order Pizza Hut
for Dominoes, I'm gonna get the stuffed crust. All right they're all three around. One, two, three. All the same
corner. Every Pizza Hut smells like a bowling alley. No it doesn't. All Pizza places smell like
a bowling alley. Every Pizza Hut is next to a bowling alley. I mean I'm not gonna argue with that.
Bowling alley is usually served with served pizzas. Yeah. What's the matter with bowling
alley? I don't like bowling in bulk. And I find it. I can, I can see.
You know what? Okay I'm gonna give you guys a little bit of a how the hell is it possible
scenario. So bowling is like an old like boomer thing to do. That's what a lot of you
would say. Right? So how do bowling alleys survive and not arcade? Bowling alleys are
like kind of old and old school and a lot of arcades don't go away.
It's the same thing. A lot of arcades have closed down. They've kind of been
stuffed into the Gaven Buster style. But actual, you think of a bowling alley.
What the fuck is a corporate bowling alley? They don't exist. It's like Bob's bowling alley
or the Lanes. One guy owns it. It's not like a corporation. There's no big bowling company.
So the Gaven Buster's argument like doesn't work there. How did they get to stay in business? And
arcades didn't. Mom and pop arcades I mean. I guess that their overhead really is not that
much maybe. How much does it cost to run a bowling alley? I mean you'd probably have the
same balls and same pins for a long time. All right I gotta pay attention. I'm at the final
second of the whole line. All right I'm getting dumped on here. I'm getting dumped on. I'm not
gonna get perfect. All right. Give me. Give me. Give me. Give me. Give me. Give me. Give me.
Yep. Don't let the wake up happen. No no no no no no. Don't let the wake up happen.
She's getting both the stones. Greedy. He went for the stones.
Uh-oh. Uh-oh. Direct hit. No. Get her with the bomb.
Do it. You didn't even see. Really. It's like a beta so hard by the computer.
Knock them both. Give me. Give me. Give me. Shit. God damn it. This is bad.
Oh my sweaty hand. Uh-oh. That. No. No. Where'd it go? What just hit me? What? Hit me. All right.
We're at the final battle with the Captain Hook flapjack character.
I mean let me first try Power Stone after like 15 years of not playing it. Come on.
I'm ready. No. Environment.
He's just trying to get the gems. He's just a gem hoarder. Last one. Got it. Twice in a row.
Got it. Environment. Get him with the environment. One more time. Shit. He has a gun.
Oh. He got greedy and it was downfall.
All right. No. Shit. I got too greedy with it. I can still do it. I can. I'm in trouble. No.
Oh no. I'm gonna die here. He didn't even use his special. Good. Where'd he go? Oh, he's
holding on. Okay. I see. All right. I gotta get it one more time.
Fuck. Did I win? Fuck. Shit. No. Oh, the timer. Oh, I had it. Come on. Let's go.
That was horrible placement. You see that bullshit? That was bullshit. That was
unfucking believable. I just got screwed. Really? That was so salty. That was such bullshit.
I knocked him into all three of them. That was such. I fucking actually mad about that.
I literally knocked all the gems out of him and he fell down into all three. That was
stupid. I had it, too.
I was gonna do a first try. Oh, well.
Did he just catch me in the air?
He's doing his little cheat move where he just. All this guy cares about is the smash ball.
So I don't even care about the smash ball. Just beat him.
Baby. I should have had it that first try. Those of you Power Stone vets will know what
I'm talking about. He was. He wasn't focused on it.
See? Look. He cares so much about this. I should have just fought him like this the whole time.
Give me both. Move out of my way. You greedy asshole. Your character bottle's too big.
Oh, God. He's gonna do it again. No. Why? What the fuck? That's so stupid.
It was in his. Oh, I'm gonna die. He just. Just fucking. Oh, my God. I'm so angry.
The dude just drop kicks you once. He has a move. He has a move where if he. If he
touches you with it once, he just. It's like a beep and it knocks out your stuff.
This guy's too hard. I hate this again and again.
Thankfully, this move sucks. God, I just got too mad. I'm so tilted from that first fucking
try. Fucking asshole pirate. His body. He's got like a fucking square of a hitbox that
he can just push into you. Are you ready? That's that move right there. It is a half second
frame.
Why? Why? What? It's cuz he's doing that move.
Oh, I can't see patchy from Spongebob. I beat everyone in the game on the first try and
you see like his cheap shit move that he has. Fucking believable.
No.
Get over here. No, fuck off. Just die.
No, fuck. Just use it.
Bomb. I win. I win. I win. Eat shit. Fuck that pirate guy. Hope your boat flips over
and flapjack. Oh, that's not even the last boss I forgot. Oh, right. It's this guy.
All right, let's go. Oops. Oh, he does so much damage.
Damn it, I didn't get him. Oh, damn it. Holy shit, he's insane. He does like two
and a half bars a hit. This is bad. I don't know what the hell he does.
Bad placement. That move. Oh my god. Give it here. Give it here. Give it here.
Give me that. Oh, Fafn is my real name. What the hell was that? Like, like, what happened?
Oh shit.
Damn it. I had to. Oh, what was that bounce off the wall? That bounce off the wall. The
sucked into his body like a fucking vacuum. Give me the third one right now. Over here.
Give me a good spawn. Get the fuck out of here. Come on, one more.
That bomb.
Just tap him. Just tap him.
Don't fucking throw it. I can't. I just got like, comboed. No way. Impossible.
I can't believe it. I can't believe it. I got six.
What?
Fuck you. You want to get flawless, dickhead? Is that what you want to have happen?
You want to get flawlessed after that bullshit?
Fucking god, I can't believe it. I can't fucking believe it. I had one hit.
My god, one more shit. That's such dog shit. Dude, literally took me six health. Oh, I am.
This is the maddest I've ever been in a video game in my entire life, I think. That's
un-fucking-believable. He did almost six full health bars in like two different, I'm so mad.
That's unbelievable. That is so fucking ridiculous.
Just kill me. Do two moves and kill me, final boss.
I got sloppy. I didn't get sloppy. I got unlucky.
Because I did my move and you have two or three seconds after your move is done.
For him to go do a bunch of fucking, set up a bunch of mouse traps for me.
Want to get flawlessed. Yeah. But don't worry. He just had to do two moves to do four.
Oh, I hate that. Dude, I understand like you give a final boss and you make it stronger and shit,
but like does he have to be like three or four times stronger? You know what I mean? Why?
Does he have to do like four times your damage? What the hell is that?
Who's made up that? No, it's very doable. I'm just hyper tilted right now.
It's like you gotta, you gotta beat the last boss three times. He's got like,
why even have the health bar here? Why don't you give him like, like five more health bars?
All right, this is the one. This is the one. Let me, let me beat the boss three times in a row.
And then win.
Oh my god. Why did I do that? Just kill me again.
God damn it. Just kill me. I'll try one more.
Fast. Okay. It's almost, look at the bars. Look at the top left bars.
He landed on his stomach and took 60% of my health pool.
Oh, I can't fucking believe it. You should, I should be embarrassed
because this motherfucker was dead almost twice in a row.
He's gonna get it because they spawned right in front of him. That's unbelievable.
Why didn't you, why didn't you, uh, I gotta go back to the character I played before.
Try. Let's do the roll.
No, that's pretty good.
Okay.
No, I have to beat this. This game is really good. I'm just salty at the last unfair boss.
This is like the Shao Kahn. Let me phrase it. This is, this is Mortal Kombat 1 Shao Kahn.
How did you, you're gonna jump up? Give me a fucking break. You're gonna jump over a goddamn fire?
What, what's the priority? Why did you get priority there? Oh my god. We both did this.
Still doable.
Christ.
He's gonna get it now. Fucking god, Jeremy, get out of here!
What the fuck was that?
Shit.
Yeah, another thing that somebody just said is true. Forget about like the awful gen squad.
It's like dodging and blocking something that I don't even know how to do it.
I don't, can I, is it even, I don't remember it being the game.
What's like the dodge? How do you do it? Is it possible in a certain fucking combination?
Because then, that's, sometimes you can reverse him.
I don't think it exists.
You have to jump or press a direction at perfect timing. Okay.
Am I getting baited here?
I think I'm getting baited.
Yeah, I just got baited.
I'm not timing it right.
I'm pretty sure I'm just getting fucked here. When you get hit.
No, I'm not gonna rage at Tony Hawk. Tony Hawk doesn't have a boss that has times 10 health and times 10 damage. It's a skateboarding move. It's faster.
It's so fucking sad to me because like I had it, I had it so close and then I just got
just bodied over and over again. I would have moved on to Tony Hawk by now. He's doing it. He's just so perfect.
When you talk about like difficulty spikes, right? The entire game was breezed until the last two bosses.
Like what the fuck? When did this game come out? 2025?
Oh okay, I'm gonna like just hunker down the traffic. I'm just progressively getting worse
because I'm just exhausted trying to beat this fucking guy. All right, here we go.
Dude, he's like gluing to these items. No, why did I do that? Just shut up, Jeremy. Just beat him.
What? What? What? What? When did I lose the other one? What the fuck, man? What?
You gotta be kidding me. You have to be kidding me. There's no way. That was...
I don't care who you are, everybody knows I'm stupid.
Was. Just was. All right, I'm not going in the air ever again. I'm literally never
gonna jump in the air. Not one time. Never. I'm gonna do this to myself.
Oh, you don't.
Come on. God. He dodged.
Got some fucking RNG there, didn't I? God damn it.
No. God damn it. It's okay.
Somebody did mention he is like perfect dodging almost every one of my attacks.
Fuck me, man. It is so close. I mean, it's one thing to learn how to like properly
dodge every attack, but he's dodging almost every one. He's getting so many of these
rolls to the way they just appear behind him right next to him on top of him. It's like, come on.
And it takes so much to kill him. I might as well just restart. Try to get him.
I gotta dodge that at least. I keep getting caught every time.
He can get like, I have not even one bar.
I don't like this guy super.
Oh my. Just trying to get away from him and he's just...
He also has perfect sight of the gems when you're limited to what the game shows you.
Okay, I'm gonna try a different character. Maybe it's like time to roll on like this guy.
I don't even know. I'm here. I have to be here.
Are you ready?
Flamethrower is honestly the best thing to ever use. It's going to him.
Just only run around until you get a flamethrower.
Exhibit A. There it is. I will cheese the fuck out of this guy. Do you think I care?
Let's go.
No, he got the gun before I did!
He's too focused on it.
What? Oh my god. Fuck off.
I don't know if I have enough health to do it. I think it's gonna be perfect.
You gotta be fucking kidding me. It like bounced and he was gonna get it regardless.
Oh my god. It's such bullshit. It really is.
What happened? What the fuck was that?
Fucking kidding me, man. That's... This is so stupid. That actually is dumb. That's really dumb.
Just live. Live. Three. Two. One. Don't do it. That's it. What?
I love how I got the power stone. He did more damage than I did.
Fuck you.
But like I can't move during that. He gets a free hit every fucking time.
Oh my god.
Come on. Come on.
See what I'm talking about? He gets a free fucking hit.
I freaked out. It's okay.
Don't spawn over there.
Fucking stupid idiot. Why would you even pick up an item for no reason? He's so much faster than
you. There's no reason to do what I just did. Like unbelievable. I thought it was like a gun
or something. He is so unbearably difficult. Like why wouldn't you just...
Fucking god, I hate this.
I can't fucking believe it, man. I just... I still got it. My hands are like literally sweating.
Where's the other one?
I did it. I had to have won. I had to have won.
I did it. I win. I win the game. I'm done.
I don't know what. What? What the fuck was that? I couldn't even do anything.
What? Give me the stone.
It's very... Okay, it's very possible. Oh my god. Give it to me. Do I get to do this again?
I have... This is not even as bad. This is like the jokey end of the game. I mean it's
horrible. Yeah, thank god. All right, let's go. Let me beat Akira. There's no dodging that.
He just has to take a whole painful hit. I'm trying to dodge these.
I don't even sure if I can.
Dodge roll? I don't know if it's possible because it's not technically an attack.
It's kind of just a big thing with attacks.
Try jumping over them? You lose speed when you jump.
One second.
Don't go behind him. Well, he wasn't... There was only behind him.
Watch out. Shit. I'm behind him. I'm behind him. I'm looking for like...
Oh my god. That's un-dodgeable. Just never be...
Actually, he doesn't no matter what. I think it's just random number generator.
Oh, god damn it. How much health do I have? No, god. Timer. Oh, man.
I just spent... That's what I thought. It was a bad idea.
I'll get it. I mean, this is... I hate everything about this, but I'm going to beat it.
I have like another move that's like a... I think I'm actually really just going to use it
like this and then run if I collect the stones. I'm not even sure if I pick up the stones.
It's a waste of time because you just set yourself up for getting your ass kicked.
It's just so vulnerable. I pick up items. He's doing more damage than I just did.
He's done with his dip. Show. I'll take it. Sword. End it with sword.
Game over.
Oh, that was hell. For the Chaos Emerald.
He doesn't need it. He shatters it.
Worst ending.
Yeah, that was like the world's going.
Was the ending worth it? I had to do it because internally,
if I stopped at that last boss, I would have been so unfulfilled. My reputation would have been
ruined. Mrs. Space, thanks for 10 community subs. Thank you so much, Mrs. Space. 10 community
subs. Okay, there's the Infinity Gauntlet. Game over. The end? Please wait. A new feature
has been added. Would you like to save now? Yes, sure. Do all endings? I don't think I
can handle it. What's the new feature? Extra options. Game options. Oh, wow. Now I can
set how many power stones you have to get. Extra items. Damage recovery. I can fuck around
with these. Game options. We are like bright. There's no way I'm going to make anything
harder than this. Beat the game on easy. No. What else is there? Anything else?
I just want to see something. So how do you unlock it? Do I not unlock it? How do I unlock
the other characters? Next? Now hold on. Wait, hold on. I know. I'm not going to do the
whole thing. I have to beat the game with every character to unlock it. You have to
beat the game without using continues. That's not even a joke. Holy shit.
No. You have to look under the...
This game is really, really fun, though. Especially when you play it with more than
one person. Which one are you? I'm the one that's currently getting...
Yeah. I mean, it's just that last block. It's just like, come on. What the hell
was that nonsense? Times three damage, times five dodge, times five health. Like,
it's just, it's just accurate. I have a skin. Default skin.
But it is very good. Forget about my final boss complaints. This is Final Smash.
The video game, essentially. It's very, very good. Did I say the game sucks at
all? I don't think it did. When I was, like, in the middle of that meltdown where I was
getting destroyed by the black ball. I didn't say the game sucked, did I?
Well, that move is amazing. Did it beat the boss? I did. I beat the two bosses. I did.
Okay, good. Good. Because I don't believe that. Whatever my frustrated mind would say,
I don't believe that. It was actually very good.
But I beat Valgus, but Fluggin Brothers is too hard. All right, we got, I played,
this is kind of what I figured was gonna happen. I was gonna play something like
Power Stone for a couple of hours. It's so fun. Fuck that final boss.
So we're gonna move on from here. I have Tony Hawk.
I also have a survival horror game called Carrier. Because if I put in Tony Hawk,
I'm gonna play Tony Hawk for the rest of the night. So we gotta get
some of these other ones out of the way. So just give me one sec.
Okay, I just opened the case and the glass shattered. Like three chunks of glass just,
like, shot up over here. I didn't, I just opened it. I just opened the glass.
I opened the case. I gotta be careful. I gotta pick this shit up. Hold on.
Because that will be bad. It's like sharp. It's not glass. It's that like super sharp
plastic bullshit. Sonic Adventure, Sonic Adventure is on PC. So I'm gonna do those
at a different day. The games I'm doing today are the games that are not available
anywhere else. Only on Dreamcast. The actual console. Can't, they weren't ported, etc.
I have all of them. Shenmue is another one. Shenmue, I had an option to get it on
Dreamcast, but not even last year. They ported the game to PC and they upscaled it to like 1080,
right? Tony Hawk is on PC. Tony Hawk 2 is not on PC. They did like a remaster of Tony Hawk 1,
and it was kind of lukewarm. Tony Hawk Pro Skater 2 is not on PC. It's only on the
consoles. I mean, yes it is. Tony Hawk Pro Skater 2 is on PC. What? Tony Hawk Pro Skater 2 PC?
Oh, but it's an, okay, it's an old Windows game. And you know how hellish it can be
sometimes to get those to run. I guess it is on PC. Does it actually work on like Windows 10?
All right, here's carrier. It doesn't work on Windows 10. Just get a virtual box. Yeah,
but if I already have a Dreamcast here, do I really want to make like a virtual emulation
machine to play Tony Hawk 2 when I already have it here and this is arguably the best version
is the one on Dreamcast? Why is there somebody's, somebody has a website in the corner.
Why? Why did they shoot us down? Leonard, Lieutenant Manning. Am I the only one that made
it? Is that Leonard? So the opening, I didn't press start yet though. That's like the demo
screen. Carrier. Everybody did the Resident Evil. When you press start, it says the name.
Whatever, let's just go. By the beginning of the 21st century, the North-South conflict had
escalated to military confrontation. Which North-South? The people of the countries of the South
faced with an energy crisis and a food shortage had developed a deep-seated hatred.
Is this just generic country names? And as a result, anti-North terrorist groups began to show up
all over the world. In response, the countries of the North joined together to create the
Northern Hemisphere Treaty Alliance, NTA. The goal of this organization was to stop the
Southern terrorists. In 2023, the NTA completed construction of the Heimdall aircraft carrier.
With its stage defense system and connection to the satellite defense system,
the Heimdall is like a steel wall, invulnerable to any sort of air-based attack.
The first mission for the Heimdall was to attack the base of the Southern Cross terrorist group.
This was called the Hurricane Mission. During an attack that lasted only a few days,
the base was completely destroyed and the Heimdall was able to head back to its home
port in North America. However, approximately two days of travel from port, the Heimdall fell
silent, failing to respond to any communication from NTA. Concerned about the Heimdall,
a Spark investigation team was put together and sent to determine what happened.
Oh boy.
That was a full, almost three seconds of no-lips-and-mouth.
Somebody turn the vacuum off, I want to hear the dialogue please.
I don't see anyone on the flight.
Dad is mowing the lawn right next to your window and you're in a goddamn
intense 3D3 League of Legends match and you're getting so irritated. He goes away,
he's on his fucking riding mower and he's driving away and you're gonna mute your fucking
mic. Mute. Oh, here we go. It goes by you unmute your friends, dad.
He couldn't hear anything I was saying. Well, case in point, good. I'm glad the game
would make the point. I'm happy to give this game about 25 minutes.
You just tried to tell a joke with your dad mowing the lawn. Yes, I, exactly.
This is the maddest I've ever been. This is the maddest I've ever been in a video game.
Stupid, it's stupid. This game's fucking stupid.
Leonard. So we're gonna get the big reveal to see what happened to Leonard.
Are you okay? No, he's okay. Hang on. Looks like my leg's no good.
Your leg? Don't move it. I'll take care of it. This is Colonel Burke.
Smart team, do you copy? Colonel Burke. Those goggles. Jack, you're a bit late.
He won't do anything. Have you finally landed? Colonel, the helicopter was attacked.
What? Colonel, the helicopter was attacked. So that was the big point.
He has giant ski goggles on. It must be the work of Southern Cross.
We don't know about that. We must begin the investigation.
And the other members? Are they okay? I don't know where Lieutenant Manning is.
She's disappeared. The pilot Leonard is with me now, but he's badly injured.
I see. See if you can find a first aid kit and do what you can for Leonard.
When you're done, begin your investigation. Yes, sir.
I don't know what's going on, but it's clear that things are not what they seem.
Maybe Leonard is safer than a flight. Make a Resident Evil 2 joke?
Yeah, I'll leave him here. I'll check the ship and bring back any first aid supplies.
I can't. I haven't played it.
I'm counting on you. We'll get back to the investigation on this end.
Lang should be checking the ship data in the security room. When you're done,
catch up with him and see what he's discovered. Then continue your investigation.
Yes, sir, Colonel. Be careful. Wait for me, Leonard. I'll get a first aid kit.
Oh, I'm sorry. I'll be right back. Apologizing. Okay.
Do I have control of the character now? Is this going to be another tank controls game?
We just walk around and shoot the one zombie that shows up and then grab the health kit.
I'm glad we're getting it out of the way. No scream. What happened?
It's his head.
His head? Oh, no. Okay.
So let's plug us. I love that bird mouth.
What the hell's going on? Leonard was by that. Please work.
Leonard, I'm sorry. I wish I could have done something.
The eyes shifting back and forth. All right. Time for.
What the hell is going on here? How do I? Okay. How do I shoot?
Hey, dead. Yeah, it's just tank controls. Actually, not that bad. All right. Upstairs.
Dollar store of Resident Evil. Well, more like $2 store or 30 or $40 on Amazon store.
At least 10. This was at least $10 in the Amazon dollar store.
Port side elevator. That's an impractically not long name for a store.
Raided. We got a raid. What? Who came in with the raid?
I see General Sam. General Sam, thanks for the raid. Welcome, everybody. General Sam.
Of those of you that are just joining us, this game, this is not something that you're
typically going to see on this channel. It's not a good representation. Yes, it is.
Welcome to the stream. Hope you had a good one, General Sam.
This is not a good representation of what the stream is.
It's usually not. I'm usually not playing a game like this. Usually I'm playing Dota 2 or
cards in real life. Just cards, playing cards with a friend.
A3 lock is written above the key slot. Okay, go down here. Look at how dark this is.
What does it say? Deck 1 security room and medical. A1 written on the lock.
Okay, slow down. It's just blue stinger, but slightly better. Yep, hold on.
Such passion. Such fear.
Somebody knocked on your hotel door and you walked up and asked that question.
We don't figure out what's going on soon.
Anyway, the Colonel's on deck three. Dr. Noble should be on his way to the lower decks,
but I haven't heard from him for now. We need to join the Colonel.
Yes, sir. I'm trying to open the partition to deck two, but I need two more activation discs.
There are two more discs like this one on deck one, some old, old,
old. Stupid. Where's the thumb drive? Stupid dumb old game. Where's the thumb drive, idiot?
Right? Yes, sir. There should be an ID card in the medical room in this area.
Here, take this. You should stock up on medicines in case of an emergency.
Yes, sir. This computer's running wild. It won't tell me anything about the ship.
The security lock is complicated. What a pain. You better bring those discs soon.
There's not much time. Somebody just said I missed the kind old lady,
Jerma. What? No, I've read that completely wrong. The old Jerma that used to walk
old ladies across the street. When did I do that? Does this do anything? Do you want to...
No. There's something over here. A security system console seems to be active. There's a
something spinning around over there. Just... that's it. A A3 ID card obtained and
DV tape obtained. That's how you know this is old. Doesn't help old ladies? Of course I do.
If I'm on the sidewalk and an old lady comes up and she says,
Ah, excuse me. Could I please add bother you? I say, yes, of course. What's... what is it, man?
I'm looking to go across this walkway here and I need a little bit of help.
I go, absolutely, ma'am. Of course. And we get to the end and we slowly go across and make
sure that, you know, she's stabilized and has enough room to go. We get across and
she gives like a little a little hug like, Oh, thank you, my my wonderful boy. And you're like,
Oh, have a great day, ma'am. And then like two or three hours later, you go into your wallet
because you're buying a drink. You're buying a round for all your friends. And like 60 bucks
is gone. That's why I don't do it. What the fuck is going on in here? What happened?
For a second, I saw a dinosaur face.
Here comes the scientist.
Then here's the fucked up scientist.
I'm Sergeant Ingles. I'm part of the Spark team sent to investigate the ship. What are you doing
here? Spark? You're a little too late. This is not a human anymore. Here, take a look with this.
What is it? VR goggles. Okay, the BEM T3N scope. Developed by the NTA for infantry in the
case of biological warfare, can be used to identify non-human life forms. See in the
dark and see through some objects. Do I really have to scan this guy to find out that he's a
zombie? Scanning. Danger. What's going on? What is going on? What you see? Somebody gave 50
dollars a long time ago. What? How did I miss this? I was finally able to capture one of
these things alive and conduct some experiments, but the ship is already full of them.
What? I tried to analyze this one, but it's too late. I was getting my ass kicked.
Oh, that's right. I was engrossed in self-pity playing Power Stone. Hey, what are you doing?
It, it is all because of Ark. Ark? This monster looks like a human, but, but it's not. It's
an inferior life form. Hey, stop. Are you crazy? I thought I just shot him.
Those bombs, those chains were not bound very well. Like,
human. He's dead. Three, two, one. You're a very bad shot. You're terrible. Hey, wait,
what are you talking about? He can fit like four times. You have arrived in hell.
He did the, okay. Well, I wasn't really ready for that.
Okay, that, am I stuck in a time loop here? Why did he just reverse time?
Uh, A1 ID card. I needed that. Anything else in the room? There it is. Record of research
by Terry Adams. Somebody else. What? Carrots? What just fell out?
An evil carrot just jumped out at me. What? There's more? More Nickelodeon Splat sound
effects, too. If you keep them scored. Can I please shoot this? If I die to the
fucking Nickelodeon carrot, I'm gonna be very upset. Okay. Nothing, there's nothing useful here.
So let's go. I got the A1 card. Do I have any healing items? A1 is down this way.
Use energy drink. Yep, use it. That's not very much health. All right, equip, uh, where's
my, is my helmet? No, don't welder. Look. Okay, use it. Just turned everything kind of sepia. Uh oh.
At least there are enemies in this game. The last two survival horror games we played,
people barely had to, there was no enemies. All right, what's in here? Let's find out.
Which ones were survival horror? Uh, the ring. The ring was one of them. What? Then blue stinger.
That's not even a survival horror. Hoygel was horror, maybe. Everything's covered with plants.
The bird? Okay, this is a jump scare. There's an octopus giant plant octopus thing in here.
Yes, I'm checking the aircraft hangars. The wavelengths aren't even matched up either.
Leonard? Well, at least match up the wavelengths. He was attacked and killed by some creature on
the flight deck. What? I couldn't get to him in time. I'm so sorry. No, there's nothing to
object about. Colonel. Sorry, this is no time to get emotional. Yes, sir. He came down and
attacked me, so I killed it. Stop using your voice. The elevator was damaged, so I couldn't
go up and check until I went below. It was just me and Leonard on the flight deck.
I don't know we're the creature that attacked Leonard. Just start humming it in your head
because it's going to come soon enough. There's no sense for fussing and fighting, my friend.
Yes, sir. Do you have any idea what's going on?
I saw a human turn into some sort of monster. I don't know. Let's do it. Yes, sir.
What happened to the creature that attacked you? It came down and attacked me.
All right, we're going speed run. One death, permanent death. Head gone. Perfect. Nothing
over here. Another cut scene. Radio room. This thing's going to jump up. Hey, what do
you think you're doing? I'm too late. Heimdall, why did you attack the Spark
helicopter of NTA Central? He thought that guy was alive. Deactivate the intercept system
and stop the ship. He's angry at that guy. Heimdall, respond. Stop the ship.
This is Sergeant Ingalls from Spark. Spark, okay. Our helicopter was destroyed during
an emergency landing. Stop. Hey, what the hell went on? Over here in Chicago,
what's going on? We're calling from a long ways away. Damn. That was the essentially all
that guy's dialogue. Nothing in here that I can need to grab or touch or do.
Dead body in the chair. He must have been attacked while using the transmitter. Okay.
Muzzle flash just flashed light, you're right. But, all right, let's see. There's a door over
this way. No, that's just the way I came. I gotta go till you die. What if I just don't
die? That would be really unfortunate for all of us. Who are you? What? I'm Sergeant Ingalls.
I'm part of the Spark team sent by NTA. Man, you were lucky to make it this far.
Was the intercept system deactivated? How's he going to shoot this guy? No, it destroyed the
helicopter we came in on. It's hopeless. It's impossible to leave. Don't give up. We'll
deactivate the system somehow. Do you know where it is? Man, it's in the weapons control
room on deck six, but it's going to be hell to get there. Trust me, we'll get there.
Evacuate to the flight deck and wait for help from the command center. He's got a good
YouTuber voice. Hey, we're counting on you, Sarge. This should come in handy in your
mission. Yeah, it does. It's the second one. That's what I needed. Can't do it. Let's go.
How do I find these games? Well, this is just on Dreamcast. This is only on Dreamcast.
And the last couple of nights we've been playing Dreamcast games. It's the most defining,
genre-defining even. Video games came from the Dreamcast, and we're seeing why. What? He
went right for the neck. Iron Gate. Looks like it would take a bomb to open it. It's locked. A2.
This might end very quickly. Is there another door?
People act like PS2 didn't have bad games. No, Dreamcast has a lot of great games.
Pull the door. I went all the way to the end. Look at this great game. Well, this is not a
look at this great game. This is look at this exclusive. Go this way. Well, I've only
played the bad ones. Well, because all the good ones are ported to PC. So stuff like Shenmue is
just a better version on PC. Jet Set Radio is on PC. Sonic Adventure is on PC. Space Channel 5 is
on PC. And those games are a lot of money. So I got the ports for those ones, and then we're
going to play them. But these are the physical disks that you can't get anywhere else unless
you emulate these games. Space Channel 5, yeah, is on PC. I didn't I was completely unaware of
that as well. I was shocked when I saw like the actual Dreamcast collection on Steam. It's on
Steam. Where was I back there? Yeah, Dreamcast Sonic Adventure is probably better. But I mean,
I can still get it. Let me go through this door. Sonic Adventure is actual dog shit if
you haven't played it recently. Now I'm scared. Hey, what happened? There's something over there.
Somebody hiding behind a locker?
What happened? Who is this? Is that me? I don't see anything. Did that guy run into the locker
and then the game delayed his fall down by 10 straight seconds? Or was he supposed to get
sucked in and grabbed into the locker? No, it's an invisible man. What? The scope.
Oh, he's going to use the infrared. Good. Don't use my bullets. I'll take care of it. You stay in
the locker. It's okay. You can come out. You're Jack, Bob's brother. You know Bob?
I know Bob. Yeah, he runs the dog stand down the fucking street. You must be Eddie from
Bob's outfit. You got it. I'm glad you're okay. Was Bob with you? I lost track of him when
the mutants came. Yeah, I lost track of Bob. Oh, I'm sorry. It's okay. I'm glad to see you're
okay. It's not safe here. You should go to the flight deck. Okay. Be careful, Sergeant.
Thanks. Hurry. Yeah. Medkit, we still go. I go until I die.
We go until I... never mind. I thought about it for a second.
Use the heal. I have six shots left. Full stream of carrier incoming. I don't think that's
going to happen. R2? No, just run. The game doesn't look that bad. It is not that bad.
None of these games are that bad. These games came out before some of you guys were even
born. So you gotta give a little bit of credit. Just run. What's wrong with me?
Why did I just do that? Did I just puke? Did I just like shit my pants and say no?
It's you without a mustache. Who do I shoot? Who do I shoot? I made the right call.
It's a good thing you're able to figure it out. How you doing? I'm Alan. I'm Sergeant
Inglis from SPARC. I'm asking all survivors to go to the flight deck. You should go there
too. The flight deck? There are no safe places left on this here ship. Well,
you must have noticed by now the whole ship is screwed up, son. It's impossible to tell
who's on our side and who is not. You can't trust anyone but yourself. I hope it's facial
here. Thanks, but I'll make my own decisions. That's how you want it. Good luck. I've got
work to do. Be careful. You too. Here, you better take this. By the way, son,
thanks for saving my butt. Three energy drinks. Level three. No, level three energy
whatever it was. That's a full heal.
All right, what we got? Control panel. Is it ammo? What is it? Activation disc obtained.
For what room? Activation disc. I just healed too. Really? What is- oh, the invisible guys. I
forgot about the stupid invisibility bullshit. Excuse me. No other doors. There's one right
here. God damn it. Kill him. Everybody wants me to lose so bad. Everybody's rooting for me to
lose. This is spooky. Come on. All right, we got our first major encounter, I think. How's the
speed around looking? Somebody said this game hurts to look at. It is an old game.
Nothing over here. God damn tank. It has no lighting and zero art direction. It's kind of
a blob, isn't it? Is there a reason to come out here? There's a two-hour speedrun of this game.
How long is the game itself then? Two hours for a speedrun. This game's probably like 15
to 20 hours long. Well, I'm looking forward to it because there's no way I'm gonna die.
Well, then he dies when he gets up to the top of the ladder. Wouldn't that be funny?
All right, going up Shadow Moses. Wait till I get my codec call.
Sir, this is Jack. Sir, I'm on my way to the bridge. The partition for the corridor to deck
two is closed. Captain Lang is in the security room trying to open and I'm looking for the
necessary discs. E-7 bomb. Deck one weapon storage. Can't they just turn those lights on?
Is there a pair of underwear? No. Yeah, there was that door downstairs that needed a bomb.
That guy's gonna stand up after I grab the disc. Ship's log. That's a full month. Visibility's good
and the radar is still operating. We're gonna get a good view of the... Don't trust anybody.
Still raining. Doesn't look like it will stop soon. Okay. Well, like he was probably alive.
Well, I don't know. I saw a guy and had to shoot. If I get hit one more time, I'm dead.
Yeah, that's the... that's not the Wilhelm scream. That's called the tantrum scream.
Is that what it is? Stay away from me. Calm down. I'm part of the spark team. Spark team? Yeah,
we're evacuating survivors to the flight deck. This guy's a liar. Do you know
a pilot named Bob Ingalls? Bob? He's my brother. Shoot this guy. I think I've heard
the name somewhere, but... Hmm. You know, maybe if you check the crew list using the
terminal here, you'll find something. I see. I'll check it later. Do you know where the
weapon storage is? It is. Why? Why was that used in every form of media? Was it there as a
joke? It was just an inside joke. I'm not doing so hot. There we go. Energy drink.
Use energy drink. Look at that. I really had one HP. So I gotta go down to A... A2, right?
There's a map. Look at the map. Where's the map? Where's the map? A2 doors. I need like an A2 map.
No one's paying attention. No one's paying attention.
I actually... I don't think it's that bad. I think it's actually not bad.
It's the Tony Hawk waiting room. Don't you worry. I will show you a 1 million point string.
You understand? Now, I would like somebody to cut from what I just said right there.
About 30 minutes from now, potentially, when I am repeating over and over again.
It's fucking impossible. Like, it's very... It's stupid. In fact, overlay my voice. Ready?
I'll go for it. It's just the controls are fucking dumb. Like, I press the button,
it didn't do anything. Like, it just doesn't really hold up. Oh my fucking god. This is
so stupid. How? I clearly was grinding that rail. I just... It's so unbearable. Okay,
so I would like for you guys to clip that over. Just lay it on top of it.
Better actor than people in the game. Okay, I need door A2. What game is this? This is...
I can't... I gotta... Nope. How's that for a Tony Hawk rail grind? Oh yeah, here's another
great one. This is another classic. I'm sorry, guys. I just... I don't have it today. I just
don't... I don't have it. I'm gonna try this one more time and then we'll see what happens.
That's a classic, right? No, I need A2. Is that an A2 door right there? Oh,
the invisible guy. Shit. Do I have any more heals? I don't.
No, don't rip around that way. Go! Wasn't there a locked door like over here?
The map is in the menu. Pause menu. Oh, okay. Where the hell even am I? I don't know what deck
I'm on. Okay, I'm right there. So I gotta go... Ah, this is not even that bad of a game. It
just isn't. So I gotta go out and then through. Is that A2, though? Radio room. Main passageway.
So I gotta go down the hall and through the door on the left. So I'm in the wrong room.
But can I heal in here? All right, so it's the door on the left. I don't know if I'm
gonna make it through this door. Shit. Why is this not playing? I had to queue it up, too.
All right, let's get Tony Hawk rolling. This game is kind of cool. It was. It wasn't that bad.
It was... The game gave you those key cards and you just had to kind of see where the
doors were locked. It wasn't confusing. It was... If I gave a shit, I would probably sit
there and play it for a while. He's getting defensive about this sucky game. What? I think
it's fun. But this is what everybody came here for. The best version of Tony Hawk Pro
Skater 2, if you ask any expert in the industry, ask anybody in the field, you ask anybody in your
friend group, anybody that you know. Tony Hawk Pro Skater 2 for the Dreamcast is the best
version of the game. That is just a fact and we're about to play. Somebody just said wrong.
I don't know. I'm sorry, but I'm gonna have to disagree with you. And the disc is not in
here. Tony Hawk Pro Skater 2 inside here is actually... There's a mistake. The disc is
not in here. This is actually Shenmue 2 is in here. So I got scammed. Let's go put it in and
see what happens. All right, let's actually rename this Tony Hawk because I'm gonna be
here for a while because I love this game. This is no longer just a straight up Dreamcast
fuckface stream. This is now a Tony Hawk Pro Skater 2 stream. And I'm looking forward to it
because it's a great game. Now the real stream begins. But I want to touch... Stormy Chu gave
$50 earlier and I need to address it because that's a lot of money. Pizza hut burgers taste
like boogies and you know it's true. Hungry Howies is superior in every way. Also need
to remind you that you're the best streamer and can always make me and Chad have a good
laugh. That's good. Thank you. I've never heard of Hungry Howies. I don't know where that is.
By the way, Rip Vod is a rest in peace to the Vod. But I'm not going to turn the music
off in this game because it's one of the major parts to play it. So sorry.
This is the best Tony Hawk. This is the classic. It's the best. They will never make
a better skating game than Tony Hawk Pro Skater 2. And everyone that wants to argue
what about Skate 3? Well, I've never played it. So I've heard it was okay.
All right. Tony Hawk Pro Skater 2. Let's get some stuff going here. I could create a...
If I could... Want me to do like a full career? Yes, of course I'm going to do that. Welcome
to the next eight hours. I can't wait. I'm so excited. I actually am. I've been waiting
a long time to get this greencast controller in my hand for this. But unfortunately that's
going to be the end of this night's stream because I have some stuff I got to do tomorrow.
But really though, I'm going to go pee and I'm going to get myself prepared. I'll be right back.