Hey. Good afternoon. How are you? Am I on time finally? You're on time. I'm on time too.
Just barely. You were sitting there looking out the window waiting for like the electrician to
show up in the window and it was like 358 and you're walking back and forth pacing like this is
unfucking believable. Where is he? Should I call? I'm gonna call the manager and you have the phone
in your hand and right at 359 the truck pulls up and you're like yeah you made it okay you made it
but here's the thing it took me like four or five uh seconds afterwards to put my pants on
so I'm like sitting here putting my pants on like getting ready to come in here and I technically
it's like it's 402 right now but I the truck pulled up at four get your pants on dude I swear to god
so so twitch let me tell you something about like something that doesn't make no sense
so if I stream to the test server like the twitch test server I don't I drop like no frames
the second I actually press the go live button and stream to the fucking actual twitch I drop a
thousand frames what the fuck is this it doesn't make any sense like there's a test server to make
sure that your stream is gonna work and instantly I was running that for like an hour and fucking
instantly to the same server I actually turned the stream on not going to the test server and
10 percent of all stream frames are dropped what they're the same server it's the same so I gotta
talk to twitch about this because that doesn't make that make no sense why on earth would I
drop the amount of frames that I've dropped in an hour of testing to twitch's server this
test server is the same server as the one I'm streaming to right now huh what maybe twitch
can help me route it somewhere else oh my god you gotta be fucking kidding me you gotta be
fucking kidding me this is really really really fucked up I wish I had any idea why this is
happening the second I actually go live
it's going to the same place twitch what's happening to me why is this happening it makes
no fucking sense nobody can tell me why this is happening well anyways hey I know how to fix
this problem hurry up turn on the fucking facecam nobody will remember your your 2000 drop frames
in 10 minutes not even five minutes this is like as bad as it's ever been but I got a black t-shirt
on what I'm just staring at it for a little bit this is a comb stream so nothing matters today
your webcam is 60 fps now I ask because I tweaked it is this stream canon no none of my streams I
can't they're all extended universe what the fuck I'm out of here I'm out oh I'm out of here
why there's no fucking logical reason for the shit anyways uh hi guys welcome to the stream
it's uh with 3000 frames so far to the to the same server I was just streaming to
I was just streaming to the Los Angeles server but not broadcasting out to users
and I press the fight to delete the fucking test broadcast button
and go live with a regular twitch to the same server and it's fucked oh my god
would it look good with one of these like let's look like one of these like little hairs
I was like what do they call this try it under the nose would I look good with one of these
that's like saturday morning cartoon villain whatever was bent a little which fucking like
moron Mario uh cousin of mine hold on I ain't gonna I ain't leaving I ain't fucking going
anywhere with the power of my mind I'm going to make this work all right I'm gonna like pass
myself out uh don't do that it's the Jim Carrey Robotnik but here's the good thing about this
though uh this is this is just comb stream so but that doesn't matter I want this to fucking work
oh pack it up pack it up I'm moving pack it up put everything in a box I'm fucking out of here
just get get all my shit in a box I'm fucking out of here I'm going somewhere with fiber
doesn't mean I need to leave Las Vegas by the way fucking 4,000 drop frames in not in nine minutes
I don't think I've dropped 4,000 drop frames in two hours last night do you understand how this
makes no sense like is anybody in here like a networking person to even describe to me
why last night this is not even 24 hours ago it's green for fucking like six hours straight
and then now it's it's like it don't even want to breathe it can't even
breathe like somebody's strangling it right now it doesn't make any sense an hour at zero
let me try something let me try something nobody move everybody stay there getting throttle I this
is a $400 a month business line they they they don't throttle those customers they can't this is
like a Cox business line oh it's not throttling it's not speeds are fine hold on I'll be right back
I'll be right back I'm gonna try a different server I have no idea it got it got like
exponentially worse oh if I if I wasn't if I wasn't like a nice human being I would scream as
a lot as I could right now it would just be like it would reverberate it would reverberate like
back and forth over all your ears I would peek I would not I would yeah you ever see um okay you
ever see kung fu hustle for the lady like takes the whole drag of the cigarette and like blows out
the whole like like the block and all the windows and stuff by screaming that's what I would do
right now I do a comb scream but it has it gets it has to get better it's gonna get fucking better
it always does it just it I'm fucking cursed forever I have to be cursed there has to be a
curse put on me what somebody take it off take it off take this curse off take it off whoever's
got it on me take it off I will I will go bring like I'm gonna bring like fucking incense in this
house I'm good I'm gonna fill this room with fucking incense and I'm gonna conjure up the
internet demon and I'm gonna sign the bottom of the paper it's gonna be like are you sure you're
like want to sell me a fucking soul to have like stable internet for like a while yes yeah I don't
care do whatever you want with it you're sure about this like most people ask for a fucking
trillion dollars and like a billion dollars no no no no I don't care well holy shit I'm making
out like a bandit no I know it's gonna be worth it look I wait you wait you don't want to like
wait you don't want like world peace I do but fuck I need that internet I need to work
I got a real long name I don't know what to do I'm just gonna go I'm not leaving yet I might try I
might switch another server I'm blinking look at how much I look just look at look at how much I'm
blinking right now the amount of blinks per second oh my god hey we've been up for four minutes and
I've only I've only dropped 20 percent of every frame that's been uh broadcasted out to you guys
I'm fucking believable have you seen any good movie hey you see any good movies it's a literal
slideshow wow did you guys really just respond to that how long did that take to get to you guys
I'm gonna try I'm gonna try one more thing hold on I'll be right back pause everything hang tight
I'll be back in like five minutes I'm gonna try one more thing and then I'm going to scream into
my pillow and like cry I'm gonna like scream crying into my pillow like instantly you know
instantly scream crying I'm gonna that's what I'm gonna do I'll be right back give me five
ten minutes I'll be right back I'm gonna try again I'll be right back I'm gonna try hello hello
hello hello we've got some testing to do we're gonna do some testing are you ready because
this tree might have like a 10 second delay on it are you ready I'm gonna snap my fingers
and you tell me when you're hearing ready in the chat and I want to say
you have to say I heard it ready really do it again ready so this time you're gonna say
what okay so uh what what has happened in the time that I have not been here
I have done a few things I have downloaded and set up a uh a packet loss prevention
VPN and strangely enough I think it worked look at this it's green it's it's green it's been green
for like 25 minutes okay I'm telling you I'm I will tell you the company's name if we okay
here's the thing right right hold on hold on if we get like a couple days of complete green video
oh I will but you'll it'll I will give this company as much attention as they want
I will shake the goddamn CEO's hand on camera I will shake their hand on camera and take like
fucking president photos with them because seriously like if this works it's been hell
trying to get this to be fucking fixed it might we may still drop frames but I don't know if
it'll be as awful as it is I don't know I'm willing to try anything did it cost anything
it was free to try and the amount of data that I'm going to be obviously pumping through
it costs money but here's the thing this service is this service is not free after you do it for a
while actually it's free up to a certain point but let's not talk about let's just let's just
stream and see what happens let's just do a live stream and see what happens but I will tell you
it is cheaper than you think it is okay for a whole year of this service it is cheaper than buying
one Nintendo Wii game if that gives me a green fucking bar for a year that's worth it it is a
pay service how much is a Nintendo Wii game a Nintendo Wii game is 50 dollars so on in my
opinion in my opinion what's happening what has been happening well I don't know this this is
obviously too early to talk about this but if this is fine and it's back to normal then the
issue is about routing the connection somewhere along the way Cox has these routing fucking
problems to whatever servers I'm trying to go to but I'm not gonna I'm just gonna let's just turn
on the let's just go I'm not gonna tweet this out yet because I want to make sure that I'm gonna
I want like 10 minutes of green I had the exact same problem a couple months ago and my VPN fixed
my problems too and this is specifically this is a packet loss preventing VPN I don't know where
the fucking data is going at this point I I could fucking care less where where happens to it I
I don't care does it work oh hold on a VPN might be like sniffing out I don't get I don't give a
shit this is a green do we have a green light I didn't get a chance to comb this fucking hair
once on camera and now it's like it's it's it's too it's it's too like corroded I my hair is too
corroded it was wet you're giving people your so no it's just it's like what okay it's a credit
card and it's a service that's reviewed very highly okay this is not a low reviewed service
it has pretty decent numbers no it's fine it's gonna be fine okay I'm not giving look at this
hair and I didn't this is supposed to be a comb stream today no drop frames in fucking almost
10 minutes are you kidding me are you kidding me and I got like a big zit over here that I'm not
gonna show you you downloaded a virus well this virus sure does make my internet work better
okay I don't care well what if it's like sniffing out your packets oh good I don't give a shit
whatever you're gonna see me go to like fucking like my mail and open up like my bank actually
that's probably bad I'm gonna do okay from now on I'm gonna open up my bank account stuff on my phone
oh shit maybe I should uh no but honestly God what they're gonna see me play like
what's they're gonna see what steam game I bought yesterday not that I don't have a very fucking
crazy life but I probably had to just do everything on my like phone now you have protected traffic
exactly I'm fine everything's fine I am just like kind of I'm pretty manic right now I've got like
pretty like big I got like mania right now because this is almost 10 minutes of no drop frames
and it was like 20 minutes of no drop frames before I actually turn the stream I'm going
through this service and you're not you'll get a name soon you'll get a name soon I don't know
why I'm holding that I'm holding back the name because if this drops to zero in like the next
20 minutes and like it didn't even do anything you'll get the name soon don't worry nice hair
I've it's I've got it all wet and ready get an affiliate affiliate link I don't even know if
they do that you're gonna break the spell if you say the name yeah I'm not I'm not no I'll never
say the name this is a good sign though let's see if we uh we stick with it so uh anyways uh you
almost just saw the zip and then that's that's no I don't want that so let me turn the camera
off for a second show the zip no you'll see it randomly it's huge he's getting stressed zits
what's actually happening tonight I okay I have a bunch of webpages open I have the tier list open
I have an online rorschach test I have a personality test I've got cool math games
I had a whole thing going is it do you think do you think it's ready to tweet out
once we get 10 minutes of green I'm doing it all right let me write I'm gonna write green
and then uh put my my twitch link I'll be the happiest boy in the world if this shit actually
like completely mitigates the problem but you can't have completely perfect internet
it's impossible no matter where you are but like drop in like 100 frames here or there drop in
like you know a thousand frames like every like hour or so but that's fine if if this service
gives me that I'll shake the CEO's hand on camera all right well we got I can do it all right let's
go come on stay up let's do this you can I will shake you whatever uh okay so whoever the CEO is
whoever you are I don't you know the CEO of this company you know you know who you are maybe you
don't you don't because I haven't said the name of the company but when we meet I'm gonna give you
I'm gonna shake your hand and we're gonna like go in and I'm gonna like I'm gonna give you like the
dad on the day of the wedding like the well the here comes the bride and and and the dad and they
walk down the aisle and then he shakes he shakes the groom's hand and he leans in and he always
like said something he whispers like a bunch of encouragement that's I'm gonna do that I'm gonna
be like there it is it's gonna be like fucking flashes everywhere
while I'm shaking and I'm gonna be like smiling like well I don't want to get I don't want to
get this is it side but you know smiling and we lean I'm gonna lean over and just be like
I'll tell you something this is gonna be like yeah yeah like you really fucking helped me out
here you really saved me thank you so much for everything there's like fuck 10,000 cameras
am I in am I those are flashes cameras we got no drop frames set up the meeting set up the meeting
those are those are cameras what are you talking about flashes of cameras what are you talking
talking about all right let's just get it out of the way so people like just stop asking about it
there it is that developed in less than fucking 40 minutes oh my shit just popped
hey hey it's fine everything's all right we're good okay give me that give me that
fucking hand back whatever you're done oh get off of me it's fine we're fine and that was like a
little dip that was a little dip that was a little dip that what oh that was just a little little
like these little dips imagine like okay so like this is the scenario we drop like a 10,000
frames right now it's like oh set up the meeting with the fucking ceo set it up
pulling up in like the limousine and like he's getting out of his limo and there's like 10,000
reporters and they're like all of a sudden I look at my phone and I have like 10,000 drop frames
I'm just like oh shit ah we're gonna cancel the meeting we're gonna cancel this meeting
what is this what have you linked me I don't want you to see my zip
no don't touch it it'll make it worse it was the the rival vpn cox help one of the world's
funniest people germa985 is having internet issues and there were 5,000 people excited to watch his
stream is there anything you can do cox customer care please have them send us a tweet so we can
investigate guys this doesn't do shit the these like customer care lines on twitter are bots
they're not real that I don't think that's a real person because I'll tell you here you want to see
the hierarchy of support with these internet companies it's like here you go ready
ready here we go at the top ceo of cox the it's infrastructure the guy that owns the company
okay then there's like the other people like the other employees that are underneath that guy
they're like suits right executives board members executives these guys these guys just play golf
they don't even know what's going on these guys just like play golf and like drink expensive
whiskey they don't they don't do anything like that they don't like oh what's happening what's
happening on on that street down in vegas now that guy he doesn't care right let's turn this
off because I don't need any more of this so underneath that okay underneath that you've got
so here there's that this that's block one here's block like two three four five so that those guys
those guys will never know my name right why would they underneath that you've got um like
the supervising team and these are the people that like actually have to pay his edge and
and take care of things right and there's there's like a million there's like millions of customers
okay so avoiding this showing this is it you're you're very you're very observational uh yes you
are we're doing the profile today let me just get it out of the way okay there take a screenshot
of this not take a screenshot of this those are the same people that was the same person
you have fat don't push me today because i might rip these fucking handles off the chair what kind
of somebody asked what kind of chair i have i don't know fucking staples whatever it is
oh anyways okay so the here here is the the the rest of the rest of the pyramid
that's not to say that this is a pyramid scheme but i'm just saying it's it's like
shaped that way whatever so you got underneath like the supervising team you've got the guys
that come out in the truck okay guys that actually fix the nodes and they do the neighborhood work
and they do the maintenance they they work hard they do because they travel around all over the
place they've got tons of fucking complaints that's like the supervising team then underneath that
you've got like the techs that come out to reset your modem that just reset everybody's modem and
that's all they do they just go out and they go oh i guess i need to reset your modem i think it
is that that's like down here there's like a lot of that okay underneath that underneath that is
like the phone support and i'm talking about what people what people can do right i'm not saying that
like any job is more or less valuable what i'm saying is like the guy in the truck can do way
more than the person that's on the phone down here right so the person on the phone that you call
customer support is what they're capable of doing is telling the guy up here to do something about
it one of the those people here that guy then has to tell somebody up here to get actual do some
stuff in the truck and get it worked out right that guy then has to talk to one of the fucking
suit people to find out if they need to do more infrastructural work right that guy then goes
into the fucking throne room with the guy with the gold throne and he's sitting there like this i
imagine the ceo just sitting in like a golden throne like like a king and the like peasants have
to come in and be like so excuse me oh neil before sire uh over on uh in in and bumble dune down the
street we have um 10 000 dropped frames sire it's hard for us and he just said like 10 000
drop frames oh that's that's pretty bad but you know over there in in fucking england too whatever
we're gonna call it i had 25 000 dropped for and they have to make a decision right so then i get
up and i have like i got like the look i'll do the other side so it makes more sense for you
sire you have so many dropped frames and my family needs to use the internet and go to amazon
and buy cases of ocean spray juice because that's and small small figurines of venom we need to and
then he gets he looks over and he finally makes a decision right so when that determined when that
person has said it's 20 minutes by the way only 400 drop frames that's not bad so
my point is the person on twitter i'm talking about what they are capable of doing what they're
capable of doing if i were to send a tweet to cox customer care twitter or the guy that drives the
bus down the road i think this person would be able to do more for me that person would come out
and probably like oh something's wrong there i don't know but i what do you mean all right
i'm gonna be serious here i'm gonna be real get the comb out of my hair do not leave leave these
people alone don't do that don't like harass any employee that's not cool don't fucking do that
you guys are better than that but i really don't think that i that that i have like people up here
that are currently aware of it my point is is that that process starts all over again the people
that like are on the phone that are down here somewhere that like have to relay and relay and
relay i've already done that like seven times we've already relayed to the supervisor to like the
field supervisor to like the real super like they know they know they know the problem already so i
going to like the cox customer care twitter is the essentially calling cox customers care
like on the phone and being like hey uh my internet just turned off for the first time
there are people up here that already know did you tell them that i'm driven 985
no have i changed providers i haven't i can't i you can't there's only like two all right so but
all bullshit aside this is 22 minutes i think i can start this frame now okay so you're saying
that you don't enjoy it is not it's not let me get this on the screen it has nothing to do
but the people that are working for cox they can't like there's only so much that they can do
it's not like their fault it's not their problem it really isn't it's how i've been explained this
like a thousand times by various people and you know let's just find out who i am as a person
shall we that's who are you how are we doing we're good i think we're good all right let's
i combed my hair like twice it seems to be better he's going he's he's he's very manic right now
where is it where's it is it not on screen hello let's find out who the fuck i really am
that's what this is what we're gonna start with what a transition like i'm fucking like
unhinged like talking yelling and making noise what kind of poop what kind of personality do i
have he's already fucking losing his mind all right let's do it i let's move on what do you
guys think i'm gonna be do chats personality we can do that this is a comb stream and what is
it how a comb stream works if you if you're brand new to the channel it's just like you know we're
just like hanging out i don't fucking know okay like look i i just spent the last like 45 minutes
crying so i'm trying to like get back into into like i'm live mode and sometimes you can't do that
all right here we go here we go i was just screaming crying into a pillow just give me a
break here we go i mean i drank all the coffee fast and easy it's gonna take it's gonna take
like 40 minutes not gonna take 12 i'm gonna answer these questions as truthfully as i can
okay i'm not gonna bullshit i'm not gonna lie i'm gonna go piece by piece i'm gonna i'm not
you're gonna get the real me here okay do you enjoy vibrant social events with lots of people
yes i do i love talking to people i love complaining about the internet to people pretty
much every conversation i have nowadays with um with other people is about like either like the
zip that's on my face or about an internet problem that i'm currently having so yeah
i know i love talking to people i do you often spend time exploring unrealistic yet intriguing
ideas all the fucking time there are there are streams that i have tried to do that just
completely unrealistic we're never ever gonna happen but i tried anyways i have like stuff on
my mouth am i like frothing at the mouth am i like turning into like am i turning rabid
ow this is what i'm talking about i can't like comb my hair on these streams now
my hair is turning into like uncooked ramen noodles okay your travel plans are more likely
to look like a rough list of ideas than a detailed itinerary i i like to have some kind of plan
but not completely outrageous i feel like i'm getting these wrong because like they're all
agree all right no no no okay that that's correct i do i like to just kind of go and do i like to
plan now hold on i plan some stuff but not everything some stuff is is really really
highly planned and mo i would say more than yeah you often think about what you should have said
in a conversation long after it's taken place no i don't i don't i don't give a shit i mean i'm
not one of the okay hold on i'm not one of those people that's just like no because i i look i
just say the things i say i don't like think about long after their conversations over what
i should have said no i've just said it what about years later if your friend is sad about
something your first instinct is to support them emotionally not to try to solve their problem
well it depends on what they're sad about like okay if it's let's say it's like a like a little
kid like drops the ice cream on the ground just go i can go get another ice cream and there it is
and it's not i just solved your problem in a minute right okay what but what if i could see
that's a bad parent wait what do you mean bad parent hold on so if you're like kid dropped
the ice cream full ice cream on the ground you wouldn't go get him another one what if they were
like but i okay what if what if like the worker like didn't get it in there well and it just like
fell out and like oh god and the work was like oh yeah you're right i didn't secure that i didn't
secure the ice cream in there good enough the ice what what all right besides that you didn't secure
the ice cream you have to take them with you to develop what do you what just don't drop it
because i would buy my son or daughter an ice cream that they dropped on the ground or try to
get another one that makes me like a crazy person what the fuck are you talking about
all right but uh i would i would do that first i would just try to support and then maybe like
how do we maybe fix this right yeah people can rarely upset you it depends on the day because
like i don't know some days some days somebody could like hit me in the face with a door and
i'd be like oh oh you know well people are people are blood all over my mouth people are clumsy you
know it's okay don't worry about that have a wonderful rest of your day you need anything
like some days it's like that but other days somebody could literally sneeze like 15 tables
over and i'm just like stop don't fucking sneeze i don't know it got it i caught that you know
i'm saying it's not like it depends on the day that's probably right in the middle because
sometimes you just are irritated sometimes you're just like having a good day no it no right in the
middle all right let's go next page i'm only 10 percent of the way through this it was said 12
minutes you often rely on other people to be the ones to start a conversation to keep it going no
strongly disagree i'm always like throwing out fucking shit to talk about i'm always just like
hey what about this what about that what about this what about that so yeah i i'm always want
to start conversations if you have to temporarily put your plans on hold you make sure it is your
top priority to get back on track as soon as possible no unfortunately not that disagree but
i they come back to normal like they gradually come back you rarely worry if you made a good
impression on someone you met so like i don't really worry if i make a good impression
i wouldn't say that's a strong agree because like i i don't know i don't really think about
that too much but not that completely oh i don't give a shit you know what i mean
no i think that's correct you always talk about people coming in here for the first time
this is my first time watching and you suck well that's interesting because you have a four month
sub badge that would be uh very odd god do you see that vein is that healthy that was big
that means i'm healthy right that means like there's a ton of blood going up into my brain
right okay no that's great it would be a challenge for you to spend the whole day
no it would be a challenge for you to spend the whole weekend all by yourself without feeling
bored yeah i can't i have to like i feel like it'd be somewhere i have to be with somebody
something yeah that would be a challenge maybe not that much because sometimes you do
want some alone time right okay you are more you are more of a detail oriented than a big picture
person i just i'm a big picture you are very affectionate with people you care about yeah i
think so somewhere in here you keep asking us about the answers for your personality yeah but
i mean come on 10 minutes by the way you have a careful and methodical approach to life absolutely
not you are still bothered by the mistakes you made a long time ago no i no i oh shit strongly
um what about the book no people you grow you know what i mean you grow you learn you grow
and you become the person that you are no i i just i kind of disagree at parties and similar
events you can mostly be found farther away from the action i don't know does this imply like the
the dance circle at the wedding because like okay there's the i love the dance circle at the wedding
but i don't really like the when it gets when it gets too crazy you know the dance circle of the
wedding is fun and then you're like all right i want to go back over to like the bar and just
sit around and like watch so i don't know probably like right here now jerma lied about the clown car
just gave five community subs thank you that's five community subs right now it's a fucking lot
thank you so much jerma lied about the clown car big subs don't look at that
you often find it difficult to relate to people who let their emotions guide them
somewhere in the middle because i don't know because like sometimes i think there needs to be
a balanced approach to stuff like that maybe a slight disagree because um i i i'm i'm fairly
like emotional for certain things i said don't answer neutral yeah that's right i did one neutral
i know i'm trying not to answer neutral that i slightly disagree when looking for a movie to
watch you can spend ages browsing the catalog no nope i just i don't care what it is i'll pick
something for fun um i here's the thing i actually do this thing this is fun to do
uh the next time you're on netflix or you're on hulu doesn't matter right a fun uh project is
to find a movie that you've never seen that you'll never watch that you're like i will never fucking
watch um i there's no reason why i'm gonna watch uh the other guys too right i'm just i'm not gonna
i'm not gonna do that there's no reason why i would do it i just i it's not a movie i'm gonna
pick to watch it's if it's on tv i'm not gonna watch it but what you do is you do the 20 skip
and how that works is you start the movie and you watch for about 60 to 120 seconds and then you
skip 20 minutes watch for about 60 seconds skip 20 minutes watch for 60 to 120 seconds skip 20
minutes and you'll get the essentially the 20 skip of the whole movie and you'll be able to like
just take it in you'll be able to see at least seven to eight minutes of a movie
and you're not gonna watch this fucking movie anyways so just have fun and just skip through
it and just see what they do just look at like the weird shit they do on camera you're fucked up no
but i'm not gonna watch that movie i'm not going to watch that movie okay think of movies that you've
scrolled through on netflix that you're just like i will never click that because i'm not gonna give
an hour and 45 minutes to um what the hell was the name of that movie the last one i did this
with was uh it was a will ferrell and mark walberg movie and it was uh what the hell was it
they were like dad dad's home daddy's here dad's home too dad's home too right what was it called
dad's here what is it called the dad it would where we are where the dad's too
no somebody knows what this is daddy's home too right no not stepdad um no gibson's in this movie
i'm pulling that hand away ever so slightly saved daddy's home too okay we're good we're good so
uh daddy's home too is the last one i did this with and i would do it again because there's no
way i'm gonna give two hours to daddy's home too i watched like nine minutes of this movie and i
i feel like i've already seen it there's a dad's home one yeah so no i just pick shit and just
will watch it for fun sometimes doesn't matter what it is you can stay calm under a lot of pressure
yeah strongly agree but i can stay real fucking calm now don't say that the internet problems
are cracking under pressure because the internet okay listen the internet problems
that's not pressure that is that is like that's not even pressure that is just extreme stress
you know i'm saying it's not just oh well something's happening today that i gotta be
calm about this is literally somebody just like throwing darts into your chest for like a year
eventually you're gonna be like can you stop throwing fucking darts at me like
you're gonna have like seven okay 700 darts go into my chest this is like getting 700 darts
thrown at you over the course of a year i i walk out the door like this is a you live a completely
normal life and i open the door sometimes and there's just the there's the dark guy and he's
just lining up the shot and you're like okay go ahead and he's just like hold on and it bounces
it doesn't go it's not gonna he didn't throw it hard enough for it to go and it just hits you in
the chest and falls down and you have like a mark that happens that by the way this happens like
two or three times a week after a year you're gonna like kick out the dark guy you're gonna be
like don't fucking get don't come in my house ever again he's gonna look at you like what don't don't
leave don't ever come back get the fuck out of my house and he'll just be like with his bag and
like his bag fucking darts on his back like okay all right bye you'll never see me again and you're
like yeah get the fuck out of here dart asshole okay fine bye you're never gonna see me again
the door closes and he's gone by the way two months later um a dart hits your like window
and you look out you're like that motherfucker and he's just like
and he fucking runs away he never leaves you alone so after a year of that you're probably
gonna be pretty annoyed with the dart guy but i mean i yeah i'm pretty good under pressure
somebody just get 50 bucks who was it don't look at that zip i was ryan hogs gave 50 dollars
50 bucks slender man kind of quirky kind of hitting that what is this slender man kind of
quirky kind of hitting that what's that mean i don't know what that is i i i'm not i can't i'm
not gonna read that i i does that mean anything that's it is taking up 80 percent of your face
right now why did you read that i don't know what that is somebody could have just
wrote random fucking words i don't know uh another 50 dollars just came in from frost throw these
bits are for your funny joke that's 50 bucks from frost uh tro thank you both to the both
of you there's 100 dollars in fucking two minutes 12 minute test by the way yeah but we have to like
interact and talk about this i have to go over let me comb my hair for an hour what funny joke
did i say a joke by the way you can always tell how far back somebody's hairline goes if you really
pull it that's not that bad i'm 30 fucking four give me a break i'm not like 20 like honest to
god this hair looks pretty good for a fucking 34 year old man give me some slack seriously you
know how many fucking 35 year old men i know that that hairline goes back to here i think i deserve
a little bit of slack it'll okay i'm not and when i'm 40 this will probably be all the way but yeah
i mean i'll be 40 though whatever you can't look like fucking 25 forever i'm not gonna get me work
done i mean you know maybe i'll get like you know that's not true maybe i might get like a chin
implant when i'm like 45 i'm thinking like a like a like a double like a two like a chin implant
and then like a eyebrow bone implant because i want to look like a banana uh ryan hogs also gave
five community subs so thank you for that 30 percent of the way for this test by the way
five more subs come and thank you guys when in a group of people you do not know you have no
problem jumping right into the conversation i can do that very easily i just go like hey i scroll on
like this and everybody like notices that you did that and they're like who's this guy was this guy
funny and then i go kind of and i like get in there and i just start talking about whatever
you got to get in there like this if you and here's a good icebreaker like oh like we're
at a party it's like rolling hey everyone's just like oh this guy this guy might be like a funny
guy don't do that by the way uh when yeah but i can when you sleep your dreams tend to be bizarre
and fantastical um does this count as like crazy nightmare shit i had a dream a couple nights ago
that there was this big gigantic thick paint wall of glass and they were like three or four people
around me then i don't know what they were doing they were like just hanging out right and they
were taking turns trying to run and jump and break the glass with their bodies this just was this was
like as big as a whole wall like in like a mural of like just glass i'm just like what the why you
guys do what are you guys doing they're just like yeah come on man and like running like making a
dent bang and like the little spider weapon breakout and then finally after like probably
six or seven more attempts at this one of them actually got through it was like he broke through
and he fell back and landed and like he got like cuts all over and he was like bleeding he was like
ah like screaming and like blood was coming out of his back and shit and i was like why why did
you do that does that count at least nightmares because sometimes they're like that yeah that
counts in your opinion it is sometimes okay to step on others to get ahead in life well they're
dialing up the questions into fucked up territory is it sometimes okay to step on others to get ahead
no it's not do it do it yourself do it yourself don't use people i'm talking more of like like a
strict like in in the in a don't use people don't like just step on somebody to get to the top
now get to the top on your own get to the top because you you belong at the top right you know
you know what i'm saying get to the top because like you belong at the top you know what i mean
i'm kidding i'm kidding jesus you are dedicated and focused on your goals only rarely getting
i don't need to even talk about that one if you make a mistake you tend to start doubting yourself
your abilities or your knowledge no i typically take take a mistake and turn it into something
else that works when at a social event you rarely try to introduce yourself to new people
and mostly talk to the ones you already know that's that's pretty that's kind of true i think that's
true for everybody though most people don't just go walk up to strangers and do the fucking thing
that i told you not to do people don't really do that if i if i would be introduced to somebody
from somebody else then that's a completely different story but typically you just kind of
hang out with the people that you were there with yeah that's accurate you usually lose interest
in a discussion when it gets philosophical ah that's like fun to do that's fun to do sometimes
i'm all about like hypotheticals and stuff it's fun you would never let yourself cry in front of
others no i've i've done it in front of you i've literally cried on this stream like twice you've
seen me cry twice for very different reasons by the way you feel more drawn to places with
a bustling and busy atmosphere than quiet and intimate ones yeah lash vegas come on you like
discussing different views and theories on what the world could look like in the future oh yeah
you know is a robot's gonna take over we've had these conversations over the stream what's gonna
happen in 500 years are they gonna write books about this yeah all the time when it comes to
making life-changing choices you mostly listen to your heart rather than your head yeah sometimes
yeah yeah you cannot imagine yourself dedicating your life to the study of something that you
cannot see touch or experience probably probably because i would get i would get lost i'd get lost
yeah that i'll get lost comedy oh wait i thought they were talking about like oh yeah you're right
okay but is that comedy that that's something there's no study of comedy oh what are you what
are you doing in college oh i'm a comedyologist that no you just kind of you don't like study
dedicating your life to the study of something you can experience comedy yeah but experiences at the
end that you cannot imagine yourself dedicating your life to the study of something that you
cannot see touch or experience i'm gonna go with i'm gonna go with this group because
i guess like comedy is like a thing i guess right there's no or here it's not the study of
or the experience of it's just the study of it's very clearly not meant as comedy yeah it is it's
like it's like what they're talking about here is they're talking about like religion and that's
mainly i'm assuming what they mean by this yeah what about physics particle physics yeah but the
particles exist okay you usually prefer to get your i thought that said massage you usually
prefer to get a massage rather than i'm like wait what usually prefer to get your revenge rather
than to forgive i've never like had to get i've never like had like revenge though before
revenge when have i ever had to get like revenge like maybe in like a video game world no i don't
know you make decisions on a whim all the time the time you spend by yourself often ends up being
more interesting and satisfying than the time you spend with other people it really depends but for
the most part no somewhere in here you often put social special effort into interpreting the real
meaning or the message of a song or a movie hmm that's tough i don't really think i do that
though no because every time i watch a movie that confuses me i just find the subreddit that the
movie is based on and read ending explained what did mean when explained and i just look at
somebody on reddit has like two paragraphs that explains literally everything you ever want you
go oh yeah okay cool so i don't like sit in a chair and have like a pipe in my mouth just sitting
there like hmm what happened in that tv show no somebody else will tell me no i don't
he trusts reddit no i'm just saying like it's somebody else like already somebody else already
has this is the thing about the internet and pretty much this is how it works somebody on
the internet figured it out already if this is something that you think that like hey wait
hold on is that what is that what's what happened in that movie i think no no somebody already
figured it out there are people that figured out the end of like every tv show and every like movie
in every book like years before they were even done so they already they said somebody else has
already figured it out that's why i just don't even use the internet if you're ever going to
watch a movie just don't go on the internet you always know exactly what you want no i don't
you rarely think back on the choices you made you rarely think back on the choices you made
and wonder what you could have done differently rarely look back so like i don't typically look
back and see what i could have done no i do i do you always try to figure out like uh it would
no i can't pick the middle one because this website hates me no i don't that often maybe
like once in a while no no i don't i usually just kind of stick with whatever happens
yeah i do when in a public place you usually stick to quieter and less crowded areas
no i usually like the hustle and bustle you tend to focus on present realities rather than future
possibilities no i'm always trying to think of like what cool thing could i try or do in the
future you often have a hard time understanding other people's feelings no when starting to work
on a project you prefer to make as many decisions upfront as possible some it really depends on what
they what what the thing is though no i do when you know someone thinks highly of you i mean like
all of you everyone here you also wonder how long it will be until they become disappointed in you
we actually talked about this like two days ago i don't give a shit about what people think about
me i give a shit what everybody thinks about me about flippy floppy no but that's different
though that's different because i thought when you know someone thinks highly of you this is
not flippy floppy because when this is a word differently when you know that somebody thinks
highly of you you also wonder how long it'll be maybe if the big yeah no that absolutely
because you want you want to make sure that they still think you're like cool they still like you
that they still happen like a good time yeah you feel comfortable just walking up to someone you
find interesting and striking a conversation no i don't here's the thing about walking up to
somebody and like starting a conversation everybody has this thing in their head of the conversation
that they're gonna have and it's usually the first like three sentences everybody blocks out the
first like two or three sentences and then after you have your pre-planned like two sentences that
you're gonna say uh-oh there's nothing else here um so like for instance right like oh hey you
notice that oh somebody's somebody likes garbanzo beans at the grocery store i love garbanzo beans
hey i love garbanzo beans those are really delicious here's like i got an interesting
recipe for like hummus that you could try okay cool hey uh those that's the best brand i usually
buy that bread it's a good one you're big i'm big fan of garbanzo beans too i got a recipe for hummus
that got my grandmother passed down to me okay i gotta go bye what do you do like everyone has
the two sentences ready okay let's go no i do not you often drift away to daydreaming but very oh
yeah you look after yourself first and others come in second hmm there's a reason yeah secure
your own oxygen mask first before helping others i just read that somewhere probably on reddit
no you can all right for me listen listen for me to be able to look after somebody else
i need to be capable of doing that i have to be kind of in the right mindset i've got to be
in a good spot i gotta be okay with me before i can be okay telling somebody else what to do
you know what i mean take care of yourself first make sure you are good because how can you expect
to like take care of somebody else if you're not kind of locked in on yourself you know what
i'm saying like think about that put your own oxygen mask on first got that on reddit
even when you have planned a particular daily routine you usually just end up doing what you
feel like at any given moment yeah self-absorbed streamer steals oxygen masks and claims they
belong to him if you have you have you ever been on a fucking airplane have you never been on an
airplane before that person never been on an airplane confirmed somebody gave 50 bucks 50
dollars from lacronda thank you lacronda for the 50 dollars 50 selfish streamer steals bits from
homeless viewer well no no thank you for 50 dollars but the the homeless viewer walked up to me
and like gave me 50 dollars and i and then ran away and i was like what the hell happened
the homeless i didn't say hey come over here give me that money no no i was just walking down
i was just walking down fucking twitch street and like somebody like came up and was just like
turbo hey turn up and i'm like huh hello yeah what's going on hey uh i had to catch up to you
you know i noticed that you like garbanzo beans yeah i mean i like garbanzo beans too
hey here's 50 dollars i got a recipe my grandmother gave me like like 10 years ago
and so you can make good hummus i love the stream somebody escaped say another person
just like straighten it up turbo hey it's 75 dollars whoa jesus hey here's 75
see you later uh that was from fly for shy fly for shy gave 75 fucking dollars after lacronda's
50 dollars this is a lot of money guys uh fly for shy just says thank you i got the comb look see
always look out for yourself fuck everyone else that's not what i said i'm gonna be missing i'm
gonna be misinterpreted this white screen is killing my eyes hold on i'm gonna i'm gonna take
care of that person hold on wait wait wait wait wait that's true let me like help let me help this
person out here i agree you're right hold on is it better that's better right is that is that better
is that better that's better yeah i'm sorry you know you're right i'm trying to say i was sitting
in the chair and i was i'm looking at the screen right now and i'm i'm good i'm locked in i'm taking
care of and i can see that it's not bothering me so therefore what do you let's go what do you need
i can take care of you now okay uh you are in it are you in a dungeon that would be a really
unsecured dungeon door i think i could run through that as if i went as hard as i could
i do if i ran as hard as i could into that and used my uh shoulder and and did it as hard as i
possibly could fucking do it i could crush through that door i could destroy that fucking door it
would be like it would explode it would be like boom i'll give you a hundred dollars if you break
the door i'm not breaking no that's not gonna happen yeah okay i'll take i'll take a hundred
dollars to have my twitch channel like permanently banned i'm not doing that that's another oh my god
so all right hold on uh jareden just somebody just ran up to me right listen to this so a hundred
bucks jareden gave a hundred dollars so they they sprinted up to me they gave me a hundred bucks
take it i'm like okay fine and then they said thief give it back is what they said here's a
hundred dollars that guy stole a hundred dollars from me get him you just you planted that on me
what am i gonna do i'm gonna let it go at that point i would just be like i i don't i have my
fingerprints on it oh i'm gonna put gloves everywhere i go now literally i'm gonna have like
like leather gloves so if anyone never does that i can just be like oh doesn't matter i didn't touch
it you know oblivion npc uh thank this oh a hundred there's a fucking shitload of money
thank you jareden for the hundred fucking dollars and the money that i i got the gloves on so it's
all right and fly for shy cave 50 i'm never gonna get through this personality test it's been like
an hour uh thank you they say really thank you thank you for the hundred fucking dollars that's
what should happen here thank you uh your mood can change very quickly you've seen it happen in
the last hour i went from the okay there's this this this is a vaude still right yeah
go back like an hour and a half when the first vaude was capped right and look at the mood i
was in there and look at the mood i'm in now that was in a second it was in literally less than 30
minutes yeah i can go all over the place you often contemplate the reasons for human existence and
the meaning of life no that's too much to think about once you start thinking about that shit
you start to you go down like the path and you're just like wait a minute what the fuck is this why
can i see you ever think about that shit why can i see i you i have like my own vr3d goggles on
like i can see in color no that's fucked up i don't even want to know you have a brain i know
but like why why can we do this why can you see why can you smell why do things smell why does
anything have a scent there are hundreds of thousands have gotten millions of different
smells why do they smell like that why do things taste differently shit's fucked up i'm not going
to pretend like i know why maybe sometimes we're almost done you have got detailed you have got
detailed education or career development plans stretching several years into the future
no you know what my career development plan is tomorrow and today and like september so this is
hey that's right there's a stream tomorrow yeah there's a stream tomorrow as long as this uh you
know vpn keeps keeping us at like pretty decent frame drops uh we'll keep using it you rarely
dwell on your regrets no like i told you before you gotta you grow spending time in a dynamic
atmosphere with lots of people around quickly makes you feel drained and in need of a getaway
i like going out with people you see yourself as more of a realist than a visionary it's like that
you know what i mean like if my if your brains are all in here my brain's in here but like it
occupies like this that's not saying i'm smart that's saying that whatever like like low iq
idiocy that's in here is not like densely packed into the brain it's like up like as an aura around
like all over here i got a pretty decent iq though you've already proved that you find it easy to
empathize with the person who has gone through something you never have that's hard to do you
like to try you like to try i wouldn't say that's i i disagree that much on that because everybody
has such different experiences you know if you have an experience and i have an experience and
it's completely different like the common ground is you know something you have to reach kim's
calling me out right now hey wait wait wait why why is kim personality doxing me right now
what do you mean i'm a realist a realist a realist okay a realist would have probably
a realist probably would have gotten like a job eight years ago i'm not a realtor kim called you
a bb that's not a guys that's not a personality thing that's like a like a cute terminology
that's not like a personality type she calls you a bb oh yeah i'm a what are you a realist
a visionary or a bb which one of these things are you no i'm a fucking visionary okay your
personal work style is closer to spontaneous bursts of energy yes than to organize consistent
efforts first bursts of random energy that's why sometimes i don't stream i don't have a schedule
right so like sometimes i it's like oh today i'm today i'm ready right let's go your emotions
control you more than you control them sometimes sometimes no we're good we're good don't worry
we're good i don't i don't think this service is going to let this turn off that's i look i can
live with that i can live with like nine eight five i have 900 i have german nine eight five drop
frames in an hour and 15 minutes look at it i think you guys can see it then nine eight five
somebody's fucking with me here turn off the vpn and see what happens no i've already seen what
happens we i was doing tests for like 45 minutes it was way worse all right let's go yeah after a
long and exhausting week a fun party is just what you need no no no no no no no i like going to
fun events and fun parties but no it's not like oh i can't wait to go to like a big party no no
sometimes it can be fun but not oh no you frequently find yourself wondering how
technological advancement could change everyday life all the time yeah like not every day but
yeah we just talked about it like 10 minutes ago you always consider how your actions might affect
other people before doing something yeah yeah you still honor the commitments you have made even if
you have a change of heart yeah yes because i don't you you don't you look i there's been a
lot of times when like i it's taken me a long time to do something but like i'm just so
scatterbrained you know like i what do you mean no pikachu socks who says that that's not gonna
happen i have to the end of the year clown car i have to you guys i've got i've got plenty of
time to get that situated just wait just just all right let's have this conversation with me in the
end of the year and tell me what happened fine i'll drop it down one i'll drop it down one okay
doki doki literature club i said on stream 10 times i'm never going to play that game that's
not a change of heart that is a real realist non-visionary statement i am not ever going to
play this game that's not a flippy floppy that's that's not a commitment the commitment was to not
do it so i think i'm doing pretty well yeah i think so you rarely feel insecure oh this is it this is
it this is it what am i your personality type is campaigner enfpa wait let's let's go over this
mind this trait determines how we interact with our environment 72 extraverted it's 28
introverted okay energy this trait shows where we direct our mental energy 69 intuitive and 31
observant i mean i'm pretty intuitive all right all right that means that means i'm smart
nature this trait determines how we make decisions and cope with emotions
30 65 just feeling this is the psycho trait by the way what this is the psycho trait
this trait reflects our approach to work planning and decision making prospecting 72
prospecting okay identity this trait underpins all others showing how confident we are in the
abilities and our abilities in our decisions assertive versus turbulent i'm very assertive
i'm a very assertive intuitive prospective feeling person okay here we go here we go why does this
look like this start reading hey all right introduction i don't want to read all this
hold on let's just get the tldr the campaigner personality is a true free spirit they're often
the life of the party but unlike types in the explorer role group campaigners are less interested
in the sheer excitement and pleasure of the moment than they are in the enjoying the social and
emotional connections they make with others charming independent energetic and compassionate
the seven percent of the population that they comprise can certainly be felt in any crowd
i am in the top seven percent of people right this is astrology why are they minecraft characters
you can change the world with just an idea more than just sociable people pleasers though campaigners
like all their diplomat cousins i'm a diplomat should i run for office hold on let's read let's
read the thing let's read like the part of the ign article that like everyone just reads and then
scrolls to the end let's see what the score is uh campaigners are fiercely independent and much
more than stability and security they crave creativity and freedom yeah don't lose that
little spark of madness wait what do you mean madness it's all right the care the campaigner
personality type needs to be careful however if they rely too much on their intuition assume or
anticipate too much about a friend's motivations they can misread the signals and frustrate plans
that a more straightforward approach would have made simple this kind of social stress is the
bug bear that keeps harmony focused diplomats awake at night campaigners are very emotional
and sensitive and when they step on someone's toes they both feel it what's a bug bear all right
let's go to strengths and weaknesses campaigners you may know oh shit really oh wait wait wait wait
that's iron man over here all right so all right that's that's really cool this is like
celebrities and people of like interest that's cool uh rm who's that so i'm like 20 iron man
20 percent robin williams 20 quit in tarantino and 20 percent no 25 percent holy shit that's
pretty cool that's not how that works i know i'm just kidding all right so that there it is i am an
uh enfpa what does the a stand for wait hold on russell brand brand kelly clarkson will smith
so this is everybody combined makes me all these people make me meg ryan michael scott
i get to be spider-man i get to be spider-man and iron man hold on why am i spider-man let's read
that spider-man why peter parker aka spider-man the personality type of a webslinger i don't i
don't even have wait you said i don't have the personality type of real people i get i get to be
spider-man i'm okay with that that's about minecraft spider-man does that count you have a fake
like cartoon character personality what you didn't get adam sandler you failed how do you know
i'm so happy i get to be spider-man wait a minute spider-man is enfpt i'm enfpa you william defoe
by proxy get to the end of the list come on load it wait is adam sandler on the list at the very
end oh hold on i have to click this button again okay let's see okay let's keep going will smith
spider-man the guy from modern family never seen that show firefly i just know that everybody loves
this you gotta be fucking kidding me just wait for the last one wait for the last one there's
one more on this list it's willy fucking wonka i'm i'm a combination of okay let me tell you
something i got both genies on that list just saying i got robin williams and will smith uh
iron man spider-man the genie and willy wonka and like carrie bradshaw from sex in the city
no i'm not the one i'm not okay you guys i know some of you guys are being a little bit of a dick
i'm the guy behind willy wonka that's real funny it doesn't say guy behind willy wonka it says
willy wonka not person standing behind willy wonka that was fun i like that i like that that
was cool i don't know who piper chapman i don't know who that is in this way isn't that the weird
guy that's like the weird guy that everyone thinks is like not funny right and like he's like a dork
that's the boss right and everyone's like oh he's the whole thing of the show is he's like not funny
and he like is a weirdo i'm gonna make a lot of people upset right now i've never seen the office
i swear to god i've only seen maybe two episodes ever i don't even know but i just know that's like
funny you've seen it i know everyone's mad russell brand quentin tarantino okay the u.s office sucks
hee-hee i don't know i know that there's like two different ones all right let me go pee i haven't
peed i've been sitting here for like two and a half hours trying to get this internet to work
let me go pee i'll be right back we're gonna do another one i'm gonna do i'm gonna do an inkblot
test after this i'll be right back let me know how the internet is keep an eye on it tell me if
it got worse okay so now we're gonna move on to the rorschach test tier lists yeah we'll do tier
lists let me just get this in the right spot because this website is a little weird so
let me get it over here i took that quiz and it couldn't be more wrong let's go here
because this one i want to make sure you can see it because the images are kind of small to go here
and then get me back here because look come on look at me all right so this is an inkblot test
let me just get this up out of the way it's like annoying me that looks so much worse but i don't
care is it dark in here all right so the inkblot test it is a little dark in here hold on it's too
dark in here that's better now you can see okay so uh the inkblot test also called the rorschach
test is a method of psychological evaluation psychologists use this test in an attempt to
examine the personality characteristics and emotional functioning of their patients
this test is often employed in diagnosing underlying thought disorders and differentiating
psychotic from non-psychotic thinking in cases where the patient is reluctant to openly admit
to psychotic thinking what um all right i thought this was just like what do you think this image is
a hundred dollars came in from haunted moon 100 bucks they just say party time for a party
thank you for the hundred it's been like five or six hundred bucks today just in the last like
hour and 10 minutes you guys are fucking unreal thank you i'm ready to go let's go rorschach test
okay what is this image hold on i'm gonna move this all right i see okay i'm not gonna look at
the answers yet i see there's two animals going like they're that's a they're holding hands it's
like a at the circus or something and they're going like this like they're like holding hands
together they're doing it's like a big presentation you know what i mean like this is the animal like
the bear or something and it's like flying his arms out or like they're presenting both
yeah that's what i see all right so what i see a face in the cards i don't see no i see a face
in the card i see a scary face things look like they're whirling around in the card looks like
we're looking down on people or something in the card or something it looks like we're looking
down on people or something i see a mask i see a flower i see sexual imagery um or i can type in
my own thing i don't think i want to type in my own answer things look like they're whirling
around like it's like they're like i said all right they're whirling at this two bears continue
all right just like just let's look hold on i'm not looking at the answers that's there that that's
two people doing the the mind thing you know when they go face to face and they both feel like i'm
moving and you're moving at the same time like the mirror they both have hands like this going
right right here look okay that's what i see it looks like a bunny rabbit looks like an elongated
horse head it looks like an x-ray it looks like spilled ink it looks like two distorted eskimos
playing patty cake it looks like a giant open mouth well i mean that's the closest one right
why is it an eskimo that makes them what the fuck are you talking about it looks like a tunnel
into another dimension or maybe new jerk is this a joke website like is this like a is this this is
not real or maybe new jersey okay i mean it looks like that like i said the two the mirror
all right this looks like like i see it's like a it's a okay face a face here and like these are
the legs and it's like back it's like a monster leaning forward those are the front legs and the
back legs could be back here hidden that's what i see look no it looks like the coast of italy
after and it looks like a pair of one-legged cannibals fighting over a victim i love pudding
is an answer that's the closest thing this is a butterfly a moth i would say it's a moth to me
moth you know when like you go into the science land to a site like an exhibit and there's like
the moth up on the wall thing that that stuff looks like the universe exploding coming at me
no no you idiot it's a butterfly it's been crushed by a boot heel ah that's definitely an
ink blot finish it what's that it finished it's not gonna be real that's like a skull
or like a butterfly or a moth again that's satan eyes oh i see a fluffy bunny rabbit i see a big
naughty shape what okay looks like a guy that was hit by a train it doesn't look like anything can
we have some lunch to me it looks like a mask it looks like you just threw ink on the paper and
folded it i'd say it looks like a mask but i'm not i don't really need to write that
what did i get what does it say let's zoom in sickness 70 sickness you're you have difficulty
concentrating on keeping on task probably because you're an idiot with this i'm not i'm not gonna
read it i'm not even gonna read it that was fun that website was from 2006 okay let's do a candy
list what what why is it not working you really fucked that entrance up didn't you what the hell
so what's the problem why is it not showing up oops it was cropped just the black somehow so this
is a candy tier list if there's a better one please direct me but this had the most that i
could find all right that looks pretty good uh unfortunately there are no charleston shoes on
here i'm already irritated hold on now you got a brightened screamo charleston shoes suck they do
they're terrible they're absolutely fucking revolting unless wait you put them in the freezer
put a charleston shoe in the freezer for a whole day and then eat it when it's out of the freezer
it goes from like an f to like an a a frozen charleston shoe is is really it's pretty great
that's cheating no it's not it's the same candy you just you're just like mutating it a little
all right let's do uh reese's pcs they're pretty good let's put them in b for now
all right hold on i gotta brighten my cam up i'll take care of that
i can brighten let me brighten up the room uh reese's pcs sweet tarts are on the same level
i think maybe not be a little lower you have you still have a comb in your hair it's a comb
string let me brighten this up a little bit with my uh my smart lights what color do you think i
should do no that kind of like make you look like i have like sicker like i have like green face
red blue whoa yeah that i forgot that's this this is the streamer color right
i like it good thing i have my like puppeteer outfit on so i could like be backstage the stage
hand all right where's your monster fridge all right let's go uh starburst i'm just doing i'm
preliminary reese's up here catberry cream egg hold on swedish fish fish no i'm gonna change this
wrong this is gonna be f lighten up the internet window is it i thought it was too bright
i was i was being screamed at about how how bright it was people were like yelling in my face
better are you gonna scream in my face i don't want you to scream in my face
okay that's fine all right so uh 100 grand let me change this by the way i want to change this to
um f and then this to trash trash f is trash no the trash is just like you wouldn't even
have it pocky i've only had it like once or twice i really don't like swedish fish i don't
jelly belly these are okay you eat two of these and then you fold the bag up and you that takes
you like three years to eat these you'll eat like one bag in like two years i think i've had the
same jelly belly bag i think i got i got some jelly bellies for christmas like two or three
years ago and i think i still have it yeah i'm not a fan and plus the toasted marshmallow is
the only one that's good in there and lemon is there a lemon lime one that one's pretty good too
am i a vegan admit that you're a vegan how can you admit something that you're not
tootsie roll is f tier as well it just tastes like synthetic chocolate flavor yeah i don't i
don't like it all right hold on butterfinger you can't you don't eat butterfinger what do
you mean so wrong a tootsie roll it just tastes and smells tootsie rolls tastes like when okay
we know when you have like the nesquik powder right you got the nesquik powder when it's empty
just like smell inside of that that's what a rese not a rese that's what a tootsie roll tastes like
a tootsie roll tastes the way that an empty nesquik container smells let's go up here and
butterfingers are too hard to eat when you bite into a butterfinger it just like gets all of your
teeth you have to sit there and go like all day they taste really good but you have to go into
every single crevice of all of your molars with like a pickaxe even if you brush your teeth a
butterfinger is still there i have an electric toothbrush that goes at like 500 milliseconds of
a minute whatever it's like and i it doesn't work i've eaten a butterfinger before and done
my super toothbrush and there's still like deposits of fucking butterfinger gold in my teeth
they still taste good but you can't i don't like to eat them all the sour shit goes down somewhere
at the bottom for me sour patch kids airheads may even be made out of plastic i don't know what
are they made out of once you okay there's like chocolate caramel and then this could be plastic
i like nerds though kitkats we'll fix this jolly ranchers are oh they're okay but i don't know
they fit in that weird category of you don't you can't have more than one and plus you can always
tell when somebody has a jolly rancher in their mouth because you can hear it it's how do i do
this without putting something gross in my mouth it's like you i can't how do i do this how do i
i was gonna put a coin in my mouth but i have not cleaned those coins actually i got it this is what
it's like when somebody's eating a jolly rancher what's up i don't like it but i'm sorry bottom
tier both almond joy and whiz mounds not very good i just did not very good i can't i don't
really love it you guys always talk shit about boomers this is the ultimate i'm a boomer and
here's the thing i like to eat this is the boomer candy it is it no that is that is it just is you
can like it but like my grandfather probably thinks this is great but i don't really like it
i can't place these yet snow caps are kind of gross what was the last time you even had a snow
cap i think the last time i had a snow cap i think i was watching toy story 2 in the movie theater
this is the last time i ate one oh what are these dairy milk spree fun dip
it's pez why are there two skittles no not naturally crunch is pretty good i'm not sure
i would put it above like Reese's Pieces though pez's shit yeah tell you tell me pez's shit
when you know that pez is like Campbell's soup you could literally eat it forever it doesn't
ever go bad does it am i making that up i made that up i don't know i might have just made that
up i don't like i'm not a it's all right i'll say the the snickers bar is not very good to me
but the mini snickers the mini little ones are up here so i'm gonna average that out
Cadbury eggs are down here it's too heavy better than sweet tarts it's the same thing it's not the
same thing it's completely different they they both have different textures they're just different
it's different because when you bite down on a snickers you bite through and there's the only
one end of the chocolate you get when you have a mini snickers you get all four corners of the
chocolate it encompasses it surrounds the whole bar it's better it just is you get four corners
of the coated chocolate on a mini snickers big snickers bite through one of those ends is like
peanuts and gravy whatever it is uh it's that's not the same somebody just said negative iq
some of you guys understand what i'm saying here you do Mike and Ike's that's D
these are disgusting i it's cinnamon i don't like this it's what it is it's just cinnamon 3.0
all the fireball is is just like this weird overly spiced latte cinnamon shit
i don't like it plus people drink this stuff as alcohol and it's i've had it makes me sick
what are these gumballs oh sprees sprees are the little chewy i gotta get this right right
sprees are the little chewy uh discs that have that really sour fruity kind of taste
i'm gonna make sure i get this right yes okay they go they go up here they have a little chewy
discs they remind me of mentos the fruit ones the fruit mentos but like a way better version of the
fruit mentos where why are fruit mentos not on here it's strange candy corn just should never
be eaten it's a decoration i wouldn't put a decoration in my mouth so why would i put that
in my mouth i'm actually kind of upset that one of my favorite candies is where's um where's three
musketeers three musketeers are one of my absolute favorite candies it would be up here
this is bullshit can i pretend one of these is three musketeers it's in the trash no it's not
lemon heads they're i don't they're on the same tier as like jolly ranchers and airheads that's
that same theory there are two pockies pixie sticks gross well hershey's kisses
huh hershey's kisses are actually kind of good but but they that good no these are warheads
the sour cave never had warhead before um i would put warheads up at s tier but you honestly only
eat one of these once every few years and you go oh wow that was crazy but that sucked i don't want
to do that again but you have this weird memory that you liked them i have a memory right now of
those being s tier but they're not at all they're just they're horrible why is it that every time
you see this at the store you go oh warheads oh cool man warheads and you buy them and you
fucking hate them every time so like in your mind they're up here but in reality they're probably
down here and that's a chad candy it's because of nostalgia nostalgia nostalgia am i saying that
word right nostalgia am i saying that correct why does it sound weird saying that no nostalgia
nostalgia that sounds odd now i can't say it anymore i don't like i mean pocky is
and i have only had it a few times but it's just like oh it's okay it's like i wouldn't choose it
it's better than warheads though it's probably it's better than butterfingers it is this is not
final just this is hope everyone's freaking out this is not a final list this is a general idea
and then we go from here dots okay dots are the equivalent to me of finding gum under a seat
sorry they're always okay why is it that dots are always seem to be stale
their dots are the stale bread of the candy world you put one in your mouth and it's like
took a little while to go through it almost feels like it gave you way too much give
it's not soft not a fan i also am going to make people pissed off here i really hate
twizzlers i think that they don't taste like anything it's just like it doesn't it i it's
like that weird taste it doesn't it doesn't do anything for me they taste like artificial
like i don't know how let me try to describe this i'll get it hold on let me use my visionary brain
um twizzlers are like the only thing that's fun to do with a twizzler i got it it's in my brain
i'm pulling it out somebody get like the fucking wand when you bite off both ends of a twizzler
and then you stick that into a drink and you drink up the drink with the hole in the twizzler
that's it there's no other reason to eat them in my opinion they're just chewy gamey it's okay
twizzlers are like the lamb of the kingdom that means it would be not that's way off it's like
chewy and gamey and i can't describe it you know what i mean they're not they're not good m&m's
nobody want nobody orders m&m's i'm doing this based on like if i was at a candy store what would
i get there are m&m's everywhere there are too many m&m's m&m's are the ant of the candy animal
they're just everywhere why am i doing these like weird analogies here there's so many m&m's
there are more m&m's than people on earth yeah i think that's true they're better than swedish
fish i feel the same way swedish fish and twizzlers are the same kind of flavor profile
for me and these also swedish fish also you open a bag and sometimes they just taste like stale
it's hard to like you you have to eat the whole bag in the first day i do they taste stale they
think hard to bite through i can't be the only person that thinks this i can't be crispy m&m's
are s tier uh peanut butter m&m's are way up here but regular m&m's are not i don't think
i'm beyond wrong uh laffy taffy if this was saltwater can i pretend this is something else
because i have to tell you my s tier candy can i pretend these are something else
no can i how can i how do i pretend let me just pretend these are something else
saltwater taffy is is s tier is the best candy ever nice soft delicious saltwater taffy is s
so but can i pretend that's what that is i don't want laffy taffy that's like the
fucking joke brand add images well i don't have an image of saltwater taffy i'm like
it's not my desktop background i don't like uh wafers either here's another one that you only
eat at a movie theater then they have that kind of they have that malty taste to them don't they
what is that i don't is that that weird like coated sour straw stuff double bubble
it's going up here i remember if you were like really good in class a teacher of mine would give
a double bubble you got like an a on a test there you go there's a double bubble for you
all gum is what it tastes good for one second better than bubble tape bubble tape is down here
double bubble is better than bubble tape look bubble look at look bubble tape oh i'm so old
bubble tape is old too that's boomer gum bubble tape is old they ran an entire commercial campaign
guys 20 years ago about how bubble tape was not supposed to be eaten by old people they did a
whole ad campaign with it was like the same like old librarian looking lady that would like be
going like dish into the camera and stuff and it was like skateboards and it's for you not them
bubble tape it's six feet of bubble gum for you not them that was the commercial so that was 20
years ago just wait better than pes i've just let me get these up here the rest of these are
i don't like those tootsie pops are much better than tootsie rolls because there's a new there's
a new thing there there there's like a variable included here do i like tootsie pops better than
sweet tarts i'll figure that out later mr good bar is interesting because uh i don't have any
memories of eating this but i've eaten a bunch of times this is the memory wipe candy because
nobody knows or can remember what this tastes like i know it's good this is one with a little
crunchies in it it's got the little crunchies in it right it's kind of like um is it peanuts
it's is it's it's peanuts it's some it's peanuts and something else though can we pretend this is
three musketeers what are these no no i'm thinking a crackle okay yeah you're right that is that i am
thinking a crackle oh dumb dumb these are little lollipops i love these these go up here dumb
dumbs are fucking awesome it's the perfect amount of lollipop they're this big they're like tiny
they're like this they're miniscule you just put it in your mouth it just sits in there that's the
doctor's office lollipop no no no no the doctor's office lollipops are flat those are the little
round ones yeah no no this place is i love it yeah definitely up there little dumb dumbs oh
you like dumb dumbs because you heard dumb dumb let's say that uh lifesavers should be up here
but they're not because they hurt lifesavers do this thing where after they're one of them's
in your mouth for more than um like 10 minutes or so and it gets to be really thin it starts
to become a knife that like pierces you and stabs you they don't dissolve fast enough they just
turn into weapons in your mouth and then if it gets to that point where you were oh this is
getting really kind of small now i need to break it it's like biting on glass and you like have
to be real careful they're good though they have a good flavor i would probably rather have a
lifesaver than a skittle what is this uh haribo i don't like gummy bears i wouldn't put these
i'd put gummy bears over okay i'd rather have a gummy bear than a hershey's kiss
the what was that like the the explosion here i just don't eat gummy bears a gummy bear
i that they're the these two are the same thing one of them you can chew through the other one
just is clangs around in your mouth these are the same flavor what i mean wrong despite i'm not done
i'm trolling i don't like gummy bears i don't i don't like gummy bears i don't like to eat
gummy bears i don't like gummy bears i'm not trolling everybody i just don't like gummies
i like peanut butter and chocolate and bubble gum i don't like gummy bears are we really gonna
do a fucking green eggs and ham segment with you guys here will you follow me around and i try to
get me to eat them and i tell you no plus i've had gummy bears before that this is like the
mcdonald's bread oh shit i can't say that i just probably made a lot of people this is like the
coca-cola of gummy bears right if you go into a candy store and they have like a local kind
of gummy bear usually they're much better terrible aren't they like the gummy they're like the
coca-cola kind of pepsi of gummy bears that's that's real right there are a lot of candy shops
that make their own gummy bears or they pull them in from some candy store and they're way better
i've had gummy bears before that were like oh those are fucking really really good
but not like that is the bag from the store should i pretend that these are not haribo
should i think that they are like other gummy bears because this is not this is not like
general gummy bears this is just what i thought about haribo oh god i'm being invaded are you
here to critique my choices again what's what's hold on what's wrong with these all right wait
let me ask you this would you put okay haribo gummy bears out of the bag right
like out of the bag what better or worse than like a local candy store gummy bear
oh we have a local candy store that's what i'm saying and they were and how much better were
they than than like the bag of gummy bears i like gummy bears though baby alert that is a baby
he's a baby hello i told you he just had a treat a treat yeah he just had a treat he's such a good
boy are you a good boy how do i miss you good boy uh all right so i don't i what's have you ever
had i you like whoppers whoppers i like whoppers yeah i did dad me too they're pretty good i put
them in like c up here probably better than um why is this bubble tape there it's just it's like
it's not there it's like a preliminary thing can you make trash put that in f no no no no
i'm not doing i look i gotta i under pressure i can't i can't all right no what do you know
oh no don't don't like brush my hair on stream all right i need i need to be in my own zone here
i can't have somebody off my shoulder critiquing my choices can you okay imagine if somebody was
just staring over your shoulder no no no no no what you did those races don't belong there
i'd you'd be like what are you talking about yes i do they know they belong here you're being like
you guys are critiquing me but this is like a real person here in the room going i can't imagine
there were like four thousand fucking people standing behind me i would be like in real time
it'd be like whoppers go down here and somebody you'd hear somebody like 400 feet behind being
like you're a fucking idiot don't be looking so i'm i'm sorry it's a it's a c tier i think
kim is your conscience let auto make the next decision auto what do you think
he loves everything has he eaten auto he's really dark in here hasn't he's a centrist candy man
no i i just look i don't like the soury stuff i don't oh yeah this is when i got really mad
what these no no no when you put the sour ropes on the bottom i don't i didn't i didn't remember
what they were i they're like these s tier all right cut the mic just kidding i'm just miming
do you think sour patch goes uh id or do you think it i think no i think it goes up to i think i
think you put jolly rancher down at uh somewhere around she's like what the fuck are you doing
never mind it's not gonna work i was thinking i was thinking of trying to get like auto to sit in the
chair like be sitting here and like he picks one because he wanted to but it didn't work out that
way like oh it's auto he's i'm not gonna do that more like get what do you what i don't know i
i got it i got it i got it maybe it would be funny like to have a scenario where like
i just leave stop stop stop stop saying that stop that this is a this is a this is a a pg 13
slightly towards our stream that's not we don't do talk about that on here whatever my she's like
brushing my hair well like just imagine my scenario you know what i mean i'm just like
doing a tier list about fucking candy and like my girlfriend's brushing my hair and i'm just like
what's happening i'm very easily distracted okay where were we oh yeah okay i'm they're gonna get
back on track here ring but where's ring pops there's a rossum where where are they somebody
said ring pops are trash no they're not what's wrong with the ring pop i think i would rather
have a ring pop than like a cadbury egg in fact yeah i don't know why they're up here this high
there's no right way to eat a cadbury egg and i'm not talking about like the racy campaign where
there's no wrong way to eat a rices there's no way to eat a cadbury egg if you bite into a
cadbury egg it's it like goes all over your mouth and all over your pants and shit if you put the
whole thing in your mouth at once it chokes you because it's too much you can't there's no way
to eat a cadbury egg that should be their campaign just swallow it whole just like that would hurt so
bad uh yeah i would put them underneath here all right probably below butterfinger too i don't think
i've ever i've never i don't think i've had these aren't these the same things as uh whoppers fun
facts our patch kids are s plus no they start to they start to hurt they start i determine if i
like a candy or not based on how many i can eat in a row before it makes me sick that sounds
fucked up it does but um i mean like how many can i eat in a row before i like start to not i hate
them and while a sour patch kid or a swedish fish may taste very very good after eight of them
you start to feel like shit i could eat like a two or three bars of twix if i eat like eight
to ten swedish fish they start to turn and cement themselves into one giant swedish fish ball
that sits down here like in your like down at the bottom of your esophagus it just it turns
into like a ball like bubble tape i don't know why people like this so much or even like this
is like a little bit different but bubble tape when you eat the whole roll you feel like terrible
afterwards it's like that chewy candy when you and you're supposed to like chew it and swallow
they got like a like a fruit by the foot when you eat that whole thing it's stuck if you feel
horrible i think there was one time i ate a whole thing of bubble tape and i was watching a movie
and i like almost shit my pants that's like eating a whole pack of gum it is a whole that's like five
packs of gum what was the movie toy story one all right everlasting gobstopper i'm not sure i've ever
had these really to be honest no i have they're like in that same category of like this kind of
shit it's like a jawbreaker this is just like a milk chocolate bar but they're oh they're good
i've had them before better than the eggs um oh this is the youtube surprise eggs i'm putting
them down here because i just don't i'm sick of seeing those in my recommended feed so no i don't
want to see them anymore 100 grand they're all it's like they're all right i don't really know
what these are laffy taffy not as good as real taffy is another one of those youtube surprise
eggs i don't want it who thought it was a good no honest to god who thought it was a good idea
to put little swallowable toys in food why would you do that is it like what do you like eat around
it do you break it in half or like what they aren't even in the food they're not i thought
it was like you isn't it like inside of the the food there is the little toy only americans
are dumb enough to eat those i what about like kids what about like little kids how would they
know see like do you are you supposed to just break it in half take the thing out and like
then eat the chocolate i would just put it in my mouth and like that would be like the coolest
surprise is like put the whole thing in your mouth without opening it and then like let the chocolate
melt around you while you move it around and try to figure out what it is before you take it out
of your mouth isn't that how you do it it's like oh i wonder what this is let me see uh it's a bike
right then you take it out and see if it's a bike they're inside of a container it's in a plastic
capsule i've never had one moving on i don't know what these are um are these the the chewy um
version of the jolly rancher what are those they've flavored tootsie rolls oh they're the fruit
tootsie rolls i've had these before i don't know where they stand are these um are these now and
later's uh i would put now and later's up here if every time i ate them i was not in fear of
ripping all of my teeth out of my jaw i've had scary moments before when i put a now and later
in my mouth and gone down a little too hard and it it's stuck here and i'm not going to get it
off without actually hurting myself sometimes if you do those situations where you bite down a
little too hard on now and later and you go well this is it i'm uh this is my i'm stuck here forever
now this is my life and you have to sit there like what do i do and then you do you like a
construction worker you like start to like get leverage around a molar and sit there and hold
and slow it too many bad memories it tastes good though please check hair we're good ow i can't
even comb it fleas you want to check me for fleas is he balding no i don't know what these are
oh they're runs although confirmed to me that those are runs those only exist in a globe at a
mall but they're fucking awesome those cost 50 cents banana runs are s tier yes they are yes
they are thank you for reminding me uh this we already have one of these up here so i'm going
to put this is three musketeers the rest of these these are i don't know i don't know i don't think
i've ever had this before doesn't belong in the trash but i never had it an arrow arrow have i ever
had these before arrow what are these i don't think wait are these hold on are these the ones
that are really soft and fluffy they you bite into them they're very fluffy and very like
puffy and chewy this is good this is really good oh man am i remember okay and they look like a shoe
right they're like they're like weirdly shaped they almost look like um like circus peanuts
do they have to okay do they have the consistency of a circus peanut do that they do they do do they
have the consistency of a circus peanut and no no no no guys guys guys guys not not a peanut that
you get at the circus this the orange circus peanut candy that exact that texture that like
chewy but fluffy circus peanut soft texture no people are getting really confused there is a
candy that is as old as time they were eating it in like the bible it's just called the circus
peanut they're bright orange soft chewy candy we know no but some people were telling me i that
they don't know okay so i'm wrong so i've done that maybe i never had them before i don't know
where they go i there has to be another tier these are bubble gums air bubble chocolate
i don't think i've ever had them but i feel like i have this is this is a another country right
all right settle down i'm ready to make my final decisions here this is three musketeers by the
way it belongs up there Reese's now if this was a Reese's egg it would go up here it's not if this
is the Reese's eggs the best it's not a Reese's egg i'm gonna have this go base Reese uh spree
definitely belongs up here as well three musketeers up there double bubble belongs maybe
up here dum dums they're gonna replace double bubble every moment i look at double bubble i'm
remembering the the dust that's around on it when you take a double bubble out it's covered in like
this weird dust like this white powder is all over it drop that's gonna have to drop it a few
points i'd rather have a twix i'd rather have a dumb dumb than a runt i'd rather have a twix
than a Reese's pc starburst have kind of fallen off for me uh recently so i'd i'd rather kitkats
probably up here in front everybody loves kitkats come on they like the best in fact i think that's
fair i'd rather have a kitkat than a spree i'd rather have a spree than a dumb dumb rather than
have a dumb dumb than a run okay twix yeah nestle crunch you get sick of this after a little while
though i could i could probably eat half of this bar and it would be a b-tier the other half of
that bar is probably somewhere down here okay i'd rather have starburst than nerds that dust is
fucking with me right now okay snickers no i don't not a big fan sweethearts are really good
mr goodbar is pretty good skittles are probably better than sweethearts no they're not what a lie
pocky is here twice um i can't get rid of it so just pretend that's up here fun dip and pez
ring pops are way better than fun dip milky way is better than fun dip and pez jolly rancher is
above that but well i just i don't chew gum anymore not really sweethearts are better than
dust gum are they are they though but okay when you unwrap a double bubble if you never had it
before just close your eyes and imagine this and those of you that haven't had it before
close your eyes and also imagine this because we're going to take this journey together
that when you put it you unwrap it's covered in like the gum cheeto dust you put it in your mouth
and that first two bites is like the first two bites of a double bubble i think trumps
everything down here did you experience it with me yeah like the first minute or two a double
but it's like um what's what's that zebra gum with all like the food dye and coloring and flavors in
it that you chew it for five seconds stripes yeah i would put stripes up here stripes would be above
would be up here because that there is a flavor that stripes gum has a flavor that has never been
replicated before it has this taste that you will never have again it doesn't taste like something
it doesn't remind you of something it just is what it is and it's it can't be fucking replicated
stripes gum was awesome skittles kind of have that same weird textural flavor to them
we're slim gyms this is candy man slim gyms they're bad feeling like on snacks
okay i'm getting uh sidetracked here those are gross uh ring pop and jolly rancher are like the
same thing for me but i would rather have a ring pop than a jolly rancher i'd rather have a jolly
rancher than a lifesaver i'd probably rather have a milky way than a good bar
or a tootsie pop no that's not true to default i would rather have a milky way than a snickers
though no i i don't think so i think i'd rather choose these than pocky sweets hearts belong up
here but does pez would i rather have a butterfinger or pez you got two people both on opposite
sides of the room hey dude do you want some pez yeah hey dude i got it you want some of my
butterfinger which one do i want pez because i would like to use a dispenser it would be pez
all right that's good for me i think i'd rather have this milk chocolate bar than a pocky that's
what they say pocky isn't good pocky is good yeah good then i could just yeah yeah you get it you
get a pez for the toy then i could just run off with the toy you know oh hey thanks with pez and
i like ripped a fucking head off and then start sprinting and then like give them you know that'd
be easy but pez tastes bad i actually don't i don't mind the taste of pez okay hair just fell
out no i don't hate pez i think i think that tastes good pez is another one of those things
it has that flavor that cannot be replicated all right this is important i would rather have
these gummy bears than sour patch kids i would probably rather have a warhead
i would eat the gummy bears over a butterfinger because it's really easy to be like oh i'll have
a few gummy bears you can't have a few butterfingers when you open it that's it and
they're huge butterfingers are too big i think i found the problem i i found the problem butterfingers
are this big it's like holding a hammer if butterfingers were smaller by default you can
get mini butterfingers but they're thick even the small mini butterfingers are really thick
if they were a little thinner do they make thin butterfingers that's not as much of like the
shaved ice that makes up the internal organ why is he in a cave what was i saying crispy
butterfingers are great yeah but do they are they thin i would eat butterfingers if they were thin
add an echo to your voice oh my fucking god hold on guys let me eat i'm gonna eat my jolly rancher
all right what am i doing oh an echo i can't i don't think i can even do that
i don't think i can add an echo to this hold on can i wait wait wait i think i can hold on let me
add let me add an audio input it's gonna be the webcam and i'm gonna delay it by like a half a
quarter of a second okay can you hear me can you guys hear me is it happening at the same time
all right here we go so i'm gonna delay this by like hello hello hello hello hello
hello no hold on this just became way more important hello hello hello hello
a little more more more how's that hello hello louder louder do it louder now i'm standing on a
cliff how what's that how long wait a minute hold on a second i'm gonna try to scare the shit out
of myself hold on let me see if this is possible does this do anything hey did it work i'm gonna
try to jump scare myself i'm gonna monitor this hold on okay this is gonna come through
all right you ready okay so what i want to do here is rices uh where do i want to put rices
how about put it up an s tier did it happen i don't think it happened wait hold on what is
10 000 milliseconds did it happen tell me if you hear it it's quiet when it happens is it hold on
this just became something that is way more important all right 50 000 milliseconds
i can't i can only do like 10 000 i think i can do i can do 50 okay 30 000 milliseconds no
i can do 29 000 no i can do 20 000 milliseconds that's as much as i can do all right here we go
that's the highest i can go is 20 000 let me i'm gonna i'm gonna scare the shit out of you guys
you ready what if i mute here and then it just happens at some point that'll work right
okay so i'm thinking haribo should probably go up a tier what do you think something like
five uh percentage points up it didn't work it should happen again wait did it do it twice
it happened twice oh wait wait wait wait wait okay so i think that if nestle crunch is somewhere
over twits that would mean that sweet tart can have to then theoretically be around there too
because they're both delicious they're both really good they both taste very well and i think that
they would be in a good did it did it did i did it work uh one more i think my favorite movie was
probably um i'm a big fan of toy story 3 was really good somebody asked in the chat i just
want to make sure that i got i answered it yeah story story three story four was okay too i
didn't i didn't i i liked it i think dots should probably go i don't know much what do you guys
think not f i don't think it belongs in f i think my favorite movie was probably um i'm a big fan
of toy story 3 was really good somebody asked in the chat i just want to make sure that i got i
answered it yeah story story story 4 was okay too i didn't that sounds so fucked up like what the
hell is going on over here what the fuck are we doing oh yeah i gotta turn this off i have
this it's okay it's no longer being captured get a soundboard to do this again all right i hold on i
do one do one more but this time i'm gonna like break this microphone because it sounds so strange
hold on just give me a second last one and then we'll move on by the way i don't know how loud
this is going to be so just prepare yourself prepare yourself
tends to be a little overpowering for me i like it when it's a little uh milder it tastes
good but no i don't think it's enough for um to have on a daily basis for your candy preferences
i live in the middle of this somebody asked why did you do pocky twice i want to hear it let me
see was that one any better that's like in that's my mind that's my mind that's about somebody
wrote that that's my mind talking record yourself from outside of the room no i want to i want to
see that one and then i'm moving on swedish fish
tends to be a little overpowering for me
why why does it sound like that there's no reason for it to sound like that
okay i'm done with that i'm going to continue now i'm going to remove this from my obs and
we're going to continue with what we were fucking doing um okay where i was over here
he's coming down oh my god i would rather have a lemon head than all this stuff probably not
gummy bears though you promised up you promised us a mambo number five lip sync i'm a liar i've
lied to you i'm not doing that shit i'd rather have 100 grand than uh what would you do with
100 grand oh i would buy a bunch of stuff and i would uh put it into a 401k what would you do
with 100 grand i need it for those that gets fucking knocked down like five points don't
minus two me that's not my joke that's their joke as you wish all right i'm done i think that's
pretty accurate for me remember this is a this is a three musketeers that's not a mr good bar
what a terrible list reese's kitkats sprees dum-dums is that really that bad of a list
reese's kitkats sprees dum-dums like that's those are very very very high quality
how is pocky trash no no pocky's not trash there's two pockies i can't get rid of this one
this is pocky's up here at sea why are m&m's and f because there are more ants
though they were what they were whatever the fuck i said there are more m&m's than ants
and people on earth that's why i said it crispy m&m's would be up here peanut m&m's peanut butter
m&m's would be up here uh my favorite german 985 chat memes i'm gonna do this one okay german 985
chat memes take a screenshot here because we're changing all right let's go with here we go here
we go do i even know all these i'm gonna try i even know all these myself hold on i'm gonna make
this a little bit smaller so i can make it grow up here this down here okay all right so uh next
is an instant disqualification so is that like that not i i'm not bald i clearly have hair in
my head i'm getting real sick of that one the slap has got to be up there if you've never seen
it before take a look uh cox just like i don't even want to look at that anymore
that's not even a meme that's just real life uh okay bald coin that's i put that at a f
the wait wait is this like what i think about the memes or because i the fuck the rumor too
i like qrs i'm gonna add actually a row like stop this nonsense that belongs in the stop
this nonsense category people just fucking that's not it's a doctored image i already know that
that image is doctored and it's this big on the screen uh okay uh i'm actually kind of a fan of
the uh abator germa craft germa's iq it's you guys use that to make me look like i'm stupid but
i mean come on pre-recorded plus two minus two plus two minus two is pretty fun still i think
is like still pretty fun uh pea pants is up there dyed to pinwheel is still all right still
pretty funny coffee cheetos chicken is pretty that's a classic come on i gotta go i gotta get
out of here is that a meme or do i just say that ban that guy up there that's not is that a meme
or is that me i just say ban that person from my chat room like ban that person is me telling
somebody is to ban somebody top 1000 streamer i just i automatically put that up there because
i mean i i am gambling gambling why did i say it like that he doesn't know blind
now i put this in f lmao no oh the nintendo labo goes up here mom's making cookies ice cream i
don't i don't even need to know what it is that's up there at s that's like the best ice cream ever
yeah it's still up here grill master is uh kind of jupiter's is still pretty good turn on your
face kit play tf2 all right again this is not a meme this is just something people say play tf2
loud p it's kind of down here i think mustache hair is you know that's that's it's just true
it's not even a meme at this point it's just for real uh cheeto is still pretty
cheetos cool she's cheetos cool william defoe what a great actor i beat dark souls 3 on stream i did
hmm hey look at how huge and handsome i was no down here a hot air balloon
it's up here somewhere auto i just i just love my dog so going in a this guy is
fucked uh somewhere in c i'm trying to the thing is i'm trying to think of what will last
right i know what won't last uh and that is like some of the stuff down here that like won't last
this stuff up here will has probably test of time type shit on it mom's making cookies won't last
because it's limited edition oh short will last you forever whatever you say uh photoshop those
are always fun late uh i i just i'm i'm not i just that's i'm just late sometimes i don't know well
i'm in an earthworm gym costume here oh that's life is pain okay that's that's still that's still
pretty good doing the tuber voice now i like that one a lot thanos is just it's just thanos
germacon or jexpo that's not even a meme that this is like why is it just like a raft here
what's with the raft uh this is kind of over it's a spill joke i mean i just it's not a joke i just
i spill stuff i get angry at games sometimes not all the time though eating ass enough of that
free shit i uh the boomer stuff is down here too i mean i love the okay the boomer emote up here
though like everything you like is because you're old down there he's had enough of ass easy uh
constant conflict is uh just that's just the way it is uh jex is always at s tier no matter what
you just i he has to be number one jex cannot appear on a list unless he is at the first spot
i just there's no i can't do anything about that kim check is kind of funny still i guess
rats are just you know rats are classic up in smoke ah it's kind of overstated i think a little
bit i wouldn't call it like complete complete total theory but it's like it's it's on its way up
pre-recorded i don't it's like on its way up caught his mic is like currently fun right now
because people like say that so it's it's pretty high uh he's fucking naked uh look at me is still
it's still up there i think a little bit he's laughing about it i think that's like uh down
here a little bit worma is like probably all the way down here didn't really do much with worma
germa's liar yeah uh the seagulls can't really ever get rid of the seagulls but i don't know i
mean that's like probably a couple years ago it's not you know what i mean subsounds don't even
have these as subsounds anymore but they when they were active they were i would put them right
behind minus two plus two or it probably a little bit ahead of it what rapper and reddit what does
that mean i'm not sure what that means and then uh cheese it versus cheese nips up here is two
there you go germa lied about the clown car just gave five thank you germa lied about the
clown car thanks for the five community subs five community subs rolling in thank you remember
the house flipper oh right right right yeah that's probably up here let me think here
no fuck the labo the slap is way way like funnier just because how fucking embarrassing that is
hot air balloon is is up here too photoshop's are better than the labo
biaz funnier than uh no pee pants is thick but funny the youtube voice is definitely below
i'm a top 1000 streamers that goes above labo jupiter is probably in front of this dark souls
three beating dark souls three better than that constant conflict is better than this
um i lie so that just goes down here hey peter no that's like not even funny died to pinwheel is
like just a mean thing people did okay well i like this so far rats are better than this
i lifted weights on camera for like fucking 10 seconds who who cares um all right uh germa
craft i think is better free shit's better germa iq is better ban that guy's better grill master's
not as good as the kim check and pre-recorded is better than grill master and laughing about it is
grill master's probably better uh germa con this enough that's nonsense that's just a thing that
i think would be fun okay i think i got it no not yet done done this tier list is bad
is this a tier list of my own channel's memes it is well i didn't make these up i got i mean
some of them i did why is peter on c and bald coin on f well it's just been a while
who made the best controllers controllers i could do that one yeah give me give me the
video game controllers i'll do it but i drank too much i gotta pee again tell me if the internet's
fine i'll be right back i gotta pee this is like the third time in i've been peeing too much
i'm gonna like ask my doctor how many times a human is supposed to pee a day
i've had my kidneys checked and my bladder checked what's wrong with me i'll be right back
it is dark in here it really is a cave in here let me turn like the let's see the volume up
watch the slap i don't need to watch the slap you know how many times i've watched the slap
it dozens and dozens and dozens of times let's come back i'm gonna change the camera settings
okey dokey look at that better more controlled do i still have the comb in my hair no all right
uh let's get this off these are controllers so d i would just put do a beer tier list i don't drink
that much beer to have like a real opinion on it hold on come on get over there stop it all right
that's good uh so these these are video game controllers this is dirty whatever okay video
game controllers uh let's change this to let's put one let's put f down here new f change the
color too okay fuck that thing seriously that like one of us that was horrible i this thing was so
bad it was so bad sideways switch no you can't even hold it although what the hell what is this
chainsaw that's that's that's a collector's edition perk for buying a collector's edition
that's not a what is that no this hurts if you hold it too long super nintendo controller pretty
close to being perfect so is the n64 controller game cubes up there too i'll make a final decision
in a minute the default regular super nintendo control is at least a b this thing wasn't very
good either this was this but get in the way with a wheel really the wee wheel is here that's why
why are there spongebob controllers i wouldn't use these i mean well i'm not going to buy that
i wouldn't use it there's no i i wouldn't i wouldn't buy it can i just have another category
that's just like this is just clearly joke like nonsense category they're not bad but they're
just like why i don't want them i don't want them yeah there's a new category below this is just
going to be just like the nonsense category at this i mean that these are not bad controllers
that just they're nonsense this is just a controller skin what is that is it n64
but is it is that a left-handed n64 controller well i don't understand is that like for
i don't i've never used it it looks a little crowded i would accidentally press like up on
the d-pad when i pressed air b i'm not sure i like that i never used it but i don't don't look
fun to me the dreamcast controller actually is pretty good it's pretty well made it had the big
slots the big divots in the back to really hold on to that you can just slide into this is a
comedy controller i don't think that this is also a comedy controller this is the dance dance
revolution pad before dance dance revolution so it's going to get f just because it was pretty
it was pretty new for its time the wiimote and nunchuck i would put them up here they were
kind of fun and nice to use this is like a fishing pole what is that i i did what what is this for
this wu tang wait was there a wu tang console was there it's a collector's edition yeah but
that's what i mean it's not like a controller comes with a console the wiifit scale i'll put
it up here where it belongs and like oh it's right next to this is fun the steam control is
really not good this is the same as this just with different colored buttons so i mean i'm
gonna put that in nonsense this is just like the skittles version that's not this is just like a
peripheral it's not even a controller is this a keyboard like hold on like just a keyboard and
mouse for pc gaming i thought that's not that's not fair is it hold on what is this is it a mat
this looks like a beach towel is this another one of these like dance dance revolution maps or
something okay well that uh no the wiimote wiimote sideways was better than the switch sideways for
me it's bigger here's the dreamcast keyboard which this is just a nonsense collector's edition
controller i actually don't really like the ds's analog it was too thin for me it felt like it
could easily be worn down well this is a fishing pole like i said okay i can go over the that
fishing pole what if it is the best controller this is the pro controller right this thing's
actually that's actually pretty good it's better than this one it's probably the game cube no it's
not which one of these was better it was this one's better yeah i wasn't actually a big fan of this
one this one actually feels better in your hands but this one actually bumps if you're trying to
you might bump it i remember you know it's it's pretty good um this is just a joke this is just
a skin so right this this looks like a piano is this a keyboard or is this a controller i don't
know what this is for what is this is this a gear shift on a car no this is no it's not all right
this is like revolutionary so that goes up here those are atari paddles this is just a skin
all right now we're getting to kind of current gen i really really really like the new dual shock
controller way more than i like the original i like how uh spread out it is i think this is actually
way up here original xbox was a little too fat and chunky for me but it was definitely better
than this i actually i don't hate the xbox one controller but i do hate its annoyingly loud
bumpers the 360 controller might be up here i think so what else we got these are not very good
the old sega genesis and sega they're very clunky three buttons it was just i didn't i don't really
like the playstation one controller either but it's definitely better than the dreamcast keyboard
in fact the ds controller is way better than the dreamcast keyboard this is not yeah i mean this
thing is like what is this what the fuck even is this it's a boomerang controller i don't what is
that but that's your that's a sega uh the sega master system it really wasn't that good of a
controller though better than this it was really weird the whole thing was one button that's a
stovetop yeah you take this thing camping that's a stovetop that's pretty good that's really good
mod that guy this is just a joke this is a joke this is a cassette tape it's not even a controller
playstation camera i'll put them up here we'll deal with them later uh this this is the deal or
no deal pad i don't know what this is for this is yes or no button i don't think i think i would
use that it's just a peripheral this goes up here this this is just the evolved version of this
controller pokemon so i'm just gonna let's just put this up here i don't really like this one
though um fight sticks i don't really like fight sticks and then this is those are too many buttons
i don't know what you would do with that all right um so hold on the guitar hero is just it's a
peripheral it's not even a controller all right i gotta make a decision here what belongs where
what belongs up and what belongs down i know don't look at my zip it's done i do that that's the most
comfortable controller i think it is it has a nice weight to it the analogs feel very durable
the button placements the triggers are in a really good place i think it is the best controller
it's got really nice triggers it's got the lr l l1 and r1 i like it a lot the game cube is
really close if this is s this is like s minus but a plus i mean i don't have to move anything
i'm happy with this where's the xbox one controller that doesn't belong all the way down there
this does though i don't i they put the this is the wii u pro controller right they put the
right analog stick in a really fucking weird place up above on the top right shoulder
it almost it feels odd this is the connect this is not the playstation move
this is the playstation move okay what about just dance i don't i don't play just dance
okay hold on this is better than this i don't even remember which one of these i liked more
probably the uh do i like charizard more than i like charmeleon yeah i think so playstation
one i don't like better than the playstation like three though xbox one is xbox one's definitely
better than the playstation one just because of the introduction of analogs i don't like the
fruit slice this is superior to me are these the same thing one of them is just wireless
wait is this just the wireless version of this it is isn't it this dualshock 2 dualshock 3
these are like the same wait which one of these is which one of these is which
it's ps3 and ps2 right okay they look the same okay dualshock 2 has the wire okay yeah
it belongs there i'm all right with this the rest of this shit is just jokey weird stuff that i've
never used so hold on let me go back up here i really like the it's very minimal the dreamcast
controller is super minimal gets the job done it's got nice triggers it fits in your hand well
it's got that cool screen you got you guys didn't get to see that when we did all the dreamcast
stuff there's a little screen that is your memory card that had all the cool random little it would
play little animations you could use it you could select things you could have in-game features it
was pretty cool the vmu doesn't have a right analog didn't need it though this is back when
two analogs weren't really necessary i mean that's not minimal it's an analog four face buttons and
a d-pad there's no other analog and it's spread out it has the same amount of buttons as a super
super antenna controller now the screen is just like an added feature that's in the in the
controller it but the actual physical controller itself is very basic oh well fuck i forgot the
original xbox below it belongs way down here i forgot i just had a memory the weird sideways
tilted face buttons yeah no get out of here this thing sucked i completely forgot about that
the like like it was printed on incorrectly type of scenario no yeah that's below the wii u
i hated that those got printed incorrectly from like the machine and they had like 50 000 of them
already made and the the foreman on the at the factory was just like just do it like this just
do it it's a feature no yeah this that i hated those i don't think it's worse than the keyboard
like the dreamcast keyboard with a grill or the connect no the connect is cooler this this is no
get that out of here this is the i can't sit still all right the the steam controller is better than
like the camping grill okay it is i'll give that to you this is not a dreamcast keyboard what the
hell is this then is this a game cube keyboard have you even touched a steam controller where the
fuck is it yeah i own one i own one but i don't know where it is never mind i thought i had one
in the closet back there i bought here's how you can tell that i'm lying about this because i'm
gonna give you an elaborate story and it's the only reason why you'd hear this i'm not just making
it up on the fly you didn't have time to make this up i bought a steam controller because i
currently like maybe this is probably like three three and a half years ago i got back into world
of warcraft and during the uh legion whatever it was um what was it called yeah the lab the
expansion pack that people liked like two or three years ago so i wanted to not use my keyboard and
mouse to play world of warcraft i desperately wanted to lean back and lie on a couch and just
play world of warcraft from the computer so i was like hold on a minute wait i can do the steam
controller because i can map it everything can be mapped to this to it being like a pc keyboard
right so i tried to do it and i realized that trying to use the steam controller to play world
of warcraft was impossible and i could only really map like four buttons or like five buttons to
spells and abilities so i would it worked technically but i could really only do like three
moves so i had to just sit there and do the same like three or four move rotation and it worked
until i got to like level like 22 and then i just gave up because i got too many abilities
how is that a problem with the steam controller because the steam controller has the pads
the track the mouse pads to make it so you can actually utilize like a mouse or utilize like
turning around and move like you can't map that kind of shit to uh you can't have a mouse b on
like your xbox controller it's like the axis is too like finicky don't worry in bfa you only have
four abilities anyways i stopped playing after legion there's literally an add-on that solves
your problem now well back to world of warcraft i played what yeah i played like three years three
and a half years ago i streamed i streamed wow remember karazhan it's the worst remember one of
the top three worst streams i've ever done you guys don't remember that that was peak me trying
to get the steam controller to work why am i putting my headphones in there's no reason to
there's no sounds you can work your way up to an officer in my guild did you do the door handles
tier list why the fuck would i ever do a door handles tier list put it in the chat i'll do it
next uh all right i think i'm done i'm happy with this these are originals why is the fight stick
lower than the game cube keyboard what is this karazhan 7.1 burp uh i don't because i don't use
fight sticks i don't know am i desynced i shouldn't be all right let's do door handles
door handles tier list uh right this is fucking stupid i'm more of like a toilet flush handle
kind of guy i don't like i don't like the just regular just little doorknobs because if you
put moisturizer on your hands you can't open them you're stuck in the room if you have any like oil
or moisturizer or anything there's like a keypad i have to remember a code wait a minute this is a
code and a toilet flusher okay that's cool these ones fun fact about these doorknobs guys they're
not secure at all because on the other end is a hole that's right in the middle of that fucking
thing that somebody just has to stick a a little pin in there and can pop the lock and open the
door those are not secure you you can you can get into those what is this one i don't know it looks
it looks exactly the fucking same i'm not into this kind of stuff it's like too it's too like
elaborate for me just give me like the the toilet handle it's not even that's not even a door handle
that's a part of a train track crystal now this stuff breaks there's a shower head this is dumb
it's like that you know a little a little turn no no that's not no this is up at a because that's a
because you can't fuck that up you just you grab and you turn and push no this is like a that's
like a candy no again put these down here and put that down here all right i have a lot of season
days yeah give me that thing any day rate the alphabet that's dumber than this rate the alphabet
uh i'm not gonna do that rate the alphabet based on taste
can i play a game now well this is this stream today was just doing this stuff just hanging out
doing tier lists and personality tests and combing my fucking hair rate video game companies
3000 people are here watching him rank doorknobs well when you put it like that cool math games
that's up there hold on where did i germa rumble characters i'm not doing the alphabet
spider-man movies i can do that no don't put any spoilers in here but i can do spider-man movies
is this one legit all right we'll do spider-man movies and then we'll see what else we're doing
we'll do cool math games that's what we're gonna end on okay let's do it this isn't even all the
spider-man movies is this is is this all of them it is no it's not where is uh where's far from
home is it there i mean this is homecoming no is it which where's homecoming is that far from
that's far from home where's homecoming is it i don't recognize these posters okay this is the
first spider-man right all right spider-verse i'm gonna hope hold on spider-verse is gonna stay
there for just a second did i forget this out uh far from home is going up here for a second
i loved far from home i thought far from home was fucking awesome i loved every second of far
from home it was literally like i mean far far from home was the best uh where are the bad ones
where are the ones were like where are the bad ones it's amazing was amazing was amazing spider-man
one and two this is spider-man three which was not not that great but it was all right still
this is the original right this one's really good too it's gonna be tough this is gonna be tough
homecoming was fucking awesome too was uh amazing spider-man two i i loved homecoming
i loved homecoming and i loved far from home far from home is my favorite there's gotta be a b
one of these has to be b doc octopus is spider-man 2 is fucking unbelievable i don't know which one
is what i don't know which one it's so hard because this movie was fucking incredible it
really was awesome it was fucking awesome but michael keaton is like one of my favorite actors
ever he's my one of my favorite fucking actors he's i love michael keaton but if i just don't
have a b no but green goblin it was too good spider-man one's a b i agree with you william
defoe was not the green goblin if any other actor is the green goblin it's probably here
and i'll do a michael keaton movies tier list fixed i'm done done i fixed it i'm good i think
that's good where's the spider-man ps4 game on this somewhere in here between dna the muppet
muppets tier list oh give me this right now the i can't the i'm just gonna be the i i'm gonna
spend a lot of time on this one this is gonna take at least an hour there you go far from home is
my favorite spider-man movie i don't know i loved it just that whole that i just love i'm not talking
about it but fucking i love that character i love that character i love that character you know what
i'm talking about you fucking who cares you'll watch it it's good i just came for the muppets
you came to the stream for the muppets you came you came to the stream for the muppets
i understand that this is that's all of them this is not all of them who the fuck is this
oh sweetums this is my favorite oh guys guys don't wait wait for me guys all right oh i can't
believe it's s sweetums is s tier don't forget about me oh yeah that's that should make a whole
show around sweetums and the bear all right let me tell you what general let me ask you a question
yep bobo the bear s tier both of them this is the paper towels guy that's the paper towels guy
right ruff ruff ruff ruff let me tell you something oh i'm playing a song yep the swedish chef was
just a fucking psycho so he belongs up here too gonzo the great fuzzy eh this is gonna be hard
oh get them up here they used to talk shit about the show it was awesome the puppet show every i
don't know maybe every 15 every after maybe 15 20 minutes of the whole show they would just cut
to these guys and they were sitting in a in the booth in the theater and they would just make
fun of the show it was awesome just two old men just making fun of the show you're currently
watching was fantastic uh will doff and statler right i gotta remember their names if they can't
be up in s tier if i don't know their names no this is this is like the no this is like the new
muppet that they i'm not a fan i'm not i'm not i don't hate it but i'm not it's just like i'm
this it's they made this character for one movie and then they brought up you know no no no no no
rizzo the rat definitely up here oh this is the shit these oh man the rats that belong up there
oh dr dr dr teeth in the electric mayhem get them up here get all of them up there where's the
guitarist dr teeth and the electric band belong up here in fact they you know i might have to do
this no this that's that's that's the manamana guy no there he is okay okay this is just one
character okay this is like dr teeth as a whole all right you got sweetums dr teeth as a whole
statlin world of the bear and ralph and somebody's escaped subs clout like you clown clown daddy for
the five community subs is this like a crossover character from like the office or something who
is this i don't know who this is i really just don't know who it is miss piggy's up there too
come on they're like hiya when she's still like karate chop people miss piggy used to karate chop
people she's just fucking smash people oh is it because of mua yeah miss piggy was awesome
it's hard to place kermit though because kermit is uh kermit's like the straight man in like the
comedy right always collected except when he throws his hands up and he goes like all right
but he was he was kind of like the anchor of the whole thing that kind of has to be yeah it has
to be like a separate tier for kermit where does the animal go animal goes because that's
that's dr t i forgot to put animal up here in fact animal i liked the saxophone guy
but no these are all collective unit too many s tier no this is all one group this is a group
oh this is the pigs in space right kind of a joke just like a joke off joe it wasn't it
wasn't like a character it was just kind of pigs in space here's the mean eagle that used to hate
everything no uh the eagle goes up here the chickens were cute but like uh he's up here too
it is the guy he's the guy that ran the whole show produced the whole show i only it's hard to place
uh the cafe the prawn because he's great character but he did like a fortnight dance
like a year ago how do i have gonzo in a because i've got just a gonzo's prop gonzo is probably up
here do a beaker impression that'll be 100 bucks i'm that's a i lied it's a joke i'm kidding was
miss piggy cooler than the swedish chef probably yeah she was just she uh look they're both doing
the same thing they're both doing like the same avatar pose i'm gonna have to drop kermit down
one or two notches here because he is doing a youtuber thumbnail pose tricky so is pausey
i like it who is this guy what is this he's from the abc show i just don't i i don't even know what
the context of this character is he was in the muppet treasure island movie really toothpaste
tier list hmm oh i'm gonna do sesame street if i'm gonna do yeah i'm doing i'll do sesame street
i'll give you a sesame street list take your picture get the count up there big bird grover
grover is s you cannot find a better muppet character than grover cookie monster this is
this is uh tully is that guy smiley that's guy smiley guy smiley belongs up here snaflophagus
elmo is okay the elmo belongs somewhere up here where are those um there they are
i was gonna say where the two aliens that go like yep yep yep yep yep yep yep yep yep yep yep yep
they belong up here kermit uh kermit was we already did him oscar the grouch where's oscar
the grouch i'm getting it done getting it done the rest of these i um oh this is the guy that
doesn't like his spaghetti raw grover get them both up there that's a fucking comedy team
that's the best comedy team that you'll ever see was burton ernie sorry burton ernie not as good
as grover and restaurant guy i remember these two um who the fuck are all these other people
i don't know they are uh i know where's um i remember you i remember i remember the cow
that's just sherlock holmes although the little bug alien family right with snaflophagus he's right
here weren't these okay weren't these just like new york construction workers they were like the
construction workers from new york right why are there two counts wait this is this is not the
count that's like that's like a magician the count goes up here no you you go over here you're
better than the two aliens are you better probably better than guys smiley no baby no
baby bear sucks i don't like baby bear no let me let me i do it by let me see the voices the
voices the voices no baby bear oh no what happened to me a baby bear right that's baby bear tell me
that's if that's the one that i think it is it's uh how could i the worm yeah has to be up there
that's the best character i don't recognize very many of these other characters
this is this is kind of just like scruffy elmo this is like elmo but like a fan in front of him
is this like snoopy and spike i don't know who that is this like an owl or is that gizmo from
gremlins i don't know i've kind of recognized this person but i'm not really the cowboy i don't know
who these people are i've recognized i recognize her i'd like that i see i see some of these
but i don't i'm just not sure no you did guys smiley better than guys marley that's not true
like who is that like who are these two are these new i haven't i mean obviously i haven't watched
sesame street in a long time i don't know i don't know who these police any of these people are
i kind of recognize them but not really the horse i feel like a if i know the cow i should know the
horse super grover is s no that's just implied that super grover is grover they're the same
person he just puts a cape on and flies now do looney tunes get let's see it that just looked
like in the camera that i bent my arm my wrist all the way backwards and then all the way forward
so that was weird looking that is there should i just look forward are we got a good one fraggle
rock fraggle rock was a great show i'll do looney tunes list i've got it up here kind of in my
brain already game developer is a definitive edition looney tunes list let's try this one
do the pringles tier list uh i don't need to do the pringles tier list
holy shit okay um the say the characters pop up like this five times like silvesta the cat
i've seen him at least four times there's too many i gotta do a different one there's too many
looney tuna i think this one right here sorry i'm like sniffing you guys is this better
all right this is looks a little better i think or i no no these are like this is i don't know who
have to this no this is like naughty that's just like hannah barbara these aren't looney tunes no
that was i'm not that one doesn't look accurate this one's like looney tunes characters game
developers is looney tunes not gonna work how many game developers are on this list
oh my god this is gonna take forever i don't even recognize some of these let me see hold on can i
just do like a few because i don't even know some of these do you have it listed as mobile
it's why i even have a mobile tier that's the first one i did okay let's i can do it i can do
it i can do it maybe i can't no i can't activision why is infinity war infinity war is a oh infinity
ward and yay uh bandai namco the doxin company i don't know who they are original pop cap was
pretty good id software insomniac interplay get that up there i don't know who is this blizzard
2019 or blizzard like 2000 what year is it 2019 okay max does maxis even still make games lion
head gearbox is probably down here midway was classic up with interplay how is that how
laboratories oh how labs okay that's um what the what the hell is pokemon no pokemon smash brothers
konami not very good double fine not not very good yacht club games that's like rare right odd
world inhabitants they just make odd worlds right bungee i don't like it is there any are there
really any games companies on here that i actually know i don't play right games i don't play league
that's 2019 rare shit you're right shit every game company sucks in 2019 even valve i don't know yet
sucker punch what what is sucker punch studios sly cooper no no valve is not under e i gotta
just get them in the right spot and then move them around you guys know how this works we've
been doing this for like three hours sly cooper what else have they done though i don't i don't
i don't i don't really play sly cooper microsoft not very good level five that's metroid but 2019
level five they haven't really done anything right no what is level five professor professor
latin oh okay i didn't really play that much professor latin i'm just i'm just pulling the
ones that i recognize this is halo right i don't i i gotta make another one that's not f just hold
on i'm gonna do not enough experience not enough experience because i've never played any of the
halo games i don't really play any many of the i don't play league i'll fix this later oh what
about i sucker i didn't really play sly uh okay i'm gonna it's not i'm gonna fix it atari rock
steady is pretty good 2019 though what have they done what's the last thing they did it's like the
batman games right what's this like underwater dog cat thing sucker punch made infamous i didn't
play it i tried to remember i tried to stream infamous and it didn't work i had never played it
oh that's the that stardew okay did software up there somewhere team ninja i haven't really played
very many of those games bio where lucas arts doesn't even exist anymore but when it was
when it existed they made some good games but uh warner brothers what's the last few things
uh what's the last few games that warner brothers has done the lord of the rings games shadow of war
was it was all right that was pretty good those were good i don't play a whole lot of atlas
localized games sonic team i haven't really made a good sonic game in a while nether realm is
uh the mortal combats have been pretty good recently i'll figure it out later there's the
tony hawke company but this is not this is not just this is not a fair list because some of
these companies don't exist anymore nc soft this is the um last guardian and shadow classes
it's up there somewhere that game was really sloppy but it was really really interesting
and plus shadow the classes is really great you can't deny that minecraft wasn't like a
huge success but i don't think it i personally don't i'm not going to put it in b
isn't take take two is now take two is like all the sports games and technically gta but
they publish they don't really make they don't really develop right naughty dog naughty dog's
doing pretty well like they actually like really well i have to i'm gonna i'll head back to this
the rest of these i kind of i don't really know what they were turtle rock they made
evolve right square enix so idos idos is technically what io now like no that's like
hitman but it's not was io interactive on here i don't see io interactive on here so should i
put i should i do idos as if it is hitman because idos technically was hitman but it wasn't but it
was i'm gonna pretend that this is a hitman company no that's not supposed to be there
nexon this is like the massive multiplayer company that they like half of the mmos you
see that pop up in like an ad on the side of your youtube page is by nexon monolith uh monolith did
the ones are the ones that were responsible for shadow of mordor if i'm gonna put wb up here then
monolith should be up here too higher than that too many video game companies dice not doing it
for me not doing it for me game freak now this is pokemon i'll tell you it has to go down here
because i don't really i don't have much experience with pokemon old acclaim here's the thing about
old acclaim all their games were dog shit but they all were charming in some kind of way their games
were terrible but they did a lot of interesting things that's gonna be indeed all i remember is
the old wwf acclaim games and they were so bad valve below ea i'm not just wait wait i'm not done
with the list i have to get everybody in the right spot and then from there we add on to it and i put
that look i'm just getting him the general idea this is just they're gonna change it's not like
wait rare is about blizzard just hold on just i got there's a lot to compress here what is this
fear axis what's your axis civilization x-com i don't have enough experience with it the rest
of these i really don't know obsidian is good but we'll see how their new game is who knows
coffee stain is that's like the goat simulator team right and they did some other what else have
they done what else have they done i don't know sanctum coffee stain um deep rock they published
deep rock but they didn't develop it does that count maybe i guess it does in a way okay where
is oh god this is gonna be fucking hell sorting through quantic dream i don't think i have enough
experience didn't they make one game it was like a movie game grasshopper is we'll see we'll see
when the new no more heroes comes up because they haven't really done anything good at all in the
last like at least probably four or five years it's tough oh they're the okay yeah yeah yeah
uh i like detroit become human i thought it was fun no more heroes is awesome but i haven't really
done anything in a long time that i really played that i thought was like interesting
how do i alienate every gamer except for the people that like from software sony capcom rock
star nintendo naughty dog interplay midway how laboratories rocksteady um stardew valley guy
lucas arts eiko eidos and bandai namco except for the all those people rockstar at a gta5 was
fucking awesome red dead redemption 2 was really fun no i i am one of these is going to gum bs
now you gotta wait let me do my first draft i'm still trying to juggle of
what what the hell e-ha games is i don't know what this is what is this one i don't know what
it is somebody can tell me all right the reason why capcom is up here is because the last like
four or five games that capcom has come up with have been awesome resident evil 2 was fucking
awesome monster hunter world was awesome um i heard devil may cry was awesome i mean they've
been knocking it out of the park recently this is you guys told me 2019 resident evil 2 was
fantastic it was really really really really fucking good do you think that capcom in the
last few years should be below like epic games unless you're like play fortnite no okay look
all the companies that are in b and c i have not gone over and thought about yet this is
this is gonna take a lot a long time let me just remember okay insomniac insomniac made the new
spider-man one right they're up here that new spider-man game was really really really fucking
good so up here i'll figure it out a minute yacht club games made shovel knight i haven't
didn't really played that much irrational games what the hell is that it's so familiar what is it
bioshock right okay right right right right right right right bioshock infinite was good
didn't they just didn't they liquid didn't they they got liquidated right was it was it i i remember
like in bioshock infinite i thought it was fun but i mean bioshock one about the pandemic help me out
here this is like every video game company i'm trying pandemic was what battlefront destroy all
humans okay all right all right okay hold on i liked those respawn entertainment that's uh it's
like yeah i don't i don't play their games atari doesn't really exist anymore they still kind of
do what's the last thing that isn't the last game they made like a dragon ball z fighting game
i have not enough experience recently i know they're a classic company but we're talking like
recently like the last five to ten years no oh i don't know where the fuck they belong probably
up here santa monica studio is the god of war studio right or is that technically sony
they belong up here it's god of war yeah okay yep no they but they they belong up here all
their games are like just always good sierra like it's hard to mix in these really old ass
fucking companies with the ones that are currently you know what i mean there's too many impressive
game what is impressive games what what did they do no that's a super massive games until dawn
here's the thing trying to do this is tricky because not only is it the games that they made
but each company has like a separate tier of games that they've made so all right like sega for
instance sega as a whole exists and then when you double click sega you get the big drop down of
like 50 games so try it's hard to place them this tier list is fucked well hold on let me
let me do this first um i know it's gonna be like this i'm gonna let me work backwards
uh it's taking a lot of brain power to do this all right um this is hitman right this is guys
hitman i'm working it up see why are you doing an la noir face so uh where were you uh at four
o'clock eastern time were you in front of the store i can't even fucking do it now all i think
about is you guys looking at me with like three buttons that are watching my face gearbox is down
here i don't i'm sorry gear i'm telling you we're good gearbox is i don't borderlands you can
borderlands i don't care about borderlands no it's not f it's but why are these even on here
bethesda is still like making games though konami is not let's just be very very clear about this
konami doesn't even make fucking video games anymore didn't they like abandon their video
game development ea is very close to d-minus well let's get back up here naughty dog versus
insomniac i don't think i'm i'm gonna leave this alone i think this is accurate hold on what was
the last couple nintendo games that i played mario maker 2 smash brothers no yeah no they're
still making really good stuff they are so is rock star so is capcom so it's sony santa monica
just released like one of the best games like ever fucking made right like ever according to
a lot of people i haven't played it i don't know i've played some of the other ones it's a lie
the labo exists it's right all right hold on hitman is awesome it's a ton of fun but also
remember like this is this this is a deep these are defunct studios so it's hard to do this
blitz the league 2 exists because this company decided to have it that means a lot we're just
we're just in b right now we're just in b dipping into c but hold on i don't know i don't know if
lucas arts should be up here technically technically games like tf2 dota and cs go they still get
updates technically so i mean you can't like valve has a bunch of stuff in development right
now don't they this would be all the way up here it would but a valve being down at c is already
like a huge fucking issue that's a huge deal imagine this list five years ago if valve wasn't
up here i would be a crazy person so this is already very bad um bungee shouldn't be down that
far rare has to do something rare has to do something rare they have to go down here i'm
sorry they do they have to do something they have to make a game no i know but rare rare allowing
banjo to be a character that is that is a cool character that exists banjo is a character it's
from a classic video game series um if you don't okay if you don't want spoilers for anything mute
right now like if you don't want any spoilers for anything just mute right now i'm gonna just say
spoilers so mute right now if you don't want any spoilers for something mute i'll go like this um
some people don't want to know the characters in smash until they like actually get their hands on
it so that's like a literal like a video game like marvel spoiler um them allowing banjo in
you know what i'm saying that's not them they didn't do that is your hair in a bun what do you
mean what what the fuck how long has this been in my hair for did i start combing my hair this
morning and just stopped thank you for catching that how the fuck no holy shit dude like thanks
for catching that i that would have been in there till i woke up tomorrow morning damn uh where was
i oh yeah all right you can come back they have to make a game they gotta make something and yeah
they made sea of thieves was sea of thieves better than overwatch i don't know i this is too hard
it's too hard i give up this too hard no it's too hard it's too there's too many there's too many
things there's too many things there's too many things i just too much overwatch was good though
overwatch was fucking really fun when at first i came out i really thought it was a really fun
to game i really liked it but that's it like everything else they've done has been like
just stepping in quicksand since they released overwatch blizzard has just been sinking in
quicksand and just going hey what's wrong oh oh overwatch just released cool new game that's a
team-based arena shooter awesome anybody like the old games that we made before do you like no you
do yeah warcraft 3 is coming up classic i mean we talked about that like like probably 10 years
ago but it's happening now you guys have phones what's wrong what you guys don't have a phone
am i getting smaller hey all of our all of our ceos are leaving is that is that nothing wrong
with that right oh like more employees like top level employees are gone what's wrong with my
mouth what's happening i mean what's my chin touching what is this what was this what did you
uh
diablo 2 remastered diablo 2 remastered edition overwatch 2 overwatch 2 is coming up
give me a break but i lost the call is that okay overwatch 2 like what the what is what's going on
this comes down here because of the diablo mobile and overwatch 2 they're gonna why is maxis and d
it's not but is but blizzard's better than than tim horton's studio whatever what what's what is
it uh what's his name tim shaffer they're all riding on like hey it's psychonauts 2 right
psychonauts 2 maybe it's up here if possible you can't do this why is bethesda at the top of d
i don't know i'm having a lot of trouble i just threw up you're stressing yourself out way too
much i know but this is my legacy don't you know this is my legacy this i'm leaving this behind
right like 100 years from now they're gonna be like well i wonder what he thought about all these
things my fucking legacy how is ico i was t i go not an a we'll get hope just i listen to me
the issue with doing a video game company tier list is as if every single one of these was a
version of in and out moving one of these causes a huge issue for a bunch of people every one of
these is in and out burger but like in and out different uh like variations of it so all of them
are bad i didn't say it i didn't say that you did i have to okay if this is the thing that people
remember you for i'm sorry not anything else germa 985's legacy is remember that one time he
did the games company tier list yeah that's true if this is what i leave behind then i didn't leave
very much you have thousands of hours of online content thousands of hours this is my legacy
that's embarrassing i don't even know all right remedy you're shafting valve if you've gotten
your orange box origins that's why valve's not down here the valve like artifact that wasn't
like a big deal and people i didn't think it was any i didn't really was interested i wasn't
interested at all i didn't really wasn't interested in dota they had like a bunch of other projects
they kind of swept out of the rug i'm only doing this because of i'm only doing this because of
the spy dota underlords is worse than the game mode in dota this is the fucking craziest thing
guys do you understand what's happening in video games right now you have a game a video game
that was a mod for starcraft which then became a mod for warcraft which then turned into a full
game which then that full game was oh we're gonna make that one too so that is a a sort of copy
of a mod and then you have inside of that copy of a mod you have a mod inside of that game that
was a mod which was auto chess and is now becoming a mod of a copy of a copy of a mod from a game
from 1998 what in the name of god is happening what's going on mod game mod game original mod
yo dude i heard you like mods it's just chess no my point is is that it's a everyone's start
people are starting to want to make their own auto chess is now and they want to make their own
auto chess is based inside of a game that was a mod is wild i i almost want to like make a uh
like a chart that shows like the origin the originations of where all these things came from
it's so interesting fortnight auto chess all right i'm about to detonate the whole thing
the first two or three rows i it's gonna be too hard and there's all this shit i don't even know
what to put here comes a volcano joke why is ea not s tier i got thousand voices in my head
all you need to know just i'm gonna cover this up this is all you need this is like 2019 this is
like what i think hey this is pretty much all you need like there you go like that this is like
that's just this is this is his list writer crumb software nintendo rockstar capcom sony santa
monica somniac naughty dog idos stardew guy uh how laboratories rocksteady the mid well i don't
know why these are up here obsidian uh monolith valve is like right here valve is up here valve
okay valve wasn't the last mode of combat game trash i don't know i i was it i thought it was
good didn't people really like it all right that's it i just hit myself in a really bad place
accidentally and it was right on that that was really really close to being a huge issue
i just like whacked myself in the thigh area i'm good all right we're gonna finish this stream up
with some cool math games but which one am i gonna even play i need my uh headphones for this
i was just putting five hours of this damn i'm having a pretty good time
it's kind of been flown by so tomorrow let's talk about tomorrow i'm thinking of uh i'm thinking
of doing dos again you want to do a dos night tomorrow tomorrow night do and looks like okay
the internet's been a lot better people have been waiting for that for a long time we'll go back to
dos tomorrow uh somebody says uh play run two all right i'll try run two how what is run two
select a character runner or skater hold on i gotta get the window in here run two i've never played
this how is this a math game do i have to like solve puzzles or something because it's cool it's
not a math it's not a math game okay so it's just a cool game it doesn't have anything to do with
math at all uh okay this might be loud i'm gonna turn it down all right controls uh left space
pause and reset so just jump okay i'm gonna easier to control can't jump as far hard it
jumps farther and hard to control use the right and left arrow keys to move side this is really
really fucking loud collect all the okay uh see if you can collect the bonuses all right all right
first contact with a wall bonus not earned select level okay let's go level two it's the wrong way
how do i get this is why it's a math game right how do i get that one how do i get this bonus
i don't know how to get this bonus oh you can jump into the walls i didn't know that you could do
that i thought you had to touch them on the side we don't i don't get the bonuses who gives a shit
all right this is like a little got it uh you can catch here but you cannot catch here
this is a baby game this is a cool math game actually oh i'm good shit this is actually
kind of this is pretty fun do run three or i'm gonna pee my pants well go for it man this takes
a lot of concentration can i not get up there all right got it bonus fuck damn it whatever up up up
up up up up up up up shit ah you gotta go to the right up up up right up uh fuck the bonuses
how many levels are there in run two could i just do like a mario slide skip right there
it's not that easy is it apparently it is there's 500 levels well i won't be doing this for that long
come on i can make that oh shit i got it damn it fuck
come on what oh my god i'm so stupid i have to wait wait why am i addicted to this cool math game
whatever just end it
holy shit what is going on all right i can hold on i can drop down drop down get this jump over jump
over jump damn it damn oh i didn't even get the bonus and i went the harder way
forget it just do shit it's okay oh my god okay i'm good oh man my fingers are getting really greasy
really that didn't turn why what no okay it didn't again come out that was called cluster truck that
was like this all right i'm gonna go up and then up forget about it all right i'm gonna get to
level 20 oh fuck slow down get your greasy hands oh i'm i'm look at me i'm starting to sweat i really
am this my zit's gonna be like five times bigger at the end of this it's gonna literally take on a
mind of its own this pimple is gonna start talking by the end of the stream okay good
doesn't improve implying not new what so how would you do this with the other character
i feel like this would be hard to do unless you were moving fast oh shit i did it come on do it
i had it too all right i just tasted salt is this sweat like dripping down my face
no it's not i'm gonna go slower come on i gotta get to the level itchy nose
oh i get it okay i'm good social studies is in five minutes all right because we're in school
i gotta stick right in the middle i gotta go down that's what you gotta do you gotta go down
level 20 i'm ready jump nice and easy i got the bonus that was easy dude the teachers here i don't
give a shit i'm gonna fail this class anyways who cares maybe just run across it oh i see
i you gotta jump through the holes holy shit you have to spin it around damn all right
oh man i gotta get that come on 21 that's the blackjack number i can do it
got it all right 22 this is the last one this is actually the last one damn how do i do that i
gotta jump underneath it yeah you gotta go underneath no you don't got it okay 23 is a
scary number it's like the satan number i can't i can't i'll get 24 i can't end on the scary one
24 i can't end on that one 25 that's like a good even one he's doing an oblivion face
all right all right okay i'm good go we're good we're good i did it i won i okay i won what's the
next one what's another like really good one in the time we have remaining play run three uh run
three is not as popular as run two let me see what we got we've got b cubed i feel like i can't do
that one run two block sores awesome tanks parking fury papa's sushi ria there is no game what is
there is no game block sores block block block yeah all right right flip the block over this way
and over that way to get it to fall in the hole you'll be flipping blocks in your sleep
okay let's do it make sure you can see what i'm doing here cool math needs to be moved i think
something uh block sores does it fit all right so the aim of the game is to get the block to fall
into the square hole at the end of each stage there are 33 stages so to move the block around
use left right up and down arrow keys be careful not to fall off the edge well here we go get the
block to fall into the square at hole at the end of each stage there are 33 stages all right
move the block around the world use left and right up and down be careful not to fall off the edge
the level we restarted if you do now it's such a weird this is such a weird game to capture
is that better bridges and switches are located in many levels switches are activated when they are
pressed right you do not need to stay resting on the switch to keep it open heavy x-shaped ones
and soft round ones soft switches are activated when any part of your block presses it hard
which required much more pressure so your block must be standing on it to activate it okay
when activated each switch may behave differently some will swap the bridges from open to closed
yeah there's a different stuff pump up the iq for this one green or red colored squares will
flash to indicate which bridges are being operated orange tiles are far more fragile
than the rest of the land if your block stands up vertically on an orange tile tile will give
way and your block will fall this this parentheses switch teleports your block to different locations
splitting it into two smaller blocks that's why i think this might be a little too much for me
this might this might be it might be not too much for like an eighth grader but it's too much for me
okay you can select different blocks the passcode for each stage
it is located in the top right corner so the dead it's like megaman let's go now that i can see the
screen all right i get it he was joking funny man pretending to be stupid he is enlightened he's a
stop no shit wait pretty good oh shit he was just pretending to be funny man he was pretending to be
funny guy what is that doing no i'm good i'm good i'm good i'm good i'm good i'm good everything's
fine what do i think about this game i think it's pretty sweet i think it belongs with top two video
games on this site fuck i did it and i went too far great i forgot i forgot i'm streaming you're
right i i'm streaming um right i'm not just playing cool math games alone um i'm stumped
i'm stumped on this one i think guys they stumped me yeah they stumped me all right what's next what's
next on uh okay what's next can you play something else this game sucks this game doesn't suck i think
it's pretty cool what's next all right we're going back i never beat this one so yeah uh candy jump
duck life rob the robber jacksmith papa's papa what a papa game basketball master two papa's
pizzeria what about papa's bakery papa's bakery no no balloons no balloons papa's pizzeria why is
that not popular was it up here where is it not popular it's not popular well papa louis when
sunday's attack i'll just look for it pizza sucks bakery's okay i'll do papa's bakery
let's try it whoa too loud all right papa's bakery uh after this one uh this will probably be
this will probably be it because i had to start late and we're going late so thankfully the internet
seems to have held up pretty well with this new vpn in five and a half hours dropped 9000 frames
which really is not that bad in like the big picture okay so we know what here's what you
know what after this we're gonna do um we're gonna do tomorrow we're gonna do dos but maybe
we'll throw some of these in too like that would be fun just continue it i really wanted to start
earlier and we just kind of got fucking screwed so we'll just roll do this for a little bit uh new
game tim i'll be tim uh it's should i do this no did i all right papa's bakery day one welcome
to pop pop is i didn't make a video on one of these i completely forgot about the video that
i made customers order take an order yeah this is just cook serve delicious but different
build station we're gonna make a pie akira akira akari akira is a movie uh wants to have
graham cracker crust for her pie drag this flavored crust into the tin this pie needs
to be completely filled with pecans oh you got you got to run in first choose the filling by
clicking the pecan button yeah you should add filling exactly how it shows on the ticket
all the way up that's just all pecans this is gross that's not pecan pie those are just pecans
out of a bag uh akari wants a vented crust okay vented crust drag the pie into the oven
the pie is burning wait until the bake meter reaches the arrow okay pecan pea pants done take
it up under the tray switch to the top station uh you want top the pie needs caramel drizzle
the icon below shows they want this added all over the whole pie okay how do i do it try to
cover the whole pie with this drizzle uh did i do it once eight banana slices placed in the
outer ring of the pie okay oh i'm sorry i couldn't mute there's no way drag this tickets order onto
the ticket holder to deliver it look good 96 points four dollars and 60 cents all right basic
training in papa's bakery try this next order on your own i would like a cherry pie with apple
stuff captain crunch and caramel sauce okay what do you want what kind of crust did he want what
does it say the crust which crust was it how do i know what crust it was which one which crust was
it this one oh it's right here okay uh big pauli wants two fillings and the fillings he wants the
all right you want cherry up to here and then you want apple up to here what a sick fuck all right
we want streusel topping all right looks good get it in there grandpa played better than you
in this game all right let's top it off my grandpa wants uh caramel sauce how does he want it uh i
think i did it right this needs eight whipped cream dollops placed in the outer ring and that's
it right take it 99 points pie is a low tier dessert no i don't want you to store info not
perfect send it back use the game tickets you are in to play the houdini's daily mini game show
okay yeah let's go can you stack it high this is making me hungry i want one of these right now
onion ring swiss cheese pickle tomato am i wagering tickets or something what does this mean
i don't get it can play again oh no i don't do it again just lose i don't do it again it was i
already beat it all right let's go uh decorate the lobby let's do a um dr pepper all right new
customer johnny oh we got fudge too this is looking pretty cool all right this one i'm going to just
dump a bunch of shit that and just do like the funny youtube joke i want fudge okay can i not
do the funny youtuber joke or do i just have to make a pie shit i can't i thought i was going
to be able to start dropping stuff this could take a long time cherry pie apple pie uh crunchies on
it you got it oops how do i change that how do i it was the same color he won't even notice
it's in between it's in the middle you won't even know they'll they'll like just scoop together
it's not burning look this guy has a nut allergy anybody else what do you want you want full cherry
crunchies cherry bananas all right this is almost done i can do this fill it up with full cherry
okay you want the crunchies on it hold on what was on this how do i want his how do i get you
okay it was cherries what's cherry cherry sauce and what the hell is that what does he want them
four-year-olds drawing all right i think that's good not bad write your name on the what like a
like a latte all right this one is uh okay i'll write my name okay and then whipped cream oops
i don't think baristas write their own names on lattes no i'm talking about when you go
inside of with the milk and you'd make like a little design okay uh this one what does it want
what does this one want me to do all right i might as well do crunch coat a little crunch coat thing
crunchies okay that's it that was loud did you hear that go to the oh shit that's right this
customer is here closers are very picky about their food they will be tougher when grading their
orders this guy's a closer okay bake station okay um bill let's do it's this crust right here
chocolate and then double pecan back to chocolate this one is uh he wants this one throw that in
the oven anybody else no uh-oh she's getting angry that one sounds pretty good take out the
pecans and you got me on board nobody else all right we're closed right does it kind of be all
right he's kind of breathing kind of heavy more toppings stop saying pecan no sorry pecan what
does that mean uh no this is the wrong ticket get out of my way get out of the way all right um
you want cherry sauce on this and then bananas slices where the where's the banana oh down here
and then cherries she likes it oh fuck his pie is burning all right you want whipped cream
and what is that whipped cream no i gotta do around the whole thing shit all right something
what want drops in the inner ring and the center of the pie put one in the center and space the
rest of them out in the inner ring how many okay and then you want peanuts around the outer ring
whatever just go take it d minus and thanks for watching the stream everybody that was a fun one
tonight actually i didn't have a good time we're just kind of chilling shooting the shit it's been
fun it's getting late well we're we're approaching somewhere around midnight pacific had to start
late so sorry that we had to start so late but the internet was horrible but i'm thinking that
this vpn may have helped six hours 93 less than 10 000 drop frames in six hours is actually pretty
good let's see what happens tomorrow because we i did i gotta do a test for at least a few days
because you've we've seen this internet be perfect and then it's been oh drop 30 000 frames
we'll see how it goes but i had a lot of fun i like to do this i like to just kind of hang out and
talk shit and play random stuff and just be on cam but it doesn't happen that often doesn't happen
that often can't wait to not see half the carnival stream because of this well lucky for all of us
the carnival stream is not happening in las vegas like here i'm gonna be on location for that
so it's not happening here in vegas that's all you that's all you need to know
speak of the devil just dropped a frame right there on location with worse internet now that
would be sad i don't think that's gonna happen it's not it's not even gonna be in the state of
nevada it's uh across the country actually what happens now now we uh we we wind down a little
we say good night we turn off this screen so again tomorrow we're gonna do uh dos
join me for dos tomorrow we're gonna play there's at least a few of them that i think would be fun
to do uh sorry we had to start at like 5 30 pacific tonight it's not my intention
and i probably lost some of the subs from six or seven hours ago i'm sorry about that
when the stream gets killed like that i lose subs but uh we'll try again tomorrow
dos games and let's go back to earlier what is the german smile well that's terrifying
but thank you to frodian weapon for the 250 sorry for almost spoiling uh redacted
i did not get the memo if it makes you feel better i do feel bad about it so could you please call
off your small battalion of rats i haven't actually seen one yet but i know they're there
among us people unsubscribe over that no no no no i mean i don't have uh i do credits at the end
of the stream they scroll up and when a stream gets dropped to zero and i have to stop it
there's new credits that are made because it only takes the subs that come through
for that vod for that broadcast not the one from earlier so every time a new vod is created or a
drop to zero the subs kind of start at zero again it's annoying but it happens no i don't mean like
people are unsubscribing over that you know just the plug-in doesn't really work so well
but uh what i don't know fronty what are you talking about here what spoiler for what uh
jared done thanks for the ten dollars and 60 cents uh jared and also gave uh a hundred
fucking dollars and they say how do i subscribe and there should be a button down there but
regardless you have uh you have subscribed a shitload of times already by giving me like a
hundred and fucking plus dollars so i don't worry about that thank you there was a string of like
three or four hundred bucks in a row here earlier we got them all but thank you guys so much the
amount of money that comes in for sometimes is just fucking outrageous i can't even comprehend it
you guys are too much thank you uh we also had ten dollars come in from germa's nuts
say my name coward i said your name last night too i said it last night
but thank you i do appreciate hey buster boy thanks for the three dollars buster boy
don't forget you promised to lip sync the entirety of mambo number five
germa lied about lip syncing mambo number five i'm sure it's already been created drinking skills
came in with five community subs right now thank you thank you drinking skills appreciate it i did
i did it yesterday there's a clip of me uh lip syncing the first like 12 25 seconds there's
only one bit message that you can't see and it's five dollars and 37 from bingus tingle that said
germa when are you gonna play ed ed and eddie online is this the deep fake one let's see
yeah this is not even real this is deep fake you're right well i see people put me in situations
they deep fake me i can hear it in the distance uh but thank you uh buster boy for the three bucks
thank you to stiff funky chicken for the three bucks i don't know if you're in the mood for
watching videos this stream but i made some pretty short ones no links in chat so you can find the
three vids on youtube under this username uh hold the videos because we're going to do a
i'm gonna do it we're gonna do a once a month or once every probably to keep make sure that like
clips and videos are relevant and art is relevant we'll probably do it once every couple weeks
a video art community segment i've decided it's probably a good idea but i want to do
more than once a month because i once you do it stuff like that like i feel like mambo number five
stuff would not necessarily be relevant in like a month right so if somebody were to do something
every like two or three weeks i think sounds pretty good i like that idea but hold on to some
of that stuff we'll have an avenue for that eventually here over the coming a few weeks i
think a couple weeks probably but i do appreciate anything that you make you guys are really fucking
talented but thank you thank you dork cube for the 250 this candy tier list is inherently flawed
because it doesn't include all the types of m&m's i might agree that plain m&m's are f or d tier but
coffee nut m&m's a tier pretzel m&m's s tier also all this candy talk is reminding me of when
my cadets group it's the knockoff boy scouts would go to the memorial day parade and shoot candy
uh with a candy catapult like like launch it out like a t-shirt
walmart boy scouts a candy catapult that's so ridiculous m&m's are worthy of a b
hold up wait you're just giving candy away for free
uh free candy how could you not like it uh pretzel m&m's are amazing so are peanut butter m&m's
but they don't really they weren't there i agree with you uh wiki this thanks to the five bucks
fun fact sour patch kids are s plus dot dot dot dot dot dot in my opinion i mean that's a fun
fact fun fact is wrong thank you gnarly for the three bucks when will germa psycho be an
actual emote i don't know maybe down the road uh niall aureon aureon thanks for the three dollars
the i gotta go meme is my favorite i use it in real life and it still gets me
i gotta get out of here yeah look into it yeah uh niall aureon again thanks for the five dollars
on top of your three dollars you say germa bald won't last when reality will only become more
relevant in time yeah that's true can't go backwards on that one we can only go forward
uh invader z thanks for the 10 dollars invader z for invaders invaders z germa you're always
making me laugh and making my days and nights brighter thank you for that i don't have much
to offer but i want to support your streams and i'm happy to be a subscriber also i'm totally
going to make a germa psycho emote yeah if you i'm sure people will come up with some really wild
shit for that but thank you for the 10 dollars invaders happy to hang out here i'm just glad
you're enjoying the streams it means a lot thank you for the 10 bucks we also had uh 10 dollars
again from gts223 this list is junk why is zynga above king why is zynga above king i mean they're
both down there uh but thank you gts oh that link of me with the glue man shirt on that's not even
the same image but thank you uh gts thank you to thank you thank you to jeremy jeremy x morris
i don't know your name is but thank you for the 10 dollars hey germa do you plan on doing any
another green screen movie night another six months or so started working on a project a while
ago and didn't have time to make the deadline for the last movie night but i would still love to
participate in the next one if possible uh well i would probably we're probably not going to do
another green screen movie night what will probably end up happening is all those other
submissions or all those other things that um did i what did i do my cut did i cut out
no i think i'm good uh it would be part of the community night so we wouldn't do a oh yeah here's
the green screen movie night it would just be lumped in with here's the video portion of the
community night makes sense i think but thank you for the 10 bucks and hold on to it there'll be an
avenue for it soon uh thank you to apple shift for the 250 they say hey man my name is gwen i
just got into you a week or so ago and i've been watching all your classics for the first time
i'm loving them and i wanted to show you my drawing i did of you versus glue man i hope you like it
thank you for being you here's a link to it okay well welcome um thanks for stopping by welcome
to the channel all right they're pretty good let's put it on screen this is jacked me versus
glue man this is original this is an original look at this that's from the first ever germa rumble
right god if i was only that big still if i could only be that big too bad is that right that's
fantastic though welcome to the community welcome to the channel i'm not sure where you came from
where have you just randomly somebody showed you the channel or from another streamer or something
but welcome always happy to bring in new people for sure thank you so much for the art it's fucking
awesome and that was apple shift thank you this is good shit i love the glue man she made you tall
i am tall i am tall and i'm still young you're still young oh my god yeah but i know but i'm
i'm getting older you know they call 40 over the hill right i'm closer to 40 than i am
21 25 even closer to 40 than 25 i'm getting there it's gonna happen sooner than i think i gotta
hold on to my youth but let's show the credits i will be live tomorrow we'll do some dos games
hopefully we have a similar internet experience where it can actually work i hope this vpn really
did do something because it seems like it might be a little bit better than it was yesterday
in fact it is i mean clearly thank you to all the subs everybody that gave community subs
also this the fax machine gave five community subs earlier too and i may have missed it
you know right when i start talking about it that means like right right when you start to talk
about it that was bad are we done are we dead i think i'm off i think it's like actually shut off
holy shit yeah i like this guy like turned off that was pretty wild uh the fax machine gave five
community subs earlier is what i want to say and thankfully that kind of happened right at the very
end but thank you everybody yeah that that went right absolutely to zero better than yesterday
though the stream yesterday was seven hours and 40 minutes i think i dropped like 26 000 frames
this stream was six hours and it's 11 000 drop frames so uh better but not great better i'm just
gonna keep using the vpn and see what happens but uh we have a couple more bits to do we have um
on top of the five community subs right after that was uh mac jarlo for the four dollars here
germa want to thank you for your tf2 videos they're the reason why i started playing
yeah i'm thanks for watching the tf2 videos because that's where i started
thank you without the tf2 content i wouldn't be doing what i'm doing right now
so i really appreciate it thank you for the four dollars and finally at the very end we have
five dollars from flames flames 192 germa i don't know if you remember but you said ethan for my
friend's birthday then went on a long tangent that i took to heart i uploaded a video of my
friend enjoying the present as well included a soundboard of what you said for me thank you
again so much you made the day uh one of the most memorable birthdays ever
oh
wait am i like on a balloon oh my god
oh this is great what's that pizza
you gotta it got a birthday boy tag on here take a look that's fucking awesome
i'm more than happy to participate thank you so much for that that's hopefully you liked it
hopefully you thought it was funny but thank you the five dollars flames more than happy to
have fun and do that but ladies and gentlemen that's going to be it for me let's hope we get
some stability tomorrow as well as kind of we kind of had it today pray for the vpn and uh let's see
who's screaming right now let's do a raid who is live right now what do we got
what's vinnie doing vinnie vinnie is playing half life two episode two with a mod on it
that's cool modded half life two episode two yeah let's read vinnie go say hello it's a
graphics mod oh okay queue up say hello hang out i think my chat just crashed that was weird
all right i'll see you guys tomorrow have a good one dos games tomorrow take care tata for now
good night guys