Okay, all right. Hey, welcome. Yes. Thank you. Thank you, ladies and gentlemen. Welcome to the new show. Settle down. Settle down. Okay. Thank you very much.
Welcome to the new series here on German 985. It is a game show titled, What's the TF2 Sound?
So we're going to go ahead and invite our first ever contestant, Star Underscore. Welcome to the show, Star.
Hello. What were you doing today? I came all the way from Kentucky to be here on this.
Oh, right. Yeah. Okay. So here we go. You're going to have to guess the TF2 sound. Can you get it right? Here we go.
That's the scout. That's the scout. What is the TF2 sound?
That was just you. That wasn't the TF2. I thought you were going to get like an actual sound clip.
No, no, no. What was it? I don't know. What does that sound? You don't know what that is?
No, I don't know what that is. Yeah, cut, cut it. Cut the music. No, it was the Mini-Sentry. I don't know how you didn't get that.
That's not what it sounds like. Now, you see, I disagree, but not going to start an argument about this.
That's not the sound it makes. That is the sound it makes. It's rhythmic. It doesn't go...
No, that is the sound. I'm going to prove it to you right now. You want to hear? You want to hear? Are you listening?
You have to check it out right here. You want to hear the sound it makes? No. This is the sound it makes.
Well, it's set up time. So you're going to have to just wait a second. Okay. Watch out for the spy. Watch out for that spy.
I tried to warn him through voice communication and he didn't hear me. All right. Where are you?
I need to find you. I'm fucking dead. Oh, you died? You just watched him back there.
Well, you're about to get proven. Are you ready to get proved wrong? I'm ready to get proven. Okay, you're about to get proven.
Here we go. You're not with me. Oh, you're the healer. Okay. I'm the healer.
Take a listen. It's going to start here in a second. No, it's not. He blew it up. He's ubered. Run. Just run away.
Okay, now is the moment of truth. Now it's time for you to hear the Mini-Sentry sound. Ladies and gentlemen, here we go.
I think you're delaying. I think you're doing this on purpose. No, I'm just going back to the medicine cabinet to get some aspirin and let's go.
Okay, I'm following you everywhere. I'm the healer. Time to hear the sound once and for all.
I feel like this video is going to be 90% built up. Can we please make this thing? I want to just... All right, kill me.
Kill me? Okay, I'm going to put it down right here. Ladies and gentlemen, here we go. Time to hear the sound.
Here we go eventually. We're going to hear that this is not the sound. Listen to Sentry right now. It's just going beep beep. It beeps like one. It doesn't go beep beep beep. It beeps.
No, it goes beep beep beep. See, you're going to hear it double because of this guy. I'm going to hear a lot of it. He's going to Rancho Relaxo all over this beep beep beep beep beep beep.
See, right now, listen carefully. No, now no one's going to come over here.
Just wait. Somebody will come through the door. Going up the right side. I'm currently moving up the right side.
Just put it in this corner. Just put it in that corner and someone will come out eventually. No, not that fucking corner.
Why? I shot it over here. They're going to come out the door and just see it. This corner? This corner. Like sneak it.
All right, it's very sneaky. That's a very sneaky...
Okay, now we just need to wait and hear the sound.
Yeah, and we're going to see who's right and who's wrong. I think it goes beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep beep.
You don't think so. I don't think so this scout this scouts gonna get didi didi didi, but not that doesn't
I would love for him to walk out here
Will you just walk out here?
He's gonna do this forever
He's gone. Oh
See listen. Oh, no, did you hear that?
You heard it didn't you?
No, no, no, no, no, it never did that before. Why is it doing it? It's doing it. It's not doing it
I do you can't have my bananas. I just bought those are my bananas. I'm taking them from you
I would have to wash my dishes again. Look at all these look at all these didi didis. I'm getting you want
Oh, you think it's gonna work. What is going on in here? It's me. I'm the medic, but I'm the medic. Oh, you're this medic
Things in your brain just don't add up right away do they
Hey, I'm this medic
Oh, you're this medic
Right. Well for the second part of this, but that's a sad despite for the second part of this video
I need you to be on my team
Okay, this is my heart and join your team. This is part two of the sounds
What's how do they make them? So?
for part two
Quite quite quite quite quite quite quite what sound is that in the game tf2?
That is no sound in tf2. You just screamed for like the 12 seconds. Oh, that's not a sign. That's you great joke
I think I already fucking made it. No, that sound isn't tf2. Oh really?
What was that sense you have to guess you have to figure it out
So you tell me there is on this map mine at least was close
Yours was not yours was nothing your mind was close enough. You you just be like
No, that sound is part of this map the ecosystem. Is it the cart? Did I win? No, it's a weapon
Oh, so it's we were only doing weapons like you did the weapon slinger do it again for me. It's different every time
That is not a sound you have to know it's a gun
rocket launcher no
grenade launcher no cold
the scatter gun
No, no, no, no, no, no, you're not thinking the right way katana. No
What the fuck is it then? It's
Someone I mean, it doesn't have been the huntsman the huntsman. No
I
Lock and load. No, this is great. Yes. Yes
Thank God, how did I not get that? I know it doesn't hurt people that was the clue
I know is it hurting such as good is it hurting such as good such as good is it healing such as good?
well that uh
That sounds absolutely nothing like what you did
No, that's exactly what it is. Like the no the first initial activation. It starts off like that and it goes down
Okay, well we got that that mystery solved
I'm gonna go ahead and play some demo night for the remainder of the video and then end the video