Let me tell you something about Origin, okay? Here comes a five minute Origin Rage.
Right? That guy right now just wrote that and was just like, I fucking knew it.
And it was a joke. I'm good to go. How you guys doing?
And if it's your first time on the stream, my name is Jeremy. Your name is Dan.
One of your name is Dan. Hope you're doing good.
No, no Rage tonight. Not tonight. I'm gonna do Minecraft VR.
Not today. On the next VR stream, I'm gonna do Minecraft VR.
Am I drinking? I am not drinking. No. Not tonight.
Not gonna drink tonight. No. Because I have a doctor's appointment tomorrow.
So I'm not gonna drink a bunch of booze and then go to a doctor's appointment the next day.
So that means there's no stream tomorrow because that appointment is
right in the middle of the kind of evening afternoon.
Boomer health. Have I heard that Sims 4 has first person mode?
Yes, it is kind of the reason why I'm doing this stream.
I have a shitload of mods. If you remember, if you were here,
if you're part of the channel about a year ago, we did Sims 4 with a bunch of dog shit going on.
What's with the- I don't know what the word dog shit is with me lately.
It's like the fourth or fifth time I've said it.
Oh, dog shit. You know, I got lots of dog shit.
I need to extend the vocabulary today.
Uh, that was in November, December, January, February, March, April.
All right, so it's been like four or five months.
No, it's been longer than that.
No, no, that's been- it's been longer than that.
I wasn't in Vegas during that stream.
Yeah, that was like j- that was like June of last year.
I was not in Vegas during the Sims 4 stream.
Oh yeah, no, that was a long time ago.
So it's been just about seven months.
Has it really been that long?
I can't believe- I like- thinking about it out loud is like,
oh yeah, it's been like just under a year.
It's been like seven months.
It's like, man, I feel like that was like two months ago.
And then again, I think about it, I've lived in Vegas now for almost five months.
It's like, didn't I just get here?
I just got here.
Strange.
But anyways, uh, a lot of you probably weren't here.
During those streams and what this stream is going to be is a continuation of that.
Mods.
Lots of them.
Sims killing each other.
Sims doing drugs.
Animals doing drugs.
I got a bunch more too.
There's at least two or three other mods you have not seen yet.
And first person, figured we would give it a try.
No sex mods.
I'm not doing that.
I cannot do that.
Did you get more?
I did get more.
No, sex mods would get me actually in trouble with the platform.
Am I ever going to do a normal Sims game?
No, I can't after this.
After like watching Sims get chewed up by chainsaws, I can't go back and play the Sims.
We tried to do that.
Do you remember?
And I'm going to put a rule on this stream too.
Because once you climb over that hill, you just start to fall down.
You hit the peak and you just start tumbling.
The first person that gets a knife in their back is the catalyst to the snowball.
So we got to be prepared for it.
Anyways, are you ready to make the new family?
Because we're not doing old family gone.
New family coming in.
The Elbertsons 2.
We need a better name than that.
Let's go ahead and turn this off here.
Yeah, I don't know how important any of this shit is.
There's a weird thing about The Sims 4, right?
Does this have the most DLC out of any video game ever made?
It really might.
I don't even have this.
Get famous.
I don't have the get famous collection.
Look at all this though.
Game packs.
Stuff packs.
I don't even want any of it.
It doesn't have all the DLC.
It's just like 600 bucks for all this shit.
Each one of these is like $19.99.
You want me to spend 12 grand on The Sims 4?
Train Simulator has more DLC.
Yeah, it does.
EA Omega Lul.
I got BTTV.
Buy the vampire pack?
The vampire pack is not...
Okay, listen.
The Sims.
Strangerville.
Start your investigation and solve the mystery of a desert town that holds a dark, deep,
dark secret.
Guys, chainsaws can go through people's heads in our mod we have right now.
Do you really give a shit about this?
The Sims.
Jungle adventure.
Take your Sims on a mysterious adventure into the wild.
Discover new things, new cultures.
A guy can do acid and like pee on his floor.
This is all small potatoes to what we're doing here.
New family time.
Are you ready?
I'm not gonna buy the DLC.
All right, so you're probably looking at...
You've got...
Look, you see resume playing Bill.
That's because I had to make sure the mods worked.
So I had to just make a person.
Don't worry, we're gonna revict them.
You didn't see that, okay?
You didn't see that.
I just needed to make sure that they worked.
All right.
I don't want to live here, by the way.
We...
What did we do last time?
I want to try a different place because we got Willow Creek, Oasis Springs.
Anyone remember where we lived?
I think we lived like in Newcrest or something.
Going to the city?
Newcrest?
I think we did...
Oh yeah, we did the desert last time.
Let's do Newcrest.
Newcrest.
Or the Night City, this one.
Boring.
This one.
Yeah, but is it always nighttime here?
I don't like that.
You want it to be always nighttime?
Look, it's fucking always nighttime.
Oh cool, there's like a gym here?
Planet Honey Pop.
Karaoke bar.
Okay.
Uh, what the...
That's...
Why the...
Okay, I'm freaking out right now.
All right, anyways.
Where the hell am I supposed to live?
You want me to live in like one of these fucking apartments?
I have...
I'm gonna have a huge family.
There's gonna be a bunch of like dogs, cats, aliens.
You want me to live in one of these like New York City high rises?
Superior Cream just came in 50 bucks from Superior Cream.
Thank you so much, Superior Cream.
Five zero.
Fifty.
And...
They say, I'm Michael, it's my birthday today.
Cake and ice cream is on its way.
Thought I'd share some birthday cheer for all the best content.
Thank you so much.
Happy birthday.
You shouldn't be giving me money on your birthday.
But thanks a lot.
Means a fucking shitload.
Hope you have a fantastic birthday.
Thanks for joining us for your birthday.
Where are we going?
Uh, map.
Can I live in the art studio?
Studio apartments?
House apartments?
What about this one?
No, I don't want to live in the city.
Art family.
Not fine.
All right.
This is going to be the ship family.
Let us click.
Okay, all right, fine.
Fine, you guys get to pick where I live.
I have to be able to afford it though.
No, I don't have any money.
Are these places expensive?
They are.
I think these places are actually really expensive.
Just cheat and add money.
I could do that.
It's Control Shift C, right?
I need to use it for one of the mods I have anyways.
All right, here you go.
Where am I living?
Wow, very divided.
Exceptionally divided it seems.
I can't live in the park.
I can't live here.
I don't know why you're clicking it.
Can I live in here?
This is the one it seems.
Okay, all two apartments.
No way to do it.
All right, all right, hold on, hold on.
Wait, let's do this actually democratically.
Hold on.
You ready?
Go for it.
I want the true democratic experience.
That doesn't matter.
Everybody wants me to live in the night town.
I'm not buying this.
I'm not going to buy these.
No, no, I refuse 100%.
I'm going here.
Ready?
Now pick the place.
Three, two, one, go for it.
This is the only choice that you guys are going to get the whole stream.
So make it count.
I got to cheat and give myself money.
I don't know if the cheat is to do that though.
Why does everybody want me to live here?
Mother load, okay.
Did I do it?
Did that work?
I have to have a family first, okay.
All right, so this is where we're going.
We're going to go to this auto apartments.
Thank you for voting.
Let's go make the family.
Welcome to the next, probably at least hour of the spring.
And everyone that has, there you go.
You're about to see why.
Kind of don't want to change anything.
For like three hours.
Okay, I got to get the cheat thing off.
Forehead.
It made it perfect.
I don't know what I even want to do here.
All right, first of all, let's get out of this.
Let's do some detail work on the head.
Always start on the head.
It looks like daisy duck.
Well, let's go ahead and make daisy duck.
Daisy duck?
Like Donald Duck's girlfriend?
Donald Duck's like fiance?
That's, is that who daisy duck is?
How does this look like daisy duck?
All right, let's keep this, let's go.
So let's get, I want to do some detail here.
Bring the lips down.
Okay, let's go with a bit more fat on the outside.
Forehead being down looks fine.
Now bring this in.
Should we see the eyes?
I don't think so.
All right, now all the way down.
A little, maybe a little bit skinnier.
I liked it the way it was.
No, no, no, we can't make like another chuck schnozwell.
That's good.
Like that.
Put the nose right at the top of the mouth.
Now that actually looks like a duck.
Why don't just make the duck, right?
That works, right?
All right, let's back it up a little bit.
That actually scared the shit out of me.
I jumped a little bit backwards.
I want to grab the cheat.
I got to get rid of the hair.
Oops.
No, no, the head's way too big.
There we go.
Harry, Harry, you got to go.
Let's get something different here.
I like this one.
Not bad.
I don't hate it.
No, I don't want the nose.
The nose doesn't do it for me right now.
No, pull it back.
Uh-oh.
I think I've ruined it forever.
There we go.
Okay.
Yeah, I prefer...
The nose makes it just too weird.
That looks better.
Okay.
The hair, though, needs to be changed.
I don't hate this.
That looks fine.
Hold on, wait.
What about just like the Marge Simpson?
It's not the Marge Simpson, but...
The forehead needs to be bigger.
I'm not sure I can even make the forehead bigger.
Oh, shit.
Fixed.
Don't worry, fixed.
No, that's...
I can't make the forehead any bigger.
That's what you got.
Ooh, he's a head shape.
No, no, no.
We'll keep that hair.
No accessories.
Oh, it's makeup.
Okay.
No hats.
Makeup.
Should we just have big eyes up here?
Can I do that?
Can I paint that myself?
Holy shit.
That's terrifying.
Is there a way I can do this myself?
Eyes, cheeks, face paint.
There's no way.
Can I not just do it?
I made Dory from Finding Nemo.
Okay, let's mess around here.
The wrench at the bottom.
At the bottom, like here.
What the fuck is that?
I don't know what that is.
That just burst out.
Holy shit.
Why is that under face paint?
All right, whatever.
That's fine.
Now, let's go back to here.
Change some stuff around here.
Should we just give her a little like goat feet?
That looks fine.
Let's bring those shoulders in.
Extend the arms out a little bit.
Need to have like...
All right, what about...
Oh Christ.
Okay, hold on.
Big like thick neck.
The pear.
All right, we made the pear.
Okay, and then let's have...
That's all right.
No, it needs to be the color.
I got to get the right color here.
Is it just a onesie that you can put on?
No, no, that's not going to work.
Can I just put her in a big pear colored onesie?
I don't know if that is it.
I'm afraid to plug it.
I don't know what this is.
I'm terrified.
Oh, it just makes them invisible.
But what would that be for?
Just a floating person?
A ghost lady?
I don't know.
What is this?
Oh, just a dress.
That's not bad.
That's kind of a pretty good pear.
I like this one.
There we go.
Yeah, like Pauline Pear.
We need a last name here.
The pear family?
No, this is not going to be the pear family.
That means every single person has to have their last name be pear.
Do you want me to make a series of fruits?
The fruit family?
You just want them to be all like bananas, apples, and oranges and shit?
Is this worth three hours?
Can I make...
Okay, is there...
All right, so this we got...
Is this a green apple?
Is this blueberry?
Oh, can I do a custom color?
I hate this.
I don't want to continue doing this.
Because we're going to have like an apple.
We're going to have a blueberry.
We're going to have a banana.
Is there like...
All right, fine.
This lipstick's got to go though.
Okay, we have to have more than one family.
You guys understand that, right?
Because this is going to be a drug dealer.
This is going to be animals.
We're going all out tonight.
Make a vegetable family?
No.
Make the whole city food.
How am I going to do that?
It's just fruits, vegetables, meats, and cheeses?
Take the food land?
No, that's going to take me like all day.
I actually kind of like the idea of the food group family.
Where it's like a...
Well, we already had bread.
Fats, oils, meats, cheeses, vegetables, fruits.
Let's see how far I can take this.
And then I'm going to move on.
Welcome to the rest of the streams.
I'm serious.
All right, we need like a different color.
Here we go.
It looks better.
All right, there's Pauline pear fruit.
Make a hamburger.
All right, personality traits.
Let's see.
Food, master chef.
They all have to be chefs.
Hot-headed, self-assured, goofball, creative, active.
Because it's a pear.
Let's see here.
We got art lover, foodie, ambitious, clumsy.
This is all about what a pear would be.
Childish maybe?
No.
Probably pretty neat.
Vegetarian, snob.
Hold on.
Let's look at the other categories.
Broke, lover, mean, noncommittal, loner.
Vegetarian.
That's pretty terrible considering.
Just...
Okay.
That's actually kind of scary.
All right, we're good.
Pauline pear.
It's the fruit family coming up next.
We have...
All right, is it going to be berry, blueberry?
Berry banana?
All right, that looks good.
Default walk style.
Berry banana.
I'm not going to make the annoying orange.
Banana would be pretty confident.
Roommates with Pauline pear.
Sweet.
Okay, that's good.
Benedict banana.
Benedict.
Banana.
I can't fit it.
How about Ben banana?
Ben banana fruit.
Last name.
Oh, that's right.
Ben banana.
But don't...
Oh no, they can be roommates.
It's not The Sims 2.
Benedict.
Benedict banana.
I didn't spell that right.
Ben-edict.
Make Benedict cucumber?
And make it a cucumber.
What?
No, just have it be Dr. Strange.
Benedict cucumber patch.
Just make him green.
No, no, no, no, no.
All right, we got to focus.
Focus on the banana.
Benedict banana.
Fuck this already.
How am I going to do this?
How am I going to make Benedict banana?
Is it looking costumes?
Is there actually like a banana costume?
Let's see.
Suit jackets, business swimsuit, vests, full body.
Costumes.
Banana.
First person to die, by the way.
No, this should be the drug dealer.
No, all right.
Focus, focus, focus, focus, focus, focus.
Take this costume off.
No banana though, unfortunately.
But there is a hot dog.
But what if I make the hot dog?
Can I color the hot dog?
Can we just pretend this is a banana?
I can't make this a different color.
It's a banana.
Yes.
Okay, guys, this is a peeled banana in a bun.
With mustard on it.
No, that's just, that's banana puree.
Okay, can I do anything else with that?
Okay, let's see if I can make this work for all of us.
Let's go in closer here.
Bring it out.
Bring the face in.
Okay, really, it's hard to do this with the...
I need to get in there.
It's hard to get in there though,
because its head is so in such a strange place.
I wish I could move the camera more with a detailed edit,
because see how it's too big?
Pull that in.
Angel fish.
There we go.
It's a good start.
Pull these ears back.
I really need to get a hold of here.
I can't.
I can make his head temporarily smaller.
Damn it.
You really don't want to let me grab that, do you?
Okay, I need to bring these out further.
Oh, shit.
There we go.
I need the back of his head.
Come on, give me the back of the head.
We got to kill all the eyebrows and shit.
No facial hair.
Get rid of the eyebrows too.
It's Lex Luthor.
Not quite.
I need this to come up.
I need to get under here and like pull that up.
It's too long.
See, I can't even grab it.
Jesus Christ, this is horrifying.
Okay, I need to get these eyebrows out of here.
Okay, hair.
Facial hair.
Accessories, eyebrows.
Delete eyebrows.
Okay, there we go.
I can't get rid of them.
Yeah, yeah, I can.
Oh, this sucks.
This sucks.
Absolute ass.
Put them back?
No, I'm not going to put them back.
I need this skull to come up.
All right, let's widen it a little more.
He's ripping through the costume with his banana face.
Let's see if I can pull this middle back one more time.
Okay, I can.
There we go.
That's good.
I'm looking.
I need that on this side.
How do I get that little tilt there?
Come on, give me that tilt right here.
Let me see his mouth.
No, that's too fucked up.
We can't go totally fucked up.
He has to at least kind of look like a person.
That's pretty banana-like.
It is.
All right, all right.
Now we need a hat.
The nose is a little too extreme.
I agree.
Now we just need a pointy hat.
Let's see.
Let's see if we can get it.
Any like goofy funny hats?
Kind of, but I can't.
No, that doesn't work.
That doesn't work.
This is not even going to fit on his face.
Yes, it does.
Yeah, why can't you have Darth Vader?
Please be yellow.
Oh, come on.
That is as good as it's going to get.
That is a banana in a bun with some hot dogs.
That was perfect.
Even more like a hot dog.
It's not a hot dog.
It's a banana.
It's a peeled banana.
You got to go with what you can work with here.
I can't make a banana.
It's not a tofu dog.
It's a banana.
Hold on.
Can I give him a jacket or something so I can cover this up?
No, no, no.
It has to be this.
Tops.
Can I throw something else on top?
No.
God damn it.
Shit.
Yellow tux.
No, but it doesn't work.
I can't do a yellow tux.
Okay, it kind of does work.
Wait, wait, wait.
It looks like a mustard dispenser.
Hold on.
He's just like a regular guy in a suit but just happens to also be a banana.
That's not bad.
Just do a filter for yellow.
Let's get, oh, let me get, let me get out a full body.
I actually kind of liked, oh, look at this one.
I like the idea of he's just a regular guy but really, really, really took on that banana persona
and is just killing it.
Plus, make sure we pick stuff that they're wearing that it's easy enough for me to replicate
when these assholes inevitably end up in the next rumble.
Hold on.
I said that's too yellow.
That is mustard.
This is banana.
Let's see, what do we get for bottoms?
Oh no, you're right.
You're right.
We got to make some very, very minor changes here because this is just like dickhead man.
This is just penis guy.
This is not even a banana.
Okay, I got to fix this.
A banana just is a dick.
If you think about it, how do I fix this?
I'm talking like I'm going to create a character.
I'm making a peeled banana and it's this, a peeled banana is this kind of like fleshy color.
Just make it yellow.
I can't.
All right, he's just, he's just going in a regular, he's going in regular clothes.
Take off the hot dog head.
That makes it so much better because that is, he is a banana.
He's just a guy with a big chin here.
No, that has to stay.
All right, let's go.
Time to complete this guy.
I'm going to put him in, what was that suit I had before?
No, no.
He's unfriendly and scary.
How do you know that?
Just make him a real person.
What is that?
What?
Oh, there it is.
Why did his chin get smaller?
Excuse me.
What happened to his, what happened to him?
He lost all of his charm, his eyes.
That's okay.
That's actually pretty good because it's not as extreme.
I don't hate this.
The outfit fucked it up.
All right, looks good.
This is Benedict Banana.
Gonna change the bottom here.
No, he's not gonna be jacked.
He's gonna be skinny.
Hot dog hat and the yellow raincoat.
Should I just take the hot dog hat off?
Is it technically still on?
Yeah, it's technically still on.
Nah, it doesn't change anything.
It's perfect.
All right, we need to 100% perfect.
That's the banana.
Peel.
He's peeled back.
All right, let's see what I'm gonna do for pants here.
Whoa, hey, hey, hey.
What?
Oh, because this is full body.
We can't change the pants.
Oh, what the fuck?
What happened to that?
That's kind of dumb.
Well, that's the way it's gonna be.
There's Benedict Banana for you.
And this is every day.
Yellow rain.
Dude, the shoes, the yellow rain boots.
I don't even know if they have that shit.
Boots here.
So what's going on here then?
All right, that looks good.
Benedict Banana.
Banana's a potassium, right?
Chef.
Genius.
It's a brain power food.
No, it helped.
It's got plenty of vitamins in it.
Cheerful.
I would say childish as well.
Lots of kids eat bananas.
It's in every lunchbox in America.
Clumsy.
Why would a banana be clumsy?
How would a banana be clumsy?
All right, got Benedict Banana.
I gotta change.
Okay, so you're done.
I gotta change your name to Pauline Pear
and not have it be the Pauline Pear.
Oh, it's because it was a banana.
I get it.
Pauline Pear.
All right, we're gonna make...
Let's make Apple Andy.
How's that sound?
Apple Andy.
All right, let's see.
How am I gonna do Apple?
Adam Apple.
And just have him have a huge neck,
like a big fucking bump on the front of his neck.
Let me see if I can do that first
and then we'll go from there.
I don't think I can do that.
All right, we need to get the first things first.
You should add a baby
so you can have like a baby carrot.
No, no, I'm not going to add a baby
considering the in-fucking-sane mods
that are in this game.
That's not gonna happen.
That would be the worst mistake
I probably could ever make.
I'm telling you right now,
trust me when I say no baby.
No, no, no, no.
Boo.
All right, we gotta have a huge head.
There's an apple.
That might be too big.
All right, get rid of the hair.
Let's go with no eyebrows.
None of them should have eyebrows.
Fuck the eyebrows.
They're fruits.
All right, what does an apple look like?
It's square, right?
I mean, it's...
First of all, no, I'm fucking kidding.
Do you even have a face?
No, how big should the nose be?
Nothing extreme because that's just like dumb.
I can go absurd with this shit.
What is like the...
Hold on, where did I get the...
I know I can tilt.
Where's the thing to pull it down?
I just want to show you this
because it's fucking crazy.
If I can get it to catch on it,
you'll see just how stupid this is.
That's nothing.
If I can get the camera in the right place,
you can actually do some stupid shit.
Somebody has to be a dinosaur.
Damn it, come on.
It's just so hard to grab.
Is there a way that I can make it do like tilt or stretch?
Or do I have to have it be in the exact spot?
Is there a certain combination of buttons I can do?
Hold shift, detail edit,
because yes, I'm trying to get the little tilt thing
because I can pull this all the way down to the ground if I want.
I'm certain of it.
I got to get like the combination to do it.
So it's crazy.
Make the nose small first.
All right, there, not that one.
All right, right here.
That's what I'm looking for.
I want that on the nose.
Come on, let me see it.
I'm just, I'm just making Michael Cera.
Come on, do it.
Just do it.
No.
Oh, whatever.
Make it normal.
This is supposed to be an apple, right?
Yeah, pull the bridge out.
It's too deep.
It needs to be way fatter than this.
That's not a bad head shape.
When I said square, what I'm talking about is,
you know how an apple has sort of the beefy buff chest
and then comes down a little bit?
Some of you guys know what I'm talking about.
It's fine.
Any bigger than that.
That looks good.
Okay, look, maybe the head a little bit bigger.
Look at that.
Perfect apple.
It just is.
I want to make the head wider, but I don't think I can.
That's all right.
It looks good.
Oh, Jojo, right?
The Jojo song.
I don't know why I just did that.
That's all I could just hear right there.
That like, I don't even know what it is.
What does it say?
It goes like, the torture dance, right?
That don't ask me why the fuck I just did that,
but hey, there it is.
Vocal percussion on a whole nother level.
There it is.
For those of you that are watching,
I've never seen that show.
I don't know what it is.
And we want like a big happy family for the apple.
Love?
Nature?
No.
Apples want like a big huge...
Look, that's an apple tree.
Very, very clear.
Self-assured.
They're kind of assholes.
They think they're the best fruit in the bunch.
No, he's not done.
I just want to get this out of the way first.
Love the halfway half of this.
Oh, we didn't get to see it.
That's sicko.
You're fucked up.
Okay.
How does this sound?
That's perfect for me.
All right, we're gonna add hair.
I mean, just stem.
That's not gonna work.
That's way too frayed out to be a stem.
Is there a single ponytail I can put up?
What about the bun?
That's pretty close.
So is that.
Oh, God.
But that could be a tomato.
That's not even a fucking apple.
It doesn't need to be brown.
What about this one?
This one's a little smaller.
I think that's as close as it's gonna be.
All right, what about clothes?
Tomato is a fruit.
Should he just have no clothes on at all?
I feel like an apple wouldn't have any clothes on.
Apple's very basic.
Doesn't need anything.
You don't add stuff to apples.
You just eat it.
At least make the underwear red.
Yeah, I'll try.
What do you got right now?
Can I make it red?
I can.
All right, there's Apple Andy.
Actually, it should be Andy Apple.
Last name is gonna be the fruit.
Change this into a formal outfit.
This is everyday.
Formal.
No, I'm keeping that.
I'm not taking this off.
Why would I take that off?
Who's next in this shit show?
We're gonna go with five.
What's left?
Apple, pear, banana, apple, blueberry.
Do we already have a berry?
Is it berry banana?
No, it's Benedict banana.
Okay, okay.
The candy one that sounds better.
Wait, wouldn't blueberry...
No, blueberry would have a tiny head.
Not a big one.
Wouldn't a blueberry be little...
Did you just say blueberry Andy?
Why would I make this guy's name blueberry Andy?
I do that.
Okay, let's detail this up.
I think the chin, everything has to come up.
Everything.
Small, condensed.
I'm losing his neck here.
Let's make you...
What?
No, no, no, no, no.
Yeah, yeah.
Smaller head or right.
I can't make it that much smaller.
That's as small as I can make it.
Without distorting.
I mean, why is it that long?
Okay, that looks not bad at all actually.
Let me just go in here.
Do the eyebrows.
Should the blueberry just have eyebrows?
Why would that happen?
I don't know why the blueberry has big ears.
Nice.
Looking good.
Hold on.
I gotta fix that.
Eyes gotta be a little smaller.
They're taking up too much space.
Holy fuck.
He looks like he's in pain.
I gotta bring this in.
In.
Come in.
You look like a guy wearing a slipknot mask.
Okay, I want to bring this up and pull this back.
Oh no, I think I broke it.
No, I didn't.
We're good.
This is Gonzo from The Muppets is who this is turning into.
All right, back to normal.
I think my hands are up right now.
How big?
I need to make you a little bit smaller.
Okay, let's go.
No, this is fine.
Berry blueberry is done.
This is just a house of the gushers fruit people.
Yeah, it kind of is.
All right, Berry.
No, he needs clothes.
Everyone just can't be naked.
Make him short?
I can't.
I can't without making him a child.
I can't do it and I can't have a child in this game.
This is guys, this is gonna be like a fucking long ass stream.
Okay.
All right, here we go.
Smaller, small.
I can't.
I can't do it.
It's gonna fuck it all up.
If I go down to...
No, his whole head is...
Everything's gonna be fucked up.
All of his head is gonna be misshaped.
I'm gonna have to do it all over again.
No, do you see how long this took?
I'm not making Berry blueberry again.
The undo button with control Z.
If this fucks it up, I'm gonna scream.
Okay, it works.
Do you understand?
Teen didn't do anything.
See?
Young adult didn't do anything.
You have to make them a child.
No, no, no.
How far?
Thank God.
Do you understand why this cannot be in the game?
Nope, I'm sorry.
I gotta stand on my moral soapbox here.
Old man.
No, I'm gonna keep the way it was.
You have to make a prune.
All right, let's get through.
We got Berry blueberry.
Let's get the aspirations.
It's a brain food.
Nerd brain.
Blueberries are a little on the...
They're blue, right?
Childish.
Hmm.
Berry blueberry.
There you go.
Okay.
Now we need another one.
All right.
I'm kind of sick of the fruit theme at this point.
This is one house.
One apartment.
So we've got pear, apple...
Pear, banana, apple, blueberry, grape, baby carrot, or riot.
No.
I ain't gonna have...
I ain't gonna be the guy that...
No.
Uh-uh.
Grandpa lemon?
Let me see.
Let me see what I can do here.
We could do...
What else is green?
Like a lettuce?
Larry lettuce?
Is that gonna work?
Lenny lettuce.
Grandpa lime.
Lemon, lemon, lemon.
We don't have like a pure yellow, yellow, yellow.
A kiwi?
Yeah, but that kind of like grandpa lettuce.
Can I make a piece of lettuce?
Let's see.
What would...
What would lettuce be?
But that's not a fruit though.
We'll do a lime.
Or a raisin.
Let's see what we get.
Let's go in here.
Hmm.
I actually like it already.
Just a big head for a raisin.
I'm done.
I'm not gonna do any more...
This is it.
Fix the shoes?
What's wrong with the Donald Duck shoes?
It's a prune.
Grandpa prune.
All right.
I gotta change the nose a little bit though.
If he's...
If it's grandpa, grandpa has to have like a really bulbous, fucked up nose.
If it is a grandpa, how's that?
Not too crazy.
Just enough.
I have to keep it.
Jesus Christ.
I can't even select anything.
A little on the buggy side.
It's old.
Not that much though.
All right.
Can I get rid of the Wolverine sideburns?
Oh God.
It's like broken.
A little bit more.
That's gotta be bulbed.
I need that now.
What the front?
There we go.
That's better.
Okay, good.
I need the eyes to be spread out a little more than that.
Bring him up.
No, that's too too clipped.
Too much clipping.
Okay, I'm good with that.
There they are.
You just made the old guy from up?
Yeah, I did.
Now I'm gonna leave it like that.
Except for the sideburns.
They look just stupid.
Now I miss them.
Shit.
I miss those sideburns now.
Bustache maybe?
Somebody's gotta have a beard, right?
No, I don't...
The Wolverine looks just...
It doesn't look good.
That one's fine.
Now I don't like this one because it takes away from his face.
Bring the shoulders in.
Get the ass a little bit bigger.
Prunes aren't blue.
Yeah, well, I can't...
I can't make anybody like purple.
All I can do is give them...
Look, I gave them the correct hair color.
Make them more wrinkly.
Okay, let's get the name here.
Do I just make them green and just call them like a kiwi or something?
I can't...
I want the...
I'm gonna keep the eyebrows, I think.
Maybe not because he has facial hair.
So why wouldn't I keep the eyebrows?
He does look like a Warcraft gnome.
It just is.
Should they be living...
No, this has to be FRUITS ONLY.
Just pretend he's a Warcraft gnome.
Peter Plumb.
All right, all right, all right.
We got one, two, three, four, five in the fruit household.
Let's do some detail work here on the face.
What the fuck is this?
It's the creepypasta Plumb with YouTuber hair.
Put him back.
What is going on?
What are these?
Look at this shit.
What's with the weird smiling shit?
I don't know what that means.
That's just a terrible selfie.
These are all just bad selfies.
You go through and you delete these in your phone.
Okay, more wrinkles.
These are fate.
No, this is screwed all up.
Skin detail.
Laugh lines.
I guess you can kind of see them.
All right, Peter Plumb is ready.
Different clothes, though.
These clothes suck.
Not even purple.
You don't have purple here?
That's fine.
It is a vet shirt, isn't it?
Why would it...
Yeah, I'm just realizing this now.
Better.
All right, here's the fruit household.
We've got Pauline Pear, Benedict Banana, Andy Apple, Barry Blueberry, and Peter Plumb.
It's still a vet.
That's fine.
He's a vet.
Change that shirt.
No.
All right, let's move them in and we can make another family.
I have to make a drug dealer.
We're going to make the gnome a drug dealer.
I'm going to make him the only one that's worth the shit in this house.
Okay, more than five is too much.
This family is ready to go.
Let's make sure to double check.
Pauline Pear, Benedict Banana, there's the apple.
No, you need to be in your everyday wear.
This berry, Blueberry, and you got Peter Plumb.
Okay, name him Ben Anna.
Blueberry.
Leopard gnome.
I can't get over that.
I'm trying to get over it.
I can't.
Peter Plumb is the wrong color.
It doesn't matter.
Who cares?
Is that better?
Make him just rotten.
Gray food.
What color is it?
Plumb.
Second row.
What color is it?
Plumb.
Let me see.
Purple.
I think that's, that's actually, that's, I think this is close.
I'm gonna get it.
Is that, that's too, can you see?
Is it purple makeup?
But there might be.
Probably not full face though.
Peter Plumb.
Look at the color of prune.
Prune.
The prunes are like, prunes are raisins.
Now that's close enough.
Just go download more colors.
Is there actually like a, can I actually get a mod that it's,
yeah, but I'd have to leave the game.
Prunes are raisins.
Get the color wheel mod.
Yeah, you know, it's probably, it's probably simple.
Can any of the mods give me just a quick link while I finish this up?
Because I'll get like actual like purple.
It'll be worth it.
Yeah, it will.
We're taking this long to set this up anyways.
Yeah, most of the mods for The Sims 4 you just drag into the mod folder anyways.
Let me just close this out.
I can edit, I can edit the family at any time.
So this is good to go.
We'll get that later.
You have to save the family though to use the mod.
That's all good.
Okay.
So I got this family.
We're going to move them in.
Let's see.
Click the check to save the pear household.
No, this is the, no, this is the fruits.
The fruits household.
Okay.
I need to make sure the game is saved.
That's better.
Now, okay.
The fruits.
So they've got 28 grand.
Let me just cheat real quick.
No way.
Okay.
Hold on.
So this is for, this is one bedroom, two bath.
This is four bedroom, three bath.
Weekly rent is $3,500 a week.
Who's my neighbor?
Lobo?
All right.
This is the one that has to be with only this five people.
Furnishing is a hundred thousand dollars.
A huge family home with luxury chef's kitchen.
This apartment is the epitome of uptown chic living.
Let's go.
Remaining funds, negative 87,000.
I don't want the damn thing furnished.
I can't even do this.
I have to move into like a shitty place
then get a bunch of money and move.
Type free real estate.
Command fail.
Free, you need to enable cheats.
Testing cheats on.
Oh, is it on?
Command fail.
I need to move a family in first.
Yes, I have to like go to one of these shitty places then.
I'm just gonna Google it before I just get debated
for the next 30 minutes.
Sims cheats.
Open the cheat console.
Bring up the cheat dialog box.
Enter cheats.
Don't forget to press the yeah.
Okay.
Thanks.
Thanks for telling me how to open the cheat box.
Hey, here's how you open the cheat box.
That's it.
Okay, thanks.
All right, here we go.
I'm gonna get like five auto playing videos.
Okay.
Testing cheats space true.
Now, let's see if that does anything.
All right, so I'm just gonna move.
I have to move into a random place.
Why can't I just do it from the menu?
All right, I need to find like a little shitty apartment.
All of us have to move in here.
All right, good luck.
Would you like to move in with or evict the Pizzai victim?
Get the fuck out of my way.
Yeah, I got rid of the pizza family.
All right, here we go.
This is really important.
I have to like pause the game
because there are a ton of fucked up mods.
And I need to be totally sure that nothing happens here when I'm gone.
Because if I get...
Hold on.
What are you doing?
No, no, no, no.
Go back, go back, go back.
Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick.
What the hell just happened?
Get in here before everybody kills each other.
Come on.
How do I...
What just happened?
Oh my God.
Okay, thank God.
There we go.
All right, let's get out of here.
That's good.
All right, let's live right here.
Move.
Invite up to seven other Sims.
Select sit...
No, no, no, no.
Buy.
We're traveling.
Okay, do I...
How do I like get them out of here?
You have to use your phone to move.
Oh, okay.
Check social media.
Plan an event.
Work.
Household.
Here's the dealing drugs.
Buy a retail, buy a vet.
Purchase gifts.
Hire a service.
God damn it.
Oh, fuck that.
You evicted people to move somewhere else.
Travel.
Move household.
That's not traveling.
Okay, okay.
Move household.
Oh, don't...
Be careful.
Don't do anything stupid.
Wait.
Everybody just wait.
Get in.
Make the call.
Hurry up.
Bingo.
Let's move.
The fruits household is moving.
Keep furniture.
Wait.
No, no, no, no.
Sell furniture.
I'm not going to bring all the furniture with me.
Furnished.
Let's go.
So, welcome to the stream, everybody.
Here is why I wanted to do this in the first place.
This is first person.
On the Sims 4.
I'm going to go ahead and save it real quick.
Save as...
Call this the fruit household.
Fruits.
Okay.
My current game.
That's fine.
Save.
All right.
Here we are.
Let's just test a few things to make sure they work.
This place is fucking huge and it's beautiful.
Get to know.
More choices.
There's...
Sim Torments.
This is a new one.
I don't want to do this right off the bat.
But sometimes you just have to try.
No, no, no, no.
Plead, plead, plead.
All right.
This is perfect already.
We can't jump right into...
I was supposed to wait.
No, no, no.
Load game.
I'm going to load the game.
And we can't go that hard yet.
Okay.
Everything's going to be just fine.
Load game.
That's it.
See you later.
That's pretty much what the stream is.
See you tomorrow.
So we have the fruits here.
I need to make a couple of people before we do anything.
In the same complex, maybe?
Can I get rid of Lobo?
We need them to have neighbors.
There are already people that are here.
Let me see some of the neighbors, though.
Who lives here?
Nobody.
The Feng family.
So we will come across random people who have been randomly generated.
The karaoke legends.
I'm not going to kill Lobo.
No, not yet.
We need to get started first.
I'm not killing Lobo.
But I will make...
We have to make one more family.
Somebody has to be the drug dealer.
We need to kill Lobo for the fireplace.
Not yet.
Let's go back here.
And not destinations.
Where's the new family?
Create a new household.
Okay.
I need to make the gnome.
Gnome.
It doesn't matter.
Gnome is just anything.
Uh, what is this?
Male pregnancy.
Okay.
Let's go ahead and do formal wear.
It's going to be the costume as well.
That car, man.
I'm going to abuse that.
No, I'm not a gnoblin.
I don't know why I'm doing this.
This is...
I'm just embracing the ultimate...
I'm embracing the ultimate annoying meme right now.
Oh, formal.
I can't change formal wear.
Is it just a randomized button?
There is.
Wow.
That was a gnome right there.
That's fine.
You can look just like this.
Just remove formal wear.
Uh, okay.
Cool.
Full body.
Let's get that gnome outfit on.
All right.
Watch out.
Sportswear.
Doesn't matter where we are.
You're always going to be in that.
Sleepwear.
Yep.
Doesn't matter.
I guess I could just type in gnome, couldn't I?
No.
Where the fuck is it?
Where is it?
Am I going to not use it here?
You can't go to sleep in the giant costume?
Do I actually keep this in it?
No, I do not.
I do.
What a fucking idiot.
Can you actually go swimming in this?
Oh, there's going to be so much to do.
There's so much to do.
Is this person going to die inside of this costume?
They really might.
All right.
Looking good.
Pretty close too, actually.
For voice.
That looks good.
Okay.
Uh, deviancy.
Mischief.
Uh, I need to put on...
I think I need to put on, like, the drug.
Where is...
I actually think there's a drug dealer trait that I have to put on.
Incredibly popular, by the way.
Joke Star or...
I mean, I have to do Joke Star.
Let's see here.
Where is...
These sims refrain from using alcohol.
No, no, no.
Where is it?
They actually have to have this trait.
Neat slob.
Lazy.
Where is it?
Am I missing it here?
Evil.
Committal.
Mean.
Insider.
Kleptomania.
Am I...
What is wrong with me?
I'm looking for, like, drug dealer.
Oh.
It's got...
I can't...
That's because it's, like...
That looks weird.
It's, like, rolled up.
That looks like a cork.
I was expecting to look for, like, drugs.
I'm not a wine cork.
All right.
Here we go.
Materialistic.
And, uh, evil.
Sounds good.
Let's put you somewhere.
Anything else I need to do?
I don't think so.
Animals?
No, we did the drug dealer animal house already.
An evil meal chum.
Who else would live in this house?
What are some of the fucking stupid memes that I could put in here?
In, like, the drug meme house?
Let me see.
Garfield?
Put the vroomer...
No, the vroomer's gonna have his own house.
No.
This...
The drug dealer's gonna have their own house.
Just one little apartment.
We'll have the meme house in a minute here.
That's enough for, um, not a gonoblin.
Is there one where he jumps in front of the camera?
That looks good.
Not directly next door.
Some little, just...
Let's put you in, like, a little dump.
Who lives around here?
Nobody.
I should live with Garfield.
This one's fine.
No, no, no.
One bedroom.
There's often a party going on.
That's fine.
All right, he's in the world.
Who the hell is this?
Who is this person?
Did someone else live...
I thought this place was empty.
Oh, I've been going right for the video games.
Wee bowling.
Not gonna run her over.
We can't do that yet.
Everyone has to just relax.
Okay, settings.
Assign NPCs.
A shaman?
Wait.
Hold on.
I think he needs to have, like, a certain...
He's the drug dealer right now.
Let's see.
Let's open up the phone.
Dealing.
Doctor's appointment.
Invite the shaman over.
I remember the shaman.
All right.
Doctor's appointment is 100 bucks.
What does that do?
Am I going to the doctor to get drugs?
Feeling a bit under the weather?
God, not a.
Come by and we'll get you a checkup.
How do I, like, zoom in on him?
Can I show him?
Does he see him in the game world?
There's nothing wrong with you.
Don't hesitate to call us
if you actually feel depressed though.
I think I just got drugs.
Uh, okay.
Hold on.
Is he just going to do drugs?
What was inventory?
Where is their inventory?
It's, like, down here somewhere, right?
It's career inventory.
You don't got anything, man.
I'm supposed to run him over.
He's currently making gnome videos.
He just joined chat.
He's just putting it in the chat right now.
Okay, let me save it again here.
Oh, let me try this one.
Oh.
Call over partners in crime.
Take a selfie with a gun.
I'll use this one in my next video.
I can't even see.
He's too small.
Where's the gun?
No, it's because I was in a weird spot.
He's still holding the gun.
And we still have some population to take care of.
You can upgrade that.
Try to calm down in...
No, he's not going to kill anybody.
Automatic killing is off at the moment.
All right, that's fine.
He's doing just fine.
Let's head back.
Make our last household.
Wait a minute.
Welcome to the neighborhood.
Holy fuck.
The ghost!
Say hello!
It's Alita Battle Angel.
What does that guy have on the plate?
Is it like a meat cake?
Oh, what's this?
Fucking dick.
Funny...
I knocked...
I delay knocked him out.
He was at like 6,000 ping.
All right.
Let's tell an unbelievable story.
That was such a delayed knockout.
Fell asleep in five seconds.
No, I can't do it.
I can't do it.
Please.
We can't go this far.
It's too late to go.
I can't.
I have to do.
We have to go fake.
I can't let this get out of control
this quickly into the stream.
Somebody just...
And the chat just broke.
Can someone please explain what the fuck just happened?
No one's safe.
Even inside.
You're not even safe.
What else is there?
I just need to see what they do.
What?
What is snatch self?
Okay, okay.
It's gonna be a long night.
I needed to...
I just need...
This is the test period.
I just need to test.
All I'm doing is testing.
I haven't seen these yet.
What?
P self?
He's gone.
I don't know what this means.
What?
I don't understand what just happened.
Why does this person have a face?
Why does death have a face?
Death should not have a face?
This is...
No, I can't believe it.
This is ridiculous.
You took my...
Gang...
There's so much here.
All right.
It's time to go back.
That's P.
All right.
So we've seen what some of these do.
Who's crying?
I'm crying.
Okay.
It's time to go.
We gotta make our final person.
Send to hell.
Crack neck?
Body slam?
Who does the body slamming?
That kills you?
He's dead.
The game saved...
Currently in a state where saving isn't possible.
Don't save.
I'm gonna load game.
This is the one right here.
I just want to see what they did.
There is the gnome.
Final family.
This is the last bit before we just...
We're gonna play.
We will get to playing.
I promise you this.
This is the final household.
There's gonna be about three or four people in this household.
This is the fucking meme family.
Uh...
Vroomer.
I'm just gonna do randomize until I find the right one.
The memes?
The memers?
How about Vroomer?
Who gives a shit?
Vroomer McBoomer?
Vroomer the Reinhardt family.
Okay.
Fine.
Sure.
All right.
Final household.
This is an absolute dickhead.
Make enemies and be a famous criminal.
Yeah.
You're a pain in the ass.
Incredibly active.
Uh...
Is there a car lover?
Erratic?
Mm-hmm.
Loves the outdoors.
Can't get enough.
Mean.
No.
Mean and evil.
By the way, if you're curious,
this is the person that just drives by three or four times a day,
and they just step on the gas as hard as they can.
If you don't know who this is.
Let's randomize.
Oh, that's close.
I'm gonna randomize until I see the person that I think is driving by.
Close.
No.
I think I found them.
Okay.
Oops.
Oh, shit.
No, come back up.
Back up. Back up.
You're just making a Chad.
This is not a Chad.
Um...
I didn't do that, but fine.
Somehow better.
Why do they always have such fucked up chins?
There we go.
I can...
That's who's...
That's who you are.
I know it.
Put an ad out for this guy.
To be arrested for speeding.
This is the police sketch of what they look like.
Cat ears.
It just keeps getting better.
That was not bad.
This is...
No, I'm kind of making just Nico from GTA IV.
I want to go back to the clown here.
Whoever this is.
This person is a fucking clown.
Oh, no.
No, no.
That's not the person that's driving around.
This is clown.
Okay.
Oh, that's like Amish.
That's my haircut.
This is not even close to my haircut.
All right, what about for clothes?
Give him like a Twitch hoodie?
Clown suit?
No, no, no, no.
Like, this is cool.
Change something here one more time.
That's better.
Oh, God. 50 bucks.
Mostly lost.
Just gave 50 dollars.
Thank you.
I'm not going to let you continue without making this guy's personality bro.
Is there a bro?
Outgoing?
Yeah, but they're mean and evil.
And they're incredibly erratic.
They just drive by the house every day.
No, you're right.
That's good enough.
Formal?
You dress like a dickhead.
That's your formal wear?
No jacket?
You show up to work with no suit jacket on?
All right.
Next, we've got...
Who else can I put here?
Oh, let's see here.
Nice.
That's fine.
I'll show you what I have for hair.
It's more like that.
No, I don't look like Cyclops.
Last time I made myself a joke.
This time I'm going to make what I actually look like.
Get in there.
I don't mean hair is not correct.
Yes, it is.
I know what I look like.
And this is what I see in the mirror.
Put on the webcam to compare.
Hold on.
I will.
I just got to put clothes on.
I got to put like something on.
Be right back.
Okay, here.
Incoming joke.
There's no joke.
I just don't have big clothes on.
Let's see.
Let's see how accurate this is.
You're going to turn this a little...
This is what I see.
Okay?
I think that's good.
Right?
There it is.
I think that looks pretty close.
I need a bigger chin.
Are you sure?
No fucking way I don't look like that.
Bullshit.
I can't look.
That's better.
Are these out far enough?
See?
I think that's fine.
The lips are too big.
Hold on.
Let me get in there.
Okay.
That looks fine.
I'm going to grab the corners though.
How far?
That's...
This is kind of up.
Yeah.
Higher.
This ratio is wrong.
These eyebrows are going to come down.
Well, the eyes have to go up.
Yeah.
This has to come down.
There we go.
Am I getting there?
The nose is too big.
Eyebrows have to change.
No.
There we go.
Bring them down.
Bring these out.
I mean, it looks pretty similar.
Skin tone.
Yeah.
Hold on.
You're right.
I got to get the skin tone right.
There they go.
I think that's it.
Let's do it.
Let's get the whole thing, right?
The hair is not right?
No.
I think it's perfect.
Like that.
This is actually what I see in the mirror.
Eyebrows.
Look at my eyebrow.
But look at...
Look at...
See?
He's a bigger.
All right.
Now they're just doing it on purpose.
That looks good.
Forehead's bigger.
Add lipstick.
Why would I add lipstick?
All right.
What about...
What about if a clothes on right now?
None.
I actually don't have any.
No, I wouldn't wear this.
I wouldn't wear that.
My chin's bigger than this.
It is definitely not bigger than...
You want to make me look like a cartoon character?
Pretty stylish.
No.
I don't want...
Not the black shirt.
Let's go with...
I don't want to do like fucking Civil War Soldier.
Do they have any Star Wars shirts?
Wait.
They probably do.
They have a Darth Vader mask.
You tell me they don't have a Star Wars t-shirt?
Where the hell is it?
Come on.
Star Wars.
Damn it.
I don't want the headphones on.
Let's go full body for a second.
I have a big fan of Star Wars but that's not...
I'm not...
I wouldn't wear this.
Just be in the Vader costume.
This would be my formal outfit.
Okay?
Every day though.
Let's go with like a tank top.
Okay.
T-shirts.
Star Wars.
Tank top.
Pretty close.
Sweatshirts.
No.
That's fine.
Bottoms.
Let's go with...
I mean...
Just a pair of jeans.
Yeah, that's fine.
That's pretty close to what I would wear.
Especially in Las Vegas.
Put those things away.
What do you mean put the...
What the things?
All right.
I'm happy with this.
My personality.
I'm an animal.
No.
I would say let's do like creativity.
I mean like genius.
Best-selling author.
Knowledge.
Really smart.
Computer whiz.
Wicked.
Popular.
Joke star.
Leader of the pack.
I'm a leader.
Little hot-headed.
Very, very creative, aren't I?
And I also am very clumsy.
I'm good.
No.
Fine.
So who lives here?
Oh yeah, I forgot.
I've made this person.
That is not at all what the person probably looks like.
Can I go back and delete...
How do I delete somebody else's character?
You know what I mean?
Seriously.
All right.
Let's add dog.
What kind of breed?
Uh, no, we're not making an auto.
Let's make a little, a little fucked up on the face.
That's fine.
Extra large nose.
This is the Budweiser dog.
Yeah, that looks good.
It's a giant rat.
Mm-hmm.
Perfect.
What about the tail here?
You can change the tail.
No, rat tails are thin.
Little legs if I can make them smaller.
Let's go in detail mode here.
Can I make these any bigger?
No, it just looks like a bird.
A duck.
Eyes all the way back.
It's a rat.
It does look sad.
Yeah, I gotta make it...
I gotta make the dog not sad.
The rat, whatever.
It just always looks sad.
Why?
Why do you look sad?
Let me go make the body bigger.
That's so creepy looking.
Okay.
I think that's good.
I think it's a mouth that's doing it.
How big are rat's ears?
Are they huge?
They're big, right?
No, they're tiny.
How big are they?
They're like that.
They're massive.
Let me say rat.
Yeah, they're a little tiny.
They look like this.
Okay, here we go.
Now we need to have a coat here.
I think I can just do fur, right?
Here we go.
That's kind of rat-like.
That's pretty close.
That's better.
That's better, yeah.
Paint the tail pink.
Paint the tail and paws pink.
That's a good idea.
All right, let's paint.
And the ears.
Damn it.
That not so pink.
What do you mean not so pink?
Not Barbie pink?
It's too dark.
What?
Pale pink.
Well, who cares?
What?
Salmon?
That's like salmon.
That's fresh salmon.
Oh, it's never going to get fixed.
I have to do the whole thing again here.
Okay, that's better.
Oh, who cares?
So let's go pink.
Is that better?
That's salmon.
That's a salmon color.
He's done it.
He's finally done it.
Now let's get the tail.
What color are rat's feet?
Also pink too, right?
Yeah, it's like the same color.
All right, roll over.
I want to get the underside of your tail here.
All right, you're good.
Now let's get your paws disturbing.
That's how far it goes up, right?
It goes up a little further.
I painted on it.
It's like knees.
I didn't mean to, but that's okay.
I'm gonna give you the eraser.
I'll get it.
I'll clean it up.
Gloves there.
Perfect.
All right, stand up.
Let's get a good look at you.
That's just a quick little reference
to people that saw the last one.
Okay, let's draw whiskers.
Kind of already done for us here.
Now I can do them myself.
Thank you very much.
Which way do they go?
Out?
How do they look?
Wrapped face.
No, they're only...
The nose is pink too.
Here, stand up straight.
Let me see that nose.
I can't do the nose.
Nose is unpaintable.
Guys, sorry.
Maybe I could do it on the nose option.
All right, let's give them whiskers first.
They gotta be smaller than that.
And they gotta be clear, gray.
All right, let's go to the nose.
Tails, body, fur, pet clothing.
And I do nose.
Body, breeds, tails.
How do I get to it?
Just click on his nose.
The eyes though, the eyes have to be...
Yeah, there we go.
Holy shit, that's pretty close.
Get rid of the whiskers.
The whiskers just fuck it all up.
Oh no, I kind of missed them now.
Hold on, let me try again.
Let's go with like three.
What an even worse proximity.
That's like a cat though.
Get a little darker.
Got it!
All right.
Hello, my name is Giant Rat.
There you are.
Wait, there's a little bullshit mark right here.
These paws need to be cleaned up a little bit.
I'm not gonna just have to suck.
Bigger brush.
I'm not just gonna have to suck, guys.
This is Giant Rat.
Beautiful, beautiful, beautiful.
All right, there it is.
Look at that avatar.
It's perfect.
So this household is Vroomer...
Jeremy Reinhardt.
Vroomer Reinhardt.
Giant Rat.
And let's go with another...
I'm just gonna...
I'm gonna see what I can do here.
I'm gonna make...
We'll find out.
Here we go.
Clear everything.
Clear hair.
All hair.
All right, all right.
Let's start.
Start with the nose first.
Let me out there.
What do I grab?
I want to grab this.
Okay, I have to make an elephant.
Come on now.
Let me just grab in there.
You know you want to let me do this.
Come on.
Nice.
Elephant.
Bring it in.
Looking good so far.
I like the kind of Dumbo eyes.
Fuck.
Okay.
How much further down can that go?
I think that's as far as it can go.
Unless I can...
No, that's perfect right there.
Wait a minute.
No, fuck it.
I'm making a goddamn bird.
This is a bird.
This is big.
It's like a pelican.
I need to make this mouth much smaller.
This is just...
I'm making the seagull.
Here.
Saved forever.
Well, never mind.
It's a faucet.
Delete this.
No, it's staying.
This is terrifying.
Make the eyes red.
This needs to come up.
It's better.
I need to get that mouth much smaller.
Maybe actually...
Hold on.
Bring this back up a little.
Wait.
That's good.
Okay.
That's a pretty good elephant.
Just got to do the ears.
Oh, easy.
No, I got to go bigger than that.
They can't go bigger than that.
I don't know why there's an elephant living in this house.
Please kill this one right away.
Oh, I must just throw up.
This stream hadn't even gotten started yet, guys.
Do you guys understand?
We haven't even begun.
I wonder, is the...
I mean, elephants' heads are fucking huge.
They are huge.
But that's just...
It doesn't look right.
It looks strange.
There's five and a half thousand people here for the pretty stream.
I'm welcome.
Hope you're having a good time.
We haven't even started the stream yet.
This looks like Stuart Little, somebody said.
That's better.
It can't be that ridiculously huge.
I need to get...
See, when I go into detail mode, can I spin them?
All right, here we go.
Oh, come on.
Don't do this to me.
Better?
I think they're out more now.
What elephants wear for clothes?
Fixes eyes.
I don't know if I want to.
I feel like I want it like this.
For some reason.
No, they're better out.
Oh, shit.
I fucked it all up.
Here we go.
I like it like that.
I like it the way it is.
Let's go with...
Well, elephant doesn't wear clothes.
Can I make them go down on all fours?
There's got to be a jokey feet, right?
Come on.
You got to have something strange,
like a goofball outfit down here.
It's nothing at all.
I mean, you got clown shoes,
but you don't have...
You got Pac-Man feet.
Wait, aren't...
Don't elephants have pink feet?
They do, don't they?
Yeah, they do.
Elephants.
Elephant's feet.
No, they don't.
They have like big dinosaur toes.
They have big dinosaur toenails.
Definitely going to make the ass bigger.
All right.
No, they don't have that.
All right, that's fine.
Max's favorite of the household.
What?
Fruit don't wear clothes either.
Uh-huh.
But yeah, I guess that's better.
Okay, I'm all right with that.
And you want to...
Because they have like three toes.
So look, it's like one, two...
That's like a heel.
You know what I mean?
That's just pretend that's what it is.
Fine, I'll give you a t-shirt.
Yuck.
No, that just looks like a Saturday morning
kid's cartoon character.
Perfect.
All right, he's an animal.
So friend to the animals.
What's the...
Elephants are like sad, skittish, right?
They eat a lot.
Are they vegetarians?
Yeah, they never forget.
Dance machine, insider, jealous, loner, hates children, outgoing, a bro.
Make the elephant a painter.
A bookworm.
Okay, a little bookworm.
Needs a lot of food.
Uh, no, not a gloomy.
We'll do...
Vegetarian, bookworm, and like loves children, right?
Or...
What should the last one be?
No, no, not hates children.
Where...
No, just hates children.
Just make them...
Make it smart, okay.
Loves to hate children.
All right, is this house ready to go?
I think we're ready to go.
We've got all our dickheads.
I need one more animal.
One more animal.
Final animal.
Cat.
All right, bolognese.
What's ba...
Uh, how do I pick breed?
No, breed.
Head shape.
Where is it?
All right, I just missed it.
Get deleted.
All right, hold on.
Let's have...
Breed, breed, breed, breed, breed.
I want a cat with a very, very small head.
Like a big ass neck.
Mm-mm.
Oh, boy.
All right, I'm gonna...
Should I make one of the human skin cats?
Let's get in there.
No, I don't want you to be like eyes crossed.
I'm turning this cat into a dog.
It's just a dog.
Not...
Hold on, not yet.
I like that, though.
Yeah, big, thick neck.
Now, you guys...
I don't think you guys got it right.
This is the statue gargoyle things
from the first Ghostbusters movie.
How big is this thing?
Tail...
Tail big.
All right, looking good.
That's good.
A little bit bigger.
Make the neck a little longer.
Oh, I didn't do...
Uh...
Fluffy.
No.
Select traits.
Custodious.
Territorial.
Wow.
Okay.
And a prowler.
This is...
This thing's scaring me.
I don't like this.
You're wearing, like, a Dragon Ball Z t-shirt?
What the fuck is this?
No.
Get that off.
Don't let...
I hate it.
Let's go over here.
Oh, let's see.
You like fire?
Like flames?
Would flames work on the cat?
Like a car?
Like a fast car?
It's not the right color.
I need a good, like, fire.
Here we go.
This is like feathers.
No, I don't like it.
This might be better.
That's a little better.
No.
Somebody put paint on a cat.
Oh, wait.
Fire.
Come on.
Ooh.
Fire?
Quite.
No.
It's a prehistoric cat.
It's like stone.
You guys have seen the Fantastic Four?
You know that character, The Thing?
It's like a rock.
The cat is...
It's not tire marks.
I'm gonna make that clear.
Dammit.
Now I have to get rid of these.
That's so fucking awful.
I'm not gonna have...
It is Rumors Cat.
Ugh.
No, that's too dark.
This is too dark.
I don't know if I can do this.
Ugh.
No.
Poor cat.
No, I can't.
That's too terrible.
I...
Ugh.
No, that's awful.
This is just the shit in the ass all over again from last time.
All right.
What if the cat didn't get run over?
But it's just...
It's Rumors Cat.
So he has a certain tattoo.
That's worse.
It's not worse.
He's trying to justify it.
No, I'm trying to correct my wrong ways.
It looks too sad.
I can't.
It's just a rash.
Vertical tire marks.
He ran over the whole cat's whole body.
This is terrible.
That's worse.
It's worse.
I hate this.
I hate this, but it's a tattoo.
Just delete it all.
We're done.
Sim5 doesn't even have a name.
Ugh.
I don't even know what to call it.
This cat.
About nine...
Uh.
No, I'm not gonna have it roadkill.
We...
I've removed the tire marks.
Not speed bump.
You guys are fucking awful.
You guys are terrible.
Eight lives.
Holy shit, you guys are awful.
Here's the new...
This is the last family.
Move them in.
Carfield.
There they are.
This part doesn't even have a name.
Fuck this guy.
Who cares?
What's this guy's name?
An elephant.
How's that for a name?
You ready?
Oh, the rat needs traits.
A junta.
And friendly.
And a little bit stubborn.
A little...
Pretty vocal.
Trouble maker.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Trouble...
Okay.
We need trouble maker.
We need...
Not friendly.
A hunter.
Praying at night.
Stalking.
Like hunting at night.
So we got...
Making trouble.
Hunting.
And then...
Uh, stubborn.
We want no vocal because they sing.
You got traits, right?
Yes.
Everybody all set?
Are we ready to start playing the game?
I don't remember what we made.
All right.
I think we're good to go.
Here we go.
Welcome to the stream, guys.
It only took us about three and a half hours to set it up.
Change the animal voices, you got me?
How do I do that?
How do I change his voice?
Top left.
Dumbo.
Tough.
Too low.
Deep.
Let's see if we can get a good one here.
How's it going?
Hey.
Hey, it's me, the giant rat.
It's pretty good.
I'm ready.
Oh, the cat needs it too.
This is a...
This is a bird?
It's gonna stay like that.
My voice is fine.
All right.
Let's play the Sims.
Four.
Time to go.
We're gonna be saving frequently.
The tutorial just ended.
We need a place for them to move.
I like this one.
That's perfect.
I like it.
You look just scary in every single photo.
New cool 3D world.
So in here, we have the fruits, then Mr. Lobo.
You've also got the Reinhardt family, and then the gnome.
So where...
I need three bedrooms?
28 grand.
Could go here.
How many bedrooms are in here?
Two.
This lives right next to the gnome.
Two beds.
I can throw another bed in there.
Who cares?
This one's a little bigger.
You do not want to be next to the gnome.
No, I don't.
But I think it'll be okay.
Take a pee break?
Yeah, all right.
You know, it's been three hours.
I'm gonna grab a drink.
We're going probably all night just to let you guys know.
So go take a piss.
I'm gonna grab a drink, and I'll see you guys for a probably
straight night that's gonna be for at least another four or five hours.
Be right back.
All right, let's get this show on the road.
Thank you for hanging out in the creation of the three or four families here.
All the mods are go.
Let's do it.
So who do we want to play with first?
I need to save the game, first of all.
It begins.
Whoever's gonna die the fastest.
I think we have to start with the Reinhardts.
It makes the most sense.
Reality can be whatever I want.
1,800 second slow vote.
Holy shit.
This is where we're going.
I'm gonna put another bed in here.
It's a little small, but it needs TLC.
Somebody said don't do that.
Lively neighbors that make sense because the drug-dealing gnome is over here.
Let's see.
What's in here?
No, this place is too expensive.
I can't afford the pool.
What's in here?
All right.
I didn't kill these people?
No, I didn't save it.
Okay, this is a party place.
We'll go downstairs.
This is a quake zone.
What does that mean?
Quake zone.
Oh, no.
Okay, right, right, right.
I'm gonna do this free real estate cheat thing.
I have to be in a game for that to happen though, right?
Not, I don't for this, do I?
Didn't I try this last time?
All right, here we go.
All right, let's do it.
Let's move downstairs underneath that, those people, those partiers.
Where was that over here?
All right, this two-bedroom, two-bath.
We live underneath the karaoke legends.
Move on in.
Fully furnished.
I'll take it.
Okay, we're gonna take it slow.
I am going to have two bedrooms with three people.
Yeah, that's fine.
All right, here we go.
Game starts now.
That is such a tiny dog.
What's wrong?
Acquired the comedy skill.
Didn't even have to do anything.
We all go right for the TV.
Get off the table.
We all went immediately to the TV.
And so let's do my perspective.
I watch and think America's got talent.
Quick, run him over.
I'm not gonna do...
No.
Why does it say first to die?
Oh, that's the person's name.
He's still at it.
Let's interact.
Play with the laser pointer with the cat.
No, I'm not killing anybody yet.
Go get it.
That rat just doesn't shut up, huh?
No.
No car joke.
I'm not doing that yet.
We can't just go to a thousand.
Let's see.
What's going to do?
What's going to do with the cat?
Pick up.
You can pick up the cat.
I could pick him up?
How do I get out?
I guess I can just do this.
All right, let's see.
You can actually pick the cats up.
I didn't even know that.
Guys.
I can stalk the cat.
Why would I do that?
I'm not going to do that.
Here's the thing, though.
I can use...
I can move around with the animals.
Remember this?
I'm going to be nice to the cat.
Look, I'm holding the cat and hit no.
Okay, now just get picked up.
More choices.
We got drugs.
Not doing these yet, but I can't control the animals.
Yeah, get a spot right on the sofa.
Oh, also, we can't go right into this yet,
but any object of the whole game can be worn as a hat.
Just throwing that out there in case anybody was wondering.
Let's see here.
What was in here?
All right, can we do something as a group?
What do I want to do for them?
What do I want to actually do with the characters?
I got to make like a decision here.
Pet obsessions.
Oh, we have...
Here we go, here we go.
Do they like cats?
Welcome to the neighborhood.
The cat is about to greet them.
Is that it?
No, no.
Who is this lady?
Whoa!
Oh, sorry, my little shit cat.
My cat's an asshole.
Hold on.
Come on in.
Let's have some fun.
Both of you.
They're relatively normal.
That's sort of.
What do you have in your hand?
Oh, I forgot that you like reading.
Can somebody get the door?
Somebody get the door.
You're just watching TV to get a stop.
She just looks like a fish.
Oh, you like red cars.
Do you?
Uh-oh.
It's funny.
You say that you like red cars.
All right, hold on.
More choices.
Drugs.
This is the drug dealer.
I got to make friends with this guy.
We're getting some fucking drugs in this house.
I'll take care of this.
What, am I frayed?
All right, go here.
Yeah, there's a gnome.
Jeremy just became friends with the giant rat.
Yes, we did.
All right, head out here.
I need to get like a good view of this.
All right, greet new neighbor.
Benio.
Just as the prophecy.
There you are.
Glad we got a chance to chat.
Yeah, you and I.
Impishly Pester.
Bye, weed.
Discuss current drug.
Hey, it's really nice to meet you.
It's really interesting.
By the way, what's the current drug market?
Brand new neighbor I haven't even said hello to.
Buy MDMA pills.
All right, we're going to buy MDMA.
Is this illegal?
Just in front of everybody.
Who the fuck are you?
Who is this person?
Where am I going?
Oh, you made scrambled eggs?
What am I doing?
Am I cooking the MDMA?
This just looks like VR chat.
I'm sure I haven't taken them already.
Did I take the drugs?
I'm going to go out the window?
No, no, not yet.
Not yet.
That's illegal.
Oh, I'm cycling through people.
Okay, I get it.
How do I put this down?
What are we following?
All right, hold on a second.
Let me get back up here.
I think it's because I'm eating.
Open.
Oh, shit.
Okay, I have a lot of them here.
I got high quality pink disco biscuit.
Kick every party up.
No pet is truly fearless, even eight.
Each pet has its own unique fears.
What do you mean?
What's going on?
What are you afraid of?
He's just mashing controls and scaring my cat.
Can you cut the shit?
All right, let's put these back on the table here.
Uh, let's just take one.
He's in mine.
I'm the only one that's gonna take.
What does this do?
Well, I mean, you didn't even take drugs when you're in here.
Rumor is busting some moves.
He has unlocked some new dance moves
that can now show off the arm charm.
Let me teach you about a dance.
What the fuck is that move?
Well, then I can work for money.
Who's going to pay me?
Who's going to pay me though?
That's what I'm curious about.
Forget about teaching dancing.
I want to know who's going to pay.
That's not very good.
The gnome just gave me 500 bucks.
What did you start with?
These like trading cards?
The life of a streamer.
Anybody have any donations?
Anybody?
Did I just dab?
Oh god, I dabbed.
Here, buy weed.
Buy a Ziploc bat.
Ask about drug quality.
No, no, no, that's...
I don't want to eat the whole bag of Doritos.
All right, stop this.
What do you think, chat?
I'm going to discuss the current drug market.
All right, stop twerking.
Nobody wants to eat the whole bag,
but everybody does.
That's what I'm saying.
If I dial this up to a thousand right now,
the whole stream is going to go just derail
and you know what happens.
Thanks for hanging out.
See you later.
Well, at least I got your phone number.
Is anybody else still in here?
Instagram?
Send?
What else is here?
Leash pet training.
Friendly pet care.
Give a bath.
I thought he was leaving.
More drugs than twerk.
I'm supposed to be taking my dog out for a walk.
Oh, talk about the warm temperature.
Joke about politics.
Where am I going?
Oh, it's time for a bath.
I know you're tired,
but it's time for you to get some clean bath time.
What?
Were you just trying...
Was he talking?
Where do you give the dog a bath?
Do a rat cam?
Okay.
Look at how fucked up I look.
Did I just put my hand up and grab him?
I just like high-fived him.
Oh, that's my hand.
Okay.
All right.
Thank you.
I appreciate it.
Oh, I'm shaking around.
The life of a dog.
What is he doing?
He's taking more drugs.
What do you...
Oh, I'm just gonna leave.
Bye.
No, don't just leave.
Go back.
Where are you going?
No, you don't just leave him.
I'm sick of this shit.
Oh, he used to go outside.
He used to go outside.
Take your dog out.
I thought that was another animal in the house.
No, it's just one of my roommates.
No, he's still here.
I need to feed the dog.
I need to feed the animals.
Where are...
Where's the cat?
Oh, they're fighting for food now.
All right.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Pet talk.
Wait, wait, wait.
Where are they going?
Why are they out here by themselves?
I don't even know where he is.
He just went out on his own.
Okay.
Where's the cat?
Who are...
Oh, it's tomato.
It's the...
No, not tomato.
It's the apple.
This is the cat's point of view.
Did I throw a knife around?
I didn't know how I got out here.
Trash.
Playing the trash.
What?
The cat take drugs?
The cat's tripping up.
No, that's not good.
No, it's because I scrolled out.
Oh, I'm like just out here now.
Wait, why did they get so dirty?
That's pee?
That's a shitload of pee.
No, he took a picture of himself.
What is tornadoes?
I've done that before.
I should really get going now.
See you later.
Well, okay.
How do I get the cat to come back?
Where's the cat?
Am I ordering food?
Wait a minute.
Yibsbadeesh.
Barovay Senzin Dumbayakalo.
I should be able to...
If this guy dies...
Can I just go in now?
That's how it is, bro.
Finally.
You've been waiting all day for that.
Who's gonna run...
Who's gonna run the popcorn stand?
Go home.
I will feed you.
The music still is just blasting.
All right.
Get up.
Claim.
What do you mean claim?
Where's my window?
Skills?
No, where's my attitude?
Okay, there we go.
Join a club.
Own a business.
Buy a vet clinic?
No.
All right.
My hunger, everything's fine.
My sleep is all right.
Let's speed it up a little.
Okay.
I need to get a pet bowl, first of all.
Finally.
That's so funny.
All right.
Pet bowl.
I'm gonna say it's probably...
It's like a pet option.
Kid's room.
Miscellaneous.
Kitchen.
I wonder what would it...
What would it be under?
I feel like a bowl.
Like a pet bowl.
It's like just pet.
Pet food bowl.
Hey, look at that.
All right.
Bow wow chow.
Let's get the automatic one.
How do I move it?
Let's hit the spin button.
Alt.
Control.
Shift.
Hold.
How many of these do I need?
Just two?
Pet mate.
Just two of them.
Somebody said R.
I can't...
R doesn't do anything.
Oh, there you go.
Okay.
So that's good.
Pet.
Pet toys.
Good to go.
Fill them up.
Fill.
They'd both be good.
I had to wake up for this,
but somebody had to do it.
Why is your sim more handsome than you?
It's unrealistic.
Ban that guy for five seconds, please.
All right.
What am I doing on this?
Is this a computer?
I thought this was like a toaster oven.
Write jokes.
Web order.
Purchase crackers.
Purchase medicine.
Purchase fireworks.
I can buy drugs on here?
Okay.
I'm buying drugs online.
Uninstall origin.
All right.
Here we go.
Vaporizer.
Fill these packs.
Smoking papers.
Weed bung.
That's all you got, huh?
I'll take one of each.
You can stream with the Get Famous DLC.
Are the dogs and cats still outside?
You little shit.
What are you doing?
Bladder.
Oh, how do you go to the bathroom?
Is it like a dog bathroom?
Oh, I got to walk them.
Get over here.
Request song.
No, no, no.
Go potty.
Walk the cat.
Get up.
Wake up.
Where's the cat?
You walk a cat?
No, you don't.
They have like a kitty litter.
Like cat box.
Cat condo.
Cat wand.
Like glitter?
Littermatic scoop free.
Here we go.
There it is.
$175.
Throw it over here.
Where can I put this?
There's a good place for this.
Let me go down a level.
There we go.
Okay.
All right.
That's good.
Cat can now go to the bathroom.
Take the dog out.
I was going to put it on the kitchen counter.
Yeah, you're right.
Take him outside.
Take the dog outside.
Now.
Take dog outside.
What's going on up here?
Wait, you can actually eat this?
Where am I?
And why have I not taken the dog out like I was supposed to?
Was I just eating out of the bowl?
Oh, you asshole.
Please.
Where's the dog?
What is that?
Did she knock over the bowl or something?
What is this?
Is this?
All right.
Clean that up.
I thought it was...
Mop it up.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Stop it.
I thought she knocked the bowl of macaroni and cheese off.
Stop.
Now, please.
If you would.
Go for a walk.
Okay.
Finally.
Am I still fucked up from drugs?
Walk time.
Let's go.
Finally.
My god.
For a second, I thought I could drink up them.
All right.
Take dog for a walk.
Here we go.
What?
How did we...
We got out here really quick.
All right.
Go pee.
We need a new cam.
Where'd it go?
Where am I?
We didn't even get to see it?
He just deleted himself.
Okay.
I was hoping I could get a POV from the dog.
All right.
We were here.
Okay.
It's time to check on...
Let's check on the other families here.
The fruit apartment here.
Who gives a shit about any of these people?
I think it's time to start activating fucked up things.
What are you guys up to?
Let's see.
There's Mr. Banana.
All right.
Go jogging.
Let's see.
Practice singing.
Mr. Apple.
Specifically made these...
This family to just have horrible things happen to them.
So here's the thing about call over part gangs.
Enable the Thoughties gang outfit.
Join the Thoughties.
Join the Hardwood gang.
Invite the Thoughties gang to town.
Invite the Hardwood gang to town.
This is probably going to be very bad.
Who the fuck are you?
Oh, it's the landlord.
It's so much worse in first person.
His apartment's up for rent.
What are you doing?
Oh, I forgot how fucking stupid this was.
I just slotted the landlord.
We're gonna put butter and cheese in here.
Stir it up.
The singing.
Clearly you are a terrible and inconsiderate neighbor.
You just made a big mistake.
I will remember this.
What do you mean you're gonna remember this?
He's still alive?
How is it raining inside?
Gangs.
Let's add death to the Thoughties gang.
Okay, death is now a part...
Oh my god, shut the fuck up.
I see people like burning on the TV.
Alright, enough.
Enough, enough, enough.
Join the Thoughtie gang.
Jesus Christ.
Oh god, wait, he's...
No, no, no, he's opening fire.
On who?
What?
Infinite ammo.
Did he kill everyone?
I've never...
That's a new addition.
I gotta restart it.
A police cruiser has just been dispatched to your location.
Who's alive?
Just like AOL.
What is death from above?
Death from above?
How did he die?
What?
Why are they coming in and shooting themselves?
Who's left?
Back to Reddit.
What do you mean, ow?
Let's reopen that.
Death coming in and twerking.
Because he was part of the Thoughties.
Alright, we gotta bring...
We gotta do a gang thing.
He typed in explode in the command, in the console command.
Alright, back in here, let's go.
Alright, new life here.
We should go dancing or something.
No, drink energy juice.
Go for it, yeah.
Also, important.
We may as well see what this does.
Let me go get it.
We have not even seen half of the mods that I have.
We have the genie lamp, which has a genie come out of a lamp and grant wishes.
We also have a scary horror mirror, so let's go get it.
Should be...
I think it's down here.
It's a lamp, let's try it.
Where is it?
Looking for the lamp.
It's like 10 grand or something, too.
It's ridiculous.
Where...
Here's the...
Okay, here is the haunted mirror.
Legend says that a bride was betrayed and murdered on her wedding day,
and this mirror was the last thing she saw herself before she died.
Join a club in the bottom right so you get tons of friends.
Yeah, right now I'm just going through what these things even do.
There's the haunted mirror.
Can you filter modded items?
Um, I'm not sure you can.
Maybe base work?
Spa day...
Nah, you can't.
Unless I can do it from a different content.
Let's see, purchase custom content.
There we go.
Here is the book of chaos.
Torture and chaos to those who are unworthy to live.
Put it down.
This is a speed package.
This is the weed bong.
Oh, who ordered all this?
Cocaine brick?
Vintage baseball bat?
Baby laxatives?
And there's the genie lamp.
All right, so let's see.
I have a...
Let's just get him out here.
Rug can stay there.
And let's go back to live play and let's have the leopard gnome inspect the lamp.
Let's see what happens.
Okay.
So what happened?
I've rubbed the lamp, but what's going on?
Oh, shit.
Okay.
All right, here's the genie.
The genie just comes and just watches TV.
Where are my wishes?
I just added an NPC to the game.
Everybody rub the lamp.
Oh, no, only the leper gnome can now.
Do I get another genie?
How many genies do you get?
Just one genie?
All right, well, what can you do?
Friendly introduction.
Let's start a conversation.
How are you?
Have her join the thotties.
Not everybody has to join the thotties, okay?
Are we just meeting for the first time?
Reveal brilliant invention.
All right, let's flash our crazy eyes.
She liked it.
How about ask to hang out?
I wish this was VR.
Okay, so I'm getting some real interesting,
give fake news, ask to hang out,
asking about the day.
That's fucking mean.
Are you trying to make a friend
and potentially a romantic interest?
Are you trying to be an asshole?
What the hell was that?
Where are you going?
What are you doing?
Eat cereal.
Wow, that's next level.
Oh, blah, blah, blah, blah.
I'm going to eat some cereal.
I'm going to eat some lucky charms.
All right, can you keep talking?
All right, let's go with romance.
Make a flirtatious joke.
Talk about priorities.
This guy sucks.
All right, we got playful.
And with the bars on his folder,
by full I mean no.
Look at the lamp again.
Inspect the lamp.
This is his genie.
Inspect lamp.
Grandpa's gaming.
We're having a good time.
It's a lot of new love.
The lamp is so dusty,
I should probably rub it out.
Oh, God.
The plum looks like a genie.
She's following me around.
I think I made a friend.
How long does the genie stick around for?
The genie is going to make the same
eggs, cheese, and flour dinner.
All right, more choices.
Pick up line.
Ask if single.
Ask on a date.
Make a wish.
Not yet.
We're going on a date.
The banana and the genie.
I'm going on a date right now.
Remember, the chaos book is missing.
It's okay.
Where are we going to go?
Fashion district.
Karaoke bar.
That sounds like fun.
Okay, here we go.
We're going on a date with the genie.
So socialize with your date.
Sit and talk with your date.
Socialize.
How about...
What are you doing?
Why would you leave the date immediately?
What's wrong with you?
You got an other worldly being.
Romance.
Flirt.
What?
ADHD.
Why are you naked?
Why are you naked in a karaoke bar?
What?
She's taking a sh...
Why are you taking a shower?
No, don't leave.
Don't leave.
No.
I'm gonna get fucking stood up.
She's checking out the other mystical being that's here, isn't she?
She's flirting with death.
All right, give me a break.
The lady was naked.
She came out and was taking a shower in the rain.
And somebody ran her over.
Why is everyone crying?
Everyone doesn't have to be crying.
No, I gotta reset.
I have to redo it.
Reset.
I got an unbelievable story for you.
So this girl, she was naked in the bar.
She came outside.
Nude.
Started washing under her armpits and shit.
And what do you know?
A car comes flying down the street.
Nails her.
I mean, like fucking nails her.
It was ridiculous.
I'm in.
She likes me again.
Recycled joke from last time.
If a line works, you know.
No, I'm not gonna open fire.
Okay, how about romance?
Are you single?
Why would I do that right now?
I don't want to have to save the game every five seconds.
Okay, let's see.
Romance.
Okay, exchange numbers.
Does Genie have a number?
All right, can we stop?
Can we go somewhere else, please?
What?
That doesn't...
Who's changing into nude?
Me?
Put it back on.
Put your clothes back on.
Before anybody notices.
Quick.
She's disgusted.
I think I'm losing her.
It's all right.
Never really calm down.
Oh, what a day.
No, it's not.
You don't like it?
She's sitting down.
Okay, I don't know how to put my clothes back on.
I really, I don't know.
Okay, okay.
This has gone too far.
Time to hit him with a car, I guess.
Can we go home?
Like, I need to get out of here so I can clean up.
Really?
Shut up.
Good.
Wait, is that it?
You got, you don't have more.
Age down?
Oh, shit.
Where am I?
Did I just clean myself from the toilet?
Where can I get clothes?
Can I change clothes in here?
Uh-oh.
I think I'm about to lose my date to the gnome.
Date unsuccessful.
Jesus Christ.
All right, no, no, no, no.
Back home, back home, back home, back home.
Where'd she go?
Where's the genie?
Go home.
You fucking blew it.
Get out of here.
Up next on American Idol, yeah.
All right, go home, go home, go home.
Leave.
Go home.
I'm just going home.
Fuck it.
Get there.
Center on that lot.
Get out of here.
Leave.
Just go home.
Where are you going?
Pauline Pair reached video game level three.
That's the funniest thing that's happened to all stream.
He let go of his hands, sneezed.
That's the funniest fucking thing I've seen all stream.
How do we get out of here?
Oh, fuck.
Now I'm doing this.
It's happy hour at the karaoke bar.
I have half drinks, a half fries.
I don't give a shit about the banana.
He's a moron.
What kind of super villain can sneeze without the urethra closing?
I have no idea.
So go to the bathroom.
All right, I didn't even get a chance here.
How's everybody doing?
Bladder and energy.
Go to the bathroom then.
What's the problem?
What?
Didn't I shoot him in the head?
Okay.
Do I not have a bathroom?
No, I do.
So Pauline Pair is the best gamer in the house, just in case anyone's curious.
For a second, I thought she was naked and I was going to say,
wait a minute, I shouldn't have that on the screen.
Like, I thought it wasn't censored and it was just open.
All right.
Come back home.
Tidy up.
Care for yourself.
Bring Benedict Banana here.
Get over here.
Still naked.
Go just take a shower.
No, that's okay.
What is in here?
The Humor and Hijinks Festival is in town.
Click on any of the dynamic signs around town to find out more.
Okay.
Travel to the Humor and Hijinks Festival.
Who wants to go?
I don't know.
Who is it?
I don't even know who these people are.
No, you guys have a stay.
The banana is the piece of just crap.
This is the genie?
Is it?
No, it's not.
How would I get in contact with the genie?
Actually, is the genie?
Oh, I fucking stink.
God damn it.
The pranksters and jokesters challenge has begun.
Drink from either the dark or light tea to join a side.
Okay, I mean, can I have to drink from the dark tea, right?
Oh, Jesus.
All right.
Give me the...
Order food.
Funny.
How do I order a tea?
Of course, the gnome is here.
Hijinks.
Where am I?
I wasn't even ready for this.
View.
No, get over here.
Stop viewing things.
Go to the bar.
He's very sad.
Oh, come on.
Well, join the pranksters.
Join the pranksters together.
I was trying to get him to go to the bar, but he's too sad to move.
Okay, so the genie is going to join the pranksters.
I told you, I won't move.
I'm all the way back into the art gallery.
Can I take a shower in here?
No.
Hurry up.
Get over there.
The girl you are hanging out with here is currently doing things and having fun.
Go.
Take a sip.
All right, better just join the pranksters.
Perform pranks?
All right, so we got to prank people.
Festival is starting, I think.
I think we now just have to do some pranks.
Something...
Nothing too crazy.
A prank.
Order a drink for...
You got to prank the people that are glowing.
All right, let's prank this guy.
All right, let's prank you.
Okay, more choices.
Uh, mean.
No.
Funny.
Funny introduction.
This is a prank?
Oh no, the people that are glowing.
Okay, other way, way, way, way.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
All right, let's get a prank here.
All right, hack info.
That look.
The jokesters are in the lead.
Cut this shit out.
Um, what else am I supposed to do?
Chat with Penny.
I mean, is it mean?
Is it just like funny?
Steal money.
Fuckin' snitch.
No, I can't kill anybody.
We have to...
There's a cooldown period for when we can kill.
All right, I'm gonna introduce myself.
Probably should have slept before this, but I kind of just knee-jerked.
Where am I?
What am I doing in here?
I'm going all the way up the stairs?
No.
Okay.
This is what you wanted to do?
Why?
He's like playing with dirt.
You walked all the way up here to do this.
I'm very disappointed right now.
What does that do?
I snatched my own weave.
All right, go home.
I'm done with you.
Go home.
Let's focus on somebody else.
He's like putting his hands out and running like...
I'm an asshole.
All right, here we go.
I think it's time to assume control.
Where is the question?
Mac and cheese.
Excellent.
Okay, fun and social.
He needs to have some social shit.
Where's the lamp?
Rub the lamp.
This is the guy that technically the genie is...
It's his, right?
Okay, I want some wishes.
Call over.
No, not you.
You.
More choices.
How do I get...
Genie.
There we go.
Wish for the genie's freedom.
Wish for wealth.
Wish for youth.
Wish for world peace.
Wish for the genie's freedom.
Not yet.
Wish for world peace.
Let's see what happens.
Did it work?
What does that do?
Peter, your wish has been granted.
Well, that's funny.
Because it's impossible for there to be world peace.
Because I still have the decisions to make here.
What does that do?
Wish for romance.
Okay.
With who?
Is the banana still sad?
The banana still is at the gallery playing with mud.
Everyone's really happy now.
Oh, this is gonna make the banana real sad.
How many wishes do you get?
Peter, your wish has been granted.
Okay, so who do I flirt with?
Am I...
It's just us?
Where are we going?
Nobody can stop me.
Cupid's arrow.
She's the ultimate gamer.
Look at this.
Evangelize vegetarian benefits.
Oh, you blew it.
You blew it.
You blew it!
Let's have a conversation here.
Let's see.
Cupid's arrow, huh?
My ass.
Let's go to romance again.
Let's...
Casual discussion.
Okay, hold on.
Let's go on a date.
All right, I'll take you on a date to the gallery.
Has it got the...
Did I just say no?
I didn't get a chance to do it.
Taking her on a date to the gallery.
At the Casbah gallery.
Shit!
How about just...
I'll just say a compliment.
I don't know.
What book is that?
What book are you reading?
Reading real her in.
Perfect reading material right now, apparently.
Okay.
Look at this fucking gamer.
This is unbelievable.
He read the book and now he's gonna see if it works.
The banana is still...
I don't even know what the banana is.
Playing with dirt.
Shower in the rain.
Why is this...
I don't understand the shower in the rain shit.
He's picking up the book to go learn.
That's right.
You go fucking figure it out first before you make any dumb moves.
Ah, fuck.
I really gotta learn what the fuck I'm doing when I talk to women.
I'm not really making a fool of myself.
Uh, let's get some...
What happened to the book of chaos?
Oh, banana's back.
No, not even hello.
Nothing.
Just good night.
I'm going to bed.
I feel bad.
I actually feel kind of bad.
I really do.
All right.
Who has the highest...
I want to see if somebody can...
I want that...
I want the genie as a love interest.
Who has the...
Okay, awkward.
Should I wake up the banana?
Free the genie first?
Where's the genie gonna live, guys?
I mean, that's great.
Like, oh, like, yeah.
Genie, here you are.
You don't have to, like, be in the lamp.
We got two beds here.
Let's get to know each other.
Ask about your career.
All right.
The reading paid off.
What are you doing?
No, this is the problem.
You guys, you can't just go play on the computer.
She's gone.
She left.
Time to go play Sims forever.
What?
What do you mean forever?
Okay.
Well, I think it's time to check on the other household.
See how they're doing.
Let's head out to the map.
Let's get a save.
Let's check on the other household.
No, we gotta go back, right?
Cancel the travel.
Oh, how do I go back to manage worlds, right?
Just go to manage worlds.
All right.
This is the fruits.
We don't need to see them.
Let's go to...
That's the gnome.
I don't want to play with the gnome.
All right.
Let's do some stuff with these three.
Let's go to like a club or something or a bar.
Some like a video game hangout or something.
Select the Sim to play.
Me.
I just saved.
Yeah, I'm good.
I saved.
I'm already at the bar.
All right.
I'm ready.
I'm here with the dog.
Why is the dog here?
How would I bring the dog?
There's nobody here.
What am I doing outside?
Well, that's...
There's two people at that bar.
All right.
Let's go.
Let's take a walk.
Go do your business.
He's pissing on me.
No one has died in a bit.
Just saying.
That's because I haven't turned on auto kill.
Well, I can't pick it up.
How am I doing on stats?
Where is it here?
Let's see.
I'm actually pretty good.
All right.
Get unpleasant surround.
Let's go home.
Let's go back.
Back in the house.
You don't need to be here.
Back in the move-in household.
Visit apartment.
Who's visiting?
I'm visiting somebody's house.
Or...
Okay.
Whose house is this?
I didn't get kicked out of my own house.
702 Zenview.
This is my house.
All right.
Let's see what happens.
Let's save it here.
I didn't get evicted though.
Where's the broom?
Everyone's obsessed with the damn computer.
All right.
It's time to make a murder mystery happen.
Let's have a killer here.
And maybe not.
Not yet.
Let's have a fucking party here or something.
Let's...
The cat is sick?
How is the cat sick?
Anxious plus three.
I'm not putting the cat in the fucking oven.
All right.
I need to...
Cat needs to eat.
So eat and then let's play.
Are there food bowls?
There's food right here.
You sound like a goddamn ghost from Mario 64.
Where are the food bowls?
Didn't I have two of them?
Apparently not.
Maybe it was before I saved.
I'm gonna throw a party.
No, I gotta fill it with me.
She's hungry.
All right.
Let me see what happens now.
Hunger is pretty low.
Let's go eat.
And then I'm throwing a party.
I'm inviting all my friends over.
Why?
What's wrong with the cat?
What?
Play.
Let's play.
Play with...
Get attention from Vroomer.
What friends?
I'm gonna call people over and hang out.
Let's get a party set up.
You think this is a shitty grilled cheese?
Really?
I'm an asshole.
All right.
Inventory.
Let's get a party going.
Yeah.
I'm gonna invite everybody.
Lock the door and have a murder mystery.
But first...
That was a liquid grilled cheese.
All right.
Let's go.
Save it.
Who ran over the cat?
Nobody ran over the cat.
The cat is just fine.
Open up my phone.
Doctor's appointment.
Invite the shaman over.
No.
Travel, work, social.
Check media, send text.
Plan a social event.
Okay.
Incognito costume party.
Dance party.
House party.
Black and white bash.
Dinner party.
Birthday party.
A wedding.
Let's say birthday party.
Let's invite.
Click to invite someone.
Caterer guest.
I don't have any friends.
Ancient ruins.
Island bluff.
Invite a...
Yeah.
I don't have any friends.
I just don't.
All right.
Let's join a gang.
We have to make friends somehow.
Partners.
Call out gangs.
Join the thotties.
Enable the thotties gang.
Outfit for this sim.
Got it.
Let's join the thotties gang.
Jeremy has joined the thotties gang.
Jeremy will now contribute in their acts autonomously.
You can disable the autonomy from the mod's options.
Be aware members from other gangs will hunt and kill Jeremy
if he killed a member of their gang.
I have a joke.
Is the cat dead?
Okay.
So gang.
Let's see what we got here.
Gangs.
Invite the thotties gang's town.
Jesus Christ!
The thotties gang are arriving to this lot soon.
All right.
Is that a thottie?
What?
They're logging.
Uh-oh.
I don't understand.
Why is Red Dead Redemption 2 music playing?
They're all coming into town.
All right.
So they don't...
You're gonna stab me?
They're everywhere now.
Oh Jesus.
Okay.
What about Snuffleuficus?
Does he get to play too?
Does he get to join?
How do I join?
You join.
That's good.
What do they want me to do?
I just called the cops.
All right.
What's the emergency?
I don't understand what's happening.
You called the cops and now you're gonna throw money?
What's your emergency?
It's the thotties.
They're here.
Don't you see them?
All right.
Well, it's not exactly.
It looks like Jeremy isn't used to eating spicy food with time.
What do you mean I'm not used to eating spicy food?
All right.
I need to open up my fucking gang activity menu.
They just closed.
All right.
Where are the thotties?
Is this something I need to do?
More choices.
Gangs.
Remove from the thotties gang.
Pay to kill.
Pay to kill what?
It's hitman time.
Well, the thotties are just in town.
What's this?
What am I doing?
I just like strangled him for no reason.
What?
What happened to him?
No, no, no, no.
Don't leave.
They took his hair.
They grabbed his hair and ripped it off.
All right.
Fight back, dude.
Fuck this.
He's going to join the Vroomers.
Read guidebook?
No.
Gangs.
Join the hardwood gang.
Call them over.
Let's see where they are.
Invite the hardwood gang to town.
Vroomer has joined the hardwood gang.
God damn it.
Why?
This is going to get ugly.
What was that?
Is this one of them?
What is the noise?
I'm hearing noises.
All right.
This would be a gang panel.
Oh, somebody's going to be struck by lightning, I think.
Aren't these two mortal enemies?
Who's even out here?
He's sleeping.
Dog's fine.
Cat's fine.
Right?
Where am I?
All right.
I'm fine.
Yeah.
I'm just giving like I'm saying hello to all my fellow gang members.
This is the lamest gang fight I've ever seen.
Who's this?
There's a guy with an umbrella just keeps walking by.
I have a bat now.
Oh, she's gone.
All right.
Gang.
Jesus.
That thunder.
Can one of you...
Can one of my boys stand up for me here?
Is this...
It's the genie.
Is it the genie?
What's the dog out here?
All right.
Retaliation.
Can somebody else fight back?
Somebody has to fight back.
I'm hearing people getting hit by bats.
Where the fuck did you come from?
Like I got instant muscles.
Is this the genie?
I don't know if this is the genie or not.
Fame and reputation.
Who the fuck are you?
Who is this person?
Why is there a golden cowboy?
Has anybody figured this out?
Golden cowboy.
Funny introduction.
I need to know this person.
I need to hang out with this person right now.
Please be a friend.
There's a knife in my hand.
All right.
Forget it.
Stop.
I want to be friends with the golden cowboy.
Share...
Why is he asleep?
Oh my god.
Can we get rid of them so they stop crying?
He's back.
He's got his hair back too.
He's fine.
That guy also has a gun.
Don't ask me why that person has a gun in their hand.
Are we just going to continuously cry?
Oh my god.
All right.
Enough.
Make friends with this weird golden cowboy, please.
What are you doing?
Witness gang murder.
No.
I want this guy's phone number.
What are you...
Excuse me.
What happened?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
No, please.
Just talk.
I just need to get his phone number.
I don't care about anything else.
Holy shit.
No, stop.
Anybody out here that...
Stop running home.
Oh, you're the worst.
Chat.
I'm both fucking...
I just want his name.
Just want his name.
Okay, here we go.
Chat.
Go over there.
What are you doing?
Don't give me money and run.
Oh my god, you fucking little asshole.
Wait.
Fuck you then.
I don't know who these people are.
He got away.
Where was I ever going to find him again?
I let the treasure goblin get away.
I'm not killing this person anymore.
All right.
It's time for you to cut the shit and have a part.
Did I meet anybody?
I need to see if I chat with...
There you go.
I met one person.
I need to make friends.
What are you doing here?
Why is death here?
I just made him gain some weight.
Bark at.
Okay, so something we need to remember here is somebody...
That was fucking weird.
The girl was killed in here.
Let's keep moving here.
Can I move?
No, not with him.
At least you're having fun.
Can somebody clean this up?
Okay, so who...
You guys, both you two are still alive, so that's good.
I'm okay with this.
Death killed somebody.
No, no, no, no.
What are you doing with that gun?
Who is this?
He was going to shoot me and then he realized how bad I smelled and his AI fucked up.
I've got to get in front of it.
Can I go home now?
You smell something?
He thought I was already dead, yeah.
Why am I still dressed like this?
Why am I still doing this?
Why are people glowing?
Because I enabled world peace from the genie,
which I'm not even sure the genie exists anymore.
Does somebody free the genie?
World peace sure didn't work.
Get out of here.
Home.
Stop dancing and go home.
How do I leave the gang?
You just can't get over a tenure.
I did a great job upholding the world peace.
I'm gonna be honest with you.
I didn't mean to do anything.
They just...
I did like the gang fight.
You can't actually do this, can you?
What are you doing out here?
Why does everybody keep leaving the house?
I need to know what you're doing out here.
Let's follow you.
And?
What are you doing?
Is it the person that's walking towards me?
That was a huge strike of lightning.
I'm gonna sit here and watch.
This is kind of concerning.
You know the umbrella is supposed to stay up.
That's the banana.
We're getting a crossover episode here.
I came all the way over here just to do that.
I don't like this.
And now he's very sad.
Very sad.
What's your problem?
Social talk.
Meet some friends.
I need to have a party.
I apparently punched this guy in the face.
I walked over punched him in the face and then
fell asleep on the bench apparently.
But why wouldn't you just go to bed?
What?
Why?
Eight is running away?
Hold on.
Who's running away?
Eight is running away?
But posting an alert via computer or a phone can help find.
What do you mean find her?
Where?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Don't leave.
No, no, no, no, no.
Stop.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
You.
You're out here.
Go get her.
Right now.
Stop what you're doing.
Where's the fucking cat?
Where is she?
All right there.
You.
Go get her.
Take to the bed.
Get over there.
Hurry up.
Don't let her run away.
Come on.
Quickly.
Don't let her get away.
How do I run?
Run, run, run.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Go over here.
Over here.
No, sit here.
Lie down, lie down, lie down, lie down, lie down.
Get the fuck over there.
Come on.
Where the fuck are you?
Where is he?
Hurry up.
He's just strolling there.
Wait.
Hey, hey.
Who's?
Back up.
No, no, no.
Wait, wait, wait.
My.
I'm just taking drugs.
Where am I?
Oh my God.
You're so dumb.
Go pick up the cat.
Go.
What are you doing?
Why are you not paying?
Pick up the cat.
Put the bat away now.
Put the bat away right fucking now.
Pick this cat up now.
Don't you dare.
Why would you yell at the cat?
What are you doing?
It's so bad.
Hey, don't beep for your shell.
What the hell is wrong with you?
Rumor is mean.
Mean Sims become happy when they say mean things to other Sims.
What's wrong?
Okay.
Comfort.
Take cat to the vet.
All right.
We're good now.
Everything's fine.
All right.
Go home.
Time to go home.
No.
Take it to the vet.
Time for vet.
Bring to vet now.
Okay.
Thank God.
Traveling to the vet.
Where's the vet?
Is it that different world?
Can we leave the Brindledon Bay to the vet?
It's the Wharf Vet Clinic.
Let's go.
I've got a cat here.
I need some.
I got a cat.
Okay.
Let's go in.
Can you treat my cat?
Why am I walking like this?
What is that dog?
Okay.
This is liquid.
Liquid diarrhea.
Am I taking money from the register?
No.
Okay.
I'm fine.
So I don't give a shit about the cat that's out there.
Coffee.
Okay.
What about that Rudolph the Red-Nosed Reindeer dog?
I'm not supposed to be in here.
Why am I in here?
Is he spraying?
Spray painting?
What is on my gun?
What?
What was my gun?
The wallpaper of the bathroom.
Why?
What?
What are you doing?
Why?
What?
What on earth?
Somebody please help my cat.
Why would you do this?
Unfucking believable.
This is so sad.
What do I hear?
Alien sounds.
Hello?
Oh, this is the worst.
I need treatment.
Please.
Treat me.
That's got another cup of coffee.
The thing in the front desk?
Oh shit.
Okay.
Sign 8 in for curing.
Sign 8 in for a spay.
Death is hitting on somebody over there.
He's gonna do it again.
No, I'm gonna prevent that from happening.
A vet will be with you soon to examine and treat your sick pet.
Please be patient.
So where's...
Get pet examined.
Who's examining the pet?
Oh, he's going up there now.
Okay.
Of course, the vet.
Has cat ears.
Really?
Are you serious?
Pet examined.
Looks like 8 has woozy-kiddiitis.
Which option would you like to have?
Expensive treatment.
Spare no expense and cure your pet with the best medicine available.
I'm so used to seeing dogs, man.
All right.
Back to normal.
We're good.
Thank you.
Back to normal.
All right.
We can go home now.
What's the sad music for?
What's going on?
Sad music.
That was kind of scary.
You got one too.
Okay.
Both armed.
Wait, death just got arrested?
I don't even know what that was.
What about the kitty?
No, stop.
Stop, stop it.
The dog is just like here.
How do I get him out of jail?
You're going to jump up and eat the treats?
I'm going to get him out of jail.
I can't.
No, I can't.
I have to stop that.
I have to stop that joke.
It's not...
We did it too many times.
I've done that too many times.
There are no more vets.
All right.
No, it's not funny anymore.
I'm out.
Get me out of here.
Go home.
Why is he taking a picture?
Does the cat know how to go home?
It's going to arrest the cat.
No, you can't arrest the cat.
I need to get this cat back home.
But nobody can...
Somebody's going to pick the cat up.
I'm in a different world right now.
What's Jerma doing?
I don't know, but at home.
Okay, you need to come get this cat.
Stop shooting.
Oh, this is bad.
Why am I...
What was that?
Am I covered in blood?
Is death going to take my cat?
I need to get you home.
That's a bad idea.
Don't attack death.
All right, go.
Let's focus on switch control.
I got to pull that cat back.
All right.
Cat, call over.
The cat brought two friends, I guess.
All right.
Invite over.
Funny introduction.
Welcome to the house.
It's time to have a party.
How do I get you out of jail?
How are you still at the hospital?
Where is he?
On the computer at the vet's.
We got two more vets.
We're good.
Cat is home.
Everyone's home.
Time for you to go home, too.
He's about to make a coffee again.
Oh, my God.
No, just get out of here.
Just make your exit.
Home.
Goodbye.
All right.
Thank you for treating my animal.
Let's get control.
Let's switch control to Jeremy Reinhardt.
All right.
The pets are doing just fine.
Everyone's okay.
Let's check.
Let's actually check on traits here.
Let's make some food.
Enough with the bullshit.
I don't know who this is,
but they are currently in my house.
Oh, you're watching the people burn and fires video again, right?
That's great.
I guess I'm going to introduce myself.
How did the Grim Reaper die?
What?
Somebody killed the Grim Reaper in here.
Go home.
All right.
Hungry.
It's time to make food.
Cook.
A meal.
I already have a party here.
Hire staff.
Cook a grand meal.
I'm going to make a turkey dinner.
Nice things are happening, I guess.
Tofurky.
Wait, what the hell is Tofurky?
I have no clue.
That's all you need to do.
First to die, just kill somebody.
What?
Why?
Technically, he was first to die.
He was out of control.
He was.
All right.
Can I make a grand meal, please?
Okay, can we...
Don't forget about the Tofurky.
Right.
I was going to say, why?
Get out of the turkey.
I can't even click it.
Resume.
Turkey dinner.
Are you eating out of the bowl?
This is so cute.
It really is.
This is absolutely adorable.
And what was the photo?
Did I add money?
I think I put money in here.
My secret ingredient is money.
This is not a turkey.
At all.
This is a bowl of tomato.
Paste.
And that's it.
It's tofu turkey.
Really?
Oh, what?
Okay.
You can turn the oven on?
That's not how you turn an oven on.
It is a notch on the top right.
I just threw a lime in there.
Turn on the oven.
It's already on.
Okay.
So it looks pretty good.
Yeah, it does.
Did somebody just throw a glass at me?
What the fuck was that?
There it is.
Who's hungry?
I've got a Tufurki dinner.
I killed the vegetarian.
Did I actually kill the vegetarian?
I'm just sitting down.
Where's Doug?
I think me and death are having a flirty conversation.
I need to see what the hell you're doing up here.
Where are you?
Why do they always do this?
Just go home.
Why would you sleep on a park bench?
Like, go home.
What are you doing?
All right.
We're good.
How's the cat?
Pretty good, actually.
Dog?
Bladder?
Where's the dog?
Have you eaten?
Dog needs to go to the bathroom.
This is first to die.
This is Akira and Miko.
Mourning a friend.
Oh, right.
First to die.
I think it's time.
We gotta clean this up.
Release all these spirits.
Release, release, release.
Release this one, too.
Get them all out of here.
Yeah, get out.
Out.
All right, come eat.
Cat was eating out of the...
It's all right.
You are the most fucked up person out of everybody.
I swear.
You just...
I give you a task and you just don't do it.
Well, fucking whatever.
All right.
Dog, cat, everybody's good.
Oh, getting you mail?
Do we have mail?
Oh, shit.
We have mail.
The urns are blocking the way.
Oh, we'll just get rid of them.
What?
I heard bad sounds?
All right.
He's sleeping.
Okay.
All right.
Fast forward.
Playing with the cat.
When you get up, eat.
I'll just queue it up for you.
Pick up a serving.
Go eat.
No, no.
What are you...
Why?
What would you do to...
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
What are you doing?
Why?
We were just playing.
Oh, my God.
Why?
Where are you now?
This is unbelievable.
What?
No, no.
Cat has to...
No.
I still have you.
Hold on.
I need to redo this.
Oh, my fucking head.
The cat made the right choice.
Yes, the cat did.
I'm honest to God.
Well, it's just you and me.
I need to get out of this house before something else bad happens.
You don't run away, please.
Did this bite me?
Okay.
Why are you yelling at the dog?
The dog didn't do anything.
Am I gonna go piss on this lady?
Bladder.
I need to take the...
All right.
That's it.
You're done.
You're out.
That's enough out of you.
You're out of fucking control.
Absolutely out of control.
Put it away.
You're done.
Enough.
My God.
You've chainsawed three people now.
Un-fucking-believable.
No, the dog.
Okay.
How do I get the dog in the fruit house?
All right.
Can I have the dog go to the fruit house?
You're gonna piss on the couch.
All right.
It's time to transition to a different group.
This just got completely out of hand.
How do I get the dog out of here?
I've sent him to hell.
This is where I belong.
This is where you belong.
Yeah, goodbye.
You're out.
What?
Oh, shit.
Uh, the last sim in this household has died.
Uh, adoption services will take care of giant and eight.
A good loving family will be found.
Okay.
Um, let's pick up what we left off over here.
Everyone's still alive over here and nobody's murdering each other.
Select the sim to play.
We're gonna go with a banana.
I got the haunted mirror in here and I also have the genie to still play with.
And, uh, one other thing.
I also do this to activate it by.
Let me see how to activate it.
Let's just see how it works.
So it's T let's see.
TM set hat.
TM set mask.
Okay.
TM set hat.
And then we need an object ID.
TM like this set hat.
I think like that.
TM dot set hat.
And we'll put on, um, just try something easy.
How about like a TV or a sculpture rug?
Right click to set as a head.
Really.
Enable.
So what?
I can just right click.
You need cheats to be on.
Yeah, they should be on already.
Wire social network career play game.
I can't right click anything.
Shift click.
Read clean up.
Testing cheats.
True.
Testing.
Cheats.
True.
Cheats are enabled.
Okay, good.
So that should be it, right?
And then shift right click or shift click.
Okay, set as head.
Why is it so big?
That should not be this big.
Reset that.
Reset.
No, no, no.
Get rid of this.
How do I get rid of this?
It's so huge.
Reset object.
Oh, no.
I need to like sell it.
All right.
Can I put a bed on my head and have somebody sleep on it?
Let's see.
What about a chair?
Why is that fucking huge?
All right, get in this chair.
Is he going to grow?
No, it's because the head proportions are really fucked up on all the characters, right?
Oh, no.
All right, sit on his head.
Can you get up there?
Nap lazily.
We have to be in the same room, don't you?
Oh.
Okay.
So now from here, can somebody else sit on top of him?
Rita!
George!
Can you not get up there?
Get up there.
No, you can't.
Sit on your own head.
Is he sleeping?
He's asleep right now.
I have to put a chair on the other guy.
Oh, God.
This is going to be fucking ridiculous.
He's going to be out of hand real quick here.
Oh, is he stuck in the wall?
Where is she?
He's stuck in the wall.
Hold on, get out, get out, get out.
Turn off the computer.
Everybody wants to play with the computer.
All right, come over here.
Okay, you sit here.
I don't know, you sit here.
And then you sit there.
Go for it.
No, get over here.
No!
What are you doing?
I ain't ready to go on the computer.
I think I'm going to go on the computer now.
Did you just tell me to get up?
I'm going to get up.
No, I'm going to go on the computer again.
Let's get them all.
Let's get the chairs.
What's that?
Why is that tense music playing?
What's the tense music for?
Huh?
Hello?
One, two, three, four, who's five?
Where's Tommy Tomato?
What is going on?
Do you guys hear this?
Is somebody banging at the door?
What the fuck is happening over here?
Relax, calm it down down over here.
What's going on here?
He doesn't live with anybody.
He lives by himself.
Good evening.
We have to despise each other.
Let's go in there.
Let's go.
Just take the fuck and steal everything he has.
He's gone.
He left the apartment.
Let's go.
All right, we're all here.
Nice.
I like this place.
Ooh, you know what?
It's beautiful.
You got cool shit.
Oh, this is not moving out.
That's why he's freaking out so much.
All these boxes and shit come in.
Let's go.
Get in here.
Look at this shit.
He's got a fireplace.
He's got one of those super toilets.
What is that?
He's got like a telepod.
What?
This guy's apartment is amazing.
Wow.
Hey, come on down.
Let's get a mixologist here.
Let's play the piano.
Hire pianists.
Get him in here.
Let's go.
Uh, the genie's a bartender.
If the pianist is the gnome, I'm gonna laugh.
What?
This person's dead.
Invite your friends over here.
Invite to hang out at current lot.
You too.
Party time.
Computer, I gotta get out the computer.
God, I'm gonna play the VR.
Can I hire more services?
Entertainment.
All right.
Take selfie, take photo, play game, browse web.
No, no, no.
Household.
Work.
Get the shaman over here.
Let's have a party.
Uh, what about the drug dealer?
Let's get the drug dealer over here too.
Let's get invite to hang out at current lot.
I should be able to bring, yeah, you too.
No, I, that's a wrong group.
Okay, let's go on in.
Look at this.
Everyone's having a good time.
Meeting new friends.
Shaman has arrived.
Got a couple of beers here.
This is all right.
Uh, casual disco.
Let me get, let me grab a drink.
Why is it playing baby crib music?
Okay, where's um, grab a drink.
Yeah, why, what is, where's that coming from?
Where's the shaman?
Very focused on what?
Can somebody meet the shaman?
I said the shaman was here.
Where's the shaman?
I don't see a shaman.
Is that the shaman?
That is the shaman.
Okay, um, so how do we, uh, how do we get this going?
Share knock knock joke compliment spiritual journey.
I still don't know where this crib music is coming from.
Uh, did I do it?
Uh, that doesn't look, it doesn't look like a spiritual journey to me.
Ghost is playing.
All of you go on a spiritual journey.
Throw a party.
I am trying to get everyone to invite their friends and go on like spiritual journeys and shit.
Can you call anybody else?
This guy, get over here.
He said it's, it's too late.
I don't have, everybody had that I make friends with dies guys.
I've made like four friends.
And we've killed half the town.
It's because it's 4 a.m.
Where is the owner?
Where did he go?
Okay, let's see.
Give it to me.
All right, here we go.
Time to drink.
Take it.
Do not drink this unless you are ready for what it may bring.
Drink it.
I'm ready.
Spiritual journey incoming.
This guy just brew coffee and bring it over here and just lie.
Very self-assured sims of this trade feel good about themselves and often experience extra confidence.
Some spiritual journey this was.
I'm just staring at the TV.
Just thinking about grilled cheese.
Uh, okay, how about the...
Look at this guy.
Party.
It's time for a party.
One of you freak shows has to be awake right now, right?
Get over here.
It's not too late.
They're all sleeping.
Oh, fuck off.
What time is it?
Come on.
6 30 a.m.
7 a.m.
Start the party all over again.
Las Vegas.
This is where we are.
Come on.
Definitely not sleeping at 7 a.m.
No, don't invite him.
That's his house.
All right.
Let's go.
Here they come.
Are we losing a bartender?
Get another one.
Another one.
Hire another mixologist.
Bring him in.
Welcome everybody.
Come on down.
I'll be right over.
Uncomfortable.
Come on in.
Here we go.
There's at least five or six to maybe there's at least 10 people coming over right now.
Greet them.
Get them off your asses and host this party.
Are they coming over to my house?
Here we go.
Load them up.
Arita Ma music.
Because he has a stereo system somewhere, right?
No, that's a toilet.
Stereo.
He's got to have a stereo.
No piano.
Get the pianist in here again.
There it is.
Okay.
Music is playing.
Change volume.
Hi.
Max it up.
Why would you be listening to this?
Fucking pop music.
Let's start a dance party.
Dance together.
Bring it in.
Get them all in the living room.
What are they all doing here?
Why is this person so small?
Oh, it's a kid.
I'm trying to make them leave.
I'm trying to get the kid out of here.
Get out of here.
Junk them up.
Go away.
Oh, wait, wait.
Yeah.
Hold on.
Okay.
They're good.
All right.
Welcome to the party.
Let's get some drinks served.
All right.
Nice.
This is looking good.
Fun games.
Fun friends.
Uh-oh.
Oh, he's on a spiritual journey.
Right, right, right.
I can't lock the door.
Oh, I can't.
I can't.
Where is he?
Why is everybody freaking out about him?
Wait.
Where is he?
Where's the blueberry?
What happened?
What's he doing?
Why is everybody so pissed?
Barry feels as if he's being pulled out of his body into another realm.
A presence of a benevolent entity appears who telepathically communicates
that she wishes to guide Barry around the astral place.
Follow.
Barry finds himself outside a hut with sandals outside.
An overwhelming feeling that someone sacred lives there
takes hold.
A much older version of Barry emerges from the hut.
What should Barry do?
What is your purpose?
The old man's expression changes from kind smile to berating gaze.
He speaks,
My purpose has nothing to do with why you are here.
This is a sacred place of self-realization.
You're not ready.
That's annoying.
Let's go.
What?
And cooking level one.
Who has cooking level one?
Any idiots have cooking level one?
Oh, god damn it.
Really?
What?
Why?
I don't have any weed.
Very competent.
Buy weed from the computer.
Put your clothes back on.
She was happy, but wait a minute.
Get up.
We did it.
Hey, no, try for baby.
What happened?
What are you doing?
We just started dating.
Try for a baby.
Hey, the first time I kiss you, you want to have a baby?
I can't do first person.
I can't.
No, I can't do first person.
This isn't even our house.
Man.
No, look, it's pretend, see?
Not even our house.
Here's the thing that I can't comprehend.
Where is the guy who owns this apartment?
I just had sex in his bed.
Here's the apartment key to this apartment to this one.
Here's the key to this apartment.
Okay, hold on.
More choices.
Romance.
Ask to be girlfriend.
Come on.
Let's make a baby.
Here we go.
All right, now girlfriend just became girlfriend of Peter.
Attempt more choices.
Come on.
What's wrong?
Why is everybody staring?
You want to try for a baby?
Let's try for a baby this time.
No, that's awful.
No, no, no.
I'm not going to like have him go in there.
All right, we're not going to see it.
Look, we're going to go this way.
Okay, we're good.
Break out the candles, make it romantic.
Peter is about to woohoo.
It didn't work.
I have to get that off.
All right, did it work?
Baby and baby.
No, baby.
Did it work?
I have to do a pregnancy test.
Since when?
Why does she have money come all up?
You're getting in.
Okay, all right, all right.
Slow down here.
I have no control.
I don't have control.
Where did she go?
All right, get this thing out of here.
I can't even sell it.
I don't have access to this house.
Oh, shit.
Clear out, clear out, clear out.
Everybody out.
Out, out, out, out, out, out, out, out.
He didn't even know.
He didn't know.
Out.
All right, everybody pause again.
We're going to make this quick.
You, go here, go here, go here, go here.
You, we're going to first person.
Okay, I'm just going to punch him in the face.
Knock him out.
Wait, what?
What are you guys doing?
Where'd he go?
Oh, shit.
She's back.
I think she really thinks this is my house.
He doesn't even know.
I try to get everybody out.
Does she have his key?
What?
Oh, God.
I don't know what to do.
He's got the drug cup.
This dude is dressed like the Riddler from Batman Forever.
Does he think, oh, yeah, I must have done this.
He's noticing it now.
It's our house now.
All right, that's OP as hell.
This whole thing is just fucked up.
All right, where's the magic mirror?
The magic ghost mirror?
All right, everybody back out.
Everybody back to the house.
That was awful.
It's okay, though.
All right, bring everybody back here.
We'll have a party here now.
Bring people here.
Bring here.
Bring them all here.
Everybody's here.
Here's the magic scary mirror.
Chant the bride's name.
Admire a new possession.
Protect self.
Chant multiple brides' names.
Well, here's what we're going to do.
We're going to invite everybody over here again.
What time is it?
Everybody.
How's everybody?
How are you doing?
Energy.
Tomorrow, we're going to have some people sleep.
And tomorrow, throw a party and then have Bloody Mary show up.
There's also the chaos book, too.
That's true.
I didn't have a bed, don't I?
People need to be energized.
I don't want people falling asleep.
You know what I mean?
Just go to bed on that couch right now.
I need to figure out how to get clothes on him again.
Sleep on the cat bed.
All right.
Everybody asleep?
How are we all doing?
Hey, I heard you became friends with Aya.
She's pretty cool.
That's my girlfriend.
Are you?
Yeah, you're asleep.
All right, everyone's almost there.
You're in the bed, too, right?
Okay, sleep.
Can I adopt the rat?
I don't think so.
Yeah, I use the genie.
All right, here we go.
Are you ready?
Time to throw a party.
Here comes a real murder mystery.
I'm going to get everybody here.
I'm going to lock the door
and I'm going to chant in front of the mirror.
I have no idea what's going to happen.
You get a club to join?
It's a Dragon Ball Z character.
What's wrong with you?
Where am I?
All right, set party through the phone.
Play a game, take a photo,
chat with, plan a social event.
A lot of people are already here.
Incognito costume party.
House party.
Yeah, house party.
I'm the host.
Me, here are a couple of guests.
Just these two.
Entertainer, hire somebody.
Mixologist, hire somebody.
Caterer, hire somebody.
Location is right here.
Wait, I know that this is my house.
Okay, let's go.
Dance party.
Just wait till everybody shows up.
I need food.
Bye.
All right, lock the door.
Lock the door, lock the door, lock the door.
You really just jumped the gun there.
Oh, come on.
No, stop fighting.
Where's the door?
Get in here.
Why did you do that?
What was the point of that?
We were, nobody even got in there yet.
This is lagging so much.
That's why.
Motherfuckers.
All right.
Lock door.
For everyone.
Okay.
Wait, who's this guy?
Get in here.
Allow access to Pauline.
Oh, fuck it.
That person's just gonna stay out there.
Everybody lock it.
All right, it's a dark and stormy night.
We have a handful of people in here.
Who wants to chant into the mirror?
How about blueberry?
Chant multiple brides' names.
Let's come over and hit this lady.
I don't get it.
Oh no, I get it.
Oh my God.
Oh, where's she going?
What?
Holy shit.
Nobody cares.
Now she's crying.
Who's out here?
Who's out there on the cell phone?
This is a lot more anti-climactic than I thought.
What?
Who just punched me?
Fuck off.
What?
Deal.
This is only when the chainsaw is still in the house.
Where's Bloody Mary?
Why am I outside?
All right.
You suck.
You're not even scary.
Is everybody hungry?
Get me away from the first person.
Am I gonna get arrested for killing the lady?
This is me getting in trouble.
Arrested for murder.
The cops can't even get in.
What?
What the fuck?
I don't understand what I'm seeing here.
Who just died?
It's a random person, I think.
So you can't kill her.
Okay.
I need to tell some jokes.
You're going straight to hell.
Start a fire.
There's just spawning in the town.
Hey.
This guy has a gun.
This lady.
Why is the genie here?
Why is it coming over here?
Good work.
You did it.
Where's the book?
They can't even get in the door.
The door is dead.
The door is locked.
Nobody can even get in.
All right.
Where's the book?
Wasn't there a book?
Where's the bookcase?
Read something.
Open.
Here it is.
The book of chaos.
Read the book of chaos.
Do you have it?
Where are you?
I can't even open the door.
Paul, wait.
Hold on.
Wasn't Paul the only one that could open the door?
All right.
Unlock it.
Unlock.
Everybody can come in now.
Get in.
Read the book of chaos.
Okay.
Now I can lock the door.
What the hell does this do?
Did somebody eat a piece of cake?
Don't worry, everybody.
I'll just open up the book of chaos and read it.
Did I not read it?
Am I taking it into the bathroom?
I wanted a better place to read.
Read it.
What happens when you read the whole thing?
What's going on?
Do something.
What happens here?
You're just crying.
I'm sorry.
I just had to make something happen.
This book doesn't do anything.
He can't read.
He's just pointing at the lines.
Oh, this one looks bright.
This one's different colored.
Look, he actually has to...
You all right?
Okay.
Guys, he actually has to learn how to read.
He has to learn to read first.
Galarga!
Nepha learned how to read.
Reading like the Necronomicon.
Just you wait when he's done finishing
and figuring out how to read this book.
All right, let's go make a baby.
Where is she?
All right, more choices.
Try for a baby.
Come on.
You finished reading the book?
Violence and Barry is violent.
Try for a baby.
Shift-click the ground to start a fire anywhere.
I don't have that.
Anybody in this bed?
Come on!
Where'd he go?
Let's go.
Okay.
I want a baby out of that.
You finished reading the book yet?
Where is it?
You don't just put a book like that down on the ground.
Oh, shit.
Where is it?
Somebody take it?
Where is everybody?
Carpet by the front door.
Baby?
What are you doing?
Oh, it's right here.
Wait, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait a minute.
Drown a Sim in pee.
Don't read that.
Don't.
Hold on.
Who am I torturing?
Get that book back.
All right, put it down.
Okay, freeze Sim.
Uh, who's even up here?
Who's up here still?
This lady right here.
What does that do?
Do you actually just freeze them?
Like cold freeze them?
Holy shit.
Is she dead?
No, somebody picked it up again.
Bingo.
Is this person still alive?
Hello?
Hey, like I haven't been talking.
Hey, hey, hey, wait up.
Whoa, whoa, whoa.
Excuse me.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Stop it.
You.
Get it.
You're done.
That's it.
That's enough out of you.
That's it from you.
They're both dead?
No.
Both dead.
Become best friends.
I've lost control.
It didn't even work.
He's like.
He is burnt to a fucking crisp.
Pause the game and everybody queue up to get hit by a car.
Oh, that's so funny.
Death is trying to put him out with the fire extinguisher.
No, this guy gets to live.
Fuck.
The car is just too good.
It really is the best thing ever.
Oh shit, save the game.
It's all right.
We still got the gnome.
We still have drug gnome.
Save game, save.
All right, I'll save game, save, save, wait, wait, save, save, save.
I don't think I even picked that lady to get hit by a car.
I'm fairly certain that that lady was not one that was selected.
I can't save the game.
Why?
I have, we're stuck here, guys.
I can't save it.
What?
What are you doing?
Why is it focusing on you?
Witness death, witness death.
Half the people are just locked up.
Why does this guy have a cake?
What are you bringing this for?
You're bringing a little mouse loaf.
The door is locked.
The cops can't get in.
All right, it's time for all hell to break, Liz.
Where is it?
Good luck.
Have fun, everybody.
I can't save it.
That was a million T-poses.
Who's even left alive?
Banana?
Who's gonna be left alive after all this?
All right, I can't, I don't even have to.
Oh, no.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Like, this is, I have to, like, where's the, where,
I have to move somebody, I have to move.
Not the banana.
I gotta stop him.
God damn it.
Saved.
Okay, I can't do that.
No, now he's dead.
Now he's dead, now he's dead.
Undress him in puke.
Okay, so let's just get the door open again.
Unlock the door.
Invite the rest of the guests in.
Welcome everybody.
Okay, I still cannot save the game.
I want this guy, not only as a best friend,
I want him around forever.
I want to meet you.
Spare the banana.
Oh, shit, plead.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I can't plead.
He's dead.
This guy's way more important.
Nobody knows what to do.
The whole game's just, like, soft-locked.
It's, the whole game is soft-locked.
No, plead.
Strengthen connection with the physical world.
Is this him?
No, come on.
Does it work?
No, it's Walter Sizemore.
I don't even know.
I, it has to be done.
God damn it.
What?
No, I wanted to make a baby with.
I can't even plead.
How do I, how do I Benedict Banana?
Mourn, mourn, polo.
Laugh at Peter.
That way Peter's, Peter, which one was Peter?
How do I, I can't plead.
Why?
Okay, there we go.
Plead for Lily.
Who cares?
Just getting a coffee.
Give me a break.
All right.
There's too many people that are dead.
All right, come on.
Plead for Benedict.
Bring him back.
No?
Been brought back to life.
All right, now Benedict, you plead for the grant.
I need to make a baby.
He's back.
Come on, get up.
Why are you not getting up?
Thank God.
All right, now I gotta plead for Peter Plumb's life.
Don't fight.
You just got brought back to life.
Seriously.
Do not do this right now.
You just got brought back to life.
Peter's super dead.
No, he can be brought back.
Hello?
Can you like move to UFC world or something?
We don't need you in Sims world.
Okay.
Plead.
Get out of here.
Go back to hell.
We gotta clean this plate.
He's back.
Get the fuck out of here.
Guarantee this works.
What are you doing?
Get out of here.
All right, we're aging you down.
It says you're like a baby.
And I'm like throwing you.
I'm throwing you back to hell.
It's actually working.
Wait, he's like...
That scared him, of all things.
She's pregnant?
No, she's not.
Is she pregnant?
Are you sure?
How can you tell?
Oh shit.
She actually might be pregnant.
Okay.
All right, here we go.
New sitcom.
Clean up.
Everybody clean, clean, clean, clean.
Get rid of the urns.
No more parties.
Release spirit.
How do I just delete them?
Release.
You're drinking a lot of coffee while you're pregnant.
That's not a good idea.
Booty.
Invite her to move in.
She already is, isn't she?
There's the apartment key.
Invite to...
Chat?
No, and travel?
No, no, no, no, no.
Friends, household.
Is there an actually add to household?
Invite to add to group.
More choices, maybe?
Clubs, more choices.
I have to marry her.
Well, I can't...
Can I do that?
As the banana?
All right, friendly.
Ask about giving when we discuss interests.
Complain about weather.
Get to know.
Propose crazy scheme.
Turn on sheets and then shift click.
Add to household.
Add to family.
Modify.
Bingo.
Okay, so pregnant, huh?
I need to get some sleep.
Now that I have less people to deal with.
Clean up the blood.
Mop up this bullshit.
Get rid of the urns.
So many people died.
Adopt the rat.
I wonder if it's possible.
Let's see.
How would I do that?
Through the phone?
Go to the vet?
The computer, okay.
Well, I deleted all the computers
because they were too addicted to the computers.
Remember?
I had to get rid of all of them.
There's no computer left in the house.
All right, computer.
What a nice one.
They're all locked.
All right, how about this one?
All in one PC.
Somebody's bedroom or something.
I can't put it in the bathtub.
Never mind.
Where was this?
Get a job?
Well, let's just put it right here for now.
Who cares?
Okay, let's go see if I can get...
Okay, write jokes.
More choices.
Career.
Household.
Adopt.
Adopt a dog.
Was it a dog?
Adopt.
Adopt a dog?
I still can't save the game.
Oh, it's because the adoption's in progress.
That's fine.
It's not there.
Sorry, guys.
What about a cat?
I have to adopt the cat.
No.
I'll try the other one to see.
What the hell?
Nope.
You can buy those.
You can adopt kids.
All right, get rid of these so we can hurry this up.
Spirit world, release.
This one, please.
Come on, then we can feed...
I just gotta free us.
Free the spirit.
Goodbye.
No!
Oh, autonomous killing was on.
Still...
It's all right, I'll plead for his life.
Plead.
Plead for Andy.
Stop crying.
Get over there.
Demand.
Let him live.
No.
Well, now it's just these two that live in the house together.
God damn it.
Turn off auto kill.
He wanted to get rid of everybody else.
Where is it?
War choices, extreme violence, options.
Turn it off.
Disable.
Disable for everybody.
For everyone, not just this person.
That's okay.
Uh, for the whole household, right?
Why would I open...
What?
Is it disabled?
I figured it would be down next to the one that says enable.
All right.
So when does the baby come out?
Nine months?
It's a full nine months?
Is it gonna take that long?
It's real time?
Is it nine in-game months?
How long does a genie baby work?
I can't tell if that's smell or if that's genie lines.
All right.
Can clean up the house.
Open the door.
Unlock the door.
Right?
No, it's already open.
All right.
This guy's dead.
Clean up the house.
Clean, clean, clean.
God.
Let's check back on the save in nine months.
By the way, why would I not see the gnome?
I'm kind of concerned here.
Hold on.
Thank God he's okay.
All right.
How do I turn this off?
Why are there like five murder brides walking around town right now?
All right.
I'm gonna get a job.
Goodbye.
Release.
All of them.
Why can't I get rid of this?
Just take it.
Who cares?
All right.
Still, I did this many people died in here.
I don't remember this many people dying.
It's like 12 people.
Get them all out of here.
Good.
Clean up.
Don't release Peter Plum.
Why?
He'll be back.
He's gonna come out of here.
He deserves better.
All right.
How you doing?
Energy, hygiene, take a bath.
Take a bubble bath.
I think you deserve it.
How are you doing?
Almost ready to wake up.
Grab some food.
See what I'm saying?
I can't like play the Sims.
All right.
Let's get up and get some food.
Take a bath.
Okay.
People just were on fire burning.
Zombies were eating people.
What happens if the genie rubs the lamp?
That's kind of an interesting question.
All right.
Wake up.
That's enough sleep.
Get some food.
Grab some food from here.
Hire a caterer.
Just fucking have somebody fucking eat.
I don't want to make any food.
Sleep.
That's not the reaction you want somebody to have.
Get your breakfast catered.
What a piece of crap.
Didn't the entire Pizzaz family die?
All right.
Clean it all up.
Oh, I evicted them.
Well, take a look.
Now the doll comes full circle.
How are you doing?
Hungry?
Okay.
I gave you a hundred bucks to come here.
It wasn't a hundred dollars to join the family.
That was a hundred dollars to cater of food.
Cook a gourmet meal.
Now, wait, what?
What's going on?
What happened to my camera?
Alt?
Alt tab?
What did I just do?
Huh?
Oh, shit.
Okay.
What is she making?
Didn't I, I ordered, I wanted breakfast.
What, is it vinegar?
What are you putting that in there for?
Is it hydrogen peroxide?
Really?
What?
A cake for breakfast.
All right.
Add like a, add a wetting topper.
No, how do I eat it?
Take a piece.
A cake for breakfast.
This is like a 12-year-old's house.
Do I not have a trash barrel?
It's right here.
Use it.
Dishes?
What's going on?
Is there a way for me to see how pregnant I am?
Very pregnant.
How do I know how pregnant?
Doesn't have a job.
Well, you're pregnant.
You just hang out.
I'm still sleeping.
Hover mouse over the pacifier for the trimester.
Second trimester in seven hours.
Oh, shit.
Second trimester coming up.
Let's see.
Oh, man.
Oh, what?
Hover over the thing.
No, it's okay.
We're good.
Guess.
I guess everything's fine.
That was a pretty wild debate right there.
It took it off and she was crying and it went to the bathroom.
Oh, that was not...
There's too many emotions going on right now.
From mourning...
From losing a good friend.
We took that way too seriously.
Oh, man.
That just...
Baby?
No, we're in a good mood.
Second trimester coming up.
This is a dirty ass toilet.
What are you doing?
Just sleeping?
Flush the toilet.
No, it's clean.
It's kind of concerning how long he's been asleep.
Uh, yeah.
It's been like three days.
He's been asleep for like 31 hours.
This game is fucked.
What is that, baby?
Second trimester.
How many trimesters are there?
Four?
How many periods are in a basketball game?
Three.
All right, let's get back to normal here.
Flirty.
Say trimester again.
Trimester.
Three-mester.
Oh, so dork.
Shoo-bee-row.
Okay.
So I wonder how long the third trimester is in the game.
I've never seen it before.
Floopy.
All right, get...
All right, quit lucid dreaming and wake the fuck up.
Up, up, up, up, get...
You're a lost cause.
Unpleasant conversation.
Tell gross joke.
Apologize.
Go away.
Mischief.
Give fake news.
Invite to fake party.
Lie about career.
Do an impression.
Get arrested for doing drugs?
Uh, hold on.
How fat can you make them?
You all right?
Why is everybody having...
Why is everybody panicking?
I'm at my limit.
Remembering a sim.
Two hours.
So close.
Is it laughing?
Everybody's just crying.
I can't even interact.
Get up.
All right, let's have a...
Let's cheer up.
Try to cheer up.
What's wrong?
What just happened?
Something unusual just happened to Penny out of nowhere
and so leave her scared for a couple of hours.
All right, let's go.
What are some drugs?
Just marijuana.
Isn't that a big deal?
Her game crashed and she cried about it.
Where are you running to?
Okay.
Third trimester in one day.
Last trimester.
Let's just...
Let's go.
How are they doing?
Food?
They're all right.
How you doing on food?
You're doing fine.
This dawn of this last day.
Pregnancy speedrun.
It's getting late.
It's almost 2 a.m. Eastern.
And as much as it is fun dicking around for 22 hours.
Remove the urn.
I can't even move it.
I can't get rid of it.
Just put it in your inventory.
Put the urn on as a hat.
The chaos book?
No, not yet.
I need to see this...
Wear this...
I need to see the pregnancy.
I've never seen it before.
You're in Nevada?
Yeah, I'm talking about for everybody else.
It's almost 11 p.m. for me right now.
But that means that it's almost 2 a.m.
For a bunch of people that are in America.
And forget about EU right now.
All right, getting there.
18 hours.
How do you have a baby delivered?
Throw this thing in the trash, please.
Do I have to have like a...
The hospital people at the doctor have to come out?
Do I have to go to the hospital?
What are you calling me?
Let's go down to the karaoke bar and sing some duets.
I've been practicing like crazy.
I was trying to say yes.
Never mind.
Baby's all I care about.
Let's go.
Put microwave on head and make food.
Am I gonna vaccinate the kid?
Oh, please.
All right.
Are you gonna...
What?
What's wrong?
Morning sickness.
And sore back.
You're almost through it.
It's almost over.
Anti-vaxxing is not politics.
No, I'm gonna vaccinate my goddamn baby.
12 hours.
Who's here?
Oh, it's me.
This cake has lasted a long time.
What happened to his banana costume?
My immersion.
It's now fall.
Prank day.
I'm not gonna go prank day.
End the holiday early.
Is it the next day?
Almost.
Prank day canceled.
All that matters is getting this baby out and away from this house.
Worst dream.
You ended prank day.
We already did prank day like eight hours ago.
What's going on?
Oh, she's puking.
Back to the computer.
What else can we do?
Practice programming.
How fresh.
You know what I've noticed?
Is anybody left?
I think we're the final...
There's nobody left.
The gnome is left.
Can I...
How do I...
I want to...
I'm just gonna bring the gnome over here.
Give me a second.
I'm gonna age the baby up when the baby gets here.
And let's see if it's just the dad again.
Let's see if we get Peter back.
Reincarnation through pregnancy.
Nothing like a pregnant woman buying illegal drugs.
How do I get him over here?
I need to call him, right?
How do I get you over here?
Have I explained why there's a ghost in the house?
Well, it's a genie.
Genie came out and started to socialize with everybody.
Granted a couple of real peace wishes.
That genie then fell in love with somebody in the house.
And then that person that she fell in love with
during a sims murder party died.
I've never met the gnome, so I can't invite him over.
Really?
God damn it.
Oh, then he like punched her in the face.
So I ran him over with a car.
All right, let's go.
Actually, you know what?
Let's save it here.
And I'm gonna go to the gnome's house.
Let's head to the gnome's house.
They'll be fine for a little while.
I need to get back to home worlds.
No, no, no, no.
Cancel this travel.
I have to just exit.
Manage worlds.
Let's take a look.
It's been a long time since we've even looked over here
and saw what was going on here.
All right.
So how are we doing?
Intro for it.
I don't think the gnome has left his house.
Uncomfortable.
I need you to go visit.
I want you to go visit somebody.
Nobody else knows who I am.
Stuck in the suit.
Yeah, he doesn't come out.
Is there a way I can just go visit the carrot?
Wait a minute.
What are they picketing out here?
What's going on here?
What does it say?
What is it?
I don't know.
Is it about the police?
About scales?
That just heard Russia.
Me too.
I also believe this.
Whatever it is.
I believe that too.
I did.
He did it on his own.
You acquired the charisma skill.
Hey, that was fun.
So what do you guys do after?
What do you want to do?
You all right?
This guy's freaking me out.
No, no, no, no, no.
No violence.
Let's go.
Why am I just the person that's doing?
This really is the gnome.
This just is like Twitch chat, right?
I'm gonna, I'm gonna get out of this.
You took the trash out now.
I took the trash out now too.
Jeremy, you're gonna miss the birth?
No, I'm not.
We got plenty of time.
This bloody stinks.
Why would you do that?
I better not do that too.
I don't know what to do.
All right.
I'm glad he was fucked.
I hear police.
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
I got something to ask you, lady.
Come here, come here, come here, come here, come here.
Hey, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Wait, please.
Forget about this guy.
Who cares about this guy?
Go.
Don't let her get away before talking and making a new friend.
Hey, come on.
No, don't let her go.
Uh, just go here then.
What are you doing?
Here's an opportunity.
Just get over here.
Call.
Call over.
Why is this taking so long?
You're running by her.
All right.
You guys have to understand.
Look at the lower left.
I didn't do shit.
Finally.
My God.
Did she just hold back a pew?
At least I met her.
I met her.
Oh, she's gonna, is she gonna get birth?
Where are you going?
Oh, my TV is too big.
I gotta go check on it.
Am I gonna go chat with her?
All right.
I gotta get out of here.
Save.
Manage worlds.
She's gonna go watch the birth on his computer.
I gotta get back there.
I gotta get back and chat.
Yeah, he's going to watch the stream.
Here we go.
Give birth in.
Okay.
There's a moment everybody was waiting for.
The sim is nearly full term.
More than ready to have this kid and be done with it already.
Give birth very, very soon.
Invite the gnome over.
That's a good idea.
The gnome is watching the stream.
It's okay.
They can pause it.
They can see it in real life.
I'm Gnata Gnoblin.
I'll be right.
I forgot that's what the name of the character was.
Oh, boy.
Do I need a doctor?
There he is.
What's the meal you're gonna have?
Uh-oh.
The grilled cheese.
Car her and end the stream.
Uh, no.
Not before we see this baby.
Let's talk about the current drug market.
How is it?
All right.
Talk about the...
Discuss the current drug market.
Yeah, he like...
I really love trash.
Looking in trash.
Grabbing trash.
Just me and this lady have a big thing this afternoon.
Why would you buy a fake ID?
If you were like 30?
Invite the gnome to move in
after we buy like a hundred different drugs.
Let's talk about, uh...
You can have one of these.
A fake ID for the baby.
Are these high-quality drugs?
The pregnant lady is not gonna have any of these drugs.
I'm gonadogonoblin is unemployed.
Let's joke about the...
Where is she?
Oh, pardon me, Sam.
Joke about the cops.
Okay, what about, uh...
What else you got?
Drugs.
Drug dealing.
Inquire about selling amphetamine.
Really?
Where is she?
She's fine.
She's just drinking like an iced tea.
So, I'm going to sell drugs for the gnome.
Give me some.
Is that what's happening here?
That's not, that's not alcoholic.
Nightclub.
Don't do this to me.
Not right before the baby comes.
She's dead.
All right, let's go.
All right, so where's...
She's dead.
Wait, is she going home?
She's going home.
Why are you going home?
No, no, no.
Get over here.
Home?
No, come dance.
Lantern?
What are we gonna eat?
Let's dance.
Whoa, what was that noise?
That was loud.
What was that?
Ow.
Pauline Parrot.
R.I.P.
She's dead.
I don't understand.
Okay, uh, how do I...
Let's just remind her.
Dance battle.
Okay, that's fucking actually hurting my ears.
Seriously.
That lady just did the coke off the ground, I think.
That was not a dance battle.
Dance battle.
Oh, she loves this.
She...
What?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Wait, wait.
I didn't do it.
I didn't do that.
Uh...
What?
What am I supposed...
I just wanted them to all...
She's...
Look at...
She's evil.
She likes being at music.
It's...
It's helpful.
All right, stop.
What?
Benedict just wants to stop.
He feels like throwing up, but though...
Through one of the pinpricks of altered realities,
he sees words wrapping around his vision saying,
if you throw up while on streams, you're gonna die.
What?
All right, get out of here.
You have to get out of here right now.
Out.
The Sim cannot go home.
Why?
She wasn't trying to leave before, guys.
She definitely...
That says she can't leave.
Get out of there.
Get over here.
You just sit over there.
Whoa, whoa, whoa!
Hey!
Shut it down.
Control panel.
Turn it off.
It's time for this to stop.
Everyone go home.
Out.
Party's over.
What do you mean you can't go home?
How do we leave?
I can't, like, control...
I can't leave.
What was that noise?
Hospital.
Everything's fine.
Hospital, hospital, hospital?
All right, hospital.
Let's go.
Where's the hospital?
Yeah, it's good enough.
Did we bring the whole party?
Whoa!
Baby's coming out any second here.
Everybody's coming into the vet.
All right, just go over here.
Just sit down.
On the couch.
Sit.
Everybody go.
Everybody together.
Go.
Whose dog is this?
That's a patient.
Okay.
Is this the guy we met at the party?
No, I'm not coming out yet.
You have any beds in here?
I need...
I need this.
What?!
Huh?
They brought it back.
What was that noise?
I need to investigate.
Oh my god.
All right.
Can I please?
Is it baby?
Sim is at full term.
Go over there and just nap.
Forget about this shit.
Oh!
Use your phone.
For what?
Travel to the hospital?
There we go.
The doctor's appointment.
Here we go.
Where the hell is she?
Did she just go home?
She's just at the doctor.
I see, I see.
Okay.
Baby, come out.
Tired.
It's time.
We'll need to rest soon.
Becomes exhausted in three hours.
I gotta...
I'm trying to get you to go to sleep,
but everyone is causing problems and making it impossible.
Everybody come home.
Come on.
What's your emergency?
No.
Get out of the doctor!
What was that?
Who the hell is this?
Oh, it's another cop.
Okay.
She's almost done.
This baby's coming.
Baby!
Why am I saying goodbye?
What's wrong?
Okay, travel.
Take them all.
Where are we going?
Click on her.
That's what I just did.
All right.
Click on her.
Go home.
She's not in labor yet.
Yeah, I can't go to the hospital right now.
Click on the actual genie.
This is her.
She's going home.
Click on the lamp to have the baby.
No, that's not how it works.
You need to wait till you get the labor passive.
Yeah, so what are you guys talking about?
I have to go into labor first.
I can't do anything about this.
Are you just going to jubate me?
All right, I'll be ready.
Buy a bassinet from the store.
Like, baby.
Is it even here?
The crib doesn't work either.
Bedroom?
I have to buy a crib or the baby will not come.
Okay.
Wait, is that good enough?
That's not a crib.
There is no crib.
Where's this crib you're talking about?
I'm in the kids menu.
I'm in the kids menu right now.
Oh, you guys are just fucking with me.
All right, whatever.
Let's go.
There is no crib.
You don't have to have a crib.
Here, I'll put the school desk over here.
Just sleep in this bed.
Get that baby out.
Today, the crib comes with the baby.
I knew it.
A bunch of liars here.
I need to eat.
Penny's office.
Penny got a job?
Put a bassinet in your home
and you'll have the option to give birth
or give birth at the hospital.
We just looked.
It doesn't exist.
This thing is called the rockabye bassinet.
Oh my god.
Rockabye.
I couldn't do BA.
All right, let's go.
Let's get this over with.
It's been a long stream.
It's been a long day.
Let's get this fucking baby out.
Oh, you could cook.
Good.
Still waiting for it.
Well, I actually just typed it and looked it up.
Oh, guys, guys, guys, guys, guys.
No, god damn it.
Where is it?
What's at work?
Where's the gnome?
All right, come on.
Hurry up.
It's so late.
It's almost 3 a.m. Eastern right now.
We can't go to bed until this happens.
Just give it a minute.
What a day of work.
Penny came home and made it.
I thought that was just sort of $1.12.
I was like, what the hell did you do for work?
All right, get up.
Uh, is he going to leave that like that?
Really?
Fix that dickhead.
Oh, she's out of jail.
I don't know how she's alive.
Oh, this lady sucks.
I took I took her wig.
What the fuck?
I'm going to lose my mind.
I hate this, but I love it at the same time.
Okay, did you?
There's no more hair for you to take out.
Why do you hate this girl so much?
What did she do to you?
Where did she go?
All right, well, whatever.
I don't know why they hate each other so much.
Okay.
Enjoy your coffee.
I'm just waiting for this stupid baby to come up.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Here we go.
All right.
What do we do?
Going into labor.
We're going to bring everybody to the hospital.
Wait, invite the gnome over quick.
Call the gnome.
Call, call the gnome.
Call the gnome, gnome, gnome, gnome, gnome.
Call the gnome.
No, you don't know the gnome.
Quick.
Okay, get up everybody.
Hospital, let's go.
All right, the gnome's here.
Half baby.
This is the moment of truth.
We've been waiting for this for like three hours.
Here we go.
Did you just get you?
Wait, you didn't just drop it in here?
Uh, congratulations.
It's a boy.
I just gave birth to a baby boy.
This baby needs a name.
That's, that's fucking ridiculous.
What is that noise?
All right, it's time for the baby to grow up.
Doc, you get away from that baby.
Get away from that baby.
Get away from the baby.
Get away.
Get the fuck away from that baby.
Get out of here.
You motherfucker.
No, don't touch that baby.
Somebody help.
No, neither.
You either.
You go back over here.
Get over to the baby.
Stop doing what just happened.
Okay, get over, get over here.
Somebody pick up the baby.
Okay, thank you.
Wasn't gonna let that motherfucker get near this baby.
Why is the gnome here?
Oh yeah, I invited the gnome over.
All right, I got, I'm done.
I'm done.
I'm going to bed.
I can't fucking handle this anymore.
I'm gonna age the baby.
All right, age up.
Here we go.
Let's see who you grow.
Wait, did I just do that to her?
Who did I just do that to?
I just made her older.
Yeah, no, no, no, no.
Get off.
Get away.
Don't feed them.
Don't feed that baby.
Put it down.
Do not feed this baby.
Watch the baby.
Oh no.
No, the gnome is fine.
The gnome is gonna be just fine.
I trust the gnome.
That's weird for me to say that.
Excuse me.
Huh?
Oh, I thought she just cast a magic spell.
Toddler's day spent playing with toys,
exploring the world,
and learning to communicate with words instead of tears.
Oh wait, this is the perfect time to start skill building.
Okay.
Inquisitive.
All right, here we go.
How I need to I want to age.
Age up.
Did age up work?
Okay, Peter aged up.
Aspirations.
All right, creativity.
That sounds good to me.
And cheerful.
That sounds pretty good.
Okay.
Creativity.
A botanist.
Sure.
And a romantic.
Come on.
Actually, dude, what a fucking insane childhood you have.
You're just crying.
You have the mental, you have the brain of a one-day-old.
How did you, you already got your phone?
All right.
Okay, I lost my mind.
I gotta get out of here.
Hey, we watched him grow up.
I'm never doing this again.
Someone just said you're a mean person.
That didn't take eight hours.
I was like, I'll bring him back.
I'll bring him back.
Just wait.
Everybody settle down.
Plead for Peter.
And it has been accepted.
What's the cheat for it?
What?
How do I cheat?
How do I bring him back?
What's the cheat for it?
There is no cheat for it.
That was so uncalled for.
Oh, at least he got to get to like 32.
You know, he went from an infant to like 40.
32 seconds.
Finish the fight.
There is no fight.
No, this is a gnome stream, no.
I got a fucking headache.
What a joke.
Yeah, I need a cup of coffee after that one.
He lived until 32 in a bathroom.
Let me just like seriously like applaud the Sims 4 modding community.
What a hell of a job.
Like how much outrageous shit.
I can't even believe this stuff is even in the game.
Did it once before, did it again.
And there's still somehow interesting things to look at.
My eyes are itchy.
All right, I think that's going to be it.
Here's who's left standing.
The genie.
I don't even know who this is.
Detective, whatever.
I don't know who this is.
I didn't make this lady, did I?
Oh, it's a caterer.
I evicted this lady eight, nine hours ago and then I brought them back as a caterer
and then made them part of the family.
No one, here's an interesting piece of information here.
Nobody here is from any original family.
The gnome was not supposed to be part of any family.
Everybody's gone.
The gnome was just the drug dealer.
Now, thank you for joining me in the nine hour car joke
with some other random stuff sprinkled in.
Who the hell is this?
What the fuck are you doing?
Is that Peter?
No, it's not.
That's not Peter.
That's some random person that died here like six days ago.
There's another person here.
Who's this?
Who is this person?
Is he going to drink out of a dirty cup?
Where are you going?
Scared by ghost.
Oh, I thought he was scared by the ghost.
Oh, I get it.
They come and they haunt you.
I'm so confused right now.
You've not wake up from that.
It just turned him green.
Take the soul.
Age down the ghost.
What do you mean age down?
Age down until what?
You're about to use the computer?
What the fuck are you two doing here?
I have no clue.
He's picking up the demon evil book.
Uh, that's okay.
That's not good.
That's all he wanted to see.
He's getting a good he's getting a spell.
Yeah, how's this for a spell?
Did it work?
I don't think I don't think you can do it.
At least you're cleaning up after yourself.
That's nice of you.
I don't think it can work.
Nah, you can't do it to uh to ghost.
I don't think all right somebody needs to get up.
Get up and uh let me try to one last thing.
Where's the book?
Where do you put it away?
Book of Chaos.
Put it down in the world over here.
Let's get these evil spirits out of here.
All right, where'd you put it?
I'm not in the trash.
All right, uh, read.
Put it.
Ask to be partners in crime.
Burn Sim.
Drown Sim in pee.
Where are they?
Can I make the ghost streak?
Who is this?
Um, naked ghost is more clothes.
Okay, bye.
We also have embarrass a sim to death.
I wanted to drown.
He's still alive.
He's not dead yet.
He's not dead and I got it.
I'm good.
He's still alive.
I caught it right at the end.
I didn't save the game either.
I saved it before that like 30, 40 minutes ago.
Show us proof that he's still alive.
Sure.
Oh, that was as chaotic as I thought it was going to be.
That was a perfect opportunity to gnome chat.
My brain can't think that far.
It's been eight plus hours of this.
Just constant just total absolute bullshit.
Oh my god.
Thank you all so much.
That was the part two of The Sims 4.
Hell.
I thought that was hilarious.
Maybe too many car jokes, but you know what happens.
Can't wait for part three.
Uh, we'll have to see about that.
Sorry we went really late.
I know a lot of people couldn't stick around because it is very, very, very late.
So I know a lot of you had to leave, but I will see you guys again.
Uh, I don't know necessarily.
I might be streaming.
I'm not streaming tomorrow or today technically for a lot of you guys.
Because I have a doctor's appointment on Friday.
So today, uh, Saturday I'm trying to think what's going on.
I think I have something I have to do on Saturday.
I know I'm not streaming tomorrow.
We'll see.
I'll let you know.
I'll make a tweet or, uh, I'll be in the discord.
The next stream I'm going to maybe try to set up the next stream to be the pogo stick
gamer challenge with Joel.
So we'll see if I can get that at some point this weekend.
Yeah, check his schedule.
Don't accidentally go to the vet instead of the doctor.
I will try, but that is a long, long stream of The Sims 4.
That didn't feel like very long to me at all.
The first three hours of that though, or two hours or so, was making people.
But I'll get in touch with Joel.
And let's go to the bits.
We've got about, uh, not very many, I don't think.
I don't think there's a whole lot of bits to go through.
Wait, as in Vinesauce Joel?
Yeah, we're going to be doing a little co-op stream over the next few days.
I'll let you know.
But going all the way back to making Mr. Cassadan for the 250.
Can we listen to this next time you do Picross?
Uh, what is it?
Let's see.
This is called becoming a gorilla fast.
Pre-experience subliminal frequency hypnosis.
I ain't going to listen to that.
That's like, that's freaking me out.
Just the name.
It's like a brown noise.
But thank you.
Uh, thank you to Robot Joan for the $2.40, uh, 54 cents.
Hey, Jeremy, just want to let you know, I want to know how your day is.
You don't need to ask me as I am a robot boy.
Also, Garfield, that challenge is happening since my cartoon is better.
Also, I have a giant bulb head.
Getting a cartoon throw down here.
Somehow.
Thank you, Robot Joan for the $2.50.
Appreciate it.
Uh, thank you, Zach, for the $4.
Did it say show love?
Thank you.
Trust no one.
Thank you, trust no one for the $2.50.
Hello, Jeremy.
You are back from the virtual world.
Your VR experience was something.
And how nice to see Star and you playing games together again.
But to get Star back, you had to make him be in robe, wear a mask,
speak into a voice morpher, watch stream from phone, crawl into window,
crawl through it during 30 minutes.
Wow.
Anytime.
It's movie time.
Last time you, Mark and Will tried your best at dad jokes.
Those were not good.
No, it's just playground insults.
Did you see the money that was in that draw?
We got a, uh, Jeremy Elberton and Will Ferrell and Mark Wahlberg insult each other.
Let's get it on the screen.
Let's take a look.
Previously.
Lazy boy.
Dad, this is the, uh, I watched the one before this.
This is another one.
We're with Germer and Mark Wahlberg about to play the playground insults game.
It's good to see you again.
You look like a made in a paper.
You could call me a fucking dumb dickhead McGee and I wouldn't even care.
I mean, I would.
It might, it might hurt my feelings a little bit, but don't do that.
It would be mean.
You're not a nice person.
Easy now.
Easy.
This guy sucks.
Like this guy sucks.
Like what a fucking loser.
Your hair looks like a brilipad that I want to scrub my sack with.
Why the fuck?
I thought he was going to jump on me.
Your hair is like baby hair.
You're a wonderfully looking human being.
What are you doing?
He's being sarcastic.
Oh, fucking swell boy.
Your feet smell like weed.
What?
When did I ever say that?
That's very kind of you, dude.
You know, just fuck it.
You are fucking tiny.
That doesn't sound very original.
Were you popular in high school?
No.
Remember I told you you could make me say anything you want.
I will.
Get ready.
You smell like baby barf.
You'll see.
You look 90.
Your mama raised you well.
You look like a James Bond villain.
You wish you could scrub your sack with my brillo head if you had a sack.
You sackless bitch.
If you think that aliens don't exist.
Oh boy, I've got some news for you.
In your movies, I can see you and your coverage
mouthing the line of the other actor silently to yourself.
Don't say such a thing.
It makes me feel bad.
I'm an actor.
You know what I mean?
I'm a fucking actor.
You're a terrible actor.
Like, oh great, okay.
Fuck, you know that, you know that like
fucked up looking freak show character, the Joker?
You look like the Joker without makeup on.
You got a great ass for a guy from Boston.
Next time.
Let's see.
What is it?
Hollywood's nobody's shutting down reporters.
Coming up next.
Good luck.
This is never going to end, is it?
Shutting down reporters.
Yeah, I told you guys this before though.
I've said 85% of every word in the human dictionary.
You talk about hundreds and hundreds and hundreds
and maybe even potentially thousands of hours on stream
and eight, nine, a hundred videos.
I've said almost every word.
Like at least 82% of every word.
Humble brag.
Shut up.
But thank you Trust No One for that video.
It was great.
Thank you.
Hey Divus, thanks for the 250, Divus.
Beware, I live thanks to the 250.
Hey Jerry, I was just speeding around in my neighborhood
outside of Vegas but now I gotta rush home to catch your stream.
Vroom.
Oh, I didn't give a link.
What am I, stupid?
Here.
Yeah, I am pretty dumb, aren't I?
Yeah, VR Josh got it.
That's the link right there.
Thank you, VR Josh.
Yeah, I'll do it again.
Yeah, watch this.
Now you got a double link.
Uh, but thank you, beware, I live.
Thanks for driving around.
Mostly lost, thanks for the 250.
I've said this before but if your stream is nothing but character creation streams,
I'd still enjoy it.
I'm already in tears, thank you for this.
I think that's half the fun.
For me, half the fun is not even getting in the game and having them do crazy shit.
It's making them in the first place.
That's why I spend more than two or three hours just dicking around,
having fun, making like two or three different families.
This is just one of those streams where it just happens in front of your face,
you know what I mean?
Sometimes, oh look, I wonder what, I wonder maybe I could come up with something funny.
No, this should, whatever, I'm in the seat here watching it with you guys.
Just whatever they decide to do and how whatever it happens.
But thank you, mostly lost, it means a lot.
And again, mostly lost another 250.
I love how you made Barry both self-assured and gloomy.
Sometimes he just picked randomly, you know?
There were five story arcs where the best story arc was absolutely the genie.
I don't know, the cat running away was pretty ridiculous.
I think the entire arc of the genie was the best though.
From start to finish, that was the longest one.
That took about like almost four hours of time.
Going on a date with a banana, the genie being in the game to begin with.
The two gangs, I forgot about that.
So much happened, it's just too much to even think about.
And there had to be a car in every one of them.
I like mod abused that car joke.
It was just, it's just so out of control.
It's the most brutal, it's so fast.
It hit the crib with the car, it was close.
It's just the abruptness of the car, yeah.
But thank you, appreciate it.
Thank you Commando Nam for the five, six, seven, eight dollars here.
More than that, 18 dollars actually.
Thank you so much.
Failing my classes can cheer me up.
Failing your classes, well, here's what I'll tell you.
Uh, try to spend a little more time focusing on schoolwork.
I know it can be a huge pain.
Unfortunately, you know, you just got to get it done.
That's just the way it is.
I had problems in school when I was in high school.
But you just got to get it done, you just got to do it.
Can't focus on school with eight hour Sims 4 streams.
You just got to do your best.
Do your best and maybe, maybe disconnect a little bit from the computer.
You know, you saw me throw away the computer in the trash.
Put some music on, relax.
Grab like a tea or something and just focus on doing some work.
That's what I used to have to do.
I work at a computer.
Well, if you, but I mean, that's true, I forgot.
Like I used to like use like paper.
Everybody needs a computer now.
Shit, this advice is bad.
Hey, throw your computer in the trash.
You know, the thing that you probably need
to do your assignment on, you just got to do your best.
Do your best and just focus whenever you can get the opportunity to.
It's really the best advice I can give.
Everybody's a little different though.
Good luck.
Mostly lost, thanks to the 250.
I'm now fully convinced the Vroomer is a stream sniper.
Me too.
Freudian weapon, thanks to the 250.
Happy Thursday.
Happy Thursday to you as well.
Well, now it's Friday.
Now it's Friday.
Commando Nam, thanks again for the 550 here.
One of my assignments is biology.
Can you help in biology?
I don't, I don't think, I didn't even take biology.
I have no idea.
I can't help you.
Only knows that biology has frogs and fish and organisms.
And I didn't really learn that much biology.
I think we didn't spend very much time on it in science class.
We spent maybe two weeks on it.
I might be completely wrong.
I haven't been in high school in like 20 years.
It's been a long time.
I don't remember.
I can't even tell you.
I have no idea.
Have a good night, class.
See you again.
Yeah, it's a late one.
Peaceful Haley, thanks for the 250.
Hey Jeremy, just want to say that these kinds of streams are my favorite.
But I'm going to miss most of it because I'm going to go see a movie.
Anyways, hope you have fun.
And I can't wait to watch the VOD and 90% of it is just character creation.
And have a good night, Jerma, and chat.
Close, close.
Thank you, Peaceful Haley.
Not quite though.
We got eight hours and 35 minutes.
The first two hours and 30 minutes.
So it was about 30, 35% or so.
Just short of 90.
But I appreciate it.
I love these streams too.
I love just watching.
You know what?
One of my favorite things in the world is watching AI be AI.
And watching people who are math problems
come up with ways to do their internal math problem.
It's just fun.
Because you never know what they could possibly do.
Sure, I'm like the orchestra.
I've got the, who's the guy that runs the concert?
What's his name?
He's the guy with the little stick in his hand.
He's got the magic wand in his hand.
The guy, he's like a magician, but he's naughty.
Like a conductor.
I might be the conductor, but all the instruments are not run by me.
It's just fun to watch them play.
But thank you though.
Thank you Super Seal for the 250.
Can you enable the vroom B-T-T-V emote?
I might have to at this rate.
It's all you guys here.
I only have five slots though.
I'm going to delete something.
What's going to get the X?
I wonder.
Hey Space Cat.
Thank you Space Cat for the five bucks.
You make the most attractive sims.
I think that they're all beautiful.
Thank you Mostly Lost for the 250.
Let it be known that Elephant Feet is now permanently in your Google search history.
Uh, so I googled something way worse.
Like an hour after that.
I think I typed in like how to make a pregnancy happen in Sims or something.
Whatever it was.
It was like how do I force a baby out in Sims 4?
I've tried trying to like because somebody said you can like just click it.
It was something like that.
Yeah, that's way fucking worse than Elephant Feet.
But thank you.
We also had uh, Mostly Lost again 250.
Eight lives is basically the cat from this video.
Oh, I hope this ain't a cat.
Something happening to a cat.
Oh, I have seen this before.
This is uh, hey Michael Rappaport.
Hey, don't fucking look at me like that.
That's a weird looking fucking cat.
I've seen this video.
That is a classic video.
But thank you Mostly Lost again for your 250 again.
Robot Jones, thanks for the free bucks again.
Hey, I'm back.
I wanted to see what your channel looked like back in 2011.
So I used the Wayback Machine installed in my brain and I found this amazing.
Jerma Channel.
Uh, it started, it started in 2011.
It was in 10 maybe.
I was on other channels too.
They were like, I'm trying to think of like other,
there was other projects that I did on other people's channels long fucking time ago.
They don't like exist anymore.
I'm talking long, long time ago.
When I think about how long I've been on the internet for,
just, oh, I like, I'm going to make videos or like go back to Newgrounds.
Talking like 2004, 2003, 2004.
That's a long goddamn time ago.
Now, how do you think I know Bloerdal?
Me and Bloerdal met on Newgrounds like 14 years ago, something like that 15 years ago.
Might even be longer than that.
Newgrounds are old.
What happened to Newgrounds?
Is it still there?
Is it still working?
Is it still owned by the folks?
Does Tom Fulps still own that website?
Yeah, well, talking about someone who's been around for a long time.
That's a very long time ago.
But thank you for the trip down memory lane, RobotJones.
Appreciate it.
Tumblr banned porn so they migrated there.
That's a very long time ago.
Well, not that, but Newgrounds in general.
Sleep tight.
Uh, what else we got here?
We have, uh, Tingy.
Thanks for the 250.
Nice twerking.
Take some money.
Forgot what happened five hours ago.
Thank you.
Mostly lost for the 250.
What's your price for twerking on stream?
Zero.
Zero, zero, zero, zero.
Free twerking.
It's like hitting me like a ton of bricks right now that I'm just exhausted.
I'm coming down right now after that.
Pass the old man's bedtime.
Something like that.
Hey, where are we?
Future gamer, thanks for the 250.
There's a new VR RPG called Shadow Legend with voice recognition.
That came out today.
On a separate note, I have 18 rooms clipped and timed.
Shadow Legend.
I'm gonna have to look this up right now.
RPG exclusive VR where you play as the grandmaster of the Knights Templar
in a story-driven medieval crusade.
Freely explore densely filled worlds.
And use your sword, bow, and magic to save the kingdom from destruction of Lord
Adaroth.
It's voice controlled?
I might have to play this.
This looks pretty good.
You can feed horses carrots.
All right, add that to the list.
Thank you, Future Gamer.
Thank you something or other for the 250.
Hey, German, it's me from the Applebee's.
Just want to say thank you again for taking the time to come over and say hi to us.
It was really cool to meet you.
As you might remember, it was my grandfather's 80th birthday.
And while your grandmother's 80th birthday and while her mind is slipping
and she doesn't know what twitch is,
she loves meeting new people and thought you were a charming fellow.
She had fun and I'm really grateful.
Just one quick question.
Why did you spit in my food and slip my grandmother your cell phone number?
Well, one, you were rude.
Two, she asked for it.
She like wanted me to give her my number.
She like asked me for the number.
What you don't tell the story that you're not telling is
you came and spit in my food first, three or four different times.
I didn't even know who you were.
You said, German, you screaming in my ear.
I'm at dinner with my girlfriend.
And then you did, you mashed up a bunch of Skittles in your mouth.
I'm like, what the fuck is this guy doing with this problem?
You swallowed and you did like the big daddy Adam Sandler movie spit.
But you dropped a huge, huge Skittle spit right onto my hamburger.
They said they were going to call the police,
which I don't know if they did or not.
You got out of there quick.
I walked over to your food and spit in yours.
I don't have any Skittles though.
Your grandmother simply said, by the way, what's your phone number?
So I can get in touch with you to repay you for the meal that my obnoxious grandson
just ruined.
So yeah, I gave my phone number to your grandmother.
The whole story, guys.
That's what happens when you don't get it.
Unbelievable.
I was there.
I saw it.
Is that what it takes?
Now, thank you something rather for the 250 and happy 80th birthday to your grandma.
I am now fully, mostly moistened thanks to the 250.
For anyone that may have doubted that German is a good man,
I'll have you know that when he saw an old man beat up his pregnant genie girlfriend,
he immediately ran him over with a car
and made sure that the genie had a place to stay.
What more proof do you need?
What the hell is going on there?
Lone MGR, thanks for the five dollars.
First time donating to a streamer.
Love your content.
Sorry, it ain't much.
German nose wipe.
Don't worry.
Don't apologize for giving me money.
Thanks for even considering.
Thank you.
I really appreciate it.
Do not say sorry.
Sorry for the cash.
Peter.
Welcome back, Peter.
P337R, thanks for the 20 bucks, Peter.
Congrats on the baby.
Thank you.
Thank you for the $20 bill.
2,000 bits.
Thank you, Peter.
Good to see you.
The thrill.
Thanks for the five dollars.
German, I'm sorry I called you a dick bag last night.
It was a big boy word I learned at work recently.
I was tired and half asleep when I slung that at you.
In my defense, things were getting heated in regards to the concepts
and definitions of cheating.
Thanks for tonight's fun.
PS, whatever happened to exoskeleton bug millennium boy?
It's funny you mentioned exoskeleton bug millennium boy
because I will be seeing him very soon.
Still a friend?
Still kicking around?
On the next stream, no.
A lot of the people and a lot of the friends that I have
from, you know, before even I turned on a YouTube video.
No, there's still none.
I still talk to them.
I still hang out with them.
We still converse.
When is Minecraft VR on the next VR stream?
Which will be probably next week.
I will get that set up.
We'll do another like three or four games
and then during that VR session I want to also do mine show.
So we'll get that started too.
Just want to take a break from VR.
Can't just go pedal on the ground.
You just did it today and it's awesome.
I'm looking forward to it.
I played for at least an hour.
But thank you, the thrill.
Don't worry.
I know you guys are just fucking around.
I say a lot of dumb shit too.
And it's just me messing around as well.
Thank you Pigeon for the 250.
You know, if you go into the settings,
you can edit the limit of NPC Sims.
You get to parties with like a hundred people.
I was just wanting you to know that it was me
who suggested Sims for the first time.
And I was the one who caused this stream.
I did.
Every suggestion is great.
I'm grateful for a lot of the suggestions over the years.
Recommendations.
They've turned out to be amazing experiences.
But thank you for the 250.
Appreciate it.
Be where I live.
Thanks for the 250.
I hate when none of the original cast
is left when a series ends.
They always jump the shark with a baby
and then everyone leaves.
Can't wait for the spinoff.
I'm G'naught, a detective G'no.
There are a lot of subs today too.
Let's go ahead and start running them
so you can see all the subs.
Thank you everybody.
Much love to you all.
But thank you Be Where I Live.
And DubskiDude.
Thanks for the 250.
DubskiDude.
Don't know if this has been asked before,
but what are your chances?
What are the chances of an all-star
Jerma Rumble with all the old favorites?
Every Rumble adds new wrestlers
and I feel like we're drifting further
from what made the original Rumbles great.
If you considered it.
And the Jerma Trading Cards too.
Yeah, we actually talked about the Trading Card thing
like a week or two ago.
Just about how it was going to cost a ton of money.
And it needs to be something that I can reliably do
and be comfortable doing.
As to the Jerma Rumble stuff.
Yeah, it's just a different beast on Twitch
because how it used to be
is I would, especially 2k14.
A lot of things I think people don't realize
is in 2k14, I could make scenarios happen.
I could go in and edit.
And like for instance, when Demon Lord Zaraxos
in Jerma Rumble 3 goes into the ring,
that doesn't happen in the game.
I had to string all that together with editing
and different camera angles and stuff.
So it's not like, oh, why don't you just...
They're very different.
Really, yeah.
The new games that have come out since 2k14
got rid of a lot of the creative stuff.
You're not able to have somebody backstage
put in actors and have the characters
punch each other and throw each other through tables.
You can't do them anymore.
Now, one would say, why don't you just go back
and do 2k14?
We talked about that.
Why?
And here's another reason why.
I did everything I could do in 2k14.
Every little cut scene, every little story arc,
little cut scene edit that I could do, I did it
because there's only a finite amount of them.
One of the reasons why I even did
the Jerma Rumble live action is because
there was nothing else for me
to actually physically do in 2k14.
I couldn't do anything else.
So I was like, fuck it, I'll do it on my own.
I'll just hire people and make it.
But that's why they probably feel a little different now
because the tools that are in the new WWE games
are terrible.
They're just absolutely awful.
They're awful.
The only saving grace that these new WWE games have
are the import image feature.
And it's just a giant bandaid for not being able
to create characters that you want to create.
Now, I could go back to 2k14 just for the sake
of making better characters.
But I brought this up too.
Going back, that was a end of life PS3 game
that they didn't bring or didn't port anywhere.
They pushed the PS3 to the absolute limit.
And if you have more than a few characters,
making characters is hell.
There's so much slowdown, it lags.
The new games at least don't have that.
Once you get 5, 10, 12 layers on a character,
it's pain.
Even turning their bodies and looking at a different angle
drops the game down to like four frames a second.
The new ones now just crash in the middle of the match.
Yes, that's true.
But they've stripped a lot.
Is it still possible to remake old characters
in the new game and do it that way?
I probably could.
It wouldn't be that big of a deal,
especially if it was like an all-star thing.
I'm hoping that, and I've been saying this for
five straight years now, after 2k15,
man, okay, next year maybe they'll lighten up a little bit
and make the created characters a little less serious.
Oh, we're gonna get new creation sweet stuff.
Cool. Oh, what is it?
No, no, it's not anything interesting.
What about next year?
Nope. What about three years ago?
Going forward four years now?
Nope.
They want that game to be taken as a serious wrestling simulation
and not as a fun experience.
They want that to be a fighting game.
Strangely enough.
So that leaves me in a weird position to making characters and
God, I wish this was 2k14.
So instead of complaining about it all the time,
which I still do.
How many times do you hear me complain about the new games?
It's just not worth going back and dealing with old technology.
Very long-winded response, but
doing like an all-star thing would be pretty fun.
What about other wrestling games?
There really aren't any.
The 2k wrestling games are the only ones that
have really any.
I can't think of any other wrestling games that exist.
Unless you're talking about some of the 2d ones that are essentially flash games.
Yeah, that's the McDickey ones.
That's what I'm talking about.
Not McDickey.
And what's his name?
MDickey.
This whole caliber is kind of good.
You'd probably make some characters in that too.
Yeah, that's true.
But that's another, I guess, response for that.
Thank you to all the subs.
We had Jess, you got it.
Came in right at the end with 250.
This is an AI that creates faces.
Reload it to get a new face every time.
Have a good night.
I've actually seen this.
This person does not exist.
Yeah, it's ridiculous.
Is it weird that I don't believe this?
They could just say that these are AI faces
and they just upload the whole employee notebook.
How many people work at Google?
Like 4,000?
5,000?
But that's going to be it, guys.
Thank you everybody for watching.
Hope you had a good time.
I'll see you guys.
Uh, I definitely, I'm not going to be more than a day or two.
But doctor's appointment tomorrow.
I got some stuff to take care of and continue.
Stream, oh, stream legends.
Right, right, right.
I'll give you, I got to give you guys your gear.
Got gear to give you guys.
I've got to remember to do that.
See you guys soon.
I'll let you know on Twitter and on Discord and stuff what's going on.
Much love to you.
See you soon.
How do I get the gift?
Oh, here it is.
Here it comes.
Three, two, one.
Loot.
Hooray.
Take care.
See you soon.