My mic wasn't plugged in. I hope it sounds okay, because it was not plugged in. And I just jammed
it in and pressed start now. Why was this not plugged in? I was sitting there going,
why can't I not hear anything? Stream sucks. Hi guys. How you doing? Welcome back. Somebody said,
we can only be so patient, Andy. Are you talking about me? We can wait, are you talking about you?
You're the, we can only be so patient, Andy. Or are you calling me Andy? Like we can only be so
patient, Andy. I'm trying. What does that one mean? Hey, what's up green? Oh, I just dropped that.
I'm fine. Promise us you won't be late next time. I'm late every single time. But here's the thing.
Look, it's time for defense. It's time for defense. When my stream turns on, I'm here.
It's like, boom. Data goes in. 30 seconds later. What's up? I don't got a 20 minute countdown.
I don't have a 10 to 15 minute countdown on screen. I don't have a 30 minute countdown.
I'm here and I'm ready when I press that button. See? That's true. What's your point?
You can't true me and then say, you can't true me and then say, what's the point? I like this method.
I'm here and I'm ready. True but not based. Is that possible? How does that work? You could be true
but not based. Is that how that works? Who makes these rules, by the way? Anyways, today we're
going to play Inscription. It's the, that scary card game that I've heard all about. Seems pretty
crazy. I don't know anything about it besides it exists. And I know that I'm kind of late to the
party here, but that's good for you because you get to see all the funny moments when I get scared
by the cards that pop out and jump scare me or something because you've played this game.
And we're starting late today. Well, I told you we're going to stream maybe on Monday or Tuesday.
So here we are on Monday. I had stuff to do earlier this afternoon, but I'm here now.
Also going to be live tomorrow too and make that clear. So they'll be streamed tomorrow.
I want to do, there's a few things that are going to happen here over the next couple of days.
I want to make it very clear what the kind of plan is. I'll reiterate it a little bit later, but
Ludwig and I want to do that Elden Ring PvP kind of community champions night. So I am going to do
in the next day or so, we're going to do Elden Ring PvP again. And I've got to find my champions
because I'm not fighting Ludwig. We're picking champions. So I got to make sure I get the right
ones. Yeah, I already know a few. I already know a few that I need to find and get, you know,
find them. But maybe not. Maybe tomorrow or Wednesday. I'm not sure yet. I'll figure it out.
But I am holding what is essentially tryouts. We're going to see if we can make it work.
Do an IRL Elden Ring stream or just like dodge roll stuff. You know, actually kind of funny.
But don't like one guy me and make me like, go get like sponsors and make me spend
fucking hundreds of thousands of dollars to set up like I'm doing like I'm going to I'm
like in a Dark Souls dungeon, like going and picking up items and have to dodge roll shit.
Don't I don't you're going to make me you're going to make me go do that.
Are you going to make me do that? Like I then there's a boss at the end that I have to fight
and I die like fucking 50 times. That's so stupid. No one's forcing you. It would be a LARP.
I'd have to get I'd have to go and get the shortcut and stuff. Would that even
last more than like an hour? Have like two or three bosses and have like a main boss at the end.
I would want to include chat somehow, though, and just train and do do animations as a person
in real life. Have idle animations, LARP stream, IRL fall joke. Yeah, I walk off a cliff and fucking
die. A little fake, but you know, just sit there and chug and estus and then get killed in one hit.
OK, all right. Well, here's the thing. I'm going to write this down because this is this is really
stupid and I kind of I kind of want to like explore this a little bit and be in full armor.
This would be oh, this is going to be fucking a little hard, though, but our chat will spawn
enemies. Oh, good. You haven't started yet. I was heating up my. Yeah, this is going to be expensive.
Whatever I the cost of a show does not bother me. It's being able to actually pay for it.
I'll actually be able to dodge IRL and I'm going to tell these actors are going to be like fucking
try to hit me with that axe. I'm not kidding. I don't want this to be like, oh, we're actors.
Oh, I'm like swinging really slowly. No, try to fucking hit me with that axe and I'm going
to dodge it. You know what I mean? Like I got to go all in. Not a real axe. No, not
not a real axe, guys. I'm saying I will. Maybe I like foam or something, whatever it is.
But I want that person. I want it to be. I don't want to be like, oh, I'm swinging and you're going
to put your hand up and block it. And I know you are. So we're both going to go two miles per hour.
And pretend to hit each other. No, I want this to look fucking crazy. I want it to look good.
I want that actor to fucking try to hit me as hard as he can. I'm going to take that actor aside
and be like, hey, what's up, man? Um, this little this foam thing, like keep practice. Just hit me
like in the back with it like five times. It's going to be like, that doesn't hurt. That doesn't
hurt that much. All right. I want you to hit me in the head. And I mean, like, I'm going to be
dodging it. It's going to be real. I'm method acting. This shit's going to be made out of like
fucking pillows and foam, guys. We're going to make sure that doesn't hurt. We're going to make
sure it's like it's like getting hit by air. Jack gets to choose the stats you level up. Well,
they can't. I don't think sorcery could exist. Don't worry. He's an expert at hand to hand combat.
I'm not. What about lightning bolts? I mean, I could get, I guess we could make it interesting.
Fireworks. Casting one glint stone bolt at somebody and I have to light up like a Roman
candle or something. No, that's not. I'm not shooting. That's dangerous. I don't want to do
that. I'm not doing anything that could actually hurt anybody. We'll figure it out. Use a flashlight.
That would actually be kind of funny. Well, like a little pretend like,
yeah, I actually kind of like this idea. And here's the problem, though. This is the bad part.
This was a great idea six months ago. So a week or two after Elden Ring came out, I could do this
stream. This is now going to be about four to six months of planning. And Elden Ring is going to
kind of be in the rear view for a lot of people, I think, in a year. It doesn't have to be like a
from software kind of parody. It's just an action adventure dungeon that is very heavily inspired
by Dark Souls. All right, I'm writing it down. I actually am. I'm actually writing it down
because this could be like fun. Bringing a bunch of set designers and make a Dark Souls dungeon.
This is actually, yeah, I think I could make this work. All right. See you in like a year
when the guy in chat goes, hey, I said IRL Elden Ring. And and he spent $400,000 on a stream.
You thank that guy. All right. So anyways, we're going to get into inscription. IRL
millennia. It actually would be so funny if I kept dying to a boss and I was just
yelling into the camera, like talking shit to the camera. Like this is fucking bullshit.
This boss sucks. That mechanic is absolutely broken. I complained for like 10 minutes into
the camera. And then like while I'm complaining, I'm backing up and I just drop like off the cliff
and it says like you died. Oh, this could be good. Oh, this could be very good. I'm actually really
into this. All right, I'm not gonna tell you anything else. Can you help me with my chemistry
homework? No, I don't really know anything about chemistry. Okay, inscription. Here it is.
Let's do it. Hi. So how does this game work? It's a scary game. This is a scary game. I get
the Pac-Man shirt on it. All right. This is a scary game. Lights off. It's it's not dark yet.
The lights aren't even like on. This is not a lights off game. Don't do that. It's a PC.
This is an old PC. I'm sorry. That was fucking horrible. Inscription. Turn the lights up. I'm
not I can't turn the lights off. I'm not stealing this from like XQC's community. Okay. Like, oh,
lights off. Oh, I love that guy. Yeah. Oh, yep. Oh, cool. See, I do too. This makes me look weird.
Cat. This is not a lights off game. Is that my? Okay, whatever. Okay. New game options.
Do I turn anything up or down? What should I do here? Flicker FX. Nope. Screen shake. No,
thank you. Tech speed. That's probably fine. Noise effect. Turn that off. Full screen, please. And
let's get it on ultra brightness. Turn the brightness up a little bit so it's not so dark.
What do you mean why? I don't like when any of that shit is in my games. No, I don't like it. I
don't like when anything's like put screen shake on maximum. All right. Music volume. I always turn
it down. That should be fine. Like that. Turn the noise back on. All right. I'm going to turn the
noise back on. If I don't like it, it's going off immediately. Okay, let's go. Like I can't start a
new game. Why? Continue. I haven't played this. I haven't played this game. A little challenger.
It has been ages.
Voice acting.
Does it matter where?
So I have to... Okay.
Okay, this is one attack, three health.
Unopposed.
Yeah, okay. Just like Hearthstone.
Like this. My turn. Okay, your stoat stands in the way of my coyote. Two. All right, so I live.
My coyote took two damage to your stoat. That means your stoat's health is two less. How come
that didn't kill it? These aren't Hearthstone rules.
Your turn. You may draw from your deck or you may draw a squirrel. Which doesn't matter.
Again, I'm going to draw a squirrel. How dull. Well, no, because if I played the squirrel,
then the wolf can come up and sacrifice two people. Okay, so let's put a squirrel out there.
And then I'm going to play the wolf right here. Drop the wolf down. Suffering. Suffering was real,
but you will see it again. Okay, got the wolf out. That's it, right? Because you are learning,
I will pass. Again, the choice. A random card from your deck or the certainty of a squirrel.
Let me just take a random card. A river snapper. Can I see what it does? I can't do anything.
Oh, shit. Three weights on the scale. Pass. Squirrel. Put squirrel out. Back it up. Pass.
I win. I won this match. They won't all be so easy. Let me recall your story. Oh, yes.
Pale blood, you say. You were lost deep in the forest. A single path revealed itself.
Two denizens of the forest approached you tentatively. Okay. A cat. The undying cat
sacrificing the poor beast does not kill it. A caustic adder. Damage from its poison bite
is always lethal. Only one may grace your paltry deck. Snake or cat. I feel like the adder. Everyone's
saying cat. Is it cat? I thought I would assume it would be snake. Oh, there's only one sacrifice
needed. Turn the music up. This is gonna go, dude. I'll take the cat. Sure. Another creature
joins your caravan. Some of the creatures of the forest seemed willing to follow you. You came
across an abandoned sack. You found a squirrel in a bottle. Break it in case of an emergency.
And I have a second. Another useful implement. I'll allow you to tip the scales with it. Items?
Three is as much as you can carry. He's gonna take 10 hours on act one alone. Don't worry.
You were ambushed while crossing some rough terrain. All right, so let's go.
You sacrificed me while I was sleeping. It was the right play. I get it. Maybe you'll help me.
Play along for now. You may now see my moves ahead of time. Um, wolf cub. What does that mean? A card
bearing this sigil will grow into a more powerful form after one turn on the board. How are we gonna
get rid of that? What's this? Boulder? It's just in the way. Stump. All right, these things are
just blocking. So what do we got? I got cat. Uh, I have to put a squirrel up. Squirrel. Uh, squirrel's
gonna go here. And then that's all I can do, right? Let's go. And turn. Like, wait, do I,
is there any, is there mana? Mind the ambitious wolf cub that ages swiftly. Is there mana in this
game? Give me another squirrel. All right, we'll go and squirrel here. And then I'm doing how,
what is the river snapper? One and six. Okay. I should do the river snapper. Probably. If I
do river snapper, I can put the river snapper here and then it'll last a long time. Can I move
the boulder? Oh wait, I'll do cat here instead. Right? Yeah. I think so. I don't know. Because
this comes back. If this does not perish. Okay. Now, now, now check this out. What? Uh, river
snapper here or stoat here? Which is better? Probably river snapper. Why not? Listen to your
mods. What's happening? My mic is rumbling. Wait, what? Hold on. Okay. I think I got it. We good?
I think we're good. How's this? Are we back? Are we good? Normal? Back? We good? We good? Yeah.
All right. I don't know why that happened. Sorry about that. All right. So now I'm going,
I'm just going to go river snapper because it's cool. There's a turtle and I'm going to put it
right here. Wait, should I sacrifice the cat? I have to do both anyways. I'm going to go over here
and go. And I'm going to sacrifice this fucking thing and I'm putting this over here.
Here we go. All right. He's got a bat. The airborne bat flies over creatures to attack directly.
My bat flew right over your stove. That's stupid. All right. I want a random card. All right. What's
on the board right now? This will kill this. This is just kind of to be able to feed me,
but this will kill that. This will, this is going to get through this, but it's all right.
There are three kills on the board right now. I think I, can I even do anything? I could sacrifice
these two and put the wolf out. But why would that help? I think I'm just going to pass. Okay.
And now I'm going to pull out a squirrel. Check this shit out. Squirrel going right here. Wolf
is going to eat these two. Wolf going down right here. Bingo. Get rid of you. And that should give
me a one, two, three, four. And here we go. Another wolf. I think I just killed him right now.
You prevailed and trekked onwards past the now bloody terrain. See? Nobody thought I was going
to be on that for 10 hours. New card. The young wolf cub grows into a wolf after a single turn.
A meek sparrow, an inexpensive, if evil flying creature. What do you think chat? This seems
better, but I kind of like the way that this can just fly over everything. I'll take the wolf.
That sounds, I mean, nevermind. I was going to say something stupid that would like literally
be clipped for the rest of my life. What's this? Stumbled into some strange stones in the mist.
You were compelled to choose a worthy sacrifice. One that will be lost forever. One of the squirrels.
Oh no. I don't want to get rid of the cat. The cat's like perfect. I don't, I want the cat. The
cat is just a free mana every time. I kind of like this. I just got this, but it sucks. Pick me.
Wait, what? Wait, what's going on here? I'm confused. Wait, hold on. Back up. What happened?
I thought I was sacrificing. What's going on? I'm sacrificing this. What an honor. The ghastly
spectacle, but the soul of the wolf cub now lives in the stoat. Oh, it like consumes the card and
I get it. I get it. Okay. Go with the flow, man. Yeah, I got it. I figured out. I hold my totem,
but it describes my canine cards with the airborne sigil. He's completely insane. You see that,
right? No pathetic, really no care for his cards. Only keeps me around to watch me suffer.
He's going to lean forward and it's going to be the sus face. Okay. So let's get a squirrel.
What do you have? These things can fly. All right. Two and one.
Back on the board. Okay. I think that's all I can do, right? Oh, it has to. Oh, I get it. Okay.
I thought, okay, they have to be, it's the card directly in front. It doesn't go all the way back.
My totem has granted my card the power of flight. I just lost. I need, I need a squirrel right now
and then what is the wolf? Yeah, wolf. Oh shit. Hold on. Right? Yeah. Am I doing this right?
This thing can fly. Uh, can I move these around or no? I think I'm going to take a random card.
Oh, this is a bad idea. You're three damage away from winning. Okay. Whatever. I'll take the hit.
Doesn't matter. Okay. Now I'm going to take a, I think I just won. I won. Use the pillar? Pillars?
What do you mean? No, I, yeah, I win. That's it. How do I, do I have to, do I have to play something?
Okay. I win. Yeah. What's it about the pillars? Oh, pliers. Okay. You're going to survive maybe.
Knock on wood. That's how I do it. Raven, skunk, or sparrow. What does the skunk do again?
I, okay. Stinky, this creature opposing a card bearing this sigil loses one power.
Card bearing this sigil will strike an opponent directly even if there is a creature opposing it.
But this just, it just flies over and hits. This thing smells. I feel like this thing is amazing.
Stinky is good too. I don't want to end up, I feel like I have too many cards that are too
sacrifice. Isn't this, aren't I like late checking too much? I think I need some smaller things.
A one, two fly is busted. Go, just go full damage. Um, I think I'm going to do stinky.
I kind of, I don't know. I need some smaller cards. All right. This is a sacrifice pit or a fire.
What do I, what should I do? Um, I have not, I don't know what this is yet, so I'm going to go
this way. I haven't seen this yet. You came across a small group of survivors. Faces shrunken from
starvation. They huddled around a campfire. They looked upon your group of preachers and beckoned.
I'm warm. One of your creatures by the fire. One said warm it by the fire. That will enhance
its power said another. They're going to cook it and eat it. You notice one of the survivors wiping
drool from them. Yeah, this is horseshit. I'm not putting anybody here. How do I leave? How do I do
a spinning roundhouse kick to this guy's head and kick it like 500 yards that way. They're going to
eat it. I don't want them to do that. Hmm. They're going to eat this. Maybe the river snapper. I feel
like this is one six. That's a lot of health though. One of the wolves. I feel like this is,
this is all right, but do the stoat. I don't want to kill the stoat. Maybe the skunk. Is this,
okay. I feel like this is going to kill whatever this is in here. Is this going to kill this or
does it make it stronger? The fire warmed the poor skunk enhancing its power. One of the survivors
reached toward it. Another gnashed their teeth. Without a word, you roundhouse kick the leader
in the head. Okay, I get it. That's actually pretty good though because now that will do damage and
it takes power away. Okay, this is pretty cool. There's a way out for both of us. It's somewhere
in this foul cabin. Be silent or I will tear you to shreds. Mighty leap. A card bearing this
integer will block an opposing creature bearing the airborne. Okay, so they can't fly over this.
And here they are. Grizzly bear. That's not good. Four six. Oh shit. Um, four six. How am I supposed
to hit to handle this? I think I have to avoid it. Just go, just go for kill. Ow. Uh, what does
this do? Oh fuck. Oops. Okay. Um, what the fuck? How am I supposed to handle this? What do the
pliers do again? Not now. Draw a card first though. Um, this thing, it's going to kill everything.
Okay, now what does this do? You will place a weight on the scales. The path. Oh, I just put a
weight on it. All right, so the squirrel is going to die. That's fine. I think, right? So this squirrel
gets hit. I think I'm dead here. Uh, use the pliers now. A well-earned point of damage. I didn't think
you would really do it. What the fuck? Okay, can I kill him now? No, I just lose. I don't, I think
I just die here. Maybe not. I think I just have to put a squirrel down and just let it die. I can't
take this many hits. What am I supposed to do? Like, what am I supposed to do about this? Just
don't get hit. I mean, I'm just going to, this spot, you sure? I don't know. I can't, I can't even do
anything. What the fuck am I supposed to do about this? That was like five grizzlies. You lost.
Using this as a learning opportunity may be the only way to mitigate my disappointment. Get up.
Get up from the table. Catch me the candlestick from atop the barrel beside the door. What the
fuck? Bring it here. Ugh. Can I just leave? Honestly, is this the scenario right here? Uh,
yeah. I'm going. I'm sprinting forward and just wild swinging and like screaming and my hands coming
out like this and I don't even know what's, I'm just going to be, I'm just going to be stabbing
and swinging, biting and screaming and just stabbing. Right? Like I, that's how I'm getting out.
Sit back down. Let me explain something to you. That was one of the two mistakes you can make
here. If you make another, I must sacrifice you. Now, where were we? What? Read the clock.
Okay. I should probably go right because this will give me, you have two lives. I get it. Okay.
I'm going to go this way. Oh, huh. Ooh. What's this? What do these mean? I mean, I'm taking
the grizzly. Why the hell would I not? But what do these two mean? That's your little, uh, dollops
means you already have them. I'm taking, of course I'm taking the grizzly. What are you out of your
mind? And I'm going to, I'm going to put the grizzly up here so the grizzly does even more
damage. Really is going to be unfucking beatable. There is room for a creature around the fire.
There is the warmth will enhance its health. One of the survivors said nothing at all, but could
not stop licking their lips. It's health. Maybe it's the turtle. No way. I just have a four,
eight grizzly. That would be kind of insane, right? Or a one, five skunk. Wolf would be good.
Maybe the cat too. Three, two. Oh yeah. Like a three, three, four sounds really good. Really
strong. You're never going to be able to play the bear or what does this turn into? Oops.
I take it out more powerful. Does it just gain one, one? That'd be a two, five. So then,
so this would be all right. Yeah, that's it gets two, five. All right. That's, that's probably this
then. I think I'm going for that. Although I, that I'm that's only, then you only need to sacrifice
one thing for this. He said, pick something else. Do I have to listen to him? This is probably,
this is the safest one. I think that just make, gives it like a nice strong card. I think I'm
going for it. That's just like a solid three, four. I think that makes sense. All right. This
looks like a boss, like a real boss. Is this going to be like a tutorial boss where it kills
me and sends me to the back to the beginning or something? Don't read chat. All right. All right.
I won't read chat anymore. The trees seem to close in around you as a chill mist descended.
In the distance you could hear the clinking of metal on stone. All right. Lay out your arms then.
I'm back already. Took you for dead. It was the prospector. At the end of the owner's turn,
a card bearing the sigil will have moved in the direction inscribed in the sigil. So it goes like
this way, like that. Okay. So I want to put squirrel and then cat girl and get that cat down
and then put the skunk down. Oops. All right. Is it all right? I think I did this wrong.
Uh, I did this wrong. This is bad. Okay. I'm going to act on this might be stupid, but I'm going to
do this. And then we don't do this yet. Did I do it? So it's only a three, two. What? All right.
I'm done. Okay. Who cares? It comes right back. Where is it? Doesn't it come back? It doesn't come
back. Why? Um, this up so bad. Didn't I? All right. I can save it. I think what's over here.
I can save it. I can save it. I can save it. I fucked up. I fucked up. It's okay. I fucked up.
I fucked up. I fucked up. There we go. All right. Okay. I fucked up. Now I do squirrel and
sacrifice him. This will go forward. Okay. I can take a few hits. I think I'm okay.
This is salvageable. I fucked up. Did I put squirrel over here on the left? Probably.
I can take a couple of hits. I'm going to put the squirrel on the left.
I'm looking at chat. I do. I'm a, I'm a, I'm a streamer. My eyes are glued over here. I like,
I, I'm a live streamer. I go, I go. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Blah, blah, blah, blah.
Like, that's what we do. All right. I'm not looking over here anymore.
I'm almost at the fucking end of the game. I win. I win right now. I won. I won. Game over. I win.
Bring it. I hope you didn't think it'd be that easy. Gold. I've struck gold. Oh, this is bad.
What does this do? Old nugget. Why doesn't have a description? Um, I want to read what this does.
You're dead. Well, I can't do what I can't. I can't. I just have to kill that. I,
I have to block damage somehow. What the fuck? What's horseshit? What? What happened? How did
I lose so badly? He's doing the prospector again. Easy boss. The mule's key. What's that? Um,
I just lost. What happens now? More gold for me. You aren't dead yet. This isn't purgatory.
Though you may think of it that way. Before you expire, I must ask you a favor.
I would like a memento. Your very own death card. It's quite plain at the moment, isn't it?
We will work together to amend that. I want this to be the perfect memento of you.
Here are some cards from your mediocre deck. We can put them to good use. Please choose a card
to draw the cost from. They both cost two. Doesn't matter. Cost of two blood from the
river is separate. They're both, they're both two. Add another. This time I will use its power and
health. The numbers. Or six, right? I mean, like that's a bear. Is this a bad thing? Or six. Or
power and six health from the grizzly. Now choose a card from which we will extract the sigils.
Oh, and it can live forever. Is this what I get? Or does it stink? This can live forever?
Or the, or the stink. I think the stink might be great. You can sacrifice it forever.
It's definitely the cat, without a doubt. So now what? I never did ask you your name.
Oh, this is my card? There is now but one final matter. The portrait. Here we go again. Another
challenger. Perhaps it is time. Perhaps you can understand bones. The resourceful opossum costs
two bones. You gain a bone when one of your creatures perishes for any reason. Yo, I think
I just fucking won the game. This is cool. This is cool. This is cool. All right, so there's a
rattler there. It's one health. So we're gonna go like this and go. We're gonna go and go here.
Drop that down. From the death of your creature you've gained a bone. You will not lose this
until it is spent or the battle ends. Okay, let's go. Oops. Oh, I fucked up. Sorry. Oh shit. All
right. I forgot that they had to move down. Okay. Oops. All right. So wait, I can do the possum now,
right? Oh, I can do the possum. One, one. Go ahead and get a squirrel down just for shits.
There we go. Okay. Pull it back. Oh, he's gonna die anyways. Oops. It's all right. Remember, take
your pants off. Oh, forgot your figurine. Get up and fetch it for me. It's beside the safe.
All right. Hold on a minute here. Bullfrog. What does this mean? Can I like open the safe?
Times it? Six, three, 12? What time is it? Oh, you just got your safe opened, dumbass. 12,
three, six. I was on a 12. Never mind. Let us continue. Oh, coyote. This is a game. This
game is fun. This is a good game. This game is fun. Rattler, the unkillable cockroach returns to your
hand after dying. Oh, the unkillable. I'm taking the cockroach. You know, you're free to get up
again. Keep your blood flowing. I have no tyrant. You may stand whenever the map is unrolled. It
allows me time to plan your next encounter. Do keep your hands off my possessions. All right.
All right. What do you got here? What's going on here? How do I open? Okay. I got to open the
safe. I need a key. All right. What else do I got? I got to open the safe. This means something.
This means something. This is something to do with the time or the time of day it is. What time is
the clock? It is 12, three, six. Okay. I can move these. Let's go ahead and think about this for a
second here. I need three numbers, obviously. That hand doesn't never changes by the way.
This never changes off of midnight. Okay. So this never changes. So what we're going to do is we're
going to put the whole thing. We're going to put the whole thing at midnight and then it'll go.
Oh, nevermind. All right. So I need, I need three numbers, obviously. I don't know where I'm going
to get them. I'd probably get them over the course of the game. All right. Well, let's sit down.
Whatever. I'll figure it out. What's this? Mighty leap. Oh, there's 207. Okay. Thank you. 273. You
got it. That's a 273 right there. Excuse me. Open. Clock. 273. Open. Wait, there's another
thing. There's this. 273. I got it. Stink bug. Oh, hello. I wasn't sure if I would ever escape
that iron crypt. Is, is the stoat around? The stunted wolf? This madness must end. Put that away.
We're always got the key. This is where I turn around and I go, look at what I got.
Hmm. Maybe I should put it in here. Wow. Okay. What the fuck is this? Two, zero, five, um, one,
three, two, one. Okay. Zero to five, zero to five. Okay. This is like, this kills this. So I need to,
can I move these around? I don't think you guys understand. I, I, I play these kinds of games on
iPad almost every single day. I mean, I, I, I play games like this. I've, I've beaten every single
the franchise, the room. I played every single one of those three times. I was made to play this.
Okay. So this is going to do two to one. I wonder if I can flip these. Two, one, one, three. It is
one of the five, one of the five. Is it right? Good. Five is correct. So now I got to go like this.
So this is how much I'm trying to do damage, trying to kill somebody here. Right? Two out of five.
What am I looking for here? This is, what am I looking for? One here. Okay. So it's got to be
like this up a little bit more like that and up here. I'm not even sure what's going on here.
Okay. Three out of five. So what's happening here? Let's take a minute here. What's happening here?
Sigma relax. So this is doing one damage to, to this character. This is doing two damage to
this character. This is doing three damage to this character. It needs to be completely perfectly
balanced. That's technically right. I'm not looking. Three out of five. Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Oh, that was, that was easier than I thought it was going to be. I got a stink. I forgot that I had
put that there very well. You may add it to your deck and I'll deal you one every so often. What
does this do? All right. Close this thing. Give me the next one. All right. So I get it. I understand.
I get it. This is a, this is locked out here. This can't be moved, but this can cause this is flight.
Got two out of five there. Let's go ahead and make this happen. Let me say three to five,
get that one back. We can please. Thank you. This one cannot be moved with five. You got it.
Put this back up here if we could please. Put this up. Here's your two out of five. Get that
up here please. Here's your two out of five. Get that up here if we could please. One out of five.
Let's put that back down please. I can't move them back and forth. Here's your two out of five. Put
that over here please. Close. Hold on. Three to five. Okay. I can't move this one. I gotta think.
I'm not looking. No, these are both fly. This is, this is the only thing doing the damage right
here. Isn't it? Wouldn't this do it? Here we go. I got it. I play these games in bed all day. Don't
worry. I get it. Wonderful creatures. Those ants very well. I will add them to your deck and make
them available for future challenges. Nice. Oh yeah. Let's go. I'll take all the cards please.
Let's make the game easy. I don't know what the bug does. I need to play a little bit more to
figure out what the bug does. What about this? Can't move this. Always check every single crevice.
Can't do that yet. Whatever it is. All right. What do we got here? I don't think I can do this yet.
I'm gonna play a little bit. Let's do a round. Now that I get some new cards, let's go. There's
some bone tokens for a rainy night. Four. If you deem it necessary, you may cut up one of my cards
with these. A rock might get you out of a hard place. That's kind of just a block. I have to
choose one. I don't know. I'm gonna say boulder. Just block damage. Or the scissors would be good
too. Bones are good too. Feeling overburdened enough with the full three items you carried on.
You again. Indeed. Our friend freed me. Well, I basically told him how to do it.
You got a plan? We have another friend here. You've gotta be. I wouldn't call him a friend.
But I suppose we are in deep this time. Pretty good boys. This guy has three shirts. What's going
on with my hair? Look at my hair. Bullfrog. What do we got? You are lacking squirrels.
Mighty leap. Card bearing the sigil will block. An opposing creature bearing the airborne sigil.
Alright, so I can put this in front of a bird. Let's put a squirrel down. Right here sounds good
I think. Yeah, just put it down now. Wait, oh, it takes bone, right? Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah. Alright,
let's go. Alright, so now I want... What is the stink bug is... Alright, yeah. So we're gonna put
stink bug down. Let's kill a squirrel. Get this out. Oh, shit! I fucked it up. It's alright.
God damn it. I gotta remember more about that. It's okay. Okay. Back in the game. Alright,
let's go. I screwed... I wanted to put a... Yeah, I screwed up. It's fine. Give me a squirrel and
you'll kill that. Sounds good. We're good. Yeah, that's fine. Wolf, I don't need to do anything.
This game's over anyways. A brutal of you. You dealt me more damage than you needed to win.
However, in my game, such feats are rewarded. Be precise. A tooth to keep for each extra damage
dealt. The trapper may be interested in your spoils, but I get extra teeth? Pretty cool.
Elk fawn. An ascent fawn. It quickly grows into an elk and moves to the right. And what do you do?
That scared the shit out of me. I forgot about that. And I was like, the game is reading my
hard drive or something. I actually freaked out. Um, okay. Well, I mean, obviously I'm taking this.
What is that? Six bones. I mean, why wouldn't I not take this? It's literally like the best thing
that I have. And I'm going to make it more powerful in the... Why would you... Okay, I have a question.
Don't spoil the game for me. I have a question. This is just for free. This you have to sacrifice
someone. What's the kind of difference here? Do you get more? They do two different things.
You can get multiple abilities. It gives you... It gives card effects. Uh, you like essentially
absorb the card. I wonder if I should do this one. I'm doing this. The choice is yours.
Ant Queen. What is that? When a card bearing the sigil is played, an ant is created in your hand.
That seems kind of good. Cockroach. When a card bearing a copy of his... I mean, why would... I'm
going to do that with a thermo. That seems broken. That's absolutely broken. I'm guaranteed to beat
the game right now. I'm going to beat the game right now. I'm going to walk through the rest
of the game. Marvelous. I'll go. No, a thermo is gone. I mean, that's simple. That's very simple.
I now am going to get two of these and I'm going to walk through the game. This is really cool.
I like this. This is a fun game. Now I know why everyone said to play it. So strange. Why can't
I remember his name? I believe I lost some of my memory in the flash. Oh, these are people that
played the game before he made cards for them. He took their pictures and now they like cards
forever. That's what's going to happen to me. What do you got on the board? Okay. So this thing
hurts. I'm going to be like, I'm going to be like slow game playing Andy, by the way, because like,
I need to like pay attention. The value represented with this sigil will be equal to the number of
ants that the owner has on their side of the table. All right. What do you got? That's not going to
help. Okay. I need to get this into memory. It's hard to call it cowardly. I don't, I don't understand
the ant thing. I can't play this. Why not? I have to draw for us. Okay. Uh, uh, I would play.
Thanks. What damage is this thing doing? This thing doesn't have damage. Wait, what does the
worker ant not do any damage? It's just one. Oh, oh, okay. Oh, so it's how many ants you currently
just have. I'm going to get rid of this guy. Get your hand, elbows back. I don't know if you're
putting shit on the board or not. We get a referee to blow fucking whistle. That's don't do that.
I think I'm doing this. I, this is probably stupid. This is probably dumb, but I mean,
this is dumb. What I'm doing is dumb. What I just did was dumb, but whatever. I just won the game.
Maybe it wasn't dumb at mantis. Ooh, it hits both left and right. The alpha urgent boldness,
the creatures that stand beside it. So it gives what plus flow plus one plus one. All right. So
it gives plus one damage to everybody next to it. I feel like I want the mantis. I want the mantis
and then I'm going to make the mantis stronger by sacrificing something that I would do.
Then maybe that's what I would do. That's what I'm doing right now. I think it's going to be you
sacrifice. Wait, I could do, whoa, wait, I could do the reverse. Hold on. I could do the,
how do I back up? I could do the reverse. So if I sacrifice the mantis, I can give it to somebody
else. Oh shit. Uh, the wolf probably, the wolf would be crazy or the ant queen. Yeah, it's
definitely the wolf. This is, that's huge. What is that? What's that thing? Greetings. All right.
This is pretty basic here. I'm going to go, uh, squirrel bullfrog here and then, uh, yeah,
this won't kill it. I can sacrifice him afterwards. He'll actually, he'll fly over. I wonder if it's
worth it. Sacrificing. All right. We got stink bug, which what do you got? That'd be a one, one.
He's going to die anyways, so I need to get rid of him. What do you got to stink bug? Hold on.
My brain having trouble here. It's like, I could, I just got to pick a play. Okay. I'll kill. Um,
you go here. You'll kill this and then you're going to go here. This will die, but it's okay.
Cause I got this guy coming to here and let's go. It's fine. Okay. Whoa. I'm actually about to lose.
Look, there's a third talking card somewhere around here. Personally, I hate the guy biggest
kill joy ever, but he's the only one of us with a plan to get things back to normal.
Okay. That was a misplay. What are you in my chat right now? Relax. Okay. All right. All right.
All right. Ooh, good draw. Awesome. Good draw. I see the way this is going. I concede. You may
accept my surrender or you may finish this match the slow way. Why would I do that? Because if I
don't get extra tokens, if I do a bunch of damage, um, is this a dumb thing that I'm doing? All right.
Well, hold on. If I sacrifice stote and the opossum, I'll have two and two, right? That's
okay. That should, then that should do it. And that'll overkill. I think. Yeah.
Our numbers, the ants creed and put this out. I get extra. Um, all right. This is going to be
a huge overkill. Ooh, I love that pot. What's your opinion on the tectonic plates? What do you,
what do you want me to say? A thing that's, uh, it's a thing that's under the ground and
it makes the world shake. You were stopped along the way by a trapper looking to liquidate his
pelts. There was something uncanny about his appearance, but you were quickly distracted by
his wares. Here to look at my pelts, take a pelt free of charge. Um, rabbit. What do these do?
See the quality. Oh, it's the extra tokens. What do they do? I can have one for free. I don't get
it. Do I have to do this? Take the gold ones. Well, I mean, that's, I was going to take the
gold one, but I don't know. I'm going to take the gold one. That's what I would do. Golden pelt.
And I'll take a rabbit. You're leaving already? Please consider me pelts. Didn't I already take
them? You'll need, how do I leave? I'm done. I, thanks for your business. The man assured you
of the value of the pelts. They appear to be useless in a fight. Stop doubting yourself.
That's all I do. He mentioned that the trader further down the path would reward you for them.
I don't know what to do. I could sacri, I don't, I don't want to run like I'm getting rid of all
my cards though. No, I, I, I sacrifice like three cards already. I think warm light of a campfire.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Through the 10 hungry guys. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Enhance its power. All right.
Stop this. It's going to be Wolf, man. You kidding me? It would be me too. I think I'm doing Wolf.
I haven't, I haven't seen this card come up once. Balance your damage across the cards.
Yeah. I kind of am just being like a two card Andy. Yeah. Aren't I? I like this one,
but I also like the opossum. I think I'm going to opossum. Opossum. That's what I'm doing.
That's what I'm doing. They had enhanced the creature's power, butting a few of the
survivors to ruling. You made a, Hey, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. What the fuck? What? No,
I wanted, I, that's two bones and it gives me two damage. What? My boss battles are high stakes.
Test of your aptitude. With one flame, you'll either overcome them or die or not. I will let
you keep the smoke. Oh, it's this dude again. The incessant clank, clank, clanking. It's the
prospector, the prospector. Yeehaw. All right, let's go again. What does this do? What does that do?
Again, the smoke. When a card bearing the sigil dies, four bones are awarded instead of one. Oh
shit. Can I just get that out there now? Let's get that out there right now. Kill the mule first,
right? That's a card set. All right. This is what I'm going for. I'm going for, get rid of this,
put this here. I don't know what the pelt does. Squirrel. But don't be stupid about this. I fucked
it up already. This thing goes right. Shit. Can I sacrifice that? I can. All right. So just sacrifice
it. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. So I can just sacrifice this and put down
the, what does the most damage? One, three. I'll put you down. Good. You go here and then
you go here and then you go here. And then what is the, I don't know what this does. I'm afraid to
use it. That's fine. Rabbit pelt. What the fuck? All right. I have to, I don't want to use these.
What do these do? Why is it going this way? This will get killed. That's fine. I'll be all right.
They're blockers. All right. I'm just gonna put this one down. I'm putting this here.
I'm about to, I'm about to win. Perfect. This is two, one. Perfect. All right. Move over. That's
fine. Good. All right. This is super wolf. Super wolf is going to take out these two. Oh, fuck off.
Wait, what? Oh, it's all right. Wait. Okay. I, it goes like that. Oops. Okay. Okay. Do you have to
kill this stuff? Get them. Yeah. Please get rid of it. I don't, I can't do anything yet. Just go,
go again. Doesn't, I can't do anything yet. I'm putting Jerm around next turn. Here we go. Bingo.
Squirrel. Squirrel. Boing. Boing. Okay. Where's this going? This is, this is like just unbelievably
good. Go right here. Yeah. That's game over right now. Goodbye. What's that? Dag nabbit my mule.
Thank you. Okay. What do I got? Um, I think I can win pretty easily here. Hold on. Elk is,
alpha is okay. Wait, I can do alpha. I got to put it right here. I could do
and don't have any hands. Ant queen is okay. Here's the deal. Uh, Elk is kind of sick too,
though, isn't it? I think I'm going to do Elk. Oh no, wait, no, no. This gives ants.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What's this do? Okay. We're good. All right. That's good.
I'll have to win again. All right. I just win the game. Bingo. There it is. All right. First boss
done. Allow me to light your candles once more. I won't be killing you quite yet. Very nice.
You're the first in a while to overcome a boss. As a reward, you are granted an opportunity to
select a rare card. Boost carefully. Strange larva. The level of brutish strength needs no
explanation. Seven? Seven and what? And Gek. The uninspiring Gek, perhaps you can find a use for it.
Um, this doesn't cost anything. I feel like these, these are, these are bait because this is free.
It does one damage and I can sacrifice it whenever I want. Um, what does this turn into? Probably
some kind of big bug or something, right? Taking the Gek. It's just a free card. Huge early game.
With sound of the prospector's pickaxe still ringing in your ears, you carried onwards.
The rank smell of rot and mold permeated the humid air. Every step forward was answered by
some nearby slip or slither, but cautiously into the wetlands. Good card. Barbara's nice, but Gek
is cool, dude. Yeah. River snapper, adder, barren. It spawns a rabbit when it is played.
Zero one rabbit. This is kind of an annoying card. Well, this is a zero two and it gives you a zero
one. Hmm. That's kind of, that's kind of annoying. I think it's, that's, that's, that's the adder.
I would take the adder just to in case you get run into a huge enemy or something. I don't know
what that is. What is this? I think this means I'm like deleting a card for some reason, right?
What does the pack do again? What's the backpack do? I clicked on this once. I forget what it was.
Items. I guess I want to see what this is, so I'm going to click it, right? I don't know what
this is. Some familiar stones, but there was something different. You intuited. The fate of
the creature selected for this would not be pleasant. I delete a card. Do what you must.
Nope. That was the worst card that I have. The rabbit. I have just like a shitty rabbit
belt. No elp. I would probably get, I don't know. Bullfrog kind of sucks, but it only
sacrifice though. I feel like I'm going to need these later. I'm doing bullfrog. I'm going to,
I don't know what this does. Slaughtered the bullfrog. However, the bone lord was pleased
by your sacrifice. A minor boon of the bone lord. You will start each battle with one extra bone.
That's kind of a big deal. Kind of at least, right? Worth it. Yeah. What does this mean?
All right. Let me go down here again. How many ants do I have? I got to move one person here.
Come on. I'm so close. There it is. Caged wolf. There's one, there's another one of these over
here. I don't want to hit that. I can't. Okay. So I have to hit this one. It's three. Got it.
What is that? Without having met her, this wood carving is meaningless. In time you will
understand its power. And there's a squirrel right here. Oh, it's just like hearthstone.
What does that mean? That doesn't work. Still didn't do the clock yet. Is there another thing?
Oh no, I didn't. No, I didn't. Is there something listed here? Ah, hammer. Staff. Oh, teeth. Okay.
I got some teeth. Is there anything else I can do? I got another card. Oh, I don't think I can do
anything about that. I got another card. What about the candles? Oh, you get a stump and you get a
frog. Okay. I'm doing ant queen. Uh, yeah. I'm going to wait until ant queen. All right. I don't
want this to get killed. So ant queen's going over here. Oh, perfect. All right. I'm going to
put this down here in just a moment. All right. I want a squirrel. All right. So let me see here.
Out here. Work our ant here. Perfect. Very perfect. Very perfect. Very good. Excess damage is not
wasted. It carries over to the card behind the mangled corpse of the victim. So that was cool.
I didn't even know that. Lucky for you. All right. What do we got on the board? Adder. Bullfrog. I
don't care about the bullfrog. Although I could put the Adder out here. Oh, I need two. Shit.
Probably should have read that. Oh, whatever. Uh, go here. Oh, I thought I won. I think I
win anyways. I think I win anyways. I keep fucking doing this. I keep fucking doing that.
I keep forgetting this is two. I should still be fine though. Okay. Now go like this. I'm so
close to winning. Just win already. I'm not going to lose. I'm not going to lose. I have to pee.
All right. I'm going to pee soon here. River otter. The elusive otter. It submerges itself
during my turn. A beehive will draw a bee when it gets attacked. Or Kaminsky. When an opposing
creature is placed opposite to an empty space, a card bearing the sigil will move to that empty
space. Let me read that again. When somebody on the other team is placed in an empty space,
opposite an empty space, this card will move to that space. And it's like a thorns. Okay. I get it.
That's a good card. Submerged itself during its opponent's turn. While submerged, opposing creatures
attack its owner. All right. So this is just like stealth. That's not bad either. This is cool too
though. I could buff this at a campfire. I think I'm going to do the beehive. Otter is unkillable.
Um, they all suck. I would probably, I'm going to, I'm going to do beehive. You need to go piss. I
will in a second. I'm busy. All right. Now I'm going to, I'm going to buff the beehive. This might be
health. It's health and that's big. Or I could sacrifice somebody. Maybe I'll sacrifice somebody.
I'm going to sacrifice someone. All right. What do I want? What do I want to sacrifice?
Oh man. Beehive. Beehive on somebody. Go piss. Why are you saying go piss girl? What? All right.
I think I'm doing beehive. Yep. I'm going to give that to the ant queen. No. Somebody that I can,
it has to be somebody that can stay alive. What is it? Ooh, cage wolf. That's just six health.
What is it? Okay. This is kind of interesting. It'll just spawn a bunch of shit. It's got to
have to be something with at least a few health. Maybe the cat. Skink too, right? I'm going to say
probably this because that will just spawn bees over and over again. If it's a bad idea,
it's a bad idea. Whatever. It has a ton of health. Bullfrog, rabbit, pelt, squirrel. Okay. I'll put
the, just go here and I'm going to put the pelt down right here because why not? Oh, I, oops.
Ant queen. Can I even sacrifice two things? Shit, that was stupid. Yeah. That was just,
that was just bogus of me. I don't know why I did that, but it's all right. I can just go another
turn. I actually want you to clear this shit out. I don't want it. Oh, that was a, that was a big
problem. That was actually really bad. Uh, I think I have to do this. Oh my God. I'm fucking dead.
I'm going to die right now. I blew it so bad. This will be two. All right, hold on. I'll kill
this. Okay. If I get an ant out here, it'll be two, two, which it'll kill this. It'll kill the
thing behind it. I think I really blew it. I can put the pelt down here or something. Or should I
kill this row? What row is more dangerous? What row is more dangerous? Probably this one. Actually,
I don't know. They're both kind of the same. The spider is like, was that loud? And then I'll put
the pelt over here. Right? I hope that's right. You scared me. Like there's a bug in the room.
Well, I don't know. If you were watching, I clearly gave at least two or three seconds of like a, oh,
I'm about to yell because it's a spider. All right. I got to put something down here so that I don't
die. This is going to get killed, right? Or do I not care? Cause I'll get some way out. I'll be
I'll be fine. Okay. Now piece of shit. I don't think I need this yet because hold on. This'll
do two or will I beat it? Will I kill him if I take it too without? This is risky. I will. I
think this is going to kill him, right? And then that's four. That should be it. Just to be safe.
I'm going to think that's it. I think I did it. Rattler, Reginald, tragic rat king. When their
tangled bodies become corpses, you will gain four bones. I don't get it. What four bones instead of,
Oh, okay. So I just get, I feel like I'm, I need more bone cards though. I have tons of bones.
You know what to do. I can't spend the bones. This is huge too. Card bearing the sigil damages
another creature. The creature perishes. That's pretty huge. Monkey W. That's pretty big. Yeah.
I'll take it. Should I get an item? I'm going to get an item. Gustrum. This may lift your creatures
into the air if only for a turn of fliers. That means like they can't be targeted or something.
This seems kind of cool. The creatures will attack as though they have the airborne. Oh,
that's amazing. I want that. Bleeding yields three blood if you can ignore the
beating. Wait, what's happening? Oh, but what, but what though? Black Oat is created in your hand.
A black goat is defined as zero power, one health, worthy of sacrifice. It counts as three. It gives
three blood. Okay. There we go. There we go. So this is going to spawn bees, airborne and
submerges. So this thing is going to be paying the ass. Okay. So this thing's, this thing I'm
never going to get rid of. Uh, so I'm going to deal with these two. Oh, a scream because
it's a spider. How much health do you have? All right. Keep me alive. I'll try. And do you know
what? Let's put a, uh, none of these are going to, uh, please go pee. I'm not going to use the goat.
I'm still confused on what this means. It costs one blood, but I'm confused at what, what the
point is. When this thing dies, what happens? Goat is better than the wolf. Use it and find out.
It gives worth three for a sacrifice. I don't, I don't get it. Cost one gives three. Um, so I get
to play more. Okay. Whatever. I'm kind of confused. Um, holy shit, Jeremy. I hold on. I'm sacrificing
it is like sacrificing three cards. So is there like an indicator of how many I've sacrificed so
far? So I can play. So if I put this goat down, if I need three blood, I just eat that and it counts
as three blood. It's worth three. Okay. It's the cost. Yeah. All right. That's what I thought it
was. I could just put this down and put this down too. I actually don't really know what the hell
to do right now. I don't think I want to use that now though. Like that's like a boss thing. I'm
just going to do this and whatever happens happens here. Cause like I kind of been screwed here.
This is probably a bad idea, but it is such a bad idea. This is a really bad idea, but who cares?
I'm full of bad ideas. This is a terrible idea. This is literally the worst move I could possibly
do. I think it is lost. Um, I don't know what to do. Let the wolf die. Yeah. I'm just going to farm,
but I think I'm dead next turn. I'm just like dead next turn. I fucked up this whole round. Um,
I think it's lose cause this can't. All right. So this card can never die, right? This can literally
not be killed. No matter what I can cut this card and get rid of it. So I will live if I put,
but this goes over the bee. Is this bad to do? Let's just do it. Okay. So that's gone. This
can't attack it. This is going to do one damage regardless. This is going to hit the, all right.
So let's do this. Let's just put this down like here and cause, uh, Oh my God, my brain. I just
don't, I can't. Well, the, will this bit lock it? Cause I need to tip the scales. Otherwise I'm
going to lose. E brain. Well, I mean, if I don't, I can't, if I don't tip the scales, I'm going to
fucking lose. Right? What are you talking about? Cause if I could take one more damage, I think
I'm dead. I think that's what's happening here. Right? Like I kind of had to do that. Didn't I?
All right. Ron saved. I can sacrifice the squirrel and the bee, kill both these motherfuckers over
here. I don't want to screw this up though. Let me get this right. Cause this is how I hate this.
I have to kill. This is going to die next turn. Do I wait until next turn to play me and just put
the bee down because then I'll kill this. I'll put the bee down here and just, or let, I can't,
I sacrifice this and kill this row. What I, this is the one that's going to Kurt kill me though.
I don't know. I have no idea. I'm just going to fucking go for it. I have no idea. Like I
don't play these kinds of games. I don't play Hearthstone in bed every night. I do every night.
I have like 2000 hours in battlegrounds. All right. I'm going to put the bee down. No, I'm not.
Oh, I just need to stop talking and just focus. Oh my God. What do I do? I'm fine. What was that?
I didn't want to, I didn't want you to do that. What the fuck was that? I didn't want you to do
that. I kind of blew everything, didn't it? All right. I'm going to kill this row here. Please be
right. Please be right. I think this is right. Okay. Good. Okay. I'm good. Please. Let's get,
let's get, let's just fucking look. Pay attention. It's like here, like a voice over here and a thing
over here. No, you go that way. You go that way. And I'm just like, no, no, no. Everyone,
everybody stop talking and let's, let's go. Is it, I got 18,000 people in my head and they're all you.
All right. Kind of cool. For the beehive. I need bone consumption. I need bone. All right. I'm
almost at the boss. I can't, I don't have, I can't do items. Do I want to put in here? I mean,
that's, I could just get that on somebody or I could do this and then Ant Queen maybe. What about
the Gek? Holy shit. And I can play that for free. You suck at strats. I know. Oh, I know. Trust me.
All right. I got to pee. I'll be right back. Pee time. BRB. One second. Well, maybe like a minute
or two. I'll keep this music on too. It's interesting. What happened? Oh, I see. Got minimized.
Oops. Let's continue. Let's get this shit out of you. What? Sorry. Why is the, why was the music
not on? That's kind of weird. Oh, it's because I hit the windows key. That's right. Oops. All right.
So this is the boss. Let me get one chance. How smell invaded your nostrils and caused your throat
to seize. Hulking man sat by a brackish pond with his feet submerged in the dark water. He pulled a
hook from a pile of rotting fish and rose to his feet. I am the angler. Go fish. The angler,
mind his hook. Play a squirrel or something when he aims it. I will protect your best cards.
Okay. He's not going to be happy about this one. All right. Everybody quiet. Everybody's silent.
Okay. Here we go. This play thing. Go squirrel. No smoke. No. Squirrel. Squirrel going out.
But again, still stink bug. I'm going out too. Oh, he did it wrong. He did it wrong. He did it
wrong. He did it wrong. He did it wrong. Whatever. Which fish are choose. What's that mean? Um,
can I put something on top of this? I don't get it. I don't get it. World. He's, he's saying he's
going to take this card. Um, what do I do about this? Pressure fish. Easy. Choose. Oh, okay. I
get it. Oh shit. No, I thought, I didn't know he moved again. I didn't know he moved it again.
All right. I thought he just decided. Oh, okay. But what, what is he going to do about that?
Oh, I'm in trouble now. Oh, I'm now, I'm in a lot of trouble. Okay. I, I messed it up. Wait. No,
I didn't get it. Whatever. I didn't. Oh, okay. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it.
I, I, I, that was good. That's not a bad move. Decent play. Really? All right. So if I do, uh,
Gecko's not good here though. Maybe it is because it'll kill that because if it kills that, he gets
the bones and then this won't attack me. And then I go like this and then I say, let's go.
We're good. Stale fish. Hard choice. Um, wait, cause he's going to take that. If I play a card,
he takes it. So I don't really care if he takes this because I could, he'll take the pelt. All
right. Let me see how dumb this is. If I go boom, boom, and then I put the pelt down. Okay. That's
what I'm doing. Okay. Let's go. Okay. I'm going to go ahead and take that one. I don't give a shit.
Oh, wait. Does it shuffle the board? It does. Okay. Go fish. Uh, he just gets a free turn.
I will use this opportunity to pull a, um, a scout and end my turn.
Oh my God. What did happen? What the hell is that? Um, okay. This is bad.
Uh, I need bones. That's bad. Not good. Four, five. I don't think that's enough. Is it enough?
I sacrifice a squirrel and do the fan. Is that enough? That's enough? Sacrifice. Huh?
Enough. Wait, hold on. Everyone relax. Sacrifice. Yeah. What happened? Wait, does this come back?
No, no, no, no. This doesn't, that doesn't work like that. What do you mean?
You use, hold on. Yes. I hope you guys aren't lying to me.
Did I do it? And do the fan now. And there's four or five. Is that enough? Just end your turn. But
are they going to hit shit? You win. You win. You win. You win. What? Oh my God. I thought. Okay.
The reason why I freaked out is because I thought he was going to hit this for some reason.
Relight your candles. Thank you. I thought he was going to hit that. Okay.
Didn't need to even use the fan. Okay. Another larva. This thing.
Wild 13. Doesn't die when sacrificed, but you have the heart to try.
So it just stays on the board forever. I feel like I can't already have a couple of these,
don't I? In a way. I'll take the larva. Why not? Dinner would have to wait. Let me see.
Bridget gust of wind billowed unwelcome into your lungs. Beauty of the falling snow failed to
distract you from the chill in your bones. You had to send it to the snow line. Plus you got in your
fucked up little room here. Um, finally pried my special dagger from the paws of that squirrel,
though you may wish that you hadn't. What can I do with that? I have an item now. Smoke.
You have the knife. Okay. Yeah. I use it on the, do I have to sit down? That one's only for card
dueling. You encountered a small outpost in the woods tended by a mysterious woman. It was the
trader that the old trapper had mentioned. Her appearance was unsettling, but you were mollified
by her offering. Do you mind if I examine those pelts of yours? Start with you hair pelts. Here's
what I can offer. I can trade you any of these. Take your time. You may search your deck or any
card and take it into your hand when you play this. That seems really good. Ringworm. This
thing kind of sucks. What does this thing do? This thing's terrible. I think I want the coyote
because I have things that generate bones. I have barely any bone spenders. This thing doesn't even
have a description. Bagpie. Yeah. Magpie is good too. I don't have any bone spenders. I have all
these things generating bones, but they just sit on the table. Okay. The last like three or four
games, I had like four or five, six bones just sitting there. I'm thinking about taking mantis
just so I can sacrifice it and give it to somebody else. Is that a golden pelt? Magnificent. Deus.
Chime is created on each empty adjacent space. The chime is defined as zero. So when you put
it down to zero one. Oh man. So this just kind of gets in the way or it's a random card. Two
seven. Oh, oh, this is just like a tank. I'll take the tank. Who the hell is this? Who's that?
Choice is yours. Who is this? It's me. Okay. So I'm going to give the spreading move. Will this kill
everything? This will kill two things, right? That's kind of a big deal. That's a huge deal.
That's three bones too. Perfect. I don't know what this is. We haven't seen it yet. FD.
Creatures in the way get pushed. That's kind of scary. So this is going to move forward.
So I should try. I got to get. How many bones do I have? I only have one bone. That'll be two.
If I put Reginald here and they come down, it'll kill them both. All right. I need to think about
this. Oh, let's just put something out there. I'll put the skink here. Right? Yeah. Right.
Is that stupid? I think that's it. Yeah. Then that's a bone and then it's two bones. I can't
do anything else really. So we're just gonna go.
So that's your three. Unfortunately, I will kill these two. Let's go ahead and get that out of the
way. Let me draw first. I'll draw a scroll. All right. Reginald's going here. That'll kill both
of these and I need to put something over here. No, I can just wait. What does the knife do?
You will place a weight on the scales. Pain is temporary. Okay. So that'd be like,
point point. I gotta draw something, right? That's kind of bad, isn't it?
It's me. Okay. Hi. You're really kind of screwing this up. Oh, I think it is when I just went.
It's not a bad play. I just win right now. Hey, what? Hey, what are you talking about? Oh,
it gets in the way of right. Okay. Whatever. I win right now because that'll be it's zero.
It's going to go, I'm just going to sacrifice these guys. No, I'm not. I'll win next turn. Who
cares? Yeah, I'll win this time. Yeah. Good for you. What is happening right now? I might,
I might be able to do this. If I go boom, boom and go this way, it might be a victory already,
right? I think that's a win. I do that. That's one, two, then I can do two, which would go
here. Hey, I think I just won. I didn't. No, I win the game. I win. I win. The game's over. I win.
I win. The game's over. The game's over. I win. It's fine. Whatever. What's this?
I have the most exquisite pelts. I got a lot of teeth. First one's free. Don't buy more. Yeah.
Isn't this going to just kind of load up my deck with a bunch of shit? Maybe just buy this one.
I feel like this is going to load my deck up with a bunch of crap. I'm going to buy the gold one and
that's it. All right. What am I sacrificing? Mole man or larva? Mole has two effects. Yeah,
I don't know. I feel like this would be cool though. Mole man can make somebody crazy.
That one's good too. Yeah. This one's good because then I can put it on. Oh, it would not,
it would not hit whoever it was and they would move out of the way. And okay, I wonder maybe the,
maybe the mole man or larva. Yeah, that's a good one because then this will absolutely live one
turn and then transform. I'm starting to get it a little more. Although games like this really kind
of nerve wracking for me. All right. You got a mole man, but this pushes in direction. This one
will always be a tank. So I keep, I, that was the scream at the bug joke. I wonder if I even do
anything or just skip. I think I'm just going to skip or something. Yeah. Cause if I put this down,
I feel like he's just going to die like immediately. And I guess I'm just going to do this ever.
Ow. That hurts a lot. Again with this shit draw. Oh my God. I'm going to kill this and I'll get
free. If he's going to kill this anyways, and why not just be able to put something out,
use the knife. I could. All right. Hold on. If he's going to kill this anyways,
why not just me kill it, be able to play the coyote next turn. Cause he's going to kill the
ant instead or wait till the queen comes up. I thought I had a lot of bone. Yeah. I thought I
did too. I thought I had a lot of bone makers. I'm going to, uh, whatever. If I lose, I lose.
I'm going to see what happens if I do this. Like this could be stupid, but what up? I'm going to
try it. I got the four. Okay. Now let's pull this. All right. So now I got to do one. It's
going to bounce off this anyways. So I'm going to have to put a pelt down. Pelt down here. Coyote.
It doesn't really matter where the coyote goes, right? So whatever. I'm in, I'm in trouble,
but what am I going to do about it? Oh my God. I'm like going to die. I think I might have to
open this. What does the knife do? Uh, okay. I can't do anything else. So, um, oh, I'm so
fucked. How am I supposed to do about this? That's how he had so much such an advantage.
I'm just dead. I'm going to lose. I, he started, I started, I, all the bones fucking ruined this
run. What did I say? Oh, hey guys, I didn't buy it. Get a bunch of bones. Cause I have so many bones,
uh, creators. I had like, I'm just dead. It's all right. I lose. What am I going to do here besides
this? I mean, I could just sit here and get killed. I'm not going to, this is over. I mean,
might as well just open this and see what it does. So I put this down. This is worth. So if I do this,
I get three blood. You have two lives. Oh my goodness. I do. Right. It's only for bosses when
he blows out the candle. So what, what should I do here? Kill the squirrel with this, put down the
queen or kill the coyote and go queen rattler. Okay. So who should I, if I sacrifice the squirrel,
then it's fine, right? Cause I'm still kind of confused how this works. So I, I'll get three.
So put that down. This is now, I can put this down here. I sacrifice this and then
let's be put this. I don't want this to die immediately, but I'm going to fucking
the ant down. Um, I don't know. World queen to ant bones. Um, did I not draw a card yet?
So should I kill the coyote? Like all this? Okay. I actually have no idea what's going on.
I, I'm just fucking dead anyways. I got to lose anyways. Like I'm not like I couldn't do anything
about it. I blow a candle out. Not disappointing. Believe it or not. You're not the first to lose
an eye here. Not much fun if you're half blind. Like to replace it perhaps. Oh, I wanted to see
what it looked like. I didn't get a chance to look at it. Choice is final. Okay. Wait, I get to keep
going. I wait, hold on a minute. I definitely don't want this, the goat. So it doesn't store it though.
So if I put this down and I use something that costs two blood, it's not like I get to keep
the other one blood in reserve. It just like up to three. So I have, okay. I understand. I get it.
So you would only want to use this if you had something that had at least two or more.
I get it. I get it. I understand. What does this do? This one's kind of interesting.
This is way too many bones. I need to get some, I need to do something. That's not,
I'm actually just take this or this is, I need damage. My deck kind of sucks before I'm gone
here. I don't get it. Okay. So this is health. Please know larva. Oh man. One three with poison
or Richard old one three with poison is pretty ridiculous. Yeah. And it's free. I would love to
see it. Let me see it right now. All right. This is not a bad start. Do you not have anything?
Okay. What do you got? Turkey. Okay. This is this annoying thing. All right. So I'm okay. I'm going
to put the, I'm going to put out me next turn. Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no. We'll put a mole
man out right now. Let's go. Oh man. Or do I just wait till next turn? Like it's too late now.
Ah, I died. Oh my God. What am I doing? What happened? I don't know what I fucking did.
I thought I think I die anyways. Even if I didn't sacrifice the mole man. Yeah. Yeah. Stay there.
No need to move. I am afraid you are not dead yet. Yeah. Hold still. Where did I put that
camera of mine? Stop taking pictures. You don't have 30 HP. This is an art stone. I know, but
still, man, I took a picture. Wait, did I just take a picture of this guy? You really think I
would leave film in there? Do you have any idea what that camera is capable of? Give me that.
We have a memento to create. Behold your. Oh, I do a new one every turn. Oh no. I had a good one
last time. Cost? This is free. Power and health in the rattler. 31 sigils. I feel like the wolf
is better. Good Riddler. That's such a stupid. Fine. One thing remains. It must capture your
photo or whatever. Jeez. Oh, raid just came in. What? Hold on a minute. I got to correct this.
This is like, wait, this is like white. The light is white. I need to change that. That's why I look
like a fucking skeleton today. Hold on. Big raid. Big raid. Laniya Lazar. Lazar. I fucking said that's
so wrong. I'm so sorry that I oh my God, that's so fucking embarrassing and stupid. Thank you so
much for the raid. Welcome everybody. I look like such a fucking dickhead right now. Thank you so
much for the raid. Welcome everybody. It's a big raid. Yeah, if you don't know a lot, it's a Vtuber.
I've seen, I've watched. You don't think I don't know who that is? You don't think I don't know?
Now it's time for an apology. Here's the thing. Let me explain. I'm so sorry. I looked over here
and I just, my brain just immediately started reading and it's like I looked over and it just
was Laniya Lazar. I'm such a fucking dumbass. My brain has trouble sometimes, but I do appreciate
thanks. Welcome everybody. We're playing, uh, playing Inscription. Apology song. I'm not singing
an apology song to anybody. No. No apology song. Oh, I can see the music. Okay. You will learn as
we go or you will die. Hope you had a good stream though. Thank you. You see, he was defeated
recently and wishes to redeem himself. Ear wax in your eyes. My ears are clean. Relax. It would be
unfortunate if you were to fall to the prospector before he was given that chance. This hook is
powerful. You may steal one of my cards with it. For that reason, you will not find any others along
the path. Use it wisely. It seems the lowly stink bug has made its way in, but it is dealt so it
stands. What's going on? What's happening to everybody? Why are they all messed up? What
happened? I get to pick one. Yeah. Why is his head turning into a square? This is my deck right now.
Ah, I see. So, so let me guess it. So I beat two bosses, but the game is like, okay, you beat two
bosses. So we're just going to get you on the path to the last one you beat before the area you were
just in. Is that how that works? So I have to beat the angler again. No, I'm such a fucking idiot.
No, you may not choose a specific beast. Instead, you must now decide on a tribe that you prefer.
Yeah, I'm gonna go with insect. A randomly chosen insect card. Do you wish for something else?
What's wrong with insects? This game is crazy. I think the rules are kind of changing. Choose.
What am I choosing? This is for the cockroach card, which would be, this would be unkillable. Okay.
The old woman bared her teeth in satisfaction. Your first totem was complete. Many lives sigil
will now be marked upon all your squirrel creatures. Huh? If you lose this run, you are
fucked. I'm probably gonna man. Oh, oh, what the fuck, man? Is this what that looked like?
This is what that looked like. Holy shit. Looks like Dr. Robotnik. Somebody put a mustache right
here. Somebody put a mustache right there. That's fucked. Jesus. Hey. All right. So this thing,
what does this do again? What happened? So this can't die. So I can sacrifice a hundred times.
Hold on. Let me test this. So if I do bullfrog on this. What? Really? Oh, okay. How do I get rid
of them? But if it can't die, then okay. All right, dude. Relax here. Um, all right. I gotta do this.
Yeah. And then stink bug. I'm gonna save the stink bug because I'll put that out after this.
He sucks. I, dude, I, I don't, what do you, I don't know, man. Like I'm just trying to play the game.
I suck asshole at card games. Did you watch me play Hearthstone? Did you watch me play Hearthstone?
I just sometimes just put cards down because they look pretty. I, they look nice. I don't know. I,
by math in my head, I'm doing fine. I'm doing fine. I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine. Total misplay.
Shut up. Again, I have to pick another. All right. So I'm doing insect again because it's an insect
build. Ant. Okay. Cool. I got a lot of teeth. Okay. Gently shaking hands. She placed her
offerings before you. Another offering. Uh, what's, I don't know. What am I picking here?
Okay. What does the snake head do? I didn't want to, I didn't want to pick the snake head. I just
want to see what it did. I don't know what, what, I don't know what I just did. What just happened?
I don't know what just happened. I wanted to look. What do I do? What, how do I fix this? Um,
eat the squirrel head. I don't understand what's happening. Do I click the squirrel head? Press S
keep squirrels. Does this mean I'm keeping the squirrel right here? Or does this mean I'm
keeping the squirrel? Click the squirrel. Now click this. Okay. I thought I could look at that.
No, dude. Okay. I wanted to read it. I thought I could read to see what it was going to do.
I just wanted to read it. I, it was like a snake head. I didn't know what that did. It's for
lizards. Right click to see it. I didn't have a book on it. All right. What do you got? Okay.
So it's going to go forward and then this way. I don't want anything right here, right? I want it
like here. Well, that was a dumb thing that I just did. I literally just said, don't put it there.
Bro, please. What? We got a good one. This looks like I have boogers coming out of my nose.
This one's good, but I'm not bald. Nosebleed. Uh, mantis. Who health? Who's wisely? The ant or the
wolf. Probably this would be good. This would be three, four for the mantis. One, four. Awkward
should be interesting because it was never, it would just always, but yeah, I think this would
kind of get in the way, wouldn't it? This would last too long, I think. Four bones. I'm not
bone generating. Put it on the mantis. What's this shit? All right. There's two birds. Uh,
I think I'm going to get this out here first. Oh shit. I need it. Okay. You don't get tokens for
that, huh? You back on the board. Yep. Ooh, wolf. All right. Uh, who do I want to get rid of you?
Cause you'll kill this whole row and that's good. That should be good to go. It should be good to
go. All right. Three. That'll kill, that won't kill this, but I think we're good. Don't read it
again. I'm not going to read it again. Ooh, mantis. Mantis in replace of the ant. It's just a better
ant. I mean, it's just a better ant and it'll hit. Yeah, let's do it. I wish I could get rid of this
game over. Let's see if I can do a ton of damage though. Cockroach. Nah, that's it. That's a lot of
gold. Elk fawn, Reginald again, and a river snapper. I mean, we have to take, and then we just
sacrifice. We're putting Reginald up to sacrifice now, right? Cause I'm generating very much bone
or that would be huge too. Cockroach or Reginald, which one? Who do I want to give that to? I mean,
probably mantis or probably Reginald. Maybe the mantis. Wolf is good. That's just very clean
though. Very clean. Ant. I don't, I don't have a queen ant though. I'm going mantis. I don't have
a queen ant. Okay. So this is the angler again, right? Hold on. I have to play the whole game
over again when I lose. It's a roguelike. That mule. Yep. I know what I'm doing. All right. Let's go.
Squirrel going out. You. Boom. You. Boom. Bullfrog. Stay. Okay. Now I get four bones when this is
broken. There we are. There we are. Check this out. We go one, two, smack that. We go one, two,
smack into that. We go. Let's see if I care. I don't care. Mantis. Good. Mantis is going to go.
I wish I could get rid of this. I don't want to. I wish I could delete the boulder.
Just don't just leave because he's going to kill everything. Yep. This is a jump. No,
can't do anything because it's just stuff in the way. So whatever. Just kill it please.
All right. Now. Perfect. Go and kill that please. Please hit that. I can't play anything.
I can't play anything. Just hit me. Thank you. I can't play a squirrel otherwise. I have too
many squirrels. I can't do anything still. I could do this. What am I going to do with all these?
All right. No. Use them as tanks. I can just do that. Yeah, that's over. How many levels are in
the game? Like how many areas? How many bosses are in the game? 20? When do you, how do you like
four? It's complicated. Don't ask that question. Okay. Brutant pack rat never dealt the utility
of a well-stocked pack. When a card bearing this is played, you will receive a random item as long
as your pack is not full. It seems broken. I just get an item every time I play the card.
All right. This is the last one I'm going to show. This is the last one I'm going to show.
I'm not showing anymore. Let's be very clear. This is the last one that we're going to show.
No more after this one. Yes. It's the funniest movie of the year. Let me think. The air grew thick
with void. All right. This is the, the angler. Wetlands. Pinky black mouth of a cave. Strange
beast lurked within. Spoke past one of my, did anybody have one? I did that like two years ago.
The clip of the, it's the funniest movie of the year. That was a joke we did, right?
Anybody have that clip? It was like a Bernie Sanders political ad, right?
Nobody cared enough. I thought that, I thought that was a great one. Pass one of my trials and
I'll be yours in a raspy voice. Three creatures will be drawn from your deck. They will decide
your success or failure, but first you will choose a trial. Trial of bones. The three drawn cards
must cost at least five bones combined to pass. Three drawn cards must have at least six health
combined to pass or at least three sigils among them to pass. We got it right here. Bernie approves
this message. Funniest movie of the year. Is this it? Sanders and I approve this message. My name
is Bernie Sanders and I approve this message. It's the funniest movie of the year. Critics
at Bernie Sanders are saying it's the best movie in February. Sonic the Hedgehog. Pretty PG.
Yeah, that's pretty funny. I like that was funny. What's wrong with that? All right. It's probably
health. I'm going to say health or sigils and I have like five. Every single one of my cards has
a sigil, doesn't it? I think it's I'm doing this one. I did it twice. How many times did I do that?
Hold on. There's a different one. It's the funniest movie of the year. That's not the same. Critics
are saying it's the best VR game of 2020. I've done that. Whatever. It's a funny routine. That's
a funny routine. I don't care. I think I'll do it again too. Got it. So what do I get for this?
Um, this is what is this? When a car, but this is so I get four bones and this dies
and it's got quills. This is underwater. So it's like stealth. That's actually kind of amazing,
but eight bones. Oh, that's way too much. Or copies comes back when it dies and it has that.
That one's not that great. I picked one of these two. Probably this one. Eight bones. When am I
ever going to have eight bones? I'm going to pick this one. Hmm. The amount of items you can carry
is three. And do you have three? Instead, perhaps you'll accept this gift from my friend.
Another pack rat? All right. All right. That's looking pretty good. I got two of these. Dude,
you fell off. You were using old jokes. I didn't, I just was remembering an old one. Okay. So this
is, so I might as well just use something, right? Because if I get an item, I might as well use
something. What does this one do again? No, I want, book one of my cards and take it as your own.
I'm not going to use the knife. That's probably going to come in handy later. I don't think I'm
going to use that. The knife, but the squirrel, probably the squirrel. Cause what the fuck? Who
cares? I have so many infinite squirrels. Yeah. What am I going to do with that? Here you go. Now
let's play and check this out. Ready? Watch this. This is something fucking crazy. I'll show you
right now. Bingo. Done. Flyers. Done. That's fine. I want you to kill it anyways. One, three. This
spot. You sure? Yeah. Don't question me. This is okay. This is fine. This is fine. This is fine.
I'll kill that. Okay. No, sorry. That'll die. This won't get killed next turn. And then, oh,
I just win. I think, oh, I just win in a minute. I was rip a tooth out and just get another, um,
I think I fucked it up. Okay. Uh, I think I just have to go. All right. How can I kill now?
Stink bug is one, two. I will kill that. Pack rat. I really want that stump to die. Oh, there we go.
Okay. Game over. But should I, I'm going to get an item first. Oh, who cares? Just fucking win.
Just one. Yeah. Who gives a shit? Who gives a shit, right? Yeah. Who gives a shit? Wait, who gives
a shit, right? Whatever. Who gives a shit? I win. I don't want a bullfrog. I don't know if I want
that. Ooh, I'll take this one. Mushroom land. Thick and pungent mushrooms. You squint to see a figure
through a thick cloud of spores. We are the mysologists. Yes. And we are performing our
experiments far from. We are not welcome elsewhere. We will experiment on your flock. Yes. We will need
two of the same creature. I have two pack rats. This could get messy. Look away. Oh, that's pretty
huge. That's a big deal. I'll take it. Does the sigil stack? That would be amazing if it did. I
don't know. All right. We've got B. These are going to fly over me, so it doesn't matter. I'll put
out here. We'll go blink and doesn't really matter. So the blink. It's fine. All right. Pack this up.
Oops. Fuck. I think I screwed this up. I'm in a lot of trouble now. I need to do. I'm just so bad
with like placement and like thinking two, three turns ahead in games like these. There's no car I
can just drive into like a wall. You know what I mean? Like I have trouble with these. Stink bug
is going to drop down. Put the stink bug here, right? Because then if this take this can't do
anything, I might just be dead. I think I just lose. I'd have to use the knife. Yeah, I have to.
Okay. Now it's sold. Oh, I fucked it up. I whatever. It doesn't matter. I just I have so much
trouble like thinking two or three turns ahead and like, I don't know. ADHD is just like, well,
what do these do again? I don't remember. All right. Okay. If I get hit one more time,
it's over. That's two. I pull another squirrel hook something just too many, too many options
for my brain to focus on. Use the rat. Yeah, but I just okay. I wish I could just like pull the
camera out. You know what I mean? I wish I could see my hand and the board at the same time. So
I wonder if I should. Okay. I got to make a fucking play here. I get to sit here. I can't
just hit her and cycle menus. This is to if I go bang, I'm going to pull a squirrel. Fuck it.
Whatever. I'm going to die anyways. Oh, squirrel bang bang. That'll kill this whole row and then
see what happens. I guess. Oh shit. It's going to went over right. Oh, fuck. It's not much
trouble. What's this new item? I just want to look over there. I don't know to do. I could fishing
hook the which I fishing at the stump or the be D to look at items or damage. Yeah, but is it going
to? All right, let's go. I don't think I do anything. I'm kind of screwed because I can't
get rid of those squirrels. I could use this here. All right, I'm going to try. I'm going to go for
this. I draw this. All right, Wolf 32. I can't remove this shit. I think that's going to do it.
Yeah. Yeah, I just my brain is so much trouble. Just so I never play games like this because it's
like I just get lost looking at like the cards and then I go. Wait, I don't even know what to do.
Let's take this one. Happy with that one. Find salvation. Cuckoo clock. I didn't already do
the clock. I did the clock already bugs. Take the film roll before he sees it now. What are you
doing over there? He's self gaslighting. I just you give me a dodge roll and I'll fucking beat
that game. All right, I got film for the camera. So does it mean can I take a picture of him now?
He's gaslighting himself. Don't look around some more. One. What is this for? Oh my God, that's
fucking weird. I did that. Is the eyes turning on do anything? Does this mean anything to do the
game board puzzles? I did all of them already. I did them all. I already because this there was
a card here before. I don't know what it was. I keep going. I think I have full items.
So let's go this way. Move with a certain figure in spite of her considerable age. Yeah. So this
is this I don't want to do anything about this, right? Keep the squirrel. Yeah, I don't really
want to. I guess I could have gone to the backpack. Fix the squirrel. I'll keep the squirrel head
though. Is it bug build? The squirrel I think is fucking me up. I keep putting out too many and
then I just like I get like overwhelmed with what I need to do next turn. Maybe I should try the
bug. You'll get used to it. You need two cost cards in your deck. I'll try. I'll keep it.
Let me try the bug. I'm just curious what this does. I have like a yeah I'm gonna try. I have a
ton of bugs. Half my deck is bugs. Let me try it. I can always put it back on, right? I oughta thank
you. How has it been? It has been what is going on with this guy? I'm trapped in the body of a stote
in the paper of a card. I see that and I have of course set up a way to reset once more. Go on.
A player friend here. They already hold the key. What are they? What are they turning into? Like a
tv. Okay ants. Just gotta be careful. The number of ants is a problem. Let's go this way. What does
this do? Just this is 2-2. This will kill this if I I'm gonna put it here. Here we are. Yeah this
would have killed it. So I mean I gotta get hurt but oh god. Maybe that was a bad idea. Oh yeah yay.
I gotta hook something. I think I have to otherwise I'm just gonna lose right now. What should I pull?
One of the ants? No. Skink probably. Why did everybody want me to do the ringworm? Doesn't work
like this. It only pulls the front one. Oh I'll take one of the ants because now this will live
forever technically. So wait can I I can sacrifice that now like this right? This is correct right?
Tell me I'm tell me I'm a good boy. Tell me I'm a good boy. Okay I found the stunted wolf. I've seen
this play out enough times to know that plan is in motion. Make haste. You're oh you're a bug right?
This will clear all this. I think I just win. Pretty sure this is just a win right now. I think
so. Is it right? One more. You're such a good boy. This was cool. I'll do this one again. Oh you've
been such a good boy this year. Everything has a sigil right? So three drawn cards must be.
Every card I have is a sigil. Your scare cam is blocking the text. What's a good place to put the
camera then? What? Oh I passed. This is always three blood and it okay that beehive. This is never
going to attack right? This doesn't attack. It has no attack right? These all stink. I would pick this
one. Four bones. This one's not bad but bad roll. So if this attacks will it actually because this
these things don't attack because it's not gonna hurt anything. Does it actually just have to
physically move or does it actually actually have to hurt something? You could sacrifice this one.
I'll take it for the bugs. Oh you can't use that. What the hell is this? What? This bottle of goo
has no use. All right angler time let's go. Huge man approached. Go fish. You guys use it? I'm
serious you cannot use that. There's no possible use for it. I'll place it on that shelf over there
for now. I need my advice avoided. Oh oh oh it's oh shit I'm an idiot. No oh it's fucking nice drop.
I can't play this game. I would have done whatever. Fuck. Shit. If I had gone this way it would have
I would have had four teeth land. Ah whatever. All right it'll do the damage fine. One two three four.
I can't really do anything. I can put a squirrel here. I think I just have to go right? Oh I can
sacrifice that. I didn't think I could. I thought I had to get killed. Okay I didn't know I could
sacrifice it. I didn't think it was an actual. I thought sacrifice. This is so loud I need to turn
this down so I can hear myself think. Um I thought I didn't think this was like a thing to sacrifice.
Okay so I'm gonna put the adder over here and that'll kill that. All right I'm back in business.
Take this stupid squirrel. Come on. Thank god. He's I'm not I'm not panicking. I'm not panicking. I'm
all right. I'll turn it up for you. I just don't want to hear it. I'm kind of in trouble here.
I should go put him here. Oh where I? What the hell is in here? Okay this is frozen away. Will
this help me here? Okay so if I put that in front of one of these guys here that'll block and then
come back to life? Could I sacrifice this now? Would that be stupid? All right well
I don't know. I have to pull a tooth. Save your head on stream? I don't think so. See what happens.
Okay now let's scroll down. Sacrifice squirrel and the frozen thing and then I can use this and
that'll kill it. That's right. Wolf then fan. Okay so now I go squirrel mantis and then bang
I win. Does it matter where I put this guy? Right here and then that's free. Do I need to use the fan?
I think it'll just work right? Do I have to use the fan? Fan. Yo let's go! See I just need like to look
over it have you guys play the game for me because I can't fucking do this. We're good.
Oh we got a we got a Gek. I always take the Gek always every time. This game is really fun. I think
it's a good game. My brain just okay what here's the thing when I'm streaming my brain is going in
two different directions. This is the type of game that I would like be on the toilet and just be
like and each turn I get to sit there for like fucking 15 minutes. If I sit here for 15 minutes
and just go like this then like people are going to be like what's wrong with his brain? Is he
all right? What is he? Hello is he alive? What's he doing? Why is it taking him so long? I would
sit there like this and I would like get up and eat a sandwich probably halfway through one of
these. I think it's great. I love this but when I'm streaming like it's my brain is like operating
in two different places. All right we're back in the snow. Let me at least beat this part. Oh move
the camera right. Sorry we do a sweat check. No it's like yellow under there. No it's not. Shut up.
It's not. I'm kidding. It's a joke. I actually am sweating. I'm fucking kidding. It's not. Look see
see it's a joke. It's the light. I have a yellow light burning down on me. It's not. I have a
yellow light right here. Look you see. Look at it's yellow right there. Yeah this is this is this is
like this. Is this on iPad? No. Oh this thing is ridiculous so I'm taking this. It's coming to
switch soon. Oh that's awesome. All right health. I mean nine health. Oh I gotta let. Hold on. I
gotta talk about what's going on tomorrow. Tomorrow we are going. Just because there's a lot of people
here. Tomorrow we are going to be playing Elden Ring PVP. Tomorrow is very important. I'm not
ending this. The stream's not over yet. Elden Ring PVP with the intention of finding my champions
because Ludwig and I are doing a 1v1 community versus community trial by combat night. He's
look he's got his own shit. He's got his own shit going. He's got his own community to worry about
right. He's gonna find the community kind of champions there. I'm picking mine tomorrow and
we use rivers of blood. Now that's a good question. We're probably gonna we're probably going to I
would assume maybe we'll ban a few items. We'll find out. We have to have some rules. We're not
sure what those rules are yet. What's the rune level? We'll figure that out in the next day or
so. Let's have a ban list. But tomorrow we're gonna mess around again. That was so much fun
just doing PVP invasion night. I want to do it again. I had a lot of fun doing it. It was awesome.
But the biggest intention tomorrow is to find who I want as my champions.
We're later on probably this coming week. This weekend. I'm really tired and want to go to bed.
I'm not going to go that long tonight. And if you want to know am I going to play this again?
Yeah. Yeah. Am I am I capable of playing this again? You think so? I really like it but I have
trouble. I have a lot of trouble. Maybe you guys can help me. Maybe you guys can help me play it.
All right. What do I want plus two health? I love the concept of this game. I love it.
Am I just my brain is cross-eyed when I play a game like this. It's really as good as a good game.
No. I mean it is. This is awesome. I love the art. I love the lore. I love the atmosphere.
If you guys can help me. I don't care about that. Right. Whatever. All right. I was thinking moose
buck or or geck. I'm sorry. I'm so scatterbrained. I just you know what I just my brain has so much
trouble sitting here and like doing this. So if you came here looking for a you know like oh I
I won't come on like why the fuck can't you do this? I apologize. I'm sorry. I hope it's like
fun. I'm having fun. I hope you're having fun. My brain is just can't like focus. It's stupid.
Okay. We're good. Okay. So what's the what's the stipulation here? Thorns. Okay. Cool. Yeah.
Ooh. Right off the bat. Over on the right. What do you think? I know exactly how you feel. You're
doing better than I did. Yeah. I know. I know sometimes I'm concerned about being an absolute
like idiot in the game and people just sit here calling like dude what the fuck are you doing man?
I'm gonna say all the way to the right and then a squirrel and then we go is your first try.
Yeah. I know. I'm just having fun. I'm just having fun. I just really don't want people to
think um oh do I really care about being like an idiot? I don't know. I literally like ate bubble
soap two days ago. I'm concerned about looking stupid in a video game. Oh really? Uh what? All
right. Here we go. I'm bringing out the uh I'm bringing out the moose. No. Bring out the wolf.
Shit. I don't know. Should I put them? Oh that hurts a lot. Thankfully it moved over there
though. Okay. Fuck that hurt. I need the moose. Do I live? If I don't I think I live one more time.
I don't know what to do. Grab another squirrel next turn. Oh actually I'm not this is okay.
Okay this is all right. This is not bad. So now I can sacrafo- oh I think I'm dead. Game over Andy.
Okay well whatever. Let's just uh just kill me. I lose anyways. Do I live one more turn? No.
Yeah I just lose. I want to at least see the other boss right? Do I even have any
health? Oh I know. Okay. That's it. I don't want anymore. I look around the room. No I have I have
I've done um a lot of stuff I could do so far right? Yeah let's just I did the clock. I did
the little minigames here. I did the sword, the dagger right? Took that and I did all that. Yeah
oh wait a minute this is the goo right? Keep sealed. Pain is unbearable even after all these
years. What do you want? I have very little to live for these days. You have the master's eye.
Does this mean the master can see me? Magnificus. Can you see me? Can you free me? It is done.
Master is free. Well the end must be close now. If Magnificus is free it must be close.
Watching the angler lose now that soothed my pain. An old rival of mine that fisherman. He
bested me this time but I will have another chance. Oh I see you have a little something
special up your sleeve. Fear not I won't blow your cover. You just need to get a hold of that
camera of his. Maybe if you defeated him you would get a chance. So I have to like beat the game and
then take a picture of him. Interesting. Very interesting. I want more buffs. Plus two health.
Echo again. One five or adder. I'm gonna do adder. I feel like that's very useful. All right I did it.
I bite my lip and I don't want people to see. Bad habit. All right squirrel, mantis. Seems like a
good idea. And then bullfrog. Is that a stupid idea? All right okay I got it. Bingo. Porcupine
going in. Um which will give me the bones to put Reginald to kill this. Then this can go here.
Then you will kill that. Then I will take one tooth worth of damage. Now I kind of need a squirrel
and then hit the pass button. All right okay. Okay now. Oh that's too bad. Do I keep Reginald there
and just pass? I think so. I think I'm all right. Okay all right now that kills that. Let me take a
look at the board. This kills this. This is gonna just hit that. There'll be another one of these
coming down. Oh okay. This is gonna swing. This is gonna come down and hit and then go over here.
So I'll put the adder here. Eventually this kills that. This stays here. This is gonna move down.
I put the adder here but I can't really do that yet so I'm gonna pass again. Confirm. Confirm.
Confirm with me. Confirm. Adder kills rock. And now I got two squirrels. Adder. Bang. Bang. Good.
Another squirrel. We're good. Very nice. Because that was gonna bounce over here.
Okay grab another squirrel. So Wolf will kill that. Hold on a second. I want to place this right now
and then we go boink boink. Because then that'll move down here right? That didn't do what I
thought it was gonna do. I think I win. That is it. Game over. Game over. I win. See? I am smart.
See? There's something in there. It's not empty. It's watch. Apparently it's made out of metal.
Hold on. Can I make it like sound hollow? I'm smart. Me smart. All right show me some pelts.
Okay. Raven egg. That's new. Goat seems good. Just beaver. Sounds kind of good too.
Gross. Raven egg. Okay this is important. Mantis god. I don't even care about the others. I want
that one. Okay. I want to put the mantis god up there and I want to give the mantis god something
crazy. Oh my god. Adder. Boom. Yeah. Adder for sure. I did the wrong way? No I didn't. Is this
not backwards? Is it backwards? No it's not. This is the thing that you're sacrificing. The thing up
top. I'm good. Yeah it's not backwards. You just made me freak out. All right we're doing Adder.
This is gonna be amazing. There's only one health glob. Wow. That's really cool. Okay let's see.
I hope I get it. These are gonna turn into something crazy. I mean I'm gonna put that out
here. Okay. Um I can't do anything really. I could. Oh wait. Hold on. Wait. Wait. This comes back.
So I sacrifice. Put the wolf here. So it'll kill that and do up there. Okay. Nice. Yo what the
fuck? Wait. Wait. What the fuck happened? What? I died instantly. Oh my god. What happened? Crap.
Oh that's so sad. I thought I was fine. The fly. Yeah the fly. But I thought I didn't think I was
gonna die in one turn. Shit. Okay one cost. They're all one. Doesn't matter. Power and health.
Gonna be this. Sigils. I mean yeah mantis god. God. Hey chapstick boy. How are your lips? Thanks
for the reminder. Yeah we're not gonna start at six o'clock. What are you looking at? Keep your eyes
on me. That foul stunted wolf. You really want such a creature in your deck? The sight of it does try
my temper. But it has been dealt. So it stands. Don't forget to. Don't. Don't do that. What's this?
Different kind of choice. Choose not a specific beast. Decide the cost that you wish to pay.
All right probably one. Lewis. A weird card. Stealth and moves around. I feel like that's kind of
pain in the ass. You're kidding me. I've been typing chapstick chaps in chat for months and
nobody else does it. Oh when when this is the worst card ever. I think it's gonna be you.
Chapstick. I keep running into these. I gotta take a look at the map before I do this.
Okay um. Defeat him first. Two four. Holy shit. I'm gonna put you over here. No I just woke up from
that. I'm sorry. He's still in act one? Dude. I don't. I know. But whatever. I'm having a good
time. Who cares? Somebody said it was gonna take him 10 hours to get out of act one. He hates this
game? No I do not. Who said that? I think this is fun. I did not say it. I think this is really
genuinely cool. Okay so um. That'll kill that. I've got this defense here. So we're just gonna go
whack and then we're gonna go whack. We know when you hate something is when you growl at us.
I don't have enough money. All right so I did that for a little while. Thinking about going back to
squirrel. Like all squirrels have flight? Oops that was not good. That's not what I wanted.
Squirrels can't even attack man. Oh great. Good idea. It's all right. We're good. We're good. It's
gonna be fine. Why did that not work? And we have to use Lois. Ow. Oh what a perfect draw. I want to
do this again so bad. All right you suck. I'm putting you here instead. You have me here. I
surrender. Why would you do that? I'm losing. No. All right nice. I'll get you this next round.
I'm really good in act one. If you want a really good puzzle game just try The Witness.
I don't really like those kind of puzzles. I'm more into the puzzles that go like and they open
and stuff. That's my favorite. If a puzzle game has like a draw that opens like puzzle noises.
Yeah like escape rooms. You know okay. Does anybody here want a multi-billion dollar idea?
I'll give it to you. I have a multi-trillion dollar idea. Good luck whoever wants to do it because
like I'm not gonna do it but I'll give it to you. I just want five percent of every sale. So I made
it up. So I will tell you right now I want five percent of all your sales. Have an escape room.
That's not an escape room. It is just a huge box that has all the like kind of box puzzle game
shit. Like you know the box inside of the box that has like the key. You have to twist like the bottom
that pulls out the little thing that has to go into the slot that's on top. Which then the whole
thing opens up and there's a big thing in here that you have to figure out. A huge puzzle box.
That's not a toy store. It's yeah the room. The room but real. Actually make it. And the thing
takes like three hours to complete. So the thing starts as like a cube. Right? A huge cube that's
a big wooden box and there's a padlock on the left of it underneath. And it's like okay what's that?
Well there's a little device over here that you have to look at that'll give you those three
numbers. When you do the three numbers in the padlock that thing opens. Like a little tray comes
out and there's a key in there. You take the key out. There's a keyhole that's on top of the box.
You stick it in. Open the top of the box. Inside of that comes up pops up another big puzzle.
Every time I played a game like The Room I go my god I wish I could I would I would pay an
exorbitant amount of money to do this in real life. An escape room that's not an escape room.
An escape room that's condensed inside of a gigantic like three hour puzzle box. And this
thing could be four three four five feet tall and like five feet wide. That's what an escape room is.
No escape room is like all spread out. I'm talking condensed in like go play The Room and you know
what I'm talking about. There's a billion dollar idea. Five percent of every sale thank you.
Oh by the way if you don't if I don't get five percent of sale. Oh god lawyers.
You'd be in trouble. I'm gonna take Reginald. Your pack was full so give me something cool.
This is worth just going here with full um full items. Why not? Wouldn't The Room just get five
percent? Imagine you made like a puzzle box thing and I heard about it. And I mean that's not like
that that's like that's an idea that probably everybody's probably thought of. And I'm like
demanding five percent. I said on my stream that a big puzzle box was a good idea. Yeah you know
what's had this great idea? Jeffrey the giraffe from Toys R Us. He has a whole store full of them.
You guys know who Jeffrey the giraffe is? I don't want to grow up. I'm a Toys R Us kid.
I always want to be a Toys R Us kid. Now that those commercials would have been really funny
if they got like a 50 year old guy to do it right. Because like I don't want to grow up.
I'm never going to grow up. I'm a Toys R Us kid. And the guy's like 50 like dancing around the
store brainwashing. I don't want to grow up. I'm a Toys R Us kid. That would be like kind of
fucked up. I don't yeah that wouldn't be all right. That guy no but they said that it was like I don't
ever want I'm never going to grow up. I'm a Toys R Us kid forever. I don't want to grow up. I'm part
of the Drew crew. Yeah and he's like he's like kind of like in his 50s you know he's like acid
reflux. I don't want to grow up. I'll always be a Toys R Us kid. That's how the commercial ends.
His like stomach goes up a little. He's got like a hot dog in one of his hands. All right Reginald I
want you to kill. What's wrong with this guy? I just fucking lost the game again didn't I? No I
didn't. Back right. Do I have three items? All right let me see the items. I don't look over this
way. Whatever dude I want to open up the squirrel thing. That's two. I need to go bang bang. I
actually don't need to use it yet but I might. Whatever I'm an idiot. Your puke noises are so
gross. This is a terrible play. I should have just opened up the fucking thing. What happens if I
I pull this back. Cancel this so I can break this. I don't I I mean I thought I could pull it back
for a second. I always want to be a Toys R Us. Okay I'm done. I'm done. I'll see you tomorrow.
I'm done. I'll see you tomorrow. I'm out of here. You know that I have a video of me with no shirt
on that I recorded like 10 of these on my phone and it's me board facing the camera like board
facing this way with no shirt on. It looks like I have a huge fat stomach and it's me saying that
I was gonna try out to be the next Armin for Attack on Titan and at the end I go like Aaron
Aaron run away and then I go and when I do that I fart in real life and just Holly just starts
laughing her ass off. Um the video is fucking crazy. It's like I went like too much. I went like too
hard and you just hear Holly start laughing. Will you ever show that? Maybe. Maybe one day.
Maybe one day. Maybe one day you'll see. Ooh one day maybe you'll see it. Randomly one day maybe
I'll just be like you know who cares. I don't even give a shit who gives a fuck. You can't say that
and not show it. Yeah well just maybe one day I'll fucking put it up. Make it a main channel vid.
At least do the audio. You know I could I could do the audio and I would also probably yeah okay
maybe. I've recorded here's the thing I recorded maybe 10 of them so there's like 10 versions of
this. I really think a lot of people think I'm making this up when I say that I will just sit
there and just do something like that over and over again and just I don't know I said maybe
something wrong with me. I don't know. I fell asleep two days ago to a like seven or eight
hour Kathy Mitchell playlist of various like infomercials and her showing cooking food and
stuff. It's like it's like better than television to me. The like eight hour Kathy Mitchell playlist
is more entertaining to me than like Mad Men. I don't I don't know why. I don't know I don't
understand why. Imagine picking Bird with like that would be stupid. You just say things. I mean
I I I don't know and no I didn't guys. I gotta be clear. I don't I didn't fart 10 times in a row.
I just on like the seventh or eighth one. It was like this did I want to leak this so bad.
It's an idea and I want to leak it but I kind of I can't because if I ever actually get to do it
because what if it doesn't happen then maybe maybe you'll never know. Not this. I'm talking
about something else. No I'm not going to leak it. I'm not going to leak this thing I'm talking
about because if it actually happens it's going to be my favorite stream I've ever done in my
whole life. Nothing will ever compare. Ever. If I can get it to work. I don't know if I can.
I don't want to build excitement for it but it'll be it'll be the best thing.
Nothing will ever compare. It'll be better than dollhouse. At least from me it will.
From me it will. Okay wait wait wait. I actually think I'm just going to use this here.
Egomaniac thinks about himself only. Not always. Maybe leak in two years. Okay so let's go. I need
something to kill that. Five two. Exactly what I wanted. Okay this will kill that now. Dude what
the hell's going on? How am I? Break this fucking thing please. This is okay. Elk with flight.
Throw us the fart video. I will. I will show it to you. One of these days. I'll show it to you.
I will. One two. I mean this whatever. Ow. This thing's stupid. What does this do?
I don't want this boulder. Sucks. Two four. I'm going to replace you here I think. Yeah then
I'll save the rest for now. Go ahead and knock this all out. Out of the face. I think I'm
still fine. I have a bunch of squirrels already. There we are. Okay just kill this stuff. All right
I need. Ackrat will kill this and then I can do cockroach. Wait wait wait wait wait wait wait.
Two. Mile please. Ah it hurts to do that. Um cockroaches what is it just dies
whenever you play it or something. So I gotta just put this out. I could do squirrel. I'm kind
of in trouble. What does this do again? Ackrat or should I do this? Ackrat. I just have to not die.
Fake fuck Andy? What? What are you talking about? What is this? Oh bones. Fake fuck Andy. Thank you.
Boss time man. It is. Get out there. Thank you. I almost lost. When will the fart leak? I don't
know. Maybe. I don't know. Maybe like. I don't know. Maybe somebody's birthday. Always. I like
this game a lot. What is this? Did I do this one yet? Whose birthday? That's for me to decide.
I was the pelt one. Okay. Orbs maggots? The creature that you own perishes by combat. A
carb bearing is automatically played in its place. Another wolf would be good. Or uh mantis. I feel
like I don't have a lot of damage. Leak it if you lose your trial by combat community knight.
The Ludwig. No because the people that get picked will just throw so they get to see like the
leaked fart video. I'm gonna do the wolf. I need damage. I need like more than. Everything I have
is like one. Leak it if you win. Maybe I'll leak a screenshot of I win maybe. I'm not gonna. I'm.
It's a video. Yeah. I told you. I'm lying in a bed. Aiming it up like this. Like the camera's
facing this way and I make it so I'm like filling the whole frame. I look huge. I don't know why
I was doing it. It's fucking horrible. All right we're going uh. I don't want to do the kick.
Atrioc. Big A. Welcome everybody. I'm playing uh inscription. Thanks for the raid. Hope you had a
good stream Atrioc. I'm doing really well in this card game. I've gotten past the second boss. I've
gotten to the third area. Almost at the end of the game. I'm doing very well. No one said anything
uh about how poorly I'm playing the game. Another raid? There's not two raids in a row right?
No. Okay well that's. There's a lot of. There's like two three raids today. Thank you. Appreciate
it. Well let's go. We're playing inscription. I can't say I'm gonna be live for that much longer.
Maybe like when I get to the end of this run. All right let's go. You don't know how to play
inscription. Um neither do I. So I can't really explain it to you because I'm not the person to
ask. All right uh I'm doing gecko over here on the right. And let's go. What should I do now?
All right I got squirrel. This is gonna be perfect. Squirrel squirrel. Bang bang. Hold on a minute
though. I'm not gonna kill that. Might be Dumbo. I don't know whatever. I'm just going for the win
as fast as I can. Remember is there a penalty? For what? Dr. Oldker raid? No way. That's crazy.
Dr. Oldker's been dead since like 1850. That's really crazy. I can't believe he's raiding.
He's here right now? Holy crap. Uh I don't want to kill. Give me another pack wrap. Pack wrap. Pack
wrap. Pack wrap. Pack wrap. Did you hear about Joel's shit talking? Dr. Dr. Oldker's pizza?
No right? That's gotta be it. That's gotta be fake right? No no no. He would never. What do you
know? No way. That's fake news. Hold on give me one second. Just typing. It's in mod chat.
All right squirrel uh putting the gecko out obviously. Obviously. Will this kill me if I
put it here? All right if I put this here it's gonna be the next turn I'm done right? If I put
the the gecko there it will die next turn right? Oh they said they all have flying. Okay all right
well then I'm putting it here. Let's go by the way. Yes. No Lois is bad. Raids. Raids. Raids. Yeah a
lot of raids. Did I just lose? What the fuck is that? I actually just lost. What just happened? I
just threw. I'm not in my element. I'm not sitting on a toilet or lying on my back in bed at four
o'clock in the morning. I'm not in my element right now with a game like this. I am gonna take this
because I feel like everything's dying so quickly I need something to take hits. Power. All right
what do I want? All right pack rat. I love using the pack rat so I'm gonna or the yeah gecko too.
Yeah always. Always. He has to. No I'm just saying I'm usually I'm in my element more when I'm
lying on my back like this. Okay taunted wolf is actually really good. Okay so now I'm gonna go
this way. Let's go. These are gross sex jokes? What are you talking about? When do they make a sex
joke? What do you mean? When did I do that? I didn't do that. These are gross sex jokes. Dude no. All
right I do this IRL. I do that all the time. I don't have to do it now. What do I have for items?
Okay I'm gonna use the cat bone thing over here. Your adversary will entirely skip their next turn.
Yeah fuck you. B is free right? Yep. Now can I at least kill the the fisherman again? Why are you
so dirty today? I'm not dirty ever. I just look dirty because this thing is the sun is shining on
my face. It's right there and it's just glistening off all the face oil that I have. Do the same. I
do. All right it's 11 a.m here. Yeah we're not gonna go much longer. This is my last run and then again
tomorrow don't forget write it down if you have to. Tomorrow is Elden Ring PvP community tryout
night to see who has what it takes to take on Ludwig's community in the community champion night
when I decide who's gonna be my community champion or the stream where we fight each other.
Sorry. All right I'm not fucking this one up. This is it. I keep messing this one up and I'm
an idiot for doing it. Yes it does. I'm gonna save this. Okay let's go. It's fine.
Then okay don't screw this up. I already did didn't I? No I didn't because now I play this pelt.
Take pelt and then good. Close the pelt. All right and then I play stink bug here right off the bat.
All right good nice top deck. It actually uh for real you're right. There we go. We go here. All
right let's do it. That's round one right? One more. Yeah that's it. That's it. Round two. Go fish.
This is the part that sucks. Huge. Very very good. Very good. Very good. Very good. Very good.
Actual awesome. Awesome. Awesome. Awesome. Do it. Oh stabbed my arm. Oh fuck. I'm in. Did I have
the knife? I forgot. Do I even have the knife? It was oh my god. I forgot it even existed.
I forgot it. It was like blending in and hiding back here. Give me this fucking thing. No fuck.
What do I do? Um I have to do it and then I can put this section might be okay. So if I do that's
four five six seven. I think that's a win right there. Yeah that's a win. I got it. Thank god.
I almost just blew it. My god man. I seriously almost blew it. I just whatever. Long elk amoeba
or two. What is long elk? Weird. I like this one. Three three two. Safe. Please replace the eye.
This one. Take the glowy one. Does it matter? I thought that was just like a funny little thing.
Did that matter? The eyes matter. I didn't know that. All right can I get to the at least past
the third boss or add to the third boss? Didn't I pick it before? I thought I already clicked it.
Whoa expensive though. It just can die. It's just kind of like tanky. Well let's go get the item.
Another knife. Knife is really helpful. I mean this was awesome too. I'm picking up. And I guess
I'm a fan. Pretty good items. Not bad. Okay you have flight. I just hit this. Echo always goes out
always no matter what. This is zero four so that's fine. Keep you here. And I got stunted wolf too.
Stunted wolf will. Maybe I just have stunted wolf kill this. Just be hitting this. Of course I have
him over here. Eventually it'll kill that. Yeah. Oh it's gonna fly over you. Okay cool.
I'm just gonna pass. Um I think I just lost. Did I just lose? Did I? If I take the knife and then
pack rat before kill. No I have to sacrifice this. Don't use items. I have lives. Yeah. Could I have
played that better? I feel like I did everything correct. Wolf will kill the bird. Yeah I'm just
gonna pass again. Then I guess I should. Am I okay? I think I'm okay. Am I dead? Not yet. This is.
All right yeah I'm fine. I'm kind of scared there. I need to use something. I'm gonna try to use the
knife. This pack rat's gonna come out and it's gonna be wasted. Use the fan instead of the knife.
Okay and this pack rat in here. That will kill that. That will. I think that yeah that's it. He
wasted the fan. I can't. I just want to replace it. I don't like these. They're too hard. I'm going
this way. I'll take a two. What's this do again? This deletes one and gives me um. What's this do?
I'm deleting Lois. This card's awful. This card's awful. I'm getting there a little bit longer.
See if I can at least get to the boss. I'll be happy. I mean put the geck over here. That's all
I can really do right now. Is your face cam too small? All right that's gonna be. All right so
I'm gonna rip a tooth out and then pack rat and then kill this fucking thing. Oy! Oh that's it.
Oh my goodness. I'm so. I was trying to be so confidently correct but I don't know. Whatever.
ADHD brain. Yeah dude check this out. Okay this is gonna be like a 6-6. This thing is gonna be
insane. Get me up there. All right don't quit absolutely squirt. Just quit squirring around.
I've got it. It's a 6-6. I gotta take this shit out now. I don't care about the fawn. I got the
rabbit. So we're gonna go squirrel. The rabbit does. Whenever this is played I get a rabbit in
my hand. So we're gonna. Oh eat shit. I win. I'm not gonna use this yet. I just beat him one turn.
Raven. Okay let's make pack rat even better. If I get pack rat flight I could win games in one
turn. That's what I'm doing. But I have to get rid of the raven. I just got it. I'll go for it.
This is a 6-6 flying pack rat. See if it helps. I feel like it's gonna be all right. I'm at the
boss. The man stood before you. A man you recognize immediately. It was the trapper. He reached out
to examine his wares but he stopped you. All right but today you will supply the pelts. So this okay
it's just crap. When a card bearing the sigil perishes the creature opposing it perishes as
well. You don't want to kill that. Like you want some shitty thing to kill that. All right there it
is. There it is. So I want to use the rabbit and then I'll get. I got another raid. Criken coming in
with a raid. I got this with so many raids. What's going on? Thanks Criken. Welcome everybody.
Playing um inscription and I'm about to beat the guy in one turn because now I can do this.
I'm gonna kill him in one turn. Okay now what? I'm gonna beat him in one second.
Cycle must continue. Let's trade. Powerful cards. I will accept only the finest pelts for them.
Okay. Great for what you can but know this. The rest will stay and fight for me. That's fine. I'm
just gonna fly over you and kill you in one hit. So I have to pick a card. Please read. Take the
wolf. Take his big health cards. Like the grizzly. I still win. No I still win. Take the bloodhound.
Oh that blocks me. You're right. Okay who else do I want? And the grizzly. Or the raven. Yep raven.
Raven. Okay I kill him in one hit. I'm done. Yeah I win. Goodbye. Just end turn. It's over.
Come on. I didn't do anything. Need a light? GG. And you know I'm taking another pack rat. You
understand? I'm gonna upgrade it again. You can see a light in the distance. The end is near.
Let me see. Please pay attention. All right. What do I want to do here? What's better? Probably the
merge one. Wait is this the merge one? No it's not. It's pelts. I'm so nervous. All right. Who's going
in here? Who should I put in there? Pack rat? Buff the rat. Maybe one of these? Or the stinky one?
Oh no no no no no. Yep that's an amazing thing I'm gonna do right now.
Gecko. Holy shit this is huge. Absolutely unbelievably unequivocally, equivocally huge.
So this I'm at the I'm at the I can fight this thing? I'm at the boss? Your eyes have fixed
themselves in the small cabin. It's warm light a beacon in the oppressive darkness of the night.
Surely surely this cabin marked the end of your travels. You guys gonna have to help me. Just get
the fuck out of me. I like knew something might have happened too. You're presented with an
opportunity. I don't offer my boons to just any traveler. If you're able to pass my trials you
will be rewarded mightily. Trial of the swift. Redrawn cards must include a card with the
sprinter, waterborne, or they must be rare. Yeah I don't think I have. It's definitely this one.
One two three. Ah pack rat is a rare card. Success. I will grant you one of my most powerful boons.
Cards that dramatically alter the game and you don't even need to draw them.
Boon of the bone lord. You will start a battle with eight bones. Boon of the ambidextrous. You
may draw twice at the beginning of your turn. Boon of the forest. You will start a battle with grand
urs on all your spaces. I feel like draw twice is just like that's a I don't know if anything
these are the tanky things that stay in front and this is a shitload of bones. I'm taking this one
and draw twice. We will repeat that once more. The trial of skins. The three drawn cards must
include a pelt card. No. Airborne. I have a few of those. If you have a ring you pass automatically.
Look at the table. 11 o'clock. What does that mean? 11. I don't think do I I don't have a ring.
I'm gonna it has to be airborne. What's he doing? You managed to get a boon. This may be a fair
competition. He's gonna scream at me. I'm ready. What the fuck? You took your time out there.
And I'm itching for another game. Are you ready to play? I hope you are all adequately prepared.
Perhaps one more to be safe. That's not fair. Shit. What do you got? Okay mole man. Okay I can do
whorl smoke right here right? Put stow down on the right because then it'll be one no. I don't want
to screw this up because that will hit. That should be correct. I think that's correct. And then should
I put the smoke pelt out just to get the bones and get it hit? I wonder where the bones should go.
All the way to the next door? Plug the lane with the pelt. Save it. Okay all right let's go. Okay
I'm like nervous. I'm gonna I feel like I'm gonna look like an idiot. Okay I have a rat king which
gives me bones. I have a lot of bone things but I don't know what this is gonna hit three times.
So we have to go like this. Draw. I can draw twice. Two squirrels and then go straight up here.
I have items too. Yeah nice. All right I don't want to get hit three times here. So I'm gonna go
squirrel, stunted wolf right down uh main street here. Wolf pelt here, smoke here. Got it? Oh my god
I have this thing. All right this is going all the way to the left. This is going all the way to the
left. It's gonna tank this damage. That's what I'm doing. And then the smoke is gonna go here um right.
Okay so let's do this and then pelt here. Let's go. Yeah let's go. What the fuck is he doing?
What is happening right now? Why is he doing this? I didn't what's he doing this? What the
fuck is going on? He didn't take another zero. What the hell just happened? Did he do that before
every turn? Oh my god it's over. Oh he's putting on the different masks.
That's not good. It's really bad. It's not over. Okay I think I just have to pass right? Or should
I put the squirrel down to not? I have to pass I think. Should I use the knife right now?
Or just block him with the smoke? God. Oh okay I have to frog. I have to knife. Knife hourglass.
Should I put the amalgam? Knife hourglass? Knife hourglass amalgam. Card cut. Oh I thought it was
a stab. Okay so I obviously want to kill the amalgam right? Or should I kill? This is going
to be three damage regardless right? Like this? Let him hook the squirrel. I know my health is
just I'm dead. What should I get rid of? This one here? The amalgam put bullcrab onto mantis god.
Yeah that's the play. I have another squirrel too. Dead man. Bullfrog. Oh but wait! Hourglass
hourglass hourglass. Alright I can do it. I can hourglass. Now you can't do shit? Now?
Um does that mean he won't do that? So now if I put the pelt down in front of this
will he still? Okay he will not hook right? Pelt down here. Squirrel. Um use the pelt here right?
Yeah. Stop reading chat. Dude I'm telling you I'm gonna fuck this whole thing up if I don't.
And then squirrel. Or it doesn't really matter right? And then pass. Squirrel down. Okay let's
go. Okay okay dude this is um got a squirrel. Um no what? Um don't play anything. Just don't okay
don't do anything. No I can't play this because he's gonna hook it right? I just have to pass.
What are you putting on now? Okay what's it what the mask is on? Okay I'm gonna draw
two times. It's gonna be I have one I have one squirrel. I can get amalgam and reginald down
this turn. And then should I do two squirrels or should I just draw for another card?
Fill both amalgams with reginald and your amalgam. Yeah it's gonna have to be it has to be two
squirrels right? Has to be. Squirrel brain draw for a pack rat. It's all right okay all right whoa
whoa whoa whoa whoa I need help somebody help me somebody help me I don't know what I'm doing
I don't know what I'm doing somebody help me I already said rip bozo all right I need
somebody's help help me help me what to do so this is I can't I cannot play these games
this is where I like get up and somebody else just sits down and I go yeah yeah oh yeah yeah yeah
yeah oh you move you put the squirrel over there yeah very cool nice nice nice nice very good
okay tech support amalgam and block all right so I here's what I'm telling you
squirrel squirrel amalgam reginald here that's what I'm doing I'm gonna go for it if you want
to scream we go scream and get here now go all right now what do I do this is gonna go up
this is gonna hurt me I need two squirrels rip bozo all right so I need to um world warren
just block stop reading bozo I'm gonna read I'm literally taking my eyes on here
world warren block and block here too yeah right here yeah yeah um definitely this thing I hope
that was not a bad idea say I look at how many fucking bones I have I got a whole graveyard over
here okay I can kill that I can wait if I hit this will it kill me but will I kill this thing
back here you win don't release this walk with walk skink with squirrel and kill amalgam
all right rattler on the right do not kill that you will die what rattler on the left
but what about this guy don't kill the skink oh come on what is it for fuck's sake dude I'm
just trying to look for help all right no more help if I lose it's my own fault here we go
how many rip bozos are in chat right now no he's okay don't do anything don't do anything don't
do anything rare creatures but the true challenge was forthcoming how do we figures appeared before
you and their eyes glimmered a recognition of kinship but colored by guilt they were betraying
you oh no not lois and reginald bad this is actually really bad rattler will kill reginald
but I only have one more squirrel in the whole deck sacrifice the rattler just draw for pack rat
oh no it's the wrong one that's gonna kill that this is gonna all right I'm gonna do
I'm gonna put this out it's free okay okay let's go okay okay let's go no what are you gonna do
chat saying a million different things I know man he's the prospector dude I don't know shit
that has to die okay um I think I get that and then I sacrifice it after or I just let the
hell get hit by it that's what I would do it could be this oh wait what what wait wait wait
wait what happened what happened what happened what happened oh my god I thought I had two health
oh my god what happened what just happened what I've ruined everything okay all right all right
okay squirrel pack rat fucking hit him it's all right squirrel okay I have two squirrels
back rat on the right right yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah what about the hook does he have the hook
out yet back bar left this hook isn't gonna kill me um stop what he has the hook right now so I
want to just am I dead if I don't block why is it so tense pack rat wins pack rat kills in one
will it though you're at minus six pack rat will kill will it please tell me you're right
so if I go far left with it attack left defend right all right let's go no more stalling let's
do it let's go that's it three four five six oh yeah I think I just won don't delete it please
don't delete it this damn moon it's dramatic yes it provides no value to my board I wonder
now that is value oh out of cards I'm sorry I will attempt to hasten your demise the moon will be
your mercy what I win I win I just beat him he's gonna go by this right and that's six
I won I won back rat I can't even do anything I could make him not he thinks wrong it defends
against you have to win it and you have to win in three turns just hourglass him what the
fuck is this I can't even do anything huh so what I just lose this dipshit has an air block
and I sacrifice the pelt I don't know I can't yeah I just this is it I just think I just lose
uh unfortunate 22 oh you made it so far I feel like I'm not supposed to win that was cool this
game's cool well I got to the end once I probably could have beat him yeah probably but you know I'm
not cost uh this one all right that's gonna be it though uh it's getting late power and health I mean
obviously this one and this is this is I mean I upgraded this like three times it's all right
that was the end of the first act I imagine so this game's fun you have to beat him to get to act
two please play this again yeah no I that was really fun this would be something maybe that
you just jump into sometimes I'm not in the time limit what is that okay so now I think that's it
yeah that was cool I can see why people think the game's really good you're actually we're good
you yeah I mean oh not really but I definitely need help from you guys that was really enjoyable
oh the clock puzzle that's right 11 o'clock right does it have to be a certain hand
oh there we go oh that was the wow it's that if you have a ring you automatically just beat it
more of these all right awesome so I'll see you guys tomorrow we're gonna do some elden ring
tomorrow uh probably four o'clock specific but we're not gonna start at six I just had uh some
stuff going on I had some stuff going on this afternoon so I'll see you guys tomorrow for
for elden ring pvp tomorrow we're just gonna be chilling for I don't know how long this
stream is gonna be tomorrow long enough to at least hang out and do pvp for a few hours
three four maybe why elden ring uh because me and a lot of we're gonna do a thing we have community
members fight each other um that's probably at some point later this week or next week
and I want to do a little bit of uh tryouts there's one more image one more image where is it
uh it was an image what do you mean when are you gonna leak the fart I'm telling if you're
if you're good on somebody's birthday it's some it'll be someone's birthday and I'll be
say happy birthday here's that's a weird thing to say I never tweeted the stream whatever that's
fine thanks for hanging out though thank you to uh thank you to uh Laniya, Lazar, Atriok,
Kraikin with three raids today with a lot of people so if you stuck around and watched me
fumble through uh the first act of inscription then Laina I know I'm so bad Laniya dude I need
to eat some I need some fucking protein or something yeah I my all right whatever you're
gonna stare my brain just has trouble thank you so much for the raids though you guys are amazing
like I'm just thank you see you tomorrow take care good night