Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight, not exactly sure what I'm going to be playing as.
I'm going to be playing as one of the nine classes, I assume. Maybe even the tenth class, the Indian Chiefmaster.
I have no idea. So this video is not going to talk about Team Fortress 2. It's going to be a discussion video.
It's going to be something that was brought up last night when I was hanging out in Star's stream.
If you were there, then you probably know what this commentary is going to be about.
But if you weren't there, let me briefly bring this up.
We were playing a game in Alpha, and it's called Cannon Brawl. It's pretty fun.
It's a 1v1 type of Worms RTS hybrid base building tower shooting game, and it's great. I suggest you pick it up.
It's like less than ten bucks. If you got the money, you and your friend can have at least a few hours of fun.
Regardless of any of that, a couple of developers were actually in the stream chat.
The guys that made the game were hanging out in Star's stream.
We got to talking with them. They were legitimate. They weren't making it up.
It wasn't like, oh yeah, I'm the developer. And it just wasn't them. It was actually them.
Which was cool in itself. I love talking to developers.
I love seeing where they're coming from, seeing their angles, finding out stuff about them, the backstory, etc.
And that kind of conversation got into people talking about in the comment section how much they hate certain developers
because they don't do certain things, they have bad customer support, and screw them. Like, fuck EA.
And that's the topic of this discussion. That's the topic of this video. That's where I want to go with this.
Because when you say something like, in quotes, fuck EA, end quotes, what you're effectively saying is this.
At least, for the most part, this is what people mean when they utter this phrase.
What they're really talking about is the consumer-company relationship.
And the consumer-company relationship can mean a million different things.
It can mean the amount of money you have to spend on something.
It can mean who's in charge that's making broad spectrum company decisions.
It could mean how the company reacts to negative criticism or positive criticism.
It can mean a bunch of different things.
But a lot of people really, really get upset with, and I'm in this category myself, I'm included in this,
I get really mad at a company when they blatantly just mishandle the stuff I just said.
For instance, when a company charges way too much money for something, it annoys me.
When a company doesn't follow through on promises it makes, it annoys me.
When a company has a CEO that's like a complete dickwad, that annoys me.
But something that we all have to keep in mind is it's not just one guy that makes a video game.
It's not just one dude that is making all these decisions for this company.
There are thousands and thousands of people that are working for EA.
There are artists, there are programmers, there are coders, there are marketing people, there are advertising people,
there are people on the board.
If it's just one person you don't like, then do you really hate the company?
Or do you hate the person that's in charge?
Or do you hate this one particular person on the development team?
I'm going to give you a real situation of this.
For instance, Diablo III.
Diablo III was one of my most anticipated games ever.
Like, I was waiting so much for that game, I couldn't wait for it to come out.
The second it came out, I bought it like midnight release, let's go, I'm going to spend like 30 hours playing this game straight.
And I had a little bit of fun in D3.
I enjoyed myself.
But after a while, it started to really annoy me that the developers took this game such in a far direction away from one of my favorite games of all time, which is Diablo II.
I made a review of Diablo III, and I even said, if you're a die-hard Diablo II fan, this game's going to let you down in a lot of places.
And it really got me thinking, do I hate Blizzard for making Diablo III the way they did?
I guess maybe there'd be a couple of rage moments when I was sitting in a game going, man, like, I hate Blizzard.
What the hell, man? Like, what did you do to this game?
Like, how could you, Blizzard?
In quotes, just like the same EA, how could you?
Fuck you, EA.
But then you break it down even more and it's like, but who, who was even really responsible for this?
It was not Blizzard as a whole.
It was only like a few guys in Blizzard that probably made these decisions.
The StarCraft guys didn't do it.
The friggin' Warcraft team had nothing to do with it.
So why would I hate Blizzard as a company when it only was a couple of people that really had the say?
And something else to keep in mind is most of the people that work for these companies, guys, are just going to work.
They're just going to work and they're doing their thing and they're going home and they're going home to their family.
They're working their ass off as a programmer or an artist or a coder or a concept designer.
And then they leave and they go home to their families.
And they don't read forum posts about how much people hate the company that they work for.
Hell, they might not even like the company they work for, but they're doing it anyways.
And my whole point here is when you make a generalization about really anything, you include all the people that you really didn't mean to include when you made the generalization.
So just keep that in mind.
It's something that we were talking about in the stream.
And I was like, you know what?
I want to make a commentary about this.
I want to see what everybody has to say.
So please in the comments section below, leave what you think about this.
Leave your opinions on this and maybe some generalizations that you've made over the last couple of years, because I know I've done plenty of them when it comes to game companies for sure.
But yeah, that's going to wrap it up here, guys.
Thank you all so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it.
And I'll see you guys all next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.