Why are you upset with me? We're upset with you. Where? Why? Why? It's like 15 minutes.
Why are you upset? Oh, right. You guys changed. I see what you're doing. Oh, right. Because from
a day or two ago. Right. Now I remember. Finally. I'm here. I just want to be ready.
Be remembered. I did remember. I'm here. And here's what we're going to do. I didn't even...
Look, I'm glad that there's people that remind me of certain things. Certain releases and games
that I played about a year or so ago that come out later. Because I play something,
even if it's a demo, whatever. Right. And then I just forget it exists. So one such game was
such art. I played the demo or the free version of it. It was a lot of fun. I made some paintings.
And I've been told that it's now out. How long has it been out for? Four years. I'm excited.
Re-run Andy. Yeah, the queen died. Yeah. Crazy. I don't have really anything to say about it.
Other than, yeah, that's crazy. Almost 100. I hope I fucking live to 100. Is your mic better?
That's crazy, Omegalul. Look. Oh, that's crazy. You're going to be on Twitch for 50 years?
No, I'm not. I'm telling you right now. Yeah. What a take on that. Oh, man. That's crazy.
That's crazy. Anyways, so we got some stuff going on today. Yeah, that was not a good take.
I don't even know what to say about stuff like this though, right? I'm so bad with giving takes
on anything. That's why I never give them. He gives cold takes. Here's what I will say.
I took the queen. I'm going to sound probably dumb here. Is that the last queen? No.
Is this just going to keep going? I guess we have the prince and the princess, right? But is it
going to be the queen of England? NA education. There already is. Monarchy sequel. King for now.
I don't know. I genuinely don't really know how it works. I just didn't know.
But yeah, as a popular streamer on the internet has once said, that's crazy.
I'm quoting somebody else. But now, I mean, like I said, I would hope I get to live to be 100.
But we're going to play such art. That's crazy. I would love to be 100. Yeah. When are you going
to play Disney Infinity 3.0? You know, one of the things I was going to do, I was going to play that
new Disney game that came out today. What's it called? Like Disney magical village or something,
whatever it's called. Just to have everybody say, wait, I thought you would rather show your
asshole than play the Disney Infinity, but you're going to play the Disney kind of animal crossing
game. Show people the question marking. It's like two days ago. You would get it if you were there.
Look what you did. Look what you started. Is it bathroom mic? It's not a, this is all right.
That may be angry. Yeah. Let's let's let's start playing. You should play Splatoon three. I don't
I don't even know those Splatoon two. I can't play Splatoon. I can't do it. I've already talked about
I can't play Splatoon. It's skill issue. Yes, it is. I've been very vocal about how it is.
It's a skill issue. You are correct. What about art? I'm doing art right now. Well, in two seconds.
He's really bad at it. You've never seen me play Splatoon. You don't know that.
Yeah. The only thing I will say about the queen is then we'll move on. I hope to live a long,
fulfilling life. 96. That's very old. So that's, I mean, I know some people that live up into their
nineties, eighties as a long life. That's crazy. God damn it. This is why I don't talk about anything
on stream because I'm so bad at articulating a single fucking actual point about anything
that it always just kind of comes out as. Yeah, that's, that's crazy, man. I can't do it.
I'm so bad at articulating like serious points. God damn it. Now that's the all right. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. All right, we're done. We're done. We're
going. We're moving forward. I can't, I can never. This is why I can't talk about anything
because I was thinking about it before the stream. I'm like, oh yeah, that's right.
If the queen did die. Okay. Let me think of something meaningful to say. What could I say?
Okay. That's wild. Steam like coming out of my fucking shirt. Nice public statement, Andy.
You're a Looney Tunes character? No, dude. I'm just not good with serious topics. I never have been
ever. So let's go. How you doing? Dude, you're like the Joker. I'm not. No, stop. I'm not at all.
Please. Anybody that says they're the Joker is actually the Penguin. Anybody that says they're
the Penguin is actually the Riddler. And if you say you're the Riddler, you're actually the Joker.
We already went over this. We did this already. I don't want to, where are you? There you are.
You're far away today. I don't want to, I don't want to be the Penguin. I'm not the Penguin,
but actually I might be. New angle. Yeah. You're up there. This camera angle makes you look short.
I'm sitting in a, no, there's no routine. There's no bit coming. The people think it's a routine
coming. No, no, there's no routine. There's not gonna be a joke. There's no bit on the way. I'm
just sitting in the chair and I move the camera because I got sick of moving because, uh, so the
camera used to sit here on the monitor and the problem, he's in a high chair. I think it's a
good angle. This looks super set up for something. It's not. It's, I swear to God, it's just a new
angle. I just put you in it. No one's going to come out of the closet over there and like
strangle me with like a bag or something. I promise. I'm, it's just a new angle.
Cause when I, when I move my mouse, my keyboard's on the desk and it shakes the desk a little,
which shakes the camera that's on the monitor that's being shaken from me touching the desk.
And I don't like it. So now I can go like this and I don't shake you. Nice isometric Andy. It's a bad
angle. Fix it. It's staying like this for at least the whole day today. It's zoomed in all weird.
The background is massive behind you. What are you talking about? What is going on here? It's a
different camera angle. It's a different, it's just a different angle. That's a closet right there.
What? See, look, this is a closet. That's the closet. I'm just sitting down. We don't like change.
Yeah, I can see that. It's all zoomed in and weird. It's not. It's a CCTV angle. Well,
get used to it for the next like six hours because that's what we're doing today.
You look so small. The FOV looks odd. There's no FOV. What are you guys talking about?
Anyways, today, ladies and gentlemen, we've got some, hey, there you are. Ladies and gentlemen,
today we've got some fun stuff. I'm going to be playing such art as you see on the screen right
now. We're going to be playing multi versus later security camera. What the fuck? Why is it going so
high? Huh? Is this what it looks like? That's what all right. Well, whatever. Why can you see the
ceiling? Why can that go? Why is it going so high? I cropped it. I cropped it. Yeah. I didn't know
it was that much space above me. Well, you're getting to see, you get the CCTV angle today.
This is a bit, it's no, I swear to God, it's not. Keep the full view. You, you want me to do this.
Okay, guys, welcome to the stream. We're here. You can see my ceiling. Okay, so I got streamer
mode turned on, by the way. Somebody said Alice in Wonderland. I don't know what streamer mode does,
but I'm surely going to turn it off in probably five minutes. All right, so we're going to play
this. We're going to play multi versus later, by the way, in case you didn't know. Hey, hey,
hold on. I got that juggle. Hold on. Can you see this? Oh, can you see that? Can I do like
tricks like that? All right. Anyways, we're going to play, we're going to play multi versus later.
Gizmo just came out, which is awesome. I'm very excited. It's going to be a sponsored stream,
sponsored segment of the stream. This is, this part's not sponsored, but I mean, I'm going to play
it. And Gizmo, it's, Gremlins 2 is my favorite we've ever made. We literally just talked about
it on Hey, Donna, which if you haven't seen Hey, Donna, it's a great show. Go check it out. Will Neff.
Stretch the game to fit. It looks weird. No, I'm, this is funny for five seconds and then we,
I'm turning, I'm going back to what it was. But yeah, Gizmo from Gremlins is in multi versus,
as of right now. And I, I would be lying if I told you I wasn't very excited. And I was going
to play it. So that's really cool. Warner Brothers is going to obviously sponsor that segment of the
stream, which is just cool. I'm just, I'm happy to do that. I very much enjoy the game. So,
all right, we're going to show this only once and that's it. And we're going to move on. Finally,
it's been like 15 minutes. Can you guys hear? My name's Jeremy Storymode. What's fast forward?
Try just to fast forward. Speeds at the pace at which you will gain fame and money. If you want
to say only play a couple hours for the purpose of a stream or a video, this might be for you.
What? Are you serious? They made a streamer version of the game. That's actually kind of
perfect. Let's try it. Let's do the streamer version. Oh, yeah. Cutscene. Okay. I've got
artistic talent. Just play my MS Paint. This is not even close to being the same thing. For decades,
art has been largely dominated by robots and other artificial, I can't, if a word has more
than four syllables, I can't say it anymore. What happened? Artificial. That's four syllables.
What actually happened to me? It's been in the last three streams. What happened? I'm fucking
serious. Artificial intelligence. By the way, this is already happening. Yeah, I've seen the
Kermit the Frog in Scarface. Realistic 2015, right? It's crazy. It's actually, it's crazy.
Wow, that's crazy. Again, here we are. Great. I'm really good at talking about anything.
Okay, the world of art has become stale and in need of renewal. It is time for you to act.
You've been assigned a studio on board the International Space City so you can fully express
your artistic self. As on Earth, the threat of a robotic revolt is rising. An alien species,
the Crabucks, covet the planet's saltwater. Only you can decide what to paint on your next canvas.
All right, so I remember this game. I did, I think it was pretty fun last time. I have a streamer
menu. I don't know what the streamer menu is, but we are going to do this. I'm going to turn this
down. Streamer menu. Is that working? Does that work? We're at 0.5%. I feel like that's not
changing to that level. Okay, that's fine. All right, so what, you can't see it? Streamer menu.
Well, I don't want to spoil anything because I know if I pull this up, that's my camera, you idiot.
If I pull this up and there's like a command you can write, I want to make sure it's not something
you can spam right away. Hold on. Challenge my skills, challenge my style, boo me, rate my
painting. Okay, this is fine. How does this work? Well, let me get in the video game first. Wait,
I can ask you to boo me? All right, well, let's go. How do you do this?
Ongoing poll, boo or applaud German985's performance. How does this work? Did you guys
see anything in chat? No? 14 viewers? How many people are real here? Only 14 of you figured that
out? Hold on a minute. Wait, there are 12,000 of you here. There are 12,000 and only 14 of you
figured it out. No way. Type boo or clap in the chat with an exclamation point. Holy shit,
that's insane. I can't, that's crazy. Yeah. Okay. End the challenge. Okay, that was fun.
Ooh, yeah. All right. Get it off my fucking screen. How do I get this off the screen? Okay.
All right, I got a new, I got a document. Apartment A64-3 International Space City
secure password 123. This one, right? Washing a toilet? All right. This was not in the other game.
Welcome to your studio. So this is the real thing. This is the real game. Okay. Check your email on
the main computer. Let's go. Welcome to your studio. I am ico62, your assistant and contact
with United Earth. Following the results of your last DNA test in light of your artistic potential,
you've been registered with the Talent Development Program, the United Earth Program.
All right. There are boxes everywhere. Is that normal? I have to sit up too, people. That's what
here. You have to type boo or clap with the exclamation point. Okay. Okay, cool. Some equipment
could not be installed before your arrival. Some of them essential to your work will soon be
assembled by our technicians. You have to pay the installation costs. All right. Fine. Who replies
with an email back? Okay. Just okay. No, you've got to write okay and then hit, no, first you
got to say, hey, uh, comma space, write a, write a whole thing that writes right. Okay. And then
hit enter, enter dash Jeremy space content creator space brackets, Twitch streamer, uh, and then
enter. And then like, uh, my way you can reach me and you know, what my email, that's how I do it.
F let me F there's no F you lied to me. Yeah. Content creator, comma artist, comma producer,
comma director, comma, um, world renowned physician, comma. I just add a lot of shit.
I just do a lot of things. Okay. Dear, dear big brother, I heard you have some hidden artistic
genes. I didn't know in a new studio in space. Why saying F? Stop saying F. Okay. Meanwhile,
yesterday was my birthday and I didn't get anything from you. So I suggest you paint me a great piece
of art to make up for it. I want a beautiful painting of a unicorn with plenty of colors.
Okay. You got it. A unicorn with colors. Well, I was about to paint the screen.
Okay. I'll do it here. Okay. So we need to do a unicorn and this would be beautiful.
Okay. Cool. You can throw an object with E. Yep. There's no paint on this. Pick up an object by
holding. Yep. Let me get used to the controls. You can jump some items have a special action.
Uh, press F to trigger it. Okay. Yeah. I can turn it. Cool. Press left control to crouch and paint
the ugly floor. Okay. Very cool. Nice. All right. It's time to paint a unicorn. Do I have access
to the whole studio? All right. Think of clouds. If they can lose, I'm thinking like a really nice
blue. Okay. Wait, how big does it need to be? Oh, right. All right. Here we go. I can move this
thing up and down. Can I? Yeah. No, I don't want green. Get that out of here. All right. I need,
um, I need more blue. Why? I don't need an easel. Fuck it. Looks pretty good so far. I gotta,
I gotta get up top though. Ruined. Not really. Let me go down actually. This is a 90s design.
Well, I'm a fucking 90s kid. Of course it's gonna be 90s. It's bad on purpose. This is not even,
I haven't even begun. I just put the, I just got the canvas. It's not even close. It looks pretty
good. It does actually look kind of good. It's not, it's not even close. Uh, I need more blue.
Is this empty? Yeah. How do I throw this away? Is there a trash? Uh, this is gonna be the trash
for now. All right. I want this. I want this and this. All right. Let's get that combined over here.
You throw trash into space. Hold on. I gotta flip it. I just, I gotta get it covered first.
I'm sorry. This is not a TikTok video. Yeah. It's gonna take me more. It's gonna take more
than 10 seconds for you to see this. Speed it up. No, I'm, what do you mean speed it up? I'm gonna
take my time. And this is actually going pretty fast for what I'm making here. I need a background,
obviously. All right. So this is pretty, this is getting close. I need to add a little bit of,
uh, finesse on here. Hold on. Yeah. Okay. Let's like this. I gotta get some texture on it. All
right. Now it's time. We've got our kind of a background here. Gifted Andy. It's ruined.
It is not ruined. I'm about to ruin it though, because I, you know, painting is not something.
Okay. Unicorn. Purple. Pink. Wait, I need to do outline first. White. I'm turning to go like
unicorn. Unicorn is like blue, like light blue. White. This is gonna, I'm gonna fuck this up.
All right. What does a unicorn look like? It needs to be perspective. All right. It's gonna be the
front of the unicorn's face. It's going to be like this. It's kind of a droopy nose. What does
an animal even look like? All right. What the fuck does a horse look like? I can fix it. What? Oh,
I thought the game, I thought I was doing so poorly that the game said you have to leave.
This kind of looks like a party hat. All right. Hold on. I'm not done. I did the same exact painting
the first time. The, the last stream, the same exact one. It's the exact same painting as the
first one I did last time. Identical. It was an alligator. The first one was an alligator,
wasn't it? It actually is the same exact thing. I made an alligator painting and it was the same
face. It needs, I know I'll give, hold on. Let me just get this done. You guys don't even know
what. Yeah. It's like turning this way. Unicorns have, um, this is fun. This is cool. They have an
ass horn. This one does. I need a thicker brush. This is too thin. It's gotta be way thicker than
this. Otherwise I sit here all day doing this. All right. This painting is for a sister as a gift.
All right. Let me finish this part. Oh, fuck. There's all this empty space over here. Um,
it's all right. I'll put hay over here. All right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
Wait, hold on. Wait, one thing at a time. Should you, should you be like, like munching on hay?
You know what I mean? Like I need thinner than this. Shit. Don't go that far. Wonderful use of
colors. Yeah. No, no, no. I gotta lighten this up. I gotta wait. Hay is kind of darker, isn't it?
All right. I'll spray paint it too. This looks like Dark Ooga drew this. Is this too big of a
brush? I don't know. It might be. Is this too big? I'll fix it. Fuck. Sorry. I can fix it.
That looks like, uh, that looks okay. Control Z. There is no control Z. It's, uh, it's, it's an art
program. Wait, that's wrong. Okay. So, um, you gotta be like, looks like a Dark Souls boss.
It's like half the enemies in Bloodborne look like this. What about the ears? I don't, what does a
horse's ears look like? No. What do they look like? Uh, wait a minute. Can somebody do me a quick
favor and go get a screenshot of Grandpa is an MLG series I used to do on Machinima and the
thumbnail of that series? I need it right now. I need an image of it right now. Right now.
Somebody get it to me. Somebody get it to me right now. Get it yourself. I can. I'm busy.
Okay. So it is, it is what I thought it was going to be. It's almost, it's like the same image.
Okay. It's kind of close. This is like the, the, I don't even know. This is like a weird de-evolved
version of this image. I can only do one thing. Okay. Well, that's interesting. By the way, if
you haven't seen that series, uh, Grandpa is an MLG, Machinima got liquidated. It's gone. Okay.
Uh, so I can fix it though. I was trying to do the perspective,
kind of like a fish eye lens in a way that I'll think this is wrong. I'll do the eyes better,
but for now we need, Hey, no, it's not you. Hold on. I gotta have the lip come up. Can you tell me how
to use frat? You don't know how different the world was back then. Okay. Doing tutorials on how to do
just random shit. People were looking for stuff like that. Oh, how do I unlock this weapon in call
of duty, right? People made videos on it because it was, it didn't exist. I need like teeth. Horses
have really human teeth. Don't they? What does a horse's ears look like? They go down, right?
Are they pointy? They go, no, wait, hold on. They go back. They go search for a horse. Yeah. What
does a horse's face look like? They point up. Yeah, they do. They're tiny. Shit. All right. Hold on.
I gotta fix this then. I don't know why I thought they looked like that. Um, are you serious? I'm
hiding it. There we go. Okay. I can fix that up there. Let me finish the body. That's important.
Why would I wash this? I didn't want to put that there. Okay. I should have done this first. I'm
going to clean it up. I'll do some line work on it. Okay. I need to do some line work or I do this.
Hey, you would hang this up on your fridge. If this was an eight year old, you would. All right.
So I do like dark line, right? Yeah. Now I got to fill it in first. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Fill it in
first. I need a white. Yeah. Any white. I would buy this for a hundred dollars. He's 37. Yeah. You
don't magically just know how to draw because you're 37. This is not something that everybody
knows how to do. It's not like, oh yeah, you're 35 and older. You know how to draw. That's not how
it works. This is a skill that takes time to develop. I promise this will look a lot cleaner
in a minute. You have to trust the process of what I'm doing. Once it's cleaned up, everyone's
going to be like, oh, well actually it looks like kind of good. And those people get timed out.
How dare you not believe in me from the very beginning. They get timed out for a while too.
Like, I'm not going to have that here, right? I'm not going to have that. Yeah. I'm not going to
have that here. It's, it's scaring me. And I'm the one that drew it. The issue is this double nose
thing. It's like, it looks like Chester Cheetos, uh, unicorn cousin. This is an ad for some hay-like
cheese dusty snack. Imagine hay coming out of a bag. It kind of looks like what you smell like.
You don't know what I smell like. So that's interesting. It's not what you think either.
Oh my God. He must smell so good. No, not at all. It's fucking terrible. Disgusting. I smell awful.
Everything about me smells bad. Everything. Like when I go up and walk up and talk to somebody
and I'm like, oh, hey, what's up? They go, oh, because my breath is so fucking bad. I need more.
Now, you know what I smell like? I smell like, um, you know that the Axe body wash. So Axe body wash.
I go in the shower and I get a mound this high off my hand and I go pop, pop, pop, pop, pop,
it hits all of my body and shit. And I don't guys like the way it feels. And I mush it all
over my hands and I put it all over my face and all of my body everywhere. And I let it sit there.
I don't do that. Got you. You're so far away now. It's so funny just how far away you really are.
Yeah. I got you. I got you. Yep. I was kidding around with you. If you're new to the channel,
we kind of, we mess around sometimes. Yeah. We kid around a lot. Yeah. I got you. Yep. You are a
prince of lies. But, um, they have hooves, right? Kind of like this. And then this is going to be
gray. I'm going to have to call that pretty good, um, hand, uh, stability. That was pretty good.
Give the horse underwear. Maybe. We'll see. I will see what inspiration hits me. First it was the
hay. I don't know. We'll see. I don't know. I have no idea what's going to happen. I don't know. I
might just get unhappy with this and drop kick this and put two huge shoe prints on it and then
throw it away. Well, I don't know. It depends on what I, it depends on my inspiration. And then
someone will find it and it'll have a ton of value because the artist that didn't like his own
material, the shoe, right? That would be kind of interesting. This was found in the dumpster or
something, right? It's got shoe prints on it. They kicked it. That might be interesting. Your life
isn't a movie, Jerma. What is this? It's not done is what it is. You can't just come in here and say,
what is this? Until you see the whole thing. I think I'm going to, let's clean this up. Yeah.
I only cleaned this up. We're going to go super abstract for the next one. I'm telling you. I
need a thicker brush. This one here. I can fix it if I need to. I'll do, I'll redo this line.
Do you not know how an outline works? I know nothing about painting or drawing. I just do it
when it's fun. This is fun. All right. What am I going to, what am I going to do here? I know I
have to fix a lot of this. Hold on. Yeah. Give me, let's get this fixed. These are too big. It's
okay though. These are way too big. What do the horse's eyes look like? I don't think kind of like
on other, like bird eyes, aren't they? There's like an eye here and an eye here. It's like a bird.
That's how it works, right? Yeah. Let me fix this then. I need a purple. What's this? Whoa. Oh
shit. That's way too dark. I need this in a, there we go. Yeah. Give me that. Is this better?
Kind of. A little bit. I'll fix it in post. Very clearly the eyes were here. Damn it. I can't do
subjects. I can do, I can do interesting color stuff. I can't draw a subject. I can make some.
You'll see. I can, I'll fix it in a minute. My God damn it. I fucking ruined everything. I actually
just ruined it. Not if it's a cyborg guy. Good start. I'm thinking like, like Kano from Mortal
Kombat, right? All right. Now is the purple. Okay. You ruined it again. No, I didn't because I can,
I can work with that. Here's my, there it is. I have to clean this workstation up. This is awful.
This horse is awesome now. I told you to wait until it was done. Everyone's freaking out about,
it doesn't look good. Just wait till it's done. Done, done, done. Take it before and after. You
need to trust me. That's kind of scary actually. I'd pay $500,000 for this. I would not sell it for
$500,000. I would be a shame to sell it to you for that much. I would be saying, no, no, no, no,
no, no, dude, dude. It's all right. In fact, you would, you would probably show up with a briefcase
with like a hundred dollar bills in it. And I'd be holding this in my hand and be like, oh dude,
I'm going to give you $500,000 for this. I'd be like, dude, just, just fucking have it. Just take
it. I just, you can just have this for 50 bucks. Take this, take this from me. All right. I need a
bigger brush because yeah, I'm trying to figure out if I need to just thin this. I, it's got to
be thinner. Yeah. This edge part can't be here. So let's go like this. I'll fix the rest. Thanks.
I need more white. Yeah. Well, maybe we'll do it. I'm going to do one of my own and then maybe we
could do some abstract stuff. Maybe you guys can give you some tools that I could only use
or something. I don't know how it works, but we'll try it. I need to, that water is dirty.
If you're wondering why I did that, it's going to start to not work. Okay. Almost. We're actually
pretty close to being done to do some detail work. I don't want to lose this part. I need the line
here. I need more water. Water. Where's water? How do you just place it down? Oh, come on. How do I,
how do I put it down just normally? Is it? No, it's not E. How do I do it? Okay. There we go.
Uh, where's my brush? Okay. So I just got to fill this in and we can start to actually make some
cool changes here. I got to kind of remember where some of this stuff was because there's a line that
needs to be here. What does this look like? This looks like something. What does this actually look
like? It looks like, um, fuck it's, uh, I don't know. Somebody will see it, right? No, no, no,
not sans. Something else. The dog from Toy Story? The dog from Toy Story. It looks like, hold on.
Toy Story. Toy Story dog. No, it does not. Remember he's like, like chewing like that.
So we know we got that done. Okay. I got to be very careful here because this is kind of the way I
want it. I just have to do some line work. Yeah. All right. Give me this. What the hell just happened?
Bring me up. I'm concentrating. Relax. I'll put some more, um, Kano I smoke in a minute. Actually,
this is kind of good. I can get rid of the big chunky gross part. I got to give it a little
bit texture at the bottom because it's like coming out. All right. Almost there. We'll do some more.
We'll do some more touch up work later. But for the most part, this is almost ready to start doing
some detail with the face. Why is this different color? Am I getting paid for this? Oh, this is a
birthday present. Hmm. It's a birthday present. I can't just like send you like a $50 gift card
to Applebee's and have it be a card with a cat on it, a little kitten with a party hat on and then
write, Hey, scratch this off your list. Dinner's on me tonight with like a cat scratch. Why can't
I just do that? Okay. Let's do this. I actually, I'm just going to, I can fix this in a minute
because I'm going to put some, uh, we'll add some more lines on top of it. So it doesn't look like
it's in front. The perspective is going to change. So just wait. It'll be fine. How come there's no
fifth leg? If you want me to draw a horse dick, I'm sorry. That's not going to happen on this stream.
This is actually tricky, but whatever. I need you to be more, this is going to start to look weird.
Okay. There we go. That's better. It's fine. Don't worry. I don't want to mess with this
because it's already under his lip. This is the leg that's the front in front of the camera the
most. That's gotta be the biggest one. All right. It's time to start doing this. Time to actually
care about this. Give me. All right. I don't want to screw this up. Let me think how this would
actually look with the same type of, it's like kind of looks like, huh? Hey, wait. I was like,
what happened? What are you talking about? What? Where'd you get this? I'm so confused. What's
going on? Did I steal this? Who's is this? Snooze and copter drew this. That's just,
that's just the ice cream truck version of that. What you drew. Wow. That's unbelievable. All right.
Well, cool. Should I just stop? Did I just stop my painting? Wow. That's actually awesome. All
right. Well, snooze and copter. That's awesome. Um, I feel like I can't even make mine now.
This is the part of the movie. Jerma, your life's not a movie. I don't care. This is the part of the
movie when we're at the talent show and we both did the same thing and mine sucks. And I have to
figure out what I'm going to do instead. And the guy with the headset comes over. He's like, hey,
you ready to show what you, what you did for the talent show? And I'm just like, um, uh, yeah.
And then I come up with a dance routine that wins everybody over. And I beat your painting,
by the way, try to get up and dance. And ladies and gentlemen, here he is showcasing his art,
Jeremy Albertson. And I walk on stage and I'm like looking nervous, sweating. And I grabbed the mic
and it goes, okay, everybody, huh? Well, I was going to drop something and then like night,
like really sad kind of uplifting music starts playing. Well, I was going to draw for you today,
but I was going to bring you a painting, but it felt like, no, I wanted to do something different.
You're in, you inspired them. Why are you acting like this? It's not a talent show. They just were
inspired by what you were doing. Yeah. Yeah. That's what I mean. Why are you so insecure? I'm
just walking around. That was a phenomenal painting though. Seriously. But check mine out. Yeah.
Check mine out. I might not be the fastest, the brightest. I might not have what it takes,
but there's something that I do know. I have perseverance and I have gumption. And then a fat
boy, slim song comes on and I start doing like a Napoleon dynamite dance. You're an anime character.
Yeah. Shut up. Help. Help. Help with what? What's wrong? All right. So I need to make the lip go.
I can fix this. Hold on. Oh, yay. I think I'll be all right. Just to do more of the,
Hey, all right. We're going to make sure the head is correct. This is the moment of truth.
It's perfect. I need the other eye. Teeth too. Shit. All right. It's a moose. It does kind of
look like a moose snoozing copter. I didn't mean to show off. I just wanted to draw along like
Bob Ross. You're a vision. No, I'm not. Don't take it that way. I'm just messing around, man.
It was awesome. It was actually fucking, it was a great, it was a great part of this drape,
actually. It was funny. Kind of looks like a duck. It does kind of look like a duck. What about the
other eye? What should I do with the other eye? I need the nostrils too. It just kind of looks like
he has rotten teeth. He's got fucked up rotten teeth. Okay. Um, I can fix this if I go like this.
All right. I got to change some things here. I need white. Do I still have any white left in here?
No, of course not. Wait, there's a spongy tool. Hold on. That didn't do anything. I need white.
I need to do teeth and then I need to do the eye and then do some detail work and I'm done.
It looks pretty good from far away. Okay. Let's do some teeth. All right. I'm actually not unhappy
with this. Oh, fuck. I have to do it in the other color. Okay. That looks good. I'm not going to say
anything. Okay. Now I just need to add a little bit in there. Should there be a shoulder coming
out or something here? This feels weird. Like it cuts off too quick. You know what I'm saying?
Kind of have like a little bump like here. That makes sense, right? Does that make sense? I hope
it makes sense. I hope so. Cause I'm just going to do it. Fuck. It looks terrible. Hold on. Does
that make any sense? I don't know. Find out. This game has background music. Can you not hear
anything? Has it been quiet the whole time? Oh shit. Sorry. Now let me see if this works.
Cause now once the detail work comes out, this will actually look a little better. It's going
to look weird and it's going to look like a weird cartoon, but whatever. I think it's going to be
fine. And then I'm done. I'm done after this. Cause I want to do another painting. I want you guys
to choose. It doesn't look right, but fine. Something about doesn't look right, but whatever.
Needs another eye. All right. So what should I do for this eye? How about just like purple?
Is this a bit, I don't know how to draw. I mean, is, is not knowing how to do something a routine?
No, I just don't know how to draw. What is it? Wait, do you think I'm pretending to not know how
to draw and I actually do, and I'm going to do the next one? It's going to be fucking sick.
That actually would be kind of funny. I like the texture on that. Ooh, I like it. You idiot
fucking ruined it. I'm doing the two feet prints. Just stick right in the middle. I'm going to jump
and lay out on my back. So my back is parallel to the ground and kick as hard as I can right here
into the, into the front. Cause I just fucked that up. Okay. Getting close to being done.
Eyebrows. Do horses have eyebrows? They do, right? Kind of, but this one's going to have eyebrows.
Okay. They have this though. I know for a fact, like a little opening, right?
Looks a little strange, but whatever. There needs to be more texture here. All right. Wait,
I need texture, texture, texture, texture, texture like that. Here we go. This is going to ruin it
or it's going to make it look much better. Find out. Fuck you. It's glowing, actually glowing.
I'm fine. It's fine. It looks, it actually looks cool. I was trying to smudge it a little.
That actually looks kind of cool. Look at how magical this is. What do you mean? Stop, stop,
stop. What I think it looks better than it did. Now we truly go through and fix the details.
I want to do some more line work. Where's the hair? Um, I don't have the tool to do that.
I got to fix this and then I'm do one more pass with the line and then I'm done. And I'm going
to sell it to my sister or an Applebee's gift card. Maybe should the outline be purple?
Yeah. You made an NFT. Yeah. But I mean the combination of the hay in the mouth and the
two Kano eyes, it's got to be worth at least one Ethereum. I actually don't think I want to add
that much more line stuff. Yeah. I don't like that. Let's fix that right now. Quick, quick,
quick, quick herb before it dries. That's all right. Okay. So he's, why does this have white on
it? Why does this have white on it? Oh my God. He's phasing into reality. Oh my goodness. This is,
this is worth it. 25 people. He's phasing in. Are you kidding me? This is white. What the fuck?
All right. It's time for the finishing touch. Let me practice. Two shoe prints. Well, so it
will be like, it kind of looks like two feet prints. That's my signature. Dude, you're cooked.
I'm fine. All right. How do I get this off the wall? Why is it brown? Cause I got dirty ass feet.
Okay. There it is. It's complete. It's time to, I'm going to give you 20 seconds. All right. Here
you go. You ready? 30 seconds. Rate my painting. What do you think? Is it between zero and 10?
I think you guys are breaking it. And a 6.5. That's not bad. I'm okay with that. All right.
Let's send it. Okay. How much money? I just made money. How do you clean?
Is that a good wah or a bad wah? Is that a, is that a Waluigi wah? Like you fell off the side
of a cliff Wiley Coyote style, or is that a wow? This is great. Okay. I got to go to my email.
Cleaning is more fun than painting for me. I love this. I love this. Is there a business
where you can just kind of clean, like paint off a wall like this? Cause they, around it,
they have the stuff where you break things. I don't know what's, what's going on with the,
oh, let's have it be going and you smash stuff with a hammer. I want where you clean stuff.
I want to power wash a dirty driveway. I want to use a sponge on like a dirty wall and clean it.
Should I just become, do, be like a janitor, be like a, be a power washer, do power washing.
Yeah. Okay. Here's the thing. I wouldn't be able to do a professional job doing it.
Right. It's not like, oh, just, I'll just do power washing. I'll just, I'll sell a power washing
business. No, no, no. I just want to clean dirt off of the wall. I don't think I'll do very well.
Right. Like I just want to do it just, oh, we like put dirt on this wall and you just
spray it off. It's a weed store. You go in and you just smoke, there's like a thousand different
kinds of joints. So you pick which one you want, you smoke it. And then they bring you into the
room where you could just play with a bunch of toys. Dude, man, you can, yeah, you could, by the
way, you can power wash this wall. It's like a 15 foot wall. Power wash it, man. What? Yeah. Or you
can just watch me do it. Oh yeah. Can I just sit in the chair and watch you do it? Hey bro, you know
those baby toys that we have at the doctor's offices? We've got a huge one. Oh, you put the
beads around the, with the wire. You do? Yeah, man. Yeah. Hey, you don't, you don't gotta play with
it. You just watch me. Oh yeah. Can I just watch you do it? Don't operate machine. No, I'm not
talking about like heavy machinery. I'm talking about just like easy toys or something. Like I
could watch somebody power watch a driveway while I'm high. Dude, why don't you just find a power
washing business and be like, Hey, can I just like come with you to a job and just get high?
I'll pay you just to sit there in a chair and just watch the power washing. I could probably
just do that. A ride along power. Yeah. A ride along power washing thing. What a weirdo.
Can I come with you to the doctor's so I can just play with the toy in the waiting room?
That's weird. That's not, that one won't work. That one's not going to work. Um, just buy the
toy. Hey, hot doctor asks you to power watch him power wash the driveway. Sorry, I don't mean to
annoy you. I just want to watch the surgery. Literally just buy it, dude. It's called a bead
maze. Where's the trash? No, you're fucking with my stupid, uh, scenario that I'm coming up with.
Wouldn't be honest with me. What is a job or a business that you really don't think you could do
that takes skill to do that you would just like to watch? Like wood cutting.
Can I just watch somebody cut wood? But I want to be there. It doesn't, when you, when you watch it
on a video, it's like, Oh, the person like chopping the wood. It's like, Oh, that's so cool. But I
want to like be there. I'm gonna smell the wood. I want to be there and just like hear the sounds
and just be like out in the, in the woods, just hanging out. Can I just watch somebody cut wood
just with a big ax, just chopping the wood painting. Yeah. Sculpting porn. No, I don't,
I don't want to watch someone make porn. That's not what I don't know. I know I'm talking about,
I don't know. I'm talking about just satisfying stuff. I think this is cleaning up. So now let's
go check the email. I just received my unicorn while I have the digital version, the real
painting will take a little longer. Um, your unicorn is a little weird, but let's just say it's,
but let's say it's approved. I will name it Ragnarok because it looks like it will bring
about the apocalypse. I, oh wait, this is a, wait, this is my sister. It's a great name. You're just
jealous of my unicorn naming skills. But anyway, I'm having an online call with some friends of
mine. I'm showing them your painting. Good luck with your artist stuff and everything. What do
you mean? Hmm. Good luck with your artist stuff. What is that? Okay. Oh, cool. I'm ready.
Your artist stuff. Okay. Let's go. You can paint whatever you want. Follow your creative impulses.
Printer. Wait, I can make a, I can do a printer. Cool. All right, let's do it. So what do I got?
Now what? You don't have any commissions yet. Should I just do whatever I want? Um, challenge
my skills. Which one? You can go off the email that you just read. Okay. I think I just have,
okay. I just have to make stuff and sell it. Make the horror. I don't think I can. That's
way too big. No, no, no, no, no, no. Give me something else. I want a little one. We're going
to get a little one. This is too big. I just want a small one. Here we go. I need an easel.
What's an easel? There it is. Okay. This thing out. Okay. It's an ICU. Yeah, it is an ICU. All
right. So what am I going to, what am I, I got to do something quick. Something without, without
thinking about it. I'm thinking, uh, just don't think, just do it. Just don't think. I'm just
going to, I'm not going to think I'm just going to do it. I don't want to see any tools yet.
What am I feeling? What am I feeling? I'm feeling a, um, what color am I feeling? Slate. Yeah.
Slate. What are the colors am I feeling? Slate. I'm feeling, uh, a little deeper of a slate blue.
I'm also feeling, uh, yeah, sand, olive. Okay. And it'd be a bright yellow. Let's go. All right.
I'm not going to think. I'm just going to go for it. I need, I need a bucket of water. All right.
We're going to do, we're going to start with tornado, a fury of wind and rock. Where did the
fucking yellow come from? Oh, actually kind of cool. Why would you do that? I need the inspiration.
I need a small, really thin one. I need a thin brush, a really small one. Can I buy,
where can I buy it from the computer? No, I can't access the store. Where's the little paintbrush?
Okay. Here we go. That's good. Don't think, don't think too hard about it. Just do it.
Give me the sponge. Quick, quick, quick sponge, sponge, sponge, sponge, sponge. I hope this works.
Just trust it, right? Just trust it. I didn't do what I wanted to do. I thought it was going
to smudge it. I didn't, I thought, okay, because I thought, so I wet it and I, I tried to go like
this to get the water off and I thought I was going to smudge it. That was kind of cool. You
have to use a blender too. I don't have it. I thought I could like smudge it with a sponge
and just go like wham. So it looked like a gust of wind. Why wet it first? I didn't want to paint on
it. And then I thought if I like did it on the ground for a minute and like did like over here
for a second, it would be not wet anymore. Um, it's okay. This actually might be kind of cool
if I can salvage it, which I'll try. Actually, wait a minute. That might've been a good thing.
Actually, not really a bad thing. Did you see this fucking swirling action? Do you see that?
Turn a quick cut your ear off. What? Yeah. He's like, okay. Yeah. You can faintly. I want you to
faintly see the face. I need one more thing to put the cherry on top of this. Yeah. Be careful. I
don't want to screw it up. Oh, I know. I'll smudge it with this. I only have $71. I feel like there
needs to be something else in the middle. Is this too much or is it good? I need a cloud. Okay.
Well, what if I do this? Like I'm talking like that and like very faint. Now it's done. Sell it.
How do I sell this? That's just trash. Oh, okay. No, no, no. Flip it around. Oh, okay. What do you
give this for a rating? Too much light on it. I would, I would have, I would mood light this.
What do you think? Oh, I got up. Did I sell it? 7.5. Okay. Cool. That's not bad. Isn't there a bunch
of weird shit too? Oh, cause I'm in like story mode. I get it. This is like a paint cannon.
There's, there's a lot of cool stuff to do. Try to just keep, try to play this more. Would
you guys want to see more of this? How do you guys feel? Yeah. Okay. Well, maybe I'll just come back
to this in a couple days or something. You guys having a good time? All right. We'll play like
another half an hour. Cause then I do, I want to play multi-versus. Should I just play this
literally in like two or three days? Just that's what we're doing when I come back. Okay. Yeah.
We'll just do this again on this weekend or whatever it is. I'm having fun. It's just a,
it's a fun game just to chill and play. All right. Let's get one more going here. How about you guys
can you guys decide? All right. Challenge my skills. I'm gonna need a little longer.
Paint with two colors, rotating easel only in one minute to paint. Oh, and the winner is
rotating easel only rotating easel. How do I do that? Small easel. Where is it? Make the canvas
spin. Yeah. How do I do that? I do that from here. Let it do auto rotate. Um, the blue attachment on
the easel. Oh, okay. Let me see. What do I, there it is. I get a very, I need a bigger canvas than
this. I'll use, I'll save this one for later. Let's get a, I guess that it seemed like a size
I can do. That's fine. Put it on here. You said the blue one, you need to buy a new easel. Oh,
really? That's not your easel. What the hell is this then? You don't have the one that rotates yet.
Oh, well we're doing another challenge. Only spray paint 30 seconds to paint or use a single tool.
Looks like spray paint is going to win by a lot. All right. I'm going to make, um, what can you even
do with spray paint? I'm going to do a lot of blues. Maybe the, maybe the green. I think it looks
all right. Maybe green and oh, I got some points. All right. How about this? So look only spray paint.
How's this look? Let's get a, let's get a blue background. I'm going to saturate this completely
by the way. Complete saturation. You can't even see what the hell I'm doing. Am I even on the screen?
There we go. Press F. Oh, scattered. Excuse me? How does that make any sense? What just happened?
How am I painting the windows? All right. That looks good. I kind of like that. All right. Now
we're going to do, not much I can do with spray paint. How about, okay, we're going to do this color,
this color. Yeah. We're going to do this color here. Oh, I got, this one's going to come up
because of the seafoam.
Call this one the flu. I call this one microscopic germs. It's mold.
Look at all the layers.
Get a load of that one. Get a load of that one. I don't know why I want to do this, but
I want to do this. I don't know why I want to do this, but I'm going to do it.
Something's making me do this. I'm just like, Hey, do this now. You should definitely do this.
Done. Sorry. I really concentrated on that one. I added so many layers that you can't even see the
other layers. I, it was perfect before and I kind of fucked it up, but whatever. I actually screwed
it up, but that's fine. It's art. Ooh, 6.3 ain't bad. All right. One more, let's do one more
challenge. And then I'm going to play multiverses. Eyes closed. Oh no, no, no. All right. I need a
small canvas for this. Is that too small? Just a one by one. All right. Eyes closed. I need to get
set. I feel like I did this one already, but all right, let me just get rid of this. Use the huge
canvas. Big canvas. Big canvas. But how am I going to ever, I'm not going to be able to go up or down.
Okay. Let me get my tools ready. This is going to be right here. You are stupid. Okay. There's that.
I want a new easel. I don't want an easel. I want to be able to remember where paint is over here.
An easel would be too hard. I need to block it out. So from here it's one, one, two, I need like
three colors. Okay. So let's do that. We're going to go with, um, how about a, I don't know, this
kind of lavender. And actually I do need an easel. I need a ton of it because I need to be able to
miss. I think it looks like delicious. Lavender, maybe a, one of these, like a light blue, maybe
white. Oh, maybe one of these. How's this? It's yellow. Grapes. Gittles. I haven't, I'm out of
money. Mine is $3. What? I'm in debt right now. That's weird. What do you think? Like this? I like
like an orange or something. Yeah. Orange. That. And then maybe a green. I have a plan if this
doesn't work. And then what? Maybe light green. You need to put a blindfold on. No, I don't. I'm not
going to cheat. I'm thinking of green. Skittles. Yeah. Like the skittle is tropical either, or
maybe gray or like a dark red. What do you think? Just paint a hot dog. Turn off the monitor. Light
green. Like a lime green. Oh yeah. That might work. Yeah. Let's do that. I don't even know what I'm
going to do with this though. If I can't see what I'm doing on a huge canvas, it's going to be a
mess. I'm just going to let it do. I'm going to let my body decide what it's going to just go for
it. Okay. So in the middle we have orange. I want to be able to reach, I need to be able to reach
the whole canvas. I think that's good. I need my roller. Can I reach it? Okay. I can reach the
whole canvas from here. And now I got my brushes. Okay. How do I prove to you guys that I can't see?
Um, I actually got to put a bag on my head or something. Hold on. Give me one sec. I don't,
I don't have a blind blue. Where am I going to go? Oh, let me, let me see if I can find something.
Okay. I found something. So this is going to work. Not see through or anything. Uh, it's no,
it's not a duck beanie. I think I could just do this. So I was at the G4 studios to do obviously
Name Your Price and Hey Donna. And I got this like this G4 thing. I don't know what this is.
Like a cloth. I could just go like this. Wait, does that work? And I can't see through this.
It's pretty breathable. G4 ad. I didn't steal it. What do you mean I stole it? No, I didn't.
No, they, they, they gave this to me. They said, Hey man, here's some, some cool stuff.
I didn't steal this. I didn't like take this from the green room. All right. Hey,
G4 TV. You're over. You just saw in real time. We fucked that up. I thought you were right here
because that's where you usually are. You're over there now. And I did the thing where I
looked into the camera and it's not the right spot. All right, here we go. I don't know how
much time limit you're censoring your face with a G4 ad. That's funny. That's fine. I don't care.
All right, G4. Here we are. That this is not affiliated with this stream is not affiliated
with G4 in any way at the moment right now. There's nothing that G4 is not part of this
stream here. I just, this is a cool, uh, towel that I got and it's, it's pretty cool. And I'm
using it to blindfold myself. Make sure that they make that very clear. All right, let's go.
How much is my time limit? But I will say G4. Thanks for having me. That was really fun time.
Studio is really cool. All right. Okay. Am I in? All right, I'm going to go. Put it like five
minutes. There's no possible way I'm going to know where I am. Finding the paint is half this whole
thing. Is it not right here? I've no, I don't know where the paint is. I, I don't know. Can I reset?
Let me reset. Oh, I was right there. All right. Hold on. Let me reset and okay. Make sure I can't
see. All right. I'm ready. I know. I didn't know where I didn't know where to start. I'm with my
WASD. I don't know whether that is. All right, let's go. So straight over here, left, straight,
down. Do I have paint? All right. I heard that. I can't, it usually, it makes, it makes like a little,
uh, plop noise, doesn't it? When you touch it. Wait, I'm, where am I? I hear, I hear splashing.
Why did I just hear splashing? I think I'm next to the bucket, which means, oh, hold on. I heard
something. This is not, it's just impossible. If I had paint already on the brush and I could just
cycle through it or something. Am I too far away from the table? I think I'm too far away.
All right. I'm still on the ground. Why would I not be on the ground? I think I moved way too far.
I give up. I'm done. Use spray paint instead. Cheating. All right. I'm going to, I'm going to,
let's play multiverses. I will come back to this. We will do this. Uh, we'll do this on the next
stream. Maybe we'll do this. I like this double, the double feature shit keeps things interesting.
We'll do this in another game. We'll play this like a couple hours, two or three hours,
play something else two or three hours. I like, I actually enjoy doing that. So we'll come back to
this on the next stream. All right. So now I'm actually very excited to do what I'm about to do.
Because Gizmo is in the game. Yeah. This, this, this, this is sponsored stream, but it's awesome
though. And I'll tell you why. So I genuinely enjoy this game and Warner Brothers has essentially
reached out a few times. I've been like, Hey, do you want to like get sponsored again? I'm just
like, that's fucking, yeah, that's fucking cool. I played this game off screen. I genuinely enjoy
this game. Yeah. Well, uh, let me just set it up. We'll be right back. Give me like two seconds
and we'll come right back.