Hey, what's going on guys? Jerma here with a live commentary. Just want to go
over a couple of things. I want to talk about the new changes to the existing
items and how they change them and what I think about it. I am really really
excited. I'm so happy about some of these two new changes guys. As you see there
I'm using the Widowmaker which is the new... I don't want to say new because
that's not really true. It's the new-ish shotgun and they find... oh my god I'm
going to... look at what I just did... going on an absolute tangent... oh my god
this is a century. I just killed three people... well two people with an assist
and I didn't have to reload and I had a million shots. It was amazing. This new
gun... what they did... let me tell you... if you're unaware they made the Widowmaker...
I'll show you... one, two, three, four, five, six. You can now shoot this gun six times
with 200 metal and even if you miss... if you miss once or twice it's okay. You're
probably going to be able to get seven or eight shots with this thing if you
miss a couple times. It's a great, great change. Oh my god I'm gonna get killed.
See this... three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine... I just shot the gun nine
times without any reloads. That's more than the... what's the heavy one called?
The heavy shotgun... the family business. That's more shots than the family
business. The family business has eight and you have to reload it. Unbelievable
change. Hopefully I'm gonna try and go on a... some kind of tangent here. I'm not
even putting my sentry gun down. I'm being a real idiot. Oh it's on... this is
awesome. I'm so glad they did this. Oh what a backstab. So let me try this one
more time before I go into the other items. This is awesome. I'm so excited
that they did this because now I can unequip the Frontier Justice for a while
and use this. I'm not gonna say completely goodbye to the Frontier
Justice but at least for a while because they added this. This is so awesome. Okay
we're... there's a sentry over there. Oh my word. Let's see if I can pull this off.
There we go. Now notice how I have more metal than when I started with. What just
even happened? So I shot... I put down a mini sentry. I shot that Demoman two or
three times and I got back 40 metal. I'm pretty sure that it still gives you back
60 metal. So you shoot for 30 and you get back 60 if you land all the pellets on
somebody. So instead of before where you kind of was one for one, one for one. Let's
see here. Oh maybe not. It's 30 for 30. Okay. That's... that's still fine. That's
still awesome. I'm cool with that. So that's... I'm just so happy about this. Oh
they still have a teleporter up. Nice. Oh let's not... let's not reload one time and
just keep shooting this guy. Are you kidding me? Why is he not dying? What the
hell is going on? Are you serious? I haven't reloaded once. I haven't reloaded one time. Are you
kidding me? Why is this not being destroyed? Are you serious? What the hell just happened?
Why could I not destroy that teleporter? What the hell was that? Okay I want to
count after I'm done with this. I'm going to count. I think I shot like 30 rounds
in a row. Okay but don't ask me why that teleporter didn't go down. The engineer
must have been on the other side repairing it because that was pretty
ridiculous. I'm not gonna lie. That was pretty ridiculous. I think that's a spy
and maybe not. No it's not. I think there's a sentry over there. Nope. So you
guys get the idea. I'm gonna move on to the other items. Maybe see if I can get one
more kill. Nope. I'm gonna move on to the pyro and see if we can get something to
happen with the pyro. Oh nice black screen. So now please take a look at this.
The reserve shooter. You can now use it on the pyro. Very very cool. So let's see.
I'm gonna use the degreaser to get the fast switch. So essentially what you want
to try and do is you want to blast somebody in the air, switch over real
quick and get the mini crits. I am gonna love this guys because if you know how I
play pyro I play only pretty much with the shotgun. Where did that spy go?
Because he's around here. I could test it out on him. Oh well. Well I could test it
out on this dude over here. Heavy right here. Let's see if I can get behind him
or screw around with him. See if this works. Oh it worked but just not enough
damage. Oh this is ridiculous. So I'm gonna I'm gonna really like this. I
probably shouldn't have gone after that heavy. Actually what do I do? Why do they
light them on fire? They don't have to be on fire. They just have to be in the
air. Okay I don't know. I'm kind of freaking out about that right now. I
shouldn't have lit them on fire. Should have just blown them in the air just to
confuse them. Because yeah it's just when they're in the air when you switch over.
Now I wish they added the engineer. I mean they obviously they changed the
engineer a little bit but oh my god. Oh boy. Can I? Oh my god. Come on. Come on.
Nothing up here right? Did I get him? Sort of. Sort of. You do only get the three
shots up but I'm not concerned about that. I should be fine with that. Oh that
was awesome. Oh I could have just crit it. Oh come on. Oh damn it. I'm getting too
I'm freaking out too much about trying to get people in the air. I need to just
play pyro. Obviously I don't play pyro that often but when I do play pyro I use
the shotgun. So this should be really interesting setup. I'm gonna try one more
time because I don't want this to really drag on. So I'm gonna try this one more
time and see what happens. But yeah very very exciting. And one of the other
changes I'm gonna show you guys. One of the new changes they added but they
didn't really talk about it. And not very many people are talking about it is they
nerfed into the ground. Okay here we go. There we go. It's not doing a whole lot
of not doing a whole lot of damage. Usually a point-blank shot like that.
Mini crit. That should have killed them. Try this one more time. Actually no.
Not gonna be able to. I'm gonna try it one more time. But something that nobody really
talks about is they nerfed the shortstop. They made it 50% slower for reload.
And we might be even changing maps. And if we do yeah I'll see you guys in two
seconds. Okay we are back and we are on upward now. I actually changed service
because that one was going to a weird map that I didn't really know. So I'm
gonna show you guys. I'm gonna try and get a kill with this to try and
demonstrate it. Obviously if you've seen my previous live commentaries you know
that I'm pretty much a monkey in a box when it comes to trying to play in live
com at the same time. Don't know what that analogy even really means but I
just kind of made it up. Oh come on do that again. Do it again. Oh boink. Oh my
god I'm gonna die. So yeah yeah like I said before if you know my live comms
you know that I pretty much cannot play and talk at the same time because my
brain, at least in first-person shooters, it's hard for me to do that. Oh my god.
There we go. Nice. And this guy I'm gonna die. Oh don't you jump in the air. Don't
jump in the air. I got the reserve shooter. That was pretty cool. All right
let's get another kill and then I'll move on. Oh damn damn damn. I need heals. I
need to be healed. So this is very very cool. I'm so glad that they still care
about balancing the game even if it takes them a long time. Sometimes it
takes Valve a fairly long time to balance things and yikes. All right let's
see if I can get behind these guys and really mess up their day. Oh health I'll
take you and ammo. Thank you very much. What am I doing? I was like oh let me get
behind him or just pretend to get behind them and oh jump in the air. Jump in the
air. Okay looks like he's building a sentry. Ah damn it. I'm in a lot of
trouble because he's just got a sentry over there now. Maybe oh come on let's
cause a little bit of confusion. Oh my god he's back. No I'm so dead. I'm so
dead. I need that health. There we go. God I'm just like the oh my god. It's over
for me. Come on health spawn. I'm gonna have to go around the other side. Oh god.
Um can I reflect one of these rockets? No god. All right this is it. I'm gonna
change to the Scout just because this is kind of dragon. Oh goodbye. The question
is can I? No I'm screwed. Now it's over. All right I'm gonna change to the Scout
and show you guys the new change to the Scout. My god I have to put this on.
These don't really matter. Okay so the shortstop now as you can see. Let's see
one two three four. Oh man yeah the reload speed is 50% slower. It's a nerf
that nobody talked about. I'm gonna see if it really really affects gameplay.
Let's see this again. Yeah that's a lot slower. It used to be just pretty much
instant. Now it's about another couple seconds. Oh that yeah it's slow. That's
pretty damn slow. No I'm gonna get killed. Oh god. I want to kill that engineer.
Yeah there's a there's a pretty obvious difference. I don't think it's I don't
think it's really game changing or anything but I just got critzed and I
didn't do anything. I gotta get rid of that sentry. There we go. I didn't even do
it. Oh no no. Oh you are done. Oh reload time you are so slow. There we go.
I guess it's not too bad. A lot of it's not as fast as it used to be of course
but it's not terrible or anything. No boy I need to get healed or find a medic.
I got milk. I got the milk. I'm fine and give me that health. Give me that health.
Give me that health. What? Oh alright so it's not that big of a deal. I thought it
was gonna be terrible. It's okay. What else did they change? Obviously besides
I have to show you this just because I have to. So here's a look at my heavy.
Look at how ridiculous he is. Look at how stupid he looks now. I'm so glad. Look at
this because they made the the mask a miscellaneous item. So I can look like a
scarecrow from the Wizard of Oz now. Alright I'm gonna just I'm gonna end it
here. Just wanted to get a video out showcasing the new stuff the new changes.
Obviously I can't go over all the hats because I mean hats. Hats are hats. You
guys know the deal about hats. So let's just end this by going on like a tirade
as a heavy as the scarecrow heavy. Yeah!
Oh see you later sentry. I need a medic. I need a medic. Why I don't even know why
I have the shotgun equipped. I should have the sandwich equipped. Hmm hmm.
Oooh I can get rid of you. I can get rid of you. No I can't. Crap. Crap. Crap. Crap.
Crap crap crap come on, and I'll get this one over here, and that engineer is
Next time hey next time he goes to get metal. It's all over for this century. Oh
Come on go get metal go get some metal. Oh, yeah, there's nothing you can do now
Except that soldier can kill me for sure. Oh, it's gone
ooh
Before he kills me gimme gimme all right. Maybe we can actually win this now here. We go time to drop down
Let's get on that cut
How did I not that was weird?
There we go there. We go got to get rid of you got to get rid of you
What what's going on? No? It's up there. No spy you bastard. Give me on the cart. Give me on the cart. Oh
Jumper's gonna cap it as heavy and now we got okay. Come on over here. Come on over. Oh
I just have to get over here
Come on, and that's all she wrote we're gonna win. That's the end. Oh come on
Yeah
Nice all right guys. Thanks all so much for watching. I will see you all next time
hopefully you enjoy some of the new changes the new hats all the new things in the
Mano the Mano economy the man economy you anniversary god. I can't even talk, but yeah, see you all next time take care everybody