Hey, what is going on, everybody?
Jermah here, with Facecam Fortress 2, Saturday's edition.
Hope you're having a fantastic Saturday afternoon.
Cause it's Saturday afternoon, and your eyes are the size of the moon.
That's not the lyrics of that song.
But, what was that group's name?
Oh, god, they're the ones that were...
Like, what is, I can't...
Panic at the Disco.
They had, like, two songs that were famous.
Maybe, even one.
I'm probably thinking of two completely different bands.
Anyways, let's play some Pyro on upward.
Upward.
I think we're meant to change the bad water, I hope not.
Cause I just wanna play upward.
Mmmmm, delicious!
Oh, that's a coffee, by the way.
It's just gonna turn into a copy copy. Yeah, probably not though. It's only one. I haven't even drank
It's like that much gone set up time. Well, I've just been talking this whole time through set up time
Let's just like teleport to like the beginning the beauty of time travel. Let's do it, baby
Oh, you were our spy get out of my face
That took a long time to show up in the kill feed. All right, this heavy this heavy is dead
I'm gonna come out there. I'm gonna come catch up. I'm gonna come out the corner turn around
He's gonna get smashed. What are you on the cart? Get on the cart gentlemen. That is by for sure
No, it's not there's a sniper right there though. He's trying to pick me off. What were you going?
Where you going, bro? All right, too heavy. We've got two cod heavies. We're gonna be good
You know, I'm just gonna yeah, right Wow, a lot of these guys are the thickest spies are just not spies
Where's the enemy team? Oh dear goodness. Yeah, he's still alive. Yeah, I don't think so
I don't think so, dude. Maybe he does think so. Oh
No
What am I doing? What a terrible shot. That was like I caught up on my cord. I would have killed him
I like tried to turn my mouse and my hand went like
Sorry, we're good. We got this we got this that pyro. I got the home record on whoa. Whoa lag
How am I supposed to fight this battle? I know how to fight this battle though
I got to sneak around the back sneak around the back
Sniper you are getting lit and then you're gonna get what do you get backstabbed or something? Ooh
I'll doll here comes the dance. Here comes the dance of dragons dance of dragons. Oh
This guy's come on. This guy needs to die. Oh my god
How is that guy was just?
Unloading on everybody and nobody attacked him. Come on dudes. He's just like hiding in the corner
Somebody kill that damn heavy. I think somebody got him. Good job dudes. Oh, no somebody he's still alive. Oh
My goodness, that guy was like a spy heavy just sitting in the corner. Do do do do do do do do. Oh
Don't you dare? Don't you freakin dare? Oh
Me and this guy got this on the lockdown baby. Oh, I wish I got him with that. I got him with that though
Oh
Snuck your head out there. Not a good idea, baby. Oh
That's how you get some shots laid down any century over here, I'm definitely gonna drop down and just die
I had it. Oh dear goodness. No, no, no
No, oh
That was bad I had a
Mmm. Oh, well, let's just get back to it five minutes left in the mission five minutes left
In the mission. Oh
What do you think you're gone? Where do you where you go? What that guy was a slippery bastard?
Where the hell did he go? No, you killed my friend. What? Oh my god. That guy just like freaked me out
Oh knock him over the whole gate. Oh
God, I'm out of ammo. Oh, he's gonna get home wrecked. That's his fate. Oh, no, he's not. He's got the freaking crits
See you later. Oh god, stop lagging. I keep like glitching out. Yeah, stop it, you know, we're going all the way back to spawn
I don't think we're going to win this
Something tells me that this is not gonna care. Oh my god. You have that thing the beggars bazooka
Oh get away from me
I used to do that with my chocolate milk and
One time I did that and I almost puked all over the dinner table because I like how how is this even happening right now?
I'll explain why I almost puked in one second. No, don't burn to death on this
This is intense moment here. We got to push this card up. Okay now
I'll tell you so when I was little I used to do that all the time and my brother used to try and make
Me laugh when I did it
So one day I think I was like
11 or 12 or something. I don't remember but I did this I was going and my brother told a joke and I sucked in as
I was like I was like blowing out and then I went
And I literally almost threw up all over like the turkey dinner we were having it was pretty ridiculous
Okay, guys. Well, I just got back from a crash. Oh my god, and I'm gonna try to play upward again to change sir
Oh my god, dude, how many centuries are up there?
Hold on a second, dude
What is good? Why is there but it was three centuries up here. You guys are out of your minds. Oh my god
All right, well that's that's the one way to defend a point I don't think unless they
Louise with a piece of cheese
So yeah, I just came back from a crash happen sometimes and I record the face cam and the game at the same time
So hopefully it doesn't happen again. Hopefully I get this next few minutes of pure uninterrupted team fortress to goodness
And I changed to the medic and let's do let's get an uber going here. Let's smoke
Those sentry guns are freaking me out. No, no lag. Oh, I just what's happening here back it up back it up my friend
There's no way they're taking any of that out. No, no, not even had to use it. We were dead. We were dead
I'm just standing behind him. Hi. Oh, no, dude
I just went like flying and like broke my chin on the like the railing jeez
No, now they're gonna get it now. They're gonna get it. You know, I gotta change for medic
The heavy brass beast. All right, let's do it brass beast, baby
Gonna get a good position. I'm just gonna get back stabbed. Oh this heavy doesn't know he's no idea what's gonna happen
I'm gonna turn and just unload
Didn't kill anybody. I'll kill this guy though. This guy's gonna know what you're good. Do it again. Do it again
Come on. He didn't do it again. Oh boy. I need help. Why do I have these equipped?
Oh
No, that's the end of the line for me. Come on. Keep it up. Keep up the D
Keep up the heavy D two and a half minutes. We got this. Let me take off this though
I'm gonna put on a regular minigun and the gloves of running urgently
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Oh
Righty, then. Oh many crits. Is that many crits or is that the battalion? Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no
Get the medic just kill the medic and the sniper and the soldier. Oh just eat the sandwich
What a bad place to eat that sandwich
Thank God for that spy. Thank you spy. You just saved us all that's by just get out of here
I'm going up top going up top to deal with the rats in the vent
No, this is the moment of truth right here. I'm gonna get a million people in my face. Ooh sneaky
Sneaky that guy's gonna headshot me. I gotta get back. They're gonna get on the kill him kill him kill him
on fire
If I had made it around and like hid under those stairs, he would not have seen me that would have been so awesome
They're gonna cap it. They're gonna get it. Don't let him get it. Don't let him get it boys and or girls coming back
Now coming back. This is gonna be the final push. Here they come. I'm like being so like concerned right now
I'm just like okay. I gotta like stay around at the side get rid of this guy. Oh
Yes
Yes, feel the power of the uber and heavy. Oh
My god, it's like almost glitched out. Oh man. Oh man. Oh jeez Louise. Oh
We're gonna win that's how you win right there and they can't even get out of here. Come on out
Come on out boys and girls
We
41 points up because I was playing medic before
All right. Well guys that's gonna wrap it up here
Thank you so much for watching really do appreciate it and can I make it off can I jump it off?
Can I jump off the cliff quick quick? Come on? Come on. Come on. Jump off the cliff free. Oh
Take care everybody. I'll see you guys all soon