How's it going?
What's up?
Today, we're going to play Bouncing Duck Simulator.
Those of you that watched the Team Fortress 2 Man vs.
Machine stream, you would know that Poke gave us a pretty, pretty good
recommendation to play this game.
So we'll find out.
I, I do trust Poke's game recommendations, plays a lot of interesting stuff.
So here we go.
It looks kind of, it looks kind of good.
It looks pretty good.
I feel like I'm going to have fun with this for a little while.
I thought you retired.
I mean, yeah, it doesn't mean I'm not going to, I'm going to stream when I feel
like it and make YouTube videos still and work it off brand and check in.
Yeah, what's up?
I'm here.
I'm right here.
I'm still here.
He's a YouTuber now.
I can still hear him.
Yeah.
Cause I'm live right now.
About to play Bouncing Duck Simulator.
All right.
You guys ready?
I don't know.
The stream might not, might not be too long.
I know Armored Core 6 is the elephant in the room, but we'll see.
I did say I wanted to play this too.
Maybe I'll try Armored Core 6 on my own.
Maybe I'll stream it.
Maybe I won't.
Maybe we'll play Sorcery.
I don't know, but let's go.
You guys ready?
This song, by the way, has been stuck in my head since I was sitting here.
Listen to that.
Ready for the song?
Not the one.
I mean, this one's a, this is a banger too, but hold on.
Listen to this one.
This one has just been burning in my brain for a full, I want to say 20, 30
minutes of hanging out and getting ready.
You guys ready to hear this?
This is what I've been setting up to.
It's a, it, this thing's great.
It's great.
I can't, I, yeah, this is the game that poke mentioned.
Yeah.
I got to like DM poke and be like, Hey, I got to give him a review after this.
I will give him a full review.
That full review is going to be one sentence, but all right.
You guys ready?
Let's just play.
Let's hang out.
Make it louder, louder, louder, louder.
Um, it's kind of, it's all right.
That's good enough right here.
I don't know how loud the rest of the game is.
So not yet.
All right.
Bouncing duck simulator.
Start new game.
Stir would hate this game.
Oh, that's right.
Yes.
Durr would hate this.
All right.
So we woke up, we're in a, we're in a room.
Okay.
This mouse sensitivity is very high.
Hold on.
Uh, give me one sec.
How do I turn the mouse sensitivity down?
I do.
Okay.
Wait, can I do it through here?
How do I change the DPI of my mouse?
Does anybody know?
How do I affect the DPI of my mouse?
You're a grown ass man.
Yeah.
Wait, do I have to open up my like razor program?
Okay.
Razor.
This is the thing that I force quit every single time it opens, but I'm opening it
for real now.
Okay.
Here it is.
Uh, I don't have performance.
Okay.
Sensitivity.
The number of dots per inch.
It's currently at, I'm going to put it at 800.
See if that helps.
Holy shit.
This sucks.
How's it in here though?
Ooh, that's actually much better.
It has to be even lower.
Hold on.
Even lower.
Like one, like 600 probably.
Oh my God.
This is awful.
All right.
There we go.
I think that's okay.
I might have to lower it a little more later.
Why did I turn it off?
Okay.
That's much better.
Like a million times, but okay.
13, five, six.
What does this mean?
Zero.
What's up?
Okay. That's turning music on and off.
I mean, we're going to keep the music on.
Is there a sprint?
What do I get?
What do I get a duck?
Oh, wait, we're here.
Poke is worried that you're going to hate this and be mad at him.
That was okay.
This is loud.
I'm, I'm turning it down.
Oh, poke, poke.
Our friendship relies on me enjoying this game.
Uh oh.
He's nervous.
I'm going to love it.
It's a game where you, you don't have that to play.
I love these kinds of games.
Poke. One of my favorite games of all time is a game where you clean houses and
like hit walls with a fucking sledgehammer.
I, we're going to, it's going to be fine.
I just got 10 bounces.
That's gotta be a record.
Okay. So a whole left click and then left go to throw it.
Okay. What does right click do?
I'm going to do the thing.
I'm going to take my bouncy ball.
I'm going to run, sprint, hop, hop, hop, jump at the ground as hard as I can.
It didn't really work.
Can I spawn more than one?
No.
I only have 27 bounces.
What, how do I get more into the corner?
I probably get, if I get to a hundred, I bet it changes.
I kind of feel like a dog right now, but that's all right.
What happens when I get to a hundred?
99. All right.
This is it. 100.
I just got it.
Oh shit.
All right. So now I can press this button.
I have two, I have two ducks in here now.
What is this?
Health?
What do I do with that?
Can I feed it to the duck or something?
Whoa. Okay.
It's bigger.
Does this count for more bounces?
It was a battery.
All right. Well, all right.
I get it. I get it.
I know. I get the game now.
Poke. Don't ever call me ever again.
I'm just kidding.
I think I actually, I'm going to really like this.
I get it.
I get what's going on right now.
I'm into this.
I got to get to two.
What? 500?
I'm going, I think going in the corner corner, we'll get at least three or four.
Right?
If we stuff it in here and get it glitched.
That's a good strategy.
500. I'm going 500.
Shit.
Whoa. I got more.
Can I pick up more than one?
These things are worth two.
Watch this.
Can I pick up more than one?
Okay.
I love how this game was recommended for me.
Hey man.
I got a great game that I think you'll really like.
Oh, what is it?
Baldur's Gate 3.
Strategy.
RPG elements.
There's a lot of decision-making.
Not that one.
Armored Core 6.
Action-oriented.
Tons of difficult boss encounters and tons of upgrades to put in your character and make a mech that you can fight with.
Not that one either.
Dude, I think you'd be a huge fan of Zelda Tears of the Kingdom.
You can explore a vast, incredibly large open world.
And create any- No, not that one either.
I'd like to have you play with toys.
Now that one.
That's the one for you.
I'm just chasing around dog toys.
Is this what Otto feels like?
He's got Otto brain.
Oh, I got another one.
Oh, look.
Another thing to press.
Yes.
What is it?
All right. This is a big deal.
Do I give the battery to the pink one or to the yellow one?
Should we keep them the same size or?
I'm going for that.
To me, that was the right.
All right. What about like, wait, I can't pick it up anymore.
Why can I not pick it up?
How much is it?
Wait, I can't pick it up.
Oh, that's worth 10 now.
I think.
All right. I got it.
Just keep throwing shit at it.
You ruined it.
You need to restart.
No, I'm good.
I'll be okay.
Nice. Okay.
Thousand.
That one's different.
Okay. This one is permanently bouncing.
We're going to have to.
Okay. When we get the next level up, we're giving it to that one.
Also, by the way, I do apologize for anybody that does have a dog in the room and you're listening to this with a speaker.
Honestly, I can't.
There's not much I can do about it.
It's either that or turn off the volume, but I'm probably making a lot of your dogs head tilt at your computer right now.
And I, for that, I apologize.
All right. We got more.
Almost at 1500.
This one's different.
This one's like glass.
What is this one?
Can I break this one?
I'm scared to break it.
This is worth a hundred.
How much is that worth?
Okay, dude.
Oh, oh, I don't know if I did that wrong, but whatever.
All right. We have to focus on bouncing the big one with the little one.
That one's just a permanent stat increases.
So I'm gonna play this for at least a couple hours.
Like, that's what's happening today.
Ow!
Is this a pre-recorded stream?
No.
Wait, I can press the button.
All right. All right.
All right. This is, this is really important.
I'm going to give this to you because I want you to get, that's the right call, right?
Min maxing this, you would give them all to this eventually.
All right, here we go.
What's that giving me?
That's 20 each one.
All right. Keep that one moving.
Can I trap that in a corner or something?
Is he going to play this for 52 hours?
Not that long.
I do want to get to at least a million bounces.
Is that going to take a long time?
Is that going to take like more than two hours?
More.
More!
Okay. That one, all this one's metal.
I wonder if this one breaks.
Is that worth anything?
I can't tell.
That's not very much.
Maybe, I guess it moves more?
Heavier?
Nice.
I'm definitely gonna get to a million.
Easy.
I have so much training playing any video game on the iPad.
I'm going to be really good at this.
It kind of sounds like they're like yelling at each other or something.
He's an iPad baby.
I'm already at 10,000.
You don't think I'm going to get to a million?
All right. What do I up?
I'm going to upgrade this one again.
It's just too consistent.
I mean, the game is corrupt.
Is that going to keep, is that going to keep going the whole time?
That's not going to stay there the whole time, right?
Because I don't think I can sit in this room for two, more than an hour,
listening to this on loop.
Well, this one's magical.
What if I do this?
Shit.
All right.
I might have to put my own music on.
I'm going to have to put my own.
All right. At what point have I won listening to this?
Does anybody, anybody want to tell me?
At what point have I won?
30 minutes?
What if I just do it again?
Get over here.
Oh, get the fuck over here.
You're doing, you're doing like what every cartoon character in every single
piece of media does when they have sugar.
I don't, I don't think I can, I can't pick it up.
All right.
Where's the, where is it?
No, I lost it.
Oh my God.
Shit.
All right. All right.
All right. Right.
Right. I have to just yield it.
I'm giving it to this one.
If I knew that I was going to do nonstop Nyan cat, we would not be in this
scenario right now, but here we are.
If what, what 50 K is going to give me something good.
Probably. Right.
Should I break this?
All right. 50 K.
What's this one?
This one's just a regular one.
It's a blue one.
Yeah.
This thing is somehow not hitting anything in the room.
What is this giving for points?
Like 80.
All right. We got to actually start to use skill here.
This feels like an experiment.
A hundred K is going to get something good.
Right?
What's pokes high score.
I should wait.
Don't tell me.
Nobody tell me.
Uh, clear chat, mods, clear chat, mods, clear chat, mods, clear chat,
mods, clear chat.
Nobody tell me.
I have to, I have to beat pokes, uh, score, whatever it is.
72.
I got to get to a hundred K.
I have to turn this off at some point.
I personally can't take this.
I personally don't think I could take this.
This not the game, this song.
Look, it's a classic classic song.
Wait, that's another power up.
All right.
Can I please feed it to you?
Do you turn into something else?
Come here.
I'm just gonna stand still.
It'll hit me eventually.
It's given a lot of points though.
Right here.
Stupid.
I can't track it.
Just give it to the crystal.
Oh, I can't.
Um, who should I give it to?
Is this it fully upgraded?
What about the King?
No.
Uh, what about blue?
Who can I give this to?
Whoa.
Somebody just to throw pink.
Oh, guys make one.
Hold on a second.
I just made.
Oh dear God.
Uh, where's wait, I need both of you over here in the corner.
No shit.
Come here.
Can I crouch a hundred thousand bounces?
Let's go.
Okay.
How much is this one worth?
That's a lot.
I think this, ah, it's a bomb.
It's a bomb.
That's a bomb.
Just leave it over there.
I want to shut that off so bad.
I used to, how do I upgrade?
Who wants to upgrade?
What about you?
Get over here.
Why can't I upgrade anybody?
Oh shit.
That turned gold.
Should I blow one of these up?
I'm afraid of this.
I, we need to make more.
This is so loud.
I'm so glad I turned it down.
I think it's all about making, um, I think I honestly, I think it's all about putting
on the plock OST in five minutes.
You know what I mean?
I'm into this though.
I I'm definitely into, uh, I want to keep this going.
I want to get, I gotta get to a million.
If you're going to open this game, you'd better get to a million points.
Otherwise, why did you open it?
Why did you open the game?
Right?
I think that's fair.
Each one of these bounces from the baby is given, uh, at least one.
He's in the way.
Let me move him.
I hate when it flies by my head.
It's like somebody's zooming by me.
It's like when a fly flies right next to your head and it's in full stride and you
get that by your, oh, imagine if they played Nyan cat.
Another one of these.
One 50 probably is a milestone somehow.
I talk about like YouTube shorts.
Oh yeah.
I checked out YouTube shorts the other day and oh, I wasn't a big, I wasn't a fan.
And this is what I'm exposing all of you to.
There's a, there's a little bit of hypocrisy there.
I'm just going to focus on this.
Folks said, dude, he just disappeared from my friends list.
Just like, oh, he, why is he not?
Why is it not online anymore?
What happened?
I, is he, is he appearing offline or what happened?
No, if anything, poke, this strengthened our friendship.
I just want to make sure you understand that.
This, this strengthened our bond.
What's the goal?
Well, that's simple.
Number on right side of screen goes up.
That's it.
It's pretty, I mean, it's pretty self-explanatory, I think.
Number on screen go up.
I like.
Oh, will we, will we, I can't fucking do it.
Will we reach 500,000 subs today, guys?
I don't know.
I have a feeling it's possible.
Will we cross 200,000 subs tonight?
What would I have had to have done to get this many subs immediately?
What would be causing this amount of people to sub to a channel this fast?
What would it take?
Is this what, this is what happens if I shove the baseball up my ass?
Somebody said.
I'm not, I'm not, I am not shoving a baseball up my ass until we hit a million subs.
Right?
Let's just sit here.
Just what?
Just holding it.
I feel like it would be going down.
This would be going down.
This would not be going up.
No, this is very, hey, everybody in chat, quiet for a second.
We're talking about a comedic jokey thing.
This is not a real thing.
We're just talking about a jokey thing.
This is me pretending, please for the love of God, stop it.
Stop.
We already crossed a million followers in the channel like a year ago.
So excuse me.
All right.
We'll check back in on that later.
What's the next one?
Ooh, what are we going to upgrade?
What can I upgrade?
The bomb?
I don't think you can upgrade some of them.
Some of them just cannot be upgraded.
What about one of the little babies?
I got to get my subs up.
Oh, I farted.
It's working.
Oh no, they're going to go down.
All right.
I have to turn this fucking audio off.
Is it going to explode?
That honestly, that sounds like a, that sounds like a video that would be made in
2023, right?
On the wall here, I have my sub count.
I have to be in this room until my subs go over a million.
I cannot leave the room until it crosses that threshold.
I need more of these.
Look at this.
There's something here.
There's something on this wall too.
Look.
See this?
This like panels.
I'll probably get to open them.
I bet.
All right.
What was that?
Two 50.
What happens in two 50?
Maybe smash them with the metal duck.
Okay.
I mean that very clearly, it probably, maybe you upgrade it and it opens to like
another button to press.
All right.
Where is, where is the metal duck over here?
That was, it's so loud.
So you say smash this against the wall.
It worked.
All right.
I got something.
What is this?
X marks that.
All right.
What about over here?
Ooh, what's that?
Yeah.
I knew you could open those.
Is there any more of those?
There's gotta be.
Wait, a bomb.
Bomb, bomb, bomb.
Why is this a skeleton?
I'm going to throw the bomb at this.
It's absolutely what you have to do.
There's one on the roof.
Oh, there is one right there.
I don't think I can make that though.
Maybe with the, I don't think I had to like get higher.
All right.
Two.
We crossed two 50.
No button to press.
Who can I, can I, can I actually upgrade the, this thing still?
The, the Nyan one, or will you guys upgrade the skeleton?
Ooh, can I?
Whoa, it worked.
What does that do?
It has a face.
Is it worth anything?
I can't tell.
Okay.
That's cool.
We got to keep these things moving.
If you see one on the ground, it's not moving.
We have to make it move.
There we go.
That's much faster.
Something broke.
Whoa.
What, what was that?
Oh, look at this.
One of the big ones broke into a little ones that are giving me more.
I think when they break, they give you money or whatever it is.
Subscribers or whatever, whatever that who cares.
Nice.
Yeah.
All right.
Bomb on X bomb on X.
I can't get it to blow up.
Do I need a fire duck?
That would make sense.
I, you know, if there was a statistic to tell how many people muted the stream,
put it on the other monitor and are doing something else on the other monitor.
I think I might've broken the record for this channel right now.
Oh, pixel duck.
Dude.
That's every stream.
That's you're, you're so funny.
All right.
We have to blow this wall up with the bomb, but I don't think we're going to move the
big one around more.
It's worth so much more.
Where'd it go?
There we go.
Look at that.
300 K already.
What is it worth?
It's hard to tell.
All right.
Every, uh, everybody minimize the screen for a second.
Okay.
Minimize the screen.
Just like, don't just don't watch for a second.
I'm warning you.
Here we go.
Three, two.
What's going to get wild on the screen.
You ready?
Three, two, one.
That actually might be a good strategy.
I think we just need to do more of this.
No, I don't want more than 340,000 subs.
It's going to crash my computer.
I need to break this very clearly.
The last one broke and it was, it gave us a lot.
Throw gold at glass duck.
I was going to try that after.
Oh, it's going to work.
I can hear it.
Ooh.
Um, all right.
Once we get to half a million, I will put on whatever, uh, mods.
Just, Hey mods.
It's hard for me to talk, to take, to think and talk.
Um, can, can one of you, all right, hold on.
I need to say, I need to take my headphones out.
Uh, can somebody put a poll up of four fun OSTs to listen to and
just check and vote on it?
Mods can determine what they are.
We're looking for video game OSTs.
I'm good.
Okay.
Now I, now I cannot talk anymore.
I can't think anymore because my headphones are in.
Can you mute the music?
I wonder.
Progress will be saved.
All right.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
Can I mute the music?
I can't.
What duck decks?
Oh, it tells you what you found.
Wake it up in the corner of the room.
Oh, I don't know.
No, I don't.
I don't.
I don't care about how many subs I have.
Why did I do this?
Why do I give a shit about this?
I could just be doing anything.
I could be relaxing on the couch right now.
I don't care about how many subs come in.
It's too much.
Too many subs.
Hey, what's going on everybody.
Welcome back to the video.
It's me checking out that sub counter as we see here.
It's at 400,000 subs getting there.
I'd like to see that hit a million.
Jerry, I want to see it at a million subs, Jerry.
That's never going to happen.
We are absolutely going to get to a million.
There's no way we are not.
All right.
What do we got for, uh, what we got for, uh, OST voting?
Blow up the wall.
I don't know how I was thinking about this.
Yeah, I was trying to.
I need to light the fuse.
See, there's a fuse.
I need to light, but I was holding that way.
These are closed again.
This is going to blow up in my face.
It's going to blow up my face and be extremely loud.
I don't think so.
I like that one.
It's like a bullet going by my face.
It's that's, I don't like that.
Wait, hold on.
Can I pick an OST?
The mods have decided on a few, uh, get us in something.
Just chill and play the game.
I haven't seen an upgrade in a while.
These are not generating any points.
They have to be increased.
What's the diamond?
Uh, diamond is a diamond.
I can, I don't think I can reach anything up there yet.
I can't throw the metal on that.
I can't throw the bomb that high either.
Maybe the bone.
No, I don't think I have enough power to throw.
Maybe this one.
Oh, I actually might hit it with that one.
Hold on.
Shit.
Damn it.
Uh, congratulations, everybody.
Plock has won.
Uh, give me one sec while I turn this down.
All right.
I feel like my soul just re-entered my body.
Let's put on Plock.
Plock OST.
We listen to this all the time, but it's a good one.
All right.
Yeah.
Now everybody can relax.
Now we got a vibe going.
There we go.
I'm missing the quacks, but it's fine.
Turn it up a little louder.
You got it.
That's as loud as I'm willing to go.
All right.
Almost a half million.
Oh shit.
I just, I just turned the stream off.
I can jam to this and just play.
I'm into that.
All right, here we go.
We're at half a million.
Yes.
All right.
This is an upgrade.
This one's really important because I don't know who to give this to.
I think that, can I give it to anybody besides the skeleton?
What about the metal one?
Bomb?
I don't think I can give it to bomb.
All right, here we go.
All right.
Uh, this one, what did it do?
Give it a pixel duck.
Oh shit.
Uh, we're at 515.
It's going, it's going a lot faster.
All right.
I'm going to focus.
I need to start.
Look at this.
Look at how terrible I'm doing.
Look at all the, all the ducks that are on the ground that are not bouncing.
What am I, am I, am I even playing the game?
I need to be moving this one a lot.
Yep.
There we go.
Look at that number climb.
I need to like whack it.
This does feel like a YouTube short now.
600.
What happens at a million?
I missed the quacks.
I missed the quacks too, but removing the quacks also removed.
Um, uh, for the next three hours straight.
So it's a sacrifice we had to make.
I got to move the big one.
It has the most points.
So we just have to use the metal one is continuously move the big one.
Just play quacking sounds in the background.
No, no, I, no, I need a break.
I need a break.
I've been playing this for like 40 minutes.
I need a quick break from all that.
Let me just listen to pluck and throw things into walls and talk just for a little bit.
We need a break.
Everything's gonna be all right.
There's a speaker box.
Yeah.
This is the speaker box.
Unfortunately, it only turns off the music coming out of this.
It does not turn off the Nyan cat song.
I think I was going to go with some growth and growth makes sense here.
I'm going to focus.
Okay.
I'm going to focus on growth for the next 10 straight minutes.
All right.
So if I do anything besides focus on growth, I would like for you to all to be yell at me because that's exactly what I'm trying to do.
So at one hour streamed exactly is when I'm going to stop focusing on growth.
And then we'll focus on something else for a little bit.
If I see one, I'm going to bounce one.
How did I miss that close?
Where I wasn't actually, it actually is a little too soft.
Let's put it up a little louder.
All right.
That's a little meatier.
That's meatier.
We don't want it to meaty, but we'll be able to hear it.
You'll hear it.
All right.
Growth, growth.
Yeah, I know.
I got it.
Got it.
I love the Super Nintendo trumpet sound.
Well, like what is it?
Tuba.
All right.
Seven more minutes of this and then I'll be probably close to a million.
600,000 stay in the corner.
This is perfect.
I wish these would just automatically jump around.
I need more of those.
Um, Nyan cat ones.
Somebody just said, I don't understand.
Uh, honestly, I think, I think you do.
I think you're just afraid to admit out loud that this is what I'm doing today.
So it's like, no, he's not, he's not doing this, right.
But I'm into it.
So that's what we're doing.
You wouldn't get it.
I mean, there is not very much to get right now, but there's such, there's such
little to get right now that I do understand the, like, what am I looking at here?
I get it.
Okay.
Uh, we have five more minutes of this.
Five more minutes of growth and we'll be good.
All right.
Get moving over here.
What is going on with this corner?
Get moving.
Boss fight, right?
Shit.
It's actually going to get hard to pick up the ducks on the ground.
Oh, this is the one that I did that dance to that.
I keep seeing the same dance.
Point.
Point, point, point, point, you know, the one, uh, three more minutes we'll be at
700 and then after that, we're going to bounce around the big King duck and
hopefully get to a million pretty quickly.
Green light.
Ooh, okay.
It's 700 Ks in a green light.
We got, oh my goodness.
We're still focusing on growth.
So actually starting to get hard to move around.
A million was going to be easy.
Really underestimated how easy that was going to be to get there.
I mean, actually it's an hour.
You have to dedicate like at least 30 to 40 minutes to doing this.
I mean, I'm into it though.
I'm here.
Oh wait.
Bit rate, bit rate, bit rate, bit rate.
Oh no.
Is this going to be a bit rate stream?
How bad is it?
It's not that bad.
Okay.
It's actually fine.
It's fine.
I wonder how bad it'll get like vampire survivors.
I got one more minute of growth and then I'm going to focus on just trying to get
points with the big one and the metal.
There you go.
Uh, all right.
We're, we're pretty much done with growth.
800,000.
This is an electric guitar.
Why is it darker?
Oh, one of the lights is out.
Hold on.
Did I do that?
I think I knocked a light out.
All right.
It's time to focus on a million.
Let's make sure everything on the ground is moving pretty much.
All right.
Whoa.
That had a, I broke the radio.
Oh shit.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
What do I give this to?
Who should eat that?
Pixel.
All right.
Where's pixel duck over here?
Oh, is it, is it going to be, what's it's worth now?
Like the rainbow.
All right.
Um, is it going to do, is it going to bounce around like the Nyan cat or no?
It's just worth a lot.
It's probably worth a lot.
All right.
Focus on hitting big one.
Throw the bomb up.
Yeah.
I can't reach that far.
The roof is still not broken.
Yeah.
I can't reach this far though.
Skeleton.
Wait, is that, that's not a fire.
Is it?
It's not like a candlelight.
Is that a candle?
Wait, this thing's smoking now.
Does this count as a fire?
That might count as a fire.
Wait, maybe I can throw this to the roof.
I might be able to make it to the roof with that.
Ah, oh shit.
I almost had it.
Damn it.
That's hitting it.
Oh, somebody said, maybe I can do this.
Place this and maybe throw something heavy at it and smush it.
I don't think that's going to work.
It's a couple of good direct hits.
Break the other lights.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
This is important.
I'm almost at a million subs.
Get, get out of my way.
This is my moment.
I was at a million subs guys.
I was here.
I need to unmute for this.
Did I unmute?
No, I'm going to miss it.
I'm going to miss it.
No, I'm going to actually miss it.
One million subscribers.
Something's happening now.
All right.
We need to turn this off, this music off.
What is going on right now?
Turn the volume up.
Did I just beat the game?
I can't move.
I just won.
I think I have to catch them.
He's coming.
He's actually walking towards me.
Shit, he's coming.
Is this going to do like a five minutes at Freddy's?
Like, if I'm just, I'm warning you, it probably will.
We're probably there right now.
You jump scare probably incoming.
What?
I didn't beat it.
The end.
The game just turned off.
I got the, no, that was the good ending.
I said, good ending.
How do I get the bad ending?
You had this open for 15 minutes before your stream.
Yeah.
Cause I had, I was like getting my stream ready.
And it was just sitting on the menu because I was like, I had to get my stream ready.
I had to, you have something to eat.
I didn't want to just close everything.
All right.
So how do I get the other endings?
I need to open that thing up there.
You need to, okay.
Skeleton duck.
But how do I open this thing?
I don't know how I need to blow up the wall too.
All right.
Blow the wall up.
That's important.
Okay.
How do I do that?
I need the bomb.
There are multiple endings.
Apparently I want to get at least a couple of them.
Upgrade the skeleton all the way.
But I might have to do a new game for that though.
All right.
Where's bomb duck?
How do I light bomb duck?
Break the radio on bomb duck sparks from the light.
Yeah, we'll get, let's break all the lights.
How do I get more force?
Do I have to do it with the gold one?
Maybe I have to get some, get some air stand on the box.
Oh wait.
I know what you mean.
Okay.
Damn it.
Can you smash the screen?
Smash the screen.
Hold on.
Wait, that might actually work.
I broke it.
What did that do?
I want to open that.
I want to open the ceiling panel.
Wall panels might do it.
That's a good idea.
Stop knocking it out of my hand.
Stop.
This might be fire.
It actually might be, but how did I break it before?
I'm going to start over.
Try to make a spark with the metal one on.
Yeah.
I tried that before.
It didn't really work.
Start over.
Smash the radio with the metal.
Oh shit.
Shit.
Okay.
I got one.
Now who do I give this to?
The bone?
It's not there yet.
Do I get any more?
Um, do I get any more juice to give to the bone duck?
Bomb?
Uh, I can't, I can't give it to the bomb.
The bomb doesn't take it.
You might have to restart.
I think you get one more.
You have to smash the radio when it's off.
You would think this would work.
All right.
I got one more for the bone.
Ooh, now what?
What does this do now?
Maybe I can break the panels now.
I can't remove the panels with this.
It's just really cool looking.
Smash the radio more.
I feel like a caveman.
I don't think so.
I got to get that panel off.
Maybe I shouldn't have upgraded the duck.
I think I, all right, hear me out on this.
I might have to start over to get the small duck to break the lights and
break the panel off the ceiling.
You know what I mean?
The metal duck will create sparks.
I can't get it.
God help us.
Use the angel for the ceiling.
Does it have enough weight?
I'm not sure this has enough weight.
Break the angel maybe?
That's not a bad idea.
Oh, that was a direct hit.
That was a direct hit.
Smash the button.
Good idea.
Smash that like button.
Press it a hundred times.
Oh, what just came out?
What was that?
I heard something come out.
What is that?
Potato?
Like a baked potato.
Ooh, wood.
This is wood.
Wood makes fire.
Fire makes electricity.
Electricity makes currents.
Currents allows for a bomb to be lit.
Okay.
Here we go.
Come on.
I need a spark.
This has to work.
How could I, how would this not light on fire?
You need fire.
I need a fire duck.
Wait, what if we put the fire, the wood right on top of the vent here?
Can we like roast it?
Like a marshmallow kind of?
No, we need, we need a duck that's on fire.
So the way that you're problem solving is concerning.
Dude, it's a, it's a duck game.
I'm not changing a tire.
You were right the first time.
Restart.
Fire.
Okay.
All right.
Well, you have to, we're restarting.
It's a lot of ducks I haven't seen yet.
All right.
We'll get, we're going to restart.
New game.
Stop bullying Jerma.
Stop.
What the heck did I do?
Thank you.
You've ruined it.
I don't think I did.
I had the, okay.
That metal duck was small enough for me to throw.
I think I need to use the metal duck to break that panel and break the lights.
Oh shit.
I can get them back.
I'm not getting to a million again.
I just want to see, I want to see what's behind the panels.
We, I want to see the content.
That's a good strategy for the beginning.
It's kind of very gently.
You got to get, here we go right here.
And then just shake.
This gives us the metal one.
No.
All right.
I don't want to use that.
Okay.
Keep all the power-ups in the corner.
Cause I don't want to use them until later.
So now, wood, you get the wood duck.
Oh, that's right.
All right.
Wood duck.
Upgrade the wood.
Let's see what happens.
Nothing.
No upgrade for the wood duck.
Okay.
Well, how much is the wood duck worth?
Nothing.
All right.
Well, we have to stay with the strategy.
Strat's going to stay the same.
What was that?
Look at the above.
Wait, what if we get to one, three, five, six and just don't do anything?
Does that make sense?
One, three, five, six.
And then I'm done.
Right.
I know I'm going to see what happens.
That's worth two.
All right.
We're going to do the wiggle strat.
Yep.
Right.
This is the one.
All right.
Keep that power up.
I probably want all of them over here.
I have two right now.
Don't let me forget that.
Cause I will.
One, three, five, six, seven 52.
I don't, I don't want anybody bouncing around right now.
Use the bottom tri corner.
I think I can't really crouch, but that actually worked pretty well.
I wish I could crouch.
What's your favorite pasta sauce?
Uh, that varies.
Sometimes it's like a tomato, garlic, basil.
Sometimes it's, um, nothing at all.
Actually.
A lot of times it's actually just olive oil and a little bit of salt.
A little bit of pepper.
That's probably actually my favorite way to eat it.
My favorite way to eat pasta is just a little bit of olive oil and a little bit
of salt and pepper, maybe sprinkle a little bit of Parmesan, but not necessarily.
Pesto is amazing too.
Butter, buttered noodles.
Andy, I would like for all of you to just look up pasta and olive oil and
understand that that is a classic dish.
That is not, that is not like a children's menu dish.
You actually need to look into that because you've got that wrong.
This is really upsetting him.
All right.
One, three, five, six.
Stop bouncing around.
Yeah.
I really, a nice olive oil pasta.
Not a whole lot either.
Just, just enough to get it.
A little bit, just like a touch of salt.
He's having fun.
Actually, I am actually having a lot of fun.
All right.
Wait a minute.
How many bounces does it do?
If I just let it go like right here, two, three, four, five, six, seven.
Oh my God.
This is going to be fucking horrible.
Did I get it?
I don't know what happened.
I don't understand what I was supposed to do.
What did I, what did I do wrong?
Nothing happened.
You understood you just messed it up, but what did I do?
I have to actually restart it.
You were impatient.
Do I just stand in the middle of the room at one, three, five, six.
You need to click the button.
It just gave you, it just made the button green.
All right.
Did it actually even do anything or am I being gas lit?
3000.
All right.
Keep these.
You lost an upgrade.
Where's the, where's the other one?
Did this thing eat it?
Okay.
Um, I want the metal duck, so let's just go ahead and hang out and talk about
pasta for a little bit of minutes.
All right.
Uh, so there's the metal one right there.
Cool.
Perfect.
Nice.
Okay.
There's electricity up there now.
I think that means bomb, but let's break everything.
What happens when I do this?
You stupid piece of shit.
You actually got into the corner.
You viewed the DVD menu thing, hit the corner.
It's impossible.
That's exactly why I placed it all over there.
All right.
What happens when I do this?
Okay.
That's kind of creepy.
Don't touch that.
Okay.
Now what?
What was that?
It's like Satan duck.
I feed it.
I'm going to feed the Satan duck.
You can't.
Okay.
So what's the point of this though?
Now I'll get the angel duck.
Um, okay.
Angel duck is just any points, right?
What gives a lot of points?
I got to catch the, uh, all right.
This is going to be unbearable.
I'm apologize already, but we have to do this for a minute.
Uh, I need to grab that and go into the corner and just do the wiggle.
I need bone duck.
Oh, yep.
Yep.
What corner is it in?
Thank God.
Hey, this bone green button.
Do not do not do not do not.
Here we go.
I think I have enough to do it.
Don't I?
The three or four are angel duck.
And I have the Satan duck.
What happens when I put them together?
Nothing so far.
I'm glad I have light though.
Let's put it like right in the middle.
All right.
There's a blue.
Hold the bad one.
Hold on.
Oh shit.
You make them evil.
Wait, can you do that with the angel duck too?
You can.
What is it doing?
Is it making them just regular size?
That's an original duck.
Now make it the King evil.
Can I even upgrade wrong duck?
I wish I could see anything.
Okay.
So wait, get over here.
Does it not do anything?
Read the duck decks.
Dark duck.
Bomb duck.
Holy duck.
Skeleton duck.
Still missing a few.
Extra large duck.
16 bit duck.
Holy duck.
Isn't that the one I already have though?
Read, read.
I can't like open this.
Throw the wood at the wire.
I don't want to throw the wood at the wire until I have the bomb.
That makes sense.
Doesn't it?
If I light it right now, will it stay on fire?
Oh shit.
I don't even know what the panel is.
Not that side.
Evil duck is removing points.
That's all right.
All right.
This is all right.
Here's bomb duck.
I need to take a second because I need light.
Where's the bomb panel.
I think it's, I just got hit in the head in like real life.
That felt like, okay, there's this panel.
The other panel is on the other side, right?
Where is this panel?
Where is the panel?
What side is the panel on above the button?
Does that work?
Hey dude, do you want to see the burrito?
Um, I'm sure it's delicious, but I'm good.
Thanks man.
There it is.
Okay.
I see.
Is that it?
I should have broke this before.
I wanted to place that there for some marker.
Got it.
Okay.
Wood duck.
Where's wooden duck?
Wooden duck is right here.
Light wooden duck on fire.
And then hold on.
It's a button to press.
Okay.
Put that in the corner over here.
Where's that bomb panel?
It's right here.
Get over here.
All right.
There it is.
Place.
Can you place that a throw?
I don't think you can place.
I'd like for it to end up hanging out in the corner over there though.
Oh, whatever.
I know where it is.
Just give me.
I can't just let go of it.
And when you let go of it, you just whip it against the wall as hard as you can.
Is it off?
Okay.
It's off.
Now I need to, I have to place this here.
Like I have to just figure out how to get stuck.
It just bounces way too much.
We're gonna have to just guess.
All right.
Where's the wood?
Okay.
Let's light that.
Actually leave that there.
I'm going to put the bomb right here as close as I can get to this.
Cause it's going to fall and then I need to light it.
So it's right next to it.
Okay.
It's right here.
That's probably too close.
Is it not going to work?
Oh shit.
Okay.
Where's the bomb?
It's the bomb.
How long is that on fire for?
Get over here.
Where's the bomb?
Where?
Oh my God.
You stupid fucking thing.
I hate that Nyan cat thing.
You just ruined everything.
Where is it now?
Oh my God.
Get out of my way.
Where did it go?
All right.
Stop right there.
It's directly across.
No, it's not.
It's a little bit to the left.
All right, here we go.
I need to grab the bomb because it's right here.
It's not directly across.
Where did it go?
Did that stupid Nyan cat thing fucking knock it out of the way?
I hate that thing so much.
I don't even know where it is now.
Where did you knock it?
Well, here's the bomb.
Oh my, give it to me.
Oh my God.
I'm I hate this game.
Give me my panel back.
I need one light panel.
Is it, is it lit?
All right.
It's lit.
What is this?
This is a purple duck.
Oh, it's pink.
Where are you?
Okay.
There he is.
Now, wait a minute.
Right across here.
I have to, oh my God.
This is going to be loud.
Is that the right spot?
I got it.
I love this game.
Okay.
Now I can break that open with the big metal duck.
I have power up somewhere, right?
Oh, do I need a key?
Do I need a key?
You have a negative score.
I just found out you ate him and this game.
I didn't even want to click on it.
The Nyan cat pushed it into me.
Can I break it?
Do I actually need a key or could I break it?
I can definitely break it, right?
All right.
Break this.
I can't skeleton key duck.
Uh, I already have this.
I don't have a skeleton anymore.
Wait, does that actually work?
Upgrade fire.
Can't yeah.
Skeleton became angel.
I can't leave without, I got it.
At least I got it.
I can't not open this.
This is like the big treasure chest of the game.
Burn it.
Upgrade the chest.
Oh, you need a negative score.
All right.
So, all right, all right, all right.
Let's go.
I got it.
So we have to make a bunch of devil, um, bunch of devils and that will bring my
score negative.
Is that accurate?
All right.
This is going to take a little while.
So we're going to put a new OST on.
Can we get a recommendation?
Maybe make, can you make the Nyan cat want a devil?
I'm not sure you can.
Now I'm not leaving until I open this box.
This is like the good ending.
Uh, I'm just going to keep making them.
Can I upgrade them?
All right.
Uh, yeah.
Mods get a, get a good four choices.
No, no one's forcing you to play this.
I, I want to play this.
That's why I'm playing.
I not jokingly enough want to see the end.
Am I, I'm not losing points though.
Smash the battery again.
Make a negative battery.
Uh, it sounds a little too complicated.
I feel like I have to restart to get to the next part, but I can't.
I feel like I gained way too many points with the Nyan cat one.
Cause I'm gonna have to sit here and make a ton of negative scoring ducks and it's
going to take an hour to reverse it.
I'm going to give it one more try.
The runs are ruined.
It's all right.
The key is minus 50 K.
Okay.
Leaving the lights on this time.
So this time the goal is to get, just don't break the lights.
Okay.
You need to break the lights to get devil duck.
Oh, that's true.
You need to break the lights eventually.
Hmm.
I think, yeah, I think I can get the wood duck first.
Get the bomb done out of the way.
Yeah.
I'm going to, once I get the chest out, then I can figure that out.
Bomb will come after the Nyan cat.
Yeah.
Trying to not get the Nyan cat to upgrade is the real problem.
Where can I put this?
We're just maybe like behind here.
Okay.
What if I do this?
I'm going to make a shield.
So it'll never, it'll always have to bounce off of this first.
It's not going to ever go in there.
We need to make a protective box.
So now it almost physically can't touch it.
Okay.
I'm giving this one more attempt, and then I'm going to open up the
armored core six tutorial and, um, get very angry.
I don't think I will.
I think I'll have fun.
Okay.
So what's the order?
What do you guys think?
What's the order?
Wood duck?
Blow up wall.
I got to get metal duck.
Oh, that's a good idea.
Hide the batteries in the, where the bone duck was.
Break one light.
Make a bunch of children.
Then once you blow up the wall, turn all the lights out to get the
devil and bounce them around.
Good idea.
Actually.
Great idea.
Okay.
That was about right.
All right.
We got hot wheels, stunt track coming up.
Hot wheels, stunt track.
Oh, S T.
Is this, what was this for?
Hot wheels, stunt track.
Oh, S T.
I think this is correct.
Ooh, this sounds pretty good.
All right.
I'm into this.
Cool.
It's like rubber ducky death metal.
He's saying all kinds of fucked up shit right now.
This is not death metal.
He listened to this death metal.
You need to open poke stream right now.
It's very important.
Why?
This warlock thing, this warlock, this warlock, this warlock item.
He's kind of doing it to the beat.
Oh, keep going.
You're cooking right now.
Just keep farming money.
It's got a lot of gold and we should start investing on items.
Is it cheating if my viewers send me items and I buy it?
Respectfully, for a good price.
Does he have my stream up behind him?
It sounds like a promo for poke stream.
Like here's the crazy stuff that poke gets up to.
Oh, we've been caught.
Jerma, did you, did you get the ducks or what?
Yeah, it was awesome.
I got to a million points and I'm still working.
I'm still trying to figure out how to, uh, get the box open, which is pretty,
it's been pretty interesting so far.
Okay.
I can't listen to the stream anymore.
Cause I'm listening to myself three times.
How do I get the box open?
I'm stealing your content right here.
Thanks Jerma for the content.
He just starts throwing shit in his room.
That kind of sounded like he's doing his own duck bouncing.
He's like, Oh, Hey, thanks.
I got, I got, I got some ideas now.
He just starts picking up shit in his room, throwing it into the walls.
All right, let's keep going.
Hold on a second.
This is important.
Let's see if we can get ourselves up on the, don't, don't say anything to poke.
You're sweating.
I was not sweating this much when I played Elden Ring.
It's just my right arm too.
My left arm, my left underarm is perfectly fine.
Holy shit.
All right.
Well, that was fun.
Stay with the, uh, stay with the, what I was doing.
What did I get behind him?
Was that, did I get to be on the screen behind him?
Good.
Was it good?
He's in the middle of like a hard fight in dark and darker.
And I'm just sitting there behind him.
I just start smoking behind him.
Hold on.
Here's the clip.
Wait, wait, wait.
This is important.
I want to see this.
Where's the clip.
I got to get this on.
Hold on a sec.
We got it.
We got to get this on the big screen.
Hold on.
Oh, where is it?
Okay.
Here we go.
All right, here we go.
Let's see.
Did your name's a bad look for me, man.
I'm just going to say it right now.
I don't know him.
That's so stupid.
I love it.
He's flipping me off.
Oh, you can see him like pull out.
Oh, that's great.
Oh, that's, I love that.
That was amazing.
Okay.
So, uh, let's get back to the game.
What was that?
What was the, I want to know what, what was I doing?
I forget what I was doing.
Back to business.
Yeah.
All right.
Back to this.
He stayed full screen after that.
Cause he was in the middle of it.
Oh, I need the music.
Can't just have no music on what's going on here.
Okay.
So stay with the plan.
I'm doing this and I'm, I, this is it.
I'm having fun with this, but I want to do this tutorial in armored
core and then turn my stream off.
The battery in the corner.
Yo.
Yup.
Oh, yup.
We do not want that Nyan duck to touch this.
Hopefully this is a good spot.
We need the metal duck yet.
Wooden duck right now.
Um, wouldn't, what was the process to get wooden duck?
I need to break this.
Let me break it.
Wait.
I can't break that without metal duck.
I think I have to keep going.
Ah, that's right.
It's a button.
Thank you.
Appreciate it.
Oh my God.
I've lost it.
Lost my touch here.
Looking good so far.
So now, now I just need to get enough points to get, uh, you know,
that's just putting up like fucking like Lord of the Rings.
Would we both get banned?
Okay.
I think we're close.
All right.
Do not bounce into the corner at all.
We're going to continue.
What do you mean ruined?
What?
Upgrade the normal duck.
Guard the corner.
No, it is this it's blocked over there.
Okay.
We have to, we got to hurry up because we need to start.
We need to, we need the blue duck.
Then we got to get rid of all the lights.
Did I fuck it up?
Don't break this.
What poke stream in your corner?
I can't, I can't do that.
You just broke it.
I'm paying attention to too many things right now.
I, I need the blue duck.
I'm, I'm going with what I know.
His Sims queue is full right now.
You, that is a good way to put it.
Seriously.
Actually a great way to put it.
Did we get that way though?
Honestly?
No, like joking around.
Okay.
Here comes now the strategy that that chatter said, don't you dare touch that.
You cannot upgrade the wooden one.
Unfortunately, it's not upgradeable.
I think I need like 5,000.
What pokes webcam on your stream?
Oh, but that would mean poke would have to be full cam for me to do that.
Hey, we'd have to be full cam pretending to play this game.
I don't think that's going to happen.
No, poke is, is playing dark and dark.
He's probably having a good time.
Crop it.
So you can crop it.
Now you've got me.
Now you got me interested.
All right.
Hold on.
This is going to take a minute.
Don't tell him we're doing this.
I know you, you guys are going to just, you guys are going to rat us out.
Okay.
This is going to take a second.
Cause I'm going to crop it.
Well, you know, try to stop talking to, don't tell him I'm going to stop talking
to, this is going to be actually fucking hilarious.
Hold on a second.
Nobody blow this because this might be very funny.
He's going to be talking about the game.
His game is going to be like, what is he talking about?
Okay.
Hold on.
You need this to be bigger.
Turn it up.
I have to do this quick.
Cause the background in his stream is going to change.
Okay.
Where is this?
Shit.
That's not the right one.
Okay.
Give me a sec.
It's important that nobody blows this.
Keep chilling.
You guys are doing great.
You guys are doing great right now.
Just hold on.
Where is he?
Rat pendant.
I'm going to go for it one time, guys.
Wait, isn't rat resourcefulness?
This could be very useless, right?
Resourcefulness could be very useless.
Wait, resourcefulness is that right guys?
Yeah.
It's probably the worst one too.
But what if it's at a 900 gold, 900 gold?
Oh shit.
My food's here, guys.
I gotta go to a laughing face.
I look at my food.
Oh shit.
I can't move.
Oh, he's getting food.
He's getting food.
We can't move.
Wait, the face cam's not even right.
Fuck.
Hold on.
I got McDonald's.
I turn off the blue.
Don't never buy no weed from the gas station, bro.
Wow.
45 months in the pond.
Love you, man.
Hey, when does he notice though?
Hope he's making coffee.
Okay.
Wait, what's going on here?
What?
Yo, what?
I, uh, so I think what's going on with the, you know what?
I think it was bugged for a second.
Did you guys see that?
There's probably internet, something going on with the internet.
I, uh, heard that there's like an internet, like Ross thing today.
There's like a, like a cross, like some wires or something today.
Guys, well, we got food.
So let's just react to Derma now while we have eat food, but to react to my
favorite streamer and eat food.
And what, while we have like a little bit, like a little bit, but to react
to my favorite streamer, while we have like a little bit, what's happening?
Is he, was it me on his computer?
I can't hear him.
Talk.
Is it bug?
Is he, is it me on his computer?
I can't hear him.
Oh, is it buggy?
No, I just got to hit this duck more.
That's all I got to do.
We're just doing this duck thing.
And if this, if I restart one more time and get this battery hitting this, uh,
that, that duck thing, you know, it's going to piss me off more.
That's all I got to get this right.
Duck here, guys, duck thing.
And if this, if I restart one more time and get this battery hitting this, uh,
that, that duck thing, you know, it's going to piss me off more.
That's all I got to get this right.
Duck here, guys, duck thing.
And if this, if I restart one more time and get the battery hitting this.
Uh, that, that duck thing, you know, it's going to piss me off.
I feel really strong about this in my, uh, my arms hurt.
I've been a sore.
I've been sore.
And, uh, I've just, you know, yeah.
Oh, yeah, I've been just really sad about what is going on in the community of us
You know, but it's okay. We can get through this. I
Don't even know if he's hearing me right now
my butt
with enough time guys, we can get through this duck stuff and
I am
Gonna address the swollen balls allegations very soon
Jerma, what are you doing?
I don't know. I just kind of went off the rails. I'm sorry. I just want to eat my food man. I'm sorry
It's just kind of went off the rails
You got McDonald's though, enjoy your McDonald's I love McDonald's
All right, I closed a spring let's finish this out now the game is really fun poke
I don't know if you're still watching but that's fun. All wild Nyan cat is in the background makes that better
Oh
That was it that was a good that was really good that was a good call on his part. Okay, so I
What did I have to do
Get rid of that. It already upgraded. How did it upgrade twice already? What how how did I have this much negligence?
Okay. All right. I gotta get this back on track. I need the metal one. All right
No, no, no, no the chatter said to do it like this
Here we go, we're gonna make a bunch of
We have to make a bunch of babies
At least what 20 or 30 metal is already upgraded. Oh, yep. Okay. Oh, so it's over. Oh, it's over
Okay, it's actually over because it was already upgraded already upgraded
Okay, we're gonna play armored core. That was really fun
I did not think I was gonna get two hours out of this, but I did that was really fun
Poke recommendation. I'm gonna give this in a minus
All right, let's play armored core. That was fun. I enjoyed that
Okay, let me let me actually do a beer beef. I'm gonna pee refill my water and I okay
the armored core section of this stream is gonna be like
Not even 40 minutes. So I'll see you for armored core 6 in about 2 minutes. I promise
I'm not gonna leave you with this