Hello, hey man. Hey, what's up? I didn't do my tweet yet. Oh, you said hi there. I
thought that was an invitation. Well I see I said hi there because you said you
had me say hello so I was responding to myself before you. What are you talking
about? What do you mean? You just you have like a soundboard that says hello?
Can I at least give you a new one? A new hello? Yeah. That one's old. I don't like it. I don't
know if I have it set up correctly right now. Say something. Hello. I don't have it
set up right. Do you really want me to take the moment and get the new hello?
No, no. God no. Oh, God no. Why not? Why do you do a folder on your computer
that's just Jerma saying hello? Wow, ego on this guy. It's also Ashley and Ronnie
and I think someone else. It's just a randomized hello from multiple people. Oh
it's randomized. Okay. All right. Let me tweet in as a TF2 with stirliftsfood 2014
time machine active. That looks good. Looks good to me. It does. Okay. Hi stir.
How are you? I'm good. How the heck are you? Headshots. I'm going crazy with the
headshots in my chat still saying lol aim for the head. So good luck today pal.
All right. So are we gonna be on a team together and we're gonna queue for team
Fortress 2. Are we? Yeah. Can we please God? All right. You want to just do I have to
wait for you to be done? No, I can leave. Are you ready? Like now? Or are you ready?
Like already? I'm hold on. I didn't say I didn't do my like intro. Shut up. Shut
up. Shut up. I'm ready. Can you invite me? Yeah. I should be able to be invited to a
game. You just have to be appearing online. I mean, uh, my God, there's there.
There. There throw a tantrum there. I'm on. Is your name like it's a break the
fish. You'll find it. You have to be in the game. I'm in the game. Well, it
didn't work. Why not? Oh, wait, wait, wait. Are you me? Yes. All right. I think
it's gonna happen. I said I said yes. I said I clicked on play game. Sure. What's
happening after rejoin? Maybe let me try inviting you. You have to do it from the
main menu, not the steam invite. Oh shit. I disabled my entire friend panel in the
config file. Hold on. Okay. How come I have this thing next to my name? You know
you carry on. I'll get this figured out. I'll get this figured out. I downloaded a
custom HUD and shit and I fucking deleted the whole friend panel. You need
the friend panel. Hold on. Here's the bigger question though. Why? How come on
my steam is permanently broken? What do you mean permanently broken? I can't
ever be invited to what's going on with my voice. Why did you do this? I can't
get invited to any games. Nobody can ever invite me. This is I'm like
permanently blocked forever. You might be shadow banned, but this one again is
not like technically steam invites don't work. This is from the main menu. All
right. Give me a second. I can invite you in two seconds. Yeah. Maybe you have your
privacy on no friends. I'm ashamed of my friends and I didn't want their names to
wait a minute. Wait a minute. You don't want your friends like furry avatars to
No, it's just like you get like 7,000 friend requests that you steam did this
thing where you could never like stop that from happening. You remember that?
No, no. I remember having so many friend requests that you actually couldn't send
anymore and I left it that way so that I wouldn't get anymore and every time I
wanted to actually let someone on my friends list I had to like ignore and
deny one person. Otherwise they couldn't send a friend request because steam
couldn't handle it. Going through the console command? No, we have to be in a
party as we queuing up casual. Let me take one second and see if there's like
something fucked up in my steam because I got a problem. If your chat tells you
to do something they're telling you how to do it from the perspective of it's
2010. That's true. Hold on. So when they tell you like oh do the Sandman canteen
combo, it'll be fun. Don't listen to them. Yeah, like friends. I'm just gonna turn
the panel back on just to add you. I don't care. Yeah. I don't know why
like I just can't ever be invited anywhere. My steam profile is private but
yours is too, isn't it? No. Oh, maybe that's why. Yeah, friends only. My basic
details are public. That's fine. Profile friends. Do you remember one and a half
hours ago when I asked if you wanted to like test anything or anything else we
could do before? Well I didn't know that this was gonna be an issue. First time I
opened this game in like 10 years. What if I do this? All right, let me try that.
If that helps. That could fix it. If this doesn't work then just join a game and
I'm gonna change a few options in my. It actually says you're playing TF2 now
which is a step up. Oh it does. I don't think it was before. Oh, I fixed it. Do you like that we
both have default medic icons? Oh we do. We do both have default
medic icons. That's kind of funny. Great minds think alike. Yeah they do. Okay, you
joined a community server is what it's saying. Okay, well it's the thing for the
decal thing. Oh, okay. I thought okay. All right, we good? Yes. So you should be
able to invite me now. I sent you to the invite to the party and it instantly
disappears and it does not show you as inviteable. It like instantly just
closes. Why? Why the fuck is this happening? All right. You invite me.
You just go. Let me figure this out. I don't know. You invite me. I know but I
have to like re-enable my friends panel. Okay, well can we talk about like
sausages or something? Well, if you want. What do you want to talk about? Um, I
don't know. Like when do you think civilization started? I think that is a
lot of things during the pyramid times and maybe even before the pyramids. Where
there is, we already talked about this. You didn't just immediately say sauce.
Has your opinion changed? Um, hold on. I can't do two things at once. Give me a
little bit of slack. Hey, when you first opened TF2 after like eight years, you
probably spent like a long time figuring this out. And that's why I offered to
help. Yeah, but then you all but you offered to help but then you set up
starting early and you ran away and turned your stream on. And I was like, I
thought he was gonna help me. You did do that. You did say that. Not quite that.
Yeah, you did do that. You did say that. Yep. Okay. Let me just re-enable this. So
what is of all the new maps? There's like 30 new maps, right? The best map that
everyone talks about is the meme map with the seal on it. Okay. And then
there's like upward and. Are you just playing like the old map still? Um, I
have it queue me into the new maps. A mix of both. Okay. I like Phoenix. Phoenix's
first point is pretty cool. Did they add anything else? I saw like the cases. Like
I opened it for a second to see. They added an official versus Saxton Hale mode
and it's actually not that bad. As someone who never really liked Saxton
Hale. He has like three abilities he can use and it's a whole like set up for it.
Okay. Give me. I'm gonna mute for a second. Did you hear what I just said? I did.
It's Saxton Hale stuff. Yep. Let's go. Okay. No, I'm just checking. I'm listening
but I'm like I have to go in like the command list shit. Let me see. Yeah. You
just you answered in a very dismissive manner. What's going on with this? Oh, that's
right. That's wrong thing. Hey. Okay. I should be able to do it now. Cool. I got
to play for 10 seconds. I got to. No, no, no, no, no, no. Like just just hang out.
Make sure it works first. Oh, sure. I shouldn't have to leave to get it. It's
been 10 years. Don't worry. We'll do a full intro. We'll do like a whole door.
Everyone can relax. I'm gonna do a full intro. We're gonna be. It's gonna be a
huge deal. It's gonna be a bunch of fucking cool stuff happening. Just wait.
Just hold on. It's been 10 years. What's up, guys? I didn't even take the splash
screen down. That's just how much I haven't really done. I mean, it's another
late night live commentary with German 985. Tonight, I'm going to be playing
as. Oh, wait. No, I'm going to be waiting. All right. Joe, Joe, I can join
your party. I do that. Can you can you do that? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You did it.
I'm in. Okay. I'm gonna I'm gonna exit this game. Okay. I am going to kill us
or you want to see the new maps? Yes. How does this work? Do you want me to queue
for Saxton Hale as well? I we get it. I would like for you to queue us or it is
the new anything. Well, I want to just play Team Fortress for now. You know what
I mean? Okay. I just want to see if you see that's what happens. It's like cool.
There's 14 new maps. And then you join TF2 and you're like, I'm gonna play the
new maps. And then you're like, where's the health kit? Where's the health kit?
Where are they spawning? And you just run around into walls. And it's like this
isn't Team Fortress. I'm confused. Especially if you're like first games.
This is fucking cool. Alright, so first of all, let's go over what's going on
today. Today. It's only been like we've been sitting for like 12 minutes. 11
minutes. Sorry. Yeah. This is Team Fortress 2. There are honestly I really
we have to do this because it's probably like, no, shut up. Listen to me. No,
you're right. I'm laughing because I'm like, wait, do you know how many people
probably don't play this? This game's older than the people watching. There's
probably a lot of people that have no idea what's even going on. We have to
give a brief explanation of what Team Fortress is. While you explain it, can
you put like subway surfers on the side? No, I'm gonna show the game. If you're
good, you'll get a face cam. By the way, you have to be you guys gonna be good.
Are you ready? Am I joining this? Are we good? We're good. We're joining this. Are
you so ready? We're gonna look at all my points, dude. I would say it is
versus Saxton Hale. I don't know this map. Oh, it's versus Saxton Hale. Well,
this will be a good reminder. I don't know. I don't I don't want to play this.
I want to play team. Is this Team Fortress? Okay, we're leaving. No, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. I left. I left. You already started complaining and the map
didn't even load yet. Okay. Trust me. All right. So do it again. I'm gonna put
you on a real map. We're gonna do a real map that you're aware of. I just you
like I have I okay, I loaded the game for like maybe 20 minutes and it was
just to buy keys. Okay, that's that's what I did. So I need how many did you
buy two or 300? Why? What? I made that up. I bought like 15. I don't like being
lied to as a joke. I don't respect that. Whatever happened to honesty. Everyone's
always like 15. I got 15. Okay, I don't know. I just like that. I have somebody
crates in my inventory. They don't even know what they are for. They might be
like rare. Do you know this map? I mean, I know I have the fucking pyro. Why is
this on? Oh, you're a spy. I can't heal you. You're good luck. All right. So this
is way. This is different. Oh, this is this HUD looks cool. I actually like this
HUD. I should customize it a little bit more. Okay, so how do I? Okay, I have a
gas can on. Wait, what's my menu? I don't want that. I want to I don't know what's
good nowadays like the flare gun still. Well, you're not in spawn, so it doesn't
matter. Sorry, whatever. I'll go back to change your view model. Is my view model
too big? People have been telling me that for like a week. Yeah, they don't know
the real TF2. What people want them the small view models. They make me want to
throw up. They make me upset as a boomer. I'm upset. Maybe the small ones. You
mean view model underscore fov. Oh, I hate that too. When you can see their
arms. I'm a purist. Okay, it's going pretty good so far, I would say. Oh, I'll
keep it for now. Maybe I'll see how I like it. All right. I don't do I want to
play pirate. What do I want to do? What do you want to do? I don't know. What was
your favorite Team Fortress two class in the original Team Fortress two that
we're playing right now? It was this by this by for sure. Really? I'll do quick
fix uber saucer. This looks good. Oh, there's a moment. Hey, by the way, stir
just want to make sure I let you know. Where are you? Um, I'm dead. All right.
Well, I got a I got a quick fix for you when you get up. Are we doing that? I
mean, I'm I'm just healing because we need it. You just said your favorite
class was the spy. Why would I play as a spy? I'm a team player. A spy is a team
player, but we needed another medical. Okay, I'll come find you. My god. I'm
gonna activate over. I love the quick fixes uber. Is that is it bad?
I mean, it's it's it's why are you so scared of like what's considered good
and bad? Why can't you like, enjoy yourself? I am enjoying myself. And by
the way, I gotta let you know something, Star. It's over. Oh, oh, no, it's over.
Did you get the laugh track stuff?
Uh, no. Oh, okay. Well, never mind. I forgot I was supposed to get a laugh
track. I thought you were gonna have like a whole soundboard of like booze
and cheers and laugh track. I forgot. That was the bit I knew. Oh, he helped
me behind you. Not that soldier can pick up the health kit. I'm working on it. Do
this. Do that. Do what I say. I don't have the crits, by the way. If I get
backstabs, your fault. I know. Well, also, you're the medic. It's easier for
you to look around. But okay, now it's not because my beam will get detached.
What? Fuck? What? Oh, that's right. I move with you because I have the
fix. Oh, that's cool.
German versus star German versus star.
Everybody wants to see that happen. This is the reunion episode, guys.
Spee, spee, spee.
This stream is going to have like a four on fucking IMDb. Oh, god damn it. I'm
dead. This stream is gonna have like a four on IMDb because it's a reunion
episode. And we're just gonna say the jokes we've always said for like 14
years. And it's just gonna be flashbacks. And my hair is all gray and shit. Like
it's and by the way, it's been like eight years since we've even been on camera.
So I just want to make sure everyone's aware of that. And I lost.
Oh, let me get crits, actually.
Germa, the crits, the crits.
Wait, you want me to scream for the crits?
Yeah, let's go. Come on.
Hey, come on. We're back.
And then after I say that, it cuts like this part of the video, it cuts to like
total playtime in the next six months to like four hours and 10 minutes, which is
this stream.
Yeah, because you're not a real player.
You're Frank.
You know, it's in lore now that Matic is the soldier's sister.
You just die.
I did. I got I got hit right in the face.
Oh, dude, we're so back.
I do want to make the HUD a little different.
You can customize the whole thing, right?
This does look better than the default HUD in a way.
I always use the default HUD just because of, I don't know, I always felt like a
custom HUD crashed the game all the time.
But I guess it's been a long time.
What game were you playing?
I don't know, but you're doing pretty good.
You know what to do, by the way.
Oh, you're healing me.
Oh, OK. So Team Fortress 2 is a team based shooter.
There's a red team and a blue team.
You're probably looking at this and going like, what the heck's going on here?
So the cart, that blue cart is the objective for the blue team.
It is our job to stop them from pushing that object.
Hashtag ad.
All right. You know, hey, you know what you have to do.
Well, let's does this still work?
I haven't had like a medic where I like build Uber for you by damaging myself.
OK, let's go.
Oh, OK. You let me know when you're.
Oh, scout, scout, scout, scout, still alive, scout, still alive.
Oh, that's how you tell we're back.
That's how you can tell we're back.
That's how you know we're back.
But behind spy. Oh, no, I'm sorry. I'm a liar.
I lied. Liar, liar.
I don't want to pocket you. Why not?
Because that's how a team loses.
You don't have to.
Also, that's the opposite of true.
Is it? I always want to make sure the other medic is overhealed.
And what's over here?
I mean, that's true.
That spy has like 600 health.
Doesn't make any sense.
Kunai. Oh, he could have had Kunai health.
People saying, well, shitty aim, shitty aim.
Hold on. But a lot of people don't even know how this game works.
All right. Almost everything in this game is a projectile that he's playing
is mercy from Overwatch.
This game kind of just ripped it off.
You don't like really have to aim.
You just like kind of like put your beam on someone.
And then you say heroes never die.
No, you don't say that because this is Team Fortress.
But see that they have this an arc and it's all a projectile in the server.
And look at how far how long it takes to go to travel.
I see. I mean, everything's a projectile.
Skill shots.
Yeah, this game is skill shots only.
Oh, hi. Nice.
Yeah, this this feels this feels like the game that we played
for a very long time. Remember, fake hair everywhere.
That's a classic line.
What are the classic lines that we not said is this by
he's bored already?
Wow. This was just really like, oh, this is a game I played for years.
Oh, you guys, you guys have heard of this game viewfinder?
Yeah, we might have to take a rain rain check on that game.
Well, I feel like I'm going to play this a lot.
This is fun. Oh, he said it.
All right. We got. OK.
If you don't get at least seven kills with this, you need to do 10 push ups.
Well, I didn't get any with it.
But you got to do 10 push ups, bro.
I feel like that's on you to do the push ups.
What? No, I didn't need the crits.
Oh, my God. You killed like four people.
I got a random one. I got two of it there.
How about like you?
How about I do push ups, but you like lay under me?
Does that even work?
What are you talking?
I've you know, you know, wait, wait.
What? OK, I work out.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
No, I don't want to die. I don't.
I'm going to kill this heavy.
The way, you know, if you go down a map, maximum depth on a push up.
As if you kiss.
OK, whatever you're saying, I just got I have a full Uber right now.
Where are you? I'm dead.
Well, get back alive.
I'm getting back alive.
I'm coming through a teleport.
I have to create a sniper.
Is this a bad? This is bad.
Don't do it. I'm behind you. I'm behind you. I'm behind you.
It's me. Let me know.
Yeah. You know, the signal.
Hmm. Good.
It's one. It's two.
Nice. Almost. Hey, we did it.
There is no one else to kill.
Hmm. I thought that was a crits noise.
I thought that was a burp.
I was convinced you burped.
Maybe you should play spy. You like spy.
I it's going to be so embarrassing.
There's no that's like three spot.
I'll play engineer. Do a stair stab.
I'm going to play engineer for one specific reason.
And I don't know if you're going to be very upset with me
or if you're going to be very happy.
What's the reason? You'll see.
Yeah, I have to wait one full minute, though.
Why? You just you have to wait a minute.
How's the audio? Is the volume good?
Doesn't need to be a little bit louder.
A little quiet. Oh, let me.
Oh, shit. I didn't want to do that.
Wait. Oops. OK.
Options, audio. That's that's neat.
I remember you're like old hat loadouts.
You're playing the self-portrait engineer.
Yeah. Oh, shit. You can't see.
All right. So this is why I wanted you to.
You're either going to be very mad or very happy.
We'll find out really shortly here.
Oh, no. Wrong one.
Oh, my God. No, no, no, no. Wrong one.
You have to for this. No, no, no. Wrong one. Wrong, wrong, wrong.
This one's important.
All right, Hank Hill.
Best of luck to you.
This is I love this so much.
You can get backstabbed on the go cart.
Why not? You have what you have a back.
Oh, it should hit the fucking metal.
You know what? I'm changing class.
I got a better idea.
I don't want to play engineer.
I want to play fucking heavy.
OK, I'm with you.
All right.
But we're going to be engineer friends.
OK. Oh, yeah.
Where were you?
I'm I was building a century.
Are you so that you're I saw you.
I get the oh, you saw it already.
I get that you bought every single drivable.
I can shoot the gun.
Yeah. What?
It only has five bullets.
Wasted them. Pay to win, dude.
Does this actually hurt people?
I don't know, actually.
Hey, it has to, right?
It doesn't have to buy by.
Watch your back. He's right here.
Yeah. Fuck you, buddy.
That didn't do anything.
How do I do that?
It was inevitable.
All right. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
You got to go push that cart.
I would. We could have run for a second.
Hold on. There's a lot of things going on.
You got to push that gear up.
I heard steps.
I'm doing it.
I'm really doing it.
They have a bad ahead of soldier with a conqueror, whatever it is.
A soldier with a brass beast.
Excuse me.
The conch, the conch, whatever it is.
The soldier with the what?
The con the shell, the like
soldier with the what are you talking about?
Well, let me let me actually take this off.
I do have some cool items.
I love the Thomas love.
It was awesome.
Nana. 50 percent.
Yeah. For those of you that don't know,
Team Fortress 2 has like five thousand items that are different
and can't change the gameplay there.
They are all different now.
Everyone that you remember that was fun is different now.
Really? Yes.
So much stuff changed.
Oh, my God.
Wait, is this 40 percent?
I might have to take a whole stream
just sitting here looking at every item that might have to happen later.
Tell me which one you put on and I'll tell you if it was.
OK. Gloves of running urgently.
I think those are still the same.
Are they the same?
I haven't actually played like no heavy.
Don't ask me about any heavy items. Never mind.
Is this live? Yeah, it's live.
It's late night live.
This is late night live commentary.
My hit series. What are you doing?
What are you doing?
Yeah, that Tommy's love is much quicker.
All right. Let's actually I'm going I'm going for it now.
I'm going for it. No more fucking around.
No more. Oh, man.
I picked the only time that our team had was not pushing.
And I leave.
What do we actually need?
Why should we need?
Maybe demo. Yeah.
What do we what's my I'm sorry.
I'm just all over the place.
That's overwhelming. I forget everything.
Loose cannon was cool. Is that different?
Uh, no. I'll keep.
All right. I'm going to do loose cannon.
What about the shield of the shields?
Any better or different or anything?
Tied Turner makes you go anywhere.
This one's just defense.
I'm going to just do defense.
And the donk whatever it is, bonk whatever it is.
Oh, what the fuck?
All my stuff's getting sapped, bro.
Oh, shit.
Teleporter down.
It all went to shit.
That's all right.
I'm playing one of my favorite items in the game.
Everything is about to change for our in our favor.
Just get the game behind us.
I'm aware. I'm going to kill this guy.
Oh, I give up.
Don't give up.
I give up on engineer.
I'm going to go back to spawn and get in the little car.
Oh, my God. Never back down.
Yeah, never back down.
So the loose cannon is you have to hit them twice,
once with the directed and then once with the explosion, right?
That's how I remember.
Mm hmm. If you charge it up all the way, you blow yourself up.
Don't do that. People are going to do omega lols.
They I mean, I did definitely omega loling the whole time since I opened the game.
That's why. Well, I'm glad they're having a good time.
Oh, oh, omega lol.
I do have a hit sound, I guess you have a hit sound.
Yeah. You didn't even ask me for like a hit sound.
No, I do.
I installed a custom HUD for the first time forever.
We would have sat there for like three hours while you tried to explain.
Holder in one spot. Oh, I'm the soldier going around.
It's not too late, Jerma.
I can give you a hit sound. You're going to love it.
See if I can get this done.
Oh, I can't take this thing.
Oh, no. Wait, why can I shoot this?
Thought I couldn't.
The crits. Let's go.
That was a good crits, too.
That was like almost everybody.
They're proud of you.
Oh, we're so back.
We're so back. Oh, I'm having I'm having fun.
Oh, I'm. Are you not having fun?
I am having fun.
I just find it funny that
I'm having fun is code word for what's next.
You know, it's funny to say.
I mean, I've been playing this for like a week.
Hold on. Oh, shit.
I'm good. All right.
So if you don't know what's going on there, that weapon.
Dude, there's a lot of people here.
We this is a business.
This game is like our entire you and I.
Can you explain what a spie is?
You and I are like entire lives are because this game exists.
You know, you understand.
We need to make sure people understand this.
OK, so this thing, when you get a kill with it, you get healed.
You get healed 50 percent of your health.
But what? I had a mo.
I'm sorry. That has nothing to do with you.
So but if I take this out and I don't kill someone,
this is completely different.
I don't understand how this item works anymore.
Which item? The the toy.
You can't put it away.
No, you will heal if you kill someone.
No, no, no, you're not. It's different.
No. OK, so you get 50 percent base health if you kill somebody.
There are no random crits.
And once you draw this thing, if you put it away,
you get hurt for 50 damage unless you kill somebody.
Oh, OK. That's interesting.
Yeah. Most things have changed.
I actually like that better.
Hold on. Let me see. Oh, wow.
Oh, shit. Maybe that's why I was getting hurt.
I didn't even know that was happening.
Were you just weapon swapping it? I think so.
Yeah. I'll do it.
I'll get my contract going or get five kills as a demo in a single life.
Press F2. Why?
If you if you want to hack, I just want you to see this menu.
OK, F2. Hold on.
I'll do what I'm good.
This is the Deus Ex fucking screen.
What the fuck? How is he still alive?
What does a crit do with the melee?
Don't say swears.
All right. Press F2 to open up the contract menu.
Yeah. OK. Yeah.
I mean, I did a lot of this when it was relevant, like 10 years ago.
It didn't exist 10 years ago.
How long? Yeah, this is like five years ago.
Eight years. It was a long time ago.
They changed it to that during the jungle inferno update, like two years ago.
I must have played for like an hour.
Oh, yeah, I never saw that before. Did I play?
Yeah, I did.
When was jungle inferno, guys?
It was not five years ago. It's two years ago.
There's been so many updates this game. It's hard to keep track.
He was playing off stream.
And I played this game for a little bit like two or three years ago.
I must have. No, I did.
I did. I did very briefly.
But like maybe a day or two.
But I immediately dropped it because it was just kind of fucking fucked up.
Jungle Inferno was 2017.
Yeah, that was two years ago.
That's right. Two years ago.
That was to 2017.
Yeah, it sounds like two years a long time ago.
It's like 2018 now.
Somebody said, hey, dude, is your mouse on gravel?
What do you mean?
You mean like like a mouse pad of rocks?
Maybe my sensitivity is too high.
Pyros exist. It feels like I give up.
Bye. Behind.
Well, he just fucked everybody up.
I made the call out to and they didn't hear you.
Oh, I'm in trouble.
I'm I'm getting ready to use the schwicky swag.
I'm not doing bad.
I mean, I got 53 points.
That's like doing pretty good.
All right, let's do engineer engineer with the mini century.
Yeah. Oh, yeah. Let's go.
OK, I want to do this.
Get a teleport. Yep.
Teleport. Teleport going up.
Do not get backstabbed.
What if I want to?
Well, well, well, help.
I'm on fire. I need a dispenser.
Help. Help.
What a dispenser.
Get out of the dispenser. Get out of the way.
Wait, was it you?
Oh, I think I was being OK.
I was a sniper asking for help.
Help level this dispenser up.
I only have 55 mana.
Where's the ammo on this map?
This guy thinks he's playing World of Warcraft.
Look at this. We have like a little nest over here.
Perfect. Lay down the rug.
Always help. Always help your fellow engineer.
Everyone's just going to be over there helping you.
There is no one else playing the game right now.
Oh, my God.
Oh, I got two kills with this thing.
Holy shit. That means I get crits with it.
The only thing I care about when playing as engineer is the frontier justice.
Oh, oh, oh, that's why it's fun.
It's probably going to try to tell somebody.
I killed them, killed them.
But you got one of the teleporters.
All right. Now this is where I go and fuck somebody up.
All right. I'm happy with it.
I'm happy with it. Is this all the way it is all the way?
All right. We're all good.
No one's going to be fucking around over here.
Are you sure about that?
I don't know. Oh, bye.
He's at the spawn.
My own shit got in the way.
God damn it.
Yeah, it's going to be hard keeping that up.
He's dedicated to his craft.
All right. All right. That's fine.
Let's go, bud.
Got him.
Was that you?
What? The velociraptor in the call.
Oh, spy spy's coming for you next.
Spy's coming for next.
Back at spawn.
Now, the dispensers, did they all get destroyed?
My dispensers there.
I'm trying to get the teleporter back up.
Somebody is at the dispenser right now.
Let me tell a frag him.
We're trying. Oh, fuck.
This is bad.
We're going to get this thing a little free.
Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quickly, quickly, quickly.
But I'm just trying to have a decoy.
Yeah, good, good.
Exactly what I wanted.
They killed the mini sentry like three times.
They didn't even go for the big one.
Those fools.
Change your hit sound.
My hit sound is like a squishy sound.
Change it. Change your hit sound.
Change your view model.
Change your sentry to me.
Change your loadout. Equip the pen.
Jerma, equip the pen.
Oh, did you say pan?
Equip the pen.
You talk about the pan like the pen.
Why do you keep saying pen?
Equip the pen.
I like to be annoying with the pistol.
Oh, shit. Sorry, he's going to die.
What is the why do you keep saying that?
What is that? What's the pen?
Um, that's it.
There's really not much more to it.
Come on, we can do it.
Over time.
All right, get in there. Get in there.
Get in there.
This last point is really hard because there's always a million sentries
at a perfect angle.
Wait, no.
We're just losers. Losers.
That's why he has 83 points and he's playing with a track pad.
He's lying.
You sure?
Yeah, I'm sure. Where do you want to go?
This is where you leave.
Yeah, this is where you 100 percent leave the game.
OK, because nobody is going to stay.
And I told you this and we discussed this.
OK, do you want the new maps now?
I'll put some of the. Sure.
The good or new maps on.
Let me look at Medic.
They add, OK, the Vaccinator.
This one was weird at the very get go.
I wonder if they changed it.
I don't think so.
And it is still weird.
A crazy Uber charge rate.
You press your reload key to cycle through resist types
while healing provides you and your target with a constant 10 percent
resistance to the selected damage type.
The Uber charge provides a two and a half second resistance bubble
that blocks 75 percent base damage and 100 percent crit damage.
It's like we're playing D4.
It's a Diablo four item.
And what does this say? I just picked up a sign.
And what does it do?
OK, minus 66 percent overheal, whatever.
You have to switch it between things.
So it requires more buttons.
So like when when a pyro is coming, you have to switch it to fire resistance.
I wonder, was that any better than the quick fix?
Um, situationally, maybe to like anti crits.
If you know somebody has a crits creed.
But why wouldn't you just use the Uber?
I guess it's faster.
Crit would probably kill someone with a vaccinator.
No, it's 100 percent.
When you Uber, you block 100 percent crit damage of the selected type.
That might be new, then it may be new.
Vaccinator is OP if you get good with it.
It is very strong.
Like if a pyro is walking in and you switch to fire damage,
it they'll they just start doing like one every hit.
You just outheal any damage they can do.
Well, I missed the entire Uber build period, so that's bad.
My phone needs it.
Oh, this is nice. This map school.
Oh, I like this a lot.
It's like water spike.
God damn it, I taste a spike.
It's great to hear you having the takes that I also had a week ago
and how how quickly they've changed.
Really? So you don't like this map is cursed.
This map is not one that you want to play on, even though you had the same.
I do want to play on it.
I want you to experience it.
Everything bad that could possibly happen to you is going to happen
because like this map is haunted.
What? There's ghosts on this map.
Wait, there are you mean that?
Or is it like you just like around like in the program ghost?
Not like, oh, I'm going to see a cute little girl.
No, like in the program, someone died on this map while making it.
And there's ghosts on this map and it's haunted.
Wait, what?
You'll see by the end of this map.
You're going to like, no, I get what he meant.
I don't I don't. I have no idea what that means.
But are you going to like a haunted house and like all the spooky stuff
starts happening and things start going badly for you by demo?
That's Venice. Venice is haunted.
Oh, OK. That's by two. Who knows what somebody in the chat
just write their type in all caps.
Get your fucking beam on that heavy.
Oh, that was bad.
That was a bad crack, but it's OK.
You know, don't say swears.
We don't have very many hourglass, do we?
There's one demo.
I've seen a lot of spies, a lot of snipers.
What do you want us to?
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, I don't.
This is three pyros, two scouts.
Are things not going well right now?
Is that what you're suggesting?
Not necessarily.
Yeah, I use cow mangler.
There it is. The conk.
The what? The conqueror.
I don't even know how to fucking be a good teammate.
I'll show you.
Especially to the engineers with the holding shit.
I don't know where we're going into the haunted mansion.
Am I going away from the.
Wait, there's usually arrows on the team fortress.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Wrong way. Wrong way. What's he doing?
What's he doing? Get that fucking beam on that heavy.
It's a big map.
Who thought spy was a good idea?
This map haunted.
No, this map is haunted.
Are you just not very good?
Do you think ghosts are real?
That's a whole can of worms.
Answer them.
Um, I mean, not necessarily.
I think there's a possibility there could be some phantoms.
I feel like that was a yes or no question,
and you cannot answer it with not necessarily.
Oh, my God. Oh, how did I miss everybody?
Did it hit the wall?
There it is. What?
Dude, I got the conqueror.
I got the conqueror. I got the conqueror.
I got the conqueror. You got the what?
I have to stop doing that.
It's not even funny.
All right, let's go. Where are you?
I thought I knew that was a spy, too.
You just stop muting and centering my words.
You're about to put your lips on it.
He's fucking with me and messing up my video game.
Was I messing with you? They're ghost real.
They might. I don't know.
How am I supposed to know?
Because like once you reach a certain level of status in society,
don't you like get invited to these events where like the president's there
and he's like, oh, he's like, tells you all this shit about ghosts.
Or you're in a party and there's like all actors
and they all like have the same.
What do they call it? What do they call it?
Sir, it's been nine days since I've left my home.
What are you talking about?
Again, I think I'm going to get invited to like fucking special events.
Are you is that what you're implying?
Well, you went to like the streamer awards.
There wasn't like an Illuminati there.
Yeah, we talk about aliens and ghosts and shit.
Oh, yeah, I'm expecting to get 10K more subs this week.
Yeah, because my yeah, I found a good ghost.
I got a poltergeist. We were doing an exercise.
You didn't hear any conversation like that.
Hold on. This is important.
I got I got to get a cow mangler here.
I have an opportunity to help the fucking team.
OK, what was your question?
Do all the do all the streamers talk about like ghosts
and conspiracies and stuff?
Is that what you said?
I want to know that you're not necessarily.
And you said it's a whole can of worms.
And now your ghost answer is I don't know.
Well, because we evolved from I was interested to what you had to say to
you lost me because that's a very loaded question.
That that's like an hour and a half long conversation.
Do you not want to have it?
You're going to not play this game that long.
I'm currently enjoying Team Fortress.
And ever since we started talking about this,
but my skill level has dropped by like at least 30 percent.
Do you want to know why your skill level drop?
No, no, no, no, no.
I was doing fine until we started talking about fucking aliens and ghosts.
Until we came to Venice.
TLDR. What?
It missed him. You got to be shitting me.
Oh, my God. How does it matter that miss?
That thing has a gigantic explosion radius.
OK, I got to step it up here. I'm not doing very well.
And to play the worst possible thing I could play
and play spy with the Spicycle and the
is the load out here.
I forget how you play spy the default revolver because the ambassador was
nerfed and the enforcer was nerfed.
And like every spy equipment has been nerfed.
The dead bringers been nerfed.
Oh, my. I had the Spicycle. That was a mistake.
Yeah, it should not.
That should not have happened.
Why do you think it happened?
I don't know, but there's a fucking scout over here.
I need help. Blue Team, help me.
He's getting me help.
Oh, are you fucking kidding me?
What happened? Oh, he's using the crossbow.
I thought he was I thought he was stream sniping.
He's using the
I was calling for medic as a spy and this guy
he kills me with the crossbow.
OK, kind of spooky.
That was fucking funny.
Medic, medic, medic.
I'm not I'm a real person.
Oh, what's that thing?
That was cool.
Did you did you know they made the Liberty launcher
the best weapon in the whole game?
What do you mean?
That's just flat out.
They they buffed the Liberty launcher.
It's the best weapon in the whole game now.
What was different before?
Is it the blast damage?
It's had like three different changes.
They removed a lot of the downsides.
I mean, 25% penalty is actually pretty bad considering.
And it's really not because you get an extra rocket and extra projectile speed
that makes up for the consistency on the why don't I just use the stupid thing
damage the what thing the the sneeze gun?
I don't know. Do it.
OK, you can only hold three.
No matter what you do, it's not going to go well.
And that's not I'm not being mean.
That went pretty well.
It's just Venice.
I'm out of ammo already.
Oh, you hold them.
That is actually scared the shit out of me.
I thought something happened.
I need ammo with ammo on this map like everywhere.
I better not fucking die.
I swear to God.
Oh, there we go.
I, I almost got the conch and then we can really go for it.
But what that item that's on soldier, the Liberty Lauchers.
Let's go.
Well, let's get them.
Oh, it's all right.
I think you would have killed him if you had the Liberty launcher.
I don't think so.
Oh, you had an extra rocket?
This just makes sense.
And you would miss less because it goes faster.
I'm using this fucking weird thing.
Those of you that don't know, Team Fortress Classic is also one of my favorite games of all time.
And I use this weapon all the time.
Classic is you have to hold the button down and then release it to shoot.
A lot of people say trash item.
Fucking terrible.
Just wait till you see somebody that knows what they're doing with it,
and then you can fucking go talk about it.
It's the trash item.
I was scrolling through my old TF2 videos the other day,
and even my description of the video I made about the classic was like,
why would you do this?
Just get the ambassador and be invisible with it.
We'll see.
We will see.
It doesn't make people pop when you kill them.
That's neat.
It is pretty neat.
Oh, fuck.
He's terrible.
A scout versus a sniper is an automatic loss for the sniper.
Don't you kidding me?
You're digging yourself in deeper.
Are you kidding me?
Guys, he's not bad.
Venice is haunted.
Where are they? Where do they even come from?
Where's the enemies?
Where's their like spawn in the shadow realm?
Don't think about it.
My sensitivity is too high.
I got to drop it by like at least 10 percent.
Yeah, way, way, way too high, way too high.
Like outrageously high.
What is it at right now?
No, I don't want it at zero.
One point five.
That's better. OK.
Oh, you got to be ready for the pub push.
You got to be ready for the pub push, Jerma.
Five seconds, 10 seconds, 12 seconds, 11 seconds, two seconds.
You got to be ready, Jerma.
I haven't played this game in 10 years, dude.
You weren't ready for the pub push.
Come on.
I just I was I'm just trying to figure out how to play the goddamn game again.
Oh, and are we leaving again?
Unless you want to play Venice again.
I didn't find that map particularly terrible.
It's just kind of big and too many places to go.
Well, next time you're like, well, hey, Venice isn't haunted.
Remember, you've never won a game on it yet.
We played it in one time.
What a coincidence.
Played it one time, lost one time.
I'm going to play with the bazookas beggar backwards.
The bazookas beggar.
I it's been 10 years.
Actually, it's been seven.
Are you still going to play viewfinder?
I don't know. Maybe I'm bad.
This is great. It's been a while since I've jumped in and played and cared.
Open some crates.
I could open a few crates, maybe.
Maybe we'll save the crate stuff for another day.
Huh? Because I want to play.
But you already got the keys.
Jerma, I don't want the quates opening.
They don't disappear.
Well, more team fortress.
Maybe. Yeah, there's another new map.
It's shark Bay. Don't go in the water.
There's sharks in the water.
Sharks in the water.
Always vote. Yes, always vote.
Yes, always. OK.
Don't even look. Don't even look.
OK. Oh, this is a off map.
Where is everybody?
Yes, again, I guess.
I mean, I don't know.
Wait, what?
Now I'm feeling like there's a little bit of a mix up.
Is it mix up?
There may be. I still put it.
Yes, anyway. He's gone. OK.
Where is the other team?
I don't know. Should we try again?
Yeah, you vote. Yes.
No, I mean, like, should we requeue?
I don't see anybody on Red Team.
There's like three people over there.
They're coming.
OK, I'm going to stay at this point.
Stop voting. Yes, I think.
I think we're being trolled.
OK. But maybe one more. OK.
Oh, where's the other team?
They're capping the point, Mr.
I got it. Have you ever seen a ghost?
Now you have. Nice one.
You've got to be fucking kidding me, dude.
I hit the guy twice and I get randomly dead in one hit.
You've still got some Venice on you.
Hasn't worn off yet.
It's very laggy, but I'm all right.
Are they on it? They're dead.
Now they're ghosts.
Come on. How much does it take?
I hit him like five times.
Oh, this isn't your grandfather's FPS game.
Oh, that's right. We get a little raunchy in here.
I got about the islander saying it is literally.
It actually is. Whoa.
Tracking my day.
I mean, you have to have skill in an FPS game.
Kill this motherfucker before he can build a set for it.
There's so many people in there.
All right. I got to I got to like stick with something
and stop switching every five seconds.
Equip the pen. Now we're going back to soldier.
I'm not allowed to get off of soldier for the next 15 straight minutes
no matter what. Oh, it's not happening.
You've got Liberty Launcher is incredible.
Whoever buffed this weapon out of their mind.
Oh, that fuck.
What am I voting? What am I voting?
That's a no for me. I know you.
OK. We're we can win it.
You know what I miss?
What's that?
The ghastly gibbous.
It's a great hat.
Yeah, you're not seeing too many of them these days.
See some ironic gibbouses.
This weapon is awful.
I'm going to play a different weapon.
I forgot it was inaccurate.
I forgot it like shoots it like there's a deviation of like
20 or 30 degrees every time you shoot.
There's what? Three minutes before I left me.
What is wrong with me?
Do I stink? Maybe.
Oh, no, because they're all healing.
What the fuck? Never mind.
I get it now. He'll stir.
He's playing. You had three.
Did I actually have three medics?
Yeah. And seriously, I was running around with like 20 HP like, hey,
don't say no to that. That's me.
I think we leave and we leave.
I think I think this is a three medic type of type of situation.
All right. I'm up.
I think this is a vote kick random people until we get three medics on Jerma.
No, I don't think so.
All right. Don't believe in ghosts.
Don't believe in like any conspiracy theories.
Apparently you believe in Bigfoot, the Loch Ness monster.
Yeah. The Jersey.
No. Wait, what do you mean?
It's the same game. It's the same.
Oh, shit. It's like this game just crashed.
OK, I think we joined and left too quickly.
It says you're currently offline.
OK, well, we may have I may have broken some stuff.
I think you broke it.
It's not letting me start searching, but it does say a member of your party is offline.
OK, well, maybe restart TF2.
All right. It's not Tuesday maintenance.
It's literally Sunday.
OK, I'm going to restart TF2 and we'll go from there.
Are you relaunching?
I'm relaunching.
Give it a second. It has to do that weird thing again.
You broke it.
The government broke it when I brought up Bigfoot.
I mean, Bigfoot makes sense to me because this I mean,
there's a very real possibility that there's just like a huge gorilla just somewhere
and it's just way bigger than everybody else.
They're called gorillas.
Yeah, but but like a Bigfoot could potentially just be a huge gorilla
that people just oh, my God, it's Bigfoot.
No, dude, that's just a giant gorilla.
OK, are we still in a party?
Yeah. OK, should we try it again?
Yeah, I'm doing it. OK, go for it.
There we go. OK.
In the U.S. in the wild, do you think a giant gorilla is walking around?
I mean, I don't know. Possible.
It's just a furry.
I would buy that.
Yeah, I would just use like for the OK.
You want a weird story?
I don't think I've ever talked about this with you that you saw Bigfoot one time.
Well, yeah, but also, OK.
When I was a little kid,
we're talking like a real little like it may have been preschool age. OK.
I got a Spider-Man costume on Halloween and I loved it.
So we got to leave. OK.
OK, the hardest part, you got to find matches.
OK, so when I was a little kid in preschool, I had a Spider-Man costume
for Halloween and I loved it.
And I just thought it was cool to like be Spider-Man.
So I'd just wear it on days that weren't Halloween.
And I'd like go out back and like play around in my Spider-Man outfit.
And I would never wear clothes under it
because I wanted to authentically be Spider-Man.
What my brother hated it.
My brother hated it because he's I have an older brother.
And me and my mom would go pick up my brother from school
and I would wear the Spider-Man outfit to greet him
when he's like coming out of school and like all his friends.
He like little Spider-Man running up to us like, that's so not cool.
And I think my mom would bring me along just because like she knew he hated it.
So you so you were like a you would you would like a practical joke.
Yeah. So my dad says, where is this going?
Bigfoot is totally just someone like testing out their first 100 percent.
I can relate to that.
All right. Are we are we going for it here?
Because like this is this is it.
This is the one I've got.
I've got my shit going here.
And now I'm going full on.
No, I'm going engineer.
This is my map on engineer.
Now I'll play good here. Check this out.
Top 15 minutes on soldier.
It doesn't count.
Yeah, it is a new map.
Hey, who cares about what wrench I'm using?
I just got to equip one.
Come on. How did you do that?
My mom says I can confirm.
So I guess that is why she brought me.
I don't know if she's saying I can confirm that's why she brought me
or I can confirm Bigfoot is just a guy testing a fursuit.
She may know more.
It's been a while.
Quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack, quack.
I got to go. I got to go. I got to go.
I got to go now. I got to go. I got to go. I got to go now.
I got to go. I got to go. I got to go. I'll be back.
Where's our sentry?
Fuck. Hold on. I just been a long time.
The gates opening.
It's been a long time. Hold on.
I didn't have the right equipment.
Just wait. It's been like it's been 10 years.
Where are you putting it? I'm going up here.
I hope it gets the build.
I'm keeping an eye on you.
Keep an eye on me, please. It's been 10 years.
All right. And that Pyro would not been able to be there.
Spy spy. Good. I just. Good. Good. I'm good. Good.
I wanted to die, so I come on, get the sentry.
Everything's fine. Protect my shit for a minute.
It's what shit?
There's a spy. There's a spy. There's a spy back there.
And he's eyeing my fucking cool building.
Your medic defended it.
Let's go.
All right. Now I'm good.
That's a spy right there. No doubt.
We're good. I got you.
It's me.
All right. Let's go check it out.
It's a cool weapon skin.
I don't know why I do that.
I'm just such a weirdo. I can't help it.
He's a freak.
Get that Pyro. Don't let him out of here.
I don't know why the fuck I do that.
Spies around here. Watch out.
Keep your eyes peeled.
Oh, nice pick up. Nice pick up.
See, you don't think I know what the fuck I'm doing.
Got the Wrangler?
No.
I bet you really know.
I mean, I don't like the Wrangler.
I don't like how it turns your sentry off for like three seconds.
You know, they they completely changed the short circuit as well.
Are they really?
Yeah. It's really weird now.
It shoots like a spear.
That's kind of cool.
I'll short circuit.
I'm doing fine. I'm good.
OK, so do you understand that you're doing fine because people are helping you?
Are you denying my help?
Engineer is the class that is incredible.
Soldiers above you.
Engineer is insanely important, but it requires teamwork for it.
He had the crits. He had crits.
All my stuff is still there besides Sentry. It's fine.
I just didn't whack my sentry.
Whack my helicopter once.
OK, oh, and there goes everything else.
I got your dispenser saved if that matters.
Um, it might.
It actually might be a huge deal.
My accolades.
I'm all right. I'm moving. I'm moving my shit.
Are we good? Are they on it or should I?
No, you're good.
I think we're still all right.
We're holding.
Yeah, we are. They're moving it.
They're moving it. Oh, shit.
But long, I freaked out and I grabbed my dispenser and died.
Hey, I'm doing fine, though.
You're doing great.
Turn off motion blur.
Is it on? Probably.
Does default on.
Well, that fucking was loud.
Uh, no.
Hey, nice. Easy.
The sentry being up at the time that it did in the zoning that it provided,
I believe I should get at least five friend points for that.
You should wait. You should have points.
You should also get five friend points because you protected my nest
when I was out there.
Where are we on friend points right now?
Am I above you?
Uh, you have 11. I have nine.
So I have. Yeah, we're pretty close in points.
Wait, those those points are friend points. Yeah.
All right. I'm going to go back to
I thought I had a strange gunslinger a long time ago.
Maybe not. So you said that.
Let me see the short circuit.
Fire has launched a projectile consuming energy ball.
Sixty five metal. That's a lot.
Yeah. Short circuit was kind of insanely good.
Was it? Yeah.
So you have to destroy projectiles with the ball and you can't just do it forever.
I'm not sure.
Did you begin weird ever since you got bitten by that bird?
What? When did I get hit by a bird?
You didn't get bit by a bird is what you're saying.
Are you denying it?
No, I just seriously going to go live right now in front of all these people and deny it.
Does that mean I'm being like chased by a bird and pecked in the head or something?
Like, how do you get bit by a bird?
I have a bird story.
My mom's here. I have I have the mom bird story.
Follow up. You get a lot of bird.
You get a lot of stories, don't you?
You could say that there's my birthday and there was a bird flying around.
It was being really weird.
It was going crazy.
It was coming for my birthday cake or something.
And my mom smashed it with a bag full of eaten corn husks
and smashed it down on the ground.
What? She defended me from the bird.
It was going it was insane.
Like, have you seen the movie The Birds?
It was like that bird.
So wait, so you didn't have friends.
You were being attacked by a bird.
Yeah. What the fuck?
Yeah, it was a bird dynamic, but real.
All right. Now that we're out, I can do this.
No, we're not. There's a there's a soldier back here.
What the fuck is happening with this?
People just back here behind the cart.
They must have a teleporter or something weird.
Unfortunate.
Is there they have to have a teleporter, right?
I didn't see one. I was jumping around all over the place.
Hey, somebody's killed that guy.
Oh, no. OK, he's all right.
I'm bringing this all the way up.
Make sure I don't get killed by anybody.
All right. So far, so good.
All right. Get on it.
Why? How come every time you die, you don't scream
as though you died in real life?
Because it's childish.
OK, see you in the next circus stream.
You've grown adult clown.
So what? Clowns just don't should not exist anymore.
They should never be a clown.
The only way clowns should exist if you're adult is if you're into the clown.
But so so you're saying that that we should not have clowns
should not exist anymore.
They should never be another clown.
That is not what I just said.
But an adult clown.
Who is it? Who is a clown that's not an adult?
What are you talking about?
Oh, fuck. I just blew up.
But who enjoys clowns?
Adults are clowns, but who enjoys clowns?
So what? So your opinion on entertainment is if we should just delete
everything, that's not your opinion of entertainment.
Is that what you're saying?
Tell me your opinion on D4.
It's not good. It's not good at all.
It's not good at all.
Oh, yeah, because you have the crowd now.
It like isn't even a thing anymore.
Like every day set on their own live stream.
That's just not fun.
Our bullet point is that's not true.
The game fun. I even bring it up.
They skip the bullet point because no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Hold on. Rewind. Back it up.
Take 10 steps backwards.
Yeah. Who was three months ago?
At least a month ago, somebody said, hey, dude, how do you feel about D4?
And I went, you do not want to hear my D4 opinion.
Oh, no, you don't want to hear it.
And they were like, oh, shit, he hates it.
And I'm like, oh, I hate it.
So excuse me. I'm sorry.
Yeah, but now you're allowed to like actually say it.
I did. You've been given permission.
Who gave you permission?
Who in the story? But he gave me permission.
I just decided that, you know, OK, listen,
I think Diablo four is a good video game
that is that is not going to be done for like three years.
That's my real opinion.
OK, I think there is a good video game there,
but it's going to take like four years before it gets there.
Spy. It really was a spy.
Only four.
I don't know.
I'm going to play Path of Exile two anyways.
So what the who fucking cares?
Oh, he a real one.
I played D4.
It was like, it was all right.
Like the end game was kind of fucking terrible.
And I was like, whatever, I'm done.
I don't want to have the same unique drop eight times.
I'm done. That's it.
That's all I need to say. That's it.
Do you need more of an opinion?
I think that covers it.
I need your opinion on Ghost.
Hold on. Have an opinion on it.
All right. See if I can get.
Oh, I need a teleporter.
It's bad. I need someone to destroy the mini sentry
that is in the complete wide open next to the cart.
I'm an engineer.
No, the uber soldier.
Please. Hey, hey, look, bud.
I'm an engineer.
I saw practical problems.
That's you right now. Yeah.
That was a loud spy decloak sound.
I don't know where he is.
They're all coming up that way.
What the fuck did I just do?
What just happened? Oh, right.
That's what I wanted.
Oh, my fucking God.
I I pressed four and then five and then one and then two
and then three and four and then five and then two and then one and three.
I got to get my muscle memory back to playing engineer.
Still there, though.
Thanks for the teleporter, Chum.
You're welcome.
Really kind of need to move it up.
I did. I'm sorry.
I respect you as an engineer.
We are about to get this point, though.
We are. Now I'm going to go over here
and try to build up some shit over here.
I'm going to. OK.
Everything is good now.
In fact, I might might.
I don't want to move it that far because I don't want anyone to get killed.
Where is it in this role?
Pyro, I can help you.
I'm like the only pyre on the team.
Oh, you're good.
OK, but I thought it was about teamwork.
It is until it's me.
I think we're just going to win by right.
I don't know where he's going, but he went that way.
You know what? Fuck it. I'm going to make it quicker.
I'm going to this is stupid, but whatever.
It's like an extra five steps you don't take.
That will be the difference maker.
That actually might help.
Oh, come on. Pressure, pressure, pressure, pressure, pressure.
Help, help, help.
Entrance teleport. Wait, what's going on?
Teleporter. Wait, what did I what did I do?
Did you do it backwards?
No, no, I didn't.
This is teleporter exit.
But yeah, you're good.
You're doing great.
And I am.
My buttons are so fucked up.
It's like most button.
Why is it mouse for to do that?
OK, that's very weird.
It's not three. It's mouse for.
I I wish I could explain why that just happened.
Are you blew up the exit?
I know. But my key binds.
I had to have had a reason like 10 years ago to do that.
What was the reason?
You're still the same person.
What did you do that for? Why did you do this?
I just killed a spy.
Ah, oh, no, he didn't even kill my shit.
Oh, no. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right.
Just do you need a hand?
Everyone's just waiting for it to be done.
And it's not even fucking close.
But he's at the entrance.
You motherfucker. I'm coming back there.
I think we're losing.
We need the teleporter now. It's there.
It's there. It's there. It's there.
I promise. We need it now.
Well, you can't just demand things, OK?
Fuck you.
This guy just killed like three of us.
What are you now remembering?
The Huntsman's not OK.
Like being killed by it or using it.
It does a lot of damage.
It's really hard to use.
What's the last time you tried it?
When the enemy team has a lot of heavies,
I'm saying it's it's like brutal for them.
They can't really move.
And it's like 360 for like no charge time.
You just hop out at a heavy.
Yeah. And you get the sonar arrow.
Keep track. I'm making.
I'm being very aware of everybody.
This is risky. This is really risky.
But fuck it. I'm doing it.
Insanely risky.
We're moving up. We're on the cart.
We're winning right now.
If you're moving up, it's a good time.
Oh, that motherfucker back here.
That's why he's going to get me. He's going to get me.
He's going to get me. He's good.
He's good. He's really good.
Got him. Or I got one of them.
There's a few.
How did he not die?
What the fuck? I tried to back up,
but he still got me with it.
What just happened?
I knew he was going to do that shit.
So I backed up and he still got behind me.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Spy. What the fuck?
I knew he was going to do that.
So I backed up and he still got it.
Spy.
You got trick stabbed.
Yeah. That's whatever.
Your Boston is coming out now.
Oh, we're good.
You're not going to fucking trick stab me anymore.
God damn it.
Can we get a teleporter?
Dude, this spy is just,
he's just killing me over and over again.
There's a dude that's just making my life a living hell.
Even if I try to look for him.
Okay. Can we get a teleporter is what I asked.
Yeah. It was there.
And then you, you're not spy.
You're not, you're not spy checking.
Good enough.
Dude, you're washed up.
I was washed up in TF2 probably like seven or eight years ago.
So that's all right.
I was washed up like years ago.
Yeah. Yeah.
Or at least we're still getting scared Saturdays.
Yeah.
Oh shit. The sniper up there.
You know what? Fuck it.
Fuck it. We're going in here.
Are we?
Yeah. Fuck it.
Let's just bring a teleporter in here.
Yeah. There's a good room.
That sniper is going to try to kill us.
Yeah. He is.
He's gaming.
Can't do much about it.
Shit. Okay. Well, it's not there anymore.
You should do it in the room before that
is where you should be putting it.
Probably.
We still won.
Nice job.
Did we earn face cam yet?
Maybe in like another 10 minutes.
If you're good.
That was good.
You don't think we should stay?
No, you should not.
Okay.
As a professional kill streak haver, we should leave.
I'm going to go for the Huntsman.
I used to be so good with this.
And I mean that unironically.
This video is on my channel with me
just fucking destroying like 20 kills in one life and shit.
It's I don't even know how I go back
and watch those old TF2 Huntsman videos.
And I say, how did I even do that?
I could never do that now ever.
You can put your mind to it.
You can do anything.
There's one string in a, I think it's on nucleus.
I just hit like 10 headshots in a row
over the course of like maybe 30 to 40 seconds.
It's fucking crazy.
Was that German mad?
No, no, no, no.
This is like just a regular just commentary.
The same thing.
We're playing nucleus in that video.
I will never play an FPS game better than that.
I was so motivated.
I hit every shot I took.
Oh, I forgot about the shields, right?
This is what I had on.
Can't be burnt.
Oh, I'll do Girardi.
See if I still got it.
I definitely don't.
This weapon's really hard to use.
That's why they call it the Luxman.
Cause it's very difficult to use.
I shouldn't be using this.
I got a cool hat though.
Doesn't that matter?
It does matter a whole lot.
Just let me play.
Nice.
But that jump of all the jump.
I gotta go a little higher.
Oh goodness.
Oh, they're all Girardi.
Oh, I thought it was right in the head.
The level one in the corner.
Destroy the sentry now.
Ouch.
I'm doing all right.
You gotta go a little bit higher.
There's a little bit of drop on the Huntsman.
Show us all your hats.
I'll show my backpack in a little bit.
He doesn't care.
What the?
No, no, kill me.
I got some health here.
I can't do it.
Yeah, I did that.
I'm the reason we pushed the cart.
Cause their whole team was in spawn chasing me around.
That was me.
Is that Pyro though?
Guys flying around.
Holy shit.
That guy went across the whole map.
Cause I'm in zooming.
All right.
This guy got to be fucking kidding me.
I thought I could catch him on the way down.
All right.
Can somebody kill this market garden soldier?
They're just flying around the map and killing everybody.
Fuckin' stupidness.
I hate market gardener battles.
Are you doing it too?
Yeah.
All right.
This is where you shine as Huntsman
because people just poke their heads out
and you get headshots every five seconds.
I want to see five right now.
A little bit higher.
I'm aiming a little too low.
Oh my God, dude.
Fucking somebody kill him.
You just shoot him.
I did and it didn't kill him.
He was covered in Gerardi too.
The guy with no gun?
The guy market gardening.
With no gun?
I Gerardi'd him.
I shot him with an arrow.
He was still alive and killed me with the fucking shovel.
Okay.
All right.
That's what happened.
Okay.
All right.
He's back.
And he's just, he's back.
And that's what he's doing.
He's just trying to kill me.
He's just coming for me.
He's coming to kill me.
That's what he's doing.
They respected it.
I like, I appreciate that.
You sucks.
Spot.
I got him.
Oh my fucking God.
Okay.
I think he comes over here,
tries to kill me and then runs until I get a full health
and then comes back to kill me again.
Yeah.
Why wouldn't that?
That's what you do in team fortress too.
You go, you try and kill them on respawn.
You can get health if your health's low.
I wasn't in the head.
Shit.
It looks like it.
There we go.
Oh, he just saved your sniper friend's life.
He's beginning to believe just a little.
Ooh, a teleporter.
He won't look at me.
What was that?
Like fucking weasel laugh.
That's the sound you make before you switch class.
I hit him again, but it didn't kill him.
Trying to get him up.
Shit, he hit me.
I wish these were headshots,
but they're like neck shots.
I still have to go even higher.
Yeah.
I'm afraid to go higher.
You won't get hurt.
I used to sit on what TR walkway
for like three hours straight,
just shooting at people with a Huntsman.
TR walkway is the real one.
Oh yeah, it was.
All right.
Who's up there?
I think right now you like know when I die.
Why don't you make noises when you die?
I am making noises.
You don't hear them.
Like death noises.
No, no.
I'm seeing a lot of pogs.
No, you can't pog until I get the headshots down again.
But I mean, I'm making noise when I get hit.
No, you're not.
Yes, I am.
I might need sensitivity down a little more.
There's no such thing as sensitivity.
Fail RP.
What?
They have a cheater.
He didn't even,
his gun didn't even turn and look at me.
Shit.
Oh, we're on it.
But you can't kick bots if you're on the enemy team.
Someone from the other team has to kick them.
It's kind of awkward.
Hey, where was he?
Oh, I kind of fucked it up.
You typed that in party chat, by the way.
I don't actually know what the all chat is.
I really do not know what my button is.
You were like privately.
Oh, that was a good one.
It's why apparently.
Yeah, I got it.
We have a lot of time though.
Whoa.
Holy shit.
Ah, I thought I could get two.
Oh my God, I should have just swung at them
with the fucking melee.
Get da-da-donked.
Dude, my energy levels are increasing.
What does that mean?
That means exactly what it means.
Got it.
One shot of germ of protein shake
and your energy levels will be increasing.
Cool.
What?
No way.
All right, now this is where,
this is gonna shine.
I got a cool hat.
Make sure you buy Germa's milk.
Oh, that's not for sale.
Let me just hold on.
They kind of still have a cheating bot on their team.
You wanna leave?
No, it's upward.
That's why you stay.
Oh, check this out.
Check this out.
Does this still work?
Like when everybody gets up to the front gate
and you can hit them with Jurati before the gate opens.
That's the thing, right?
What is?
Like I can coat them with Jurati like at one second
because they're all gonna sit at the door
and be impatient.
You can try.
Are you good enough?
I think so.
Ready?
Here comes everybody in one, two, three.
He just goes back in spawn.
Oh, I thought he was gonna walk back.
Where are you?
Spawn.
Spawn, you dead?
I just died.
How come you didn't make a death noise?
That was kind of a before death sound.
I went, oh.
When you die, you're gonna be like,
oh man, I made a mistake there.
What I actually should have done is,
like, no, you're dead, dude.
Play scout?
I could, maybe.
That hurt.
Where are you?
I need you.
I'm a medic.
It's a market gardener.
Ah, he missed.
This dang fool.
Oh, I was about to go on a fucking run right there.
Where are you?
I'm playing Huntsman Sniper.
What do you need me for?
I need you.
I'm dead.
I'm alive now, and I just said medic.
I have like a cool hat on.
I have like a.
There's a soldier behind you.
What?
Where?
Is he dead?
He's dead, man.
You on 50 FOV?
No.
It'd be funny if I was.
Why are you doing that?
Don't pull a card, just blink.
Why would you do that?
Why not?
You're going to get screamed at in the chat now.
Oh, this is a serious match.
I thought there was going to be a lot more people
out there than it was.
Oh shit.
I'm going to play like gamer medic.
Play with a real weapon, please.
Okay.
One random sticky.
Heavy goes first.
Heavy goes first, that's priority.
You get priority.
You're heavy.
I'm a support class.
I got you, Frank the fish.
Everyone is hurt all the time.
Later, dude.
What do you mean later?
Our demo just turned off the map.
I got you, Frank the fish.
Thanks, bro.
Let's get them.
You ready?
Nope, I'm dead.
Coward.
Actually the heat maker, I don't want it here.
Give me the default.
Heat maker is good, but you got to get a lot of kills.
That's one of the more you headshots you get, right?
You get asked.
No, that's the other one.
The bizarre bargain is extremely powerful now.
Would recommend.
So it's mostly the same as like default,
unless you get headshots.
That was a headshot right there.
Oh, you see that 150?
Almost.
Say it.
I'm trying to...
Oh, that would have been good.
It was close.
I'm gaming, man.
I'm trying.
What are you doing?
Get him, get him, get him, get him, get him.
There's nobody to shoot at.
Come on, shoot.
You're up on the leaderboard there.
That's me, the medic.
Leave it, right?
We're voting upward, right?
Does that mean we stay?
Do you want to vote upward?
I'll click on upward if you want to.
Can't really click it for some reason.
Oh, are we staying?
Yeah.
All right, something seems broken though.
I can't vote anything.
Neither can I.
Go risk on.
This happens.
I sure hope it's gold rush.
I love gold rush.
I wouldn't care.
They nerfed the bonk atomic punch.
I can see why.
That's the one where you drink it
and you become invincible
and you just run behind enemy lines.
Yeah, I think you run slower
and depending on the amount of damage you take,
you, after it ends, you get slowed.
We're on upward.
You should be happy.
We're on upper.
I am happy.
What do I want to do?
Should I go flog Pyro?
Not on offense.
What the hell is going on?
I got this cool item.
The Nostromo, Napalm-er.
I remember people wanted this shit, didn't they?
Some of the other tie-in items, right?
Equip the pen.
Get pack is good.
I think.
Do you have it?
Yes, I do.
You guys like my outfit?
I have the barbecue on my back.
I've got the funny glasses crooked
and I got the, I have the white mask thing.
I think I look pretty good.
You look great.
I cannot find you.
The right hallway.
What do you mean no?
You don't like the strip?
I'm judging, I'm judging it.
I wasn't a no, it was a consideration.
Yes, you look good.
Does it change it if I do this?
This is allowed.
Oh, hey.
What?
How do I look?
Ooh, you got a skateboard.
That's kind of cool.
Ooh, what is that?
You have like a fishy mode.
I tried to shoot it back.
If I shot that crit rocket back,
that would have been fucking awesome.
All right, sometimes I'm into Pyro
and I do well and sometimes I just die
after walking out the front door over and over again.
Ouch.
I'm a death magnet.
What does this hit sound?
It's kind of like the little gurgles.
I don't know what it is.
Jeez, that guy killed me very fast.
What the hell?
Degreaser?
I died really quick.
Oh, I got shot by a sniper.
Excuse me.
Can't pull me.
Oh, it's so low.
Nice.
Good job, good job.
I'm in trouble now.
Oh, good heals.
Come here, come here.
I can put you out.
Oh, I didn't know that Dumbleman
can equip the parachute.
Oh, he got stuck in the wall.
I would have hit him.
I'm going around.
Ooh, they're so focused.
Yeah, we're gaming.
These are absolutely gaming right now.
Oh shit.
I fucked it up.
We please see some, I'll play scout on defense.
Can we please see some scout, please?
We've been waiting.
In 2023 TF2, what is your favorite class to play?
Yeah.
Scout.
Seriously?
Yeah.
Sometimes I like doing a little bit of jumping,
but the scout guy kills everybody
unless there's a sentry.
Jumped over it, but it's all right.
Shit.
Oh, he's going to go up there.
Damn it.
You have a cat puke hit sound.
It kind of is.
Watch that right side.
He's actually dead dead.
I don't think so.
Oh, fuck you.
It didn't hit anybody.
What the fuck?
How?
It threaded a needle, dude.
That was, oh, come on.
Shit.
Save the crits.
Play with pyro vision on.
Yeah, I'll do it.
That sounds fun.
Oh, that's not going to work.
Oh, I hit him.
You're using the volcano fragment.
Oh, mega lol.
What's wrong with it?
Oh, the rift volcano weapon
from rift, the great game rift.
You can, yeah, this is fine.
It's a cool weapon.
That's the worst weapon in the game,
but isn't the cool factor of having a fire axe cool?
The sentry in the middle of the open.
Maybe.
Oh, I forget.
This is like the stereo weapon.
I can hear this in the middle of my brain when I shoot it.
Sniper, I got him standing still for you.
I am the distractor.
I'm medic.
I switched to medic.
It's me and backfield huntsman guy.
Everyone's over healed.
All right, go get him.
Oh, that's bad news.
Oh, I didn't know they were coming up that far.
Yeah, get it, get it, get it.
Okay, I get it.
I shouldn't have been up that far.
That was stupid.
That was bad news.
Bad chest.
That was kind of a tuber voice,
but we're playing TF2, that's the point.
We're back, baby.
We're back.
Feel like I'm fishing.
All right, come on.
Come on, Bloop-O.
Bloop-O is gonna win this for us right now.
Oh my damn it, dude.
I promise I'll get one Uber.
Oh, I see what you're doing.
Smart, smart.
All right, I have to hit.
All right, we're getting attacked.
We're getting attacked now.
All right, come on, Bloop-O.
Come on, Bloop-O.
Bloop-O's about to get on this.
Get the fuck out of here.
We're good, we're good.
I got an Uber.
Let's publish time, let's go.
Nice.
Why does it take the announcer for this to happen?
It does.
Dude, Bloop-O, I'm telling you.
No, Bloop-O, you're good.
Is that the heater?
That weapon's pretty cool.
The anti-spy heavy gun.
That thing's cool.
Dude, just let's roll it.
Don't even, just don't even stop.
I'm sorry, Bloop-O, I gotta spread it around.
Use your anti-spy gun.
I had to use it.
That's all right.
Hey, that was a good push though.
We got ourselves another three and a half minutes.
All right, what song am I doing?
Poker Face by Lady Gaga, mum, mum, mum, mum.
Wow, actually nice.
Just drop.
I got it.
I thought I was gonna hit him with at least one of those.
That was just the equivalent of,
I'm like two or three miles away from that guy
and I'm throwing rocks at him and he has a sniper rifle
and I'm sitting there in the open
just throwing multiple small rocks
that are not gonna go that far.
And why are you doing that?
It once fell off.
Are you one ear or two ear?
It's a two ear, it's two ear right now.
And you're able to function, what changed?
I think that's, I'm talking a little louder
because I can't hear myself talk.
Maybe that's why I'm being louder today.
I'm proud of you.
Thanks.
You're my little baby boo boo.
I feel like I haven't seen you in a while.
I was in the back line like all game doing absolutely nothing.
It, I was having a good time.
No, no, no, no, don't let him do that.
Ooh, where is it?
It's unkillable.
50 HP stationary thing.
Beware.
All right, I have, what class are you playing?
I'm sniper, you were just healing me.
I know, but sometimes I'm not Ubering you.
Let's do it.
Okay, one, two, three, go.
Why did you tell me to do that?
We got the sentry, technically speaking.
Actually a net win, that's true.
Yeah, look, we're doing it.
Oh shit, that's actually true, nice.
Oh shit, it actually did work.
We just inspired everybody.
Holy shit, the whole clip just went into somebody.
I just freaked somebody out so bad.
Smash, smash.
I was ever saying minus four.
Whoa, you must've told a really bad joke.
I've never even seen a minus four before.
What happened?
No, did you guys hear the,
it just wasn't on screen, I looked away.
I am not dying over there.
Whoa, Chris Krieg.
Whoa, what is going on?
Okay, so when you were giving me shit for like,
how come you're not screaming every time you die?
But when I say, whoa, Chris Krieg,
that's for you to make a little joke.
That's not a death noise, it's very different.
We're being stupid down here.
Turn around, turn around, turn around.
You stopped healing me.
That would've been so cool,
everyone would've thought I was cool if I did that.
Somebody said, this feels like a bit.
I think it's because me and Ster have not played this game
for 10 fucking years on camera.
I think that's probably why you feel that way.
We're playing separate games as well.
I feel like we're doing entirely
and completely different things
like we're in two different games.
I think we're doing fine though.
I got put into the ceiling.
I mean.
Oh, come on.
Did that really just happen?
Somebody shoot something, for goodness gracious.
We need the Uber.
I just have to try to stay alive longer.
Medic, wanna build Uber?
I'm coming.
Medic, can only run so fast, bro.
Oh, here, I'm charging, I'm building Uber for you.
You want me to play a class that gets Ubered?
Or do you wanna roll the dice?
I got this is direct hit soldier up here.
I think I'm all right.
This demo up here too, I think we'll be okay.
Oh, I almost got it.
Do not as a sniper, I'm gonna get hit in the head
if I show my face.
Every time I see a heavy,
they are seconds away from being backstabbed.
I need to heal, I gotta heal.
All right, I'm ready to Uber this soldier
if they're still alive up here.
Fuck.
Oh my God, dude.
I thought he killed them.
See, he had like the pan kill
and I was like, oh, he killed the guy.
I didn't know there was like three people
in the fucking corner.
No, I'm bad.
I saw the crit pan kill and I was like,
oh, nice, you got him.
Fuck.
Somebody up here now.
All right, get me out of the way.
We're going to push an Uber in.
We will eventually.
They just crits our front line.
Our front line is down.
Oh my goodness.
Oh heavy, peek this corner.
Not you.
You got dominated.
Yeah, the guy was behind us.
He didn't, I didn't, I did.
There was nobody there and then I turned around again.
There's a rocket in my face.
Medic, we need you.
Well, you need to keep the medic alive
and no one's doing that.
You keep going on the flank.
You're like down in the basement.
No, you follow where the medic goes.
Medic is the quarterback of Team Fortress.
I haven't seen you.
Well, you're playing sniper.
Can you heal me?
I'm the only medic on the goddamn team right now.
All right.
You're right next to me.
Look at how many, who takes priority?
Heavy or sniper?
Who takes priority?
You weren't healing him.
I was.
Oh no, you go get a health back.
Blue bow is gonna carry again.
Oh God, he's dead.
I got an Uber right now.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Jump through, jump through.
We're going, going, going.
Go, go, go.
Get in there, go.
Don't touch it.
What, what, what?
It's chaos.
Go, go, go, go, go.
Chaos, chaos.
It's chaos time.
You guys gotta get this.
Failure, failure, failure.
Leave.
You gotta leave now.
You're embarrassing me.
Wait, is there another round?
I left, I left.
Minus four?
What?
I got minus four.
I don't know why, why are people saying that?
What does that mean?
I think it means, I don't know.
What did I eat four of today?
If you want to see just how far
my gamer skill has fallen.
I got 52 points of the spy in one life.
I got like 60, but that's not ever gonna happen ever again.
Oh, this is one of the new ones.
You can definitely just go onto your walkway again
to get that the same way you got it the first time.
No, no, no.
I was very careful to make sure I didn't do that.
Cause I always wanted that to be accurate.
Cause when it happened, it was like, holy shit.
And now you want to preserve it for life.
Oh, I'm going to do, I'm going to go heavy with
maybe just default minigun.
I like the chocolate bar.
And we'll do gloves.
This thing is cool, but it's kind of distracting.
You got a banana?
I do, but chocolate's kind of fun
because it gives you more max health.
But banana got potassium.
Bananas are great.
I have no idea where I'm going.
I think I'm going the right way.
There's arrows.
Yeah, I bit my tongue a little bit.
All right, let's do it.
I bit my tongue.
Oh, they come out this way?
Cool.
Is there a spy?
Why do I feel like there's not very many people?
Because they're cowards and they all died
and they need to respawn and respawns take a while.
I even turned around.
I turned around looking for a spy
and that second I turned my back, I'm dead.
There's a spy coming.
Spy dead ringer, spy dead ringer.
Pirate spy, pirate spy.
Let's do the fucking slowed down
instrumental version of that.
Do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do.
Do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do.
You just did the brown noise to me.
That was so Basie.
It really wasn't.
I mean, my pants tell a different story.
All right.
Honest to goodness, honest to goodness.
What the fuck just happened there?
What happened?
I haven't got to run all the way back there.
A lot of spies.
There are, I get there, turn around to look for a spy,
freak out for a second, spin my mini gun and die.
Their team may have like four or five of them.
I fucking knew it.
I knew it.
He might not even be dead.
Yeah.
There's one behind.
Sure is.
It's in my head.
I got 400 fucking health.
Yeah.
Oh shit.
Can someone do the spy math?
How many Ubers do they have?
Shit.
It's, it's, it's, this has to come down to like 1.2.
It's way too high still.
Even lower.
This has got to be like 1.1?
1. like 1.5?
Do it!
Get it right!
That's better, I think.
Turn off the mouse.
The mouse acceleration is on.
It's off.
I feel the love of God.
Okay.
He's here.
He ain't dead.
Wow.
Did the heavy appear behind me?
Ain't nobody killing me with a backstab now.
My whole team's there.
I don't want to be that pyro guy.
There's just too many species.
Can we get a director's cut of the speed video?
Like what you were thinking.
Like a whole walkthrough.
A whole walkthrough?
Yeah, you can like slow it down and point stuff out that like maybe like you don't notice
on your first watch.
That spy is not.
Oh my gosh.
I need ammo.
Dude, he's too good.
Ready to go.
He's not dead.
He's absolutely 100% still life.
Don't do it!
I thought I was part of a way.
Oh my.
Wait.
What?
Was it the pyro?
No, the pyro sprayed me.
The pyro sprayed me.
The pyro sprayed.
Jesus.
Gee whiz.
It was the scout.
Oh, he jumped up on the rock.
Oh, that bastard.
You played with the Dragon's Fury?
That's the new pyro one, right?
The pyro flamethrower.
I looked at it, but I never really actually tried to use it.
I've been enjoying it.
I'm a Dragon's Fury appreciator.
Come on.
Play scout.
Okay.
Fine.
It's a flare gun primary.
Yeah.
You don't actually hold a fire down.
It's like a weird like projectile in it and your face came on.
I'll turn my face.
Come on for exactly 10 minutes next round and I'll make sure to say now we're doing
it.
Now we're doing it.
Oh my God.
Jerma kind of looks like the scout.
Are you full of shit?
You real?
All right.
Wait, wait.
Hold on.
Do you kind of look like the scout because you played this game growing up?
What?
Do you just like mold it your life around it?
Is that kind of cringe?
What are you talking about?
Oh, look.
Oh, TF2.
I love TF2.
Like I'm going to like look like the scout now.
Oh my goodness.
I just I don't know where to go.
I think I have to go back here.
I don't know the route.
It is impossible to talk to you right now, by the way, dude.
We're playing separate games and everything I say is just like, wait, wait, wait, okay.
Like you're so involved in the game and you're so interested about what's going on.
I've kind of just given up.
All right.
What did you just ask?
Say it again.
It's no way.
It doesn't matter.
You asked me if I played with the pyro new primary and I was like, oh, it looks cool.
No, no, no, no, no.
I am answering your questions.
I'm just like stuff is happening in the middle.
You're answering them if in that exact moment you have like three seconds of attention span
to give me your one word answer because I am 80, 80, 80, 80, 80.
Oh my God.
This guy's fucking watching the screen.
You didn't even finish that bit.
I've changed, dude.
I keep getting killed.
All right.
What?
Let's start over.
What did you say?
I have nothing left.
I said it all.
It's all been said.
It's all on record.
Sorry.
This game requires a lot of attention.
Does it?
Yeah.
When you're playing scout.
Did you hit the meat shot?
Uh, eight, eight D meat, meat shot.
80, 80.
Wait, no, no.
Eight smiley.
That was very loud.
Uh, turn your face cam on.
Okay.
Fine.
Hi, everybody.
Well, I'm like really zoomed in.
Oops.
I don't care.
All right.
You get, you get face cam for one round and it's gone forever.
You got long hair.
I told you I was just growing it out.
I'm going to just grow it as long as it can go.
I'm going to be as gross as possible.
All right.
You guys get face cam for one round, but mine's like bigger than his is.
It's fine.
Should I reset?
Hold on.
Let me resize it.
Wait, hold on.
Are you making yours bigger?
I just made it like 10% bigger.
It's free points.
That's free points.
I'll take it.
I actually really like this thing.
I never use it though.
Oops.
Camera's too high.
Camera's too high?
Uh, hey, I don't, I'm not, it's fine.
Yeah, I think mine's good.
Is yours like half the screen or something?
Well, no, you, I'm trying to copy what, yours is too high, mine's too high.
Like you think you're a special kid?
Thinking like, like cool joke, like nice fit.
Like, oh, it's so hard to like make your webcam too high.
Like funny.
Ha ha ha ha ha.
Oops.
My face cam is going to stay the way it is.
Okay.
People say my chin's cut off.
It's fine.
It's because the camera.
You cut your chin off?
My, the camera's, I'll fix it in like a month.
There's a whole point of a face cam to show your face.
How long have you been streaming?
How many years?
I don't even, I don't even understand how this person keeps finding me.
There's like an eight second delay.
All right.
I'm going fucking psycho mode now.
Oh yeah.
You know, here it comes now.
Same.
You want to do double flog Pyro?
Ah, I'm Dragon's Fury.
I'm a Dragon's Fury enjoyer.
Oh my.
Oh, nice spy checking Pyro.
I flew the fire on every single person.
I wish they would make fall damage happen.
Just like, just like three feet higher or lower or you know what I'm saying.
That's a backstab right there.
There's my face.
Help.
Where'd the medic go?
Ouch.
Whoa.
Where?
From where?
He did it.
That was good.
We're good.
Hmm.
Sniper, they're coming.
How does he stay alive with 16 health?
Because he had 16 health.
Sometimes I forget that the fire projectiles like can kind of, you have to like move him
around.
Like they're like almost like delayed if you've tried to track somebody.
Are you serious?
Yeah, sometimes it's like it's hard to get it like directly on their body if they're
scraping around sometimes.
That's Mei from Overwatch.
Bye.
I heard it.
You are full of shit, Scout.
He's right.
They changed Pyro.
They changed all the flamethrowers work?
What?
Yeah, it's like you have to, the flame is its own like weird projectile that moves like
trails.
Oh, well I only use the Dragon's Fury.
Because I'm a gigantic.
I'm going to put the shotgun on.
Let's go shotgun time.
I should play with the degreaser, but I don't care.
Your audio got cut off, by the way.
We didn't hear the cool song.
Oh, we're doing a plenty hairstyle today.
Um, I don't think so.
I hit him with like almost every shot from a shotgun.
Just killed a hamster.
I don't believe that he's dead.
Oh, God.
The spy has almost a hundred points, by the way.
A hundred?
Yeah, because they feel bad for the spy and they give them all those points.
Don't you know that one spy backstab is like 30 points?
Ever since they nerfed the dead ringer, they're like, oh, I guess it's even harder now.
I think it's like 40 points for backstab.
The next person on the team has 38 points.
That's freaking ludicrous, dude.
I explained it.
I know.
Can someone push the cart?
I'm going to try to get on it.
I've noticed this is one of those maps where no one touches the cart at the end here because
they think someone's going to stop them and then they don't.
See?
Sniper is back.
That just happened.
That's two for two right there.
Ow.
Spy check mania?
Kind of what I'm doing right now.
It's the only thing I can do.
Alright, we're on it.
He still killed me.
This thing sucks, doesn't it?
Should I use this thing?
I'm just going to rig the fire axe.
I feel like the sound effect was even like lower.
It's like a...
Oh, fuck.
Fire axe is even worse.
I got to read all the items again.
Everything seems to be changed so differently.
That's cool though.
I'm happy about it.
It's like a whole other game to explore.
That's cool.
You got to read them first.
Why was that guy just a hundred miles per hour?
That was weird.
Dude, is he still alive?
What the fuck?
He is still alive.
That's a difference in bio.
I thought it was the same guy.
Why is that Pyro there?
It's not me.
It's me.
Literally me.
Did he not light on fire?
What was that?
I think he's dead.
No.
He's still alive.
Dude, does the dead ringer make you not get hit by fire or something?
How come I couldn't do it?
It does extinguish you and then you have to light them on fire again.
If I'm not mistaken.
Because I felt like he died and then was invisible.
I lit him on fire and then it went off of him.
Spicycle?
You could also use the Spicycle, but that makes a noise.
Oh, right.
Okay.
It melts the Spicycle though, right?
At the same time?
Yep.
It does.
That was a good fucking shot.
Jesus.
It literally was falling down.
It's me.
I promise.
Okay.
The enemy team is like right up here.
There's a health kit, but they're going to look at you because this is their spawn.
Did you get the health kit?
I'm not there.
I think that's a spy you're looking at.
That's not your name.
It wasn't.
No, it was an engineer with me.
And then you look straight at my face and said, this is me.
I promise.
And I fucking believed you.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You're an engineer.
I'm a pyro.
Oh, wait.
What?
There was an engineer in the side room with a sentry and I walked up to him and I was
like, oh shit.
And he was shooting me.
He thought I was a spy.
So I was like, I'm real.
Were you in the middle of also a separate, but I was a pyro and like a damaged engineer
was walking around the corner and he stopped and stared at me as you said that.
And it was like, don't like, you're like, oh, don't worry.
It's me.
And I was like, oh, cool.
It's you.
Were they, were they good enough for his webcam time over?
They're being good.
I keep it on another round chat was bad.
Were they bad?
My chat was being very bad.
What the heck is going on here, guys?
All right.
Fine.
I'll do it too.
Is there enough time for me to pee?
Oh, yeah.
Let's all pee.
Let's actually leave the game.
Okay.
And let's do a little pee break.
All right.
We're back.
I am back.
Are you also here?
How are you?
How's it going?
Oh, he's not here.
That was quick.
Yeah.
I mean, he's usually pretty quick.
So that's why I'm usually pretty slow.
So I took my time.
That's what I mean.
I was trying to.
You're usually pretty fast.
I was trying to match your time.
I'm like a fire hose.
He's seen it.
Are you ready?
Wait, what?
All right.
Let's go.
I'm going to keep my face game on because they were good.
They were good.
That spy was very good.
Wait, did you mean good at the game or good in chat?
Probably both.
Where's the game?
There it is.
We're joining.
Very cool.
Epic.
They were like three spies trying to kill you.
What's your most played time class?
So it is.
It's fine.
I think it's spy.
Honestly.
Either spy or engineer.
That was loud.
Is this the same one we were just in?
I don't think so.
No.
I have a way better version of this.
Yeah, I got a factory new one of these things.
Let's put it on.
Oh, there we go.
That's way better.
Getting a little spicy.
It's a little.
I'm going to scout around town.
They're not.
Okay.
He came.
He became aware.
He did the you strap on heavy.
You just pretend you're not there.
You have a gibbous on.
You don't know what's going on.
And then you just awaken.
He's probably still alive.
Why are you doing that?
Why are you being weird?
Me?
Spy.
You are.
There's no way.
I'm sorry.
You're alive still.
There's no way.
You know, I think you might be the most attractive streamer on this website.
Thank you.
I guess.
Anyone else agree?
It's not just me, right?
No, I don't know about that.
Well, like who else?
Who beats you?
I don't know.
Okay.
That's why.
Nobody beats you.
Ah, a nice movement heavy.
That was actually good.
Same guy.
I'll leave him alone.
He doesn't know what's going on.
I want him to enjoy the game.
I knew there was going to be a spy.
You should have your ego inflated.
I don't.
Look, I'm on a webcam.
That's like 480p.
Room is dark.
You look you look really good when I have to squint.
But I don't.
The blurriness just adds to the mystique.
Well, I appreciate that.
But I have what it that's a spy right there.
There's a spy right here.
You can't get a better webcam.
I don't want a better webcam.
Why not?
Because then people will just see like you like my face.
Your pores.
Yeah, I don't want to look.
Oh, man.
It's in like 4K.
No, don't look at me.
Fuck off.
I don't want you to look at my 4K face.
Like who wants that?
I don't want that.
There's a lot of people.
Looking at your face right now.
But it's like in 480p.
It's different.
That was weird.
Look at me.
Well, we're doing it.
You ever heard of like a something called the responsibility of a 10?
I have no idea what you're going with on this.
It is your responsibility as a 10 out of 10 man to just reproduce and to give as many
people an opportunity to be with you as possible.
What the fuck?
Heavy is the head that wears the crown.
That's so fucking insane.
I can't even play the game right now.
That was so fucked up.
I can't even fucking talk.
What do you mean?
I'm trying to snipe.
Do it.
I just heard that use.
That means it's a spy right here.
Oh, I see it now.
Oh, there's a secret sentry up there.
Oh, nose.
No, my nose was itchy.
Oh, he's not dead.
He's not dead.
He's coming for me again.
Oh, finally.
Come on, make it happen.
Jeremy, you really need to make it happen.
He's going sicko mode with the Wrangler.
He actually kind of is.
He's killing everybody.
Say thank you.
You are ungrateful.
Fuck.
What?
Whoa.
What do you mean?
Like the 10 out of 10 thing you're saying.
I said thank you.
I don't know what to say.
I don't know what to say about that.
It's fine.
He doesn't have to say thank you.
Am I going there?
Don't tell anybody.
I went the wrong way.
Don't tell anybody I went the wrong way.
They'll think I'm an idiot.
You can't do that.
No.
Don't you dare trickstab.
You're going to jump off a fucking rock.
Somebody help me.
So bad.
It's a spy and he's a revolver and I have to get.
It takes me two and a half seconds to shoot him.
What was that supposed to mean?
Huh?
I'm really bad at spy.
Is what that meant.
Listen, Jerma, if you're not ready to accept compliments, I want your chat to know that
that's fine.
Not everyone is like I'm not good at receiving compliments, but you know, you got to hear
him more.
Does your chat let you know how fucking sexy you are?
Now?
What?
Now you're laughing about it?
Yeah.
We're just bros being bros.
Like, bros can't compliment each other.
Like, dude.
Yeah.
What's the problem?
What's the fuck?
What the fuck?
All right.
I'm going to lock and load.
Lock and load.
I.
Dick.
Let's go.
This has three shots now.
Wait, I feel like that was they're like little balls.
Hold on.
What does this weapon do now?
What weapon?
The lock and load.
It used to be cylinders.
Now it's like these little balls.
What's the speed damage versus buildings?
I think they just made it a little worse.
It sucks now.
It was always it was always three.
I thought it was two for some reason.
I believe it always was three, even though it has two slots.
That's probably what it is.
But I do remember it also having like a crazy damage bonus that doesn't seem to have.
It was two.
It was.
Oh, yeah.
Yeah.
I think it was two at release and then they buffed it.
And then it was like, why is it three?
There's only two shots.
But it sounds different, too.
I think I remember there being something with that.
Compliment.
Stir back.
I was stir.
You have very handsome beard.
Thank you.
It hides my face.
It's not what I meant.
I know.
But if I didn't have it, then you'd be able to see my mandibles.
And you've been very physically fit recently, really kind of taking your health very seriously.
That's good, too.
I have not.
See, I'm not going to take compliments either.
Apparently not.
See?
Hard.
Yeah.
All right.
They're probably going to go the other way now.
The other way.
They got to come this way.
Oh, OK.
They're coming up.
Wait, can I go in there?
Cats being bad.
You should turn face cam off.
Um, it's all right.
I want to be the swordsman.
I want it now.
I'm going to switch to medic in a little bit and I'm going to give you some crits.
I think.
What are you playing as?
Demo?
Yeah.
There's no way he's dead.
I'm playing the swordsman.
Wait, you wanted to give crits?
I knew he was dead, too.
Is that a difference?
Hello?
Yes.
I want to give you crits.
Oh, goodness.
I was very.
I was paying a lot of attention.
This one's me.
You heard the Liberty Launchers, the best gun in the game.
I have heard some theories about it.
Do you disagree with those theories?
I trust your theories because I feel like you know kind of what you're talking about.
That's a medic spy.
Yep.
Oh, fuck.
God damn it.
They came up with an Uber, too.
Yeah.
Ubers are kind of cheating.
Oh, shit.
How are we going to lose with Jormungandr on our team?
Holy shit.
The whole team was dead.
We all just came out at the same time.
Oh, my God.
You just run.
Okay.
I'm worried about.
I wanted to save the.
It was a.
It was.
Okay.
What the fuck?
That's a.
Do you want to give me the crits or do you want to run down and try and melee pyros?
The guy was running away.
I was trying to heal him.
I was depending on you.
I almost have it.
And your goldfish brain activated.
There are 10 people on the team.
All right.
I got it.
Where are you?
Press E. Fuck you.
Press E. I heard spy.
Keep going.
Nice.
Oh, all right.
We did.
Good.
We got it.
We did.
Good.
I think I forced it.
There weren't a lot of people, but I guess we did kill people.
So we did kill people.
They got a teleporter behind us.
I got to go do this.
I will handle it.
OK.
I will be back here.
And you can come with.
Well, people need help over here.
Bad.
The guy who came up with the dead ringer.
Dead ringer is not that big of a problem.
I think it's the dead ringer, spy, sickle combo potentially that because you can get
out of a lot.
Jesus.
Back in my day, if you're if you died, you died.
If you're consistent and like, I mean, once I started really, oh, no, yeah, delete spy
from the game.
I agree.
See what?
No.
What if you start to pay attention to good despise?
I don't think he's dead.
It is.
So somebody has to be like constantly paying attention just constantly if there's a really
good spy on the team.
I can't.
But what if they make a mistake?
Shouldn't they die?
Didn't they nerf the dead ringer really, really bad at some point, like in 2015 or 2016?
Yeah.
But shouldn't they have done it four times?
I remember there was a pretty massive they made it loud, much louder, right?
I haven't maybe I'll play with it.
So yeah, that's a spy.
You're literally you're literally me.
There's three of you.
OK, now I think the problem is the spies that are on the other team are like they're just
there's like five of them.
One of them was me being extra paranoid.
Don't you think it's weird?
All right, we're getting a little too far up here.
This is kind of this is kind of scary.
This is scary.
We don't have Chris yet.
This is scary what we're doing.
Well, it looks like I'm behind you.
I'm behind you along with spy number 16.
I think he's still like, yeah, I don't know who's who.
Me neither. Let's walk forward.
Come with me.
Wait, wait, I need to heal his viral.
Come on. Yes, I do.
I'm a team player.
You're going to get back. He's not dead.
Do you do you want it?
There's people everywhere, dude.
Do you want it or not?
No, no. Am I screaming?
I would get scared the shit out of me.
Just don't get back. I thought it was going to die.
Did you? I have no ammo.
If I die because of this, I will be pissed.
Just just keep yourself busy.
I'm so busy, honey.
But here's an iPad.
Oh, I can make the crates.
I don't know if you could guess, but there is a there was a
high five behind us.
I'm trying to eat his sandwich.
TF2 on iPad.
That should be pretty.
That would be pretty lit.
Would it?
No. Will you get out of here?
Get out of here.
You give your little Billy.
Give little. Oh, God.
That guy should be dead.
All right. I must have some
bullets for you if you want some.
I'm coming. I'm dead.
Give it to someone else.
I'm about to.
Why is this thing not charging?
Come on, heavy. Go for it.
No, no, no.
Get it. How many are there, two?
How many people does it take to kill one spy?
That was like 11 people versus one guy.
We're good. How much damage reduction does the dead bringer give?
I don't know.
I think it's like 90 percent.
Let's leave. OK.
Op score.
Would I get a top score?
I don't think so.
That doesn't even say on the item.
I think this is coal allows you to see enemy health.
Sixty five percent damage reduction. Lame.
Collect the organs of people you hit with the Vita saw.
What was this before?
Oh, no, it looks like it's still the same.
Wait, that's actually kind of good.
What is organs?
I don't know.
So this is the one that keeps Uber if you're dead.
You get to keep a certain percent.
So percentage of your Uber charge level is retained on death
based on the number of organs harvested.
Fifteen percent per.
And you can get caps out at 60.
I think you have to hit people with it, though.
Minus 10 health.
If you're going to hit people, you might as well hit them.
Oh, my God. That's true.
You want to play Phoenix again?
Oh, I don't mind.
I'm I'm leaving.
I want to I want a different thing.
I'll take it off the list. OK.
I am out.
Let's start startling down to them.
Let's play some like classic ones.
Let's go to like, like nucleus or harvest, right?
Or bad water was that bad water an hour ago.
Yeah, it's been a while.
Sawmill. Yeah, so I'm a good one, too.
I don't think I want to play too for it.
Maybe not yet.
Undermountain. Undermountain is a good one.
Don't play Brazil.
I want to go to Thunder Mountain.
OK. Oh, ready to go to thunder.
Oh, here's the thunder because he lays down that lumber or something.
Oh, frontier. Cool.
Shout it from the mountaintops, baby.
Undermountain server is changing the way it actually is.
Yeah, a lot of time when you casual queue,
you'll get into a game at the end of the game because that's
what everyone leaves to find a good game.
But if you, you know, you see what I'm saying?
I kind of hope is going to Egypt.
Oh, God, I played Egypt the other day.
Once was enough.
All right, let's let me let me do something here.
Soldier has a lot of cool weapons.
Let's just go default.
Default rocket launcher like like it's a lot of cool weapons.
I you will use none of them with the pen.
This brings me back to like 2000, like 11, 2012.
My biggest nostalgia map turned out to be Snakewater.
Yeah. Snakewater.
What was the one that it was two payloads that had to cross each other?
You each had to push one.
There's Hightower.
And that one is the one that they cross paths.
I've been trying to remember the name of that one, too.
Not Hightower.
There was payload race.
Pipeline. Yep. Yep.
Pipeline. That place sucked ass, but it was so fun to play.
That's not what I expect you to say.
I mean, it did. Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah. Pipeline that I fucking that.
Mm hmm.
Yeah, but it was a ton of it was a ton of fun to play.
But that place was just a mess.
But when the two carts were in the middle together,
it was just a mess.
The enemy team comes from up here where you're looking.
That's the enemy team spawn.
They're going to want to back up because they come out in 10 seconds.
I know what I'm doing.
And they are going to come out with an Uber. Good.
For those of you who haven't seen this game before,
an Uber makes them invulnerable and a medic gets it after a certain amount
of charge. It's an ultimate ability.
That isn't a spy.
Is this by get a dishwasher?
Oh, go, go, go. Quick, quick.
That guy is good.
Don't you? He's not dead.
Oh, shit. The engineer died.
Why? I'm going to stand in front of the fucking killed the engineer.
I'm going to say anyone.
I'm literally going to take any damage.
I'm going to use my I'm using my body to make sure there's nobody here.
It's this. Oh, man.
I don't care if I die. Tell me more.
Tell me. Tell me what you're doing with your body.
All right. He's back to this fucking spy.
Your health seems low.
If you want to know, maybe there's a dispenser.
We have no medics. Oh, shit.
I'm going to come heal you. OK.
Oh, you've got this pal.
There's a demo in the hallway.
Hit in the distance. I'm dead.
I'm dead, too.
Got to watch out for those.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
I don't even. Oh, he's up there.
Honest, honestly, who's your favorite character from World of Warcraft?
Um, that's a good question, dude.
That's that. Thanks.
Hold on. I got a minute because I'm dead.
Who's the best character from World of Warcraft?
Your favorite, not the best.
The best is obviously Sylvanas.
She's so powerful and so relevant all the time.
This is going to be a stupid answer, but I don't know if it is or not.
Uh, I got shot in the chest by this.
This is like a 14 kill streak.
Am I going to go pyro against hold the button down in a circle?
I mean, no one is even like I just watched like three people in a row
actually AFK standing still that he stabbed.
There's not much threat.
Uh, Kelthuzad, either Kelthuzad or Kael'thas.
There you go.
Why is Kelthuzad your favorite or Kael'thas?
Because they're like, I don't know,
they're kind of like they're goofy.
And Kelthuzad is like, I need more power.
Give me the mana, more mana.
Like, you know, he was cool.
I like to build sentries with.
Yeah, I got the crits.
Frank, let's go, Frank.
All right, I'll tell you when to do it.
Ready and activate.
Why did you not do it? I told you to do it.
What are you doing?
I just told you activate and you didn't do it.
I got hit the fucking head.
Activate means.
Why did you not do it?
Why didn't you scream?
I guess you're right, I didn't scream.
Oh, well, there goes another crits.
Just totally wasted.
I died.
We probably would have killed at least three people.
But only you had just screamed.
Well, that's that's your activation, not mine.
Yeah, and I'm the medic and I want my activation.
I get to call the shots.
The medic has the power.
You never knew that.
There's somebody, there's a spy.
They're all behind us.
What the fuck?
It really has just been all spies.
I'm every game.
Oh, I have one help.
I got the crits.
Where's Papa Papa?
I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming.
I don't trust it, but who knows?
OK, all right.
Not yet.
Uh huh. I'll know.
Dude, I don't play this game.
I don't play this game that often.
It's never you should never do it.
Don't ever do that again.
Germa, I've got the crits.
Where are you?
Damn it.
They were also spread out and I was so paranoid
I was going to get backstabbed.
Well, you know what they say?
Your responsibility is a 10.
Oh, I'm going to change to the pen.
Equip the pen. Equip the pen.
Heavy seems like a really stupid idea right now,
because it's just spies.
It does. Just circling us like don't do it.
Don't do it. I'm going to do it.
I'm going to do the heater.
Oh, my goodness.
They ain't going to fucking get near us now.
He's brilliant.
They won't simply just walk through it
and then never, ever, ever die.
At least we can see where they are.
I need I need mana.
Don't backstab me. Don't backstab me.
Don't backstab me, please.
Why would you eat it into the wall?
Did I just get crit with a was it a random crit?
Yep. And then I turned around and there was a spy.
There's a spy. There's a spy.
There's a spy.
Are there any other classes in this game?
We're fine.
I spawn new spy.
Demo player left.
Oh, my God.
I even was looking around for him.
I'm surrounded by fucking fire.
What the hell happened there?
They can still stab you if you're surrounded by fire
that deals three damage.
Yeah, but he shouldn't they light on fire?
I thought that was the whole point.
It's not constant.
Like, there's there's like pulses.
They can get in between the hole.
It's all that common.
I'll take care of it.
Got him.
Thanks, Frank, the tank.
That person's item says, hey, star,
like, I'm going to kill your head or something.
That's a threat I can sue.
How did they can't kill my head?
Nobody messing around here.
You want to crit for who are you?
I'm a pyro. I don't think it's a good idea.
I think it's a great idea.
But where are you?
Dead at the moment.
I'm going to see Barbie tonight.
Nice.
Let's watch Barbie together.
Good if you really wanted to.
Because Vegas have like a giganto theater
where you can buy out the whole thing
and it can just be us in it.
Why would you want to do that?
Because no one will see us hold hands.
Let's go.
Let's go. Go, go, go, go, go.
I just got crit by that shotgun.
God damn.
They kind of just get them.
That's so funny.
I was dead anyway, so it's all right.
Oh, should I?
At least I helped his dead body, apparently.
Yeah, thank you, Frank.
Really going to start calling you Frank a lot.
That's fine.
Yeah, I know the streamer like that.
I can call him by his first name.
What is it?
OK, do we get him?
We got a big deal or anything to me, though.
Frank, not doing bad.
We're doing fine.
I'm dead.
I don't want to play medic anymore.
You know what I mean?
You ever just reach your limits?
What the fuck?
Watch that door.
I'm watching it.
I need ammo.
Is there a dispenser over here?
Oh, I need dispenser.
Where's the dispenser?
I need a dispenser.
There are other sources of ammo.
I know, I got it.
That's a lot of Pyros.
That's a lot of Uber.
That's the biggest piss I've ever taken for men.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
I haven't hit anyone with this.
Are you using the pen?
The pen?
Are you actually using it?
The what?
The pen.
I put the pen.
Please, Jerma.
I will before the stream ends.
Help, help.
I'm going to hit someone.
Just wait.
I feel like I haven't been hitting anybody either.
Wait, this is a bunch of ammo down here, isn't there?
Full box, yes.
Do you know that when you kill people, they drop ammo boxes?
I have to kill them, though.
I want to be sure to have the sure thing.
Just letting you know, not a lot of people have played this game.
No one really knows what's going on right now.
We could explain it.
We should.
You want to do like a class in TF2?
Sure.
You want to be the teacher?
Well, they're going to have to pay up.
$60 an hour lessons for TF2 esports coaching.
Let's go.
I'm not even aiming near people.
I'm cracking out right now, dude.
What am I doing?
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I'm fine.
Is there just a Spencer around here?
I kind of cracked out a little.
You're kind of cracking a little bit.
Your skin's kind of cracking.
I'm going for at least number three on the scoreboard this round.
Or honorary mention.
What the fuck did he just wait?
What's going on up there?
Did I stop doing that?
Oh, they're having fun.
OK, never mind.
Yeah, well, hey, this server, this server.
I didn't kill them in 10 seconds going.
It's all or nothing time.
Yeah, I was aiming at you.
Here it comes.
Oh, I didn't get up there.
Thirty nine points.
Would you have forty four or fifty two?
I think I hit two arrows.
That was fun.
This game is fun.
Have you played it before?
Briefly, I think I'm going to go.
Who would have thought a simple game like this would have bred
the sexiest, most attractive streamer on Twitch?
You're on to this today.
This is like your thing today.
I don't know why.
Why is this your thing today?
It really all just comes back to Team Fortress 2.
I'm going to just be a dickhead this round, so see if I can make it happen.
I'm going to be a dickhead this round.
What does that mean?
Yeah, you two spies think you're so fucking smart.
I'm going to click their head real gun.
OK, I really.
Wait, the good spies on our team now.
Oh, my God, that's amazing. Thank God.
You better go get them.
You better really step up this round.
No excuses, man.
All right, let's go really step up, bro.
This is bullshit. You're trying to pull on me right now.
Did you hear the rumor, by the way, that they're adding another class to the game?
I did not. I think that you made it up.
It's going to be like a dog.
There's like a dog.
There's like a mechanical thing on its back.
People just brought it into the train.
It ate like three people.
Shit, should have turned around.
And the train hit people.
The dog class. Yeah.
What would the dog class's loadout default loadout be?
The woofer. OK.
Is this like an arcing lightning wand or something?
What are you talking about?
What does it do?
I'd have to go. There's a meet the dog that leaked.
Oh, nice. Oh, oh, there's too many people on the cart.
The spies here somewhere.
Dude, I fucking popped off a little bit right there.
It's all right.
All right. For those that have no idea,
because it is actually probably worth explaining some of these things explain,
explain with if I kill somebody with these gloves,
I get 100 percent crits for five seconds.
I then because it's not very much time, you can either keep these on.
I like to go to the family business.
This is a shotgun.
You get 100 percent crits on any weapon.
And this thing has a bunch of clips and you can pretty much get,
I would say, all eight shots out in that five seconds.
Fat scout. Yeah, it's pretty fun.
There's definitely a lot of people that probably don't really know.
So sincerely speaking, it's probably not a bad idea to teach them.
Well, because people you know this as well as I do.
A lot of people jump into this game and they get backstabbed
and then they uninstall the game.
They're just like, what the fuck was that? This game's stupid.
But like, if you kind of knew like kind of what was going on
and just like why and I know what's going on, I'm uninstalling afterwards.
No, you're not.
And these hit someone.
Oh, let's fucking go.
W I got a lot of fucking health.
How many dead skin cells are built up on your mouse buttons?
I clean my mouse all the time, actually, so not very much.
I'm actually clean my mouse.
I'm going to check.
I'm going to validate.
Go for it.
All right, let me make my dumb build happen.
Oh, I'm real. Help, help, help.
How did that not hit?
That shot him right in the chest.
It didn't even do any damage.
Despite their losing a lot.
You're real.
It's the whole frontier payload feels like a spy
all the time when you're on it.
It's so big. I heard a clunky.
I heard a
you got to dodge in real life.
That guy just blew up into the wall. What?
That's weird.
Oh, that was a big crit hit everybody.
All right. I'm going for the actual heavy now.
Have you opened any cases or crates or anything?
Oh, I told you I did.
But how many? How many?
Oh, five.
Whoa. OK, that was more than I thought.
I did not know these windows were here.
OK, I'm going to try the Liberty launcher.
You say this is like the best weapon, right?
Yeah, like pound for pound.
This is the like, wow.
Yeah, I don't think anything in the game compares to it.
OK, that's right.
I think I jumped into that.
But I like the sound it makes.
We're getting this.
Get out of the way.
Who's opening the door?
Where's the sentry up? Sentry's almost gone.
Oh, there's a second one. Shit.
You know, it's over there.
I got it.
We're the same as how walls go fast.
Well, this is the door you're talking about.
Astrology.
Did you believe in astrology, girl?
Um, I mean, like stuff like Orion's Belt.
Like that, there's stars in the sky and that like the universe is real.
And there's like the universe is expanding and all that.
Oh, my goodness.
I lost him.
I had to pay attention to it.
I'm sorry. I had crits.
This is sentry over there.
OK. Astronomy or astrology?
Astrology.
You're talking about like, like,
ergo and like the Milky Way.
Um, all of that.
Um, I mean, I know we have like stars and planets and people gave them
certain names and certain like attributes.
I don't know.
Do you think they gave them bad names?
What do you mean, bad names?
I don't think they're bad.
OK. Yeah, wait, I think you're.
So you believe in astrology?
I think you're mixing up two things.
I'm not.
Astrology is Zodiac.
Astronomy is stars and shit.
Zodiac's the killer.
Liberty launcher.
How's it serving you?
I think it's fine.
I mean, I can't tell anything bad about it.
Oh, my goodness.
I didn't kill anybody.
Why did I do 100 damage to that guy?
The Liberty launcher sucks.
Oh, are you trying to get me to use like a weapon that's bad or something?
I don't think it's bad.
What's wrong with it?
Nothing. You trust me or you just a random guy in chat.
I mean, it's like 20,000 random people.
Where did that even where did he even shoot that from?
I'm going to start to like I'm going to start to walk forward
and then walk backwards and then walk forward again.
What what was what astrology sign are you?
Ergo, they're pretty compatible with Leo's.
Why is that you?
Is that what this is?
Is that where this is going?
Oh, right.
Would you look at that? OK.
Oh, hey, I'm going to get you.
Are you a healer?
I'm a sniper.
Sentry down. Cracked out.
Oh, oh, oh, my hand, my arm.
Oh, oh, my arm cramped up.
Oh, gaming hurts that playing video games hurts.
Dude, my arm is fucking cramped up, dude.
Hey, bro, my arm cramped up, bro.
That's why I just walked into the train.
Hey, bro, it's all good.
Don't worry. Don't worry, dude.
Motherfuckers, people.
Hey, bro.
This is fun. This game is fun.
I don't even know what you're screaming about.
Dude, I didn't hit the wall with the rocket.
You got a bunch of fucking gunk on your screen, OK?
Clean your screen.
What the fuck? No.
I don't walk away.
We've missed a few too many walk away time.
I can you do your best to theme song?
Ba ba ba ba da da da.
Get in, get in, get in, get in.
Get this is time. Time's time.
I'm coming. I'm coming.
I am with you. Yes, I am here.
60 points in like five minutes that's cool oh damn it we get this hey I moved
it pretty far yeah I got a couple points to tell me
oh that medic just looked up directly into the Sun what even happened he
grabbed his eyes he was like my eyes you have to focus German you have to focus
how do you expect to raise the family if you don't focus what we're doing this
we're doing somebody help me I have I have a power I have a magic power oh my
god what auto reload on I hate it it it actually distracts me I hate when it's
just constantly moving we're in just somebody touch it there's like nobody
there where's my team yeah yeah yeah yeah me we gotta leave the server okay
that was a good one that was intense that map that map that made me feel
something for once that was fun my blood was pumping my lungs were breathing air
I've been too loud today I feel like I'm like yelling a lot I'm yelling over the
gameplay I think you're good that's good all right what about the engineer
wrenches would they change it all probably oh boy he doesn't know wasn't
the Jag always like best in slot almost always that repair rate is yeah pretty
much repair it's pretty bad though Eureka effect will teleport to the exit now
the teleporter it's pretty cool everything's like subtly changed where
it kind of feels like it's the same thing and you just don't remember what
the right thing actually was that's yeah that's true um let me use the Sandman
Sandman is cool cuz you go like this no Sam is do not equip the Sandman what
what do you mean it does not stun anymore it slows and it reduces your
health by like 15 whoa that is not even close anymore you're right well that's
different is this I remember it from ancient times but I haven't played on
it yet we gotta leave it's over oh shit I'm gonna try dead ringer I'm gonna try
it oh we lost him I forget everything but it's alright big earner what is
there to know don't even go for a backstab just use your revolver and then
you're no die button he's doing dead ringer kunai cringe no I'm not I'm
looking that's kind of cool oh I love this thing yeah the the latranga cloak
duration that's huge it was a new sapper too wasn't there
rewinds um centuries right the red tape or I think that was in a long time ago
though now this is what I'm talking about I actually feel like I'm it's like
2014 right now like 2015 this is exactly what I was looking for
looking for some thunder boys you using the Liberty launcher you gotta use the
Liberty launcher oh wait no you're doing your spy thing oh this is important I
can't play this character unless I put this on right because then it's like
people will be like oh that guy probably doesn't know what he's doing I can't
there's two centuries on the skybox can you go sap those um maybe he's not even
moving he's no fear fuck shit I don't it's been I I don't even know man it's
been one week since you looked at me cocked your head to the side and said I'm
angry two days since you laughed at me how did you know the pain train I still
haven't looked at it you were actually a gibbous spy yeah I click hi yes I got a
you remember the fucking you understand I keep fucking walking out of spawn I'm
dead in one fucking second what does it crash what was that sound don't kill me
oh I don't even know how the map connects anymore I'm playing the map
knowledge class without remembering anything I got it right here I got a
sapper on it I'm gonna play it on defense yeah spy is not the class to
play how did he get the century up there what was that you see that you got a I
think you got a Wrangler jump the balance you got to try your hardest
right now German I need you okay well I'm on me team is it is not a balanced
game the enemy team is strong okay okay okay I need you to play your best class
um okay I need you confidently to walk out the spawn door and show me what
you're made of okay are you building real centuries no mini century that is
the real century I wish there was a button I could press they would make a
lawnmower sound effects I got that can you play them you just place lawnmower
play lawnmower sound effects over your mic right now if you can always sunny
that's the closest I got enemy team's cheating cheating every team's
cheating but they're not actually they're not lagging really bad enemy
team has ubered which is also cheating you ever seen an honest man who was
invulnerable okay it's fucking slice and dice time did I get a century widow
maker right yeah this is the one when you do damage you get ammo back right
this thing's pretty cool isn't it man that sure is a pyro that's a lot of
pyros bro kill someone we can't walk out our front door I'm an engineer he's
running he's running I have no ammo oh that's right you have to okay I forget
how this thing worked it shoots metal doesn't it not ammo yes okay all right
now I can contribute now I can help I can't hit that demo bro you made a
tutorial on this 12 years ago I don't know what's changed I don't know where
the spots are anymore I don't know what the fuck's going on you might as well
say my smite gameplay fucking tutorials are relevant to what are you gonna
return this might all right I'm concerned because this spy everywhere
yeah there's a spy everywhere all right I'm gonna hopefully watch your tutorial
you should what I have a dispenser down there I'm having a hard time getting the
angle I'm being denied the angle and everyone I see is is so incredibly laggy
laggy yeah everyone I go to sleep at is teleporting shitty got it okay
teleporter going up in I don't know this room here get out of here you still
alive yep nope are you friendly okay no this guy's friendly he can see he can
live for another five seconds somebody go through the teleporter police and
tell a friend I'm gonna be so funny I need to like build this don't do that oh
you're gonna get he's gonna get teleprags it's gonna say yeah that's how
it goes I think we're about to win we kind of are aren't we yeah we were we
were the mega loser team so something changed I don't know it's doing good
he's okay well take it you didn't do anything I teleported two people one
person I teleported went on to kill eight people in a row he was not up
there he was not at the front lines in that 10 to 20 seconds they could have
turned it around I don't think you guys understand how important engineers
really are on team fortress what are these clown pants I love these what what
is that wait you have one of you see the tank somebody was in a tank the soldier
was in a tank like a real one yeah I feel like we're playing the mobile game
version of team fortress right now they're not just playing team fortress
right now no I mean like we all have vehicles and it's like a go-kart game
that's just you it was a few of us what is the other isn't that's another
shotgun to you right oh I'm gonna go boost bonk bam Omsen I gotta look at all
these things before even committing to anything
Jesus so good this heavy wearing shorts who's bonk bam we're on it
whoa damn it I check couldn't pick it up fast enough whoa hello do you like or
dislike being tickled it depends on who's doing it
I mean you don't know it was your answer why are you even asking these
questions you've asked me like just as weird questions I am cracking out right
now somebody just said bro dude he wants you you fuck I want you to answer the
question some people like being tickled some people don't I don't it's a very
not really but humans can be tickled isn't that just fucking bizarre you know
you can't do it to yourself now I do yeah you're right yeah isn't the whole
thing weird so do you like it or not like it the whole yeah no I don't well
thing is weird hey you're being very evasive I want you to tickle yourself
right now see doesn't do anything just feels like yeah it's like hurts it hurts
it like hurts I'm like it's like ow that like isn't like painful it hurts me if I
can't ask stupid questions you can't have stupid answers isn't that the
point I want real and I thought the point of asking stupid questions was to
get stupid answer no I want to know your truth what about you I hate it I don't
like it I'm on team I don't like being tickled I don't understand why you
would like being tickled yeah like I was kind of hoping that you would be like a
tickle me guy no what happened to me what happened to me I'm playing pretty
well server just somebody said what constitutes a correct answer yeah I got
I don't know what he's looking for well you said the answer was the question was
do you like being tickled okay answer all right tickle yourself it hurt no
okay listen so there's a spy at spawn by the way okay if you're you know
hanging out and you're like girlfriends like oh okay we're like cuddling and
like oh I'd be oh that tickled right like that's fine well I got you on why
not that would piss you off yeah god damn it this fuck is okay I'm I'm
actually okay with that because that was a gibbous spy right on I'm glad you got
that kill I have a weird tickle spot that's why I hate it okay someone
touches my side I like spasm and freak out it's like not a tickle it's like a
like a I don't know it's beyond it's beyond tickle and Ashley says yeah I
know where it is smile she does my mom was also acutely aware of where it was
and she would torment me because like it's not like oh tickles it's like if
you just put a finger there I like I just freak out it really feels like my
in my internal organs do like a 180 like it's they all shift it is it's weird
somebody in all caps just said can we change the subject what do you mean
every person in your chat in the world has been tickled why can't we talk
about it we are extensively by the way does that a problem no I'm just laughing
because somebody said it in all caps okay change the subject what do you got
your ADD riddled brain is gonna just start talking about what spies in front
of you in like two seconds I can't hold a conversation with you for a minute
what else what other was what are you gonna switch the topic that was way
longer than a minute that was at least five minutes that's the first one today
because I was very persistent and now Chad's mad that I was persistent how big
do you want a pepperoni you just tickled me hey what the fuck big pepperonis
kind of creep me out actually true I agree with you on that one and I had
there's a there's a middle ground because I also had small pepperonis yeah
and they cook and they like curl up into like moon craters and they just house
every ounce of grease from the pizza cooking and it's just if you if I eat
like one or two of them I start feeling like I'm gonna die yeah too many
pepperonis is yeah I agree especially large pepperonis no I like the really
small ones because they fit on pizza really well I don't like when the entire
pizza looks like Kaled no I like when pepperonis they're small and to get it
at least a few in like every other bite but no no don't get don't turn that
shit into Kaled no thank you are you a fan of any type of pizza that does not
use like a mozzarella tomato sauce yeah like a white pizza yeah it can be good
what's your ultimate alternative pizza um oh let's go hold on this guy's
friendly uh I don't think there's very many other than that what's another like
alternative pizza that's like a not mozzarella not traditional hold on I'm
gonna think about this just just not like tomato sauce oh yeah barbecue
chickens pretty good I used to have one I can't remember what it was and I'm
really sad I'm gonna say it randomly and then I would just know that that's what
I like does buffalo chicken have red sauce on it I think sometimes it depends
on where you get it I mean the color isn't the relevant component oh I went
blind I think it was like a garlic piece yeah buffalo chicken pizza is great
anyway you get it stir looks cute you should compliment him stir apparently
you look cute right now is that true I don't I don't like the term cute for me
you know what I mean yeah I feel you I like things like if you call me big and
chunky and gigantic and huge that's way better that's I'm not a bass that's
better yeah oh you want to be called big and chunky and huge yes oh I mean I get
for like working out maybe I get it not even like working out here's the thing
because if you're like oh you're so cute I feel like it's kind of disingenuous
and it kind of just glosses over the reality so I'd rather someone
acknowledge the reality of like you're kind of fucking you're chunky man I'm
like that's that's really me and I I like me like I don't care I'm a little
you know but it's like you're acknowledging that about me and I'm
like yep it's real it feels real you ever just hang out in the pool with your
bros and measure your thighs I did recently I got really big thighs you
even take out a tape measure and no we had a third party what are you talking
about today you you measured your thighs like how big they are well no I had
someone feel my thighs and someone feel short for size and compare it's going
on right now do you want to change the subject again as everything that I'm
interested in just like not okay no it's fucking funny hey bro so I don't the new
armored corps coming out that seems cool I know I didn't tell you to stop get
away from let him cook yeah my chat says in the text to speech I'm looking like
an entire jar of just extra chunky peanut butter today and I loved it
unironically absolutely just lit my day up mr. Jerma is hyper focused so stir
has free reign right now I can do anything I want I mean I'm I'm doing
alright I'm just having fun it's fun to run around and spray people with the
fire flamethrower I cannot let you get away with that oh he has a healer now
if you put pyro vision on oh you should feel like pyro visions the original
developer intended route what is your favorite movie of all time um it's hard
to pick one you know everyone's always concerned about favorites through but
like don't they all have like their own purpose and their own little spot in
your heart yeah your own little baby boo-boos like I want to watch this one
blah or I'd like this one for me yeah that's fair get out of here that I have
like the shortest memory possible for it and I forget movies that I like every
time I'm asked that question or like there's all the time where a movie will
come up I'm like oh yeah I do love that movie a lot can't remember it or like if
I'm just on the spot I think a lot of movies have come out so it's really easy
to kind of forget some of them even if you really like them yeah how spoiled
this I've had this thought many times how spoiled are we when we're all like
I'm so sad and I'm so bored and like I can't even remember all of the great
media that I love in a single moment I can't even sit here and be like what
movie do I like I don't fucking I got it's too hard to tell you all of the
things that are awesome how many games are on Steam I look this upward like
very recently what is it like 10,000 so you would have to play but that might be
outdated from like you would have to play like 30 games a day until you were
dead into if you couldn't play them all why do you want me to die I'm just
saying there's 50k now yeah I think that the number I saw was like 2018 or
something over 700,000 games I like bad movies that chattel disagree with me on
like mother I think mother was an awesome movie mother mother I never saw
I watched mother with you I love that movie all right let's go movie night
let's do it and if anyone who knows the movie the guy bouncing on the the
kitchen counter and she's like come on get off the counter that's like YouTube
comments to me at that point in my life I was like this guy's a YouTube commenter
Birdman you seen Birdman I have yeah it's great great movie come on we do it
again we can do another fucking movie four more movies in a row all these
idiots all these morons don't know what we're really capable of doing movies
about me I am Birdman you are Birdman I don't like there I don't like the ending
I had can in a different ending and they did rewrite the ending like we're
leaving right we're leaving yeah I just think Birdman is one of those movies
that the style of trying to shoot something pretending that it's all
essentially happening in a row even if it's not happening it still takes a lot
to get that to happen and make any sense it's like a great piece of cinema it's
very good it's it is like what I would describe for like a true movie like this
is a real movie this is a piece of cinema hidden cuts yeah that's fine
though there are at least a few times when Michael Keaton's walking around
going from space to space without a cut that even let me tell you something
coming from the YouTube world where you have to go like this you know what I
mean think about like the like all the YouTube videos ever seen and like I've
done this I do this all time this shit where it's like hey everybody welcome to
hey yeah we're back and here's another cut and oh and I fucked that up do it
again so at the end of the day the most important thing is to make sure that as
we go forward as a species we should always drink water right like it's almost
it's hard to actually go in the first half and we should drink water is where
I picked up as a species yes we should always drink water I agree yes but my
point is is that the youtuber shit where we cut every five to twelve seconds
because we don't remember what we're gonna say what's wrong with that it's
I'm just saying it's hard it's hard to go right in a row you know who does this
really well you know let me tell you something me no oh damn well you know
actually I think you're pretty good at this too but you know who's really
really good at this you one take is so fucking good at this and I don't even
know how the fuck he does it is Ludwig Ludwig will do like a 20 minute video
where he does not miss a single beat not a single beat and it's all one take I
don't even know how he does it it's actually a talent it's truly is and he
it's not like he's stopping he is full-on explaining something talking
addressing the camera it's fucking crazy what he does he can do it in one take
you probably would like Ludwig you guys should meet you you probably like them
versus sax and Hale yes no yeah why not let's try it well I think we have to
wait for this round done I will try to do that and I'll get like 30 seconds in
and be like fuck me and have to start the whole thing over again all if I do
it I feel like the video would be better if I didn't do it yeah but you do it
anyways you start over anyways there's been a couple times right like start
over multiple times and then I feel like I get one take because I've just said it
like eight times in a row yeah but even then I still think it would just like
why not cut why not cut like a second or two of dead space and that like you
know and also too if you'd go through one thing in one take there's a huge
possibility that you somewhere in that like five straight minutes you said
something that wasn't correct and it's like god damn it you left yeah okay
I realized it in one place sax and Hale. I love that was your idea and you're like nah never mind
well it put us in there and then you know but like getting something wrong in
the middle of a commentary like that or a talking like that then you you watch
it back and like wow I did pretty good job one take oh the thing I said at two
minutes is completely fucking wrong now what do I do just take a little cut and
put it in there and leave the rest or is that weird I mean is he I haven't seen
his videos is he full on camera 100% of the video or does like yeah it's so
he'll do like mobile mails or does something go over him where he can do
like a fake cut no I don't think so I think he just does it he just goes for
it man what a legend stop trying to make your boss sound good dude he is good he
is good what do you want to pretend he's not that's weird that's weirder that's
weirder for me to pretend that he's not I mean he I would say I think he is the
most attractive youtuber here we go again you cute us right yeah we're cute
all right good uh did you did you have a favorite movie you want to toss your
hat in gremlins 2 I'm about I'm hovering over the leave game I just I'm
threatening to leave the game explain why you just left I'll click it it's a
mixture of like shocking wow gremlins 2 is his favorite movie but then also like
it's funny cuz it fits yeah I feel like if you had the opportunity to have a pet
mug why you would gremlinify it because you think the gremlins are cuter he
gets it if you if you think that the gremlins are cute is that is that
appropriate I just think okay the gremlins to me are looney toons
characters they go from being these like cute little oh it's such a cute little
like kitten it's a cute little puppy to turning into a looney toons daffy duck
character I mean I like the looney toons daffy duck character more than
the like cute one I find that to be more interesting to me exactly full circle
that's why I don't want to be called cute and I'd rather be called a full tub
of jiff extra chunky peanut butter I feel it I'm gonna do you want to be the
cute gremlin or you want to be the cool gremlin I want to be the gremlin that
talks because that's the best one the one that sings New York New York I
disagree completely oh you would want you would be the vegetable one wouldn't
you oh my I don't like it when there's a show where one Pokemon Meowth in the
whole world learns how to talk no but it's not that way have you seen
gremlins to probably like 30 years ago before I was born okay he didn't learn
how to talk he drank a fucking potion in a weird lab that gave that grew his
brain it that he didn't learn how to talk he drank a potion that made him
smarter and there was only one potion to drink of course there was only one
potion to drink oh my goodness that's a lot of people yes it is oh he went rage
heavy that just like hurt dude you need to get that potion I think I'm I think
I'm just fine I need help I'm abandoning the point winning right now they can cap
the last point like this is steel and they're just straight doing it and no
one is they just capped it this is gonna be awkward this is awkward oh shit
this is kind of awkward possible to win I have never seen it happen hey that's a
challenge then just one if they got D where you're at I got a crits I'm on the
point oh hey Frank hello do it you ready oh right at the end they're nice all
right it's a time to get out there I what happened what's going on what did
you just stop talking something's broken on my stream and it is doubling text to
speeches so I had to go drown myself and they pointed out the me out with lore
what's the me out floor that we I think me out learn to talk so you could
impress a girl really that's apparently that's all it takes all right we get
we're gonna get on a point or something oh shit behind us this is bad two scouts
this is bad I'm we're in trouble here oh my lord no no no no I gotta abandon
you I'm sorry help me help me heavy heavy help help help help help oh shit
guys if this guy's a okay he's got an awesome outfit though all the crits
create on I forgot that's right what was that cute little duck sound do you still
have any unusuals or did you get rid of those on yours I gave them all the tip
hats for the keys what is considered the the unusual now like what is like the
best one now any idea no clue I have never had any comprehension of the
unusual market after it like like ancient times it was like the green flame
and then once they started adding more I had no idea anymore people are still
saying ones yeah burning team captain oh okay I guess I still know damn really
even after all the updates no no new one is come on crates are rarer because
they're old it's true it's rare okay do you want it right when the door opens or
oh we're doing a Frank the fish are we hey let's do this let me know okay I'll
wait for you spawn hey it's me behind you I'm right behind you right behind me
mm-hmm he did he did it again yeah he did do it again I'm not pyro this time I
can't focus on it I fell you got you got a couple yeah I thought we get more but
I was nervous there's a lot of pyros I think it was still worth it yeah look at
the momentum that we're driving for our team right now oh he's the real power
it's me again hi there's a lot of people in this area by behind spy behind demo
right here there's way too I'm fucking running back spawn dude there's a
century in the water at our spawn what I got it
oh yeah they can't shoot out of the water so they only kill desperate losers
like me oh shit this is bad this is really bad I got stuck in the fucking
water help heal me medic help died help medic medic medic medic medic dude the
Liberty launcher is insane I don't even have to worry about it getting
reflected because it won't do any damage so is that is it bad and you that's the
thing what do you I feel like you're tearing in two different directions
there I believe in it I'm a believer I think it was no one believes in it it
does a lot less damage but someone at long range it scales down to 18 damage
oh that's why I was doing like 30 damage right yes oh this is scary there's a lot
of stickies here yes there is I'm not going over there yeah let's go on the
left side left side let's do this left side let's go left I have one make sure
you got full rockets it's dangerous I'm not playing pyro that's my class what
the hell am I doing sure mother there was a demo man in the water why am I
getting the receiving end of all this nonsense I changed class by the way yeah
you better I'm going I'm going whatever mode I'm going I'm going in fuck I don't
think it should be this hard to leave spawn yes accidental taunt cancel is
that what I did mouse plus W yeah well sometimes you have to they're the pyro
character someone said flog does not deserve hog log hog wow oh my oh my oh
my vlog this is all your fault I don't think it is considering I have you
needed I think you more point on medic I have more points than you okay that's my
game running like 30 FPS why is that is a good question I don't know I don't
think we it was only me knew that we're able to touch the point for like a
millisecond 64 gigs of RAM can't handle it leave so tell me how good how late are
you going how how much you like how much team fortress is enough for this addict
I think like another hour I'm having fun are you trying to get going I want to be
with you okay so let's keep playing I want a good engineer around a really
good one won't happen sorry man pyros fun this dragons this is what you said
you're using you like it the dragon's fury oh yeah oh yeah no more stamina I
did work out very early this morning long day get up early um 7 a.m. 10 a.m.
now or 10 p.m. now first chat for a streamer oof that's true that's pretty
early for a live streamer I'm going up Ireland by the way okay um oh wait you
don't need the goggles why is gremlin 2 better than gremlins 1 gremlins 1 is
kind of a horror movie it's not really like a comedy it's sort of a oh I
remember okay because they did the gremlins do they like take over the TV
station they're all goofing around yeah Hulk Hogan's in it I like them both I
think they both really good just like second better comedy horror yeah the
second one is like full Looney Tunes though this pyro land to work in here no
but I'll keep the blower on why not I'm gonna play get pirate spy I'm gonna
ever played this map really this was like every single server one contract
came out oh no yeah okay I had to see outsider you know what I'm gonna be the
dead ringer guy when I die I'm just gonna play spy as a scout with a revolver
and just be immune to dying smart what is there somebody in the water so you're
okay you're going for it let's see it Wow dead ringer wins it did you actually
just do that no I just spawned and didn't get to do anything yet there you
go oh jeez love what does the happy camper on
sniper do these days no no lynching and yeah you get healed that's the big thing
you get healed for health every couple seconds I think pretty damn good shit
adjust your view model so we can see the goddamn game that's cuz I'm using the
rainbow thing I like it big same yeah I like it this games about to be over in
like two seconds are you all the way back there no I just feel like we're
rolling I'm just this is just bubbles everywhere guys running all over the
place we re queuing or what are you relieving can we do can we do one or
two on bunker hill no you haven't even done cell bling yet which one do you
like out of all them so everyone's gonna want you to experience saving okay
let's do it it's like the map from the update and I'm shocked it hasn't I even
tried to queue into it exclusively before I wasn't doing it I typically
always get it didn't they nerf the pumps and lay into the ground at one point I
guess I don't even remember what that thing does we play different I'm not an
engineer you really don't play it right and I don't play engineer I don't play
your your your spy very much your your medic so this is the one that when you
hit somebody with it the medic will lose up to ten percent in Medigun charge
really doesn't seem that bad I don't remember it having the on-hit victim
loses cloak it feels new but again I would not remember I'll try the short
circuit so now it's actually a projectile is not like electricity that
comes out of your hand so alt fire just what is the regular fire do anything
you know it still is electricity okay bro this is the worst loadout I could
possibly have well let's try to make it work why not what's your secondary
Thompson short-circuit and the Jag is that the worst possible engineer load
up I don't know the Jag seems intelligent that's wrong I could put on
the Eureka effect put on the Wrangler what is so bad about this actually it
looks like they buff the Eureka effect all like a lot I remember just being
kind of quirky that's your reload key to choose to teleport to spawn or your exit
teleporter minus 50% metal cost when constructing or upgrading oh that's
actually kind of good guys we can't get a cell blown in server they just don't
exist I'll try it don't use the pumps and you'd be better off turning your
monitor off and playing the game with your face Wow why they're doubting you
they are you can handle it they are doubting big-time yeah what did you
kiss you I'm trying to get us in the sale begin there we go I'm gonna I'm
gonna go get like a water after this my voice is like drying up I feel like I'm
gonna cough dust out in a second hmm so this maps is this maps a little bit
different this is a little bit of a mixture of Call of Duty's kill confirmed
with a zoo okay so what you're gonna want to do is you're gonna kill enemy
players and pick up fish but and then when the seal appears you want to feed
the seal the fish you collect okay I'm gonna play something else you already
gave up just not engineer I don't know what the hell's going on Wow so get
kills pick up seals pick up fish feed the fish to the seal okay and if you are
the leader if you hold the most fish then you will um you become a dispenser
effect for your team and the enemy team can like see where you are through wall
oh at the bottom left it'll if maybe I don't know your HUD if you see like a
random floating number those are people who have the fish I like that little
truck oh our seal is swimming around it's everybody's seal everybody needs to
feed the seal oh and the seal is an eldritch old god and it favors whichever
team feeds it more and then it banishes the other team from this mortal coil
which is the only part I've made up but it's the only reason why we'd be feeding the
seal and fighting over it oh shit no the medic was still there I don't get it at
all but I think I after a round or two I'll get it oh yeah it really is just
like it's not you'll see because the seal isn't always active so like right
now he's doing three two one seal feed the seal so that guy's 20th okay I get
it yeah yep yep you got to kill that guy and get that guy's fish because he's
feeding the fish pretty hard right now oh shit spy we're all the way back to the
spawn kind of well you got to feed this thing oh there we go who's got the most
fish it's by as by I got a banner I got a banner dude come on I feel like every
time I'm about to do click a good thing I get backstabbed every time maybe you
should look behind you I did maybe you should dude maybe you shouldn't be
streaming what the fuck that's a fucking spy right there guarantee it yeah he's
still alive he's not you don't he's he's like writer you see the guy with 11 you
gotta get these 11 oh my god I'm just gonna play pyro never change ever I feel
like I get I get I can play the game if I play pyro ooh this is cool okay we
gotta feed the steel steel time he comes out of the van seals and you have
to play the objective I'm surprised I didn't get that but I stopped spinning
so angry I got him okay how did they nerf the dead ringer when this shit
fucking disciplinary action whips you out of the danger zone how is that nerf
sounds like a skill issue to me well I'm using it right now that's how I noticed
insane it actually uh heavy is probably the worst possible thing to do but I'm
gonna do it give me that snack all right do I think I have it damn he got me Wow
I thought there's gonna be a spy right behind me there is turn around don't do
that I really thought you were serious I did see one what is going on I'm bad
focus just aim just actually aim that's a lot of fish there's no way wait drop
an item I think I'm safe I'm so not used to being able to feign death and cheat
life itself but I didn't do it oh I keep forgetting that I'm allowed to cheat I
think the sniper is the spy but it's this guy get out of here we good this
guy's got 29 holy shit
what is wrong with you we did it we're having a crisis you're having a meltdown
I keep getting killed by spies hey we did pretty good that was a good round we
won yeah I'd say pretty good is what you say when you lose but we actually won I
like in a spy I'm forgetting that I'm allowed to cheat death and and I keep
dying you're one of these people is a spy I'm certain of it hmm I think we
might need a little bit if I kind of need to see how bad the ambassador is now
for myself isn't the default revolver like it's really good it's it's pretty
good but it gets like random bullets spread after a shot and I just want to
aim it ahead god damn it 14 fishes all right this is where the fuck is that
spy knew it I knew I was like where the fuck did he go I don't want to do I
think I'm yeah I'm going for it I'm just gonna play it with the is a
teleporter evenness probably yeah not really not really on this map it helps
but it's not the most important thing on kind of close what's really important
is feeding this seal I guess I'll play pyro yay I was gonna tape my fucking
left mouse button down I'm bad at it I am bad at this one I didn't want to do
that give me a fucking break it's so not worth it I believe everyone okay let's
try this damn oh that makes you take crits I forgot right does it oh yeah you
get right you take many crits too that's right let me put this away I'll do fish
I'll try it I'm already fucking dead uh what do we need right now we need you
to step it up I'm trying I mean the game's pretty even we don't really
specifically need anything hey I almost killed me okay is good at sniping give
me those fishes see I'm gonna go on another run a dungeon run dude that's
some pretty nasty thunder I was like what the fuck is that sound that was
some pretty bad thunder yeah yeah in real life I saw a flash out my fucking
I was like what the hell is that and then the thunder rolled in that's why I
don't stop playing how often do you get like storms in Vegas um it happens
pretty frequently especially in summertime not a lot of rain but we'll
get like some pretty nasty lightning stuff the big eye thing finally awoke
that's enough fish can never have enough fish the Vegas I oh that's scary
over there I love the Vegas I whoa nice what's happening what's happening I
don't know and of course the fucking spy is the one that kills me out of all that
out of all that horseshit the spy is the one that gets me oh shit did you hear
that oh dude that was like holy shit if the stream turns off then well I'll see
you later bye bye this was really fun though I had a great time I love this
game it's fun yeah see you were like I don't know I got a like maybe play view
finder it catches it catches on you get into the groove before you know it 16
hours have gone by that's very true your health your job and your wife I don't
want to get random crit I'm gonna get this guy I'm gonna get this guy boy you
have a healer you really just let me walk this map is so laggy for me
sometimes too I don't know if you like feel that I I'm sorry this is I have a
lot of distractions over here right now this is like this is the loudest fucking
oh there oh my god all right my stream just turned off my stream literally just
it just blinked my whole my computer blinked oh you should probably go all
right see you later goodbye thanks everybody for watching I actually gonna
get the fuck out here before this gets worse my screen actually turned off for
like two seconds all right one more kill one more kill one more kill I'll be good
you gotta do one more life dude alright get out of here all right yeah see you
later buddy Mike I'm actually probably gonna lose
power in like a minute or two you keep saying that I don't know that we got you
that last one power that last one was fucking nuts my I'm telling Mike how many
kills as you can before the power goes out holy shit can you hear this you have
to be able to hear that right I don't hear it I think you're I think it's
dementia Wow whoa what the fuck this is crazy what on earth okay I heard that a
little bit can you go can you go like hold your mic outside whoa holy shit
all right yeah I gotta go see you later goodbye it was fine we should do it
again sometime mr. thanks for hanging up yeah have a great rest of your night
everybody TF2 I had a great time it's fun to play it again for sure thanks
stir for playing I'll talk to you soon love stir everybody loves stir come on I
mean I love the idea of stir but stir is just actually okay sir is what's wrong
with stir he's chunky he's yeah it is actually I don't know why I like it that
much all right I'm gonna get out of here before my computer turns off take care
all right thanks dude peace out friend all right yeah we plan on probably
stopping around now anyways team fortress though I feel like there was a few good
games there I'm not playing for a long time all right the next time I play it
I'll play it again maybe we'll open some crates and chill and play it maybe the
next time next stream is probably going to be damn this is fucking crazy next
streams are we gonna be on Wednesday or Thursday I'll let you know keep an eye
on this us and see you later take care have a great night and goodbye call your
brother