Hey, what is going on, everybody?
Jerma here, wait a second, Otto, you have to make your camera debut.
Jerma and Otto, and there's actually somebody else in this call, go ahead and introduce yourself.
Hi.
Who's that?
It's Boo.
But yes, Otto wanted to say hello, because you haven't had a checkup with Otto in a while, he's doing okay.
See, he's got a good face, he's got a good white stripe, he's a good dog.
He was actually lying down right here for a while.
But yeah, Space Game Fortress 2, this is Monday's edition.
Hope you're having a fantastic Monday.
I'm just like standing still, like oh, let me like talk for like five minutes, just not play.
I have no idea who I killed, but they're dead.
So Otto wanted to get down, he's down there now, and oh my god, what just even killed me, I don't even know.
I don't even know.
But we're on offense now.
We are on the offense.
And I changed what I was using.
I want to get my scarcely lethal...
I think that's what it is.
Scarcely lethal...
Why can't I not even think of the name of this weapon?
The Liberty Launcher.
Scarcely lethal gun.
No!
Hide.
Watch the dead ring spy behind us.
Oh god, really?
No, he's a scout.
No, I got him.
Oh, is he truly dead though?
Yeah, I got a new rank on my pistol for it.
That's one way to tell.
Oh, how did I not kill him?
Very, very good.
Is that actually like a spy check, or does it fake that to be your new rank on your weapon?
I don't think it would fake that.
That's something I would...
That would be very weird if it did.
The spy is up top right here.
Oh, I see him.
I think he's dead, I don't know.
No, he's not.
He's actually like stuffed in this corner over here with me.
And he got the health too, that prickly bastard.
Hey, there's a spy here.
Watch it.
Oh, I just picked up the ammo.
I'm sorry, dude.
That guy's an energy.
I got him.
You got him?
Yep.
Okay, good.
I'm gonna go put a tele-exit upstairs.
Oh, we are absolutely rolling right now.
All right, black box soldier coming from the upstairs.
Ooh, really?
You know what?
You die.
We have a friendly spy crabbing out of spawn, making his way through the field.
Oh wait, we have a wild spy crab?
Really?
I didn't know we had a wild spy crab.
That makes me happy.
All right, let's push this car.
Nobody here.
Oh, this is a heavy...
I want to go back and just shoot that guy.
He probably has no health.
But there's nobody here.
Where is everybody?
Oh my word.
Where's the sentry?
Where's that sentry gun?
Is it up top behind everybody?
I don't see it.
It must be up on the corridor.
Hmm.
What does this take?
I swear, that sentry is up here somewhere.
Maybe I'm just crazy and it was a heavy behind me or something.
No, it's definitely up here.
They have a teleport.
They're all kinds of guys.
They got a lot of things up here.
Oh boy.
Oh my God.
Screw the spy.
We got to take this stuff out.
No!
Liberty launcher, this is not the good place for you.
Oh, I got one sentry.
Oh my God.
Damn.
Oh, we got to...
Just trying to wall bang this guy.
Come on.
No, I got the other sentry.
Oh, you got him.
I got the engie.
I got it.
Oh, spy.
Both of them down.
Both sentry down, though.
Two spies up there.
Oh, there's a guy disguised as me.
Doctor...
If you see a demo man.
What was that guy's name?
Doctor Octo...
Octomagopus?
Rocket jump.
Right on top of the health.
That was my plan.
Grabby.
Oh, watch out.
That medic.
Where are you going?
Oh man, that medic just backed up into hell.
Oh, you bastard.
Possibly a spy disguised as me, a demo man.
Okay.
Oh, there's a spy disguised as a soldier.
What?
What the...
All right, I want everyone to go back and watch that.
That guy, he was reloading.
And it looked like he was putting his hand down on the dispenser to sap it.
That was one of the oddest things I've ever seen.
Oh, you stupid spy.
You are not dead.
That was ridiculous.
Man, we got to get a push here.
We're just stuck in the alleyways.
Anything else?
Get rid of all this garbage here.
Heavy medic and a pyro coming as well through the tunnel.
I got the pyro.
Oh, a spy.
Man, they don't really have anything here, do they?
It just dropped down.
Get on this cot, get on this cot.
Push it, baby, push it.
You've got to push it.
Heavy medic and pyro on the bridge.
That medic is insane.
What's he doing?
Nothing I could do there.
I got one kill.
It's almost there.
Are we going to close it?
Oh, no, I'm out of coffee.
Four and a half minutes.
We got this, boo.
Center's gone down.
I'll change from demo.
Oh, my phone's ringing.
My phone's always just ringing.
It's either Burger Boy or like Mama Germ.
Where are you going?
I'm just going to club this guy right in the face.
I kind of did.
We're going to get it.
This is it.
Oh, don't uber me on the cart.
Nice.
Nice job, team.
Good job, dudes.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, that's going to wrap it up here for Facecam Fortress 2, Monday's edition.
Boo, thanks for joining me.
I'm looking at the camera.
I don't even know where I'm looking.
But thanks for joining me, boo.
Always a pleasure.
And thanks, everyone else, for joining me as well.
And boo.
So see you guys the next time.
And of course, take care, everybody.
Bye bye.
Where's Otto?
Otto, you have to say bye.
Otto, come here.
He was just like...
Oh, I just...
Otto, I'm sorry.
Goodbye, everybody.
Thanks for watching Facecam Fortress 2.
My name is Otto.
Look, look at how tired he is.