Alright, hello. Did we lose Ster? Ster's gone. He left. Oh no, he's not, he's here.
So for 12 months, way back when when you were allowed to do that as a channel.
Are you sticking around?
Yeah, I got guilted by my mom. My mom said don't stop playing video games right now.
Keep playing games. And now I have to keep playing games because my mom told me to.
You know what? It's such a... I feel like that could be true.
It is. It is 100% true. Okay.
My mom and my wife teamed up to guilt me into playing a game.
Because she's just like you, one of her favorite games is House Flipper.
She's put a ton of hours into it. She loves watching the Jerma House Flipper streams.
You ask her what her favorite stream or video is of her son, she'll say Jerma's House Flipper.
What, what incredible taste. I just have to say, seriously.
And then she says your welcome chat, but it's your, not apostrophe, you are.
She's just...
What about you are?
All right. How do we, how do we play this game?
Are we loading it up right now?
We're going to open it.
You guys don't even know.
Hope it's not loud. Hope it's not loud. Hope it's not loud.
Prepare for loud game. Hold on.
Oh, I'm going to mute just in case.
It might be loud. Star's going to be getting, Star's getting grumpy.
What's your favorite food?
Now, like at this point.
Yeah. Uh, hold on, hold on, hold on. Um, what is it? Is this a, is this like a joke?
No, no, no. Like the, okay, the opening page.
I don't even want to show this.
No, it's like a person's phone number.
Thank you for playing our early access.
By the way, if you want to like call this person, that's like the CEO of the, wow.
I don't, I, I, this might be fake. Is this part of the game?
No, no. Fuck that.
All right. No. All right. I would still, how do we play together?
Start game. Hold on. Progress report a bug. Remove is split input.
All right. I'm going to go start game.
How do we play this together? Anybody? Do we have any idea?
Well, hold on. I think you have to do the tutorial.
You'll be all right. You're going to be fine.
See, we've, do you believe that?
Well, then that contradicts what you just said.
Okay. So I don't know if it's like, no, dude, I'm serious.
At talks, it shows like a guy's phone number.
Oh man, guys. Hold on. You guys have been muted this whole time.
I'm so sorry. He's all right.
That's okay. I wasn't even talking.
I muted you for most of that time.
Okay. Fuck. I was muted the whole time. God damn it.
Okay. I'm going to call this guy and I'm going to do that.
Hey, do we have to play the tutorial first?
Yes. Just do it.
No, I'm going to ask him.
Oh my fucking God.
I'm just going to play the game and we'll, we'll kill them in a minute.
To craft new track pieces, you need wood and iron.
Grab region is plus 49.
Stop, stop it.
Dude, anyone who wants this can just buy the game.
Oh, it's Germany.
All right. You have to chop down wood.
What time is it in Germany? It's late.
I think we'd, yeah, we're doing the tutorial.
It's too late. I'm not calling them.
It's going to go to his answering.
Yeah. It's probably like five 30 there.
He's probably asleep.
No, it's 2 a.m. They're saying, I mean, I'll tell you, you gotta,
you gotta have some like iron, iron body to put your personal telephone
number at the splash screen of your video game.
It probably goes to like a Hulk Hogan fake answering machine.
It probably does.
Okay. So what am I doing?
What do I do? Start game?
But how do we play? I gotta call this guy.
Just do the tutorial.
Is that when you click start game?
Yeah, just yes.
Yes. All right. So you put both.
Holy shit. This is going to be insanely difficult.
Is it?
I think so.
Okay. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
This is on Twitch yet.
What's it called? Unrailed.
Unrailed. Okay.
It is. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
What are we holding up for?
Can you do me a favor?
Yeah. What is it?
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
I don't know how to bring that screen back up again.
It doesn't do it if you reopen the game.
All right. I'm going to be I want to be the first one to finish the tutorial
so I can see how smart I am.
I don't think he is.
His phone number lost to me.
It really doesn't show it again if you don't.
That's like I don't know how to bring it back up.
Oh, I got it.
The train overheats over time and will start to burn.
Build a bridge to the bucket and fill it with the river.
Nobody tell him.
How the hell are we going to do this together?
We've got like sleepy star on the call.
You think he's going to want to do this?
How do I do a plus on the phone?
It says zero is a plus.
Done it.
Tutorial done. I win.
Well, I didn't know.
I'm the smartest gamer.
I didn't even know it was a competition until you said it.
You could have been speed running it.
Okay. There we go.
Online game.
Yeah.
All right. Do we know how this...
Is this just through Steam or what?
That is a good question.
Create private lobby.
Might want to hide your...
What the hell are you doing?
Fucked up.
Are you trying to call this person?
That's the way he wrote it.
But then it says that's not how you do it.
You can't call from the United States.
You can.
Two tur...
No, you can't.
You can just sit...
Best case scenario.
He answers.
He goes, hi, how are you?
And you go, hi, I'm streaming your game right now.
He tunes in.
Then you insult him and like say his game sucks.
And you personally call him to like make fun of him.
You have to do like star something something.
You can't just call the number.
No, no, no.
See, because it's plus 49 for Germany.
And then it has parentheses zero.
You gotta do something before that.
What it just said is not to do the parentheses zero.
But that's the way he wrote it.
Plus that call is going to cost you like $60 a minute.
Guys, I'm...
I can't.
I'm making Jerma very uncomfortable.
Like I just wanted to have a conversation about his game with other people.
And Jerma said, you know what?
I have...
I have a session.
Are you done with the tutorial?
I see.
And it's people like you is why we're never going to find Hillary's emails.
What do I do in this tutorial?
Well, I could try moving your character.
Oh, you motherfucker.
I was calling him.
I was busy.
You were trying to call a person that you don't know's random telephone number
for a laugh out loud.
Fucking look what I'm doing on the stream.
I'm going to call this guy.
And even moved your character on the screen.
I didn't even...
I just got in the game.
Oh, my God.
All right.
What are the buttons?
How do I join you?
You have to give me your session ID.
I have a session ID.
I'm about to give it to you.
I'm going to put it into the chat.
Star, don't leak this.
That's the session ID.
He wants people to call him, though.
It's different.
Yeah, if there's like a bug or something, you're just going to...
What's the purpose of your call?
I was going to ask if we had to do the tutorial before we play together.
You're our speakerphone on my stream.
Okay.
What do you want?
Just hang up.
Do you honestly think that's the worst call he would have ever done?
No.
Excuse me, sir.
I'm showing interest in your indie game.
I know you worked really hard on it, but I'd rather not talk to you
and not share it with anyone.
Fine.
Tal, do you have 466 ping right now?
Why?
Grab some wood.
Jerma, where's the wood?
Why is this ping so high?
The wood...
If you chalk down...
Have you ever played a video game that's come out in the last 10 years?
You have to get wood from the tree.
Is there action we're not seeing?
Yeah, there is.
But the session ID is on the screen, so I can't show it.
I don't know how to do this.
How do you make the rail?
Oh, wait.
Did the Talix show the session ID?
What did that tutorial message just say?
I'm out.
I almost got it.
I left the call.
Not the call.
I left the lobby.
Okay, Star, you have to host this lobby because we're on like...
You have to host this.
My train's on fire.
Yes, go get the bucket.
Stand next to the water and let it fill and then walk over to the left and pour it.
Oh, okay.
Remember when you wanted me to play and my mom wanted me to play?
Changing diapers here.
Isn't that weird?
Oops, was I muted?
Oh, I was.
You leaked us.
I know, but it doesn't matter because he's not even done with the tutorial anyway.
Make sure you put your region to US West, by the way.
I have to do that?
Yeah, go to online and then go to region US West and select it.
What if I did Korea?
Then it would be very bad because you would be relaying through entire continents.
Okay, how do I join you?
Or do I need to call the guy?
You're going to hit a BRB screen or black out your screen.
You're going to go to create private lobby.
Okay.
There's going to be a seed in the top left.
Don't tell anybody else that seed.
That's just for me to tell us.
Wouldn't it be cool if like a hundred people joined though?
This game can only have like five...
I think there's only four people.
All right, and then you're going to just type into the chat.
Make sure you're US West in your region.
And you're going to type into the discord chat with the three of us in here.
And that five digit seed session ID.
Hold on.
My game like froze.
What the fuck is happening?
Are you...
Did you click on session ID and it's got a little cursor and you have to press escape?
I'm focusing.
Okay.
And now I...
Do I start the game or do I give this to you first?
Just wait to...
Don't hit start yet.
Just give...
It is definitely not poo poo.
It's definitely not...
That's not the password.
That is what it is.
Because I know it's not special.
It is.
Hang on.
Are we sure?
I don't know.
I don't know if that's real.
I actually had to look on Steam to check to see if he even installed the game.
I wondered if this was just a bruise.
But yeah, he is in fact in the game on Steam.
He's in his poo poo lobby.
Okay.
Let's go.
Yeah, we have to...
Is that how that works?
I'm going to join your lobby.
Session ID.
Oh, wait.
No, you want session ID?
Yes.
You just made a custom seed.
Okay, cool.
I thought I was...
No, make sure you're not showing this to anybody.
I'm not.
Why would I do that?
Okay.
I can't get off of the typing.
There we go.
Now don't...
Game mode.
Difficulty.
Enable checkpoints.
Who would leak such a thing?
Do not allow random players to join.
Are we good?
Difficulty?
Don't put it on medium.
Don't put it on hard.
There's no way we're going to do that.
We're idiots.
And game mode endless.
Why would we not do game mode like normal?
Well, isn't endless the normal?
I guess it is normal.
All right.
Endless is like see how far you can get before you crash.
You ready?
Let's go.
With checkpoints enabled,
you can restart at the first station in each biome after you crash.
All right.
Are we ready to start streaming this game?
Do not show up on the leaderboard.
Hurry up.
I showed it.
So everyone come stand up here.
You have to all stand here.
I think I showed it.
I definitely showed it.
You showed it.
Let's go.
It was an accident.
I thought we were starting.
He showed it.
Okay.
If you guys actually have this game, call that number.
Tell me what happened.
Okay.
Let's go.
We got to kill the creepers.
The Enderman.
We got to build a train track and we got to dig a path for it straight ahead.
So go directly in front.
The train is already moving.
Yeah, it's moving.
All right.
We're making train tracks.
Yeah.
This is endless.
This is stressful.
All right.
So we ain't seen nothing yet.
What is this bucket?
What's the bucket?
You did the tutorial.
No, I know.
But what's the water?
Water, water, water, water, water, water.
I got to make another mine.
We need track.
We need wood.
But there's no footies.
Wait, wait, wait.
I got to go up.
You got to dig up.
Who is this person?
The person is hitting me.
We're dead.
All right.
Get out.
Where is it?
I can't move.
You have somebody to break me out.
We got trees.
We need that pickaxe so we can actually...
You guys can't get over here.
Oh my God.
You just made a turn.
No, no, no, no, no.
Okay.
How do we get water?
Water, water, water, water, water, water, water, water, water.
We got to get a crossing.
We're killing the creepers.
Where's the pickaxe?
I got it.
What?
Put wood in the thing.
Put wood in it.
There's no wood.
I'm chopping the trees.
Come get the wood.
All right.
I need one piece of wood to build a bridge.
Not a space.
No, no, no, no, no.
What is that?
Why is this a mini?
How do I...
No, this way.
Right here.
This is just grass.
Okay.
So we can go over that.
Should we go right?
No, go straight.
I cleared a path already.
It goes all the way up to here.
Oh, okay.
Where's the axe?
I got it.
We need more wood.
All right, wood behind me.
Fire, fire.
It's about to die.
It's over.
It's going to crash, it's going to crash, it's going to crash, crash, crash, crash, crash.
Just get the tracks.
Uh-oh.
I fucked.
We can turn it.
No, you can't turn it.
What do you mean you can turn it?
Is this snake advanced?
Where's the axe?
Oh, my God.
All right, turn it again.
Hang on.
Time, time.
We need more wood.
I'm chopping it down right now.
I've got a ton of wood up here.
So you got...
Oh, my God.
I'm going to chop down every tree over here.
Too many cooks in the kitchen.
We're just going to go on a straight line.
Yeah, but we need wood and shit.
I'm just going to be the wood guy.
But you just chop a straight path all the way through and we'll be fine.
But wood.
Where's the bucket?
I'm already splashing.
Okay.
How are we doing?
Good.
Right.
We need just regular old track.
Tons of stone.
All right.
That was almost...
What can I chop?
Over here.
It's the right...
I'm going to throw up.
Things have kind of calmed down a little.
Yeah, that was good.
That was a little panicky for a minute, but it's all right.
All right.
We got tons of resources.
We have a lot of resources.
Build resources.
Remember back in the day.
Yeah.
Good.
Is your track ready?
Oh, my God.
You see, it's hard to place.
Actually, that's not a bad idea.
It'll take a long time to get over here.
All right.
I'm going to chop down some...
I'm going to get some more stone.
I think we're going to go straight down this way.
Why not go...
You got to go to the station.
That's what I'm doing.
Oh.
Well, why not go through the trees and then we get a bunch of wood?
Look at all the wood that's already around all over the place.
We got a fire.
There's tons of wood.
How about we speed this thing up?
It probably will when you hit the checkpoint.
All right.
We got plenty of resources.
Where's the axe?
I'm going to use it.
Good.
Very good.
Pass game.
Turn your volume down.
All right.
Quick.
You got to get in front of it.
What do I do?
All right.
You're good.
Just it's about to go on the...
On the...
Straight away.
Yeah, we can build bridges, dude.
We need more stone.
We need stone.
Stone.
Water, wood, no stone.
There's stone on the ground here.
Fucking crybaby.
It's raining.
Let me introduce you to who is what character.
I'm Penguin.
I'm...
Cowboy.
You're Indiana Jones.
Snowman.
At the top right of...
I don't know what I am.
Stone?
Who are you?
Stone man?
Skull man?
I think I'm like a man.
Skull skeleton in a suit or something?
I just call me Sans.
Remember that game?
I played that game.
I did not.
I wonder if I...
Can I pause it and...
What if I show the session ID?
Uh-oh, it's nighttime.
Dude, what?
Well, there's tons of it down here.
It's going, it's going.
I need some stone, though.
I'm on it.
Sorry.
It's too dark.
I can't see anything.
I'm honestly scared.
Wait, how did I ruin it?
What?
We're gonna need that bucket.
Yeah, we'll get it, Will.
This is a tight fit.
All right, this is just the first station.
That means we beat level one.
Got it.
Oh, no.
Why's it going so fast?
What's fucking happening?
Because they've got to run to the station.
Oh.
We're gonna get money.
You can spin your bolts for wagon upgrades.
Oh, what?
New wagons?
So we get two bolts.
What do they do?
New engines and you unlock.
Crafting speed.
So it makes track fast.
More...
Is this a water tank?
Or more...
Or more supplies can go in there to be crafted.
I think it's gonna be difficult to deal with the speed.
We need more, like, stacks in the storage thing.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Let's do that.
But then we got new wagon.
Lights up in the dark.
What's this one?
Crafting speed of 60%.
Converts wood to iron or iron to wood.
Steam engine for the Wild West.
How do we go fast?
Where's our money?
Is it one more bolt?
Yeah, we only have one bolt.
Let's get capacity on this thing.
Yeah, that's good.
We're good, we're good, we're good.
That's 60% faster and extra stacks.
Exit stand here.
Which one of these is correct?
I think exit stand here.
Exit stand here, dude.
All right, Chad's mad that we didn't get a ghost.
I don't know what it meant.
All right, we don't have time to sit around and dilly dally.
We surely do not.
How come I can't pickaxe?
We didn't get a ghost.
Is some stone not...
Is only the...
Yeah, you can't do the black, gray stone.
I got it.
This song absolutely fucking just is...
Slaps.
Yeah, I was trying to think of that word and I'm too old to know what it was.
Okay, we know who the real boomer is.
Oh, you guys better be making a path.
We need wood.
I mean, we need...
Yeah, go for it.
You can't just see hanging out with some of your friends.
Just building a train track.
You could get this.
Oh, I put the wood in.
We need stone.
Where is it?
I've been hitting it.
Okay, we're bringing you the torch.
You guys just want to make like a super big path.
Don't leave all the tools back here.
Across the wall.
Uh-oh, we're on fire.
I'll handle it.
I'm the oldest.
Okay, we...
Yeah, we just go through the stone.
Yeah, we have to start stoning.
We need stone.
Start stoning.
Start it.
I'm going.
We actually need wood to go...
You all right?
We need to go...
We need wood to go across this path here.
Gentlemen, we need wood.
Otherwise, this thing ain't going anywhere.
I'm wooding.
No.
Who's got the pick?
It's in front of you.
No, it's over...
We're stuck on the wrong side.
You got it.
Hey, what?
Can you say that again?
What?
No, say that again.
Don't make me do it.
I will.
Okay, can you guys do something?
We can't move.
I can't.
Literally can't.
Can you literally do something?
No, we can't do anything.
You have to build...
No, we're stuck on...
No, we lose.
You have to do the whole thing.
You have to do it all.
We're about to lose.
Oh my god.
He's just still chopping.
He can't hear us.
Well, you kept picking up the fucking thing.
I tried to come back there and get things.
And you had...
You picked them.
Look how easy that was.
We need a shitload of wood.
I'm going to fucking scream.
We need a shitload of wood now.
In front of us.
I'm just getting wood.
You have a clear path to the next area, Ghost.
Fire!
We're stuck.
Where's the...
I got it.
We need a pickaxe.
Dude, Star, how could you not have made a rubber ducky joke here?
Come on.
Isn't that your thing?
We need to have a track build.
Are these cows going to get in the way?
Kill them.
Wait, why are you going that way?
Because that's the station.
Kill them.
We need stone bat.
All right, I got you on stone.
This is too stressful.
It's actually less stressful than the last game so far.
All right.
Excuse me?
You can go up.
If you wanted to go up, that'd be good.
No, go straight across.
Well, you got to go up eventually because that's...
Yeah, but we just go up one here.
And it's all cleared.
Yeah, but like we can just go straight across.
Like this, ready?
All right, now we need wood.
Where's the axe?
I'm killing the cows with it.
That's great use of our materials.
We desperately need wood.
Good use of the materials.
You murdering animals.
Good.
I want to make sure our train doesn't hit a fucking cow.
Oh, there's gold down there at the bottom.
You see that shit?
They're actually...
What is that?
Wow, there's so much gold.
Turn it around.
Turn this around.
I think...
Do we just need to pick it up or does the train need to pass?
Train has to hit it for sure.
How do you know?
That has to be what this is.
How about we try the easier thing first?
All right.
Chop.
Gotta get the upgrade map.
How are we going to...
Oh my god, you just turned it...
No, no, no.
Don't do that.
You're doing it right.
No, no, no.
Because it has to cross.
How are we going to put it back the right way?
The old track.
Yeah, we can pick the old track.
Yep.
Oh, you can make some big stacks.
Fire.
Oh shit, I got it.
I got it.
Oh.
All right, I need regular old wood.
Regular wood.
There's quick...
On the board here.
Make a path.
You gotta hurry or it's gonna cut us off.
You gotta do it from the other way.
All right, now we need wood inside the train.
Okay.
Okay, I picked it up.
The train doesn't need to touch it.
Wait, you got it?
Fuck you guys.
Yeah, I got it.
Okay, wait, wait.
Hold on, hold on.
I told you.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Now we can't pick up the track.
Uh oh, we can't pick up the track.
No.
What happens if you loop it in on itself?
Put one in between.
No, put one on the other side.
Oh, you can't.
Ah.
Yeah, you can't pick it up after it goes over the track.
We're going up.
No.
Can we go to the bottom?
Can we get through?
Hold on.
We can't get through this.
You fucked us.
Well, it seemed reasonable that the train would have to pass over.
No, just check first.
Because you have to build the bridge no matter what.
And we had like seven stacks of wood.
You could have built the bridge over there with your axe and checked it for us.
I'm not giving up yet.
Don't give up yet.
Hold on.
Oops.
Okay, you're going to yell at me.
I'm the one who fucking noticed it in the first place.
You fucking entitled, spoiled brat.
If Star hadn't have noticed the golden nugget,
then we wouldn't have even gone for it.
And we would have still been training to the right.
I saw it.
And I said, build a bridge first.
And then Jerma said, no, turn the train.
And then I fucking spit in his coffee.
That's my secret.
My coffee is exclusively made out of spit.
All right.
Try again.
Do we have to hide everything?
I don't think so.
Why'd you leave?
I fucked up, dude.
I fucked up.
Have you ever fucked up before?
No.
Would you leave?
Hide everything again.
Give us a session ID.
Oh, I'm sorry.
You have to press a hotkey for a session ID.
We had progress.
Dude, it's way past my bedtime.
If anyone here is going to complain, it's me.
Yeah, but this game is very fun, though.
This is fun.
I was on easy.
And we got one checkpoint.
That was not easy.
Turn it up to hard mode.
Put it on hard, then.
We can't.
You know we can't.
Then do it on medium.
But you may have to make the seed something fun.
No, that is something fun.
Krungus?
The last time I touched the seed, it, like,
freeze my game.
All right, we're good.
Who's making it?
He's got the code.
There, I made it.
We're in here.
Oh.
I'm Skullman again.
All right, I'm joining.
Yeah, why would you join?
Look, well, now we understand how the game works.
I don't.
But you can kill it.
You figured out how to kill cows.
Yeah.
And stop touching!
We had it ready, like, a minute ago,
and you come in here and start touching shit.
All right, but you can play on,
you can play with checkpoints, though.
You can restart at the first station in each biome.
But he left the game because he's,
just, something wrong with him.
I didn't want to do the same map again, okay?
Let's go, Taleks!
Playing on medium.
Here we go.
All right, pick a tool.
Probably eats his stakes for catching.
I'll build the track.
Keep the tool in your hand.
Let's do this efficiently, okay?
Okay, I'm just gonna break every single one of these blocks.
Well, I can't say blocks.
How about this?
We're gonna get so many resources in this first area.
Jerma is just the pick up resources
and then put the track down.
And we just chop.
Jerma's already using...
I'm resourceful.
I'm pickaxe up top.
And once you connect it, I'm gonna go chop the other side.
Okay, I need some help putting that stone in.
Give me one more.
Get one more across or we're gonna die.
Keep me!
Oh, we gotta do this quick.
Yeah.
It's on medium.
You thought hard was gonna be workful?
Could you not?
All right, gold nugget in the waterfall on the top.
Okay, turn the train, turn the train.
I'll go get it.
I'll get it, I'll get it, I'll get it, I'll get it, I'll get it.
All right, you need to make some extra bridges
or you're stuck over here.
I need some wood to get that gold piece.
Follow me, I'm chopping all of it.
Sorry, there must be water in the bucket.
There was.
The flame is out.
What the fuck?
What the fuck, dude?
We need a bridge here or shit's about to get real bad.
We need a track here.
Uh-oh, it's about to get real bad.
And we can't bring the track unless you put some wood here
and you're the master of all of the woods.
You need to chop this tree, you need to chop this tree.
Chop, chop.
All right, that's not mean.
No, no, we need that pickaxe.
Back up, back up pickaxe.
I have the track.
And the water bucket, dude.
Dude, dude.
Oh my God.
Get the water bucket.
All right, I'm going to put these ahead of us.
How about these?
We're going to drive the train.
The gold piece.
We're going to need some mining.
And I'm going for it.
Train's turning too wide.
Fire up.
Train's on fire.
Here we go.
We're good.
Checkpoint one.
Done.
Oh, easy this was.
One more track.
And we can say we did it.
And let's actually put our points in something cool this time
rather than something, uh, stupid.
Honestly, the things that we did were not bad.
It was very helpful.
With three bolts, we only had two.
They were good.
Oh, by the way, it's not a gold piece you pick up.
You pick it, it's a bolt.
I know.
They're so important, holy shit.
It's a piece of bolt.
Convert raw materials to track.
This is just another one.
What did you just get?
I'm supposed to come to it.
Increases this.
I don't know what he got actually.
Yeah, I got increased size.
Come on.
It's important.
Well, there's two that look the same, but they're not the same.
It's pretty sure you got the right one.
Dynamite?
Plus two size.
Dynamite might be fun.
Auto mine commodities.
That's pretty.
That sounds pretty good.
But we spent all the bolts already.
So I'll put it.
Germa just spent the bolt.
I'm glad we came to consensus.
That's why it auto mines things around it.
That's like a no brainer.
That's the first one you should get.
But when you put it at the front then, instead of the back?
It doesn't matter.
What's the radius?
Can you reorganize?
It should be right here next to the water tank.
He just does things.
All right, let's go.
You're a little brother.
He just did it.
See if we can get two checkpoints.
And he presses the button and you're like, okay,
I guess that's how we're going to play.
And I just get my finger jammed almost to the palm of my hand up my nose.
We going straight?
Yes.
Look, it's auto mining.
I actually can't tell what this is doing.
Now it's an awkward space between where the track comes out
and where the track ingredients go in.
What are the two hamburger buns?
What does that mean?
Which way do you want to take this?
I'm just getting material.
Go south and go across the water or go north and go through all the trees.
I think we just go through all the stuff.
Forget about the water.
I don't think the auto miner is doing anything.
Yeah, let's go through the trees.
Maybe it's got ingredients in there and you have to take them out.
Feed it stone.
Put stone in it.
All right, I'm making a turn.
You're right.
You don't really have any spare stone.
We have a lot of it up here.
Turn south.
We need trees.
Yeah, OK, it takes.
You have to use two stone to turn it on and turn it off.
Are we going straight or are we going?
We're just going straight, right?
Go across the water.
So we're going down.
Yeah, go well.
Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick.
Where's the pickaxe?
I'm using it.
All right.
Are those birds shitting on it?
I'm going to fill up the tank.
So I think you can preemptively cool the engine with water every so often
without having to wait for it to catch on fire.
Oh, shit, this stuff actually, it does do this.
That's actually pretty sick.
Yeah, it cuts down all like everything around it as long as it's got power.
Why do we get this weird haze?
It's called fog.
I know you only see when you go outside, but we're not used to that.
What's going on with this track?
What's going on with the track?
Why did that?
Wait, are we making it go?
What are we doing?
I would really like to pick this squiggle track up, but it's fine.
Oh, OK.
OK.
Don't lose that bucket of water.
I'll turn the train around.
We missed something.
All right.
Get a stack of wood over here.
Fire.
Oh, it's getting dark.
Shit.
There's the bucket.
Dark.
Shit.
Get a stack of wood.
Stack of wood.
What?
We got to make track.
You got to get over here.
I'm chopping wood.
Just get the wood.
I got it.
OK, OK, OK, OK, OK.
All right, start.
This is why I didn't want to come over here.
This is why I didn't want to come over.
Now pick it up and bring it over here.
Thank you.
Chopping wood.
This is going to be cutting it close.
OK, we need, I need.
I'm chopping wood.
Where's the, are we going up?
That's a decision for you guys to make.
All right, we're going up.
We're following him.
Already is.
I got to kill these boys.
Wood's more important right now.
We don't lose any tools.
I'm moving the bucket up here.
Oops.
Oh, tallax.
Oh.
To be fair, it doesn't highlight.
Is that going to crash?
Yeah.
No.
All right, we need stone.
Don't get caught.
Uh oh.
OK, just keep the train going straight.
Look at what we're about to run into.
You can't dig that stone,
person trying to dig this.
I'm not.
I'm trying to have visibility
so we can see ahead of us,
not dig the stone.
Hey, person trying to dig the stone.
All right, we need some extra pass to walk.
OK, we need a lot of wood.
All right, we got to go.
We got a big, big wood path going south.
I'm going to keep chopping.
I'm not going to stop chopping.
Don't expect me to do anything but chop.
OK.
What about, uh, we don't have any stone.
Just don't.
Quick, we're running out of, we're running out of stone.
I got it.
We're going to have a big problem here in a second.
Big problem incoming.
Stone.
I'm making stone.
Fire.
Bucket.
Oh no, I'm getting stuck.
Bucket's up there, we're good.
Um, I don't know what to do.
There's bolts at the top,
so don't connect the last piece of track until you have to.
Actually, I don't think there's trees for us to get it.
Is there not enough trees?
Hold on.
It might be.
I got it, I got it.
We're doing it.
You guys do this.
I'm trying to get this thing.
I need, like, one more piece.
Can I die if I don't move?
Is it OK if I connect it?
I don't know.
Uh, don't do it yet.
Because if you connect it, it finishes.
And then we can't build up materials and stuff.
What do you, oh, there's a golden ticket.
We need more wood for that.
We're going to need another track.
Track is right to the top of you, Stark.
OK.
Wood?
How much more do we have?
Hold on, hold on.
It's not enough.
How do we get more wood?
We need one wood.
Is there a tree?
We'll be able to do it after it parks.
Periodically, I hope.
That's not an all-in-one spot.
All right.
I'm just going to buy a random thing.
We only have one bolt, so I really, we could just save.
Why not just save?
I want crafting speed stack side.
That's not that's not bad, actually.
Put it in a good spot.
Don't do what I do.
That's not great.
So it's the same speed stack size.
We were not once waiting on the track.
What have you done?
Stack size is nice because then you can take stuff
because we always have like a full stack of shit in here.
It works out.
I mean, you could if we saved, you can actually make the auto miner like good.
Let's go.
Plus two range on the auto miner.
I mean, that's pretty good, too.
We only have one bolt.
Ghost wagon and dynamite are the best.
Also a better craft.
Like you can get a second raw material wagon.
OK, but we only had one bolt and now we have no bolts.
What does this let you die?
What does the ghost wagon do?
You die, you go to the other side.
What does that mean?
We can still get that.
Yeah, we can wrap around and get it.
We could just walk to it.
Holy shit.
Yeah, just walk.
Oh, man.
We could just walk to it.
We need to work pretty fast because we're in this awkward.
Yeah, I'm trying to dig wide so we have some space to move.
There's a bunch of stone on the other side of the river, too.
Isn't it?
You can just build stone.
We don't need stone.
Ram on this thing on.
All right.
Oh, fuck.
It's fucking great.
I can't reach it.
Hold on.
I can't move.
I was not involved in that.
I panicked.
I'm sorry.
Who are these bandits?
I don't know.
I've been killing them.
I think they steal your stuff if you let them probably.
All right.
We're going to double up.
We still have access, by the way, to the pickaxe.
Where is it?
Okay.
What do we need?
Any tracks?
Make some calls.
What do we need?
I got it.
We're going to go follow the rubber ducky.
Or just follow where he's digging right now.
We need stone delivered.
We got wood and stone.
There you go.
We got wood.
All right.
Dig.
I'm going to mine like a secondary path.
Each player has to mine a rock.
What did it say?
It's like an achievement thing.
All right.
We need to kill the cows.
They move out of the way.
You really don't.
No, I just wanted to kill some cows.
Put some stone in that machine.
It's so high up.
Beef.
All right.
Where's that pickaxe?
I got it.
Play down here, too.
What?
So we're going to have two paths.
What are you saying?
See the wooden path I made to the stone?
That's just more stone.
Well, we need to go forward.
Yeah.
The autominer's just got stuff.
Can we hit the cows or what?
No, they walk away from the track.
Walk away.
Okay.
All right.
We need trees.
We need this cut down up front.
And then we're pretty much there.
I'm going for the tree.
We got a bolt.
We'll let you do it.
Fire.
Oh, it's on fire.
Buckets right up.
Right on top, top.
Right next to the star.
No, it's out.
Who's penguin?
I'm penguin.
All right.
Talek's penguin.
Yeah, you got it.
All right.
There's an absolute shitload of materials down here.
Start collecting.
Feed the autominer.
Good.
It is looking good.
Well, don't waste resources on the autominer when it's not near anything.
Does it consume while it's not near anything, I wonder?
Yeah, it does.
You can see it digging up grass.
It's digging grass.
Well, then you can just take it off.
I wonder if there's upgrades so we can carry more stuff in our hands
because currently what?
It's two or three.
Make sure you don't leave any tools.
Looking good.
Do we have any secret loot?
There's one over here.
Behind.
We can get it later.
We're probably going to get it right now, actually.
How are we doing on track?
We got like a small stack back there.
We don't have a lot of wood.
So, yeah.
We're about to win.
There is so much stone that I put here.
I think there's enough to get both, isn't there?
Well, yeah, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Don't, don't, don't.
Wait, wait, wait.
Make sure we have enough track to complete the level.
This is more important.
I want gold.
No, I didn't.
Can I pick up the last two?
Fire.
Where's the bucket?
Oh, it's not full.
He's got it.
I'm doing it.
All right, we need one more.
Still on fire somehow.
Are we out of wood?
No.
We just need one more track.
All right, complete it.
Yeah.
All right.
Oh, yeah.
That's what I'm talking about.
Four fucking bolts.
All right, that could be a new engine if we wanted it.
What about the juice box?
Increases your strength for every animal you bring by.
That's carrying capacity.
Liquid storage?
You feed cows and you get juice?
Plus 100% capacity.
That's pretty good.
How do you do that?
All right, minor tier two.
Can I not move it ever?
How are you doing that, sir?
If you write your right analog stick,
you press it down, you can create waypoints.
It's kind of annoying.
And then left trigger and right trigger are emotes.
What did we buy?
I bought the minor expander.
If you're going to have it, it may as well do something.
What about halts the train for a short time,
dash into it to fill up its charge?
I don't know how to dash.
Dash is B.
Now we can knock each other off the bridge like in Overcooked 2.
Are we saving the points or what?
I vote for...
I'm down with the stack size.
Is that just the normal platform?
Halts the train for a short time,
dash into it to fill up its charge.
I feel like we're accidentally going to activate that.
Yeah, we probably are.
I kind of don't want our train to be longer right now
because we keep getting caught on it.
100% capacity.
We could save.
I mean, capacity is just capacity.
Well, that's for the water, right?
What is this thing for?
Executive decision.
What'd you grab?
What is that?
Now we're going to make track at a thousand times normal speed.
Yeah.
Wait, what was that one?
Increase the capacity and build speed for tracks.
Cool waypoints.
Pretty useful.
Plenty of track.
True.
All right.
I hope you guys are ready to start smashing some trees.
They delete all yours.
Oh, no, we got to go to water preemptively
just for when we need to douse it.
Capacity.
Good.
Cool.
Auto mine.
We're going to need to start mining stone up here.
Which way are we going?
Up or just to the right?
Up and then right.
What's up here?
Where's the stone?
You turn the track around.
Yeah, you hang on.
What are you talking about?
You did.
Yeah, that's not what you want to do.
You want to go like down and then over.
How do you do that?
And then right.
Well, we need to start talking trees.
You just turned it around.
Yeah, whatever.
Well, I thought you like doomed it again
that we couldn't remove the thing.
But I think a talent you removed.
I saved it.
You can remove it if it hasn't driven over it.
Oh, a ton of wood.
Like too much to even I don't know what to do with it.
There's no nothing.
No bridges to build a bucket of water.
Do more auto mining.
I feel like eventually that would be the best bet.
I think.
Right.
Let's just have a super auto miner and just build track.
All right.
Can you chop the trees that are going to go
adjacent to where we're building?
Yes.
Well, shouldn't we not because we keep doing that
and then the auto miner doesn't do anything.
Well, it should do something while it's next to all these rocks.
All right.
Speaking of rocks.
Yeah, that has to be that has to be this stone has to be in there
for it to auto mine in the first place.
How do you set those up from a distance?
Yeah.
You just click down right stick.
I'm trapped over here.
I need a wood cutter.
I can't help either.
That's auto mining now.
Wow.
That's insane.
This one was easy.
So you can pick up cows.
Okay.
We're on fire.
Bucket is off the screen.
Oh my God.
You got it.
That was close.
We need to chop down here.
What a good seed this was.
Quickly chop down here or else you're dead.
It's right next to you.
Where is it?
Oh, there is a way out anyway.
All right.
You still got it.
You still got to chop up there.
You got to chop right here.
Right here.
Where I'm standing.
Quickly.
Guys.
No, we're good here.
Up.
Chop up.
I think you're severely underestimating the severity of the situation.
Yes, he is.
He doesn't understand that we can't get the track over there.
You're crazy, dude.
God.
All right.
Are we good?
Any special things or just go?
There is a nugget in the top but there's no conceivable way to get that.
And the bucket's gone.
That's okay.
We made it.
Does it put itself out?
Yes.
We only have one bolt.
Can't even mine otherwise go.
Okay, so it needs to be like on constant vigilant bucket duty.
Yeah.
We could just buy the upgrade.
Yep.
We're gonna have a problem here in two seconds.
What's that?
Because it's a very straight narrow line and this just got way hard.
Go completely straight.
Just go straight.
Straight, straight, straight.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
There's a stone.
Put stone in there.
Track, track, track, track.
No one is getting the stone.
I got it.
No one like we need.
I'm having stress.
Okay.
Bucket, bucket.
Don't leave the bucket.
This is really, really uh claustrophobic right now.
Don't leave this bucket back here.
What?
All right, we're good.
I'm just, I'm 100% digging.
Right here.
Oh, man, we are.
Do you see the tree to your left?
We're gonna run out of stone unless I go up.
Do you see the tree directly in front of the penguin that's spinning around?
Oh, guys.
Guys, it's over.
It's not over.
It's not, it's not over.
Stone.
We need a lot of stone.
I had, there's a bridge to come up around the corner,
up top around the engine.
I got a lot of, uh, stone.
You're not finished.
Get the auto miner on.
I got, I got, I got, I got it.
I don't want to get stuck back here.
Fuck.
Oh, hold on.
There we go.
Okay, hold on.
Don't, we're gonna need this pickaxe up here soon.
I got it.
Where, what do you need it?
Oh, eventually we're going to need to start digging.
Okay, okay, okay.
That's too cool.
I, nobody, we can't all get in there.
I'm trying my best.
We're out of stone.
No, we're not, no, we're not, no, we're not, no, we're not, no, we're not.
I'm going straight, straight, straight.
Get this, get this one right here.
Come on, I'm standing right in front of it.
We need a lot of stone.
Whoever's got the pickaxe needs to go.
It's right next to, to the left, to the left, to the right, to the front.
All right, someone go feed it stone and get the track.
Yep, yep, yep, yep, yep.
I didn't do it.
All right, I'm making a path for you to come through.
Fuck it.
Fuck it alert.
We're going to need a two by two path.
We're screwed in a second.
What do you mean?
This isn't, we're not going to be able to get to the back of the train.
Oh shit, hold on.
Where's it, uh, uh, yep.
No, we're fine, we're fine.
We're good.
We're relaxed.
I got a thousand stone on me.
I have made it two by two all the way to the station.
Oh no.
Fuck.
We're going to miss the, uh, we're going to miss the, uh, the bolt, the bolt, the bolt.
We can still get it.
You, I'll do this.
You guys focus on that.
I'll get this.
Where's the pickaxe?
I got it.
You, uh, you build the track.
Okay.
Go up and get that bolt.
I need it through.
I need through.
I don't.
Okay.
I got the last piece.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Hold it.
I'm only two away.
Oh yeah.
Yeah.
Don't leave me behind up in the mountains.
You'll be all right.
All right.
We got four.
Oh yeah.
All right.
I'm in favor of water capacity at 100%.
What's this new one?
Shows you the way.
Auto pick up things placed nearby.
I mean, I, I, I think auto pick up.
And water capacity.
Yeah.
I'm in favor.
Auto pick up is pretty huge.
This is a new thing.
Yeah.
I want to put it at the front
or should I put it after the auto miner?
Maybe put it at the end.
Yeah, right back.
Because then they would just get everything we missed.
Uh, no, put it in the front.
It's most likely we're going to be digging near the front.
You want water tank in front or?
Auto, auto mine in front.
Yeah, but I already fucked that up.
Put it in the front.
Auto pick up in front.
All right.
And then the capacity.
By the way, you can only have five pieces.
So be aware of that.
We've now cannot add anything else.
Crap.
Really?
Five out of five wagons.
Mine front, pick back.
Well, that's what I was thinking, but apparently not.
Uh, where's the tools?
Right in here.
It's all wood.
Yeah, it's all wood.
Uh, go backwards and start getting their stone on the ground.
I can't go up here.
How do you fuel the auto pickup?
Uh, auto pick up his wood.
I can't go back there.
Uh, auto mine it.
Where's the, uh, we're about to lose already.
We're good.
Just don't, uh, yeah, free him and bring the bucket.
Already nighttime.
We're dead.
We don't have any stone.
We have tracks in the back that no one picked up.
Oh, we're fine.
We're fine.
We're good.
Give him some swirls.
Well, if you give him some swirls, then we.
How do we get to the back now?
Uh, that's a you guys problem.
Oh, no, it's an us problem.
Just keep, just walk around.
It looked like it was abstract.
Track, track, track, track, track, track, track, track.
It's really dark and scary.
Great.
Two by two.
Should we go straight or up?
We have to go, uh, let's see what happens if we go up.
Yeah, we're going to buy two.
Two by two.
We need wood.
That's you need the two by two.
Jeremy, you need the two by two.
You need to turn around and free us.
Take right here.
Faster.
Got it.
Then bring stone immediately.
Bring stone immediately.
I mean, now what?
Uh, two by two.
I'm going, I'm going, I'm going.
You're nudging me.
You're pushing me.
Are you going to file a lawsuit because I like flicked your ear?
What?
I'm coming with track.
Are we, we're going around?
I would, I just, I would just, I get, why are you doing that?
We don't have any trees.
Are there any trees up here?
Trees.
What do you need to this stuff?
Where am I?
Right here, right here, right here, right here.
You need something.
Someone come get the bucket.
Where's the bucket?
It's way back there, but we have to.
Thank God we can see.
All right.
We need, uh, we're going up.
I'm going to, uh, chopping wood.
We need wood.
The woods up here.
Wood by me.
I need this bucket moved.
You can just put it down, right?
No, I have to place the track.
Ooh, that's a tight squeeze.
That's, is that going to bump?
No.
Look at what the autominer is doing.
It's doing so well.
We need wood.
It's all up here, all up by me.
There's like a thousand of it.
I think this is it.
This is not it.
This is it.
No, we only, we just, we lost the engine.
That's all right.
It's going faster now.
It is.
Just stand in front of it.
Stand in front of it.
All right.
We start from checkpoint.
That was hard.
That one was hard.
That was zigzags.
It was like someone said in all capitals,
this is what we get for wasting the autominer.
That's true.
It is.
We could have had autominer once,
auto collector right behind it.
Do we get to start a checkpoint?
And why are we stuck at connecting?
Yeah, I'm stuck at connecting too.
Star, are you like all tapped?
Reach, reach off from zero.
Was this not even the,
we didn't even finish the first biome?
No, we did not.
Save it at last checkpoint.
What?
We didn't even finish the first biome.
Okay.
Now it's like six hours past my bedtime.
I just had an insane deja vu right now.
This is the same map.
All right.
We'll clean it up.
This is the same seat.
So you want everything identical?
Do you want RNG fun?
Do RNG fun?
Well, that's why I left last time
and everyone yelled at me.
Well, I thought there was a different checkpoint.
All right.
RNG fun.
Guys, the train needs to be upgraded to save the game.
We need to do the four on the new.
That's how you get to a new area.
Oh, is it?
Uh-huh.
Yep.
Tied in the tutorial.
All right.
Well, what do you guys want to do?
You want to give it another go?
I want to eat dinner.
One more.
One more real attempt.
Right?
Look, hey, just order whatever you want.
Put it on my fucking cart.
I'm not ordering dinner.
That's irresponsible.
I want to do one more.
One more could be like three hours.
No.
If we get good.
Yeah.
They'd get good.
I don't want to walk over there too.
Because this is his opportunity to leave.
Are you always just playing?
We just did one more and you died in this tutorial.
You think we're really going to go three hours?
I don't want to redo the lobby.
That's what it is.
He doesn't want to do the lobby again.
Well, come over here.
Come on.
Come over.
Let's go.
Let's hurry.
Let's fucking hurry.
He doesn't want to type the five-character code.
Just let him eat.
I'm saying just eat whatever you want.
Well, speaking of, the five-letter code is right there.
The five-letter code has been leaked.
So I hit BRB.
Sex.
Facts.
Go.
Does it matter?
Or do we not even care?
Go.
It's already leaked.
Sex fact.
This is the one.
All right.
We got some awkward initial stone.
Just once.
Two by two.
German.
To be fair, you were not doing two by two.
Well, that's why I need someone to tell me.
No, I wasn't.
I was simply trying to do an impression of one of you two speaking.
Are we just going to go straight?
What are we doing here?
I think straight's probably because straight is more resources.
If you can't fit the things, just make a wood stack next to it.
Yeah, if we just go straight, the thing is over there.
Just don't forget about those enemies.
Wait.
No, we have to kill them.
Keep your commodities safe from bandits.
Yeah, they're stealing our stuff.
Just smash them.
Well, as we know, property is more valuable than human lives.
So kill them.
Okay, we need to dig straight.
Where's the bucket?
Where is the bucket?
I haven't seen a bucket.
Get there quick.
Just get there quick.
Straight line before it burns.
Two by two, German.
Two by two.
It doesn't matter.
We just have to go.
Let's not be doing it anymore.
Yeah, because as soon as you place down the last track, we got it.
Is that a dinosaur?
All right, we're done.
Where?
Yeah, place it.
There's a dinosaur where the pickaxe is.
There is a dinosaur.
Is that a new character?
No, someone joined because it was public.
Well, it is a new character then.
Wait, somebody's in the game?
Yeah, somebody's in the game.
Well, hey.
Lucky chat member.
Somebody got in.
Well, hey, a fourth person.
This just like helps.
Let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
There's no money to spend.
You guys just fucking dilly dally.
I got to eat dinner.
Hey, whatever.
This is just like a major league baseball mascot.
They're going to be like so helpful.
I know.
Well, we shouldn't even be upset about this.
Yeah, until he doesn't two by two.
He's not.
Do you think they get the dinosaur costume without two by twoing?
I think it's random.
I think you can just pick any costume.
Can't mind the stone.
Should we just go straight?
Well, let's go down.
Well, Dingo, the dinosaur wants us to go this way.
So that's where we're going.
Is that M doing this?
Which I believe this one.
Yeah, our Sims 3 entrance mascot is going to help us out here.
Not Sims 3, go across to Tycoon 3.
I could have fucking just called that guy in Germany
and got him to play with him.
Yeah, but then.
Then what?
Well, I don't want to say, but then you end up with Dev in call,
who is like, all right, and the other features we've got here,
there are 17 different characters.
You don't call him.
You guys haven't been paying attention.
He already got the bolt.
Look it.
I saw that.
Did you, though?
Yeah.
Stuck on this tree.
What if this is the Dev?
This is playing like a Dev.
Because he has like common sense is like he's too smart.
He's just chopping trees.
You know, it's, it's called keeping your head down.
We're going, we're going too slow.
The Mario level is not auto scrolling fast enough.
He wants to keep going faster.
Things aren't building quick enough.
Yes, because we have a slow ass train.
Stone, stone.
This person just took over.
He's just chopping like a maniac.
This so good.
Hey, Star, I hope you know that we probably will be here for three hours
because we have somebody that actually knows everything.
Well, now I can leave it down to the three players, which was efficient.
Let's keep dinosaur mascot.
That's so fun.
Yeah, we're doing too good.
We have a surplus.
There's like a thousand wood, my man.
What is that extra zig for?
Look at all this.
Wait, you want to go that way?
Oh, we have to go that way.
Oh shit.
Watch out.
We've got too many resources.
Does anyone want to take care of that?
Fire.
I love that dinosaur.
I love the animation.
The animation is the best.
He just leans back and forth with his head.
All right.
This is a pain in the ass level one.
By the way, we also have to address, we have to address another thing.
Didn't you have the game is unjoinable selected?
Well, it was no randoms.
They had the private code.
Oh.
There's like a random matchmaking as well.
Well, we got it.
We got a straightaway here for one second.
I heard the like, don't don't don't don't.
I thought that was the train.
You running up the track.
It is.
All right, stream viewer.
If you pick a single upgrade in there immediately, you're dead.
You're dead.
In fact, we probably just let him pick all the upgrades.
He probably knows the exact placement.
We should probably just give him our stream key.
Don't leave us behind.
All right.
We have four bolts.
He's like, do this one.
Auto pick up commodities.
Maybe this one.
I like auto pick up commodities.
This one, I'm good.
I love this.
We have so many that we need some stack size too.
Because we had so many commodities that just four of us.
Now, the thing is, do these stay or do they come back?
Oh, I think that's randomly rolling.
Because if it's random every time, then get it now.
Yeah.
Where do we put it?
If it stays there through the next one, then right in the front.
Yeah.
Put it right in the front and then we'll get the auto miner to go.
Obey the dyno.
Hey, I'm obeying the dyno.
So the new engine lets us save.
The new engine means we are at a new place.
Is that we can go.
That's the new biome, which means that allows us to restart from that biome.
Are we going down?
Who knows?
I don't know.
Sure.
Although this is going right into unmindable territory.
All right.
Can you chop to the right?
Or you have to make a bridge.
Bridge is necessary.
It's me dyno.
Please mod me.
We got stone up ahead.
Holy shit.
Look at all that track.
Where did that even come from?
We've just been doing it.
Is this just what happens when you add a fourth player who's also a dinosaur,
who's also a dev?
What's also like anybody is a warm body and this game doesn't change difficulty based on
how many people are in it.
Wow.
Funky.
So hungry.
Why don't you eat some of these rocks?
I haven't seen my wife in days.
Pete.
I'm so hungry.
So, well, I told you just get whatever you want.
What do you want?
Pizza?
I want to make my dinner.
What do you want?
Pizza?
What do you kids want today?
Order me a pizza.
Where's the wood?
Oh, where's the wood?
We need wood to make.
That's all I've been doing since we've loaded into this level.
You could do more.
Who's the dino?
We don't know.
It's a mystery dino.
Don't lose that pickaxe.
I mean, you could.
I think we got enough to finish, right?
Well, that went very smoothly.
Did we see any secrets, though?
I think you just got it.
I think you just got the ball.
We need the little bridge.
Little bridge?
Up top?
The bridge needs to go up.
What?
How are we going to connect to this over the water?
We need a bridge over the water.
Right.
There's bamboo shoots.
Oh, fuck.
All right.
We're good.
Right here.
Look at this damn dino.
Look at that.
I'm just watching.
All right.
I'm going to have to do something.
Just there's wood right here.
Just do it.
I get it.
I'm going to say I really don't think it takes a developer to connect point A to point B.
That's not how this goes.
I chop wood.
That's not where this goes.
I'm going to mine a rock quick.
This one?
Autominer.
Me.
No me.
I'm just having fun watching the Dinosaur play.
What about this thing?
We can't have any more.
Converts wood to iron.
Oh, that's it.
Yeah.
No more.
That's it.
It's five out of five.
How am I not standing in the square?
I thought I was.
That guy stood in it.
He must have been a dev.
Okay.
You joke out.
Get your jokes out.
They're funny.
They're really funny.
Although they can sometimes be hurtful to me.
All right.
So autominer boy is on and auto collector is on at the same time.
That's pretty good.
Let's see what happened.
Are we just going straight or what?
I guess so.
Oh, there's a golden nugget.
Where is it?
I'm going to put this all the way over here because I know we're not.
No one's going to remember that's over there.
Uh, the auto collector really does chew through wood.
Uh, where's the X?
He's going to the X.
Oh, you do.
Yeah, we have to go down.
Cool.
How are we doing?
We're going to need a two by two pretty soon or the autominer to be powered or both.
I'm going to call the autominer right now.
Autominer is on.
I'm going to start.
We need some stone, right?
I'm stuck.
Are we stuck?
Oh, oh, alert, alert, alert, alert.
Now we need a miner down here.
What happened to the two by two?
I was screamed at.
I got it.
Man, get rid of these trees down here.
Nice, nice, nice, nice, nice.
How far does the stack boy reach?
Oh, when you dash them, when they drop their tool, that's what's happening.
You need tools stolen.
All right, we need the, uh, we need the axe over here on the right with the cows.
Okay, you can move the cows away.
They're just kind of, you can pick them up.
This is causing a boy out of the way.
So far.
Pretty good.
Me and Dino just got to cross up.
Did you see that?
Anyone watching right now?
Put that in remind.
We just got crossed up.
That was crazy.
I thought he was, uh, me and he thought he was him.
I'm stuck.
Don't lose me.
We are down to the final piece.
Oh, we're stuck back here.
Alert, how do we do the, how do we do the alert button?
How do I do that?
I want to do that too.
Let's alert.
Great trigger.
I think I'll be able to save you.
Uh, yeah, we need to, we need to access.
Uh, also fire.
Also we are, did we get the key thing?
Yeah.
He's got the last thing.
Destroy no animals.
We got it.
Do we get, um, by the way.
Now we can only do upgrades.
So we should probably get the new engine eventually, right?
We really should do the quest thing that pops up.
Cause I think we just got two bolts for doing that.
What was the quest?
It was don't hit, kill any animals.
So don't do anything to animals.
We just got like a boat for that.
I think upgrade the auto-mining speed.
Oh, the engine lets you have more wagons.
Should we just wait?
Yeah.
That's all about that auto-miner life.
Key.
All right.
Pick roles, pick roles, pick roles here.
No, uh, we need stone or else we're dead.
Like we know.
There's a lot over here.
Well, do you want to put one down or?
No, I got it.
Auto-miner is on.
Which way are we going?
Don't lose these tracks with me.
I need more track.
It's right there.
Well, someone didn't finish mining that all the way.
So we might just lose.
Track is right here.
Don't leave that bucket.
Don't you do it.
I know you, you right there.
You're going to leave it.
I know you were.
All right.
We're about to get the ball all stuck.
We have a little tools up here, right?
Take your way over here.
Both of, uh, both of them all become stuck.
Thank God for the auto-miner.
Miner level two.
We're going up, right?
Are we going straight?
Yeah.
Uh, off or right?
Straight.
There you go.
Look at the auto-miner leveling the land.
Oh, it's crazy.
Stuck on this side.
All right.
What we got for, uh, that pickaxe.
That means there's a secret up top.
Oh shit.
Secret.
Probably.
We need wood to build a bridge up here.
Wood desperately needed up front.
Am I finishing it?
Uh, is there any, I think, I think we're about to go look for the bolt.
It might be a bolt up there.
Put these over here too.
So we get extra, uh, crack.
Is it up there?
Okay.
I think you just got to finish it.
I know.
Already got bolt about the secret.
Dude, we're going to be good to go next time.
Look at that.
It's dark out.
Should we just get the new engine?
Yeah.
New engine?
Or I mean, we have so many materials.
We just don't have big enough stack sizes or just get auto-miner.
We have materials everywhere.
I don't know if auto-mining better is going to help as much as stacking bigger.
Auto-mine.
Let's do it.
All right.
Auto-miner and the upgrade of that thing.
And then we'll do the, yeah.
Yeah.
Then we'll do the train next round.
Did you just get two auto-miner upgrades?
We got auto-miner and auto-picker.
Auto-pickup and auto-miner.
Yeah.
This thing's going to just chew.
We got like level one hold resources.
It'll just chew through everything.
We just need, we just got to survive.
Look at all this track we have.
Are you kidding me?
This is like, we are, we just started on easy mode.
Because apparently if you take the track off before it ends, it doesn't disappear.
Make sure you keep it.
Don't leave anything.
All right.
Where are we off to?
The problem is auto-miner can reach like twice as far as auto-picker.
That's better.
Holy shit.
It is destroying everything.
So if you upgrade them at the same time, you're not getting max value out of both.
Well, those cows.
There are cows in here, right?
Straight across.
I think straight is the way to go.
Hope so.
Yeah.
He's, he's going up the bolt.
Oops.
He's doing bolt.
He can't get those materials.
I mean, this is, this is easier.
Just make sure we get tracks placed down ahead of time because we're about to be.
Okay.
We need a wood.
This, this station's right here though.
What?
Hey, Dino's not available.
Dino's taking us the wrong way.
Actually right now.
I mean, why did you listen to the stir maker?
Wait, I thought we were going to the right.
We were.
Dino moved all the train tracks.
It's all right.
It's okay.
We, we, no, no, no, no, no, no.
This is safe.
This is fine.
Okay.
I'm on to you.
Tracks, tracks, tracks, tracks.
You need tracks.
Tracks, track, track it up.
We can connect it down here.
Everybody slow down.
We're fine.
Ay, ya, ya, ya.
Don't touch a cow.
Ay, ya, ya.
Dream.
I just want to eat dinner.
And then we take it down.
So down.
And then I'm going to start clearing the path here.
Yeah, we're good.
But there was, there was some panic there for absolutely no reason.
Yeah.
Absolutely none.
I mean, there was a reason.
Water.
For the water.
Was water.
You got to get two by two.
There's so much stone.
The whole mountain's level.
Yeah.
I think we could do next engine now.
We have so many resources.
We're just like throwing them in the ocean.
Well, we need like, we need the track builder because
barely keeping up with the train at this point.
Yeah, we do need the track builder.
Look at all this.
We need the track builder for the storage.
No bolts, right?
It's already been gobbled up.
Let's go.
Track 200 meters.
We get it.
Is there, I think, yeah, we don't.
Three bolts.
We just have to wait till next round.
Yeah.
Just by autominer.
Let's get the, we've been crafting speed on the planks.
That's fine.
We do it anyway.
What'd you just replace?
I upgraded the crafting speed of the tracks.
Dino said no.
We just went against Dino's wishes.
Fuck that guy.
I voted.
I voted in favor.
I know why you just said that.
Because this guy is keeping you from eating dinner because it means we're continuing.
Nice.
I understand.
Oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops, oops.
All right.
We need a lot of stone.
We need to go.
All right.
We need to move now.
Like now, now, now, now.
Get the pickaxe.
No, me.
We might need to loop the track a bit.
Now we should be good.
We have a ton of track.
All right.
I'm just on stone, dude.
Like stuck over here.
We have a lot of plenty of track.
Oh, monsters.
Are we staying straight?
Just straight on?
No reason not to.
Somebody can get that.
Are we going up?
We're going up.
Going up.
Okay.
Only one player is allowed to pick up the bucket.
Where's the fire?
Where's the bucket?
Water bucket.
You got it?
Dino has it.
There's still stone here.
I can't get through.
Auto Miner will save you eventually.
Oh, yeah.
Should we have to go up?
I'm just looping it so we have some time.
Gonna shoot through everything.
We need to go up.
Actually, we're fine.
What do you see?
We're going.
You have to start to go up from here.
And then we need to build up the bridge.
What are we doing?
It placed weird.
I did not mean to do that.
It buys us some time.
Well, kill.
Fire?
There really is just too much stuff on the ground.
Yes.
There's so many resources.
I'm sure that would be...
I'm sure that would be a very much not an issue in about five minutes.
Too much wood stacked right there.
You need to pick up that stack of wood.
Big fat stack of wood.
Thank you.
There's so many resources.
We just build our bridges twice as wide just because we can.
This is the power of human wealth and influence.
Yeah, this is just...
We've grown too fat and too greedy.
GG, auto, miner.
That's true.
I mean, we're pretty...
We still...
We don't even have enough...
We can't even do...
This is on fire.
Fuck it.
End it, end it, end it, end it.
It's on fire.
No, it's not.
It's good.
End it, end it, end it, end it, end it.
Oh, we need to get another track up there?
Oh, shit.
We don't have enough to do anything.
But you are doing something.
We have three.
Exactly.
It's fun.
They are, yeah.
You're stopping me from sleeping and eating.
Right now, Dino's like,
we could have had the engine if you wanted to save.
Train speed is critical.
What does that mean?
Produces dynamite.
Yeah, just wait until next train.
I know, I'm just reading.
I just wanted to see what they were.
Okay.
To try hard.
Get everything ready.
Great.
Our bridges have too much stone and no wood.
Yeah, that's actually happening right now.
Auto picker could use wood.
We could use wood.
Bring up.
We're going to get stuck.
We're stuck.
It's okay.
Auto miner is going to free it up.
We don't have any wood.
Who has the axe?
Who's got the axe?
I'm using the axe up here on the only trees.
Uh-oh.
This is where it gets bad.
Literally no trees.
Just bring the wood back.
There's so much stone all over the ground.
I'm like accidentally picking it up.
Move, move, move, move, move, move, move, move, move, move.
Dark, dark, dark, dark.
Oh my God.
Oh, what are you doing?
Dark, dark, dark, dark, dark, dark.
It's actually easier to see now than when there's fog.
We don't even need the axe right now.
Where's our bucket?
I got it.
I'm keeping one eye on that bucket.
Don't you worry.
Kill those bandits.
Fire.
All right.
I'm going to mine the stone over here.
We need a bolt though.
We still have three bolts.
Do we get them quickly on the level?
Yeah, you get one when you win.
All right, well, let's just can it.
Let's kill it.
Alex, grab bucket.
Branding two.
Grab what?
Bucket.
Okay, refilling it.
All right, let's take the opportunity to
stack up a bunch of shit so we don't lose it.
Let's have like a mile of track ready to go.
I want to be strong.
All right, right.
Yeah, the snow piercer video game.
It's time for us to get a new train engine.
Hi, hi, hi, dude.
I hope that train engine goes even slower.
It's probably going to be like twice as fast.
Train speed.
It resets the speed.
That wasn't really clear until now.
So the train just starts going faster until you upgrade the engine.
That doesn't really make sense.
Train speed is at 0.185.
New biome.
To Bob-omb.
There's two bolts above us.
I'm going to dig up that way.
We should take the train up.
Move those tracks so we can go up and get the bolts.
Uh, it's too late.
That's too late.
We need the wood tonight.
New biome.
This is tropical.
I think this is tundra.
All right, everyone grab a stack of track and we need to start moving it forward.
Too much track.
Those bolts, though.
Those bolts look so scrumptious.
Also, we need to mine up here.
I got it.
I'll take it.
I know it's on the bolts.
Don't worry.
We need the wood chopping up here.
Can I get one more right here?
Actually, yeah, that's fine.
The bolts, did he get them?
Hey, it's me.
I'm the mobile point.
Oh.
And there's the save point.
Look at that.
I have a small problem where if you do not be on the left side of the train,
you're going to get stuck.
There's so many tracks.
Does the auto miner have, uh,
We don't need any more, uh, resources.
Wait, wait, wait.
This is the cactus station?
This has got to be the new biome.
Yeah.
It has a save above its head.
We're good.
Take everything you can.
Well, locked open here, so.
Man, we're not even yelling at each other anymore.
What are you doing?
What are you stupid?
What an idiot.
We should probably get storage.
Yeah, we need one of these storage.
What was the comment from before?
It's like, oh, they know what they're doing now.
Resident sleeper.
What it shows you the way and why is it only one?
Okay.
I didn't mean to do that.
Just.
I am the one.
Where are we going with this?
Oh, we have to go down there because of the.
I'm just don't.
This is not, don't.
It's not my, this is not my thing.
This is not my bag.
You know what I mean?
What?
We had a little extra track there for no reason.
I actually was doing it right.
I need to be more assertive.
We've got a lot of extra tracks, so.
Should be more assertive.
This is going to be a little weird over here.
Is the auto miner really not mining this?
Just do it faster.
Auto miner like kind of sucks.
Don't forget the water.
Wherever it is.
There is a top left.
Hey, I almost got the achievement engineer.
I've hit, I've destroyed 701 blocks out of 10,000.
So good at this game.
Don't leave that water bucket up there.
I was almost going to eat dinner,
but then it was literally the endless game mode.
Just one more endless mode.
Hey, can you come back and mine above it?
We're doing so good, guys.
We're doing so good.
Yeah, we're doing great in the endless mode.
All right, what do we need, what do you need me to do?
What do you need me to do?
Track is up.
Wood bridge.
Or we can just go around, but a wood bridge is just easier.
We need a wood cutter.
I will handle that.
I'll handle that.
Who's the founder of my bucket?
Is it just me or is this endless?
Yes, that is what you signed up for.
Can you stop bumping?
It totally knocks my stuff off.
I did offer you to order you and all your friends a pizza.
Order me a pizza.
What kind of pizza do you want?
Uh, me a pizza?
I have a pizza.
We have one tree up here that needs to be chopped.
And he's very close to getting the golden ticket.
We've got plenty of time.
We need to chop these cacodice.
We've got time.
All right, I will get it.
Who's got the axe?
Uh, Dino has axe?
No, Penguin has axe.
He did.
He just dropped it.
Bring it on.
All right, stack all the track and put out the fire.
Where's the bucket?
Who has the bucket?
You do.
Just end it.
Damn it.
Oh, it's not going to explode.
He has to stay.
All right, get a pizza.
Put it on the German 985 tab.
I don't want a pizza, Germa.
Order a sandwich from SubSandwich.
Germa, I'm on the road to commander.
What does that mean?
You know, you don't know what the road to commander is.
Wait, what about the ghost?
We're getting stack grabber level three.
It has extra range and plus one stack size.
SubSandwich TM.
Don't worry, Star.
It looks like it's getting hard for us.
And as you know, we're not very good.
It's really not hard at all anymore.
It's not hard at all.
Stop.
EG.
I like this music.
Sounds like a grandfather clock.
Oh, never mind.
We need a woodcutter.
That's me.
I got it.
I'm getting a sandwich from Subway.
I know.
I try not to.
Who would do that?
Can we just chop these?
All three of us are like standing here.
Well, if you don't chop it, you can't go around.
Dude, somebody has to deal with those.
Somebody has to deal with those peanuts.
We're walking around each person just standing,
holding track, waiting to place them.
There's an infinite amount of track being created.
When do I get upgrades to my teams?
Don't forget those.
Don't forget that bucket.
And don't forget helping me with these beandits.
And fuck your beandits.
Uh, we need to go north, I think.
East.
And take the bridge.
I told you not to leave.
I told you not to leave the bucket.
And you didn't listen to me.
I mean, where's the bucket?
I haven't.
I don't care where the bucket is.
I don't care.
Okay, I give up.
You win.
Can we get more bridges?
I'm just on wood duty.
This is wrong.
We can dig down.
Go down.
No, not okay.
Well, you just made that harder.
You know, we're good.
You guys gotta leave space on either side.
Did you get that achievement?
We're gonna get stuck.
Done.
What, you want a pizza, too?
We're done.
Just a second.
It's gonna explode.
This bucket.
You guys gotta have some foresight.
Have some foresight.
It's Alex.
This is really easy.
We have 40 tracks.
Our train is auto-destroying everything.
It's auto-collecting everything it destroys.
Guys, so easy.
You won't mind if I go ahead and complete this.
Please explode.
All right, let's upgrade.
No, wait, number four.
Increases the efficiency of neighboring wagons.
I don't think we need any more efficiency.
We are as efficient as we can get.
I think we could be more efficient.
Why not get another storage cart?
Please put it in the correct space in your rush.
Dinosaur's having a fit.
Oh, it really is the second storage cart.
Oh, two storage carts.
I thought it was an upgrade, but it does say new wagon.
Do you want to live so much, baby?
Baby, you should just do it on your own because I'm fucking...
Okay, what is going on with these?
I'm gonna address my stream at the moment.
Co-op game.
Person you're playing with hates the thing you're doing.
This is happening again.
I got guilted by my mom to keep playing the train game twice.
I think I got guilted twice.
I just keep letting, I'm a pushover.
Mom probably thinks this is really cute and fun.
How many comments about the dinosaur have been made, do you think?
What?
How many comments about like,
oh, this is so cute for the dinosaur.
Do you think it's gonna happen?
What are you talking about?
I'm talking about once since you've kept playing,
we've gotten a new party member who's this awesome,
cute dinosaur that is really effective.
By the way, the reason why this is probably so easy
is because we have the dinosaur buddy.
I mean, yeah, even if he sucked, it would be 33%.
Well, if he sucked, really bad.
Please explode, please explode.
No one is even using tools.
And you're gonna tell me,
do you think endless mode is gonna end soon?
Do you think it's gonna change dramatically
if we went to an entirely different biome?
Guess what changed?
Well, we're about to do it again.
And this has gotten a little more difficult.
This is the easiest one yet.
Well, there's no trees.
So we need a lot of chops, fast.
I got it.
Because we need to build bridges.
But you don't.
Now the station looks like a cactus.
That's pretty cool.
You don't think that's cool?
All right.
Listen, I'm just very hungry, very tired.
Oh, why don't you just call in?
And I want to be able to drown.
No, I'm on the road to commander.
What are you talking about?
What do you mean the road to commander?
What does that mean?
What game is commander?
You're playing League?
Do you really not remember that?
League of Legends?
Oh my God.
Are you playing?
That was the original YouTube
on the actual machinima channel thing to do.
To record your road to commander
and call of duty, which was like max level.
Oh, okay.
Oh, now it sounds.
Now I get it.
Okay, now I get why he spent
this much time saying road to commander.
Now it makes sense.
Can you get inside the lines?
No, I'm going to bed.
Well, this is tier three.
New biome incoming.
It's a snow biome.
And I know you love these snow levels.
It's just trees.
He did love the ice in the last game.
Yeah, I remember that.
He did.
It's the same thing, Ed.
Okay, I'm desperately trying to fix this.
Does it go faster over ice?
I don't know.
It's the same thing.
What does that ever stop you from playing?
I don't know.
That was so sad.
Yeah, the slippery ice.
Dino's clearing ice though.
You walk slower on it.
Oh, don't get stuck back here.
We need that pickaxe.
Are we going up and right?
Or which way are we going?
I think...
Just go that way, go that way, go that way.
Just go the way you're going.
Oh, why is it respawning?
There's snow coming back.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Where's the...
Where's my tool?
What is going on?
Who sprinted?
My tools.
The ash really doesn't even make you go faster.
It does though.
All right, turn it out.
Turn it down here.
The snow is fucking me up.
I can't even get rid of the snow.
I believe that is its intended purpose.
Oh, I...
There's the bucket, bucket, water bucket.
What stir won't talk to me for a month, says my mom.
Lol.
And she says lol.
I don't know what this means.
Lol.
Call your mother.
Don't craft any tracks for 40 seconds.
Apparently, we did an achievement.
All right, but we do need stone in here like pretty soon.
I'm just mining it.
There's not much else.
The stone is not really that...
What do you mean we're stuck?
What do you mean?
We're dead.
We lose.
No, we're not.
What?
How?
We can't get through.
I can't break that.
I can't break it.
Oh, I can, I can, I can, I can.
Dino, dino, dino, dino, dino.
Down to me.
Track, dino.
Oh no, I'm stuck.
And then I was the one who saved it of all people.
And built the back way bridge.
You had the opportunity to like get out of here.
But you chose.
You chose to put that track down.
You could have been like, oh no, no, no, no.
Oh, I didn't get there.
Oh, wow.
There was nothing that could be done.
You could have done that.
That could have been you.
All right, which ways?
I don't even know what's mine.
Right ahead.
How do we even get over here?
This is, we need to, we need path.
We need wood.
How do we, we can't get up there.
Oh, right in the down.
Get the bridge.
Yeah, we get a bridge.
The fuck out of my way.
I don't think we can do this, guys.
I mean, it's pretty buried in there.
Is that, we need the axe.
Pickaxe, I don't even know who has it.
I'm dashing.
Out of my way.
I don't think we can do this.
The music stopped and it stopped.
And it stopped for anyone else ominous much.
That's just where the.
All right, I got it.
It's clear.
It's a save point.
Look, dude, fuck it.
Let's just go to the next biome.
Let's just see it all.
Cool.
Let's save and come back tomorrow.
We're not going to do that.
All right.
Doesn't the steam from the engine melt the snow or something?
No, don't, don't, don't.
Why would you do that?
Why would you just do that blindly?
What?
You don't want dynamite.
We got an extra.
We got three wagons we could add.
Nope.
Let's add like a new engine.
No, no, no, no.
No.
Hello.
I want to see the.
I want to see the new biome.
It's lava.
He called it.
Pumpkin scary.
Wow.
I bet.
All right.
If I get bumped into by Jerma one more time,
I'm going to quit before Stardust.
Isn't that the gold?
Okay.
This is different.
This is slightly different.
This just turns your head.
It's a good thing that I, I don't know,
have an IQ greater than one and thus I can compensate.
I'm pretty sure some root vegetables have IQs of one.
So, I mean, that's not even accurate.
But I just mean I have at least one.
That's what you need.
And vegetables could definitely succeed at the.
That's all I'm saying.
Yeah.
When they got three other dinosaurs carrying,
they don't have to show up for work because they ate too much glue.
How could there be water here?
And like, it's cool.
It's lava.
It's orange water.
Uh oh.
I can't fit.
Oh, I wonder if we got dynamite if we could blow up that rock.
Maybe.
Where's the bucket?
What's wrong?
That's in the front.
We got it.
Okay.
I mean, that's all.
Oh, you can't build bridges.
Um, why is it going?
What?
I'm dead.
Why are we dead?
Is that the dream?
Why are we, why are we parachute?
What?
Oh, you're on it.
Oh, I don't.
Yeah, we got exploded.
Is that the grim reaper?
It was weird looking.
I couldn't tell what it was.
Well, I was confused though,
because I couldn't build a bridge, but we would need to there.
Ah, that's so funny.
Lava biome too hard.
I got temporarily cocks.
All right, guys, you know, that was a great fun night.
I had a lot of fun, but I can't wait to just stuff my face.
My road to commander continues.
That was fun.
Yeah.
I like the train game.
The train game is fun.
Train game is fun, but train game may be too easy with four people.
I like the other game too,
but I also would kind of just rather play overcooked too.
They're almost the same.
And one has cheeseburgers, right?
You could, you could set it to heart.
Yeah, we could have set it to hard.
Have you played it overcooked?
Yes.
Oh, I haven't played it.
It's basically the moving game, but with food.
I like food.
You would probably really like that game.
I feel like you'd be that the remember House of Dead Ninjas.
Remember how you like got obsessed with that
and you got the world record for one at one point.
I still have it.
You still have the world record for a Super House of Dead Ninjas.
I had to get it back at one point, but I have it again now.
Okay.
Because I feel like that's one of those games that you would just,
okay, I'm just going to beat every game at every level as fast as I can.
I don't know.
And I would have to play the game.
Well, look at how far we got.
We did get very far.
That was just a nice nostalgia watching that.
That was fun.
Okay.
All right.
Name reveal.
We got the name reveal.
They got out quick.
Got out real fast.
Name reveal.
I'm out.
All right.
Goodbye, Star.
Thanks for playing.
Thanks for streaming.
Thanks for watching Star's chat.
Oh, he's already gone.
He's already dead.
Well, that was fun.
Yep.
That was good.
I'll let you get to your...
I'll let you say bye to your stream, but say bye to mine.
I'll say bye to yours.
So just before we go.
Sure.
I just wanted everybody to know how often and frequently
Jerma has been asking me to play Halo recently.
I was just trying to figure out if...
Yeah, I just haven't.
I haven't played it.
So I was looking for like someone to play it with.
And I was just like kind of throwing some lines up
to see if anybody had played it yet.
It's been like every day though.
Well, since about two days ago.
I wanted to wait a few days after it came out just to check it out.
Halo with the Dino.
Yeah.
Come on in Dino.
Three person Halo.
Dude, I don't even know who that person is.
He left before I could even see his name.
It's Styrr's mom.
Now that would be very, very interesting.
All right.
Bye everyone.
Yeah.
Thanks a lot for playing, Talix.
If you don't follow Talix or Styrr, they both stream.
They both were streaming.
Take care, Talix.
See you soon.
I'll play Reach with you, Jerma.
I'm playing it right now.
Yeah.
That's probably what we'll call it there tonight.
And that will conclude the non-canon co-op week.
You know something I did not think I was ever going to see
is I looked over here quite a few times
and I saw a lot of Nancy Drew demands.
I'm actually, I'm surprised.
I am very surprised by this.
But just know that I do have a ton of them.
So hey, anytime that there's something, nothing to do
and I'm just like, what do I want to do?
Maybe you might say it again.
Of course you will because I bought them.
But that's what we'll call it tonight.
And you will see me again.
I have this weekend.
I have actually Otto has to go in for a surgery.
Otto has surgery.
He's getting his teeth cleaned
and he also is getting a small little growth removed from his knee.
So take care of Otto.
It's very, very small.
Tooth removal?
No, no, no, just teeth cleaning.
I've worded that wrong.
He's getting his teeth cleaned
and then they're going to remove a small growth on his knee.
There you go.
Brushing your teeth is not surgery.
The other one is.
But you'll see me again.
I did make a promise that I have to keep
and that promise is on Tuesday we're going to start with DOS.
We're going to do another DOS night.
I did say I have to at least have my word be real
for some of the things I said.
We're going to go back to DOS on Tuesday.
Tuesday.
There's apparently been a ton of new additions.
Check it out.
Am I leaving?
Yeah, that's what I'm going to call it.
That was the plan tonight.
We had these two games lined up.
Play Ultima 4 maybe.
No, we did Nancy Drew last night.
Can't do two Nancy Drews in a row.
Got to space it out a little.
That was a lot of fun.
I think Train Game was...
I think they were equally as interesting.
I think Train Game was a little more engaging in a way.
But not really.
I mean, they're both fun.
That was Tools Up.
Which, by the way, if you're going to buy Tools Up,
just be really aware of this.
There's no online multiplayer.
You have to do Steam Remote Play.
That's the only way you get it to work.
Or Couch Co-op.
So if you're like, oh, I wanted to play that with one of my friends.
Oh, you'll get it.
You have to do the Remote Play.
That was not online.
This one is on rail.
This one is online.
And it was pretty fun.
I think this is an early access.
This just came out in early access, didn't it?
It's pretty good.
But we'll see you in a few days.
Tuesday, to be exact.
I'm going to go take care of Otto.
I will give him all of your love and mine.
This looks like an awesome mobile game.
Yeah, but isn't an awesome mobile game just a good game, you know?
That's not, it's all right.
It was fun.
No.
But thanks again for watching.
See you Tuesday.
We'll do the bits.
I have to get this train sound off my computer.
Because it's still just here to exit the game.
Back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back.
Quit.
It's still playing.
There we go.
All right.
Let's go back about where were we?
Four, five hours?
Five hours ago.
Where were we at?
I'm actually surprised that Steam Remote Play held up that well.
I guess you just, you have to have a good connection to the people that you're playing with.
And the three of us are in a, you know, that Southwest sort of location.
I wonder how bad that would be if I would play with somebody from the East Coast or from Europe.
It would probably be horrible.
Maybe.
I don't know.
I don't have any experience with it, so.
But thank you to extra cheesy for the 500 bits.
What you didn't know was that I was the true player one this entire time.
I was controlling you, controlling the game, controlling their streams.
Just as right now I'm controlling you to read this.
I am Shrek and the universe is my onion, not yours.
I don't understand that last sentence, but thank you for the 500 bits.
Abomination zero.
Thanks to the 250.
Hygermia streams mean a lot to me.
My home life can be pretty shitty, but you make the nights more fun.
Don't ever change.
I don't really plan on it.
And I think I don't think I have the mental capacity to be able to do it.
So I really appreciate that.
Thank you so much for the 250.
Hopefully that home life can improve.
Thanks a lot for the 250.
Abomination zero.
Coldest fridge.
Thanks for the 500 bits.
Hey, Jerma, I hope you didn't forget what day it is today.
I did not.
We'll address that in a few minutes, though.
We'll address that in a few minutes.
It's a birthday today.
How old are you again?
How old are you?
19.
No, no, right.
Do you remember we tried to figure that out?
It's also my dad's birthday.
Happy birthday to your dad, too.
Hope you've been such a good boy this year.
Thanks for the 500 bits.
Happy fucking birthday.
To everybody that has a birthday today.
Not just one person.
How many people actually have a birthday here today?
Let's see.
One, two, three, four, five.
Quite a lot of us, actually.
Thanks for the 500 bits.
I don't forget.
I mean, I always forget,
but as long as I'm reminded every single day,
I will not forget if each day I'm told not to forget
until the day that it happens.
Thanks for the 500 bits.
Appreciate it.
Your birthday's tomorrow.
Happy birthday tomorrow.
I have to be reminded every day.
That's ADHD.
Yes, it is.
DarkSoul250, thanks for the...
DarkSoul, thanks for the 250.
Even though this week isn't real
and we're all in comas, it's been a lot of fun.
I'll see you all when we wake up.
Also, my mother legitimately wanted to know
why it took you eight hours
to beat a Nancy Drew game, by the way.
Because it was a long-ass game.
Midnight in Salem.
How long...
It's like a 10-hour game.
How long to beat Nancy Drew in Salem?
Nancy Drew...
Salem.
What's it called?
How long is Nancy Drew...
No, that's not right.
Midnight in Salem.
I'm the only person that's beaten the game,
so it's a seven-and-a-half-hour game.
But thank you, DarkSoul250, appreciate it.
UtopiaFox gave 10 community subs.
I think I missed one of them,
but I tried to catch them both.
That's the one thing when you stream
and you play with other people
and there's more than one person,
you have to find that minute
where you can just mute everybody
and then they go, what are you doing?
And it's like, I'm talking...
Hey, pick up...
What are you doing?
Are you stupid?
I'm trying to...
So it's easy to miss some stuff.
I'm sorry.
But thank you, Cole, KaoLegacy,
and UtopiaFox.
I think I got them,
but I'm just making sure.
Both the 10 community subs, appreciate it.
And we're talking about them.
Why don't we show them all?
Thank you so much, everybody, for your subs.
Really appreciate it.
Hey, that hurt.
I'm sorry, dude.
I'm sorry I didn't mean to bump you.
But again, thank you for subbing to this channel, as always.
We had a couple more bits come in.
We had TalksRay for 250.
Dingo the Dinosaur for Jerma Rumble, Jerma Venus.
We'll see.
Hey, DubskiDude, thanks for the 250.
Hey, Jerma, please don't ban me for this.
But I had to make a Reddit thread
about all the questionable stuff
you've been doing lately.
The thread got 700 upvotes and a few awards.
So I'm not the only one
who is concerned about your behavior.
I'm not subbed, so I can't link it.
But just look for the thread title
What's With All The Jerma Controversies.
I don't want to spread drama.
I really don't.
But someone has to say it.
I hope you can get back on track.
Hey, guys.
Oh, my God.
This is like, this is a long page.
Hey, guys, I'm kind of new to this community.
And I was really enjoying watching Jerma's content.
But I keep seeing talk of a bunch of controversies
he's been in.
It's weird because Jerma's a likable down-to-earth guy.
So it really doesn't make sense to me.
I'll list what I've been seeing lately so we can discuss.
Jerma regularly forces chat to sit through ad breaks.
I guess this one isn't so bad
because he does have to put food on the table.
But I'm not sure why Jerma drops so many ad breaks
when he already gets a ton of bits and subs.
He just randomly throws an ad break in whenever he wants.
I think one time he kept doing them over and over
and only stopping people started leaving.
He also doesn't.
Oh, so now this is real.
Okay, I get it.
This is a, okay.
That running ads in a row until people left.
I'm like, when did I do that?
Jerma's acting toxic towards his fans,
calling them stupid fucking idiot,
dumb fucking goddamn idiots.
Motherfuckers.
And threatening to permanently ban people over nothing.
I think I might have seen a few people get banned for outright
for just recalling him short, which is rude.
But perma-banning is overkill.
This is just a, what the fuck?
Jerma encouraging his fans to spam comment threads
that he beat Dark Souls 3 on stream.
I have firsthand experience seeing people do this
on Reddit, YouTube, and MySpace.
So I know that's likely true.
All right, that one's true.
But no, but the only true part about that is
I said if somebody ever says Jerma died to Pinwheel,
which is a lie, then you need to counteract that
with no, he didn't, he beat Dark Souls 3 on stream.
That's all I said.
I didn't say to go spamming him.
Why would I say that?
I'm saying if you see counteract the complete false misinformation.
Jerma was doing cruel IRL pranks.
I remember one time Jerma did a video where he bought
a bunch of cakes and threw them at random dock workers.
I guess it was supposed to be a reference to TF2.
He ended up hitting a guy right in the face
and it dazed him to where he couldn't walk straight.
It was really graphic.
Jerma talking about his personal fetishes on stream.
Like getting his chest hairs plucked with tweezers and CBT.
And eating.
I personally wasn't around for that stuff,
but it sounds like it was gross.
Some people are just really open, okay?
Talk shit about his best friends
and scams them out of a lot of money.
I remember Starr and Jerma collabs.
It's really sad to see they had split up,
but I didn't know that Jerma had stolen money from him.
Dude, if you would just, there are so many just lies
in this community.
It's like, there's nobody can know the truth now.
There's so many falsehoods.
Even coming from me too.
Jerma harassing a streamer called GrillmasterXBBQ.
I only caught the last half of the incident,
but Jerma seriously went off the rails
and was talking mad shit about him.
I don't even know who he was until he went ape shit on him.
I think Twitch admins might have told Jerma to lay off.
Jerma burning a live Wasp on stream.
That was fake CGI.
Everyone in the comments is talking about how much of a psycho I am.
Okay, down in the comments threads.
I also find it idiotic that he tried to copyright the planets
of the fucking solar system.
Like, what are you, what?
Glad that shit got shot down right away.
But seriously, what kind of freak thinks
he can just copyright planets?
Delusional much?
Anyway, his stupid juke spamming fans pretend to be...
This is like all...
I heard he also killed Glooman.
Glooman's still alive, so that's not real.
I love this post.
I'm calling it now.
Someone thirsty for drama is going to read this post
and take it seriously and then make a YouTube video on it
without realizing it's satire.
This does have 700 uploads, though.
Here, if you want to go through...
If you want to go through all the horrible things I've done
in my career, there it is.
And that was DubskiDude.
Thank you, DubskiDude.
Where's my apology?
I'll see you guys on Tuesday.
Public apology required now.
That was not a good apology.
Okay, sure, guys.
I'm sorry for the made-up things about me.
But doesn't that happen in a lot of apologies?
Guys, I just got to tell you, I'm sorry,
but all these things are made up about me.
That does happen.
That just happens.
Guys, just want to hit you with some stuff going on.
I want to just say I'm very sorry
for the way that you all feel about me
and how none of it's real.
It's not true.
Sorry.
All right.
Everyone deserves a second chance.
Thank you.
Thank you, MessingY.
See you guys on Tuesday.
Thanks for watching the week of non-canon streams.
Some of those could be retroactively canon, I think.
Maybe one or two of them.
What was it, four?
Last four days in a row?
Maybe two of those were canon.
Good night, guys.
See you Tuesday.
I'm not going to turn the stream off yet
because it's at four hours and 59 minutes.
And I want this to be a five-hour stream.
Because that's just going to bug me.
Padding your stats by 20, 30 seconds.
Add it to the list of controversies.
You gaming analytics now.
All right.
Good night, guys.
See you Tuesday.
Real quick, C4G, thanks for the 250.
The company that made House Flipper
and Car Mechanics in me later
appeared to be publishing a Jesus game.
It has a Steam page, but the trailer looks like
it's a fake game from a Coke commercial.
What?
All right, goodbye.
Goodbye.
No, I'm out of here.
I am Jesus...
Am Jesus Christ is the name of the game.
No, I don't want to show this trailer.
Because I want to be...
I don't want to know anything about this.
Nope.
No, no, no, no, no.
If you want to look, go for it.
I don't want to.
Nope.
I don't want to see a damn thing about this.
I've skipped 10 seconds into that trailer
and I immediately do not want to see anything else.
No way.
Whenever that comes out,
we're gonna have to think about playing that one.
Thank you, C4G, for the 250.
And look, it's 501, which is somehow worse than 459.
God damn it.
All right, see you Tuesday.
Goodbye.