What? I'm trying to... I'm trying to do the thing. I'm trying to be a streamer. I'm trying to be a
streamer that has an intro play from one to a minute. We talked about this like a few days ago.
I'm trying to... All right, listen to me. Everybody that you watch on Twitch, I want... you know,
I want to get like an assessment, you know? What's the average starting soon screen time? I'm curious.
This is... no, this is important. What? 15 minutes? 15 minutes? Okay. I'm seeing a lot of 15 minutes.
10 minutes? 20 minutes? It's like 10 to 20 minutes? Okay. Zero minutes to an hour.
Pre-stream chat is that for you? Well, my question is, so if I'm late by 10 to 20 minutes,
at half the streams, aren't I just starting when most people would start usually after
a starting soon screen? Thinking phase, you know? No, because you don't wait for the notifications.
Oh, shit. Am I right? You're right. No, you're right. No, I had to take it on the phone. All right,
so the last couple days, I've had phone calls that have come in that are just like,
well, you have to answer this or your life is gonna fuck up. Oh, okay. I'm gonna answer that
phone call. I've had like two answer this or else phone calls in the last two days. No, it's not a
scam caller. That'll sound like fake calls to me. Anyways, how you doing, guys? Welcome back. We're
gonna play Black and White again, as you see on the title and from the tweet. Where we left it
last night is an actually pretty sad spot. Not a nice spot. Our new cow friend who we made last
night, the cow's name, by the way, is Murius. If you were not part of the pre-stream chat,
he's curious, he's a little furious, and he's a cow. He's Murius. Furious Murius. You can also say
curious Murius when he's doing something that's not so mean. Mald and Murius. Minus two. Hype train
incoming. What the fuck was that? What was that? You will have a limited time to earn exclusive
emotes. What is this? What's going on? Hype train at 82%. What the fuck is this? Sub gift or use bits
to get to the next level. What? I don't know what this is. Is this new? 100% we did it, apparently.
Hooray. Hype. I don't know what that was. I didn't enable this. This is like a birthday part. Level
one complete. Level two hype train. Okay, what is this, Twitch? I don't, what, we have five
minutes to do this? This is so, this is so obvious. I don't know what the fuck this is. I swear to
God. I was like talking about my cow. Wait, hold on, people are just giving a shit load of subs right
now. What the fuck? Hold on. Hype train. Hype. What is going on? What do you mean level two complete?
How many levels are there? No, there's three, there's more than three levels?
Level three hype train. Can I, I can click this button? Completing level three requires
hype conductors. What the, what is a hype conductor? This is like a train conductor,
a current hype train tops level three emotes. Wait, you're unlocking emotes like these weird
train monsters? We just got to level five? What level are we? Okay, hold on. I can't even keep
up with how many people just subbing right now. All right, you got more emotes. Thanks for the hype
train. I don't know if we've been selected to test a new feature, but apparently we're testing it.
Uh, level four hype train. Okay, at some point we have to get off of the train.
Sub gift. All right, let me see what this even is supposed to be for. Oh my God. All right,
guys, I, it never stops. No, it has to stop at some, you can't ride a train this fast.
75% level four. Oh man. Level wages. Dead. Level four hype train.
All right. All right. So now that's it, right? Now we can, did we do it? Level four complete.
I'm going to look this, I'm going to look this up. Hold on.
Hype train Twitch. I feel like I'm going to get like a bunch of compilation videos.
Hype train guide. I can't fucking believe this is happening so close to
the new year's Eve stream. Hype train incoming. Hype train is a super size celebration when
community members unite to support a streamer that they love. Well, thank you guys. It challenges
the community to reach epic levels of hype and reward. But when did this start? Oh my fucking
God. This is like, you, you've Twitch, you've gamified hype meters now. Oh my God.
So many subs and bits are coming in. I can't even fucking comprehend. I can't even, I,
we got to go to the beginning here. I haven't even done an intro yet. Hype. You did it.
Level five. It has to stop somewhere. Look, what does it, what does it say?
What does it say for? All right. You did it. We did it. You did it. You did a level five hype train.
135%. There ain't going over this. 140. I mean, it doesn't stop. Well, there's three minutes.
150%. You guys are fucking crazy, man. Well, that's an interesting feature.
It just activates when, holy shit. You guys don't even have to do this. You already unlocked level
five. You got, you're at 175%. You don't even have to do this anymore. You've already, we've
hyped ourselves into, into outer space. You did it. I just wish it wasn't called hype train.
Cause it is like, it does the hype thing at the top. Can I customize that so it doesn't say hype?
Can it say, I don't even know. Almost 200%. Two minutes until this clock runs out and,
and I get subbed and gifted another two to 300 times. Thank you guys. I did not know this feature
was even coming through, but just remember, I'm going to be very clear about this. The ridiculous,
insane, like top 30 on Twitch in sub numbers, top 40 on Twitch in sub numbers. And
incoming money. I'm going to fucking use it. I'm going to use it for this stream. I promise you,
a million percent, 246% of this experimental feature. He's going to use it on cocaine.
I don't do drugs. If I pissed in the wee, I don't do drugs. It's a monumental task
for me to even thank any of you. I, it's so, it's, this is like, it has to be one of the most
generous supportive communities on Twitch. It has to be. I can't even begin to tell you how much I
can say thanks. Honest to God, it's, it has to be up in the top 20. It has to be. The hype train
is at 333%. Get it to 420. 400%. This is the shit you didn't even need to do. Here it comes.
The clock is running out at 350. Hype train success. Okay. Now there's the, such strong support.
Level five completed. Now what do you all get? 182 subs at 24,000 fucking bits. What in the name
of God? We're delivering emotes. You guys have emotes now? Great work. Emotes are being delivered
to supporters. Hype unicorn three. What even are these? Can I customize those? All right,
if I can customize those, I'm going to make them fucking, I can't, no. Make a hype cow.
Once again, everybody, I can't even, my brain has trouble with this shit because I can't even
fathom something like this happening. And I just want, I just want to have fun. I just want,
I just want us to have fun together as a group of people. I just want, that's it. That's all
I care about. You know what I mean? Like it's hard for me to even say thanks because I don't
even know what to fucking do. It's just like ridiculous. I hope you fucking have fun. I really
do. Let's, let's have some fun. Somebody gave 20, Furious Bear 20 subs. We're going to, there's
going to be a long outro tonight. I will tell you because there was a, there was $50 too. There's
like $50 like five times. Holy shit. Somebody gave 100, 200 where? AB Joe gave 5,000 bits. They
said keep going. That's, so how do you, how does that even happen? Is it just random? Well, Twitch,
if you just released this and you'd like to get some beta feedback, here it is. Like there you are.
You just got a bunch of it. But thank you, AB Joe 5,000. Oh my God. That's the loudest one of the
year. Clip that one. That has to be the lot. That's the loudest room that's ever happened.
Seriously, like I won't even need a category. That was next to the window. Fiddy, thanks for
the 5,000 bits. I'm pogging so hard right now. You guys are fucking too much. Well,
top fucking goddamn 40. Top 30. Let's go. Let's go. Let's, let's, let's, let's take this whole
fucking website over. You know what I mean? Let's go. Let's, let's, let's, let's do it.
You guys should get fucking hyped for this channel. You should fucking feel excited for it,
especially considering we're about to play black and white for like another eight hours.
Oh, whoa, whoa. What are you doing? No, but for real, for real, for real, for real.
Oh yeah. Here we go. Everybody. Let's go hype trade. Hype me up. German 985. Okay. I mean like
that's over here. What's that thing? Oh, that's a tree. I need more of those. Yeah. Put that over
Adam, Adam laughing my ass off gave a fucking hundred dollars right now. Thanks for the,
thanks for the 10,000 bits, dude. Well, that was an interesting first 15 minutes of the stream.
We've been in the middle of the intro. What were we talking about? I don't know. What were we
talking about? It was something important. It was the cow. Oh yeah. The cow's name is Murius.
Murius. The cow and everyone, I got a lot of shit for that name. People like, oh, Murius,
come on. Like curious, furious, whatever. Yeah. But you know what the number one suggestion was
last night? I looked over here and you know what it was? It's mega milk. So I think my name might
have been like a tad better than the number one suggestion. All right. But oh, that's right.
Those of you that weren't here last night, we have, that's a sad tale right now. While I was
going off on the sad tale on the intro, Murius was captured and is being tortured right now
over there. And we have to go save him pretty. Yeah. And that is what's happening. I am going
to go, I'm going to build up the city. Somebody said last night, I'm going to take this to heart.
They said in direct quotes, when you can look at the logs, they said, LOL, he is not ever going
to beat the third level because he didn't pay attention to one of the most important mechanics.
So I'm going to beat the third level because now I'm ready. I'm going to make sure that I have
shit ready to go. I'm going to pay attention. And I paid attention yesterday too. But anyways,
welcome back everybody. Playing black and white again. All right. So we need wood. Oops. Okay.
We need wood. Where's my wood center? Because these people are all, here's my temple, right? Okay.
I need some, where's my temple going? Why is this much louder? Oh, it's because I've opened the game.
When you open the game and all the volume shit goes crazy. Music is, where's the music? Should
we be getting music? I think I broke the music by like turning it off. All right. That's better.
There we go. Cutting the trees. How much wood do they need? Oh, I can just do this. I can help.
Let's get this temple built. How much more does it need?
3200. Why does it need so much wood? Bring back mega milk. He's, look, I'll show you. He's currently
being tortured right now. You want to see this? You really want to see this? I can't do anything
about this. There he is. But look at that will. He seems pretty chill. It's because he's frozen
in a weird ice thing. And by the way, this motherfucker is dead. Just wait till I train
with Murius and bring him over here. See, look what he's doing. He's just like burning me. I
got to get over there. He's got his hands on his hips. We got a long way to go for the saving of
Murius. There's other towns over here. All right, let's keep going. He does always have that Disney
character. Hands on hips, waving at people. All right, we need 1800 wood. Let's go. I need to
replant some trees. I miss them already. I really do. All right, we got it. We're good. Nice fax
machine. I need to put wood over here. But this shit needs it bad. Did you know? Yeah, yeah. Okay,
this is the store. Somebody, we got to get a builder over here. How many of you guys are builders?
What are you? Going to the forest for wood. No, no, no, no, no, not anymore. You're not. Come over here.
We got to get this shit built up.
Resident builder. Deciding what to do. I can decide for you. Come here. Builders.
All right, we got extra wood. This is extra, right? Yeah. I think that person just fell
off the cliff. Supply this shit. All right, come on. Hurry up. I got to like be efficient here.
Wait, did I just? What? Oh, fuck. That wasn't done. All right, all right, all right. This does not
seem like a good idea. Where are they going? I think, wait, what's this? Oh, I found a wood
miracle. Nice. All right, let's put it, uh, I'm gonna put it over here. Miracle of wood.
All right, I need 751. We'll just drop it in here. Oh, get on that hype train. All right,
somebody build it. Let's, what was that? Is this mine? I think all this shit is mine.
Shut up about the hype train. I'm kidding around. Don't worry. All right, give me that rock.
How much more wood does this need? Scaffold value three. No, I mean like build it then.
What is it? What's, what's taking, what's the hold up? Is it not buildable?
I guess I might have to wait. Rescue mega milk. That's the goal. That's not who that is though.
And I don't care if you keep calling him super milk. His name is Murius and I were not calling
him the thing that you are calling. Let's get a builder over here. Disciple Forester. No, no,
no, no, no, no. Disciple builder. Almost done. Good. Mega milk is easier to spell. It's also
porn from what I've been told. So I know that's not what it is. I mean, no, it's not.
It's not. It is. It's not. It is. Well, is it or isn't it? The last time I said those two words
together out loud, like a few weeks ago, I saw a scene of dude, shoot, shut the fuck up, dude.
You don't know what you're saying. Stop saying this. Shut up, dude. Stop. Like you were nudging
me at like the fucking dinner table. We were in front of your parents and you're like, don't
fucking say that in front of my mom and dad, dude. Are you stupid? So I don't know how much wood we
get. We're running out of wood. Oh, are we? Not anymore. Look at my miracles. Oh, wait, that was
a rock. Fuck. Fix this. Fix it. The village stored is nearly out of food. Fix it. Fix it. He's in
perpetual motion. Oh, no. Fix this. I didn't mean to do that. Oh, god damn it. When am I going to
get? I almost just called him the thing that I'm not supposed to call him. How do I repair
the building? What the fuck, man? All right. It's it's under construction again. All right,
we're good. Wear the shirt. I'm not going to wear the shirt. Hypers. Oh, I can't even.
I can't keep up. I can't keep up. I know. Well, I mean, where's the it's over here.
Is that the only one that has to be more than that around here? Right. I was going to say holy
shit. All right, we've got to we've got to take care of this shit right now. I need a builder.
I need more. All right, take it slow. 80. Fucking idiot. What am I? I'm like bird.
I need more wood for this. Actually, they're they're making food. Not a lot, but they are.
Yeah, they need food right now. I know. I know. I'm working on it. Come over here. Start working
in these fields over here. Disciple farmer. Actually, that's great. I'm actually really
happy. This is perfect. Even if not, if a rival god did this, I don't even care.
You're helping me. All right, we need people to work down here. You work over here. Disciple
farmer. Children's Day. Yeah, I got to fix this though. What is this person doing?
This is a weird spot, isn't it? Oh shit. He was carrying something. He was trying to fix the
orphanage. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. Okay, he was trying to get up there to
fix the orphanage. I got you. I got you. They can't get up here. See, it's in a way, it's in
like a fucked up spot. Can I move this? I didn't put this here. They can't get in. I don't think
they can get in there. It's in a weird angle. Okay, well, I have temple here. All right, let's get
the uh, is this thing almost done? Do they eat this person? All right, then we need food now.
Uh-oh. There's uh, oh, we need. Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay. I need to make, I need a miracle.
I can look for miracles. You're, okay, you're doing food. Who else is doing food? This still
needs to be built. Shitty pathing, too. This is all wrong. I didn't even build this shit. This was
given to me. I would have much better spot. All right. Disciple. No, no, do not breed.
Disciple builder. How much more wood? Zero? Okay, come here. We need people to make food.
Disciple farmer. The shit is so far away from where they need to be. The village store is
nearly out of food. You're running out of trees. I can make trees. Plus, I can steal them. I can
take trees from wherever I want. If the god next door is angry at me. Okay, now I need to do houses.
You're a liar and a thief. I don't see any food. All right, what's down here?
Okay, here's the next town over. Is this a neutral town? This town down here is neutral.
What do you got? They got a lot of food in here. All right, I need to send some people down here.
There's food near the orphanage. Yeah, somebody has to get it though.
That was, this orphanage is fucked up. All right, should I just like take it?
No, no, no, no, no. They have to do this themselves. You come here. Disciple farmer.
We need more farmers. What, what are you guys all up to? Going to farm, going to farm.
Who else? Going to a building site. No, no, no. Farm. Farm instead. Come here.
Disciple farmer. Big bits just came in. More big bits. All right. Crookshire gave 5,000 bits.
Another 50 fucking dollars. And they say this chat is hype. Get over here.
Disciple farmer. Hype. Getting another important phone call.
God damn it. It's going to have to wait. Dancing, dancing, dancing, dancing, dancing.
Where are these people? What is this place? What do you mean dancing? Where are they?
Isn't this the production store? Oh my god. I, I gotta, okay.
Good. More food. Farm. All, everybody farm. Only farm. What's this person? This person,
this is Jeff Keely. What is Jeff Keely doing in this game? Steve Jackson is in this game.
That's the, that's sorcery. Wait, are these all game people? Did somebody just who? Steve Jackson?
Wait, did, okay. I was going to say that was not like, that wasn't Jeff Keely, right? All right.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Forget about this fucking temple. Going to dead person. No. Come
here. No. Stop going to dead person and go get food. Farm. Disciple farmer. Farm. Disciple farmer.
They have to mourn. Age 82. All right. My crea- wait a minute. Am I going to get another creature to
rescue? Are we going to go on a rescue mission with a new creature? Disciple farmer. All right.
Well, thankfully it rains a lot. Water. Food. All right. I need to do this. I need a food miracle.
I need a site. What's that thing called? I need that thing to tell me. I need more wood in there.
What's it called? The thing that makes some worshipers can go worship.
All right. At least there's food in there now. All right. Come on. Build it. I need 4,900 more
wood. All right. It's time to start dumping trees. All right. Done. Where? Wood. Tree dump. I know I'm
ripping up everything here. I know. But I have to start moving. I'm only going to take the big
ones. Not the little ones. I promise. Okay. Is this done? Almost. You're going to have no trees.
I can do a spell that gives me trees. Plus, Murius will probably- doesn't Murius know that spell too?
Oh no. Murius knows wood, right? All right. What is it for? Does anybody remember what it is for
that worship site? Say his name, Jeremy. Who are we talking about? Talking about Murius.
Murius is the- okay. Bear with me here. Say his name, Jeremy. Say his name. Do it. Do it.
How much more wood do I need? At least there's a little dollop of fucking gravy in there. All
right. Is this almost done? How much more does this have to do? I don't want to breed anybody yet. I
don't want any breeding that's going to cause a huge problem. I need to build houses. I need more
wood. My best friend is being tortured. I'm not in a good- I don't like this. But anybody in chat
can help me out here. Don't break it! Okay. Jesus Christ. That was scary. What's the recipe for-
Get my temples done. All right. My influence grows. Okay. Now your temple looks sinister.
It's- I assure you it's not. Oh, what are they doing here? Is this the worship site? It is,
isn't it? All right. Finally. Took long enough. Build that site up. We need to pray- I'm trying.
I'm trying. I need to make a food spell and- Do not get hit by that rock, please. All right. Is it
done? Okay. Here we go. Wow. You did it. Everybody. And I mean everyone. Everyone to the temple. Now,
immediately drop everything you're doing and worship me. Tell me kind things. Tell me I'm smart.
Tell me I'm fun. We're going to have to sacrifice a couple people too. Yeah. Yeah. Who's-
Food! It's already gone. Oh my God. It's already gone. They're so hungry.
I can't- It won't even show up on the ground. We have to sacrifice somebody.
I seriously can't even get it to show up on the ground. All right. Somebody else has to die.
Yay. They're eating it instantly. All right. Who's dead? No. More. All right. Fill it up.
Keep believing. Keep believing. Continue believing in me. I need better fucking- I'm gonna
always be in need of food. More. How's everybody doing? We need food. I know. Uh oh. Okay. All
right. All right. All right. All right. One more and then I'm going to drop it down to like 30%.
Miracle food. I'm going to sacrifice one more person. Okay. That's good. I just dropped the
food over here. Whoops. I'll get it. Back to work. Sacrificing people means less people that need to
eat. This is true, but it also means I have to make sure that I'm not going to be unbreedable.
I don't want to kill everybody. All right. So now we still have these people there.
Give me more food. They switch off, right? What do you mean unbreedable? Like if there's- if I kill
all the men in the area, if I kill all the women, then there ain't going to be any more babies.
That's what I mean. All right. It's time to start growing influence. Everyone. How's everybody doing?
Everyone okay? Going to sleep on the floor. Okay. Now it's time for me to build.
Uh, what are they doing over here? What is Jeff Keeley building? What is this? Is this a game
awards arena? Maybe. He's building a statue of Kojima. What the fuck? Well, is this a house?
Maybe they're doing that on their own. All right. We're okay. I need to make a couple more houses.
Another civic building. All right. It's time to start ripping trees out. I need to build more
shit over here because I need to spread into here and take this place over. I also need this shit
too. I- I feel like this building is not being used. Like it can't be used. Oh, they are. They're
making settlements. What did you guys? Okay. Uh, let's go over here. Let's get some- let's get more
food. I'm going to get this to about 10,000. What's in there now? 4,000. Now do it like two,
three more times. You already forgot about Mega. I did not. Hey Streamer, just letting me know your
face cam is on. Oh, how embarrassing. I need a ton more wood. Where is there a forest I can just
rip out of? Save the cow? To save the cow, I need a strong enough base of followers. I can't just
go save the cow. Damn it. I really need a bunch of more wood. All right. Let's zoom this out so
I can see and just dump it into there. 7,600 wood. I need way more than that. I'll replace it.
How much wood is in there now? 8,300. Okay. I need like 20,000 wood because that's going to help me
build more civic buildings, which is what I need, right? 20,000 and I'm done. And then I'll plant a
fake forest. I'll plant a magic forest eventually. Don't worry. This is all going to get replaced.
Is that a rock? No. All right. What is that? 14,000? Not bad. Not bad. Not bad. Not bad. Not bad.
No complaints yet. Yet. Don't pick the little ones. Only the baby. Here we go. I keep hearing
somebody scream. Who's this monster that keeps fucking screaming? All right. Do food again.
Everybody's taken care of now. I'll do one more food and then I'm out of trees and shit. I'm
going to have to do tree miracles, wood miracles. Your son is screaming in pain.
My son's not a miracle food. All right. Let's start making shit. I need a civic building,
right? I need three. That's two there already. I already have one. So what do I need to do to get
worshippers to be able to help me move out and continue? I hope I'm trapped. I just need more
people. All right. Well, I'm going to do it. I'm going to do a big house. This isn't a boat. All
right. Let's put this. I wish I could make another one of those. I'm going to put this down here so
people can farm easier over here. You know, we're going to make these people over here the farmers.
Workshop. Here we go. All right. How do I cycle between what these are? Graveyard.
Should I make a graveyard of dead people? Do people like that? I need the graveyard.
How do you cycle between this shit? Workshop. No, I don't have enough influence to go that way yet.
How about down here? How did the graveyard down here? But it's not the graveyard yet.
Make another abode. I got to put that in a better spot. I wish I could make a farm over here.
All right. Making an abode. Abode right there. And then another abode right here.
Okay. So now people can actually live here and work here.
It's four scaffolds for a field. Oh, fuck. Okay. Let's do that. Do you put a storm? Get down.
Miracle food. So four and I'll put another field down. Yeah, that's a good idea.
I do need more wood though. Fuck. This game's so fun. All right. I need more wood. Let's do
the wood miracle. What is it? This one. Here it is. I don't have a wood miracle. Uh-oh.
Oh, that's very bad. That's very bad. Miracle food. I have to. This is very bad. Under the
waterfall. This is that dispenser. Oh, right. Yeah. Yeah. I did grab this. You're right.
Okay. How much wood do you need? That's not a whole lot though. That's not a whole lot of wood.
All right. It's four you said, right? We need another field. Oh, no. Maybe I should start
breeding the fuck out of everybody. What do you think? Pick up and replace the trees.
Water.
A miracle shower.
Hold on. Should I just water shit? This is not like Stardew Valley, right? Hey.
Oh, okay. It's four. What should I do here? I have five. Bigger house, civic building,
make a field, make a new village center. What words to make a field? Should I make a field?
Build a streamer house. I'm going to make a field. Here we go. Field. And I'm going to put this
shit. That's only one field. All right. I'm going to put this right. I'm going to put this over here
because this is too far of a walk. And then I'll put, I get to put like a new store building over
there. All right. I'm going to put it right here. That's a, that's a long, that's not, I don't want
that to be a long walk. All right. Food is starting to become a surplus. I have to work. What are you
doing? Don't sleep off. All right. Trees. Trees. I need, did I, did I just fuck this whole play
through because I pulled up all the trees. I can do this. Look, look what I'm doing.
I'm relocating this forest over here. Theft. This is not theft. Maybe not yet. I'm going to water
these trees after and we'll see what happens. Okay. Just let it go. Let it go. Let it go. Stop. Let
it give me. All right. There's only one more. Look at all this over here too. Okay. Miracle of water.
Let's go. All right. Let's see what happens. Do they grow? How are we doing over here? Is my field
done? No one's even started building this yet. Where is everybody? Somebody build this. All right.
Jeff Keighley. Build this. You're going to do it now. Like Jeff Keighley. You're really good at like
building shit. I've already seen you build like two. All right. You don't want to. Just do it.
He doesn't want to. Going to sleep on floor. I need more houses. Holy shit. You live a dangerous
life. Going to sleep on the floor at the edge of the cliff where the waterfall is. Sleeping upside
down. Insane. All right. So. Leave it. I'm not worth it. What just happened? I don't know what
that was. Was that another god? Actor. Is this the person talking? He's rehearsing his lines.
Should I just go get him? All right. I'm going to go get him. Actor. Go on. He's dumb. I got him.
Okay. Now. Breed? I'll do your worst but don't throw me though.
That the game's telling me to throw this person. But no. We're going to. We're going to breed?
Wait. Just what? What? What happened? You big bully. Try it again and you're dead.
Please don't throw me. Oh you big bully. Try it again and you're dead. Please don't throw me.
You didn't kill me. Please don't throw me. Uh. Why are we getting a slow mo cut scene?
Oh hell. You big bully. Try it again and you're dead. Please don't throw me. What?
What is this? Guy getting a special cut scene. Oh hell. Free influence. You didn't kill me.
Please don't throw me. Hey guys. Look at this. He's. Okay. You remember that game. Like kick
the buddy. That old flash game where he's like. Come on. Don't hit me. You like punch him and
poke him and stuff and he gets up and does this. Oh you big. Please don't throw me.
Oh hell. Am I getting points for this? You didn't kill me. Please don't throw me. Watch out lady.
Keep this guy in a box to him. You didn't kill me. Please don't throw me. All right. What do I need
for. How much belief do I need? He keeps flying. Is that him screaming in slow motion? Do it as
far as possible. Oh man. You didn't kill me. Please don't throw me. This actually is just
free influence though. All right. Fine. He's going for a long ride.
Oh you big bully. Try it again and you're dead. Please don't throw me.
What am I supposed to do with this guy? Oh hell. Kill him. I can't. Oh you big bully. Try it again
and you're dead. Please don't throw me. Ladies and gentlemen. The flying man. Are you not impressed
by the skills of the gods? My leg. Just know me. You didn't kill me. Please don't throw me.
I can't. All right. He's coming with me. Come with me. Oh there's a quest. All right. He's
coming with me. How do I lock him somewhere? How do I keep him somewhere? Should I just put a series
of rocks around him? Why would I do that in my own village? Well he's dead. He doesn't.
Feed him. Oh that's right. I'll feed him to the animal. On my arm. All right. Let him. You didn't
kill me. Whatever. He's called actor. There's a scroll over here. What was it? I just saw it
right there. What is that? Ah I see a god. Greetings. I am a guru and a yogi. I am off
to meditate and increase my powers. I have a secret place for this. Please don't follow me there.
That is all. So we follow him there. Right. You know what? Let's follow him. But let's make sure
he doesn't see us. Really. Following yogis isn't my idea of godly behavior. Don't follow me.
I ain't following you. Don't worry. This is just one of those awkward moments where we both say
bye. We both hug. We both say our goodbyes and then we both realize fuck we're both going the same way.
We're both gonna walk down the same street for like another 10 minutes.
See you later again. I guess. We already talked about everything. We already said bye. So we don't
talk. It's just fucking weird. I hate this. What's he doing? I wish I had. I wish I had my friend.
Where's my friend? Where's the. Where's. What's his name? Murius. I wish Murius was here. Don't you?
I don't know that name. So what do I. What do I get for this?
Breed already. I'm doing a reverse escort quest. I'm doing an escort quest that he doesn't know
I'm on. Jerma's mom? Well like what? Like I dropped off my kid somewhere or like dropped off my kid
at the mall. And I'm gonna have fun. Yeah I'll pick you up in an hour. And then what you don't know is
your mother actually stays at the mall and like sees where you are. And then she's like oh my god.
I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know.
And like sees where you went. And just has the newspaper up and like looks over when you're
going into fucking like EB games or whatever the hell it is. And then she pulls up in the car where
you're supposed to meet. Wait what's that? What is this? Checkpoint. You followed me so I'm going
back home now. What? He saw us boss. We gotta try again. What do you mean he saw us? Wait what?
What? Wait did you see the- hold on. Did you see the hand? I don't understand. Hold on. He can see
me. Am I just like peering in looking at him? It's the hand? He get- if he actually sees the hand.
Oh he's just skipping. He's skipping now. He's sliding. Wait what's going on?
You followed me earlier. Please don't try it again. That is all. Isn't he down here? Uh oh.
We may have got a game crash scenario. Hold on. Let it sit here for a sec.
There we are. All right. Fuck, fuck, fuck. Stay away from him then. Jesus.
Gosh he's quick. He gave us the slip there. He's going to be back at his temple later.
What are you talking about? I'm sitting here looking at him. He's right here.
What the fuck is going on? Uh okay. Okay I think we'll come back to this. Is he walking again?
Um. You followed me earlier. Please don't try it again. That is all. Okay. I don't know what-
so is it the hand? It's got to be the hand or is it my- all right. So is it my point of view or
is it just the hand? It's the camera. You followed me. What the fuck? I- He saw us boss. We gotta try
again. Rats. I'm looking all- I'm like peering over the edge here. What's he doing over there?
I'm supposed to hide my face? How am I supposed to do that without losing him?
Should I be down here? The camera's always going to be able to see him somewhere.
Like should I- but if I go- all right here he comes again. All right there he is.
Okay it's impossible for me to hide because I imagine myself being 500 feet wide as a face.
Is he gonna move? I think it's fucked and it- no it has to start over again
because remember he has to go, oh you followed me. I'm gonna try this one more time. Yeah and it's
gonna glitch out for 30 seconds. Please don't try it again. That is all. Okay so let me get this
straight again. It's just- if I go too far away he- they- I lost him boss! But if I go too close
he can see my 500 foot wide face. Stay above him? So just like get- just float above him
like this so he can't see me. He's- he can't see me right? He can't see the hand either.
You followed me. What the- I'm huge! I'm huge! We gotta try again. Rats! You can't hide when you
are this big. If I go over here he's gonna- we're gonna lose him. You followed me earlier.
Please don't try it again. Wait copy paste that. Copy paste it. Copy paste it. Somebody just said
what in order to what? Okay stay- keep the camera behind him. So you're saying like just stay with
him and stay behind him. Oh fuck. Which way is he? How is this not more noticeable? Oh fuck. Oh fuck.
Oh fuck. Get behind the rock. Save the game? You can't save the game. There is no save game.
It's autosave or you have to go into the temple. Oh fuck! We got a checkpoint. Checkpoint. Checkpoint.
Checkpoint. Checkpoints. Checkpoint. Checkpoint. Checkpoint. Checkpoint. By the way saving the
game crashes the game on Windows 10. That's what I was told. We're fine. We got a new checkpoint
right here. You followed me earlier. Please don't try it again. That is all. Have you tested that
once? No I just believed what one person with negative two points on Reddit said. You followed
me so I'm going back home now. What the fuck? I didn't even start. I just had a cut scene.
We gotta try again. Rats. You followed me earlier. Yes I did. Please don't try it again. All right.
All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. Here we go. I have to wrap- I have to whip
around him to the left side. You followed me so I'm going back home now. What the fuck is going-
This is ridiculous. We gotta try again. Rats. I think I can do it. I have to rip around to
the other side of the building. Oh my god. Game break. You followed me earlier. Please don't try
it again. I have to go. I'm just ripping away. Gosh he's quick. He gave us the slip there. He's
bound to be back at his temple. You followed me earlier. Please don't try it again. That is all.
Hold on. If I pull back a little bit behind the rock, I just have to zoom out. Here we go. Don't-
Jesus. Okay here we go. He's quick. He gave us the slip there. He's bound to be back at his temple.
I was coming in. What the- Why are we doing this? I don't know. This probably- I don't know. I don't
know. Please don't try it again. That is all. Just kill him. No we're so close. This is the
second checkpoint. There's probably one more mushroom turn and that's it. Okay but look at the-
This is so odd. Is he done? Start walking. Okay I have to rip the camera around.
In fact, let's go over here. You followed me so I'm going home now. Liar. Liar. You can't see me.
Oh we gotta try again. Liar. Rats. Liar. Liar. I'm under- What? Do you see my hair?
You followed me earlier. Please don't try it. That is all. Okay. You followed me so I'm going
back home now. I can't do this anymore. I can't do this anymore. I can't do it anymore. I can't
do it anymore. I can't do it anymore. It's so finicky. It's so weird. It's so glitchy and sloppy.
I can't do it. I- I- I- I'm so close. You follow- Please don't. That is all. Okay. Zoom the fuck
out quick and then come back in. And then the camera has to be behind him. So I have to rip
the camera around his left side. I have to. Jesus, man. Even the tiny little- Is he going?
He's going. Please quick. He gave us the slip there. Oh it's- You don't- This is so fucked up.
You follow- Please don't. That is all. Why did I zoom in? I didn't. I moved the camera to the left
and this terrain. So you go- Up. Up. Up. I'm right on terrain. Please quick. He gave us the slip there.
He's bound to be back at his temple later. What about- I did directly above. Directly above doesn't
do anything. He sees you. You have to be directly behind him. But to be directly- You- I'm- This is
like an RTS camera that I have to stick up this guy's fucking- I'm controlling an RTS camera.
It's not like I can- I'm walking behind of a third person. Please quick. I- This- This- Oh my god.
You can't. You can't. There's a wall in the way and the camera hits the wall and points down.
Please don't try it again. That is all. Zoom. I'm gonna- If I zoom out, it's gonna lose him.
If I- If I go across- It's gonna lose him. Stay below the ridge? I just did that shit and he saw me.
Go lower than that. Watch this. Alright, fine. Let's go lower than that.
Oh gosh. He's- He's quick, isn't he? You followed me so I'm going back home.
Alright. All the chat detectives. All the fucking chat detectives. Go ahead. Do I- Do I get- Do I
get some- Some slack? You followed me earlier. Please- Keep you back to the cliff. I've done
that three times. And every time the camera- Because it's a fucking RTS camera. It hits the
fucking goddamn side of the wall and goes- I'm not doing that. See? I- Do you see what's happening?
I can't even move the fucking camera. Alright. What do I do now? What do I do? What do I do? What
do I do? Which way? You followed me so I'm going back home now. Come on! What the fuck?
He saw us, boss. We gotta try again. What? Dude, no way. No way, man. Like, no way.
Rotate quicker? Alright. Let's give me a break. You followed me. Please, that is all.
I gotta save? I'm not gonna go to the temple and load the save, am I?
P to pause the game. What? I've got magical fucking Adam Sandler powers?
What? Are you shitting me? Oh my fucking god. Give me a fucking break. You gotta be kidding me.
Which way is he turning? Which way is he turning? Does he turn to his left? You followed me.
He saw us, boss. We gotta try again. He saw through the powers. Oh my god.
You followed me. Please, that is all.
Oh, Jesus Christ. This is fucking ridiculous, man. This is ridiculous. Alright, pause it.
Why would they put... If you have to go around this way, why would this mountain be here?
Do you see what's happening? You followed me so I'm going back home. He saw us, boss.
We gotta try again. Rats. My... Give me a... I'm doing this one more time and I'm throwing this
guy in the ocean. You followed me. Please, don't. That is all. It's like, honest to god,
this is way too complicated for how stupid this is. You followed me so I'm going back home now.
Kill him. Kill him. We gotta try again. Kill this guy. Rats. Kill him. You followed me earlier.
Please, don't. That is all. Wait, wait, wait. Somebody said 10 in-game years have passed?
Alright, I'm gonna do this. I'm gonna do it now. Here it comes. This fucking wall has no reason to
be here besides to make this part stupid. It's just really... If I go... I can't go any further.
He'll see me if I'm right here. He'll see me if I'm up here. He's gonna see me. It has to be down
here. No, it has to be down here. But no, it doesn't. Alright, are we ready? Are we ready?
Ready? It doesn't. It doesn't have to be down there. Doesn't have to be down there. Alright.
What if I lose him though? What if I lose him? Why do I have carrot hands? I don't know what that
means. Carrot hands? Alright, am I in the... Zoom in for a second. Alright, I'm good. Back here.
This is good. Guys, guys, guys. He was looking this way. He was this way. He was fucking looking
over here and I'm standing over here like this. Stay low to the ground. Get up higher. Stay low
to the ground. Eat those berries. Shove those berries up your ass. Smell the berries.
Get the milk. Eat the milk. Drink the milk. What the fuck? Too many people with too many
conflicting opinions. I'm trying. Oh my god. Damn it. This is gonna drive me crazy, man.
Murius is being tortured right now. I know. It's terrible. It's terrible. I know. Don't look at me.
Oh, is he looking at me? You have to be. He's got like a 500 degree radius of an angle to see.
Can he see? Is he gonna see me right here? Read chat. Reach. Jerma, Jerma, Jerma, Jerma,
look at the chat. Look at when the when the yogi reaches a patch of tall blue mushrooms.
Swiftly circle around to the left. Wait, what? The yogi will look around. Hold on. It's going
too fast. I can't see. Okay, this is directing the wiki. Patch of tall blue mushrooms. Swiftly,
swiftly circle around to the left towards the center of the mountain. The yogi will look around
twice before starting to walk again. You need to rotate back to your original position before he
starts walking. Time your move carefully so you start rotating. I did that. No, this is too broken
to do that. I'm already here. You followed me, so I'm going back home now. He saw us, boss.
We gotta try again. Okay, I'm beginning to believe that this is absolute horseshit. I am
directly behind him. I am directly behind him and he turns around 180 fucking degrees.
You followed me. So you want me to go like this. Up here and go. Going against everything that
everybody in this chat has screamed at me not to do. This is gonna be fucking impossible.
Why does it have to be like this? Just do it with pause spam. Zoom all the way into his back.
He's gonna see me. Just leave him alone. People are dying. People are suffering in my village.
Pause the game. I'm gonna try it. I'm gonna get right behind him and you say around to the left
and then around to the right. Fucking RTS camera, man. I swear to god. Okay, here we go. I can't go
down any further than this. I can't. I can't go down any further. Closer. Get so close. Get close,
close, close, close, closer, closer, closer. I shouldn't be this close. His body needs to
fill the screen. Crush him. Crush him. Hit him on the head with a carrot. The camera's fucking with
me here. I need to be able to see him. Okay. Fuck, fuck, fuck. Stop. Don't move. This is hurting me.
Swifter. The second I see his shoulder turn, I gotta move. Close, close, closer, closer. Don't
lose him. Closer. What are you talking about? Leave me alone. This is too stressful for you.
What? Here he goes. Is this correct? Is this correct? No. What do you mean no? Behind him.
This is, okay, this is, this is as behind a person you could possibly be behind. Don't fucking do
that. What? What? What? What? What? What? What? What? So it's a, so the encounter is just broken,
is what we're saying. It's a broken ass encounter? You followed me earlier. Please don't, that is all.
So he's getting bald. I, this is ridiculous. He's gonna check twice. That wasn't even checking
twice. That was him just fucking standing there. I was, I'm about to give up on this shit. Watch
a YouTube tutorial. This is the kind of shit that you have save states every half second.
Oh my god. This camera is gonna make me die. Like, I'm done. I'm done after this. If I don't do this
I ain't doing this. Oh well, I'll drop a rock on this guy's house. I don't care.
This is stupid. So I'm going back home now. This guy's hand is in front of the guy. This
guy's hand is in front of him. These are the wrong mushrooms. Wrong mushrooms. Not even the
right mushrooms. Okay, hold on. The, hold on. The title of this video is following the yogi
and the description is annoying little shit ruined hours of my childhood.
What? This is not even the right mushrooms. Is it? Were those the right mushrooms? That's
that's wrong. Dude, he's putting his hand in front of this guy. If I did. No, that is the right
mushrooms. Hold on. How did he do this shit? I fucking did this. I swear to god. I did this shit.
I did this. We're gonna watch this video on stream because I did this shit and you all know it.
Watch this with me. I did this. I got spotted from a fucking mile away when I did this.
I, I did. He saw us, boys. We're gonna try again. So you go up here and like hide up here and like
go like this, like this and like this. I don't know, man. It's, I think my game's broken.
Because he's putting his hand in front of his face. You fuck. You fuck. You fuck. What?
What's going on? What's going on? What? What? What? What? What? What? Oh, all right. I'm gonna try
this thing where you looks like you go up above him kind of. Hold on. Pause the game. This camera
is fucked up. So I gotta get up above there. These are not the same mushrooms from the video.
What? What are you talking about? Yes, they are. Okay. All right. What does he do? What does the
guy in the video do? All right. In the video, the guy is standing right here like this. I'm
gonna go to the, I'm gonna go to the exact, I'm gonna fucking put the video on screen
and I'm gonna pause it and I'm gonna do it frame by frame, frame by frame. Hold on. Okay. So let's
get to the starting point when he gets, where is it? Right here. Okay. So there he is. He's walking
up. I guess this is an HD. So he gets it. I want to see where he is. Okay. Right. Okay. Right there.
Not close. All right. Let's go. I gotta go over here. I need to put this on my, on my stream
deck. Hold on. Cause it'll be easy to switch back and forth. Lower my resolution. No, no,
I'm not doing that. I play in HD. Let me just get this on my stream deck. Okay. There it is. So.
Oh, pause, pause it, pause it, pause it, pause it. Okay. I can't see. I can't see what he's doing.
Am I in the right spot? Kind of to the left, right? Not left. I it's, I'm trying to look at
two different screens. Why is it game different? That's pretty close. Okay. What does he do next?
Jeremy, this is not content. This is not, I'm trying, this is not supposed to be.
This is me trying to beat this, this stupid fucking childhood ruining dumb part of the game.
I don't, I'm trying to win. What happens next? Okay. What does he do when he turns?
I can't, I can't even fucking see what's going on. All right. So as he stays here,
he then lowers the camera down to, okay. I see where that is. Wait, can you guys see this?
He lowers the camera down and he start. Okay. So he lowers. Do you see what happened?
He low. Wait, why are you not getting this? Oh, I'm an idiot. I'm playing it in the other window,
not the one that's the browser source. Okay. So what does he go from here?
Plus the singing HD. Okay. So where does he move from here? So he dips down, right? Okay. He dips
down. He's about to turn. So he's, he's, he's about to turn right there. Okay. Do you see what that
is? I'm going to get it in the exact fucking spot. Is that good? It's like right there,
a little bit more to the left. It's almost indecipherable. Okay. It's tilted up a little
and back. Yeah, it is. It's like this. I gotta be like tilted down and then this way. Okay. Like
that. Okay. You can't tell me that that's almost fucking a hundred percent the same image. That's
the same image. Okay. So now what does he do from here? Okay. Right when he turns, he dips down to
there. Let's look at it one more time. There's the turn. He has now turned what he's now 100%
turned. And then he dips down to there, covering himself and that top part of that tree right there.
Okay. Here we go. This is important. So let me just, let me, so pause, pause. Oh,
the game on pause guys, the game unpaused when I clicked back over on the screen,
I wasn't ready for that. When I see escape, when I went to continue, it was paused.
When I hit continue, the game unpauses itself. It was paused. Pause. Okay. Continue. Games unpaused.
Fuck. I know what. Oh, you followed me. Please don't try it again. That is all I have.
Yeah, I did. Oh my fucking God. This is stupid. This is the stupidest thing ever.
This video only has a thousand views, but I know a thousand of us that have seen this video are like,
yeah, fuck this guy and fuck this part of the game. Fuck this guy. But I'm 1089 of people that
clicked on that video and said, yeah, holy shit, this guy sucks. It's a thousand of us strong.
What's the context? You have to follow a guy with an RTS camera and he has like a
7,000 degree viewing angle. And God damn it. Game unpauses itself after I had escaped.
Is this correct? What? Don't do, I have to, okay, I have to like change windows. Do not hit escape.
Just only change window. This is the last time I'm doing this. That's it. That's close. That's
pretty close. Okay. Increase your FOV. I can't fucking believe I'm still doing this shit.
Okay. All right. Why does this game have to be so finicky? If you don't finish this,
I'm not doing like a routine here, guys. Look at the fucking description of this video.
Annoying little shit ruins hours of my childhood. I didn't make this video.
Okay. This is it. It's going to be a little bit further like this. Okay. That's close enough.
Seriously. That is as close as I'm going to get it for like a fifth thousandth fucking time doing
this shit. Okay. He wraps around. I'm done after this. I have to stop it. When he, when he gets,
I have to grab here. And when he turns, spin around. It's after he turns. There it is. The
camera has to be literally right here. Remember that tree further? Yeah. It's where's the tree
in our, we have to hold on. Okay. He comes back up and this way. Fuck man. I feel like that's,
this is not going to work. I don't think this is going to work. He comes out of there and is
sitting here and then he just stays behind him. So, so at this point he, when he starts walking,
so he begins his walk. I got to come out. Okay. So I have to come back out and up and then get
a little bit closer and keep tilting. Oh, fuck me, man. Okay. He hasn't started really. Okay.
He started walking now and then where is he? He started walking. All right. So he, he started
his walk. All right. Fuck. Hold on. Hold on. I got to zoom out a little here. Get the fuck out.
All right. Am I, is it ready to meet? Can I come out? Can I come out? Can I come out?
I think I can, I can come out now, right? This is what happens in the video, doesn't it?
Yes. Is this, am I, am I safe right here? Is this correct? This is correct, right? Yeah.
I did it. I did it. I did it. I did it. I did it. All right. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Wait, what does he do? What? What do you mean refresh the page? What? Black and white following
the yogi and it says annoying little shit. Wait, hold on. Read the description again.
Jerma sucks. What? How did, are you watching the stream? Annoying little shit. Runaway. Jerma
sucks by the way. Hold on. I want to get lovely. This is fucking lovely. Oh, lovely. Yeah. Lovely.
I'm so happy about this. Hold on. Oh no. Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no, no, no, I'm doing that yet. I'm doing that. Yeah. I just broke the whole game.
I don't care. I don't care. I was going to, I was going to show all the comments.
Everyone's being real nice. All right. Pa, unpause. Does he, does he turn around again? Is this the
end or does he turn around again? Save the game. I can't, it might crash. Okay. Let me just check
the video. Check the video. Check the video. Delete the video before he can beat it. Delete
the video. Shut up. Do not even think about it. Don't delete this video. Don't delete this video.
I need it. I need this video. Do not delete this video. It doesn't matter if he deletes it. I still
have it in my queue. All right. Then he goes, he doesn't turn around again. You just have to stay
behind him. There is more. How much more is there? Why is there more? There can't be more.
No, I don't want to do more. Oh my God. Is there a checkpoint here? Is there a checkpoint?
Fuck. But he goes, where does he go? Save the game. If I save the game in a crash,
I'm going to be fucking really mad. All right. That's the end. All right. If I save the game,
the game crashes. I'm going to fucking be, I'm going to explode. Control S. If I do this,
Control S. Don't. Do not. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do
it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Don't do it. Do it. Don't do it. Should I do
it? Don't. So many people are saying no. That's too risky. What if I exit the game right now?
Okay. If I exit the game right now, it's going to say no. Just stay behind him. All right. What
does he come out from out there? Control S. Fuck. I am so, now get over, it's over here, right?
Not yet. I don't know. This is fucking horrible. I don't know what to do.
Just carry him laughing my ass off. On top of the rock. What happened in the video? I hope you
didn't delete it. He's not deleted. He didn't delete it. He goes under the rock and then as
he goes underneath when he, he's, he's underneath mine completely. All right. He's under the rock.
You just stay above the rock and let him come out. Wait up here until, again, when he comes out,
you start to move towards him. Okay. I'll get there. Let's do that on mine. Where is he?
Okay. And then now he's almost the top of that little hill. Okay. He's at the top of that little
hill. Okay. Now what does he do? Now what happens? He's at the top of the hill. Is he at the top of
the hill on this one too? Now what? He bent. Okay. He, I see that little pit. See that. What
happened? He starts to turn this way and he stays, he stays right here. He stays in this general area
right here. So he stays like here, like this, like that, right? Closer, like right there. Okay.
And then just please don't see me. Right. Just stay here. Right. I, I, okay. When he starts,
what does that happen? When he starts to move, when he starts moving, where do I go?
What's wrong? I thought he deleted it. I'm so fucking glad you're not going to delete it.
Must resurg, resist urge to delete video. Okay. He looks, he looks, he looks, you go around the
tree. You go around to the right behind the tree. Okay. Got it. So you go around this way
behind the tree. Yes. Oh fuck. Oh, that was horrible. Your stealth surprised me. You know
the secret of my special place of meditation. If you will remain quiet, I will help you on this
land. Oh, that was horrible. Rest assured I'll appear when needed. That is all. So what? What
did that do for me? Now kill him. I'll appear as needed. I don't get anything for that.
I did it. Somebody said the description changed again. Read the comments. All right. I'm going
to go through the comments of this, uh, video. Sure. Uh, German sucks by the way. Let's see.
Let's read it. Uh, short streamer. Jeremy Albertson needs guides to finish boomer game more at 10.
This is like this guy ruined hours of this person's childhood. A thousand of us get it.
Jeremy, you short omega low. That's funny. Five one Willem Dafoe needs tutorial to move camera
correctly. That's hysterical. Derma couldn't get it right. Now you're right. Hello, ladies and
gentlemen, welcome to the German craft copper pasta. This guy may be mauled on stream. Derma
walk. You can do a German. This is a German nine eight five partner channel. Now I was here when
he watched it. Derma Venus. Derma be like, Hmm, today we'll watch a tutorial live on stream and
not save mega milk. This is painful. Annoying streamer ruins hours of his middle age. Thank
you for this video. Jeremy would be banging his head against the wall without it. It's true.
I can't believe mega milk died for this legendary heard that some streamer called grill master,
whatever, sudden change in description left me in tears. Derma, you're handsome. Derma's handsome.
That's the same person. He did it. Let's read some of the comments from five years ago. Thank you.
This is from five years ago. I never could beat that mission. So it's great to actually see it
happen. It's kind of disappointing actually. Okay. What about another one from like 10 years ago?
That's it. That's it. That's the only comment. Liar making up comments. Go read them for yourself.
Sort by date. Let's go down to the end. Let's see. This is too many. One. Okay. A year ago,
five years ago. That's the only two comments. All right. Hype train initiated. All right.
Thanks for watching that guys. Wait, did another, another hype train, another hype train has been
initiated. Wait, what's going on? It's not doing it again, right? No. Okay. It's showing up on this
other screen. It's showing up on my Twitch dashboard now. All right. No, it's not. There's
no hype train. Don't hype anything. Okay. Welcome back to the stream guys. That was fucking stupid.
Let's uh, oh yeah. I had like a village that was starving. Let's go. How am I doing?
Oh, I'm so glad I don't have to do that anymore. That sucked. That actually was the worst. What was
I doing though? I've, that was, this was an hour ago. I don't remember what I was doing.
I was doing something important. I don't remember what that was. Breeding. Breeding. Right. Okay.
But I want some more. Oh wait. I went with my, my, the forest isn't doing anything.
You were saving Murius. I'll get this out of here. This is going to cause a problem. It's going to
hurt somebody. So to get rid of it. All right. I want to go take over the other village. That's
not going to hit a village, right? You got to be fucking kidding me. That's not going to hit the
good. Okay. All right. Let's make these people believe in me. What do you say?
Let's give them some food. They look like they need it. What's the food symbol?
I got to move in to my territory and then out to these people here that I want to give it to.
Miracle food. Let's get some influence. Ready? Uh, terrible. Come back over here.
All right. Here we go. All right. Oh, I don't have influence. I can't
damn it. Well, you need the immortal guy. What? How many believe do I need to take this over?
419. Just make a new village. You want to make a new village right down here at the edge.
Let me get this situated though. What happened here? What happened here? Wood. All right. What
we got anymore? Yeah. Let's put it. Let's make another settlement down here and it's time to
breed. Let's get some children. Did the trees grow? Um, they did not. They did not. Well,
time just to harvest them. Don't worry. We'll get them back. I can't believe I took that long
to do that. There's a miracle over here. Let's get that one. We can't believe it either. Well,
that guy is apparently important. I can't just not do anything with that guy. Physical shield.
I don't need that right now. Physical shield. All right. What if I give it to them?
Here. Oh, well, how do I cancel? Can I drop this? I don't want to. I don't want to use this.
I'm gonna sneeze. That couldn't be. I don't want this. Drop. Press you. No, you said bless you.
Who am I connected to? I don't want this. I actually don't want to shake it. There we go.
All right. It's time to breed. You. Breed. We need breeding. Breed. Disciple breeder. More.
We need children. Disciple breeder. More children. Who else? You're hurting them.
I'm not hurting anybody. I am not hurting anyone. I'm trying to get them to breed.
Disciple breeder. Disciple breeder. Thank you. Okay. Children are starting to come out. We have
enough place to live. Do need a little bit more wood, which there's some in here. And when that's
done, I gotta go this way. Which way should I go? This little area down here. Tons of trees over
here. In fact, I'm gonna harvest them. I need to. Play music for the right mood. This is kind of
the right mood. My buddy is gone. All right. Let's go. More food. Miracle food. People still
worshiping. Yeah, they are. They're getting tired though. 12,000 food. 11,000 wood. That should be
enough for now. Have some kids. Breed. And then I have to make this town. I have to influence this
town. What do you think? Maybe another little center here? Oops. I didn't want to do that.
You need a lot more breeders. I mean, I kind of, but I don't want to do too much.
What are they doing? Going home. Steve Jackson's going to sleep.
Disciple breeder. More. We need more kids. We need a worship site. Our population, seriously,
is not doing so well. Going to the forest? Is this still not built? How the fuck is this not
built? Everyone's like 70 plus years old. Better start having kids. Okay. Build two more houses.
We can live in these damn things. You were gone for 10 years. Yeah. Well, I had to figure out
some things. Build it. Are there, what about the, okay, let's go to the temple. This is about
eight women up here. I think so. Are there? Okay. We need some breeding. Breed. 76 years old.
I'm going to have my first child at 80. Can I? Disciple breeder. Okay. Good. We have to have
kids. Start having kids before the whole village gets wiped out. 68, 85. All right. Well, let's
just, wait, I think that was, I think that was a female. Fuck. How old was she? I just like,
oh God. Okay. Come here. Disciple breeder. What am I doing? I'm trying to make kids. Everybody's 80
and everyone's going to die. Did you even read chat? What are you talking about? What are you
talking about? The average age of people in this village is 75 years old. I have to make kids.
Use a pregnancy miracle. I don't have that. You're talking about stuff that's potentially like
six levels into the game.
All these kids are going to be messed up. Why are they having kids? All right. Get in the temple.
I need to see what's going on here. I need a better picture. Oh, 73% male. There are
222 people. More than an insane majority of men. Breeders. This is bad. Okay. What does my,
what's my creature have to say? I'm greedy. I'm tired. I think my God's on the good side.
I want to think about the creature Chugworth. He is totally evil. Who is Chugworth? The guy
torturing him? This guy torturing me is totally evil. Chugworth is such a cool name.
What's Murius? Murius is a good name too. Let's take a look at this.
All right. I got to start influencing because I wish I just had my guy. You know what I mean?
If I had my guy, I'd be fine, but I don't. All right. Get me out of here.
This is the room where you. Well, you could influence it or you could follow a Yogi for 60
years, but that's, that's probably going to come back to be a good thing. I would assume it has to
be right. All right. Time to build. I need wood. I need to build like a, what should I build?
Like a new town center down there. What do you think? What should I put down there to put my,
to put some influence? Almost out of wood. There's no kids either. I have to, all right,
I got to use the actor. Where is he? Come here. Look at what I have. Interesting, huh?
It's cool. I know I'm shaking a guy around in front of you. You didn't kill me. Oops.
Please don't throw me. Oh, cast some miracles in here while he's running around. Good idea.
All right. Let's do a food. Let's give him food. Oh, you big boy. Try it again. And you're
dead. Food. Yeah. Food in here. Look. Please don't throw me my leg. You want more food?
There's much more where that came from. Oh, you big bully. Try it again. And you're dead. Look
what I got. Look at that. Huh? Cool. Huh? Want some more? I need 300 belief. Please don't throw me
on my arm. I got more miracles. I've got more miracles. Get off me. Oh, my head. Throw some
fireballs around. No, no, no. I need influence, not fear. I do not. I want influence. I do not
want fear. Oh, oh, you big bully. Try it again. And you're dead. Wow. 280 belief. Come on. Let me,
let me, like, look, I pick up a tree and like do this. It's crazy, huh? Look at this. Look at
that shit. Cool, huh? Leave it. I'm not worth it. Miracle food. I'm trying to grab him. Please
don't throw me my leg. He's not worth it. He is because he lets me interact with this town.
You didn't kill me. All right. How much did I get for that? 251. I think I have to kill somebody.
Where'd he go? Please don't please don't throw me. I'm gonna hit somebody with this. Eventually.
Oh, my eye. That's a new line. Put him on the sacrificial altar. Hold on. Oh, you big bully.
Put one of your guys in the village. Get off me. Oh, you big bully. All right. Well, I have to put.
All right. Here we go. Who am I putting in there? Um, you. Somebody from my village. Oh, you big
bully. Try it again and you're dead. What did I just do? Did I just make him? No, no, no, no. Don't.
I want to. What does that mean? Is he like a. Did they just capture him? Did I make him into wood?
No, I didn't. Look, he's like talking. I think he just. Did he just breed? Who? Wait, where is he?
Is that them? Oh, it is. He's going around. He's. He's breeding. Right? Yeah. I infected them. Where's
he going? All right. I still need. Let me go back to my town. I have a lot of food. OK, let's build.
What do I want? There's a fucking shitload of food. OK, bigger house, civic building.
What should I do? Should I do a new village center or should I just do another place to live?
The soccer field is broken and it does not work, apparently. Make a graveyard. Change him to a
missionary. Hold on. Where's my guy that I throw for it to be able to interact? My head. OK, we're
in. We're in. You didn't kill me. Get off. Get off me. So where did my. Where did my guy go?
Is he just in here breeding in the village still? All right, I'm going to make a missionary.
I can't. I have no access to the snow. There he is. Wait, what are you doing? Try it again and
you're dead. I don't have enough influence over there. You've got to stay over here.
So this is weird. I don't think this is the kind of dumb way to do this. Oh, my head is built down
here because I can't put him over there unless I have access to be over here, which I don't have
access to be over here. Oh, you big bully. Try it again and please don't throw me like this guy has
to be standing in this village. My leg. OK, I have to grab somebody and put him in here
because I cannot do anything in this town unless there's positive. I'm cheating the system right
now. Essentially, it was what's happening. All right. You, Jeff Keighley, Jeff Keighley,
you are now going to be a missionary. What does it look like over here on the temple
on their temple? They don't have one, do they? On top of a person. Does it have to be a person
because the breeding is next to a house? OK, God damn it. Please don't. This guy has to be
over here. What the fuck? OK. Oh, you big bully. Try it again and you're dead. OK, Jeff Keighley,
come here. So was that like Zen symbol? Correct. Could I do it here? Disciple missionary. There he
is. He's going to change. What's going on in here? All right. Jeff Keighley is now. He's a
missionary. OK, I still need 226 believe flying, flying, flying. What happened? What did you guys
do? I died. What did they do? I can't even help them. Jesus. All right. All right. I got a
missionary. I got to go back to my town. I'm going to build something down here. I can take
anything. How are we doing on kids? Very important. Fuck. Somebody else died. Do we even have any
children? Aren't these any kids? Is it no kids? I got to get some breeding done now. You need
women have to be 45 or under to breed. Well, this town's gone. Hopefully Jeff Keighley does
something over there. Otherwise, this is actually fucking ruined. Everybody's 80. Oh no, it's over.
Steal people from the other village. Everyone over here is fucking ancient too.
Everybody look at how old everybody is. 60, 50, 60, 60, 70, 70, 70. Why are we so old? 20. OK,
hold on. Give me a break. Come on. This dude's going to die of old age. I got to get him. Oh,
that sucks. I spent 60 years following the stupid guy on the cliff. Oh, help. Oh, God.
No, you didn't kill me. Please don't throw me. Where the fuck am I? Speaking of missionaries,
time to go find some people to bring back to my town. And I don't know, I guess.
You didn't get off. Get off me. 84. Who are you? Oh, you big bully. Try it again.
I don't know who this person is. OK, got you. You are on my team now. You live here now.
You live here now. Deciding what to do. You live here now. 20. No. Live here in love.
Good. How do I speed this up? All my eye. I need people under 45. I'll get a few of them.
Oh, you big bully. Try it again and you're dead. 83. We need younger than that. Please don't throw
me. 75. 21. You can kill me. You live here now. Live here in love. Good. OK. All right. Where's
the other 21 year old? 21. I think everybody's dead. 21. There you are. Come here. Disciple
breeder. Help me. Disciple breeder. We need children. We need children. Don't go to the
worship site. We need kids. I have to turn it off. Breed. Together. All right. We need a couple more.
Um, 44, 45, 21. 21. OK. Where's my actor? All right. How did I speed this up? Somebody
tell me I can speed this up. Alt and 2. You big bully. Please don't throw me.
You didn't kill me. Please don't throw me. 21, 21, 21, 21, 21, 21, 21, 21, 20, 20, 20, 20, 20,
30. Oh, you big bully. Try it again. You have to live here. You have to live here. We need more
people. Good. OK. Disciple breeder. Disciple breeder. You're 76. Not going to work. I didn't
mean to do that. I didn't mean to do that. I didn't mean to do that. I didn't mean to do that. I didn't
mean to do that. 22. Come here. OK. These are two. These are women. All right. Women, women, women.
Where's the other guy? There he is. Put that down. All right. Did you do it? They're both going into
the same hut to give birth. Oh, this is weird. Oh, kids, kids. Come here. More. Where are those
kids? Where are they? I don't see any. Oh, this hole. Everybody's going to be related.
Everybody's going to be related.
Oh, no. Oh, boy. Here we go. No. Where are they? We need kids. Oh, they don't have any babies.
I need to steal more people. No. I have to do it before this guy dies. It takes a minute to give
birth. OK. Let's get another. You didn't kill me. 46, 85, 23. This place is vacant. What's wrong with
it? It doesn't need to be repaired. What are you talking about? OK. Now you breed. Disciple breeder.
OK. Good. One more. I need another female. Oh, hell. I think I broke it. My arm. Oh, you please
don't throw me. OK. This is it. And this should be fine. God damn it. Oh, you big bully. Try it
again and you're dead. OK. We need one more person. 60, 60, 23. Wow. Whoa. Dead. Looks
like the spot for you to move in. Live here in love. All right. Breed. Breed. You too. Breed.
Breed. Breeder. You're already a breeder. I need. Giving birth. Yes. Our first child. Yes.
Don't kill them. I just don't kill them. Don't die. Don't be dead. Don't be dead. I need you. I
need a fucking. These are the only people in the town. OK. I need one more person. Live here in
love. I need another male. Oh, my God. I fucking can't believe I have to do this. Is there any
people over here? 70, 70, 70, 60, 60, 60, 80, 80. No, they're all gone. What about over here?
24. Convert the village. I mean, I can't unless I can. I can't get over there for long enough.
I think it's going to be fine. Everybody over here is going to be a breeder.
There it is. OK. 24, 24, 1, 1. OK. We're having births. 24. Breeder. All right. You.
No more of that. You breed. No more. No, no. You're 74. Actually, you keep. You do that. That's fine.
I don't want you doing that. I want you breeding. And that's it.
Disciple Forester. Good. Good. Breeder. Breeder. Good. 73. Going home. OK. I'm pretty sure
everybody is now breeding with each other. Remember, the old can also breed.
I thought you guys don't know they couldn't. Disciple Breeder.
I'm trying to make offspring. One guy killed the colony.
Yeah, because I had to follow around this dude, which, by the way, if I was supposed to follow
that person around, that takes 10, 20, 30 years. Well, going home, going home, giving birth. OK.
We got another baby. I think we're going to be in the clear for a while. You don't go to the forest
for wood. Only breed. No one do anything else but breed. Anything. Disciple Breeder. OK. Don't do
anything but have children. There we go. All right. I think they will populate themselves now.
We need wood. There's some down here. They're all going to have the same birthday.
That's pretty fucked up. That's pretty fucked up. Yeah. Yeah, it's fucked up.
Heal the villagers. They're all under 50% health.
OK. One more. Over here. Nobody's worshipping, right? No, they can't. They can't because they
need to breed. Make them have, no. Having children. Breeding. I see a lot more names. That's good.
More kids. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. That's what I like to see. More.
I need to do another heal though. How do I get another heal?
65%. Someone's got to go up here. OK. Is there anybody that's over the age of 60?
All right. Who needs help? You guys down here. 90, 40, 70, 60, 70, 70. 75%. All right. That's good.
All right. Everyone's OK. We're good. Maybe I should steal some more people.
The actor. He's dead. All right. What do they got? 49, 10, 10. OK. There's somebody 38. I can't.
I need 78 belief. All right. Let's just go trash the place until they love me.
You know what I mean? Let's just trash the place until they like me. No. Don't crash. I'm not doing
that again. You didn't kill me. Please don't throw me. All right. Look what I can do, guys.
You didn't kill me. Cool, huh? Get off me. Oh, hell. I wonder if he's going to die of an old age.
There's got to be it. Come on. Like I need like 20 more. Look, the miracle of something. You didn't
kill me. 12. That's a kid. Put the kid down. All right. How much more? 32? Damn it. Where is he?
Stop running away. Please don't throw me. The miracle of throwing the same guy into the ground.
I know. Why am I throwing this person? Because it gains belief points. Oh, my eye. Oh, you big
bully. Try it. Get off. Get off me. Do you believe me now, please? No. Once I have this village,
I'll be good to go. Heal the actor. Okay, here we go. How much more do I need? You didn't kill me.
How do you not believe me yet? You having fun anymore? I still am, strangely enough,
after all this nonsense. All right, let's go. Oh, you big bully. Try it again and you're dead.
How much more belief? 31 belief. Oops. Catch, catch. I got it. Okay, I'm fine.
Please don't throw me. Okay, time to do a miracle. Oh, my head. Miracle time. Heal.
Oh, you big bully. Please don't throw me. Oh, you big bully. Please don't throw me.
I just need like 30 fucking. Oh, you big bully. Try it again and you're dead.
Believe. Believe. God. Please don't. You didn't kill me. Please don't throw me.
You big bully. I don't have any miracles. Please don't throw me. Oh, my head. I can't wait to never
have to throw this guy again. I have to just deposit food over here. Oh, you big bully.
Got it. Try it again and you're dead. Get off. Get off me. Oh, you big bully. Try it again and
you're dead. Oh, my fucking God. Where is he? Please don't throw me. You didn't kill me.
Please don't throw me. I don't want to hear this dude ever again. I need 20 belief. I've given them
food. I've thrown people. I've destroyed things. How do I get this? Just 20 fucking belief.
Save the cow. You didn't kill me. Please don't throw me. Do you understand the cow is across
the entire game? I can't even. I can't get over there. I have to. This is somehow taking more
time than following the yogi around. Doesn't building get you more influence? You didn't kill
me. That's what I thought too. But I look at how much. I'm going to try building one building over
here. Just give me the fucking thing. Right at the edge. Somebody build the damn thing. Build that.
Disciple builder. Because I can't do anything over here until I have sacrificed somebody for a
miracle. I God damn it, man. Look at all these children. The problem was following the yogi.
Following the yogi was the dumbest thing to ever do. It just deleted 60 years.
Walking behind. I had save points and shit. That took like 70 fucking years to walk behind that
guy slowly. I got to sacrifice somebody for a miracle. Destroy a house in the village with a
rock. I tried to throw like a tree at their wall. All right. Give me a rock. Fuck it. Let's go.
I don't even know where that went. I have no idea where that just went. I need the actor again
to do that. Oh my God. He's going to die of old age. This is so stupid.
Oh, you please don't throw me. Oh, you pick it up. You didn't kill me. Please don't throw me.
Oh, you please don't throw me. You didn't kill me. Please don't throw me. You didn't kill me.
You have a rock in your village anywhere. I need a boulder. Oh, you big bully. Try it again and
you're dead. That's it. Fuck you. Finally. Jesus God. You didn't kill me.
We almost have our cow back. All this pain.
All right. God damn it. My influence has grown. Now let's do this. Everybody. Everybody start
working together. How are we doing? We have another village over here. I have influence right there.
We need breeding now. Breathe together. Live here in peace. What's going on?
I is dead. I have your creature and you still dare to oppose me.
The cow's been frozen for 100 years. I see some of your minions have strayed. What? Behold wrath.
What? No. I can't let this happen. I don't have a water spell. I don't have a water spell.
No. There he is. Save us, please. Please. You took all of them.
That's all you're going to give me is two water miracles? Thanks for nothing.
Stop lighting each other on fire. They're reigniting each other. Okay. We good? Vagrant.
Okay. So did I just get a shitload of people? Oh my God. They're all 18.
Oh my God. They're all 18. They're all 18. They're all 18. All of them are 18.
I just broke something. That just saved everything. Oh my God. They're migrating everywhere. Okay. Here
we go. Saved. Saved. Yes. Yes. All right. We need breeders. Let's go. Chop chop. Start having kids.
Don't kill anybody. Our followers are annoyed with you. Just start working. Disciple farmer.
Farmers. Disciple farmer. Get a couple of builders. Disciple farmer. Why are they 70? Oh,
it's Jeff Keely. 54. 2. 53. Okay. We need we need breeders. I need all the young ones to breed
and all the old ones to work. Like that mechanic. Seriously. Give me a break. Breed.
What the hell do you think I'm doing? He's already a breeder? What? All right. Where are all the 18
year olds? Going to building site. No. No. You should be breeding. You should be breeding. Do
any women? Oh, this is a is this a woman? Disciple breeder. Disciple breeder. More. Okay. Breeder.
18. Going to building site. No. No. No. Disciple breeder. Okay. That should be enough. Now we have
to have some wood cutters. My influence has grown this way. Any uh there's a couple is there any
women over here? 78. 19. Going to the store. Okay. This town is in trouble. Oh, hold on.
Disciple forester. Yeah, that's fine. Woodcutter. Disciple forester. All right. Looking good.
There's this other town over here. The influence is at least close enough where I can
all right. Here we go. It's time to put some people on that side. Let's let's get some
missionaries. You. Well, you're bad at chopping trees. Really bad.
Come over here. Spread our good word. Disciple missionary. Missionary. Let's get a few over
there. No one's working over here anymore. You too. Disciple missionary. 462 believe needed.
Did that just tick down or I don't understand? Come on. I can take anything you throw. Quiet.
All right. Good. We're working in the fields here. How much wood do I got? Plenty of food,
but I need more wood. You know, there's a whole forest down here. I need like a wood cutting shop.
Look at all these kids. Perfect. All right. Building sites. Leaping. I think we can take
some people away now. You. We need to start cutting this shit down. Disciple forester.
We have to make some people do some work over there. Building site. No. All the 55 plus.
You're over here getting wood. 55 plus. Where are you? Disciple forester. Okay. Anyone 55 plus? 79.
Disciple. What the fuck? This is dystopian. What are they doing down here? Somebody died.
Oh no. Jeff Keely's going to the farm. No. Catch them. It's okay. Breathe. No. Cut wood.
They're going a really long way to bring that wood. Okay. We're going to start to need food
and shit. All right. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. All right. Too much. Now the breeding's
getting out of control. The breeding's out of control. We need food and shit. Disciple farmer.
House. We're starting to lose control of the breeding now. Breeder. I need more breeders
over here to work over this way. Disciple farmer. Who else is a breeder? Who else is having too many
kids? Breeder. Okay. We don't want you doing that anymore. Stop kissing each other. Stop.
We need wood cutters and one more farmer. Disciple farmer. Breeder. Okay. You. Two.
Um. You. Okay. That's not. You done? We need you to build. Build? Disciple builder. Uh, going to
crutch. Oh fuck. They're breeding like rabbits now. Jeff Keely's still going strong. Okay.
Going to the forest for wood. Going to the farm. Going to the farm. Going to the forest.
Wizard of the Breeder. Going to farm. Going to farm. Going to village. Breeder. Okay.
That's enough. Disciple builder. We need more builders. We need more farms too. Okay. Uh, we.
I need wood. I got people working on the wood. Going to the store. Going to the building.
Digging up a crop. Going to the store. Why are they all going this way? Why are you going so far away?
No. Stop working over here. Disciple farmer. How old do they have to be? Breeder. What's that noise?
Getting wood. No. Uh, over here. Disciple farmer. I need a store in, in the capital.
What do you mean? Do they not? That's not. Isn't that a store right here? I. There's a store there
and a store here. That's because you're splitting up families. How are they doing on wood? Wood is
always in trouble. I'm going to take some. Offspring. All right. I'm going to take it.
Okay. Going to crates. Going to crates. So many kids. Oh no. There's too many kids.
There's too many children now. Oh God. This is not good. How do I need three wood for that?
Ugh. Okay. Produce. Food. Stop breeding. Stop breeding and do, uh, go get wood.
Disciple forester. So everyone's going, going to village store. Why are they going this far away?
They need kids over here. Offspring. I know. I'm trying to figure that out. You need kids over here?
Disciple breeder. Disciple breeder. Make some. Okay. You can make some kids.
Breeder. All right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. You got lots of food too. Give me that.
I'm going to just give it up to the people over here as a sign of good faith.
Oh, I hold on here. Look at this. Pretty cool. Huh? 440 belief needed.
God give and the God take it away. How are you doing? Good. What about this food?
How do you think about that? Huh? What about that for food? Huh? What about this?
What do you guys think about this? Scary. Are you scared? You should be. Believe.
Food. Take it. Look at, I don't throw all bad things. I throw sometimes good things.
Clap. Wow. Food. How much belief do I need? Not that much more. All right. How can I
destroy this? I have to break a building. Just destroy something. Just cause a problem.
336. I could put more missionaries over here. Yeah. All right. Some of the people,
this is getting out of hand. So let's do, you have 80? No, nothing. Nothing. Three
year old. Here we go. Missionary. 71. Missionary. Let's do like two more missionaries. Oh yeah.
Let's see. 58. Yeah. You can be a missionary. What are you doing? What? What is it? It's like
the, what's this link? Mega milk are missing. I love it. You censored, you censored this.
I'm not going to show this on stream, but like you censored the,
I don't even understand. I don't understand what that is, but that's fine.
All right. Missionaries over there. One more missionary. And then I'm going to throw a rocket
there building. I just want to get my cow back. Missionaries. Come on, do something. It's rock
time. I've been kind. I've been nice. Not anymore. I've played the kind card. It's time to play the
rock card. 71. Speaking of rocks, where are any rocks? I actually don't see any. I have electricity
now for his bell. You got any rocks? Who doesn't have, who has a rock? Going to sleep on the floor.
What the fuck? Going fishing. Oh, that's cool. Here. Another missionary. Disciple missionary.
We need offspring. There's a, there's a ton of people in the town already. I don't know if I
want to do that. All right. Let's do a sacrifice so I can do something in their town. Who do I want
to sacrifice? Oh, the 80 year old looks all right. I got to heal miracle.
I could do it. No, let's do it to them. Let's heal the sick. 49 belief. Holy shit. That's a lot.
Okay. Do it again. Sacrifice another person. All right. Can I, can I just, well, I don't want to
sacrifice my people though. Let's sacrifice you. Wait, I can't. It's me. I'm back again.
Here to make the sick feel better. 57 belief. How much more do I need? 200. What a kind ruler.
Are you guys doing porn? Stop doing porn. I will actually start, I will start throwing out
permas if there's pornography in this channel. All right. Sacrifice again. This time I'm going
to do food. Miracle of food. Let's give them. Yeah. Cool. Look at that. Ooh, food.
What is over there? Go get it. Wow. Warm food. It's pretty crazy. 163. All right. We're almost there.
Miracle food. It's warm food. Isn't that a good thing? How's that a bad thing? Who can I sacrifice?
838, 3, 18, 25, 7, 49, 75. And what is that over there I can do?
What does that do? That's lightning and then often some defense or something.
I'm going to put some food in. I'm going to put it over here. They really actually need it.
Chat needs cow. I'm working on it. I'm trying. I'm trying. How much more do I need?
I think I might have to start killing people in here. 153 belief. I think I might have to kill
somebody. How much more? Go faster. Yeah, I can't. 116 belief needed. Kill two more people.
22 belief. You believe. Good, good, good. You believe now. Dermot, save the cow. You do understand
that I have to take over the next two towns to save the cow. That's the only way I can do it.
I'm trying. 8 belief. Almost there. 72 needed. All right, what are we doing over here?
How many points do you need to save the cow? I need to do the take over every single town here
to get up to here to then release my fucking cow who for some reason they decided to have this
level be a thing where you don't get your creature you just got. He's just stuck up there while you
have to breed. All right, we need a mercenary. We're not a mercenary. Whatever it's called.
The gorilla wouldn't have let himself get captured. You don't know that.
Offspring, offspring, offspring. Where are we going? Right here. How old is everybody?
I mean theoretically speaking, it'll get easier when I get this other town here.
Disciple missionary. 57 belief. Come on. Hurry up. Somebody do something. It's got a heart when they
hit the dirt. 12 belief. Just make a miracle. I've done that and it gives you like 10.
I think it's time to throw a fucking fireball at this village. Who cares?
It's time. It's time to throw a fireball at the village. I'm not going to like throw a guy over
there or like pour maple syrup in their fucking coffers. No, it's time. It's time to die.
It's time to die. Maybe you'll fucking listen now. We rained hell down on him.
Are they believing yet? Oh shit. Now I need water. Now I need water.
I need to sacrifice somebody quick. Sacrifice somebody. Sacrifice somebody. Somebody. Somebody.
Somebody. Somebody. Somebody. Somebody. Somebody. Anybody. Come here. What are you
talking about? You're not even here. Miracle shower. Oh my God. The camera is going to drive
me insane. I can't even. I'm living the window. I brought water. See? I'm helping you.
All right. Now all of you go fuck yourself. All of you. I don't care about this village.
This village sucks. Give me my cow back. I just want to play the game. The fun game with the cow
and the people. Hard locking me out of my favorite part of the game. All right. Let's go. This is the
village right here. I got to get up there. Is anything still on fire? See? Look. I'm good now.
Okay. We're good. We have a lot of influence here. I lose influence over here.
What about over here? Is this a town or anything or no?
Tree puzzle. The idea is to make the nine trees the same species. Pick up any of the trees to
swap its species. Make it have the same one? What the fuck is this?
How many different trees are there? It's a Nancy Drew puzzle. Yeah, it is.
But okay. How many are there? Let's see me count. One, two, three. There's three different trees.
What's after the Christmas tree? This one. Okay. Go on. Chuck me about. I dare you.
Please don't pick me up. Throw me around. You think I care? I don't. I don't. I don't care.
I don't care. I'm not doing that. I'm wasting time. Who cares? No, I don't care. I'm not sitting
there for 20 years following a guy around. No. All right. You guys get wood. Look at all the wood
that's over there. That's what I want everyone over here to do. Wood. I'm wasting a fucking
million years. Let's get these ones too. I can actually do this too.
Because this is a huge forest. Let's just do this. Look at how many trees are over here.
An insane amount. This can feed everybody. What? Am I taking the whole forest? What the hell?
It's shrinking piece by piece. Oh Jesus. Okay. Almost a 20,000. All right. Let's make a...
What do I want to make? This is the edge of my influence. I kind of need to make... Who's
going home? All right. I got to build a building up here. Maybe a house or something.
All right. Where's the production yard? Wood required. Seven wood. Disciple builder.
Bro the guy again. I'm not doing that again.
You may have your few believers, but I can still command the beasts of the wilderness.
He's sending animals to attack us. Is it a bunch of raccoons? Oh wait.
It seems you have need of me. The wolves are possessed, but I think I can help you.
I will try to destroy some of the wolves. Can you destroy them all? Okay. Did you...
Do we have any defense or anything? I need a rock. I need a rock. I need something.
Where are they? Oh fuck. I need something. Pause the game. We need worship right now
because I need like fireballs and shit. I need lightning. Everybody worship. Which
one has the lightning in it? This one does. Okay. It's time. And that's this town here.
All right everybody. I need some of you to stop what you're doing. I need like a 45%.
Everybody. Lightning. It's 98%. Kill somebody quick.
Wolves have reached the village. Stop. Let me fucking do it. Are you kidding me?
You've got to be fucking kidding me. I can't even believe that this would happen.
Like that is unbelievable that that would be in the game.
A wolf came over. They attacked with wolves. A wolf got into the town
and now I lost the entire city. What was the last save? I'm not doing that. That's bogus.
That's actually fucking bogus. That's bogus. The true meaning of that word.
Now I want to spin. Get me out of here. What a pointless room. Where's the save game room?
I can't. Oh sire. A wolf got into the capital. Every single fucking person has turned.
What time is it? Five nine. That's wait. That's like a million years ago.
No no no. Don't delete it. Just get me back. I can't fucking believe it.
252 can i leave this goddamn place i'm actually angry just retake the village
yeah i've seen another three hours how much belief does it have
what the fuck are you i am i see am i am i am i am i the corrective lenses here
to see that's 14 fucking hundred believe i'm cheating i don't care this is stupid i'm cheating
Nah, I, you know, no way. I can't, that's unbelievable.
Is there any cheats here? That took so much time to get it and it's removed in five seconds.
This is not even cheats, this is like a guide for the game.
No, do you guys remember when websites used to do this stupid shit?
And it would be, oh, cheat codes!
And they would just tell you how to get achievements in the game, or how to unlock something.
Aren't you so happy that these websites probably get zero fucking traffic now?
Like, I just went to one of these and I'm probably the first visitor in, like, four years.
God damn it. I can't fucking believe I have to, uh, 13, I have to destroy, it's time to destroy.
I have to destroy the town. I have to just kill everybody.
I have to kill everyone!
I didn't want to do this!
Reload the save, the save reload is from an hour ago.
I can't do that. Just kill everyone and send it to missionary.
Where's lightning?
You guys are worshipping in the wrong one.
It's okay.
I just want to get the cow back.
Why would this mission even be here? This, like, level three?
What?
I'm so upset. I can't fucking believe I have to do this again.
Should I reload it? Should I reload it? How far away was that actually? What time is it?
Five, like, let's say 540.
It was like 30 minutes ago. Let's do it. Let's just reload it. I'm going for it.
Because nothing is worse than having to get 14 fucking hundred, I believe.
It was like 250.
Watch out for those dogs!
519.
Didn't you say this is as good as Half-Life 1?
See, it's 400.
Fuck, I just want my fucking cow!
Oh my god.
Give me a fucking break.
I should just play Skirmish.
I'm in too deep now.
Just stock up on Miracle Juice.
Yeah, I'm just going to go for a fucking total destruction, I think.
Like, I...
What do I need?
Alright, we have to break. Everybody get up here.
Just get rid of this for a fucking second.
I need juice.
I'm going to torch the place and then fucking water it down.
Let's go.
Fireball. Thank you very much.
And then I'm going to keep those people there and then I'm going to get the lightning ready.
I'm going to wait.
Because I also need people to be worshipping at the other one too.
To get lightning.
Abuse pause spam near Lethis's temple.
Let me try. Hold on a minute.
Kill.
Did that not hit anybody?
That didn't do anything.
Good.
Alright, water.
Hurry up and worship me so I can get some damn water.
Okay.
How much do I need?
330.
Do it again.
Don't put it all out. Uh oh.
Fuck my influence. I have no influence over it.
I'm trying to save you.
It's going to keep spreading.
It's going to spread everywhere.
Oh, what have I done? What have I done? What have I done?
Am I not getting belief points anymore? Have they caught on to my bullshit?
Alright, just kill everybody.
Yeah, they caught on.
Make them suffer.
Would you even go over there?
That doesn't even make any mechanical sense.
Oh, he's coming over here.
What's he doing over here?
Now heal them.
Why?
It's like what do you think I'm trying to do?
Do it again.
Heal.
200 belief needed.
I hope I, I gotta get a save after this.
That guy's stealing trees.
Why?
40 belief?
Nice, okay.
Now, hurt them again.
Where?
Okay, there you go.
Flamin' hot cheese?
Trees?
Just throw the wolves next time.
Can I?
What just happened?
So just throw the wolves.
Is that not healing anybody?
Alright, I'm done.
Time to fuck it.
I'm just going for it.
Just torture Twitter again.
Alright, heal, heal, heal, heal, heal.
Hurry up.
It's like 60% of my entire, I was supposed to say audience.
Apparently that's not doing anything anymore.
Now, seriously, don't do this bullshit again.
I want our cow back.
I want him back.
I miss him.
I haven't even seen him all stream.
Okay, everybody alright?
I'm coming.
Save the game?
It's gonna crash.
It will.
Don't do it.
I know.
Wait for an autosave.
I just have to not fuck it up.
No, no, no.
Lightning.
This is worse than the Wiimote gestures.
This is 2001 gestures.
Just cut it down.
Shit's on fucking fire.
Save!
Got one.
Everybody live in here.
Three people are alive.
Let's go.
Everybody's good.
Okay.
Three villages.
And now imagine my annoyance when I did it last time.
And I didn't get a game.
I didn't get a save.
The fuck?
Alright, I got a lot of energy.
Let's drop this down.
Let's go 20%.
20% and 20%.
People need to get back to work.
Am I using the 1.4 patch?
Yes, I am.
1.43?
Alright, I got a forest miracle.
Got a lightning miracle.
We're going to bring some people over here.
And change them to live over here.
Yeah, we're going to move some people.
Do you live here now?
Yeah, that's what I wanted to do.
Like...
Fix everything.
Alright, here he comes.
Here he comes.
He's upset that I did this.
Chilling out.
Come live over here.
Just throw the wolves.
I'm going for that.
I'm going to whip them.
Alright, who needs wood?
You do.
How much?
Okay, you can build that.
Fix that up.
We need food.
I'm working on it.
Miracle food.
So we just call them a crybaby?
Whoa.
Easy.
Miracle food.
More, more, more, more, more, more, more, more, more, more.
Okay.
One more.
Fixing up the town.
Everything's good to go.
There's a lot of settlements over here.
Just pause?
I could just pause, you're right.
Uh, hello?
This is taking a long time.
Miracle food.
You may have your few believers, but I can still command the beasts of the wilderness.
Did he just kill everything?
I think he just accidentally killed all of his stuff.
They're all on fire?
It seems you have meet the wolf.
Here we go.
But I think I can help you.
I will try to destroy some of the wolves.
They're on fire.
That is all.
Okay, here we go.
Get the food miracle off of my bar.
Uh, get the food miracle.
I can't pick them up.
Lightning and I, you can't throw, I can't, I can't, I cannot do anything past here.
I can't do anything past here.
I can't grab anything, I can't cast any spells.
I can't do anything past my influence.
I need the fucking actor over here.
What a crock of shit.
Use the actor and put a shield up.
What the fuck, man.
When it comes to meltdown?
No, but like, why?
You big bully.
Please don't throw me.
You didn't kill me.
On my arm.
Here they come.
All right.
Stop doing fucking slow motion.
What's the point of doing it every time?
Oh, you big bully.
Try it again and you're dead.
I need you over here.
Please don't throw me.
Oh my God.
Stop doing slow motion.
They're going to get in.
I should have just done.
Oh, what a great feature.
Slow mo everything.
You didn't kill me.
I don't even know where they are.
Are they dead?
Do I know lightning?
I do know lightning, but it's going to take too long to load it up and I can't cast it over here.
I don't see anything.
You see anything?
I think I did it.
I don't see any.
Did I do it?
Leave it.
I'm not worth it.
I think that's it.
What do you mean it's there?
Where?
What are you talking about?
This is one more.
What do you see one more?
What are you talking about?
No, there's no more.
We're good.
Oh, hell.
You didn't kill me.
No, there's no more.
All right.
We're safe.
Back to work.
Why won't the game save?
Fuck if I know.
Throw me around.
Now, how am I going to get out there?
This is going to be a huge pain in the ass to go all the way down here.
Check under the tree.
There's nothing there.
No, you don't scare me.
I'm going to I'm going to grow this town.
Yeah.
Okay.
I just scared the absolute shit out of me.
I thought there was one in here.
All right.
Let's bring some.
I got to get some people over here.
We have to build up this town.
Chilling out.
You're now over here.
I'm not worth it.
Fix that, please.
Chilling out.
Disciple builder.
Fix this place up.
Okay.
Now fix this one, too.
Disciple builder.
We need people to live here.
If you see this.
What are you doing?
Oh, please don't pick me up.
I hope that I can't wait till that guy's dead.
I really can't wait till that guy's dead.
Okay.
How much wood do we need?
Disciple builder.
I have plenty of wood.
Let me dump some on all these places.
I want the cow back so bad.
Who lives here?
Wood required, 23.
Just fix this place up.
Right here.
All right.
Build it back up.
I need to...
I need people to come and actually live here.
I thought the prison was 98.
Holy shit.
Okay.
How do I get you to live here, though?
There we go.
Live here and love.
More of you.
I think I can drop...
This town has a ton of people in it.
Let's drop the worshipping a little bit.
Yeah, we can do like...
15% is fine.
Sleeping at home.
We need more people to live.
Your worshippers are working assholes.
Good.
It's not good.
That's...
What am I talking about?
Okay, then.
Over here.
You live here now?
Can you not live there?
Oh, it's a kid.
It's a little kid.
God damn it.
Balding?
Oh, building.
27.
Okay.
It's a little kid.
God damn it.
Balding?
Oh, building.
27.
Live here and love.
Yes.
All right.
More.
We have to really start to settle in this area.
Because this is going to be the one of the last towns.
Live here.
Live here and love.
In fact, you need to breed.
Breed if you can.
What do we got?
Any...
Do we have breeders here?
Breeder?
Yeah.
You guys...
You gotta breed.
You guys gotta breed.
Wait, 80?
Breed.
Finally.
There we are.
Okay.
A couple more.
And then we should be good.
For now, at least.
I'm going to bring a ton of that food over here.
They don't need it.
No, no, no, no.
No.
You do live here already.
Live here and love.
Your people are dying through over-worship.
Stop this at once.
There's only like 10...
There's only like 10% of people doing it right now.
What?
All right.
Give me some of this food.
Okay.
Now they have food.
Now they'll be breeding.
And then I need a...
Where's a...
Where's a production yard?
Do they have one in here?
I don't think they do.
Going home.
All right.
You live here.
Somebody has to fix this shit up.
Whatever.
All right.
With this starting to fill up a little.
Giving birth.
There we go.
Do they have one of those children places here?
I don't think they do.
All right.
Wood.
Do we need a child care center or whatever it's called?
They already have one.
Well, I need to build something.
Does it need wood?
No, that's right.
It's right there.
I need another one of those construction yards.
The workshops.
All right.
I need a civic...
What is it?
What's it called?
Three to make a civic building.
Should I make a new village center?
Or should I make a civic building?
Launch an attack?
You can't.
It doesn't exist.
We haven't had the cow in three hours.
I know the time.
Yeah, I know.
Well, is that my fault?
We have this awesome, really cool, fun, awesome mechanic where you have an animal and they
just take the fucking thing away from you three hours, four hours into the game.
Can I bring this?
What should I do?
This is to make a workshop over here.
I need to like right there.
What is it?
Workshop?
How far can I go out?
Do they have a workshop?
They don't, do they?
All right.
This is it.
This is a cow waiting room.
Yeah, I know.
Me too.
The reason why I did the workshop here is because I'm going to spam trees into it.
Name the cow.
I already did.
What's the name?
How much more wood?
Okay.
Build it.
You too.
Did I just grab you?
Build it.
No.
Sacrifice.
No, I'm not going to sacrifice.
We need, uh, I need more builders over here.
I got to get this.
Get done.
Get it done.
Hurry up.
I don't know where the fuck you're going.
Put down the tree.
Is he going to ever build the graveyard?
The idea here is when this is built, I'm going to spam trees into it and build a ton of shit
and just command and conquer red alert my way over here and then take this over.
But they have to build it first.
Get a graveyard already.
It's part of the plan.
How are we doing on food?
We're okay.
We're okay on wood.
Almost done.
Do I need one more builder over here?
Yes.
Disciple builder.
Oh, I got to ask you a question.
What's, uh, what game is better?
Uh, London 2012 or Beijing 2008?
I want to play one of those Olympic track and field games.
Which one is better?
The London one is better?
I've seen a lot of London.
Okay.
Mario and Sonic?
Yeah, I'm already going to play Mario and Sonic.
All right.
Let me see how far the influence goes here.
Can we get a fresh start?
Can we get like, can we, can we start to progress instead of having me regress mentally?
I want my cow and I'm not stopping the stream until I get him back.
Not in a million years.
Send missionaries.
I can't go that far.
If I grab a missionary, I have to like, see, I can't do anything.
Hurry up and build this damn thing.
Just throw them and hope they live.
Then if I throw somebody that far, they're not going to live.
I don't believe it.
Good.
Just so you don't know.
Is it really taking the three this long to build this?
Like, what is taking you so long?
What's this?
It seems you require help.
That last village is causing you trouble.
So I have given your people the ability to build a wonder.
No.
Too many resources.
I don't have the resources.
That is all.
I don't have the resources to do this.
Twenty one thousand fucking resources.
Thanks for nothing.
Thanks for, thanks for pawning off your shitty real estate that won't sell.
Oh, I have this wonderful four bedroom.
It's just, it's a fixer offer, but you know, you can work with it.
Out of here.
It's literally surrounded by wood.
Yeah, but I still have to build it.
I think these guys can't even make a workshop.
And why do I not have any influence?
I own this building.
This is outside of my influence.
What the fuck?
No.
I need a town center.
Well, let's go.
I'm doing all this for my boy, my baby boy.
I'm coming to get him.
Was it three there?
Okay.
Town center.
It's five, right?
Five for a new village center.
Click the link.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, not yet.
Four.
One more.
If I don't see a cow this spring, I'm, I guarantee you see a cow this spring.
Okay.
There's five here.
How do I not have to be a field?
There's five, right?
Five scaffold.
I don't fucking care.
Just build the damn thing.
He hates the links.
What's the link?
Zoinks.
You've taken a wrong turn.
The link doesn't work.
Punished Mega Milk.
A cow denied by his owner.
Get that out of here.
I'm trying to save him.
I've been trying to save him this whole stream.
Build.
I'll put a hundred people over here.
I don't care.
Get to work.
How much more?
One more.
Okay.
Now get some more builders over here.
And I'm almost done.
Build.
More.
Frank, that's a whole lot of sugar and water.
Go.
Going to sleep on the floor.
Build me a new town center.
Hurry.
So I can go over here.
Might as well just start dumping wood in this thing.
Punish them?
They're okay.
I'll put like another couple of how, no, we need farms and shit out here.
Honestly, I wish Jerma would just say he doesn't like the cow.
We haven't seen him all stream because Jerma's trying to save him, but in reality he doesn't
want him.
Fuck.
God damn it.
Oh.
How could you say something like that?
I love him.
I love Myrius.
How could you say something so incorrect?
Just wait till we get him and it's going to be so much better.
You just had to remember his name.
Yeah, that's true.
You're right.
Yeah, I did.
I just, I just forgot his name again.
Like weirdly enough, I'm forgetting his name because, hold on, let me do the heal.
Because I keep trying not to say the one that you've been planted in my brain.
He's not going to be the same.
Yes, he will.
Looking at something?
I've finished building this.
Finished building that.
You're driving me crazy.
What?
Oh, they're going over there.
Why?
All right.
We're just going to get ourselves another field.
It's going right.
Where's it going?
Right in this town?
No.
Up here.
Where should that go?
Do they even have any way to produce food in this town?
No, this is no food production.
I'll leave it right there.
All right.
What are we going to do over here?
Like literally, like literally, literally right there.
Still not done.
Slowest workers ever.
Just wait for the redemption arc.
Right now we're on a yogi arc.
Just wait.
Wait until we get the redemption arc from Murius.
Put wood in the wonder.
It's too far away for me to reliably do it.
Yeah.
It's too far away for me to do it reliably.
All right.
It's almost done.
Hurry up.
Please.
I need to get over here.
This is ridiculous.
84% complete with a dozen people working on it.
Peter Molyneux, you're not old enough to work.
Here comes the filler episode.
Just wait till we get to the actual arc.
Why is there a seven-year-old up here?
Is that the cow making that noise?
What are you doing here?
Finish it.
Finished.
All right.
Is it?
This is the only area I get.
The population's getting low.
Oh my God.
I can't fucking believe it.
This person's dead.
This person worked to death, apparently.
Worked until they died.
Well, I know where I'm going to put the graveyard.
I'll put it right over here.
Just build a line of houses here.
If I build a house right here, will this expand?
Somebody...
They'll just build it.
Don't work on this right now.
I can't even pick you up.
Work on this.
I just wanted you to work over here.
Like...
Ay, ay, ay.
I'm coming.
Disciple builder.
Now we need to breed.
We're okay with food, right?
All right, breeding time.
Anybody who in this town can breed?
You too, I think.
Offspray.
No.
I gotta start moving people from the other town.
I'm so sick of that fucking happening.
Disciple forester.
What do you think I'm trying to do?
Like...
Stand next to...
Disciple breeder.
He's just pointing and laughing.
Offspray.
Oh my god.
Disciple breeder.
Okay.
We have some breeding going on now.
We're gonna populate this with that town.
And hopefully they'll finish this.
Why are they cutting the tree down?
Because they needed wood.
When are you gonna get to the half-life factory?
I don't even know what that means.
Is that supposed to mean something?
I don't know if that's supposed to mean something.
All right, build that.
How much wood do I need?
All right, there are like four or five breeders over there now.
Now finish this hut.
No, stop going.
I'll take care of this.
Why does...
You don't even need any more wood.
Why are they doing this?
Wood required zero.
What are you guys doing?
Like sledding.
Guys, you don't have to go to the forest for wood.
What are you doing?
No!
Are you going?
Somebody finished this.
They're chasing after the tree.
They don't know what to do.
They can't...
Going to the building site with the wood.
And what, may I ask, are you doing that for?
I'm okay.
I guess you don't...
You made two different piles.
I heard somebody say omega-low in real life and ironically today.
I've heard that once.
I've heard it.
Let's finish it so I can please have some more influence.
Before I actually shit my pants.
Alright, how's the breeding going?
Okay?
Breeder?
Okay, I have a new child.
What about...
Okay, let's check the other town.
We haven't seen it in a while.
That's 85.
Dancing.
Okay.
Let's do some breeding.
Live here in peace.
Disciple Breeder.
I'm going to bring you over here.
I'm going to bring some more of the young people this way.
Let's do some breeding over here.
You live here now.
Live here in love.
Live here and love.
Live here and love specifically.
These people are all like 10.
Disciple Builder.
Offspring.
Wait, what?
This wasn't a...
Alright, I need a female.
27.
Is that a female?
29.
Alright, let's go.
I'm working on it.
Live here.
Live here in love.
And breed.
Disciple Breeder.
There you go.
Okay, keep it going.
How are we doing?
Is this done?
I mean, it's really not that much more influence.
It's like barely any at all.
Save these edits for later.
For when I get the cow and then probably like turn the stream off.
Because it's been like 8 hours doing this dumb shit.
Alright, I gotta start to pull the...
We gotta start to build this shit.
Hopefully this actually does what I think it's going to do.
How many more do I need?
10,000?
Does anybody have 10,000 wood over here?
I'm not even sure there's 10,000 wood in this entire forest.
I missed the cow.
Yeah, because without the cow, this game just turns into like a grindy building sim.
The cow was fun and funny and shit and they took him from us.
They took him from you.
Yeah, but it's us.
We're in this together.
Can I not grab from this forest?
Nothing to do.
Except for build this house.
Not under attack.
Build.
Looking for something to do?
What the fuck are you talking about?
Do I have to drop the actor here?
Someone will eventually build this thing.
I hope.
How much more wood?
A thousand.
I'm starting to shimmy around in my chair.
Alright.
For the love of God, build this so I can finish this stupid level.
Is this what that person was talking about when they said,
Oh, you got to level three.
Laugh out loud.
Is this why you were laughing?
Is this why you thought this was so funny?
He warned you.
Just build this.
Just build it.
Does everybody fucking get over here and build this shit?
I want my cow.
Disciple builder.
Your ignorance has led to your defeat?
I don't think so.
Disciple builder.
What do you mean defeat?
I'm not defeated yet.
Peter Molyneux.
Go build this.
Disciple builder.
You don't have to go get food.
I'll take care of that.
Just stay there.
I'm just going to dump it right next to you guys.
Here.
No, I can't.
Your influence, you can't move.
Finish it.
Forty one.
Get over here.
Build it.
They're getting wood.
Stomp them.
I just have to get up here.
And then we release our friend who we want so desperately and so badly.
And then when I get out of here, I'm going to fucking murder.
I'm going to murder this motherfucker right here.
I'm going to kill that guy so badly.
So close.
Build this wonder.
How close?
What's the percentage?
Is it done?
Twenty seven percent complete.
Oh, that's a huge.
That's a that.
That's a.
All right.
In the meantime, let's work on.
In the meantime, we have to work on family building here.
We need offspring.
That's a two year old.
I wish I could group grab people instead of having to drag all the way across and grab
somebody and bring them all the way back.
Disciple forester.
And I also wish it wasn't the same button.
You know what I'm saying?
Like, I don't want you.
I want you to be.
I don't.
Why does it have to be the same button?
I want you to breed and nothing else.
And I have to wait till the indicator goes correct because it's a tree next to me.
Well, I just had it.
Disciple forester.
Oh, man, I'm starting to get annoyed.
The cracks in the armor is showing in black and white one.
It was the cow that was keeping it all together.
Stay strong for the cow.
Oh, I'm going to.
Don't you worry.
We need offspring.
God damn it.
Build this already so I can stop this madness and have fun.
Live here in peace.
But you possibly have nothing to do.
Fun?
We're not supposed to be doing that right now.
What percentage is this at?
Fifty one.
It's almost there.
And then hopefully we get a big circle here.
And then I can finally just take this over and be done with this.
We need offspring.
There are no women in this whole fucking village.
When I started the game, it was 80 percent men.
There are no females.
Disciple breeder.
Offspring.
Live here in peace.
Whose baby is it going to be?
I don't know.
We're not going to know.
Do the tree puzzle.
When's my wonder going to be done?
Do like a paternity test.
Wow.
Ooh.
Whoa.
We need offspring.
We need women.
We need women is what we need.
Is this person carrying a rock?
What are you carrying?
Wow, we need offspring.
We need more than three women in the entire group.
Is that a wolf?
I can't grab them because it's stupid.
This is a stupid border thing.
Which one of them is the woman?
The wolves don't care.
At least people are breeding over here.
What's presented?
Nothing to do.
Any women.
Yeah.
Disciple breeder.
Now you have something to do.
Excuse me.
Come on out.
Any women?
No.
Go back to bed.
Any women?
All right.
Who's in here?
There are breeders over here now, right?
All right.
Let's go back this way.
Here we go.
Okay.
Now we're making some babies.
Offspring.
I think this is the only woman in the whole town.
These are all her children.
Look at all these kids now.
All right.
We have lots of kids.
I think we can stop with this now.
Go back to, go back to foresting.
Excuse me.
Get out.
Get out of the house.
Oh, were you guys, oh, were you busy in there?
Wait.
I need you.
Do what you're doing, but do it over here.
Offspring.
Live here in love.
Okay.
Offspring.
Here comes the 78-year-old female.
Disciple breeder.
She's already giving birth?
Oh, there we go.
All right.
Did you build it yet?
Who's dead?
Is somebody dead?
89%.
Will you fucking just fix it already?
I need food.
How's a baby formed?
Two people that love each other.
What's half of spring?
I don't know.
Ask your parents.
But you're my dad.
I am not your dad.
93%.
Peter Molyneux, hurry up and finish it.
Peter Molyneux, hurry up and make another game
where you make this big group social experiment
with somebody that gets to the center of a giant cube
that potentially cost hundreds of dollars to spam mine the cube.
When they get to the center of that cube,
you make them the creative director for your new game,
but it's not real, and that game barely even comes out.
If you were the last person to click inside of the cube
in that Peter Molyneux cube game,
you got to be the creative director of Goddess, right?
And didn't the person that won not even get to do that?
Didn't they bring him into a room and they were like,
ah, well, you're really not going to do that,
but do you think that this would be fun?
And the dude's like, I guess.
Okay, thanks for coming.
You did it.
You made it to the center of the cube.
Wait, we're done.
We got it.
Is it done?
It's not done, is it?
I didn't get anything, so I got lied to by the yogi guy.
This doesn't do anything.
At this point, I think I'm going to start throwing fucking rocks
from over here.
I'm just building single houses in a straight line this way.
Houses don't give influence.
Only town center and scaffoldings do.
Well, how the fuck am I supposed to get over here?
Build another town center over here?
Do I have to use the throw guy?
I have to increase my population massively.
I mean, they're going at it.
They're going for it.
Offspring.
Live here in peace.
It's all men.
It's all fucking men.
Offspring.
We only have men.
There's only males.
Why?
Let's go find out once and fucking for all.
I want to see just how stupid this is.
All right.
60% male.
But that could be in the other villages.
No, I don't want to go in the creature cave.
I want...
He's angry clicking now.
I just want to...
I just want my fucking creature back because that was fun.
There are so many people over here.
So many kids.
We have to start bringing...
I mean, I have so many people, though.
Like, I have a lot of people.
I make up a majority of all the population in this whole world.
Look at all these kids.
Do I really have to get the throw guy and, like,
bring a missionary or something over there?
What's the premise of this game in five words?
Game sucks without the cow.
There.
Where's the guy that I can throw?
This guy's 94 years old.
Throw me around.
You think I care?
Please don't throw me.
94 years old.
I hope you don't die because I need you.
All right.
How much influence do I need here?
What is it at?
How much do I need?
500?
Not too bad.
Just destroy the whole fucking town.
And then I finally get my cow.
Where is he?
Please don't throw me.
You didn't kill me.
I'm gonna try not to throw you.
Please don't throw me.
You didn't kill me.
All right.
This is actually where I have to raise the banner here.
Please don't kill me.
I need lightning.
I'm just destroying the whole thing.
Where's the lightning?
Here it is.
All right.
Let's get lightning.
Let's do, like, 60%.
I'm gonna put food over there.
Must build homes.
Hopefully we can release that cow.
The village stored is nearly out of food.
I know.
But it don't matter because half of them are going over there anyways to worship.
They're going to this one, right?
Yes.
Is it this one?
I think it's that one.
Wait, which one is it?
Is it the one on the right or the one on the left?
Yeah, it's the one on the left.
Give me the lightning.
Eventually.
All right.
There's food over there.
Hey, where's that actor?
Let's torch the place.
Was he dead?
Where is he?
Where the hell did he go?
No, that's not the same guy.
That's the yogi guy.
Wasn't he, like, right here?
Yeah, he was right here.
Is he fucking dead?
There he is.
All right.
So begins the process again where we use this 100-year-old man to be able to...
And we have to listen to this shit again.
Oh, my eye.
Use him for his intended purpose?
What the hell is his intended purpose?
He has an actual purpose?
earth isn't.
Put him out! Put him out! Put him out! Put him out! Put him out! Put him out! I need to put him out.
Put him out! Put him out! Put him out! Put him out! Is he dead? Can he die? He can't die though,
right please don't throw me okay he's good what did that do how much more belief do i need
please don't throw me torture him no i need to try to like at least get this town
you didn't kill me get off get off you didn't kill him get off get off me burn down the enemy's
building that's kind of slowly but surely what i'm trying to do get off me you didn't kill please
don't throw me okay here we go let's see what about how much is it let me see
you didn't please don't throw me you didn't kill me how much do i need 400 i just did okay that
should be easy please don't throw me oh you big please don't throw me okay let's try this again
torture it again you didn't kill me
indian power we raid hell down oh you big bully try to get me
dead water oh you big bully try it again and you're dead
it's necessary okay i don't want to do this anymore he's going berserk no i'm not going berserk
try it again and you're dead you didn't kill me my hand what's going to be my hand oh you big bully
try it again and you're dead how many more beliefs do i need 270 where's the actor where's the actor
there he is you didn't kill me water duster oh you big bully try water you didn't kill me
water i can't do water it's wrong water oh you big bully try it again and you're dead
attack look at his hand you i don't want to do this anymore the blood moon is rising
um they're the wrong people are worshiping try it again and you're dead this is all for the cow
guys it's all to get the cow and then we can finally the world is evil blood moon rising oh
oh god okay i have to calm down something's wrong with your minions
looking oh shit where's the actor he's currently on fire somewhere right there he is
big bully you didn't kill me water oh you big bully try it again and you're dead
did i heal
75 belief holy fuck that's a lot
oh you big bully only 182 let's heal again
it didn't kill me heal come on hurry up it's like 60 percent of my entire population is praying
right now what is going on here don't do this we're supposed to be buddies oh you big bully
try it again and you're dead all right now i need what is this one teleport try it again and you're
i don't want this put it down you didn't kill me water you didn't kill me
i can't believe it's taken this long to get a god damn
you didn't kill me you didn't kill me this is absurd why is it taking this long for the food
are you out of your mind this is like 50 people praying oh you big bully try it again and you're
dead start sacrificing people yeah fuck it i don't give a shit anymore like this is ridiculous like
this is ridiculous it's ridiculous what on earth man like what the fuck what that was a child
i didn't see it you're ridiculous this is ridiculous you didn't kill water douse the
flames wait i just have to hold this guy on fire in front of people you telling me i could have
done this the whole time oh it's don't get too close oh shit it's okay how many more belief do
i need before i get it done with it no no no no no no five believe look look at it look at it
you must look at it look at it oh shit um i can't put them down anymore uh-oh
what am i doing uh desperately trying to beat level three you didn't please don't throw me
all right here we go oh you big bully try to please don't you didn't kill me
almost ready come on how much more like 20 please don't throw me porn link don't put any porn links
in here get that delete that and fucking ban that person no porn links 61 believe needed
big bully to get please don't throw me you didn't kill me get off get off me
heal again good idea you big bully try it again and you're dead
give me my fucking cow now give me my cow that was five hours to do this give me my cow now
we've taken over the village oh wait did somebody get loose
oh i'm sorry
again there he is super milk oh my god he's not this bad i'm so happy the game's got better
come home come home come home to us come on yeah we'll take good care of you we love you we love
you
the village store is nearly out of food he's all the way back here he can't defend this village
oh fuck okay all right all right all right let's go let's go let's go go go go go
oh we need uh rebuild you got plenty of wood rebuild we're running out of wood
best joke taking more than five hours
i wasn't even making the joke i wanted him back he got lightning bolted this
bullshit look at all this food i'm stealing all of it there is like 50 000 food in here
i'm taking almost all of it who needs it you guys do over here look at this shit yep there you go
let's heal him where is he he's back okay now we can chill we can chill he's thirsty
yay i'm so happy he's looking for something to drink okay um pull this down
and do like 30 he's learning how to use the totem he's that smart look at him our
followers are annoyed with you i gotta drop this 28's fine all right where is he come here
that's so good to have you back
it's so good to have you back go take a nice rest and then we're gonna bring you
we're gonna do some more strength training and you're killing that guy now the real question is
i've got to get him back over here actually yeah he has to defend this
oh fuck oh fuck oh fuck oh fuck oh fuck oh fuck oh fuck oh fuck
i suppose you think he deserved that lightning where's he going where's he going where'd he go
where'd he just go wasn't he just walking down am i insane where is he top right in the water
what he's not over here dickhead i can wait i don't want to waste the spell
oh i think that guy's just broken fuck it
kill oh look who's coming got you motherfucker
you gotta heal gotta heal somewhere all right let's i gotta get my buddy
let's go i should have that should do it what's he up to
you good come with me i need you it's a long walk but you can get there you can do it come on
moonshine what's his name come on moonshine come on murius i gotta build this place back up to um
teleport miracles should i use it i need to use it twice right everyone's like dead here though
you and me are gonna take this place hopefully how strong is this guy i wonder all right let
go of this uh let's do some nobody lives here i have to like deposit people over
what are we doing get the hell out of here get away from me quit looking at my screen
quit looking at my screen get out of here he's trying to get his creature to come down here
yep look at he's trying to get his creature to come down here just rest over here what's he doing
oh shit okay okay okay okay um
let's get let's water some of the shit or actually wood excellent work excellent work come here
already helping he'll be more kind and generous to those sorts of guys
i need you over here i think it's time it's time for vengeance it's vengeance time let's go
here's the redemption arc
oh no it's a mirror match they keep getting lit on fire i need water what let's go
stop
i need heal heal heal heal heal heal stop
heal heal heal what the fuck was that heal he didn't do a heal do a heal do a heal do a heal
do a heal you can do it don't be sad about you messing up a fucking like water miracle
yes what a beautiful display yeah fuck you no stop pointing stop pointing point
where are you going oh no he's like let's go motherfucker he's like let's go back it up back
it up he's angry oh right in the fucking head get in there again get his ass off the cliff he's
gonna strike first he gets the head but it's all right cheating he's cheating oh sorry walk walk
walk get in there get in there knock his ass off the cliff offense all offense get in there
come on get in there this is it this is every man for himself get it knock his ass off the cliff
no no he's got one hp come on come on with all of your fury with all of your vengeance
with all of your destructive power
oh
he tried so hard he almost had it too oh it was saved during the fight let's go
wait don't no hold on oh he had he had no health too he had zero fucking hp oh oh that was so
that was so awesome and it just he didn't finish the job he had it oh too bad too bad that was a
really good attempt wait did it actually save right in the middle you could have ordered him
to heal yeah i was trying to i was trying to do that like do i have to like cast and then do it
708 that's not correct 731 i think that's correct let's go why does he have no health
i got anti-save scum what do the one right before it i can't believe he didn't kill him
that's so sad he really gave it his all too oh we would have had like a super moment oh well
seven now that's not that one was is there one right next to it what's this one 721
yeah that's 10 minutes before that give it a shot let's try it no throw me around you think i can
it's all right god damn it i gotta do this stupid bullshit again and he's like at full health
at least he's not frozen anymore i mean i can just just terrorize his town
now
where are you going heal your creature and then load the save where you were in the middle of the
fight you'll be at 100 health really that's kind of ridiculous really lightning
how does that make sense that might make sense yeah that makes some sense
all right let's try he's hungry though okay let's get some food here i know just the person for you
to eat the village store is nearly out of food you big bully try to get please don't throw me
oh let go of me get rid of this guy once for all okay he's gonna poop his pants
is that what that means oh please don't pick me up this smell isn't my fault what hold on wait wait
wait wait wait if you eat him he let go of me i'm so confused what this smell isn't my fault
okay one more time and then he's will heal he'll be at full health stop don't fucking hit him idiot
now load that safe you think that'll work i'll give i'm gonna give it a try we'll see i just came
back what the fuck are you doing you know playing playing a game all right what's next what's what's
this one all right let's let's what's this doom song how about this one look at this one all right
ready let's see if it works so it is this one right here 7 31 p.m let's go give it a try full
health did it work cast a heal mirror i don't have enough time to cast a miracle right there
he just dies in one hit healed before he hits you yeah that's so that's gonna be so hard to do that
no i seem to the one afterwards i was to do the one that i should have done the one from seven
wait that is the is that the latest one 720 wait what 9 39 that's not correct
now whatever healed before reloading that's what i just did that is actually what just happened
you fed him you didn't heal him what how much what is it what is it where's his health
no he his damage wasn't at 83 it was at zero no you know you guys he was at zero all right
i'm i'm taking out the village he healed himself i'm winning what's the best way for me to do to do
this probably just to go like this honestly like i just took this person i was gonna one by one
wipe out the entire village this is not gonna work sacrifice their people it's just they don't
have enough time to get in here and do anything did i get somebody no i got their food lightning
indian indian we sure did a real good moving around the fire yeah good luck indian
you just threw an eight-year-old another life tossed away in vain indian throw a fireball
fireballs are the hardest thing in the world to control in this game it's completely unreliable
what i really need to do is come over here with indian have the cow do this
indian indian indian where's the actor what is this there's like a
i can't do click on the fucking jesus pleased to meet you i can make the old young
bring me an old villager and i'll wind back the years oh yes i don't like this old bat at all
i say we try our out in my i can't i can't go over here all right where's the cow you having
fun how you doing come with me we got places to go don't give me the finger i need you to come
win the game for me so you go this way well i and i'll go get the actor and torch the city
and then hopefully we can kill that stupid coyote or whatever it is and be done with it
here's the fucking here's the coyote now what are you doing get out of here your worshipers are
working and dying for you what is that noise oh hell i hear electricity you didn't kill me
don't get back here indian power you didn't kill me get off get off me
destroy the entire fucking city everything kill everything
destroy everything you didn't kill me you big bully try to water douse the flames oh you big
bully kill try it again and you're dead
douse the flame oh my god that way that was jeff keely what are you talking about
no it wasn't oh you big bully try to water douse the flames oh you big bully try it again and
you're dead ain't gonna be anybody left who's the flame oh you big bully try it again and you're
dead come here 1610 belief needed
try it again well it don't exist anymore now does it
try it again and you're dead it don't exist anymore now does it dumb is this people are dying at the
worship site now bring in the cow big bully has the cow made it is the cow still walking
oh my god what's going on here no no no no go back back back back back back back back back back
oh what's going on spare me and i will give you everything here i give you the creed from
kazaa's creature spare me wait i we were gonna it's a rematch the coyote came all the way down
here to fight me to survive and i will guide you to yet another creed it is in a land you once knew
use this vortex find the creed there it is yours i think a bird just got sucked in
but i beg please leave me with my last village without it i will be banished to the void
where you belong where's your fucking where is he get over here where's the where's this creature
roaming around back here somewhere go find him he was coming to me there he is all right you
fucking dick once and for all once and for all what's he doing what's he doing
he wants to sweep the lake oh shit he just sees play defense play defense let him burn
do it again it's all right use your strengths what i taught you that was unbelievable
ah very good job now go spawn camp him lightning
he's so good you just have to do is look at he's burning away he's like no no i don't want to do
with you you're too strong you have insane lightning moves slay him save them you only
have to lower your village totem your creature is on a killing spree kill kill him
look at the anger remember this remember when you did this shit to me i remember i remember
yes i do revenge don't let him out more fire i'm trying to help take this down you know you can
do it here burn the building down there it is more do it again burn it this is for you this is you
murius this is your fight this is your revenge i'm gonna let you have it completely
oh you what are you back for more save them you only have he can't even cast a fucking spell
he can't even cast a fucking way he shrunk me what he's shrinking me he wants he wants revenge
he's like now this is my final stand that was the plan all along don't let him beat you
he didn't care go go for the castle he's getting tired
let's go here we go again i'll let him get you back don't let him get you back
oh fuck he's he's getting close was he out of mana he's out of mana he's too tired
people are dying through over worship stop this at once he's tired he's too tired he cast
he cast like 10 lightning bolts and five fireballs at the fucking temple guy
oh no now he's coming for revenge
what's he doing is he coming he's coming
lightning
wait hold on a minute is he coming where is he going
is he coming all the way down to spawn camp me i kind of need to know guys don't ever
grief each other in the lobby because this is just what happens it never stops
this will go on perpetually forever until somebody leaves the server he's already up
he's already up the people are suffering he's already up
he's not actually oh fuck i didn't mean to do that he needs to eat something
we're gonna beat up now eat him wait oh he's torturing the village you motherfucker
what happened why did he get up why did he get up he's over here causing mayhem
oh he's coming he's coming he's coming he's stop getting up eat food miracle food
here eat this yes eat it eat yes eat it eat that food eat it he's burning
down my village i'm gonna fucking lose my mind guys okay go get him where is he go in the vortex
i'll go in the vortex after one more fight if he's not on the way i'll go to the vortex
if he's not on the way just use the vortex fuck it he's right here though look at him
fuck face your people are dying through over worship stop this at once oh are you scared
oh is he coming wait you missed you tried to cast a fireball out of what are you doing
like this done you don't have any mana get in there no more taunting get in there
this is it the final battle with the fucking lightning going in the background new song uh this
one good nice job you got meter advantage good lightning lightning storm him
lightning storm him bingo get in there right ahead smart move what did he give up what's going
on did he give up what happened wait he wanted he's like i got i don't want to do this though
look at this guy right here wait is it are they friends i don't understand
are they friendly so people are dying through over worship i wanted to see if they're gonna be
friends wrongly i know but that's fine where are they going and why is he so much faster than me
they stopped fighting and then then i changed the leash well after that i have no idea where the
fuck he's going i'm gonna just go in the portal let's go in the portal and end this finish off the
god well that's what i was trying to do last time but he fucking ran out of energy there is
no last village all right i'm gonna give this one side one second here to see what happened
and i'm going through the portal oh my god you're getting fucking flexed on
all right now fight
oh
take off the leash take off the leash take off the leash all right i'm fucking out of here
i'm out of here go in the portal quick go in the portal i'm just going in get in the portal i
don't care how do you come back from the break dance off actually no supplies it's all right
i don't know if i'm gonna continue here we are you know you did the right thing by sparing let
this leader just look at the state of the place it's been oddly blasted how cool is that
oh it's awful it used to be green and pleasant
we have actually you'll remember these oh that's the tutorial wow and i recall some of these
buildings and even our temple it's all rather damaged though you're right still the atmosphere
is much better now wait what what the hell is going on what am i supposed to do about
what am i what's going on uh what do we do we have to build up our village and shelter the
people from this terrible storm now leave them it'll put hairs on their chests it'd be better
to explore and find out what's going down in this land there he is murius here have a cow
all right i think i'm i think i'm done i think i'm done i think i'm done i don't know if i can
handle this anymore you're gonna abandon him i'm not gonna abandon him for this dancing thing okay
we need to find the big uh where's the sheep yeah the sheep's already gone what oh please don't harm
me i come trembling with fear before you you have to speak up i'm from the village nearby
well i play black and white too i asked you to remove the curse on our land visited us
long ago he showed us his power and his might it was a terrifying display
yeah actually before i let me check out the skirmishes you see this land used to be beautiful
we lived in peace here and we didn't want for anything then the gods themselves appeared with
the concepts of good and evil at first always will but then the one called nemesis arrived
and punished us for following you that dance-off was seriously ridiculous that was some loony-tuned
shit we were forced to worship him he brought forth fire from the heavens he gave us pillars
of lightning our lives have become a living hell even the sky turned the color of blood
but nemesis got bored with us and left us alone he wanted to continue his quest to be the only god
so he set three guardian stones to the first lies under a spiritual shield even the wisest of our
people don't know how to reach it it's like the end of the game the second guardian stone was
entrusted to a vicious ogre he's too strong for any mere mortal to beat that was the second to
last level oh shit this level is really really hard lonely old man who worships only nemesis
the whole game has been kind of like that this is everything we know please help us in our plight
you have all of our support holy one oh the fireballs for now at least
okay fireballs have stopped have they though i mean this is i don't know this is annoying and
loud and all over the place disciple builder i don't like this level it's too loud and flashy
disciple builder all right defeat three gods to control the realm defeat two defeat another god
defeat three gods let's see what it looks like oh there he is oh this is huge what do we what
do we got over here do you not have what the fuck is that do these guys not have creatures
i don't think they do fog of war maybe all right don't go too far let me just see we got
uh i need what do i have temple there's a graveyard there's where's he going i don't
like you just wandering off all on your own zerg rush him with mega milk that's not his name you
can scroll through some of these info signs to read all the text hold the action button on the
text and move up or down i know i know any information i know i know i know i know i know
i know added to the library in the temple now let's just we need food how we doing on farms
yeah people are doing it disciple farmer he's just going i don't know where he's going but
he's just going what can i play too that's a zebra get over here why are you running away from me
wait you have two you've got a big turtle where did you get all these people well just hang out
you want to hang out we don't have to hurt each other we don't have to do anything bad we don't
have to hurt anything we can just be friends what are you doing you don't like me i look kind of
pissed off i just gave him food cool look we i don't even we don't even need to hurt each other
what's this whole conquering thing we can just hang out with the other gods all right what about
you can i go say hi to you go say hello over here okay curious yeah what's the does the turtle
want to play all right who's attached to who here is there another god down here i don't know where
they're going that's a good question okay first meeting hey stop leaving me out stop excluding me
that's not fun what's he doing water he's being friendly i don't know i could just sit here and
watch this for like 20 minutes in fact that's what i am doing all right go talk go make some friends
hey what is he this is is this his this is his town wait who am i fighting who am i fighting
wait okay oh big roundhouse kick get him right in the stomach are my hands on fire
heal do a heal heal we're both on fire kick him kick him that's the end of the stream
i'll see you later i'll see you tomorrow the village stored is nearly out of food
why was the turtle kicking the shit out of his own house pizza tier list all right i'll do a pizza
tier list before i go uh black and white that was fun today was a little more grindy than i would
have wanted it to be but uh we still got some i think at least nine out of ten moments it was
very very fun the game's fucking hilarious it's classic and i might move on to two for the next
one get the expansions i don't know if the expansions will work on i it might be hard
to get to work i'll look into it creature isle is pretty fun yeah that was fun i love the little
creatures i wish they just made a game where you could just do this you know i wish there was a
little creature town and there was a bunch of creatures they could get along they would fight
i love this so much i love it spore but yeah spore but spores not this like this though
there's no cow in spore make one don't even make one just buy a couple of ant farms now
we'll move on to the second one or maybe the expansion but obviously not immediately
tomorrow what we're going to do we're probably just going to do katana zero tomorrow
because i've been putting it off for like two weeks so we're going to do katana zero tomorrow
after katana zero we'll have to see i'm not sure there's a lot of things on the menu
probably no more heroes too yeah but that's going to wrap it up for tonight
play viva piata i could do that but this is this has been a lot of fun i hope you guys have
enjoyed it it's an old old game and we'll see you tomorrow out of wilds i know there's a lot
there's a lot of games to play if you can get a copy of black and white i highly recommend you
try to get it installed and play it because it can be pretty fun see you guys tomorrow
seems like a perfect place to stop it don't forget the pizza all right where is it give me
the pizza tier list all right let's go over this just give me one second yeah yeah yeah you're
right you're right here here here what should i do here pizza toppings uh i need this to be a
different window all right now that this i can do this this is gonna be this will be easy
this won't take very long let's get this window open there we go pizza toppings tier list
capturing that weird fucked up window like this pizza toppings tier list yeah
okay there is this how many around here kind of a lot is it eggs why are there eggs here
who puts eggs on pizza what are you doing okay that's fine that's fine all right all right
okay here we go uh i don't even what is this i don't can't i can't even see what half these
fucking things are is this what is it cheese pizza cheese puke alert all right mozzarella
i'm gonna put it up here for now play dough what is that yogurt olives no not on pizza
hot peppers i can't eat them anymore i would ketchup on pizza what is this tier list avocado
pizza i don't think anybody does this who puts cucumbers on pizza
oh that hurt oh
corn on pizza eggplant okay onions this list is horrible honey this is not even where's pepperoni
it's like oysters walnuts tom are you tomato slices on you
now give me a new list give me a new list this list this list is bogus this is a bogus list
absolutely this one's bogus hold on close that give me a new one is this one correct
i mean this one's this one's closer than this one was okay bacon yeah this this is closer this is
closer imagine eating a healthy pizza imagine imagine putting walnuts on your pizza i'm sorry
that's just that's odd to me imagine corn all right bacon here we go uh i'm gonna move this
stuff around is a steak i wouldn't put steak on pizza peppers i don't like peppers on pizza this
is this is chicken it can be okay depends i don't know eggplant nope broccoli on pizza is actually
okay um pineapple i don't put it on pizza was this fresh parmesan i don't know i don't know
what some of this stuff is mushrooms mushrooms are good where's pepperoni pepperoni the right stuff
onions are good parmesan is good on pizza i don't even know did this is parmesan i can let me
let me get the list ready spinach on pizza no thank you jalapenos i can't eat it i can't
why is corn on this list again i'm so just sausages sausages all right let me get this
correct um what is this tomatoes what is that crab meat no thanks that's bogus um olives and it was
this garlic or what tofu is it garlic or tofu the croutons what is this you don't put garlic
bread on pizza you guys put croutons on pizza it's probably garlic all right hold on let me
get this right pepperoni onion bacon goes up here chickens and chickens up it belongs above
bacon in my opinion broccoli goes up there uh mushrooms are okay i'd rather have garlic
then bell peppers is basic and it just tastes like water i don't like them
parmesan can go up here the tomatoes just if the pizza sauce is made of the tomatoes
i don't know this is supposed to be steak well i can tell you i'd rather have pineapple on pizza
than steak on pizza these are down here are either i can't eat them or they just seem odd to me
they're anchovies odd days no they're not that looks like a cut off steak no i think that i
think this is pretty close see everyone that's saying that parmesan what's wrong with you
parmesan's incredible parmesan is a great masking of bad pizza if you dump parmesan
cheese all over your slice of pizza it's because the pizza is not very good and you're making it
taste better that you don't have to put a bunch of parmesan cheese on a really good high quality
slice pizza it's like sriracha laughing my ass off that's incorrect it's a child flavor palette
because i don't want to put corn on my pizza i can't believe you put eggplant down in f tier
when was the last time you guys ordered eggplant on your pizza probably never oh yeah what do you
want for pizza okay if i'm the child then you're you're the person that nobody wants to order a
pizza with okay oh let's get let's get a pizza yeah what should we put on it how about eggplant
and spinach it's like get the fuck out of here i don't what i don't want to order a pizza with
you yeah maybe we should put corn and crab meat on it uh you can get your own pizza actually
well if we think about this i don't want that why jalapenos down here jalapenos would be up here
but i can't eat them anymore i physically can't do it anymore you know what i was thinking but
yeah uh instead of like pepperoni onion or like bacon chicken bacon or sausage or broccoli bacon
broccoli chicken i want corn and anchovies you i'm gonna just tell you honestly guys you will be
somebody that has to order your own pizza no one's gonna want to share this pizza with you
with corn and spinach on it and i don't i don't want olives i like olives i like olive oil but
i don't like olives like just eating olives they don't they don't belong down here though
i would probably i'd rather have olives on my pizza then yeah no no i actually wouldn't i
actually wouldn't mind it if it was on it i would eat it i don't love it i don't really like it but
i would eat that slice this is stuff that i wouldn't eat if it was on pizza pineapple is higher
than spinach i mean yeah you've never had spinach on pizza then oh i have i have it's great when you
bite into a slice of spinach on it and the spinach comes off and peels off like the lid of a yogurt
and it's like it's stuck on your mouth and somebody i know at least a few you know what
i'm talking about it's it's like that solid it just pulls off and like slaps you in the mouth
and it's like the shape of a yogurt lid pineapple on pizza sucks i just i don't i would say number
one i'd want i would want pepperoni or um peppers probably should be a little higher than this
because like peppers mushrooms like i don't i don't you know i don't think so i don't think so
i don't order sausage on my pizza ever i don't i love onion on pizza it's incredible though i love
onion yeah i think that's more accurate if this is garlic then it's more accurate now it is no
it's not okay that's safe no explain your olive hate um i don't i just regular olives just just
tastes like acid to me they they taste sour and acidic olives are just bitter and gross i mean
i'm not going to say they're gross i like olive oil is amazing i love olive i put olive oil on
everything you're so based and epic for this you're so based okay you brown noser hey leave him
alone leave him alone just because they didn't want corn on his pizza leave him alone all right
you passed the test you passed the test okay you passed the test i thought if i put uh bacon down
here people are gonna freak out and i was gonna call you hypocrites okay more and more that i
think about this i wouldn't i don't order sausage on pizza i don't order mushrooms either on pizza
i do sometimes but not as much as i would get like that's accurate all right i'm done why broccoli
you've never had broccoli on pizza before it's amazing now it's done dog food why would i do a
dog food tier list i've never eaten it dog food derma tier list tier list wait hold on i'm not
doing this this is just this is just dumb like this is just bizarre i best hot pockets i can do
this one really fast okay you ready let's do best hot pockets this one's gonna go real quick
okay best hot pocket uh where is the meatball marinara where is it i know it's here somewhere
meatball marinara where is it that's it right there right and where's the steak and cheese one
it's like this it's the steak with the cheese and the peppers and the onions where's that one
right here okay all right why do we got to do hot pockets like this uh and it was a ham and cheese
was it was the ad no the ham and cheese ones right here right yep okay that's correct that's
actually accurate what about the four cheese no the rest of these diversities you should never eat
them he's eaten all of them no i've eaten most is that chicken pot pie oh gross i have eaten
the ham and cheese when i've eaten the i've had i've had some of these and i've just don't want
no these are the only ones that are really that really that good what about the breakfast one
no no just don't eat jimmy deen's instead jimmy deen makes much better breakfast sandwiches
i would rather have a jimmy deen frozen sausage egg and cheese than a hot pocket egg and cheese
burrito thing people eat these i thought there was a meme no i used to eat these all the time
especially these three all frozen fruit is gross ah i don't know i don't agree with you there
it can be okay best oreo flavors i can do this one because hopefully okay if it's on the list
i will put it five times higher than everything else is it on the list
now this is an incredibly this is a terrible list for oreos is there a better one with all
the oreo flavors there's got to be a better one than that is this one on it nope not on it
oreo here's another one what about these ones no no the moon the moon marshmallow ones are not
on here it's the best one you can possibly eat the marshmallow moon it was limited time
they were the best all right i'm gonna get out of here fat asses hey oh is it on here
no no it's not on here cool mint oreos okay they yeah cool mint oh those are good but there's no
moon oreos i don't even need to open this uh cool mint oreos um birthday cake oreos i don't like
double stuff double stuff would be an f-tier because it's just too much it's just too much
in the middle and just gross yeah this is my list cool mint's pretty good yeah all right
i'll see you guys tomorrow we're gonna do katana zero tomorrow i made about the sleeve of oreos
yeah they weren't double stuff oreos thanks for sticking around for watching black and white
made some great memories with the cow and now i'll see you tomorrow we're gonna do the uh subs
and the bits and everything there was a new twitch feature that was apparently tested today
that dumped another fucking like almost thousand dollars on the channel in an instant more than
that so thanks again everybody for that i'm gonna try to go over them because that was
insane there's a new hype train thing where if a certain amount of money comes into the channel it
activates this i don't know it was bizarre but this is where it started thank you everybody
and especially thank you sir fluke's a lot thanks for the five gifted subs brotescules thanks for
the five subs captain nemo five subs potion dweller gave 250 i don't know what this is i'm scared help
germa stop please stop it stop the hype train this is such shilling this is a shilling nightmare
i didn't even know what it was i didn't even know what it was what do you what do you what
do you was it what was it was it was it jonathan tell jonathan breaks tells you you're wrong for
47 seconds it's totally pure fiction it's fiction it's fiction we made this one it's a made-up tale
oh we made this one up we made it up i remember those that show is ridiculous uh smokewise ganja
thanks for the five subs brain land 300 bits hype train soy dev five subs this this goes on
is crazy bulbous wag thanks for the 1500 bits what the fuck is a hype train i just wanted to
say i was going to miss the stream can't wait to watch how you handle level three on the vod
love you well we we handle it if you if you're here now in the future it was kind of a pain in
the ass spent an hour following a guy around a cliff desperately watched the the one thing
that i loved in the game be tortured for five hours but we did finally get our revenge we got
our vengeance that level was that level was painful and some in a lot of regards and i and
i lost the dance battle yeah that's too that's horrible poor murius it's okay murius will come
back in black and white too yes absolutely i'll be playing black and white too i already own it
it's right here i just have to install it and do it but we're not doing that yet we'll do that
probably next week i still want to finish the no more heroes stuff show it i got the rhythm heaven
fever is here too i got a lot of stuff oh fuck yeah we also have to do all the lord of all the
ps2 lord of the rings games are here too that's going to be a nightmare of a night i think
didn't somebody say if if i don't beat the okay somebody said in fellowship of the ring
there's what the first or second level of if i actually beat the first or second level that
they'll donate like 100 or something somebody said something like that what was it i didn't
record their name i don't know who it was they made a really bold statement they said i don't
i don't think he's going to get to the end of the first level find out i don't know what their name
was i wrote it down somewhere maybe but yeah we do have some stuff here you said you wrote down
his name because you he said you'll never beat the first level yeah but then i said clip it
here it is right here what did they say okay hold on they it was a guarantee by the way they
guaranteed it you literally won't get past the first part of fellowship i guarantee it
all right i wouldn't all right i'm gonna remember your name because when i get past level one in
fellowship of the ring i'm going to fucking scream your name what was it what was your name
it's fake what i'm gonna write that name down i'm gonna literally fake grumbo there it is yeah so
what is it you literally won't get past the first part of fellowship i guarantee it okay i i will
not get past the first part of fellowship guaranteed i'm ready to scream your name when i do it should
we just do that tomorrow i don't should we do that tomorrow should i start the lord of the rings give
ps2 games tomorrow or katana zero i know i want katana zero katana zero katana zero katana zero
we'll do that next week we'll do that next week we'll do that okay all right yeah yeah yeah
we'll see we'll see i don't know that's right behind me and now i'm into it katana zero is
short yeah what's like four hours five hours we'll we'll do we'll do uh no we'll do katana zero
tomorrow that that's what i want to do travis touch town is dying don't worry we'll get to that too
we'll get to everything and i can play god hand we'll get to that too
anyway smokewise ganja thanks for the five subs a lot of these coming up here are part of that
ridiculous beginning of the stream soy dev five subs bulbous wag fifteen dollars they said again
what's this hype train good luck on level three yep and i i did i i i beat it at least i beat level
three i didn't get too upset only a little bit i only shook my mouse and like shook my body like
five times ab joe five subs jamie five subs your boy 10 subs ipod matt 500 bits they just
spammed a bunch of shit on their keyboard and smashed their keyboard gnarly thanks to the 250
hype hype hype hype quick give germa your money or else his stream will never be hype ever again
and we'll go back to nancy drew pog hype do like kittens thanks to the five subs
fitty gave five thousand bits i'm pogging so hard right now i'm glad you were i was too
frility thanks for the five subs regard no i 10 subs apathetic mango 500 bits get me off his
train not like this ab joe 5000 bits keep going you guys cross level five and you got 350 past
level five you guys are maniacs i look forward to financing some of these bigger streams
should be a lot of fun zake thanks for the 250 i don't have a message just riding the hype train
also still waiting for the cooking stream i know and you're gonna have to continue to wait
unfortunately logan man thanks for the 1400 bits classy banana five subs flare pancake 250
got to support the hype train smokewise ganja again 1500 bits 15 dollars mr destructoid
hype train let's go k pace it 10 community subs wind are 500 bits they say a hype train
jamie 2803 500 bits hype akiba five community subs tingy 250 for the hype train
peaceful hailey 250 give the goblin some bits i'm just thank you
hasnain thanks for the 500 bits hype train appreciate it 15 community subs from fitty
five from utopia fox thanks both of you drosophilia 250 hey germa it's my 22nd
birthday can you sing me a song happy birthday to you happy birthday to you
happy fucking birthday drosophilia ain't it true there you go happy birthday that wasn't good
enough what are you talking about thanks for 10 community subs to generino i gotta watch the
break dancing part again that was my favorite san pacoy thanks for the thousand bits no message
just a bunch of money i was asked 300 bits i don't know what's going on but take my money germa
i will i need to see this all right i don't know why i just need to see i love this so much
i love this cow oh my god you're getting fucking flexed on
like that wolf was so much better at dancing all right now fight watch germa live when he starts
spinning on his head it's just like no way man you can't come back from that oh my god you're
getting what a funny game what a fun little cute dumb game the model goes nuts yeah it turns 2d
for five tenths of a second anyway we had mr squishy 300 bits just hit 47 months in a row
any chance of new badges there's a lot of things i have to do there's a lot of channel shit that
i need to get done i just have to do it but thank you thank you morning maple for the five community
subs furious bear 20 community subs i think i caught this one but just in case i didn't
that's a ton of fucking subscriptions what are we at now for subs something stupid right almost oh
my god almost 11 000 subs holy shit there's almost 11 fucking thousand subs on this channel guys
top one no not not quite but i'm i'm ecstatic um so i can't even begin to tell you how i even
feel about that i am grateful i can't fucking believe it oh my god thanks a lot everybody
invest invest now don't worry i'm gonna be um i will i'm gonna try to be smart
you know what i mean i'm gonna try to be smart thanks a lot guys uh
yeah fan yeah fans bf thanks to the 500 bits germy you're a cutie germy you're so cute thank you
peter welcome back peter thanks for the thousand bits peter i want off the hype train not like this
hype train is still going at this point by the way this is all from seven hours ago
so you boy another 15 subs adam laughing my ass off a hundred bucks ten thousand bits
crookshire five thousand bits the chat is hype potion dweller thanks for the 250 bits i'm typing
this at work for reference mega milk i believe is a picture of an anime girl with a pair of large
spheres that are under a shirt similar to the toronto blue jays outfit design with the words
mega milk printed across the chest i believe in the comic she is taunting her she's taunting
someone with her spheres however i think the comic may be of an adult nature why would you take this
to work don't get fired over mega milk please taxi driver thanks for the 300 bits hey germans want
to say that you've gotten me through some rough times and i appreciate it have a good night man
don't let the cow kill too many villagers he actually didn't he didn't have an opportunity
to he was being tortured for six hours that's like i can't even believe it man last night we
had so much fun with the cow and it was yeah let's go cow get ready for level three germany
you're not gonna like it why and we sit there and grind out for six hours to free him oh
that's all good just think about all the fun you had trying to follow that man
we had to listen to the back pain guy for four hours in slow motion
i love that game though as like sloppy and crappy as some of the mechanics can be
i just wish there was more stuff like that lion had made so many awesome things
and just we'll never see him again unfortunate but we're not here to be upset try that again
and you're dead oh my back my eye put me down you're asking for it oh oh it's gonna be stuck
with me forever but thank you taxi driver i really appreciate it thanks for the 300 bits
take care of yourself molly maguire's thanks for the 300 bits can you check out giant enemy
spider by young head they made a song out of a clip of your stream giant enemies
a giant enemy spider there's a lot of these what is it okay this shit's got 50 000 views
the giant enemy spider
that's not
hold on all right now i can hear it the giant enemy spider
hey
first off i would like to say hello
never
what is it about this thing in particular it's so it's so it's so old it's just it's made this
insane resurgence people are making songs about it people are making artwork and shit
i made this video it's like six and a half years ago
she
uh giant enemy spider i honestly don't know and i don't know how i can sas got so many
views this is a hundred thousand views all right back to it that's wild though
you guys surprise the shit out of me every day the jazz version what do you
mean the jazz version this one's called germa on pineapple on pizza what that's
all right I punched yeah I remember that one all right let's keep going MGS snake
gave $50 during potential issue of the year I say issue of the year you know
what I mean just increase the FOV just increase your FOV watch that whole video
what when you watch the whole thing I didn't watch the whole I mean I didn't
watch it it's just dead air the giant enemy spider I've heard this before I've
heard this this little jingle the spider I've heard it before I can take a bath
after this I'm gonna take a nice hot bath I think so how do you even make that
I don't know how you make this stuff mulberry pancakes thanks for the ten
subs ten community subs thank you hot take alert thanks for the five community
subs thanks a lot appreciate it we also had stefunky chicken thanks for the
400 bits germa wanted to say that seeing all the production effort you put into
your stuff has really inspired me to apply myself over the years I'm currently
interning on a feature film while producing my own short I don't think I
would do it I think I would be here without you
seriously man you do so much more than you ever know thank you I'm that's
awesome that you're on a set on a feature film set right now and you doing
your own shit the best thing you can do is just keep punching at it see if it
takes you anywhere you can't win unless you try there is what you ought to say
do or dude don't do or do not do or do not do there is no try something like
that right was though you know because a Yoda could do or do not there's my
yearbook quote by the way I swear to fucking God do or do not do do or do
not there is no try that was my yearbook quote from Yoda but that's not
even accurate what I'm trying to say what I'm trying to say is try what if
that's a terrible quote no it's not that's Bruce Lee do or do not there is
no try that's Yoda what do you mean Bruce Lee listen to Yoda listen to Yoda
Bruce Lee Vod instantly got deleted no no I'm not gonna even try it was me
doing that voice I could probably do it I'm gonna mute I just tried it like six
times it's not gonna work listen to Yoda though seriously Yoda's got some good
advice try do it don't or do it don't try try it do Yoda's voice I have a note
that if you think that I inspire you to do anything I'm happy that that's the
case I hope it's a force for good hey very nice thanks for the 500 bits
Jeremy sorry for missing the New Year's stream don't apologize for ever missing
anything that this stream ever does you under no obligation to ever be here so
don't worry I'm feeling a bit bummed out at the moment because I didn't manage to
get into an overseas study program that I was looking forward to now a bit
directionless I'm sure one where I want to go next any words of wisdom try again
try again but there is no try who said who told you that all right I'll give it
a try no try not do or do not there is no try all right yeah I have to go
against Yoda on this one for a second any words of wisdom for real though
without any like jokes or anything I would probably say to honestly to try
it again I don't know how old you are but if you have something that you want
to do overseas study programs correct me if I'm wrong they're actually kind of
difficult to get into because they only take a certain amount of students right
so it's actually not something I don't think I would be too too upset about it
because it's such an exclusive hard to do they only take like what 30 40 50
students a lot of times it's incredibly difficult and it's incredibly expensive
now also remember that if you do an overseas program you may have just
increased the amount of money it takes for you to go to school by you know
times three so they do a lot of good where am I going with this one what do
I mean I'm just saying that it's it's it's expensive and it's hard to do hard
to get into overseas tuition is cheaper if you live in America wait what the
overseas study program not going to college in another country you go to
college in one country and you do a study program in another country you
don't like go to college in the other country it's a study program for a
school that's in the country of origin I'm confused what did you mean by this
yo Yoda yeah Yoda what should I do all right thanks Yoda move to a country with
better college prices he would recommend get him what would recommend drugs no I
really wish I had something better to tell you but you can try it again as a
meme no no carefully okay no stop saying ketamine what is ketamine what is it
what is ketamine it's an anesthesia or something don't take fucking anesthesia
without a doctor prescribing it for you to pull your teeth out or go in your
body and like touch you like liver and rip out your organs and stuff don't do
that anyways Strakas thanks for the 550 thanks for the 550 but Hema thanks to
the 250 hey Jeremy can't watch the stream due to family medical emergency
oh that's doesn't I'm sorry to hear that I need to say this for a community night
video it's a spoiler for dragon rompa I don't know I'm not I'm scrolling by what
if I what if I play it I'm not gonna say that I'm not even I'm gonna scroll by
thank you though thank you Razlik for the thousand bits
Jeremiah took your advice on just having fun with streaming and now it's been
going for a couple months and today I got affiliate hell yeah nice work
I'm actually more comfortable for talking for long periods and meeting new
people and I hope to make better content if the future in the future I'm still
nervous but wait if the future I'm still nervous but more excited than ever so
thank you for the advice as simple as it may have been it means so much hearing
it from you can't wait to see you plans for 2020 thanks a lot Razlik hope your
streams go well thanks for the thousand bits the thing about my advice though
guys this is a fucking miracle I can even get myself out of bed you know
like I get lost in my own bathroom I don't even know how to tie my shoes
correctly he's seen I wish you all the best though all of you I can't even tie
shoes see you get it I know you do sometimes we're all sims setting a
grilled cheese on fire all right make that have that be your can I take that
and have that be my senior quote that's a great one that is fantastic that's
that's the most accurate statement I've seen all day thank you chef gooby for
the five subs thank you chef gooby Flavius what is no music this is thank
you Flavius Dalmatius for the 250 German remember that time you got mad it was
like two hours ago gnarly thanks for the 250 a while back I asked about classic
SNES RPGs and you told me to play Chrono Trigger I got it a week ago and it's
pretty great thanks for the recommendation that's one of the best
games ever made you're welcome also if you didn't use frog in your
playthrough I want my bits back why how would I not use frog he was in every
party I'm gonna bounce into you here sticks
renegade thanks for the 250 when is the tire oil change stream you have to learn
how to do these things hey Chad did you know German doesn't even know how to put
his put gas in his car that's not real so it's okay but no I don't we already
went over this this was a huge point of contention last night a lot of people
were upset by this but we call we brought up real statistics that only 18
percent of everybody in the United States changes their own oil so I'm okay
with being part of 82 percent of every person that goes just to fucking jiffy
loop for like 20 minutes okay make fun of me all you want he's a normie I don't
change my own oil what a normie the bar for what is and isn't you're a normie I
feel like we get it's getting muddled in 2020 you know I'm saying okay boomer
okay boomer German's a damn normie guys beta what do we beta do you see how hard
I fit my controller during Simpsons what was the what was I just gonna say so I
was gonna say Simpsons rise and shine Simpsons hit and run bulbous wag thanks
to the 500 bits I'd watch a sitcom of the Super God best friends crew I would
too jump tea thanks for the 300 bits Dan's game if you love pineapple on
pizza you are a psychopath no just people just like things and people don't
like things we can't we just all like things that we like can't we all just
like things and not everybody has to like the same damn thing is why is it
so bad to be different from each other why is it so bad no we all must enjoy
pineapple pizza all of us everybody's different who gives a shit pineapple on
pizza is a sin you like broccoli actually fuck this stupid normie boomer oh
yeah this stupid no no no me your name is fucking me up yo yo can man I couldn't
say it cuz I'm looking at your name I'm banning you for one minute I'm
banning you for a minute I'm banning you for one minute I have to I have to I
have to show I'm gonna show that I'm fucking alpha you know what I mean I
gotta ban you what's your name what was that person's name what's that person's
name you're you're Yorkin this is a beta move no this is an alpha move because
I'm the York the Yorkin man wait hold on no it's not they work the the
Yorkin man the Orkin man is like a pest control ban Orkin man keep typing hide
him you whatever just know that I'm pointing at you just know that I'm
pointing at you that's super beta fuck I'm pointing at you right now and angry
with you okay hey man up with Psy hot thanks to the 400 bits thanks for
streaming hope all is well things are going pretty well thank you appreciate
that some nuts RGL thanks for the 500 bits hey German recently went to the
doctor and came back with a pretty scary diagnosis turns out I'm incredibly
allergic to cute people a chew sorry about that oh man oh you spelled out a
chew and it's like God that's fucking ridiculous what's this what's this
person's name I gotta ban him for one minute that's right okay hold on just
know that I'm looking at you thanks for the 500 bit seriously blueberry man I
like that name because it has bugleberry in it let's get the credits wrong look
at these fucking subs don't just wait you get bugleberry be back again I you
know oh I guarantee Jeremy won't beat the first level in fellowship of the
ring I guarantee bugleberry makes another appearance within the next year
I guarantee it so not this year no no no within 2020 you'll see him again Wow
who could have guessed resident sleeper he'll wake you up don't worry hey
shadows one disciple thanks for the 250 what are we looking at here I don't
know what is this what you just a screenshot of what is it it's just the
cow flipping off somebody somebody really sad I don't get it what is it this
oh the sky I didn't even see it thanks though but thank you shadows one
cycle and then thank you blueberry bugleberry man for the 500 bits I found
you from the German is mad star series loved you ever since I wonder how many
people have actually found this channel through those videos they were fun and
right at the very end we had snoozing copter music doctor says for 250 bits
there is no end video because for some reason I'm stupid and don't have it you
fix that very very quickly fix that very close a week big week value close it
dark the closure about dark dog is not the time what time do you close now is
not a time what time do you close who's talking right now all right snoozing
copter wait hold on wait a second I have no idea what this says I'm not reading
what this person said this is not the bit message I really have no clue what
they are trying to say gotcha no country for bald streamers now for real thanks
but not for getting God and still looking forward to it I'm gonna be
disappointed if you don't beat it it's a hard game gonna do you have to call it I
can't call it for you well head saying well done well done can you please for
the love of God turned down Bielgabary's reverb no it's going to 1% higher next
for every time somebody says turned down Bielgabary's reverb I'm increasing it by
half a percent fuck you fuck you fuck you oh my god I didn't think I was gonna
get this kind of response I'm gonna turn of course I'm gonna turn the reverb down
I didn't even know it was that loud I wasn't even I couldn't hear anything I'm
sitting over there screaming into a pot I don't know the reverbs that loud I had
no access to that audio every time a viewer leaves turn it up that was me no
I but I was I was not available I have was on my break I what I can't take a
break during the middle of a stream I was I was screaming into the pot I was
sitting on the toilet and I was fucking having some trouble that's what I meant
by that see you guys tomorrow first time on streams is totally not res pool
thanks to the 250 been watching since 2012 hope you have a good day thanks
welcome welcome to the stream I'm drinking green tea drink it with me I
need to go get some more green tea I don't have any more left but I'll see you
guys tomorrow for probably Katana zero or I might last-minute lie to you guys
and just hook up the PlayStation 2 and do Fellowship of the Ring it might be a
mystery the plan is Katana zero he's gonna lie here comes the lie where's my
I'll see you guys tomorrow goodbye take care ah ha ha we're gonna go on a raid
today we're gonna go on a raid because box box is currently streaming and box
boxes has raided this channel a shitload of times tons of support tons of
incredibly nice things that they have said about this community and about this
stream let's go say hi to box box let's let's go I've been waiting for an
opportunity to some of these people that have rated the stream I'm never live
when they're live and go say hello I'll see you guys tomorrow take care
yourselves and good night