Hey, what's up? Computers are difficult. Computers are hard to use. We're connecting
across the whole world to each other, all right? It's there. First of all, we had to get...
Listen, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Everyone, slow down.
We had to get our Xbox Live accounts to go through Steam to connect to the Microsoft servers to then
add somebody through Steam to then connect through Steam through the Microsoft Xbox servers to play
Halo Reach. It's 2019. We're still doing this shit. It's 2000. It's almost 2020.
And we're still doing this. Traffic was fucking slow. But anyways, today, welcome everybody,
got something special for you today. Joel and I are going to be playing Halo Reach Co-op
Legendary Difficulty. That's right. That's what you're here for. That's why you showed up
on Legendary. That's right. Should be fun. We are currently... We tried to set this up and
there's a lot of random things that go into setting this up because it's all peer-to-peer.
So, you'll see. You'll see. This is a you'll see scenario. But we're going to do Squad Stream
and when Joel's... I think Joel's doing his intro now too. You'll see P2P of Mega Lul.
P pants to P pants. Yes, no, P2Pants is what it is. P2Pants. And they got like seven of these coming
out, don't they? This is like Halo. This is not even Halo 1. This is Halo 0. If you don't know
how this works. This is Halo 0. This technically is Halo 1, right? Halo 1 is Halo 2 or something.
It's a prequel. Yeah, right. Let me ping him. Let's see. What's the deal? Let's see. What's he
say? Oh, I think he is doing his intro. All right. So, yeah, we're going to play this.
I have to make a tweet too. Oh, ping him. Oh, I'm just going to ping him. That's the professional
term. Guys, we've never played a game on this channel with Joel before. I've got to use the
professional terms. I'm going to ping him. I'll get right on that. You know what I mean? Let's see if
we can lock this down, right? Currently typing. I'm going to say, come on in. Oh, here we go.
Let me tweet. I'll be right there. Stay tuned for Halo Reach and make sure you go to Burger King.
Just for no reason. Okay. I don't know. I'm sorry. I panicked. Have you guys heard about
Raid Shadow Legends? Let me call him. Here we go. Okay. Okay. I've got a new friend. Okay. So
hello. Hey. Hey, is it working? Yeah. Let's go ahead and lock this down. All right. I was
just talking about this, but we used to play a lot of Halo together, me and Jerma. I don't know if
you guys are familiar with X2 Clan. That was us back in 2009. You know, and we didn't know
each other. We didn't know each other. We thought we had played, or rather, you know, when I discovered
that Jerma was DPP on Feed Farm Exploit, I... PPP? No. Which one was it? PPP? No, no. Back
before they reinstated the server fix on the KD or stuff. Oh, no. That was bullshit. Do you
remember the ghost cycling they did? I got on the top of the leaderboards from that. And I'm sorry.
Are you utilizing an exploit? It doesn't count. Please. No, no. They left it in the game.
That was before QQ Recycling, I think. Yeah. That's before I cleared out my recycling bin.
So that was CC. There was a lot of shit in there, too. There was a ton of stuff. Yeah. Yeah. I agree.
There's like probably 60 gigs worth of stuff. And then I did that and I lost all my fucking exploits.
Do you know where I got Clan X2 from? What is Clan X2? I was just thinking of X-Men 2 and the
fucking poster. I was thinking, what is the most outrageous clan name I can think of? X-Men movie
poster. What the fuck? I was just like, what kind of aggressive gamer terminology can I throw at
the audience before they're like, ghost recycling? I don't know. I don't know any real gaming
terminologies. I'm just like, yeah, stats and exploits. Ghost recycling. I don't fucking know.
So, well, anyway, so, Jeremy and I, for real. Legendary. Yeah. We were going to do this on
Legendary because we're big boys. That's right. We did play a lot of Halo back in the day.
We actually really did. That's not even a joke. Everyone thinks it's the first time you guys have
like hung out. No, no, no, no, no. I threw a guy at work. I actually met Joel a long, long fucking
time ago and a lot of people don't actually know this, but I've known you since we were like, what,
15? No, we went to fucking high school together, man. We went, we took theater together.
Just go from another made up story to another made up story.
Sorry. I was going to come up with a story how you're like, you smashed your niece or
something like that. And I was going to fuck with you and just be like, this was before your name
was like, Biffy or something like that. Nobody knows what's real on these channels anymore.
Is your squad stream working? I think so. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. All right, guys, by the way,
this is a squad stream. So you got two streams open potentially. Let's get an e-bike on.
So yeah. But for real though, we, we sat around here and, you know, not, not to imply that,
you know, we didn't just do something that was real, but, uh, no, no, here, here,
the brass tacks of it is that we set up, uh, the master chief collection here and it just came out
and, um, yeah, you know, not to poo poo on a game that is so beloved by both of us, but, uh, the
problem about it is that the UI is like fucking horrible because they're using our Xbox live.
Yeah. And, uh, through, you know, through Microsoft. Yeah. Back to steam, back to you,
back to me, back to steam. And then we have to, what's the point of the Xbox account?
That's what I don't understand. If you, if you can invite somebody through steam,
what's the point of the Xbox just to like track your achievements or something?
Hmm. The steam achievements are the steam achievements for this game. If there is,
then I'm going to laugh at this steam achievements for this game. Well, back in the day,
back in the day, uh, me and, uh, what was your name again? What's my name? Oh, um, it's, uh,
tended D ragoon. So, so me and, and, and tended raccoon back in the day. This is before the
accident. Of course. Uh, we used to be known as the Chivo hunters. Uh, nothing to do with the
achievement hunter, but we used to collect Chivos on, on Xbox live and, uh, you know,
dude, there's 700 steam achievements. Wow. How do you even make that many achievements?
Is this game like $600 long? How are there 700 steam achievements? So we can invite you here. Uh,
Oh, we know you have to add, you have to do it on steam. There we go. Okay. Okay. There we go.
Yeah. All right. Are you guys ready for us to play legendary halo together? I can't wait. The
second we get in the car, I'm going to, it's going to be awesome, man. I'm going to high five.
Dude, the fucking memories are going to come flooding back. It's going to be, it's going to
be diarrhea out of my eye sockets. I'm going to think back on that. It's uh, it's great.
And I remember it fondly. There's something you guys don't know though. There's something you
don't know. We know something you don't know about our connection is bad. That's it.
Nah, no, cause, um, you know, somebody else is in the game.
How is this somebody in here? Who are these people? What fucking love are you in? Wait,
hang on. Wait, wait, wait. Can I play? No, no, no, no. Where am I? Where am I? You're in here.
I mean, how do I type? What are you talking about? In what fucking love did I end up?
I think this is a public lobby. I honestly don't even know who, who's who in here. Okay. I don't
know either. I think they can hear me talk, whoever they are. No, you're going to make it a private
invite only. Okay. No, no, no, no, no, no. This is, this is bullshit. I'm not part of any fucking
crew. All right. Get out, get out. No, no, no, no. Are you in a crew that has clone in it?
Why am I in this crew? We're both in it. No, no, that's not why. No, no, no. UNSC is like a
halo thing. Okay. Why are we in a, are we in a clan? Now you can see that required experience
with this game and, uh, no, you can press J to chat. Okay. If I say this, do you see that?
No. Wait, let me see. No, I just said scrote. Okay. So we have to make this a private lobby.
All right. So go on your options. Make it like invite only. Okay. Hang on. Hang on. Hang on.
Fucking computers. We, uh, you know, we sat around for probably approximately an hour, uh,
off stream, just bashing our heads together. But, uh, this, uh, this is like oddly deja vu,
a thing that I experienced like five minutes ago. So, uh, imagine, imagine setting up like a stream
for like 45 minutes before the stream and it still has problems. This happens on every like
multiplayer game. All right. We'll do it. I was, I was joking with Jeremy. Like if this doesn't work
out, let's just like go on like a super Nintendo emulator and like hook up fucking like Bomberman
and play that instead. I'll just, I'll just come over your house. Okay. I'll take the, I'll take
the Elon Musk fucking under the earth tunnel. I'll be there in like 40 minutes. If people keep
joining my fucking lobby, I don't know how to like close up the lobby. It's like a bleeding wound.
Oh, people keep fucking joining. I don't know what to do. All right. All right. Ready? I'm going to
walk you through it. Ready? Go to your, your profile thing. Go to my game session. Privacy
invite only. Uh, Oh, here we go. A player count. Okay. Friends invite only. Okay. Bingo. Fucking
people keep joining. Kick player. How the fuck did people find me? I, okay. I said my name.
All right. So did I say your name too? Did we, did you, did I say your name? I said my name.
Oh, fuck. Oh, please. Your names are on your screens. All right. Let's try it again. Evite.
No, no, you, you invite me. You invite me. Okay. I invite you. Okay. It's a fucking miracle. I can
dress myself in the morning. Hang on. Uh, all right. Now just get, you just, this is all,
we're just pumping ourselves up with the fucking legendary difficulty. That's right. That's right.
This is harder than the game. This is way harder than the game. This is legendary life. All right.
Hang on. Uh, but I can't invite you now. What the fuck? I I'm going to have a corner. I'm
going to fucking snap. But guys, guys, guys, this is all a meta joke. You see, we set this up to be
as hard as possible because we know that true gamers recognize skill. It's not, we're going to
show you that not only are we the master of overcoming challenges, but we're also the master
of halos. Yo, where's my evite? Yo, where's my evite? I'm fucking trying. Hang on. Okay. Hang on.
The fuck? How the fuck do I invite you to the fucking game? I'm on steam right now,
but I've like lost the ability to invite you in. I love this. This is fucking great.
I was just saying this before the stream too, but like let dear God, let's not make this into a
tason day thing. Like overall, just our streams are open. Okay. Um, okay. Hang on. Let's see if I
can do this one more time. I'm going to go. Tell I have a great fucking idea, right? Hear me out.
You make the lobby because you, you have the fuck you, you, you are the brains here, right? I'm,
I'm the brawn. All right. You want to, wait, you want to put the training weights on? Absolutely.
Okay. It sucks. All right. Here we go. I'm ready. Got it. Yes. Okay. Good. Hang on. Hang on. I'm
almost ready. Now we're talking, I think. Are we talking? I think we're talking. Oh yeah. Okay.
All right. I think we're talking. If I say this now, you see it. Thank you. Hold on. Hold on. Let
me just make sure this is good to go. Okay. Okay. Hold on. Legendary difficulty. All right. Just like
the old days. Warning. If you continue, you will lose. Yeah. Whatever. No bingo. There's more gamers
we don't lose. Welcome to halo reach. Now we're going to do a big let's play collaboration here.
You know, now you're all familiar with our content and this should be no surprise that we will be
doing this on legendary. We might do the extra DP levels afterwards, but right now we're going to
be focusing on solo right now. We're going to find all the, the secret tokens. We're going to find the
scrolls. How many are in each level? There's, there's four out of five. It depends on the,
on the QQP settings, but is this, is this a, is this a ghost recycling thing? It might be,
it might be, they might patch it. Oh shit. Master chief is dead. Is that supposed to be who that
is? Wait, huh? I look, I got a question. I know absolutely. I mean, all like jokes aside, I have,
I have no fucking idea what any of the stuff on the screen is. Is it like the, is it like
the star wars stormtroopers where there's like a bunch of master chiefs and then there's enough,
is that how it works? That's everybody dressed like that. Okay, dude, hang on. I got, I gotta
shut, take off the screen because people being a little foony about it. Hang on. Wait, how do I
disable like, okay, I'm going to take off the notifications. There we go. What are you getting?
Are you getting like friend invites? Yes. Welcome to hell. He's getting hundreds of
invites. Oh my God. I got, I got, I got 200 invites from a guy called organ farmer.
All right. So which one is you and which one is me? Do we know? I'm the guy with the two arms.
Okay. For a second, I was like, oh, right. Okay. I was like, who has two arms? Commander.
So that's our new number six. Is that, so that's master chief.
Wow. Only the parts that wouldn't cover the black chat. I gotta ask you a serious question here,
but how memorable is the mission? Cause we, we remember it really well, but I'm asking you guys,
not much, very pretty memorable. Okay. We just too damn important.
You know how people have their, their like from software list of dark souls one, then dark
shows two, then dark shows three. Like everybody has like their own little, where does halo reach
sit in the dark souls tier list? That's cat noble two meal and George four and five.
You're riding with noble. Is halo reached the bloodborne of from software games or where does
it sit into some shoes? The rest of the squad would rather leave unfilled me. I'm just happy.
What's the dark souls to the full strength of halo. I've seen your file. Even the parts,
the only sensors didn't want me to. I'm glad to have your skillset, but we're a team that lone
wolf stuff stays behind. What are they saying? I mean, I know it's worth it. Halo five is the dark
souls to from software games of Microsoft games. Cool. Dude, if I didn't have fucking brain damage
already trying to configure this shit, now I have that. This is the dark souls of bloodborne type
stranding games. What happened in that cut scene? We paying, we paying any attention at all?
Um, things happened and there was a cutting and like, okay, no, we're fine now. We're fine now.
Somebody just grabbed your internet hose and like kicked it for a second. Dude, let me tell
you something. My CPU is like made out of like silly putty and like, um, what do you have for
a CPU? You got a chance. Maybe you can ask. I, I, uh, I have one. Um, I think it's an I five.
Beside the fucking point. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Hold on back up. You're streaming
on an I five. You heard her dead zone confirmed. Well, what should I be streaming with? Uh,
that's red river. Listen, here's, here's the deal. Right? Is it, there's a piece of shit. I,
I drive a piece of shit car computer. It might not be that good, but it works. All right.
That's all that matters. It's hard. All right. Listen, I don't need the most technical stuff
to be a gamer. Listen, I don't, I don't have gunner glasses on. I sit around and I use what works.
All right. Beside the fucking point. That's me. My CPU, my CPU is so good that when games get
really intense, it shuts my internet off. I'm serious. That's so bad. Do you like, don't want
that to be happening. All right. And investigate the distress beacon. Okay. So if you know it up
and down, that's, that's you. Let's check it out. Okay. So what does 117 mean? Have we figured that
out? What is 117? Is that our ping? We thought it was the ping at first, but you're going to
discover soon that it might be more like looking like a telephone number after we reviewed how
it looks. So we have to investigate the beacon. How easy is this game? Anybody remember? Okay.
So how did you, how did you do emotes? It's very hard. Is this aim down sights?
No, it's a, it's just standard gamer. All right. I want you guys to experience standard gamer.
I want to experience how Mamma Mia, this, this fantastic latency between Mexico and Sweden,
wherever you live, check this out. I'm going to jump. Ready? It looks great on my end,
but not on his end. This is my end. Do you understand how bad this is? That's really bad.
If you're on, if you look at his end, it's, it's very, very bad. So the training wheels are on.
So that, you know, when people jog and they walk and they have like the ankle bracelets and
wrist bracelets on that's what this is. You know, you know what though, Jerma, you know what though,
you know how much of a gamer I am. We're both playing, we wouldn't be playing on legendary
if we weren't gamers. Listen, listen, listen. Here's, here's why I'm classy. You're streaming
with a PC. I'm using something new. I'm using Google Stadia. I'm going to show you what late
this is all about. You know, I was literally, uh, I was trying to figure out what the fuck Stadia is
even for. I figured it out. Do you want to know the secret? What Stadia is for? Sloths? No, it's
for in, in 20 years when the internet is, that is good enough, like 8g is good enough. They will be
the ones that are here. It's a long play. It's completely worthless right now. And it'll be
worthless for probably five plus years. It is only here for 8g in like 2040. So, so you're saying
that that Google Stadia is basically, what's that thing where like people froze themselves down in
the 80s? It's a shitload of fall damage by the way. Uh, that's called cryogenics. So it's cryogenic
internet. That's the cry engine. It's called the cry engine. Okay. This, this is, this is I wish
we, we try this off a little bit off stream. I said like, this is fine. Now that I'm actually
doing it, it's like a fucking nightmare to play. That's why I would have, I would, I would have
been the person with the training wheels on. I wish we could switch hosts. Let's keep going
for a little bit. I mean, I, I can, I can accept this. You want to switch, we're going to switch
the levels after this. Like after we do this and I, I can handle it. I think it was a little
better on my end. When this came out again, I, I, I forget. 2006. No, no, it didn't.
Well, this, this is of course our 10th year anniversary. Don't you remember? Oh fuck.
These enemies. I don't think those enemies. I saw the rain.
Happy Thanksgiving. He killed some fucking Mars Turkey. All right. Where are you? Are you the one
with the 117? Okay. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Is there a fire in this? Is there friendly fire?
Yes. Where's my health? I think I just murdered you. You did, but I'd respond.
But your corpse is still there. Wait, hang on your corpse. You're standing on your corpse.
Do it again. No, no. Kill, kill me. Kill me. And I'll like materialize on top of myself.
Yes. Like an existential crisis. We're going to do this until there's 50 corpses.
Okay. Yeah. Good. So we couldn't, we couldn't get it to death match because it took like
25 minutes to get into a lobby. So we'll just make a makeshift one right here on the stairs.
This is not actually going to work, right? There's no way this works. Are you dead? Okay.
Tell you what, tell you what, tell you what. I'm right behind you. Let's jump at the same time.
This is going to kill the server. We're going to have to start the mission over.
No, no, no, no, I won't. No, I just want to experiment. I want to see like, um,
the falling animation. All right. You ready to do this? Okay. Ready? Three, two, one, go.
What? Oh, no, we have to block a door with our bodies.
All right. We have to make a door. We've blocked this whole door. Okay. Just kill me. Okay.
I don't, I think the actual bodies are like ragdoll, but boot player. You can boot you from
the game. Kill me here. Kill me. Come here. I'm going to boot you from your own hosted game. No,
this is my game. No, I forgive you. Okay. I don't wait. Don't shoot that guy.
How many bodies do you think we can actually put here? I don't know, but
keep piling up and shoot, shoot me too, man. All right. Don't poop me. Don't poop me. Make sure
you stand in the designated body area. Okay. Hang on. You know, what if you were, you were
betrayed by 10 to press X. You're going to boot this from, no, forgive, forgive.
Yeah. Don't accidentally boot me. It's always escape. Is anything despawning? No, I don't think
so. Something real bad is in this room. Legendary gamers here. True, true legendary gamers.
Let's do this until the server turns off.
You've heard of those like Counter-Strike AIs that keep on playing on offline servers
for like 20 years. Yeah. That's what we're going to be doing right now, except there's like nothing
but like piles and piles of feet sticking up. You guys can't hear the game. Okay. Let me, let me,
let me fix that. Hang on. I can't believe this is working. This, I don't think this has been one
despawn. Is there grenades? I, I think so. Can you guys hear this better now? All right. This is,
I know we're supposed to be playing Halo Reach on legendary difficulty, but what if we just,
this is what we're talking about. But what if we just make the ground that we're walking on
made out of bodies? And I'm talking like most of the ground that you see, like at least this whole
deck. We're going to show you how to like go to the secret, uh, places in the game. And it's just
like a pile of fucking like limps. Oh, how do you throw grenades? It's G. Okay. It's G.
But then, oh, fuck. No, all the cores are going to scatter if we grenade them. Wait. Oh, no, no.
It respawns the area if we both die. Oh, fuck. All right. We'll start the panning over here.
Okay. Hang on. Let me, let me redo the audio here because everything crapped out. Hang on.
It's not safe here. Okay. Right here. Yeah. This is because we're going to,
don't you want to make the whole deck? All right. Let's do it. Everyone's saying no. What? Uh,
you okay? I can't respawn. I'm. What's going on? Um, I keep spawning in the air over the edge
and dying over and over again. I can't do anything about this. We don't even need to.
Which one is me? Why is that one falling?
I'm so lost. No. You have to jump in. You have to jump in. Otherwise, this area is unsafe.
No, no, no. You're good. Okay. Hang on. Okay. We don't even need to do. Okay. We're good.
All right. So, uh, halo is this way, I guess. Halo is this way, apparently.
Legendary gamers. I thought that was in the game. Streamers.
Bad guys. Kill them. I didn't do it. That was a full clip.
Hey, you quit that.
So he's dead. Wait, what is this person dead? Yeah. Hold on. I can't, let me turn up the audio too.
Like I can't barely hear what they're saying.
The audio is like weird in this game. Yeah. I've heard like there's complaints about the
audience being like total ass balls in this, but you try, you unloaded a whole clip on that guy
and he didn't kill him. And you tell me that like a little bit of a splash from a grenade
was the end of his health pool. Where are you? Okay. I'm right behind you. Hang on.
Oh, the campaign audio is fucked up. The audio has a huge encoding issue. Oh, it's messy.
Yeah. I, this is the first time I've ever held this weapon in fake life.
Press Q. It's a punch. All right. I'm almost dead. Wait. First enemy. Our first enemy. Oh,
I was about to go. Yeah. I think this difficulty here is not going to stem from the actual game
being difficult. It's us having like collective brain diarrhea, AKA too much fun. There is too
much fun. You can never have too much fun. All right. Check time. Where are the enemies?
Tell what? I have a question. Can you see other bullet decals? If I do this?
Yeah, I can see that. Okay. You want to drop some shit on the walls? Sure. Okay. Unfortunately,
fuck. They despawn. Okay. Quick, quick one. All right. I got that. This is wind,
lose or draw. I'm going to just think. What is it? What is it? What is it? Let's see.
I don't know. Circle. This is like a draw full. All right. Ready? Here you go. No. Okay. Okay.
Okay. I'm going to, I'm going to mute. I'm going to tell my stream what it is.
It's going to be super Mario. Okay. So what is that? Man with two arms. It was super Mario.
Close. I see movement. Do you pick the guns up? I don't know. How do you pick them up?
All right. Shoot. Now we're talking. If I start dying, I'm going to start playing.
They're behind us. Oh, okay. Is somebody in the room? That's a fucking team. They're coming in
the house. Are they? What this? Okay. The, the mini map is crazy. Okay. This is not helping the
fact that I had like 9,800,000 ping. I guess a nightmare to play this. It is a nightmare.
I'm dead. Oh, fuck. I'm dead too. Area's not safe. Yeah. You have like a, you have probably
1000 milliseconds. Okay. Here's what we do. I have a proposal, right? Cause it's going to be
impossible for me to shoot, right? Here's what we do. I'm going to chase or rather you just chase
me. I just run the fuck for it. All right. Run forward. Yeah. Okay. No, basically, basically I'll,
I'll skirmish ahead and you protect me. All right. I think we can do this. You go ahead. Go for it.
All right. Let's go. I don't know where you are, but go for it. Just fucking come on.
Did you watch out? It's you doing that. Hey, get the, get the follow me, man. You gotta follow me.
Okay. I'm following you. Come on. Come on. Okay. We're good. Okay. Get in the barnyard.
Is there a barnyard? Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Nice. Watch it. Watch it. Yeah. We've got a plasma
rifle down here if you want it. Is it really? Yeah. Right here. Nice. Let me see that.
You be careful with that thing. Hold E to swap. Yep. I like this thing a lot.
Now I, I get it now. I get it. I've been playing for less than five minutes. I get it.
I'll do what's behind you, dude. What? Where are you? Right here. Dude. Do you get it? Do you like
get it now? Like after playing like that, just the way the weapons feel and the environment. I feel
it. It's coming back to me, man. It's like I never left. They never left boys. All right. Let's get
some vehicles or something. Cause as soon as we get in the car or something, that's when the gamer
skills unlock. Yeah, absolutely. I agree. Anymore down there? The fuck's falling from the sky?
I don't know. It's just like space trash. Someone's just dropping trash on me.
All right. This is legendary and we're doing just fine. We are doing, but we never, we haven't
even done died once. No, not yet. I get the space bookers across the bridge and they drop the
dropping range on this thing. I'm missing out on ammo. Oh fuck. Careful of grenades. Is there any
guns? You see any guns? You have fucking infinite ammo yet. They're complaining about like guns.
What you do is infinite. I think you're out of ammo. I, yeah, I didn't have any left. Oh,
oh, okay. Well, you switch up for the fucking like cock and ball gun. Everything sucks.
Dude, you never use the pistol in any video game. It's like the worst weapon in every video.
The pistol pistol is great. Is it the only game that's good? Yeah. Holy shit. It really is like
kind of good. You're right. Well, I don't know about this game, but I know the previous one is
pretty. All right. Shit. There might be some vehicles around. I think I see the remains of
like a space scooter or something. Hang on, dude. And the amount of time it takes to develop the
pistol in most video games that are modern video games, you could have like just maybe like fix
some of the net code. Most of the video games you play, the pistol don't do shit.
The shotguns in the Halo games are great because they literally fire half a meter.
They are disgustingly bad, but they're good like because you don't get a lot of range
in Halo, but they are completely useless. People are talking about how I just have no idea what
the fuck I'm talking about. So it's a typical Wednesday. Okay. I don't know where the fuck I am.
Oh, there you are. Okay. Hey, I was just following you. I'm just on slash. Okay.
Are there bosses in Halo? There might be. Oh, get him. Get him. Get him. I heard you get those guys.
Get him.
Get those good orders from the commander. Get him. Shoot nature. Shoot the barnyard.
Who, sir? I don't know. Him. I'm dead. You're good. You're good. You're good. You're good.
You can just spawn on me. Okay. Where the fuck are you? I'm using this fucking underdeveloped
pistol. They could have fixed the net code. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm gonna die.
What? Why the fuck am I charging? I'm not fucking going out there.
This is just, all right. You played WoW Battlegrounds when it was like 40 versus 40.
Did you play Warcraft back in the day? I'm a big World of Warcraft player, actually. I have a big,
big history with that game. Sometimes you'll aim and just hit a random person and then everyone
else is doing a bunch of work for you. This is just Altered Valley. Yeah. I think I did something.
I put a dot on a guy. Okay. Well, listen, I'm going to get the space turkeys.
Oh my God. I just took so many hits. I have no ammo. You know what? This game needs big sniper
rifles. You can take pot shots from two countries away because you don't want to be in this oatmeal
of fire and lasers. No, you don't. I need a weapon. Ow. I'm dead. Can I just give you my weapon?
This is ridiculous. No, I'm still here. I'm still here. Okay. There we go. This is what I'm talking
about. Playing this feels like I'm drunk. It feels like I woke up in this game and they sprayed my
pillow with PCP and said, here, have a gun shoot. This feels disgusting to play. I can't tell you
why this is so off. Like you might be like, well, you're playing like shit, Joel, but
I feel like these guys are so hard. Why are these guys so hard? Okay. Are these enemies
throwing grenades in here? Okay. Listen, here's my strategy. Okay. No. Okay. Check this out. Check
this out. That's right. They're standing over there. Let's not deal with that. Let's just do
this instead. Fuck it. Whatever the fuck's going on over there, we just. I hesitated for a second.
Okay. Don't wait. Don't we have to go over here though for the objective?
I found a fucking vehicle. Hang on. Hang on. I think so. Oh, please get us in that car. Oh,
no, it's not a car. It's a, it's a remains of something. Oh, hang on. I found you a gun. I
found you a gun. I found you one of these, whatever it is. This isn't good. All right,
let's go. Let's go help our friends. This is like an auto stapler. This is a staple.
This is a stapler. Is stapler any good? Um, I don't remember, but maybe.
Are you waiting? You winning? I don't know. I don't think so.
It seems like you're doing it. I'm hiding behind a tree. Okay. Listen,
my God, these guys are all like, these guys are all bosses. Dude, I don't know if you see the same
shit on my screen, but like I said over here, it's the corpus on, on local or is it multiplayer?
I see this one dude and it's like, do you see this? Yeah. This guy just makes sure he's dead.
How do you, what's the heel button? You think there's a heel button? Hi,
old halo heart. Right. Right. That's what I'm going to say. Okay. Boomer. Okay. Boomer.
All right. This guy's going to kill me. T he doesn't do anything.
Okay. They took all my shields off this game. Like again, I don't want to criticize this game,
but uh, it feels like we've taken on a task. It feels like everybody's like,
it's an equivalent of like being in a room full of like, uh, neurosurgeons
and you don't know what the fuck's going on. And you just stand in there with,
with a suit on saying, yes, I agree. Like there's so much shit happening and I can't contribute.
Do headshots matter? Yeah. They weren't a room full of surgeons. It's true.
And they just all handed us scalpels and they're like, all right, uh, this guy needs a new brain.
Go for it. Like, Oh God, what does this scalpel do? The headshots do anything.
Don't give me that. Oh, we did it. We did it. We did it.
Look at this space turkey. You guys didn't think we were going to do it.
You're with six and I will run interference on the ground. We'll meet you at the output.
Look at this disgusting, disgusting fucking creature. Look at these things.
It's a waste of imagination. Look at him. Is that a mouth? What's his mouth?
You think there's a God, you think there's a God after looking at that thing? Look at him.
You're looking at his ass.
Yes. We're looking at the wrong way. How do you? Oh, of course. How do you right now?
Can you heal? Listen, just get in the car. Wait, we're going to get in our own cars.
No, no, no. Okay. Fine. Fine. You, you want to fucking drive it? Wait, hang on. Wait,
they all get in this car? No, no, no, no. I'm coming in. Okay. Now I'm riding in a shotgun.
Yeah. What the fuck are you doing? I'm flipping. No.
I was going to put a grenade underneath the car because I forgot to get like manually
flip them and I accidentally like murder. Fuck you. I'm sorry. Okay. Well, I hit a rock. Whatever.
We have to wait for our friends to get in. It's bumbling. Fuck. Let's go. All right. So now we
have to go. Don't crash. Careful. By the way, don't leave plasma burns. Why am I getting like a
breaking news bullet? What was that? The equals control like shit inhaler. So yes, they do. Watch
out. Yes. I can't even turn the car left. No, you used the mouse, dude. You drive with the mouse.
What the fuck? Yes. You're running on a turkey. Fuck him. Fuck him. Hang on. An alligator by you.
Well, there are enemies here. There are actual enemies here and we care about the turkeys.
All right. I'm going to get in a good spot. Okay. Where are they? Go get them. Are they up there?
All right. Get them. Nice. Excellent work. That's right. There we go. Ooh, that was pretty good.
It's as if you don't. It's just like you don't have 10,000 ping. Hey, I try my best. I probably
shouldn't have gone this way. We have a blue guy after us. I don't know if we're supposed to
pick him up or. There's a blue guy. Yeah. They're like sort of a little bit more.
That guy, that guy right there. Is he going in the car or not like this?
Not like this. I don't think I think he just stands around. All right. Let me get on the road.
Can you do my favor? Can you just like smash into a Mac five? Oh, hang on. This is actually
is kind of hard to control because in my brain it's A and it's A and D. What's that?
Yeah, it's 5G. It's a 5G tower. Fucking take it down.
Google Stadia. Do you know anyone who uses that by the way? Google Stadia or whatever.
Am I saying that right? Stadia Stadia. How the fuck do you say it? I think it's I have no idea.
I think it's Stadia. Stadia. Okay. It's Stadia. You know anyone who uses that?
No, there's no reason to. All right. Let's go. Okay. You know, you know, I didn't know this
about the Stadia. Do you know that it's so you pay money a month to use the Stadia
and then you have to buy the games too. Now it fucking works.
I'm surprised you even got it in. I improvised. Okay. No, no, no, no. Ready? All right. You buy
the game so that if they ever want to not let you play it, they can just cut off access.
Okay. I was going to say that you drove like shit, but actually playing this
with a mouse delay is a fucking nightmare. Like you guys have no idea how bad this is.
You can't. Your thing's going to explode. We need that thing. But later it's over. It's stuck.
You fucked it. No, no. Just grenade me off. Lightly bump me. Boop me. Boop me. No, no, no.
Fucking shoot me. No, I don't have any grenades. Well, fucking, fucking. All right. Hang on here.
I can punch it. Oh, it's working. It's working. It's working. There you go. There you go.
The car's on fire. Okay. But it's not detailed logic. Is it? It's still good to go.
No, no. It's not detailed. It's not going to explode. Okay. I hope so. It'll be fine.
It'll be fine. Get in the car. But don't we have to kill these mutants? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. But you're
shaving with me. Ironically. Ironically. Oh, wait, wait. Are we on a timer? I don't know. Oh,
hang on. Hang on. Okay. There we go. Okay. Do you want to drive this for a minute? Maybe I should
drive. Oh yeah. Okay. Cause you have the, you have like the 5 million input delay. I have the coma
delay. Oh, we got to destroy that. We have to destroy the giant rumble vacuum. Get it. There you
go. Nice shooting. Oh, they're gonna drop out of here. You fucking run them over, man. You got the
car. We're still, we're still good to go. We're still, we're still good to go. Still. All right.
Okay. I'll teach how to do this. Get in the fucking car. All right. Listen. How is the car still
active? It's still going. All right. Does this one work? No. Now you're going to have to deal
with this one. All right. I'm getting in. Okay. Hold position. Defend the evac zone. We're going
to defend this evac zone. All right. All right. I'm ready. I'm ready. Let's get you out of here.
Wait. Okay. Here it comes. No, we're still good. We're still good. See what I mean?
Uh-oh. Hey, I got the car back. What the hell? All right. He's in with you. Corporal Travis.
Okay. Go for it. It's the covenant. Let's get you out of here. Back into this guy.
All right. I'm going to clean this up. I'm going for it. Oh, God. Oh, God. Oh,
I got to take it off a G. I want grenade on like mouse four. Well, the area sounds safer.
Okay. So you got to clear stuff up. Yeah. You live pretty good. You let me know when you want
to take off the like the weights on your arms for like the, all right. And we'll switch off.
You're going to fucking, you're going to see how bad this is. Oh, it's bad.
Gee, we tried. I have a great idea. Ready? Okay. Take this up. I'm just going to hide it.
I was going to say the same thing. I have a better idea. Get in the car and I have a great
idea how to solve this issue. Right. Okay. You just fucking murdered that guy. Like you just
now they're just aiming over. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Just get in the car. I promise.
What are you, are we going to independence day by the spoiler for independence day?
You know, so if that movie came out like 1998, do I really care that we're going to go boys on
back, just fly in the, where are we going elsewhere? We're fucked this place. They can do it.
New car. Oh shit. Hang on a little problem here. Okay. But wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
we got this. I think we have to pick up the ordinance. I don't have to wait. All right.
There we go. All right. You drive. I ride shotgun this time. Okay. And if we can't have it,
nobody can. I'm out of ammo. I don't think you can destroy it. You want to ram it and see if you
can. We've got, we've got a brand new set of wheels. All right. Grab the ordinance. Okay.
I don't know why, but this feels like,
this doesn't feel like a space shooter feels on some like redneck molasses game.
All right. We got, we got to hide back here. Okay. Well I'm fucking dead.
Okay. Well I'm going to not die. Here we go. We just defend this point. Grab the ordinance.
Where's the, what is an ordinance somewhere? What's an ordinance? What is an ordinance? Hey
gamers, welcome back to another let's play of the toe jam in Ireland. Now I don't want to give this
game shit once again, but like this feels so disorienting and I don't know if it's because
of the lag. Oh, it's definitely because of your input lag. You might as well have one eye closed
and like three spoonfuls of peanut butter in your mouth. That's, that's what it feels like.
Oh, and both of your socks are soaking fucking wet and your shoes. You're in shoes and socks.
And it's like, you stood in a puddle and you just kept them on, you know, I'm going to get a little
real with you. I don't think playing on legendary was a great idea for this, but we have to, that
if you don't play, look, you know how many people are streaming this game right now and they're
playing on legendary. We have to keep up with the streamers. All right. They're going to leave us
in the dust. If we don't, we're going to do one. I got a little pit for you. You get the fuck out
of here. You just leave it. We're going to get battlefield. It's going to say you're moving too
far away. And it was no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I see checkpoint done. What? It said checkpoint
done. So I'm doing something right. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Are we not softlocked?
Can we get unsoftlocked? We've already been here. Okay. Can't the AI like just play with
themselves for a little bit and you know, people are saying like turn on V sync and it'll be done
or like it'll be better, but see reset the checkpoint. We're seeing set pieces. We're
not supposed to see yet. The cameras aren't here yet. I'm going to ask you something.
Go for V sync. What the fuck is V sync called vertical sync. It sinks every frame.
Okay. Because, because after years of streaming, V sync for me has just become synonymous with
turn this shit off because it doesn't work. Yeah. It locks your frame rate down to your monitor's
refresh rate, which can help in some scenarios. It gets her to screen tearing, but it will not
let you go to the maximum for your graphics card is capable. So let's say if you have V sync turned
on and you have a 60 Hertz, a 60 refresh rate monitor and it'll look a little chunky and
we're dead. In fact, I think I came into two pieces. All right. So we're going to put it to
heroic difficulty. How do we turn it on? I think you have to do it. Do I have to do it?
You're the host. Yeah. Hold on. Where is settings? Okay. Difficulty. Gameplay. I think we have to go
with the exit of the game. All right. We're going to try it for real one more time.
One more try. All right. I'm down to plan on it. Try, but you promise me you will do your absolute
best this time. All right. I concentrate all your, our gamer juices into one, one, one shot here.
All right. Yeah. I can't, I can't change it. All right. Let's try it. I really like, like
just a little quick side note. I really wish we could just do like team slayer or something like
that or capture the flag because this feels so good Lord. We have to get to the first boss.
Oh, hey, look at this checkpoint. Oh, nice. All right. This is perfect. Perfect. Perfect. Perfect.
Now we can. Okay. Now they don't even know we're here. My teammates are screaming, but I don't give
a fuck. This is perfect. Actually. Holy shit. This worked. Hey, you just be careful here. Remember,
you got to press, you got to press you to, um, get the health up real quick. Is that, is that really
doing anything? You. Yeah. What? I thought it was people saying T. No, I lied to you. Legendary is
hard, especially if you are too. All right. All right. Whatever. Whatever you say. Oh, I think this
thing has a scope on it. How you doing? Doing good. Now I'm going to take it off. Yeah. It's coming
back to me, man. Also make sure this is a pro tip that I heard from the chat because I apparently
was doing poorly. If you don't hold the button down, it's more accurate. Jerma, don't take this
the wrong way, but do you play video games? Yes, I do. Did you do that? Have you, have you,
have you ever been in a video game before? Yeah. Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. Wait a minute here.
Hold on. Have you, have you, have you, have you, um, have you, um, have you beaten Sekiro? Listen,
I don't know if you know this, but I happen to know someone. His name is Jeff Keeley. He's hosting
the video game Olympics. Do you know, you actually know him? When I, when I go on the video game
Olympic stage and someone gets a little, I just notice and I wink at the camera. I don't know what's
going on. I'm here to stay. And gamers don't lose. So that was a very long-winded way to say no.
I've never beaten Sekiro. I think I've got a couple more gamer, uh, Boy Scout badges.
Where are you? Is that the challenge for me to play Sekiro and beat it? Yeah. I'll tell you what,
here's what we're going to do. We're going to settle this. We're going to settle this with some,
uh, actually there might be shit behind us. That's okay. I was going to, I was going to do
a cowboy duel. Whatever strongest weapon I have, we shoot each other in the head and whoever loses
loose the argument. So, uh, okay. Wait, you mean, no, no, you mean like here in the game?
Yeah. He's fucking murder you.
That's the easiest fucking easy. Oh yeah. That sounds like a good idea.
I would go first though. Oh, okay. Fine. That's fair.
Why are we like green? I don't know. What happened to that bridge? Oh, no, no. Okay. You activate
night vision with four. If you press four night vision, it's like goo mode. Yeah. This is not
night vision. This is just highlight everybody with neon markers. People are saying in chat,
welcome to fallout three. Did you play a fallout three? Um, I did. Not very long though. I did. I
played new Vegas, you know, something called baths. Yeah. What about the one where you freeze and it
goes, no, no, no, no, no. And I should, I can't even fucking end the call right now. Cause after
hearing that, I'm going to have one area. All right. We have to play. We have to play. Get
ready to play. All right. And then we turn the difficulty down and then we switch so you don't
have to deal with the insane horrible problem. Oh dude, watch out. It's him. What? It's him.
Who's who? That guy behind you, dude. No, no, behind you, dude. No, no, no. What happened?
Who? Him? Who's him? Who? Who are you referring to? Who? The collective who like them, you know,
like multiples. What the fuck? No, why I, I warned you about it. What happened? What happened?
I, I did, let's just say I did a very good job. Okay. You know, Jeremiah, I gotta, I gotta, I gotta
drop the, the, the, the facetious bullshit here for a second, but I think this might be the worst
fucking game play of Halo Reach out on Twitch right now in the world. No, no, no, no way.
I know I can't, no way, no way. We're in legendary difficulty. These people that are playing this
uneasy right now. Come on. Remember we're playing like limbless toddlers.
And we're doing a great job. I think we're doing just fine.
They're going to get you again, man. That was the shit on me.
Oh, this is a sniper rifle. No, no, no. I'm fucking serious. You were betrayed by tender dragoon.
I'll take that sniper rifle. Where is it? Okay. Hang on. Wait, put on a night vision.
Is that it? You didn't take it already. No, where is it? Hold still. Hold still. Are you,
are you holding it? No, no, no, no, no, no. No, I was holding it. That would be embarrassing.
Am I blind? No, I can't pick it up. Is that it on the ground right here?
No, no, no, no, no. There was one that was like a burst. Right. Am I holding it? No, no, no, no.
God damn it. No. Guys, you saw the fucking battle, right? It's on the wall. You mean on the wall.
Oh, no. Okay. There it is. There it is. Oh, fuck. I thought it was like on the ground. All right.
Me too. Listen, I think it's really awful of you guys to talk down to extremists that has
porcelain eyes like us. And I want to make, I want to make a public awareness PSA about,
you know, they are gamers with two porcelain eyes and we exist and you should
stop being so condescending all the time. Can you hear how much, how many, how many
key presses I'm pressing? That means I'm doing great. Porcelain eyes? Are you sniping?
No, no, no, no. Well, there's a guy over there. Hang on. I think you get the sniper rifle. Yeah.
Yeah. Are we supposed to be doing something in particular here? Yeah. We need to fall back into
autopilot. All right. We need to keep Kat and Ernie alive. Well, Emily. Ernie? Headshot this guy. Nice.
Okay. Somebody says we need to get the forklift. You can drive the forklift.
Wait, you can drive the forklift. Apparently. Chat's saying that. That's pretty sick. Really?
I don't know. I'm going to, I like the sniper rifle. I'm a, I'm a real precise precision gamer.
All right. The closet. Good. You can't. Okay. Good. All right. A day to stand right in the middle
and get crushed by the, like the elevator doors. You want to do it at the same time?
Is that going to happen? You want to fucking get strawberry or jammed it.
All right. Let's, let's go. Let's go. Oh, I know the thing with the elevator just opens back up.
Like, you know, when you go to the elevator, somebody's like, oh shit, hold it for you.
Cause then they make the sensor open. All right. Well, give me a rifle.
Are you talking to me? All right. We're good. All right. We did it. That only took 25 hours to do.
That was pretty good. You're in here, right? Yeah. All right. Uh, we have to use our night vision.
All right. Here we go. Press four. You ever heard of gunner glasses?
Yeah. I got gunner optics. I have, did you do that? Where's the rest of you? No, no.
We got split. Are you wearing them right now? Battle the cops. All right. Stay put.
We'll get you a combat. Are you seriously plasma damage? When you're talking to me,
you found something. I'll take that. Not your domain. I got a live one over here.
I don't have an off switch.
It's all right. I got her. Keep still and I'll release you. So which one of these is halo?
I think I died. All right. Here we go. Start that rock.
Negative four. Stay on the entrance to handle her five and six. Clear the hole. We're five and six,
right? Yeah. There's the forklift. All right. Guys, I have a really dumb question, but, uh,
Oh, I can't drive it. Oh my God. Can you get in? I don't think I could get in.
I think it's only you. You have just in the street sweeper. Okay. Can you lift me?
Can you move? Can you get out of here? Yep. I guess. Nope. Can you actually activate the
throngs? What the fuck happened? I'm upside down. All right. There you are. Good. All right. Okay.
All right. Go, go fork somebody. I'll try. Hang on. They're behind us. The complete opposite
direction. Oh, I'm stuck on some boxes. Hey, welcome back to Shenmue everybody.
Can this music start? I feel like this music is about to start, but it won't. What the fuck was
that? I don't have a serious problem with this fucking forklift. Why do you like to drive this
thing? It's awful. You're just a forklift guy now. It's the home depot theme. You know what I love
about this forklift piece of shit? Sometime in the space future decided that normal boxy forklifts
didn't cut it anymore. They had to like overcomplicate the design to make it look
like a giant fucking VR headset. All you really need is the fork part, right?
Yeah. Why does it look like that? What's all this stuff here? This is, this is a, uh,
what's the thing? What's the thing that cleans the ice? Uh, the Zamboni. Yeah. I'm trying to get on,
on the forklift here, but again, I'm just, it was right. Oh fuck. Not like that. What is this
coffee pasta right now? What is going on? There's like a horrendous coffee pasta going on. Yeah.
In mine too. Hang on. I have no idea what this, what's going on here. I don't know what started
that. I, but it's taken over everything. Something about, I have something about going to the,
I don't know. It's a Taco bell and wiping your ass. I don't, I have no idea. Oh God.
What's the funniest injury, injury you've ever sustained in real life?
Funniest injury I've ever sustained in my real life. Yeah. Uh, probably when I, um, was,
I don't know, probably like 12 years old and me and, uh, my brother were playing, um,
like karate fighters on our bed or on a big pullout mattress. Yeah. Karate fighters. Yeah.
We, we, we, we were really into like the ninjas and like karate and it was ninja turtles and
power ranges was like big and everything. So he ended up, we were just doing like fake kind of
like, you know, like the punches and kicks and stuff. And he, this was like in 94 to nine or
something. Yeah. So he accidentally during our just very, it was not, we were not trying to hurt
each other. It was just, he went, he went too far forward on the bed and I got like actually
slightly kicked into like the chest area, uh, which made me fall flying back off of the, uh,
pullout mattress. And I hit the back of my head on the fireplace and I had to get like six staples
in the back of my head. Jesus. What about you? Well, uh, I have a, I have a couple of funny
injuries actually. I, um, I, I learned a lot about like, uh, the body, uh, well, weird quest here,
but anyway, I learned a lot about like how, how, how your, your, your blood works and shit like
that. Uh, must've been like 10 or whatever. And me and my friend, um, uh, we were biking and, uh,
coincidentally, uh, super hot that day, had our shorts on. I, uh, I was thrown off the, uh,
the bike and look on the street bumper, whatever it was. Right. And I immediately thought that
what's the best way of like sustaining a fall? Oh, I used your niece. And you know, it was like,
the who rock slides they do on stage where they just kind of go with her knees, like scraping on
pure asphalt. Uh, I did like a whole meter. Where were your shin pads? Where were your shin pads?
Um, so what happened was, and he, he has the, he has the morbid pork leg. Um, my friend
just took off because they didn't want to deal with it. Well, we, uh, he took off. He didn't
want to deal with it. So I walked home to my mom and then, no, no, no, I was hardcore, man.
I w here's the thing. I'm so shocked. I was so shocked on what had happened that I, I, I came
home and I, I didn't realize like the, the, uh, the full, uh, grasp of what had happened.
Yeah, exactly. So I came home and I, I expected my mother to be like sympathetic, like, oh my God,
Joel. But she kept screaming at me. God. And I remember, uh, it was really bad, but the worst
part is this is like, I was just setting up a funny story here. I'm like puking my ass off.
But anyway, um, the point being is that I learned that you have like yellow goo in your knees.
Oh, these things are, these things are called fat balls. And yellow guck came out of my niece
and everything was fine. Really. It's just one of those, one of those things where the joints
kind of bend. I'll make, I'll make this torture stop. But the funny part is this basically, uh,
I was a big boy. They put me down in the, on surgery or they just stitched me up,
really. But, uh, they kept, uh, popping popsicles in my mouth to shut me up.
That's when I can never eat popsicles again. Holy shit. I've never heard. And you know what?
Here's the worst part of what you just said. Um, I, I like, I somehow, I don't know why,
but I know what you're talking about. I don't even, I shouldn't, but I, oh yeah, that makes sense.
Like, oh, we have like platelets and shit and like proteins and fat and stuff. And so I, uh,
Oh God. You want to know even funnier story? I want to sustain brain injuries from, uh,
from playing halo online. Is this, is this like a new injury? Is this a new injury from recently?
I just saw you run it. It happened three seconds ago.
You know, when you're playing a game and you're like, there's no consequence or like
anything anymore. You're just like, you're just like on autopilot running forward. That's so fun.
Just make it stop. There was some fucking, we were talking before, before, uh, on stream,
you said there was some story that I should have saved for, um, for the stream. What the fuck was
that? What was that? There was, there was, there was a thing to talk about. Some, some bullshit,
some bullshit. Oh yeah. Okay. Okay. So we've been trying to set up some shit to stream for
weeks on end. We were going to do Pogo stuff and all that stuff. Okay. And here's the thing. Here's
our work, Jerma. I need to like not walk around in games about the life story because I can't
multitask. I'll be the gamer. Okay. Okay. Well check this out. So I thought, I thought that
Jerma was seriously super into halo. I don't know where this fucking came from, but I thought,
cause we were trying to set this up. Jerma messages me and say, you want to play halo?
And I say, sure. Cause I know you asked the thief workers too guy. I thought you must have been
like drowning in pussy back in the halo days. Like you must have been suffocating in the amount of
like puss. And I was afraid of actually playing with you. I thought this is someone who's been
playing like halo since it came out day one. Uh, so I actually got anxious even hitting you up about
it. I'm, I was thinking I'm going to get slaughtered online. This it's going to be humiliating. And I
was just so intimidated by it. And then today I call you up and today I call you up and you say,
I've never played halo in my entire fucking life. Yeah. What you're seeing right now is the first
time I've ever actually sat down and truly tried to play it. And I gotta say, pretty fun, pretty
fun game. It's, it's kind of like going to the dentist. I was going to make some sort of smart
analogy, but I'm like, nah, fuck it. I dropped that. I mean, we, I love dentists. He's speaking
my language. That's a grenade. I tried to pick it up off the ground. Are you fucking kidding me?
Idiot. These guys, after this, these guys are going to be gone.
You know, when I said that we should probably play something else together, just be like,
play some bomber, man, a superintendent or something like that. I started off making that
joke, but now I actually like, I'm thinking about it. I'm like, dude, I probably have more fun.
I mean, this game isn't bad, but it's like, it's, it's like, I'm sedated. I mean,
I'm going in for surgery or something. Like I'm at the dentist. They're putting the fucking laugh
mask on me. Like, you know, Hey, you want to go clean a room in viscera cleanup detail?
Yeah, sure. I got the sword now. Wait, we did it. How long? Question of that's us.
If the question is when will the station be back on? I don't know. I don't think so. That's how
German gets you. Yeah. He brings up, he brings up two minutes. This is why I'm splicing into the
main overland bundle to get you a direct line to colonel Holland. You're in my life. All streams
end in viscera. That's true. Find out what she knows. You ever stuck your arm in a drain pipe?
Wait, what? What's your name? Your arm in a drain pipe? Do you live around here? How does your arm
fit in a drain pipe? Like what kind of, what kind of drain? Have you, have you ever like got in so
much hair in the, in the, in the shower drain or anything like that? And you had to like buckle up
and become a big boy and reach down into your shower drain. Yeah. And just get in there.
Yeah. You don't, you don't make snakes for that, right? Where you like snake it down and pull up.
You don't have to use your hand. Snakes? Yeah. Drain stakes. You slide down into the drain,
you move around, you pull it up. She needs a full, you're talking about contraceptive.
She's not the only one. No, it's a snake. It's a snake that it's a drain snake. Thank you, sir.
Like a hand condom for like, no. All right. Let me up. Okay. Is it device? That's you just,
you pulled my leg here. It's device. I'm still going to say, are you saying, are you saying
D R A A and snake? Are you saying train snake? What are you saying? I don't understand your
English drain. D R A. Okay. I thought you were saying train the snakes drain. Like there are no
rebels. And then I'm like, he can't be saying that he must be saying something else. He's just
saying sort of like affirmative armor for your fucking arm. Like drains. Oh no. You, you said
that you reach you. All right. You opened the conversation. You said, Hey, you ever reached
down your drain? And I'm like, no, he's a drain snake. And then you're like, what are you talking
about? And I'm like drains. And now that here we are, I thought you were saying train snakes,
trains, train snakes. Okay. Listen, listen, this game is not good for us. We're fucking dropping
like the last few brain cells we have. Oh, I lost those above two or three years ago. They're gone.
I want you to recite what the fuck happened in that cut scene drama. Okay. No, seriously. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Um, yeah. I, uh, somebody was kneeling down, fixing something for a second.
They handed in like the machine. I, if you paid me $10,000 and said, I'm only going to give you
$10,000. If you can tell me one sentence or even a small retelling of what that cut scene was,
I wouldn't be able to do it. I would not be able to do it. I got such, my brain is hurting so bad
from that conversation. I would actually in a Mandela confused attempt to say there was something
about like master chief came over and like unclogged my pipes. That's all.
I couldn't pay attention to the story because and look, we're doing it again.
We're doing it right now and we're not paying something about team noble.
Intervention to help secure sword base. Oh, right. Wait, what are you? All right. So
let me ask you a question. We're stuck with that shit for the time.
A little difficulty in host or do you, or do you hate this guy? Tell you what,
this game is giving me cataclysmic diarrhea. If we continue, we need to stop.
Six. I'm gonna, I'm gonna, I'm gonna die. If I keep playing this, my brain is hurting.
I can't do this anymore. All right. So what, anything, what would I just headshot that guy
like 10 times in a row? Let me guess. Let me guess. If I paid you like $3 billion,
you would say that halo reaches a game where master chief gets cataclysmic diarrhea.
Yeah. Is that, this, that's a fun game. I actually like it. They have, you know,
it's the worst part of this. This is the only time I'm going to be playing halo reach and I'm,
I'm an old man on my death bed. How old are you? Like for real? Like how old are you? Not,
not like you're like, this is what I say on Twitch. How old I am, but I'm actually like,
no, I want you to, I want you to embarrass yourself. How old do you think I am?
How old do I think you are? I'm going to say, well, I mean, you've, you've made,
you've made up at least one or two Nintendo 64 references that I've seen. So there's no way that
you're, you're, you're older than 20, 21, 22. You're probably, I don't think you're 30 though.
I would say, yeah. Yeah. I'm going to say 27. Close. I'm a little younger. A little younger?
Oh, much younger. How about this? 25. If I told you that I seriously thought you were 43,
would you believe me? Right. Wait, what? 43, 43. Okay. I don't know if you're asking,
if you're shocked as in like, what the fuck? Like, are you, are you, are, are what happened to you,
Joel? Or are you asking, are you saying 43 as in like, I'm a little younger than that.
No, 43 as in like decade off. Okay. Cause I thought he would like, well, you know,
40. How old do you really think I was? Okay. Uh, I'm fucking, I don't know, 53.
If I was actually 53 years old, I would talk like this. It would seriously be like this. And then
that's, this is the only way that you tell that somebody's like over 45 years old is if they
speak just like this. And this is their actual speaking voice. This is how they talk. Like if
you're 50 years old, it's just how you talk. So, I mean, my voice sounds like this, young, elegant,
smooth, slightly, slightly moving towards. You know what I love about you? You know what I
love about your voice? You describe your own voice as it is a cigarette filter. Ironically, you're
saying like, you're, you're fucking putting it on. You're, you're old as fuck, man.
You're basically walking, talking nicotine.
Smooth, elegant, may have failed quite a few classes in high school, but still made it.
Barely. You're not wrong. Wait, wait, wait, hold on. What's your opinion on vaping?
Um, well, as a gamer, as a lifestyle choice, I think it's important that we, um,
I was going to give you some shit, but I gave up. Um,
are you asking me seriously what I think of vaping? Yeah. Yep. Um, I mean, uh,
what the fuck do you want me to say? Choose your words more carefully next time.
Loki. Are you like a big vape gamer? I think I'm going insane. I think I'm going insane.
I'm fine. Oh, by the way, I feel like I've been sitting in the same spot on the same side of the
map for like an hour and 10 minutes. It wasn't happening. I feel like this game is like what
they call us like old timey, like VR goggles, but it's like one picture and you switch it out
like, what do you call stereo, stereo, stereo, stereoscropic, uh, 3d with the blue and the red.
No, like viewfinder. I'm talking like 1920s, like entertainment, a view master view, view master.
Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. It feels like that where there's like five pictures that you just kind of
cycle around. There's no, no change. And you just like nothing changes, but the scenery that's this
fucking game. Legendary difficulty. I saw somebody write, Hey man, you probably shouldn't have done
legendary difficulty. Cause I like how the story there is, we had to, we have to be like the gamers.
Do I vape? I don't know. I don't vape and neither does Joel. Good. That was awesome. Put that in
somewhere. Listen, I don't like, I don't like that you're assuming that you know me. All right.
Do I not know you? Actually, I realized I don't fall. Actually, you're right. I don't know you at
all. I know you very like, you know, I don't fucking vape, but all right, thanks.
Are you vape? Are you drinking vape juice right now? Is that what you're doing?
Am I drinking vape juice? Yeah. Do you ever, do you know about a thing called Jinkum?
I don't know what that is. You don't, you don't know about Jinkum, Jerma?
I know what Jenga is. The game where you pull blocks out until the house falls down.
Well, I'll tell you, I'll tell you what, tell you what, if you want to read, but
emphasis on read, but, uh, Jankum is, uh, the stream is done. You want to know my official
stance on, on vaping, check out Jinkum. All right. I'm kind of scared to do that.
No, no, it's, it's, it's, it's good and clean. What is this? What does the ordinance do?
Get the hell off my lawn. Did we write this, this piece of dialogue? So is, is this like a,
uh, these are, okay, I see you can either have sprint or the armor thing. Did you get the armor
thing? Uh, not really. Where the fuck did you go? Oh, there's items. There's like materials.
Oh fuck. I remember this fucking level. Hang on. Wait, no, no, no, no, no, for real. I'm not
kidding. This is the level where, where, um, shit is being shot at you constantly. Oh, it's so
annoying. This level, not good. No, it's awful, man. You, you gotta, you, you can have sprint or
back pain. You have to like watch out in this level constantly. It's so annoying. Oh no, they
locked me up. They fucking locked. No, no, no, wait. Oh, you're locked out. They put me behind
the fucking thing. Ordnance. Okay. I'm dropping a bomb on this thing. Check this out. Oh my god,
damn it. I didn't even get to see the thing I did. Hey man, you probably shouldn't have done
legendary difficulty. Why am I just lying? What are you talking about? We're having, we're having
the fucking time of our lives. Where am I? Hey man. Hey man. Uh, just so I ask, you probably
shouldn't have done legendary. Hey man, just want to let you know, what am I doing? What is this
power move thing? Doesn't mean. Uh, give me the health. All right, so this is, I'm gonna, I'm gonna
leave this up to you. You, you have the big red button in front of you and don't, you know, press,
don't press it yet until you find out what it is. I know it's big and shiny and you want to smash
it right now. But that big red button in front of you is, is the, is the out, get out of halo,
like, get out of halo and open up viscera cleanup detail. That's what the big red button is.
Want to make sure you're having fun? No, I'm having fun. All right. You watch out, dude.
Oh, I'm having fun. All right. You should have just played dragon quest builders.
So this is like a recharge. I'll tell you what, next time we fuck to play something,
it's not going to be fucking halo. Okay. Well, all right. This, this was like the big launch.
This is like the big launch game with co-op. My, my asshole fell off.
He's going to get killed. All right. Just take out that. You've got the button in front of you.
If you, I'm, I don't have to, I'm not pressing the button yet. You can press the button if you'd
like. It's there. It's, it's just, there he goes. Okay. Hang on. Oh, I'm on top of the, uh,
the tank or whatever. Oh jeez. You get on it. They're trying to shoot you. They don't get it.
Oh, I did it. I did it. I'm driving it. I think I'm driving it. I, I,
what the fuck's going on? I don't know if I am. No, no, no, I'm not. Cause wait,
you're not driving that. I don't think I am. I'm not pressing anything. Wait. So what are you doing?
Oh, I don't know. So I blacked out. All right. One different weapon. When is halo one going to come
out? Do you know? Uh, too late. Look car. All right. All right. Ready for this. Check this out.
We've got, we've got aliens plus one letter grade. Yeah. Has this game like destroyed your like
ambition to ever play a yellow game again? No, no, I wouldn't say so. All right. Activate anti-air
guns. I don't think so. Whoa. Would you give, would you give halo three online a shot? Cause I
guarantee you it's a way more fun experience. Yeah. I'm having fun. I'm having fun. I just,
I just saw in my mind, I just saw Joel's hand just hover over that button and just like,
he almost pressed it. Wait, what happened? What up my head? Why did we go? What happened? We just
started over. Why did it be the stream rewind? What's the, why is the stream rewinding?
Why are we reliving that? What the fuck is, okay. This is actually kind of freaking me out.
Okay. I'm trying to find some entertainment. I'm trying to find some desperate entertainment.
Okay. Well he's going to press it. I, I, that's the, he, that's the, that's the press the red button
voice. It is. That's, that's the, I'm going to press the red button voice. He's going to do it.
He's going to press it. He's going to press it. You know, let's, let's, let's listen. It won't
promote my gamer license. Well, it's, I don't think so. What do you mean? You, you, you fucking made
the fucking thing. You made this button up. You, you call the shots. What are you fucking talking
about? No, no, no, it doesn't. Why are we back here? What? Oh, the lag. Oh, all right. Wait,
this is us. Wait, hold on. Your desk just opened and another green button just opened to the right
of the red button. The green button, if you press it, gives you host and we load the difficulty.
What button is that? It's the green one. The green button just opened. Red button is get out of
halo, play viscera cleanup detail. If you'd like green button is get out of here, reload game,
lower difficulty, give Joel host another one just came up. It's, it just appeared on the left side.
It's a blue button. I'll tell you what, there's an old, there's an old video, um, on, uh, on YouTube,
in fact. All right. And I'm going to, I'm going to show you that video right now.
Wait, let me show you a video. Well, you're going to go to my stream. Go, we have to go
on to your, watch my stream right now. Okay. All right. Hold on. Let me watch this old video.
The blue, uh, you didn't even know what the blue button did. The blue button, uh,
the blue button turns off your stream and you go to Wendy's. All right. What do you got? We're
going to, okay, let's go to your stream. Are you on my stream? Hold on. I know when you're on the
stream. Tell me when you're on the stream. I'll tell you. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming.
All right. I am. All right. People that have the squad up, just look at, just look at the other
screen. All right. Here we go. Okay. Okay. You have the audio on. Yeah. I have to stop talking.
No, this is a, this is an old video of a kid playing halo. That's all I gotta say. Wait,
hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What? Why? This is not even correct. I'm on your Twitch,
right? Why is this a different person? What are you talking about? Dude, that was strange.
Are you, is this, is this, are you streaming right now? I am streaming. What are you talking
about? Are you serious right now? Where did Jerma go? Am I watching an ad? Is this an ad?
Oh, it's an ad. It's a fucking ad. It's an ad of streamers talking on camera. I was like,
who the fuck are you? I'm like, I'm on. Jerma, I gotta say something. I literally clicked on
your stream and I opened it and it was like, chat is there and there's some girl that's sitting in
the chair. And I was like, is this the stream? Is this video? What's, what am I watching? I was
like, is this the stream? Is this video? What's, all right. Now I got it. Okay. I'm going to stop
talking. Okay. So you're good. Okay. I don't know if you know this. Back in the day, there were,
this is back in the day video from like a hundred years ago of this one kid that really wants to
play the green halo. All right. Now for context, for this stream,
that's my answer. That's for the button. What? No, you wait. You pressed the, did you press the
green button? Well, that's your answer, but you have to press it. You have to actually make the
motion and press it. Oh shit. I pressed it for you. See, I got tons of buttons, but you don't
understand is I've got on every live stream that I've ever done. There's like 25 different buttons
here. And I sometimes forget what they are. All right. You know what button I want to press right
now? All right. Let's go. Stop streaming. Okay. Let's try this one more time. All right. Well,
that button, did you press, they said you said green button. The blue button was stop streaming
and go to Wendy's. The green button was this for cleanup detail. Which button did you press?
Yes, you know, I do. I'll fuck it down. That needs to press this fucking discord call right now and
just fucking get it over with. It's a fucking mistake. Talking to this person. I don't know
who this fucking person is. This has been a miserable experience. I just want to play halo.
I just want to play halo with one of my buddies. I, that's all I wanted. I just want to play halo
with one of my buddies. Okay. Okay. Let's just fucking play some halo. All right. Hang on. Okay.
No, you already, you already pressed the button. You pressed the button. Okay. Well, the fucking
button is pressed. I just want. How do I leave the game? Are you still here? Unfortunately.
Okay. That was halo reach just came out on screen. If you could check it out,
maybe you'd think it was fun. Do you even have this reclaimed detail? We did this yesterday.
This is like the game that we go to. Hang on. Hang on. Do I, do you even own the game?
I got to see if I do. Surely I have that. Hang on.
Oh, I have this right. Clean up detail. I have this right. Clean up detail. Shadow warrior.
Yeah. Do you have the original one? No. How do you not have the original viscera?
Fucking, I don't know. What do you mean? He said, wait, he chose green. Wait, green was.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Hold on. What was the, what did the green button do?
Well, it's your fucking body. You made them up. Hold on. The red button was to.
Dude, did you, did you choose lower difficulty and get host and halo?
Or did you choose exit halo? What did I press? Sorry.
Jeremiah was like getting into my gamer hole there for a second. What the fuck was he saying?
What was he saying? Joel cut the blue wire.
Lower difficulty. Okay. Well, so we're playing halo now or. Oh God.
I love this. This is fucking awesome. All right. So I'm going to look, we've, we're, we're,
let me ask you, would you like just no fucking messing around? No jokes, no comedy.
No. Would you like to continue to play halo straight up straight up? Let's play some halo.
Do you, would you, the answer, the answer is no. Nope. No, bit bopping. Okay. Straight up.
All right. Just halo. Halo. All right. So the answer to that is no. Fuck this game.
Okay. So, uh. I don't want to play any more halo, dude. Like if I play more halo,
I'm going to have fucking, I'm going to start vomiting. All right. Out of my school.
I can't do anymore. All right. Quick follow up question. Okay. Hold that thought just for a
sec and just keep it in the oven. All right. You know what fucking game we need to play?
I realized that we are the most inept ever. Our brains are not aligned at all to interact
with each other. We need to play that fucking bomb game. You know, when you got to defuse a bomb,
don't keep talking. And then we would be killer at that. Like right now,
not right now, but at some point that would be the most bad yes stream ever.
That would be so bad. People are saying, okay, why don't, why don't, why don't we just do it
right now? But let me, I, I, let me ask you this question. Um, did, did you want to play halo
at all from the very beginning? Were you, was, were you just humoring me that whole time?
It started off with you were setting these buttons scenarios for me and there was some,
something about Wendy's in there. But then I thought about something about the drain
pipe and you training snakes and that's steer me off the fucking road for a second.
And then you watched my stream and you mentioned there was another streamer on my stream. So I said,
okay, I'm clicking out. I'm talking out of this situation. All right. And then at some point,
you started saying, do you want to lower the difficulty? And I said, no, no. And then I said,
I don't want to play anymore. I want to, I want to go take a nap. I don't want to do this. So
you thought this was going to be so easy. So, all right. So let me back up completely all the
way to the very beginning. We're talking to two hours ago, or even like four days ago, five days
ago. Right. Okay. Okay. Hey, you, so you want like, let's play halo. You're thinking, oh, this guy's
just a halo channel. He's fucking knows what he's doing. Like, well, that's what he does on his
channel. No fucking point, German. Did I refer to you as like, oh, this guy's a halo channel.
Like I might be stupid, but I'm not a fucking amoeba. Right. I have some brain cells jumping
around in my, my big peanut. All right. Like you, you think, you think I, I, I'm in a coma.
You think I woke up one day and I said, yeah, German's a halo channel. Like, yeah,
maybe you played halo down the line, but at no fucking point did I interact with you over the
years. Yeah, he played halo all his life. What the fuck? Think before you speak. What are you saying?
Hey, you're talking about reaching into the toilet and like pulling up like drain pipes.
All right. So what are we doing? What do we want? What do you want to play? I'm going to play.
I want to, um, I don't know. I want to play, uh, bomber man on super Nintendo. Um,
the ball game. We keep talking. Nobody explodes. That sounds like a, that sounds like you. Well,
let's see. Okay. Keep talking. Oh my God. Oh, I own this. Do you own this?
The, the expo game. Yeah. Do you own keep talking and nobody explodes at the moment,
but I have a great idea. Check this out. Right. You've heard of a game called thief workers too.
You can't, you can't. Well, answer the question gamer. All right. You can't,
you can't, you can't, you can't, you can't go. You can't, you can't. Okay. Like if I invited you
into my house, right? If I was like, okay, come over my house and I got all, I got all these
trophies. So wait, so, so, okay. I got a bunch of bowling trophies. You're like, hey, you're a bowler.
Huh? Jerma calls you over and says, Hey bro, you want to fill my gamer hole with some video games?
How do you respond? I would first say, Hey, could you please reevaluate the question?
What is a gamer hole? It's your eyes. All right. I'm about to install keep talking and nobody
explodes. This stream sucks ass. This is honestly, this is, I love this street. This is like my
favorite stream. All right. I'm about to install keep talking. All right. No, you know, I just
pressed the green button. No, no, no, that's halo. I'm pressing the, uh, all right. I'm gonna ask
you straight up. Do you want to play keep talking and nobody explodes right now? I'll tell you what.
I'll tell you what. Like dropping, drop. No, this is not a fucking, this is not, this is not a
fucking thousand questions. This is not a conundrum. This is not a fucking story. Just hear me out.
All right. Without any fucking irony, without no sarcasm, no waterfall of diarrhea, diarrhea is
is she commenting stuff. Here's the facts. All right. Let's play some games at some other point
because it's 3 AM and I'm about to shit myself. All right. All right. So you pressed, you pressed
the Wendy's button. Okay. All right. You pressed, you pressed the stop streaming button. I see.