Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma and MLC Stealth here with a late night live commentary.
Nice. You gotta be cool. You're even like in the call. Oh god, I forgot I equipped this.
I'm already trying so hard, I become silent. Why did I go after him with that? That was a mistake.
This is a spy. Get out of my face. No, he's not there. But anyway, this is a late night live commentary.
Haven't done a commentary like this in a long time.
He was so WM1 that he didn't even know what to do when the edge came about him.
When was the last time I did do a live commentary besides the live streaming stuff? I can't even remember.
But here it is. Oh, well, you are a spy. I think he's still alive. Maybe.
And get... Yeah, I got you. What just happened? Did that guy just blow himself up?
There seems to be a lot of people who are doing that this game. Come on, take another one of those.
I can't hit this guy. Oh my god, I just barely missed him. What is...
You know, it's been so long since I've used the flare gun. I equipped it to like change things up and I haven't even... Yeah, that's a spy.
What are you playing as? Pyro. I gotta get my flare gun shots down.
We've been playing Shoe Mania Storm for years. Come on. For years.
Oh, that's gonna make people angry. I just shot a rocket into the spawn.
Oh look, it's Wheatley. Here we go. Here's Dean Pelton. What's he got? He's got the knife, the ambassador.
Oh, you're watching me? I'll watch this like spawn kill. Are you really just like spawn killing people?
Kinda. It's not like on purpose though. And I did face stab a heavy just now.
Yeah, I'm spawning. Oh my god. Yeah, right.
Oh, I just got a crit-rocketed in the face. I was gonna reflect it too, I just got too close to him.
Where am I on this scoreboard? It's pretty awful right now. I'm doing pretty good.
I just heard somebody scream. What? How did this guy get back here? My goodness.
And scout! Get hit. No. Why did I do that? Man, Blue Team is just not doing this right now.
I think maybe we should switch to the other team. Let's tell Black Wholesun and ReverseCowgirl133 to go on...
Oh my god, so many people just came up here. The entire Blue Team just came up the stairs.
So many people were just right there. It's almost like all of them were talking over Skype to come and get me.
I dare you, get that Pyro.
That guy's emblem is the community flag for the school of the TV show. He's my new favorite person.
I was just about to hate him for killing me, but you can't hate that. He deserves it.
And my name is Dean Pelton! How great is that?
He probably likes you right now. He loves the references.
I'm not sure what to do. I think we got it. Oh god, Sniper.
Let's go Blue. Can you get on Blue?
I'm not sure what to do. Love your emblem, says Dean Pelton.
Oh, it's too late. Can't. We're going to have to be against each other now.
I'm going to destroy you and burp at the same time.
Not even high enough. Rain needles down!
Are those even making it across? I think so. Maybe not.
Oh buddy, you have no idea what's in store for you!
I really need to put on the crit screen if I'm going to do this. I will put that on after.
Oh, come on now, you damn woman.
Kill me. Thanks, ma'am.
Come on, how does nobody die from that? How does nobody die from that?
Barrage of needles that went in his face.
I'm doing it again. Oh, he's building a sentry. Is that you building that sentry?
I am on spy. So nope.
One more hit, this guy's dead. He knows it too.
Oh, that was lucky.
Alright, I gotta turn the crit screen on. I gotta put the crit screen on.
Let's push this up.
Stay on this point, boys. Heals for everybody, heals for all.
And that's when I make my exit. Stay on there. Nice.
Is he going to get it? I hope so.
It's probably a bad idea that we're facing each other.
I'm going battle medic, man. What? What the hell was that?
Oh man. My god, a lot of chaos here.
Oh, that was lucky and close. I need the health that's up here.
Gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme.
Alright, is that guy's name Andariel?
Oh, what? Oh, random crits. Those confuse me right now.
Let's go down here. Let's go down here, buddy.
Oh, look out. Kill that heavy. Kill that heavy?
I gotta keep this thing on him. Now he needs it.
Alright, so I see a spy in my team. He's just crouch walking around with his thing.
I wish you could have seen what just happened here.
He's going to know I'm right here. See if I can't.
Oh, I thought I could have killed him. How much health?
Oh, no way.
Oh my gosh, that guy's lagging. Geez.
I hear a roar across the whole stadium right now. What's happening?
I don't hear anything.
It sounds like I'm in a haunted mansion right now.
Wait, what? Oh my god, it's a speed hacker.
What?
It's a hacker. It's a speed hacker. It's a speed hacker.
It's a guy with scream hacks, speed hacks.
Oh my god. That scared me so much.
Dude, what's with the screaming?
I thought I was in a haunted mansion.
No, don't open the door.
I just thought everyone was dying.
Oh, you bastards. Don't open that door.
Dude, he is going. Look at him. Where is he?
Oh my god, dude.
I'm just going to go. I'm holding the dead ringer out.
I'm so afraid of that noise.
Where is he?
Psycho.
Oh my god. Oh my god. Holy crap.
Oh, that's terrifying. Can you hear this?
Is he gone? Yeah, I can hear it.
Oh, man. Well, so much for the live commentary.
What are you talking about? We got it.
I know. Look at this.
Oh my gosh. I'm going to have a nightmare of this sound.
He's just following me around.
Oh, I'm dizzy right now.
Hold on a second. I need to go spectate. I need to watch this guy.
Why does it say everyone's changing their name to Dean Pilton?
They clearly are not.
That's him. Where is he? Here he is.
Look at this guy. Look at this guy's totally legit game he's doing right now.
Anyone he runs into, he changes his name to them.
This is ridiculous.
I'm spectating him right now, and it seriously is one of the oddest things I've ever seen.
Yep, here I come.
What's his name?
His name changes every two seconds.
This is hurting my head.
I know. I have to... I disconnected.
I couldn't take the screams in my head anymore.
That's scary. That's a scary sound.
That really is.
Oh my gosh.
Well...
Alright, so apparently I wasn't going crazy when I said,
Hey, why am I afraid right now in a haunted house?
What are you talking about? Oh my gosh.
Thanks everybody for watching.
I do appreciate it.
Yeah, hacks are not cool.
So I guess we'll talk to you guys soon.
Take it easy everybody.
I just said take it easy everybody.
Take care everybody. See you all soon.