He's not here. Yeah, I am here. I'm gonna one minute can go by before I come and say hello
Hello quick show ads. No, i'm not gonna i'm not gonna show ads during this
You don't see ads in the movie theater, but you see ads for other movies before the movie starts
No, i'm not. I don't think I can even do that
Plus I would just play gemini man trailer five times
Just pretend I did that
That'll be
Forever
Hey, that was a plus two. That was a that was a thought plus two
I didn't do it, but I was thinking about it
Yeah, i've already had a drink. Is there a problem with that?
I'm 21
Oh, you don't think i'm gonna have a couple glasses of cocktail
To watch we're gonna watch public domain. We're gonna watch the gorilla from 1939 guys
Like i'm i'm gonna have i'm gonna have a drink because that's what i'm gonna do
He's not you know, why are you not sober to appreciate the art?
So we have three movies
That are lined up here
because
something that I realized by
starting to put this stuff together is
The the trend of movies being more than two fucking hours long
Happened recently
Movies used to be an hour long
They used to be one to one point over that all these movies are like an hour long one point hour and 20 hour
And ten hour and ten
I was like, holy shit
I'm not gonna be able to watch more than like one or two of these all movies are like an hour and 45 minutes
No, they're not that's just like
It's like the last five years
What about the lord of the rings? That's that's where it started
Thanks a lot peter jackson more like the last 40 right
recently
Well the last like 20 no even movies in the 80s weren't more than an hour and 20 hour and 30
Movies in the night of some movies in the 90s
What about gone with the wind?
How long was gone how gone with the wind?
runtime
This is four hours
Oh, wait a minute. How long is the intermission in gone of gone with the wind?
It was a hundred and fifteen minutes
So yeah, there was there's a there's an there's a more than one full movie length in the middle
What about the ten commandments?
ten commandments
runtime
Three hours and 40 minutes
All right, one of the searches for the ten commandments runtime people also ask
Is anyone still alive from the ten commandments and if you think about that like that's
No, probably no that was like thousands of years ago
I don't think so
Is anybody even still alive from when they did that?
Everyone moses did that is he still alive?
Imagine being
Imagine the internet existed
during that whole during that time period imagine going back and looking at old pictures of moses instead of like
Fucking abbot and costello
Oh, wow. This is like an old an old moses picture
cool
Well old school cool. It's like moses with a surfboard. What the fuck? I can't even comprehend this. That's like my grandmother
We live in a weird time. Don't we redditor? I know i'm a i'm a front page redditor. We already went over this
I'm not a real redditor. I'm a i'm a redditor that only goes to the first part
But welcome here's the what's on tap tonight
We're going to do the gorilla which is an hour long and then we're going to do plan nine from outer space
Which is an hour and 18 minutes
And then we're going to top it off
With santa claus conquers the martians which is also about an hour and 18
So we're going to make a couple of rules here
For how these are going to be watched
um
Do I get?
at least two
30 second skip vetoes
Like I get to skip 30 seconds
No, why?
Um, I don't know if I know I I I can skip like 20 seconds if I need to
We want to suffer
So these movies weren't gonna be good santa claus conquers the martians is probably gonna be like a good movie
Okay, I got it's probably gonna be a good movie
That's why i'm saving it for last
What's 30 seconds going to accomplish?
um, I don't know
Skipping, uh nudity that could be in one of these movies. I don't know the second. I see clothes come off
I'm skipping 30 seconds. That's just the way i'm sorry. That's gonna happen
That's my that's what i'm talking about here
Santa's gonna be nude. I don't know
Are you guys ready?
Are you ready for the first one? We've got the gorilla
And this is by this is a horror
Comedy movie by the ritz brothers
You don't know who the ritz brothers are
They're the three stooges, but they're not the three stooges. They're just three guys that like let's get out of here
And they hit each other in the head with stuff
Uh, it was pretty popular at the time
Like the the three guys hit each other in the head with hammers and punch each other in the nose and pinch each other's ears
was
the fortnight youtuber
You know what I mean? There's a lot of them. It was a lot of them like back in like the the 30s
This was like the youtuber. This was like the influencer. They just like the fortnight guy
So you're like wait, well, how come there's so many three stooges copies you tell me not this again
That's a plus two hot take no, it's not that's just what do you want to say?
It's like the most popular game and everybody plays it
I don't play it though because i'm fucking I do stuff. I do stuff. I do different. I do stuff different
I don't play fortnight because I just I do things different
Right, uh 50 dollars just came in
from brooding
high rope tarot
It's 5 000 bits. Thank you
Hi, jerma. I'm sorry. My last donation was worded so badly
I didn't mean for it to sound like that. The dream was that you were streaming but also chat could talk on stream
And kim was making fun of me for being louder than you and that people couldn't hear you
Anyways, thanks for being such a funny guy. I've been going through a shitty time recently and having a laugh helps
Can we watch the jimmy neutron movie? That would be illegal
Jimmy neutron is currently owned by believe viacom and they keep coming out with stuff and it's not in public domain
I would get a lot of trouble. I would get sued. We're going with non-sued movies
Not in public domain. It's unfortunate
Maybe in 75 years when it goes into public domain, we'll we'll watch it. But yeah, I don't know my like grandson like german
German jr. German jr. Nine eight five when he's streaming in a hundred years
Uh, you guys can watch that together. It'll be in public domain by then but thanks for the 50 dollars a lot of money
And with that, uh, why don't we get started? I'm ready. How can you be ready? But I am
um, so I
I
So I can't skip at all at all
Okay
All right. Fine. Fine. Fine. Fine. Here we go. There comes the gorilla starring the ritz brothers. Wait, we're gonna get like a
countdown
free
All right. Shh. Fine. Fine. Fine. Fine. Thx. There is thx sound. I'm so excited
Oh the rich brothers the three goofballs, it's too loud
Show your face
No, when you watch a movie the guy's face isn't down in the corner. That's not how this works
I'm not part of the movie
Hey ten community subs. Thanks snake cowboy for the tens up. All right charge. Quiet. Quiet. Quiet
We got to invert. Oh, hey, you know, don't skip immerse us in the movie, but please put a face cam 40 percent of the screen
You're a maniac
Murderer terrorizes suburb
There he is
Is that supposed to be a real is a real gorilla at least baffled as the gorilla strikes again
Maniac murderer claims another victim. Is it just the zoo? Did he get out of the zoo?
Let's just turn stricken as murderer makes good his threat. How hard is it to catch a gorilla?
Why is he like reaching behind a desk to try to find dropped keys?
Parting is such sweet sorrow
That I shall say good night till it be morrow
Oh, I also read romeo and julia
Good night
Parting is such sweet sorrow
That I should say good night
Till it be morrow. Why are you praying to romeo and juliet?
Just put a note on her
c4
He just has a hitman costume on it's 47
Pick up a weapon, why don't you take the note off and just see what it says
Wait, this is well kiddy
What is all this racket about?
Oh
I saw him. I saw him. He's here in this house. The gorilla
You have been dreaming. Oh, no, what's that? I don't know. I'm telling you. I don't know anything
Why is he fully dressed is he sleeping a suit
You're hysterical. Oh, no, anything is just you go back to bed. That's what I said, sir. Only there is this
Uh-oh walter stevens. You are next to die
gorillas
That didn't take very long. You didn't even do individual letters. You fucking hack should I call the police, sir?
Please. Yes. Yes call them right away
Just a minute panel. This is my own way. Yes, sir. Only but it's a gorilla what I was thinking of the time, sir
Time according to the newspapers the gorilla gives his victim only 24 hours notice
I mean only what?
Oh nonsense. Now you go back to bed and don't why is the amazon prime? I don't understand. Oh, don't go back to bed
I'm not particularly interested. Where you go. Oh, well, mr. Stevens
Gorilla prime
Come please
That'll be all. Yes, sir. Yeah, but I wouldn't be frightened like that if I were you kiddy
Look you'll be frightened any way you want. This is mine, too
I want those big huge fucking cabinet doors. Hello
I begged you not to telephone me here
Yes, I know I promised but
You gave me until monday
saturday
Tomorrow that's a debt collector. That's impossible
I can't possibly raise that amount of money
Yes, I know I owe it to you but a quarter of a million dollars
Be reasonable
Now, please be patient
I have a plan
But it's only just started give me time to work it out and i'll repay you dollar for dollar
If you don't repay do they send the gorilla after you?
It's kind of fucked up
Behind you quick turn around
It's bugleberry
I want to send a radiogram, please
Miss norma denby dears in denver aboard ss paris
Regret unable to meet you at boat
vitally important
That I see you at my home tomorrow evening
without fail smork sign it
fondly
Uncle walter make sure you put smork on read that back, please
Rain was so hard to do back in like the 40s
I didn't even invent rain rain wasn't even invented until the fucking 60s
I'm norma denby
Welcome to our fuckface
Stevens is expecting you miss denby
May I take your coat? Oh, no. Thank you. I'll keep it on
Who is this person by the way place your uncle has here he likes it
You have to live in it this way, please
Huge cabinet doors. I love them. Well, well, well if it isn't the prodigal niece
I'll see you again darling. Is that her stepping down dear? She weighed like five metric tons. Good. I'm glad you did
This is jack uncle walter
This niece of mine isn't much of a correspondent what few letters she did write though were full of you
Congratulations young man. Thank you. And I hope you'll excuse me for barging in like this nonsense. I'm delighted
I was more than personally surprised to hear that you set your marriage for dune
Do you realize it's only a month away? Well, we decided we didn't want to rush things too much. So oh we put it off until
the day after tomorrow
The day after tomorrow
Soon
Hi
I know no, that's fine
That's one of the things I wanted to talk to you about
But i'm forgetting my role as host sit down my dear sit down
We may as well come to the point
I can't get this suit on to talk to norma alone. Mr. Stevenson. Oh, no. No, it's airtight. Help me as norma's future husband
What I have to say concerns you too
now as norma knows
She and I were named joint heirs under the terms of her father's will
And until she marries i'm the executive of her estate
But should anything happen to either of us by then the survivor inherited the entire estate
And I think that you norma and you jack as her future husband should know of what that estate consists
to that end
I prepared a record of the estate's holdings
And I want to talk it over with you both after dinner
But your radiogram said there was something urgent the fire feels so good. Yeah, I wouldn't want to be that close
Urgent I
I wouldn't have sent it
Something's worrying you what is it? Uncle walder? Well, perhaps i'm unduly alarmed but
Last night I received the black and white boomer face
From the gorilla
The gorilla you mean that murderer the one the papers have been so full of I do
What the fuck but isn't it possible that this is all just a joke that someone's playing a prank on you?
I wish I could think so
But uncle walder why should he just tell him that you owe a quarter of a million dollars to the fucking irs
Whatever it is possible some old enemy of mine
I admit I made enemies in my day
It's possible that one of them in the spirit of revenge has hired this this maniac this
Professional killer or whatever the gorilla is this note is exactly like the one that was in newspapers
After you murdered that widow
Still I can't bring myself to believe it
Of course, you've notified the police
No, I haven't but surely if there was anything they never do I've taken other precautions peters and I are armed
And in addition i've engaged the services of a private detective agency
Their operative should be here any moment now. Oh, of course not. I didn't call the police
I called three comedy dickheads that are going to bumble around and break stuff
And probably blow up the microwaves successes. It is apparent the workings of the police were an open book to him
Of course, it's a slim chance that by not notifying the police. We might upset his plans
ordinarily i'm not easily frightened, but
I must admit this whole affair is giving me the creeps. Well, it's nearly nine o'clock. I suppose you freshen up a bit
We talk it over after dinner
I thought about craigslist
Oh kitty
Show me some damage to the green room. Mr. Marsden to my room. Yes, sir. Don't worry uncle
Oh, excuse me, mr stevens
Yes, kitty. Oh, I know it's no no black and white face game. You're not trying to tell me you're gonna leave me
Oh, no, sir. I'm trying to tell you I have left you but kitty. You're perfectly safe here
What besides we have guests you haven't the heart to leave me now
Well, my heart is willing but i'm gonna have an awful time trying to convince the rest of my body
Whoopsie we just drove into somebody hack me detective agency
Don't call the police call it with three toddlers
I
What's the joke here
He can see through it
I'll bet there's a dead body in every room. That body won't hurt you
Can't do you any good. It's of rain. I get it. Well, what are we waiting for?
All right, who's gonna slip in the water? Someone's gonna slip and fall in the rain slip in the puddle step out and slip in the water
You get my reference tonight chief make it out of there. Uh, keep doing that once in a while. It keeps me on edge
I'm thinking come on good slip in the water. Now. What are you supposed to want to take this boy? I've got an idea
Uh, let's go in and find out you're terrific
We're joints are speakeasy
I love it. I love it so far
Me why i'm peter, sir, never mind that never mind that what's your name peter, sir
Hey, just a minute. Just a minute. Where were you last night? I beg you pardon
Oh, so you did do something. I don't like your looks. What's that got to do with it? This is no beauty contest
I just had to flick a cigarette into the car's casket. I can't even man. I keep thinking of the fucking stupid
kramer
The gun no stevens. I am i'm harrigan. I'm mulligan. I'm garrity harrigan mulligan
garrity
I assume for you because I mean what you call yourself. I'll tell you what now tell me any clues one very vital one
This warning from the gorilla. That's where you've got nothing to worry about mark that down garrity, right?
How do you spell gorilla two r's or two l's gorilla? I don't know
g o r two l's g g o
Did you did you
Did you say gorilla?
My gentleman is not afraid
Thank you the gorilla coming here, why is it scarier than a fucking murderer?
Quiet oh did you did you say an animal? Uh, just an animal like a wild animal versus a murderer with motive
Every door and window is securely bolted. I couldn't have done better myself with us on the job. Mr. Stevens
You've got nothing to worry about what's your plan? Mr. Harrigan? Well, first, we'll take a look around the house. Come on, man
Now you just sit tight. Mr. Stevens. The gorilla will get you over our dead bodies
All right
It really is the threes to just just more articulate
Probably the detectives your uncle hired
Jack i'm terribly worried. What are we going to do? Well, it seems there isn't anything we can do yet
Listen darling. It isn't that i'm trying to appear skeptical. It's just that well somehow I can't make myself believe all this
But that note you saw the note, of course I did but still I
Look darling, we'll wait. We'll wait and see if something really does happen three redditors. I just don't believe it. Well
Jack
What's that?
That's the gorilla like me. It has to be excuse me, sir
Yeah, I tried to put your car away, but unfortunately there's something wrong with it. What do you mean?
It won't start
Excuse me, sir
He gives me the creeps he doesn't exactly give me enough no, that's the red herring
That's the red herring. It's not him
Don't you think there's any cause for alarm? I'm afraid I don't
Thank you, no
But I will uh smoke all of your cigarettes. In fact, how many do you have?
I'm fucking scared. We just saw his face
Not very long. Why well, are you sure he's all right? I found him. So why?
Well, because I
Dinner is served, sir
Oh, shall we go in?
You would notice that you would know that was happening why can you hear them?
Oh here take it but my nerves really need is a good long trip
Yeah, okay, where were you last night me why I answer yes or no
What are you doing there doing? Where well, how do we know besides?
I don't like your looks. Did you ever take a good look at yourself? Yeah, did you ever take a look?
Hey now, wait a minute you where were you last night? I spent the night with shakespeare. Yeah, where is he? He's dead
A minor mystery
Have you any idea who did it? Look shakespeare's been dead hundreds of years
Hundreds. This is a fine time to call us in on the case
Say but she couldn't have done it. How do you know she can't be hundreds of years old?
That's right mark that down garrity
You two have a look out there i'll look here. Yeah
Come on break the sink enough water get all over you
What's this that's a door at least to the back stairs back stairs well remind me to have a look up there sometime
Boomer humor
That's an ironing board
Do you want this thing certainly we want it. What do you think we are you're not? Yeah
Well here take it
We found it what a psycho
Well, that's hash. Ain't that a mystery some pretty good tidy chief. I'll be the judge of that
I'm afraid gentlemen, you won't find the gorilla in there
There why will we not find the gorilla in there now listen you
Shit let that be a lesson to you perhaps you gentlemen had better look outside for
WWE how do you get out of here? That's what i'd like to know and where's the back door and back
Do the iron again, come on
I knew it was gonna i'm I think it's funny recall that the paper said the girl always sends a warning to as many as half a
Dozen people unironically laughing at this because it's just so stupid. Maybe that's what he's doing now
Perhaps it's just a ruse. Well, let's hope so
You know, it's wonderful how much more optimistic a good dinner can make one feel
Shall we have liquors in the study smoking at the table at dinner?
Oh
The lights off well the lights off I know no what happened look here it seems to have been thrown in through that window
12 hours. Oh shit
What are we going to do the first thing we're going to do or rather jack is going to do
Is to take you away from here when you're coming with us
It's him
Uncle waldo
Who is it?
Uh, no. No, he's making a handful of e-boat faces. It could be anybody
He did give me a turn
Do you see that face? I bet when he gets drunk snakes see him
I'm just trying to let you know i'm not the gorilla
Please the stem be of her Beyonce, mr. Marsden
harrigan mulligan and
guarantee
This battle seems to be much more serious than I thought
I've just received this from the gorilla
I know who brought it. No one brought it
To throw me through that window
He's right, this is my good ear
That was good cat. Oh say that's right. You can't kid us. We're outside patrolling the grounds. What do you mean?
By the note couldn't have come through that window. But why not? Well, i'll just show you stand back, man
That's why
But it was wrapped around the stone a stone a stone. Oh, why didn't you say so?
Anyway, what do you know about this thing?
Well, I don't know anything about it
We were preparing to leave the room and suddenly the lights went out and then there was a crash and oh so the lights went out
Make a note of that garrity, right?
You're outside a few minutes ago. Didn't you see anybody? Nobody but us
Take a note of that gary
Midnight. Yeah, what time is it now? It's 10 30. I got 11 10. I got 11 30. It's exactly 11 45
Remind me to put some hands on this watch. Yes. Well make a note of that garrity, right now
Look, the gorilla's after stevens. We'll have to keep an eye on him everybody into the study. Come on. Let's go
Uh, who said that? I wonder if anybody dies rope. He'll hang himself you chief. Oh, that's where I heard it before
Is the gorilla
Oh
Smash some stuff. Come on, you know you want to
This is a guy in a gorilla suit
Is it no, it's not a real gorilla
I don't know. I don't know where that was supposed to be
That's somebody's basement
That was a real ape. No, it wasn't that was like
That scared the fucking shit out of me. God damn boomer jump scares lightning in every movie
Now that you're all here, yes, but come right back quiet personally, I don't believe the gorillas coming here neither do I
Why not?
Reasons pal harrigan mulligan and garrity. It ain't enough
Now look here
Oh should have 5g tower have received the gorillas warning walter stevens. You've just five minutes to live
Oh, what jack?
Excuse me
Here now, where are you going? I'm getting out of here. There's no door there. Oh, that's all right. I'll make one. Goodbye
Quiet quiet everybody who's even talking
They're all kramer
All of them. They're all they're all castanza and kramer combined into one person
Did you hear that? I wish I didn't
He's up there man. Why are you gone? I said he's up there. That's what I thought you said
Classic absolutely classic
It's mr. X
Is it the gorilla?
Nothing at all. What did he just double barrel shotgun kill something down there? That was like a I shot something with a shotgun sound
Hey
Did you just pass here?
Yes
Yes, of course. I brought a trunk down from the attic a trunk. Yes. Were we here?
I couldn't say
Well, maybe we're not here now
Maybe
Maybe wait, is he the gorilla?
It's two minutes of 12. What about uncle walter? Uncle walter. Yes, uncle walter. We're uncle. We're just going in
Now everybody
Stay just don't get him in there. You watch that one
You've got nothing to worry about I wish I thought so me too
You have one more minute walter stevens
If this is an elaborate birthday prank i'm gonna be really upset at this movie happy birthday mr. Stevens
Someone's gonna die
I can't stand any longer. I can't you've got to call. Please. You've got to mr. Stevens. I'm sorry, but norm is right
I don't know what this is all about. But certainly if there's something to it, the police ought to know about it
I no longer know what to think
Perhaps you'd better
Hello
Lines cut
Oh just open the door the butler just came in he wasn't in the
See, how did you get in here? Why through this door, sir? How can you when the doors are locked?
I beg your pardon. It was not locked. I locked it myself
It is locked that leaves us dead locked. It would be impossible for me to walk through the woodwork. Why termites do
Oh, this isn't getting us anywhere. Now leave everything to me. The gorilla ain't gonna make monkey out of me
Now you
But who could
Turning into clue
Well, what are you waiting for? I don't know but I wish I could think of something me too. I'll go on
Don't worry darling. Oh, that's all right. I'll do all the work marston come with me
But they keep separating it you first, sir
Thank you very much. He's waving that gun around like
Point that thing down
Right from under our very eyes, I don't understand how he got out of here. Oh no
He's gonna kill her
What was that
Are you sure it wasn't a hallucination not unless a hallucination has hair on it come on
Oh, they can they can
That's obviously the gorilla
Who is he?
I've never seen him before. Do you know him? No, sir. And this is no time for no introductions
He's not dead. Yeah mark that down too. Come on darling. We're getting out of here. I'm afraid now too for you
It's him
Oh jack, it's horrible. I don't know what to make of it. Now all I can say is around here somewhere
I know mr stevens is around here somewhere and if you all look we'll find him somewhere. Where are you going somewhere?
Yes, there it is upstairs. Come on garrity you lead the way
They said he's not dead
A hillary clinton statue over there something funny about this was that kitty said she saw the gorilla's arm
We open the closet and find the sailor's body now
How did the body get in there and how did the gorilla get out without our seeing him?
That's just what I was about to ask you
Stevens was sitting right here in this chair until the lights went out
Gorilla, what is this? What is this a jervis dream?
What's funny? Nothing. I think i'll have a look around this house. Have a look around the house. Yes, I have have a look around the house
Yeah
I'll go too. Yes, it is. Yeah, you're right
Hey that guy won't talk. Why not? He's still unconscious. You're unconscious and you talk
That's great chief mark that down garrity. Right. What do we do now? Well, first we'll have to
I love these guys. Well, how do we do that? Now? Let's see when the lights went out. Stevens was sitting in that chair
You're steven sit down. I'm steven mulligan close the doors
I'm garrity you're stevens now sit down. I'll wait for lights
One oh, they're gonna find it out two
three
Ah, it's no use
I don't know. It works for sure like homes
I don't know why it wouldn't work for me
That's what i'm trying to tell you. He's gone. Is he gone?
garrity
Now we have two mysteries to solve. Let's i've got an idea. What is it? If we can find out how garrity disappeared
We'll find out what happened to stevens. You sit in that chair now. Should have thought of that myself. They're all gonna sit in the chair
You have to be tired to sit down I do
You make me tired well, and why don't you sit down if I sit down who's gonna work the lights
I never thought of that. Yeah. Well sit down. Yes sit down
One
Three gone
He's gonna make her sit down
After one you'll sit down and like it. Oh, all right. I'll sit down but I won't like it. Yep
This guy's just fucking electric chairing everybody
Well, it's just what I want to find out
Killing everybody one two two two two two
Three
What a pity
The killer
Wait, is this a scam the whole time?
Wait a minute. I
So where did the three uh ritz brothers go?
Is he taking them out? Is everybody outside?
So he just puts them in the closet
Hey, what's the matter? What's happening? Oh, look i'm standing here
And all of a sudden everything goes black
next thing I know
I'm here. That's funny
Hello
Hello, i'm sorry. I kept you waiting. No. No you turn on willow dry. You're not gonna question who this person is
Thank you. Look it ain't human. I'll tell you it ain't human
What isn't human?
For a guy to be standing here one minute and the next minute he's gone. Who's gone? I'm gone. They're gone
Everybody's gone. It don't make sense. Certainly doesn't will you have a cigarette? I don't mind if I do
He kidnapped me right from under his very eyes. Who does the gorilla?
Hey
Who are you? Watch that match. It's gonna hurt. What do you want? What are you doing here?
Listen old man, you got me all wrong. I just came in to use the telephone. You see my car broke down that phone
Look, that phone is out of order. Is it? Yes
Well, if you'll excuse me i'll be on my way you bastard you pranked me you
You're the gorilla surely you don't think i'm the gorilla. I stopped thinking two hours ago, but you don't understand. I don't have to understand
Shall I try it? Oh you've tried enough now get him up. Listen, you're making a big mistake
Well, it won't be the first time
What the fuck just happened?
Did he just like did he just kick him in the balls?
What just happened?
What just happened? Oh
All right. All right. I got your club
Okay, shake him up shake him up
Wait the safe
The safe is always behind the picture
Oh shit, he knows the secret passages
Help help me
For a second, I thought that was the guy that just left for the secret passage. I was like what the he just took his hat off
Get it right there. Oh, it was terrible the gorilla the gorilla. Why did you get all tied up like this the gorilla?
I tell you it wasn't my fault. He came in and hit me. It was
Did I leave it in there?
Everybody's in that closet. That's like that's the hitman's storage closet
Oh
You tell me what are you doing with those things on this is what happens when the npcs wake up when you leave the level
Yeah, you start to use that phone and get very far not with me on the job lucky thing for him
You had your handcuffs with you. Where is he? Where'd he go? Where is he? I'm the victim. How should I know?
Look boys. I'm telling you walked in six of them six big gorillas. They attacked me six right on my crow
He's making that up. Yeah, look at this one. Look right there
These windows are locked from the inside
Six of them not kidding kidding with the gorilla right under my nose and a ten thousand dollar reward. He says i'm kidding
Well, are you?
Who belongs to this? That's like a million dollars, by the way. Why gorillas don't wear coats. Sure. They do fur coats
Something screwy about all this
There's anything screwy about this. It's me
It's me, but i'll soon find out each of you grab a wall. What do we do with it?
You take that one
I'm, I think it's funny. Whatever. It's fucking stupid grab a wall
I'll take it easy. I'll tap each one of you. See if you can find some trap doors
Didn't he see the bookcase open?
I thought he saw this happen
Must be out there. Come on, man right out here
Who's yelling for help? Right? Right? Right? I cover the door man. That's right. Who are you never mind?
New characters being introduced late in the game here
What do you think I didn't come here to play games?
I want to see walter stevens and want to see him right now, but you don't understand. These gentlemen are detectives detectives
What are you trying to pull on me? I talked to stevens on the telephone last night
He told me he had a plan to pay his debt plan. Yeah said he'd only just started working on it
But did he tell you what this plan is? I wasn't interested. He was to square up with me here tonight
Quarter of a million dollars. That's a lot of money for 1939. He owes me now. Where is he?
Mr steven's been kidnapped by the gorilla kidnapped by
Poppycock look here. I don't know who any of you are, but I do know this walter stevens owes me
$250,000 and i'm going to collect it tonight or else
That's a pretty good wwf promo pointing
I'm one of stevens clark. I'm gonna get out there and i'm gonna fucking bury hulk hogan into the ground for over a year
I gave him until tonight to return my money and until I get it. Yeah, but wait a minute
I think he's mad jack if what that man says is true
I
I don't believe uncle walter could it's almost impossible to know what to believe darling yet things are adding up
If your uncle did have a plan
If this business of sending for you was part of something mean gene
This is going far enough. It's going too far. It's even going further than that. I'll be all right
Just too much excitement for one night get your hat and coat darling
I'm gonna see that you get to town if I have to push the car all the way myself
I can't go till we find uncle walter. We'll take you're not strong enough to do that money boys. I have to crush your ego here
Like it was walnuts
He's a simp
You know, I feel sorry for that poor girl. Yeah, what about poor us strange men zooming in and out animals running around?
Like this was a zoo crazy gongs on I want to go home. I'll say you want to go home
I'm ashamed of you. I'm ashamed of you. Do you want to take a run out part?
We'll leave that girl here to take the blame alone
We detectives aren't we are we?
Haven't we looked all over this house? Yes. No, where haven't we looked? Well, if there's a cello we haven't looked there
I'm glad I thought of that say this looks like a cello. Well
One fucking door we ever looked at the key. Oh, yes never thought of that
All right, come on man
What the fuck is the gorilla? I don't understand the whole why is this movie called the gorilla?
He was just in a cage
But is he gonna sell the gorilla to him for two hundred and fifty thousand dollars?
Is that the plan?
All right. Come on out there you come on. That's some silent hill shit right there. All right. I'm right here chief
Turn on your radio. Are you is it making weird sounds?
Is anybody with me? No, you're alone. Yeah
Takes work to do that
First time I saw a mousetrap catch a piece of cheese
Why they're not scared
We've been double crossed oh it's superman
Yeah
Bending the metal rod
Oh, no, that's a support beam. Don't do that
Why would you show your strength?
That's so funny
Peters. Yes, sir. It's all that commotion
Sounds like our friends the detectives you stay here with miss denby. I'll go see what's up
the real gorilla
No, no, thank you
I'm drinking his poison
Uh, what the hell is he doing if there are plenty ways to do this without making like a scary face
You know like hey, do you want your coat?
Instead of leaning in with your mouth open
I can hear him breathe. That's you. Oh, well open it open it. Here comes a suit of armor joke. Definitely
Have you men been drinking? No, but it's a good idea
I don't know
Oh, there's two gorillas
There's two gorillas without a doubt
A couple you can thank goodness. You caught her
You heard him mulligan. So did you? Well, never mind that you take the hall. I'll go this way
I'll stay here
Is something wrong where were you I just went to get some tea, sir
Didn't I tell you to stay here with miss denby? I'm very sorry, sir, but I thought perhaps a little tea
What right are you got to think we're not even thinking
Miss denby might have been killed. It's uh fortunate. She wasn't sir. This guy's too calm
I don't trust him. Something always happens when you're not here
An unfortunate coincidence, sir
What did you find an empty closet with harry give him it
Harry harry wake up get up wake up
Did you get him? Did you get him? No, he got you. Well, it won't happen again. Okay, man
No, he got you that's pretty good
Get down and see where these stairs lead to
Yes, you oh me voice crack voice crack
What's that funny tapping it's my knees it's a fine time to be scared you try and think of a better time
This is back in the day when you had to do it for real
I'm going in there and we'll look over this house. You'll take orders from me because the show down
I'll show this mug. Who's a mug?
You fellas stick close behind me
Anything happens leave it to me
I'm gonna tear this house apart. I'll show this mug. Who's a mug
You fellas stick close behind me
Anything happens leave it to me
Why is he watching
He's a guy like pointed shit what's eating you he must know something unless you wouldn't be running away like that
Making all of that gaudy
Oh
YouTuber noises
Gonna kill him with an umbrella. That's not gonna work. Now. Here's a random guy that's still in the movie somehow
Where's he been? He's been hiding inside the walls
Nothing to worry about that's what you think. May I give you some advice? No
If I were you i'd go to my room and stay there. Oh, yes, sir. I was just planning on that
Wait a minute. What have you been? No place honest, sir. I was just getting ready to go to town
Why not the gorilla he's in there don't be silly. He's gonna throw him out the window
God, I hope the gorilla throws this guy out the window
Get going. Yes, sir. I'm practically there
I want to see the gorilla do at least one full haymaker punch into somebody's face, right?
Like I mean we have to see it, please
Or suplex. Yeah, anything a wrestling move. I'll take a frying pan like the gorilla hits somebody with a frying pan, please
Or somebody hits the gorilla in the face of the frying pan and it doesn't affect him and it's like oh
That didn't work and they get all panicked
I'll take that
It's a gorilla. We saw it and we felt it and I tell you the gorilla is a man
I ought to know i've read enough about him. But how could a monkey have possibly written those notes?
Tucker walter, maybe it's got an education umbrella joke
Oh, where is he? Have any of you seen him? Oh poe who's poe poe's the gorilla the gorilla
Oh, you know him too, huh? No, I train him since he was that high
You're just the one we're looking for don't any of you understand poe is a gorilla a twain gorilla a real gorilla
Sure a real gorilla
Uh, so we don't know what we're talking about. Eh, yeah, we know a monkey when we see one
Listen, this is serious poe ain't no pet. There's no telling what he's liable to do when I ain't around
He's trained he hates women. Well, what's he doing here? What are you doing here?
We was hired to come here. We're working at the county fair yesterday. A guy comes along
He says he wants me to bring poe here. He says he's given a party wants us to put on a wreck
Who hired you? I don't know. I don't know all I know here
We're waiting out in the garage like he tells me waiting to do our stuff
All of a sudden somebody gives me a clunk over the head and I wake up the lady's boudoir
But the gorilla how did he get loose? You're asking me? That's what I want to find out
Listen, this is serious. We gotta find him. We got us somebody's liable to get killed then notes from the gorilla
I told this too
Notes poe can't write no notes. Even I don't know how to write now
Look the next time I buck up against that gorilla i'm telling you i'll hit i'll dwell
I'll you'll never know he'll do it. Listen, have you seen him? Yes. She's in the kitchen. Which way is the kitchen through the panel?
We'll go with you
You fellas better wait here there's no telling what that able do
Jack
I'm so confused a real gorilla and those notes and
Listen to me everybody the gorilla has done his work
Walter stevens is dead. You will find his body in the garage. Oh jack
All right, everybody follow me to the garage. Come on
Doesn't sound very enthusiastic about it. You'll find his body in the garage
I also for lunch today will be salisbury steak. Stay here and protect miss dandy this way, please
We need the big reveal police with us around lady. You couldn't we couldn't
That's right, we didn't
I gotta find out how that gorilla gets in and out of here
It must be a secret spring around here someplace
I think i'll look in the back of these books
He's gonna get grabbed. He's gonna he's gonna pull the right one
And he's gonna go
Yeah
Imagine getting hit in the head with a fucking brass statue as hard as somebody could do it
Just turned him into a goofball for five seconds
He's dead the walk the germo walk
All right, see this two gorillas here we go flash up the here comes the gorillas
It's a guy with a gorilla arm, it's gonna be a scooby-doo bullshit
Don't tell me she's the gorilla. I told you I didn't like them keys. Look under the mat. That's funny
Oh, very funny
Will you get listen? What are you doing at poe's cage? What do you think i'm doing waiting for someone to feed me peanuts?
Don't you know paul hates women sodas kipling. So what will you please get me out of here?
Hold on. Wait, what?
How about the other poe that hates women say wait a minute, I think this was a trick to get us out of the house
Come on
Whoa, what holy shit
Is he holding this lady
How do you catch a gorilla like that, oh no, he made it in he knows he's the fake gorilla
Break through you can do it
No, the gorilla was the good guy all along. Thank you. Oh, he hid me a gift right here
That's an anti-hero gorilla
You act like that listen here
No, no kisses
He might have killed somebody. What do you mean might have?
And keep them. Okay, scram and take this character with you. Has this lady been awake?
For a third of this movie
Look at that
All right, come on out of there buddy so that's how I got clunked on the head
Come on. Come on out of there. Yo, I got the slap. I was looking for
It's opening. Well, come on. Come on, but
Oh, so it's you. Do you know him? Do I know him? He's the guy I caught using the telephone
There's no law against that. I don't mind. I'll forget him. I'll just a minute. Do you think you're a little premature premature?
Well, I can't remember that far back. Just who are you? I'm detective coletti
An investigator for the securities and exchange commission what i'm on the trail of the gorilla just as you are a detective
How do we know that? Yeah securities fraud. Well
What were you doing in there investigating?
I've been on this case for some weeks now and i've discovered a little about the construction of this house
That my good friend here don't seem to have found out yet
Insider trading this house is a maze of secret panels
Now undoubtedly the voice of the gorilla came through that radio from someplace right in this house
That means that if we find the wire leading away from the radio, we'd at least find the gorilla's hideout
It's gonna be the guy that owns the house securities fraud insider trading his big plan
Just as I thought
Here's the wire now by tracing this I think we may find the answer to this entire riddle
The wire goes in here
Back of this wall is the man we want becomes the third gorilla. It'd be funny. Are you all armed? Yes
Quiet you here it is
What
It is your microphone and as I expected there is your gorilla mr steven's the gorilla
Well, sure I could have told you that all the time. I guess the party is over my gorilla
Why is he tied up? Who tied him up like that? I don't know
He figured the game was up and that this would throw off suspicion. This is a homemade job a child could have done it
Ah, it's preposterous. Don't believe him. I never saw this man before in my life. It's insane
Now what's that?
Uh-oh third gorilla theory incoming
alias the gorilla
You can make that two thousand go walter the gorilla. I don't believe it. I think I can make it very clear
Oh, sure. We can now first of all, what's that? Uh-oh. I didn't hear a thing. Neither did I but what was it?
Hey, what is this who hit me what's going on around here? It's that man again. Oh, there you are
Kidnapped kidnapped by the gorilla not kidnapped by the gorilla. Mr. Conway ap conway. The ap stands for ape
Mr. Conway, this gentleman is the gorilla the gorilla, but if uncle walter's the gorilla
Well, haven't the gorilla been killing people those notes of warning? Oh, the gorilla's been killing people
The beginning of the movie and to throw off suspicion from himself. Mr. Envy
Under the terms of your father's will if anything were to happen to you this dude's a terrorist
Uncle walter my hunch was right. Your uncle brought you here tonight to kill you for your money
Well, at least he had a reason so that's why he wouldn't let us call the police
That's exactly why but what about these men these private detectives? They almost speak for themselves
Do you think if steven's life had actually been threatened he would have called in three morons such as these holy shit
That's what i'm saying
Why resent that but I tell you I saw the gorilla right there in that closet
I saw his hand in his arm and it was no optical confusion. What you saw was this sleeve
Another ingenious little invention of mr. Stevens. It's a very cute little idea
Well
That about clears the whole matter up
And since it stopped raining, I think I better go you're okay buddy. He's all right. Congratulations. Let me congratulate you
Thanks for calling us moron
Wait a minute
I know you don't buddy
Okay, folks say howdy to the gorilla. What all right give out or this moron is gonna blow your brains out
Well, you see it was only that
He just has a really hairy hand
But the cops haven't been able to get me. So don't you halfwits get any crazy notions?
And that's what is for steven's he's just as crooked as I told you he was
The trouble with him is he talks too much and too loud
I got tipped off on what was going to happen here tonight how he was going to pretend to be me
I was going to get the two hundred and fifty thousand dollars and at the same time let him get the blame for all the gorilla murders
Are you better careful? You could have just said I haven't been manscaping lately then you'd be fine nervous tonight
I advise you not to move
Please say some quickly. What is this? I thought the phone was out of order. Maybe he paid his bill. Hello
This is walter steven speaking
Send a squad car to my house
We've got the gorilla things are so mixed up around here that even the gorilla doesn't know who the gorilla is
He's the gorilla. He's the gorilla. Look what's going on here. They're all gorilla
Don't look so sad darling. Your uncle isn't a crook comes the real reveal safe and sound now
You know, you never can tell this is liable to wind up to be a mystery
You see the gorilla murders were threatened to bank up our insurance company
Most of the victims were clans of ours. So conway our special investigator cooked up his little scheme to trap the killer
I'm sorry. I had to frighten you dear and you too kitty. Oh, I wasn't frightened. I was numb
You fellas are certainly great detectives. Oh, yeah, we could have told you that
Did you know that claddy was the gorilla all along? Sure we did. No, we didn't
When did you find out he was the gorilla when I shook hands with him? I don't get you
Well, you see I was a winter trimmer in a department store and I ought to know a phony feel when I feel one
We'll never be able to thank you. Mr. Harrigan. Oh, well, that's all right
I understand you two are getting married soon. Well, if you call tomorrow soon, well, remember if you have any trouble with her
Our specialty is following wives
You know where to send a check and be sure it's certified from a confederate bank
Oh one more thing bye. Oh, that's good. I love them. I love the bye the end
The time meets the space monster well, that's gonna have to be that's gonna have to be for a different time
That was that was very that was I loved it. I loved it. We're gonna take a little intermission break
I'm gonna get another drink
And we're gonna come back with uh this plan from outer space nine. Whatever the hell it is. I'll be right back
Get some i'll get a popcorn refill if you want to
See you in a minute. Let's go down to the movies. Let's go down to the movies
Let's go down to the movies
And grab myself some stuff
Is that what you guys are doing?
Wrong lyrics what a fifty dollars from phylactery lich 5000 bits. Thanks for the 50 bucks
I said the movie was unironically funny to me. What a gem reminds me of the old three stooges
I can't believe the last line of the movie was bye
Uh, we're gonna have to take that as a uh, I think as a tip
We're gonna have to watch more uh fucking ritz brothers movies
That's the first taste of the I think a lot of the ritz brothers movies are in public domain
I can't wait to see them as the tag team in the next room of rumble three-way tag interesting. All right coming up next we have
Uh, this is this is a lot of you've probably already heard of this before
This is plan nine from outer space. This is an old shitty movie. Uh, it's gonna be the middle movie of the night
How many characters confirm for the rumble? That's a great question
Uh, I think that was a perfect movie
It was an hour
Ritz movie thon only ritz movies. Well, here comes plan nine from outer space
Of all the weird movies
I've only seen probably 20 minutes of this movie. I I know it's a total fucking joke
The whole thing sucks. I know
We're just gonna watch it. This movie is in video games. Yeah
This movie has nudity
Where what this says this had moved is this nudity in this movie? No, this is not what all right
I'm gonna hate this movie. This is not a ritz brothers movie. So I mean i'm not gonna like it
Thanks lazy purple for the raid. Welcome everybody. We're about to watch
Uh, we're about to watch plan nine from outer space public domain movie night. Thanks for the fucking raid
Lazy purple welcome and all all the viewers. What do you say we get started?
I'm ready for a countdown plan nine from outer space. Welcome guys
You joined just in time, but you did just miss the gorilla here we go in three two one
A little loud it's a little loud i'll turn it down the mvc movie
Greetings my in the future for that is where you and I asked of our lives future events such as these
Will affect you in the future
You are interested in the unknown
the mysterious
The unexplainable that is why you are here
And now for the first time we are bringing to you
The full story of what happened
On that fateful day. Why does this feel like a bad trump impression based only on the secret testimony?
Of the miserable souls who survived this terrifying ordeal the incidents the places
My friend we cannot keep this a secret any longer feel like I bought this on fiverr punish the guilty
Let us reward the innocent my friend. Can your heart stand?
the shocking fact about
grave robbers from outer space
Jesus christ
I told i'm telling you this is the jump scare. You just had lightning and
loud sounds plan nine from outer space
Copyright it don't matter anymore. It's shit is free director of photography william c. Thompson
All characters and events depicted in this profile is fictitious any similarity to actual persons living or dead is purely coincidental
Why do they do a self-park opening for that?
Of course edwood. Yeah. Yeah worst fucking director ever that there is a time to live and that there is a time to die
There's a time yet that is always a shock and a time to die behind
And your time is good. It is even more of a shock when death the proud brother
Comes suddenly without warning
Just at sundown a small group
Gathered in silent prayer around the newly opened grave of the beloved wife of an elderly man
Sundown of the day he's reading this whole thing in his head. They're waiting for him to start of the old man's heart
Oh, sorry shadows of grief god. I was doing that in my head clouded his very reason. Come on junior start already fuck
I should have done a funeral over the saddened group left the graveside who died
This is a fucked up gravesite, by the way
It did they don't even
It was when the gravediggers I feel like they're about to break into song things began to take this is a musical
Are they gonna like start tap dancing?
15 to 4 out there now you better radio in if a landing instructions daddy
right jeff
american flight 812
over
Surprised me any if he's asleep this time of the morning bank tower
Why is he wearing a seatbelt the other guy's not you got me that time mac this american flight 812 requesting
So the shower curtain behind them
It would be fucking hilarious if they pulled that back and a guy was taking a shower right there. Oh damn it. Take a look for yourself
That's nothing from this world
What are those steering wheels mayday mayday stand by burbank tower you suppose the passenger side
I doubt that most of them are asleep, but it was quite a joke jeff. I'll check good
We'll get a ready for landing and keep it quiet until we get instructions right. Okay, danny american flight 812 reporting to burbank tower over
That's the plane
Jesus christ, did you hear anything? I thought it did don't like hearing noises, especially when he's supposed to be any
Yeah, sort of spooky like maybe we're getting old whatever it is gone now. That's the best thing for us
Like i'm watching a bad lip reading video. Am I sure that's not what this is that I clicked the right thing
Oh look at those hands his wife's death became greater and greater agony
The home they had so long shared together
Became a tomb this is sad a sweet memory of her joyous living
The sky to which she had once looked
Was now only a covering for her dead body
jesus
This narrator is fucked
Beautiful flowers she had planted
with her own hands
Became nothing more than the lost roses of her cheeks
Confused by his great loss the old man left that home
Never to return again. What wait?
Did he sell it?
Did he move his furniture out
at the funeral of the old man
Unknown to his mourners. He's dead his dead wife
Was watching first his wife then he tragic
Why is that door only like five feet tall? Why was his wife buried in the ground?
Something to do with family tradition a superstition of some sort. Oh, well, it's getting dark. Let's be in our way
Then as two of his mourners left his final resting place
Two dummies
Wait, why couldn't they just lie on the ground?
What's the I don't understand
The actors couldn't lie on the ground for a second. Why?
Somebody had to make that shit
It took probably three or four days to make them. They were too old to lie on the ground
No, one of them was like 40. I don't buy that for a second later
The police led by inspector daniel clay arrived at the scene who found them the man and girl medical
Exterminer, where's the gorilla just left the morgue wagon ought to be along most any time you get their statement
Yeah, as much as we could they're pretty scared finding a mess like this ought to make anyone frightened
Have one of the boys take the guy and the girl back to town. You take it. Okay inspector
What are you going to do knock it around?
Pretty dark out there. What once you get beyond the range of those lights
You won't be able to see your hand in front of your face. This is an snl skit. That's dan ackroy in the middle
Be careful, but i'm a big boy now johnny. He'll smoke
You guys think that's fog. No, no, no, this is what the 30s looked like
Every motherfucker smoked
50s. Yeah, whatever
This was every bar and restaurant in fucking 1955
Say lieutenant to get that funny odor. How could I miss it? Oh, that'll be the morgue wagon now
I thought they were dummies. I thought they were fucking mannequins. I was about to say why
A lot of police cars and lights I stopped but I didn't see anything
Oh, well, whatever it is. It's a mosquito
The fence you seem to still be up there somewhere. Yeah, that's pretty fucked up
Maybe I am why is this so bent? I don't think i've ever seen you in this mood before
They're at a cardboard. This is because i've never been in this mood before something about your flight
Even his clothes look fake like his shirt looks like it's made out of fucking cardboard
I saw a flying saucer
Saucer you mean the kind from up there?
Yeah, it's kind of part
It was shaped like a huge cigar dan either saw it too
When it passed over the whole compartment lighted up with a blinding glare you mean the sky
Yeah, tremendous wind it practically knocked us off our course. Did you report it? Yeah
Radioed in immediately and they said we'll keep it quiet until you land
As soon as we landed big army brass grabbed us and made us swear to secrecy about the whole thing
Burns me up. These things have been seen for years. They're here. It's a fact
And the public ought to know about it. There must be something more you can do about it
Only there isn't all but what's the use of making a fuss?
But last night I saw a flying object. They couldn't have possibly been from this planet
Honey, you should make a bunch of facebook posts about it muzzle by army brass. I can't even admit I saw the thing
Fuck
Rumor she's here. Is anybody gonna say anything say something?
We talk. Okay. I can't just be me. Oh, you know, he's a villain money. Oh, it's his arm. I'm about to get his nose
With a big cape. It's the butler again. Oh god
What where is where all the what where's the officers? Where is everybody?
Shoot him shoot him with your gun sounds like pay in trouble
Oh
Paula and russell, oh no, he's dead
Somebody said na aim
God. Ah, it looks like he wanted me invited to tsm. Is he dead? Yeah
He's messed up as bad as those two back there
Suppose that saucer or whatever it was had something to do with this their guess is good as mine, larry
Don't itch your neck with a gun. Oh my god, what are you doing?
He's gonna kill himself
You're in charge now lieutenant, yeah
This is like freaking me the fuck out his finger on the trigger. He's itching his neck with the barrel of the gun
Tell the coroner he's got to make another trip out here. Well, how about the lab boys?
Who do you think we left back up the car boy scouts? Come on. Oh, no another funeral
It's just this fucking same day than to lay down his life
For another it is always difficult to have last words over the grave of a friend
An inspector daniel clay was a friend a dear friend to me
And to all of us by the way, who's the scary lady in makeup and in costume?
Now we lay him to rest a rest well deserved
So premature
At the funeral there's more than one flying saucer
People turning south from the freeway were startled when they saw three flying saucers
saucers seen over hollywood
Whoa
It's not a rainbow in the sky telephones. Oh look, there's a rainbow forming over there kind of cool. I guess
Why was that so hard like his shit face there comes a time in each man's life
But he can't even believe his own eyes
Okay, saucers seen over hollywood flying saucers seen over washington dc
At the military convoy moved into the field
missile launchers
Already quickly set up colonel tom edwards in charge of saucer field activities
Was to make the greatest decision of his career
He made that decision
Colonel edwards gave the signal to fire
There
All of them missed
Not one rocket hit its location target
In the chat you can see
Nice air shot noob
Molding he must be pretending
Is the entire united states military pretending?
These were the things that the local citizens were saying
They were gone even to the piercing eye of radar and the speeding jet fighters
They weren't even moving they were standing still even I could do that
Quite a sight wasn't it sir a sight i'd rather not be seeing are you worried about them, sir?
No, i'm worried about your comedy radio
Visits that would indicate visitors the big guns a usual way of welcoming visitors. We haven't always fired at them
Oh for a time we tried to contact them by radio, but no response then they attacked a town
When where a small town i'll admit but nevertheless a town of people it's a made-up government conspiracy
All right, I need to rewind
I i'm rewinding what the fuck did he say a sight i'd rather not be seeing are you worried about them, sir?
Well, they must have a reason for their visits visits. That would indicate visitors. They killed people they died
I made this up right now to justify firing 10 000
Mistrels at them that were 500 million dollars for a time
We tried to contact them by radio, but no response then they attacked a town a small town
I'll admit but nevertheless a town of people people who died. I never heard about that, sir
Well, it was covered up by the higher echelon take any fire
And that's all I need to say to get another 500 billion dollars in revenue then wonder flying
Actual life are still a rumor officially. I'd like to beat them off again, sir
What do they want? Where are they from? Where are they going? They sir?
Who? Well, this is a training maneuver, sir. We only did a little practice firing at the clouds. What?
Yeah, I wonder what their next move will be so they would deliberately not hitting them
Are you sure you can't use some of the tax dollars to rebuild a few schools?
Really guys, what will their next move be?
Your space commander has returned from earth send him in wait. They're just people
It's a it's a race of bob. Hope we had to pull in here to space station seven for regeneration
We're returning to the planet earth immediately thereafter. What progress has been made we contacted government officials. They refuse our existence
What plan will you follow now plan nine?
It's been absolutely impossible to work through these earth creatures. Their soul is too controlled plan nine
Ah, yes plan nine deals with the resurrection of the dead
Long distance electrode shortens opinion pituitary grounds of recent dead. Have you attempted any of this plan as yet?
Yes, excellency how successful I want one of these costumes. We have risen too so far
We shall be just as successful on more the living they have no suspicion of your movements
We had to dispose of one policeman
However, none of those risen have been seen at least not by anyone who still remains alive
It's too bad. It must be handled this way, but it must those who we take from the grave
We can't wait for that curtain to open it is mario free continue on report to me in two earth days
I feared his excellency wouldn't take our report this well
Well had he been dealing with her own people his reaction would have been completely different
He understands the difficulties of the earth race
What do you think will be the next obstacle the earth people will put in our way?
He looks what's he gonna draw?
Just gonna draw on them as long as they can think we'll have our problems
But those whom we're using cannot think they are the dead brought to a simulated life by our electrode guns
No
You know
It's an interesting thing when you consider the earth people who can think are so frightened by those who cannot the dead
They didn't even think they like put them in makeup or something. Our ship should be regenerated. We better get started
They just have different clothes on oh they aliens. They're just like we're just people with clothes on
These earthlings which we all of us are in this room the producers didn't think to even dye our hair green
Where's the tie fighter sound? Hello, honey. I'm back from the set wall where there's nothing behind us
I still think you're going nothing's going to take me from it besides most men try and keep their wives from going home
It's not the point. That's all the point. There's going to be
Why is he leaving for work at night?
I don't people work nights, man
What are you talking about?
It's a weird kiss that was like a he fucked that up. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. I got hold on
Will you tell him to pick another house to watch this kiss that was he fucking missed that so much
Don't worry about me. He like opened his bottom lip and she right now she's thinking fuck. That was so wet and gross
They're up there, but there's something in that cemetery. I can't wait to fucking wipe my arm on my mouth when he says cut
The saucers are up there and the cemeteries out there, but i'll be locked up in there
Now what the fuck are they doing?
What are you doing? You promise you like the first time they've ever kissed a human
He said these are the aliens. These are the aliens down here with your pillow. I figured it out. I know the whole movie
I have to have something to keep me company while you're away
Sometimes in the night when it does get a little lonely
I reach over and touch it
Then it doesn't seem so lonely anymore. Wait, do you reach over and touch his what?
crazy kid
What who are you touching? What's going on? I do love you darling
These humans don't
These are not humans
That hurt that hurt both of them. They both are in pain right now physical pain. See you thursday. Goodbye, honey
You could see three distinct rolls on the side of his face that hurt them
You know, i'm not leaving here until you lock. What's the pressure?
If you're especially nice, I'm hey, make sure you smoke in the house. You keep the yard lights on smoke everywhere
Don't worry the yellow stains on the fucking ceiling and the walls 30 years from now won't drop the property value of our home
Why wouldn't I guess i'm preoccupied Danny?
We've got 33 passengers back there that have time to be preoccupied flying this flyer bird doesn't give you that opportunity
Is that a clock in the top left or a plate? I don't know. That's a weird clock
It's a clock. There's nothing wrong between you two. Oh, no, nothing like that
Just that i'm worried she being there alone and those strange things flying over the house and
Those incidents in the graveyard these past few days just just got me worried
Well, maybe they haven't figured out those crazy skybird yet
But I give you a 50 to one odds the police have cleared out that cemetery thing by now. I hope so
If you're really that worried Jeff, why don't you go radio in and find out really wish you would let me on your fucking animal crossing
Island, uh some my turnips jake
Hi, kind of fucking annoying that you haven't invited me yet
From this end of the plane since we left the field i've just been giving himself and me a study in silence
Your boys aren't feuding. I don't want to bring it up. I will
Hey, how about you and me balling it up in albuquerque?
Have you read that flight schedule boy? What about it? Well, that was relevant albuquerque at 4 a.m
That's strictly a nine o'clock town. Well, I know a friend that'll help us. Let's have a problem first
Ah, he's worried about paula. I read about that shit. All right
Let's take the loss two kids not to buy too near one of those things
We get there soon enough as it is
He thought it'd be quiet and peaceful there. No doubt about that. It's quite all right like a tomb
I'm, sorry jeff. That was a bad joke
Say I almost forgot when I came in me too. I know what it's like coffee situation. That's for me. It sure would hurt
Okay, be right back and say jeff make that call to me
Nah, not only she throw cold water on my albuquerque clan, but now she's repeating herself and someone put their fucking hands on the wheel
I can't resist your child anybody
Residents near the cemetery paid little attention to the blast of thunder the flash of lightning
But from the blast arose the moving figure of the dead old man
This looks like a deep fake
It's like a richard nixon deep fake
How embarrassing if we put richard nixon's face on here the hospital bed is that a bed
Why is a fire alarm your ringtone?
Okay, mac
Look at that picture up there
That's not
Look, that's not even the two people that live in this house. These are two random fucking people
We're led to believe that's her and him. Nope. That's two random people
I don't know who the fuck they are
there's
Wait, what? Huh? Am I going fucking crazy?
Hi, mac. Am I going insane? Sure. I'm all right. That's not even the that's a superimposed photo
Is it that's not even the picture that's there?
What the fuck?
deep fake
Okay, I I could take this guy I could take that i'll pick up a lamp and hit him in the fucking head
You know what I mean? Like if you're just like putting your hand on your mouth and like going like this
No, no, no, give me the phone. I'll fucking bash you in the head with that phone
And apparently they live right next to a graveyard
They live on the graveyard
Holy shit, we're talking property value cigarette smoke graveyard. This house was 40 dollars
They got this house at auction. Why was it? Yeah, what?
Wasn't it just nighttime?
daytime
All right. This lady is doing the I have a dump in my pants walk
Like this is the walk you do when you shit your pants
You freeze and you fucking just slowly just move your hands up and down and move shimmy
Did it go through the underwear into my pants? I hope it's just the underwear because I can take those off
I can take the underwear off and put the pants back on but fuck. Hopefully it didn't go through
This dark vader
There's a vader up there
The egg
Kind of does look like the egg, huh?
Why are you running through the graveyard?
Get to her road
Finally, thank you
Um when he knows who this is
He's talking about the egg
That's the egg right there. That's like the tucked in fan of the pants pulled up like steve urkel with tucked in
That's the egg
Okay, run him over
Just drive over that guy's head
Run over his head
I bet you probably get cursed forever or something, right?
Yeah, it's not a good idea
Why am I getting like the holy shit psycho face? This is dracula run his fucking head over
What and that makes me a psycho?
Run over that guy's head. He's a he's a dracula psycho killer guy
What i'm trying to get rid of him. No, i'll go ask him for directions guys. That's a good idea
We're gonna get another funeral
That's a home video camera
pointing at him
He's testing out his cosplay for the next convention
That was not meant to be released to the public at all
His iCloud got hacked. It's like that's unfortunate. He'll be at the hatch in a moment. You can open it now, tana
So we're back in the ufo
Where does that letter go
You're late for dinner you three
They can't tell us from anyone else. Oh brussels sprouts again mom
Sit down and eat. It's tough to find something when you don't know what you're looking for
I don't think the lieutenant does either then what are we doing out here? I was off duty an hour ago
Oh, don't ask me any questions. I'm just a hard hand just like you
Cole phelps what do you suppose that noise was whatever it was. It's no more strange any other things happening around this cemetery
Spirits like old farmer caller talked about what maybe the only spirits he saw tonight were those I smelled on his breath
Oh, don't forget. Mr. Trent claims to have seen them too. She didn't have anything on her breath. God damn it was hysterical
True she was frightened and then to stay the shock, but don't forget that thorn knight gone in the scratch feet
Yeah, I
Hadn't thought of that guess that's why you're a detective lieutenant and i'm still a uniformed cop
Sometimes it's only the brakes larry. See we don't give a shit like how far can you fit this gun down your mouth?
Let me check let me do it too. It was strange. We don't give a fuck no more than you do
Went for orders I get out of here makes you say that you remember the noise we heard the other night
We were not to the ground how could I forget exactly but you're not remembering that sound there you're wrong lieutenant
I'm with the fact the sound is similar, but what about the blinding light?
Well, haven't you heard and many times the saucer hasn't had a goal or a light of any kind for that matter
That proves it what next lieutenant. Oh lieutenant. I wanted to take that hat off
And fucking wicked long beautiful hair just blows down
Uh, why come on man out with it. We haven't got all data waste. Oh, uh, just uh over there beyond the crib
All right, show us away
Look here. Here it is lieutenant. Yeah, it's been broken into all right strange
If someone had broken in the dirt should be piled up here
How long do we have the lease on this warehouse for the graveyard?
Might as well use the fuck out of it for every single scene in the movie
This spot look we shouldn't investigate any further without the permission of the next akin. Let's go get it
How I see what you mean the gravestones down there well, let's go down and find out whose grave it is really
I'm doing that stance quit doing that stand. You're copying me now. Are you sure you mean that lieutenant?
If I didn't mean it, I wouldn't have said it scared. Well, why do I get hooked up with these spooked details?
monsters graves bodies
All right, it's the ritz brothers with an added brother caskets here, but nobody's in it
Can you read the name on the casket? It's too dark
Give me a flashlight. How about a match? We sure could buy a cigarette. Let me have them. Okay
Here have a cigarette. These were like eating apples in the 40s. Inspector clay's grave, but he ain't in it
But meanwhile at the pentagon in washington dc these guys are still flying this plane
Are they ever gonna land?
Right g2 come in. Yes, of course keep in touch. Come in colonel avers
Yes
One star general why is that so why is that I don't know why that's funny what he
Understand colonel. You've been tapped for many of our saucer attacks. Why is that funny?
I don't charge a field operation, sir. Well the mic there are such things as flying sauces colonel
Where's the mic there's a mic in the frame in washington dc
I didn't even see it right g2 where
Come in yes, of course keep in touch
Come in colonel avers close the door at ease colonel. Thank you, sir. Sit down
I'm just waiting for like a guy in glasses with like a notepad to walk in and just be like oops and see the camera
And walk back like a script supervisor
I'm in charge of field operation, sir
You believe there are such things as flying sauces colonel, yes, sir uncrowned
Yes, sir
You realize there's a government directive stating that there is no such thing as a flying saucer
Yes, sir. You stand by your statement that you've seen flying saucers. Well, uh, yes, sir
This could mean a court martial admitting this against direct orders general roberts. May I speak freely you may
No, how could I hope to hold down my command if I didn't believe in what I saw and said no
Why are you talking?
I
Like you colonel here. Would you like an apple? There are flying saucers. There's no doubt. They are in our skies
I've been there for some time. What are we going to do about them? Who knows then?
They really are there by the two phones. I thought you were convinced of that. I am we've had contact. Why are there two phones?
contact
Radio they speak our language. Well, one's a cell phone
We received messages from their spaceships for a while
It came in as just a lot of jumbled noise
I don't want my wife to know who i'm calling on my second line tried contact with us by radio
We've developed a language computer a machine that breaks down any language. See I sell drugs too
You've seen that movie that tv show with brian cranson
You've been in charge of saucer field activity for a long while
I think it's about time you heard these recordings you mind mind
I'm anxious. He's a two-star general. So he has two phones. God damn it
From a planet of your galaxy. I fully realize or as you want the language so you can now understand since the beginning of your time
We have been far beyond your planet
It has taken you centuries to even grasp what we developed eons of your years ago. We're flex, dude
Do you still believe it impossible we exist you didn't actually think you were the only inhabited planet in the universe
How can any race be so stupid permit me to set your mind at ease?
How can anybody be so stupid your planet only save it
We could have destroyed it long ago if that had been our aim our principal purpose is friendly
I admit we have had to take certain means which you might refer to as criminal
But that is the cause of your big guns which have destroyed some of our representative
If you persist in denying us our landlands, then we must only accept that you do not want us on friendly terms
We then have no alternative but to destroy you
Before you destroy us with your ancient juvenile minds
You have developed explosives too fast for your mind to perceive what you were doing
This really is la noir the verge of destroying the entire we are a part of that
This is our last that's the end of that one atmospheric conditions in outer space often interfere with transmitting
How many of these recordings do you have general and even dozen up to now?
This was the last one we received it over a month ago. Do you think they mean business?
We can't afford to take any chances come over here. Thank you language computer
You ever been to hollywood? Oh a couple of times a few years ago
You're going to be there in the morning
Just a few minutes from hollywood in the town of san fernando
Reports have come in of saucers flying so low the exhaust knocked people to the ground
There have even been stated claims of saucer landings. What is that on the left?
Is that an x-ray of his abdomen while you're out there by the way?
What do you think about these man for the job of attempting to contact them find them colonel?
See what in hell it is. They want all right, sir. I'd be concerned
These are confidential reports colonel read them over carefully on the plane
Turn them over to intelligence when you get to los angeles. They'll have further orders for disposition. Yes, sir. Here's my laptop
Yes, sir. Good luck. Thank you, sir
Here's my luck god damn it
Aliens stands up straight and they do weird things. We stand up straight. That's how you know
We're fucking aliens because we have good posture. We are ready your excellency. You are many days late
It was unavoidable. We tried to transmit via televisor, but atmospheric conditions made transmission impossible
You should have transmitted as soon as conditions permitted. I thought time was of the essence
Suspicion has fallen upon our movements our ships have been viewed near the point of operations
And what has this added time gained euros? What does even axe we have successfully risen three of the dead ones
Why is that his family crest they have axes in space bring in the big one
Use your small electrode gun. I have taken two ships from your command that will leave only my ship
It is necessary that you continue your mission alone. I have need of your other ships elsewhere
Even though you have risen three of the earth dead the plan is far from successful
And you euros must prove it an operational success before more time energy ships and your countrymen may be spent on it
No, no aliens have died. Everything is on our side
Not everything you do not have the live earth people
line
You reported that your ship was viewed at the scene of your present operations. That is correct
They have been viewed many times but not at the scene of operations something must be done about that. I want this guy to talk
Stop him turner. He's close enough turn off your electrode gun. No
No
That's a nintendo light gun
That was too close
Yes
Bring the giant here that I may get a better look at him. What is he doing to him?
He's giving him acupuncture. I don't understand what this is supposed to do. Yes. She's a fine specimen
Are they all this powerful on planet earth? This one is an exception excellency
What are the other two like one is a woman the other an old man
This gives me a plan put the big one away pick up your electrode gun
Make sure it's in working order before pointing it at him
And make sure the two tracking devices can see you in vr god damn it
How do you not know this by now mary the old one must be sacrificed?
We land on earth send the old one do what we do
Tape two to your legs then cut the electrokinetic and turn on your ship's decomposure ray
The result will astound those watching astound them enough to delay their intention until you have
Gained your other recruits from the cemetery. Yes, excellency. It'll be done report to me when this has been accomplished
Hear us the earth people are getting closer to that which we fear since they will not listen or respect our existence
They cannot help but believe our powers when they see their own dead walking around again
Brought about by our advancement and such things as soon as you have enough for the dead recruits
March them on the capitals of the earth. Let nothing stand in your way
I thought they were blurring his crest out to make them accept our existence like they didn't want to get sued by mcdonald's or something
He's just reading
Cemetery again
I have four sets in this whole movie
Cemetery backyard. This is colonel edwards from washington dc spaceship god damn
Colonel would like to ask a few questions questions. What about colonel? May I uh sit down? Oh, i'm sorry
Please do I want to ask you about your strange experience the other night when you saw the flying saucer. That's uncomfortable
After that the police brought me home
I hope I never see such a sight again. Well after your description
I don't think i'd want to see it either one thing more after you were forced to the ground
But that blast of wind was it a hot or cold Coca-Cola coke Coca-Cola
It's kind of hard to explain wasn't hot wasn't cold. It's just a terrific force. We we couldn't get off the ground
The light blinded me so badly
I couldn't see a thing
We could only feel the pressure of the wind until it was gone
When the glare left us we could see a glowing ball disappearing off in the distance which way toward the cemetery
Oh here they come
Have we seen this guy's face one time? Oh, yeah. Yeah, right right. Yeah here we have
This is the most fantastic story i've ever heard and every word of it's true, too
That's the fantastic part of it colonel
We found a lot of suspicious things out in that cemetery then again
They got mileage out of that one
Lieutenant turn the car off
Does he get zapped? Please zap him please
Why do they always when the car and close the door roll the windows up he can't get in
This guy has no fucking powers
He's just a little odd
Why are you standing still run maybe run the fuck away
This guy has the same emotion the whole scene
What do you make of that? She caught me didn't look that way a minute ago. What about your man?
Oh, did you say when I forgot all about kelton? Uh, he'll be all right in a few minutes. How do you know?
Did you see that thing? Did you get it? We got it. What was it?
It didn't fall. I fired every bullet I had so no you got him
You got him
Five-year-old
Back to the cemetery, yeah
I thought he was gonna go to smoke his cigarette
Like oh let me take a drag it's my turn
Yes, sir stay with mrs. Trent. All right lieutenant. I used to close to the officer, honey
I'd feel safer with you. Oh, yeah, there's there's still two enemies remaining
You have a gun. You know how to use one to four years in the marine corps
What just say yeah, what tell let's get going where's his did he just give him his gun
Yeah, I want you to be responsible for shooting the lady. Not me. I was here but I didn't do it
What you take it you fire would expect to find out here. Yeah, there's only one answer. Trent
We'll know when we find inspector clay is great right over here. Is that the one yeah guns?
Don't do anything. Why are they still firing?
Just pick up a fucking tombstone and hit her in the face
This is to me like someone that's broken off instead of in i'm surviving during the zombie apocalypse guys
Some things just can't happen. Yeah. Well after that apparition that was draped across mr
Trent's patio, I would say we should keep our minds open to anything. Look colonel. I'm a policeman
I've got the deal in facts. I guess i'll have to go along with you
You know, i'll pet my badge right now. We haven't seen the last of those weirdies
They'll discover our ship soon. You're going to let them find us. It's the only way
These are the same men who have been so close so often
They must be halted before they can inform others about us, but there were others in the car
This is a painted garage. That's a garage the big one for the girl and the policeman
I'll turn on the digital robotaries and burst them. Yep. That's the door going into your house from your garage
Look at the floor. The whole movie is a garage
Oh shit, you're right. No, it's a real spaceship
One thing a policeman learns. Mr. Trent is patience. Where's that burn spot you mentioned right over there. I'm gonna piss my pants
Oh, we got a long way to go. We'll investigate but move carefully. All right, i'm gonna i'm gonna pee
I'm gonna i'm gonna piss my pants. I'll be right back interlude. We got 20 minutes left of the movie interlude
Go to the lobby. Well, get back in here. Hurry up. Get in here the projectionist the project the
Projectionist it's a hard word to say back to the movie. I scared you. I'm sorry. That's a heart. No, no
No, that's that has nothing to do with the amount of drinks. I've had that's a hard word to say
Projectionist projectionist. It's difficult. No, I've had two drinks. Relax. Here we go. I got behind you turn around
Why she's sleeping in the car?
The equivalent of wiping his cheeto hands on his sleeves that doesn't do very much damage
And you will be the first live earth people the car was
a celestial ship
That's a fucking hand dryer from the bathroom
What do you see only my reflection must be some kind of one-way glass
I wonder how you get into this thing. I'm not sure I want to find out
Humans have made it on board the garage
They've stepped over the water heater and avoided the cardboard boxes from the move we did three years ago
You can open the outer they've just crossed the power washer. We've never used though. We bought truly truly saying we were going to use it
These things speed around we might just get in then off it goes. That's a chance we take
Well, I took a chance on those earlier airplanes might just as well see what the inside one of these looks like
Got your guns ready. I'll tell you one thing a little green man pops out of me
I'm shooting first and asking questions. Oh, don't worry because they're humans
You'll be shooting other humans
Can you sleep at night after that one jack do we have to kill them? Yes
It seems such a waste
Well, wouldn't it be better to kill a few now than with their meddling permit them to destroy the entire universe
We're always right arrows. Of course
But those are not my words
Those are the words of the ruler
Who is that?
You're not so different you and I
Really the only difference is you got your outfit from party city
And I wear a suit to work. No for the moment. Who's the real weirdo do as I tell you
You do not need guns. Maybe we think we do
They would be of no use to you now. They've been mighty useful before on flesh and blood
And you two look like you've got a lot of both
True, they would be effective upon us through
That's true the opportunity to use them mister if you don't get away from that control board i'll show you just how effective
Shall we talk now? All right
Your friends will be here shortly
Those you left at the vehicle if you've done anything to paul. Take it easy. Mr. Trent. Oh, I assure you no harm has come to her
Would you like to see?
Next time you try that I won't aim at the board. You're a headstrong young man
I was a cure for every illness in america see her movements. What are you stupid? Go ahead my friend
But move very carefully only in america apparently
She's only fainted you fiend
I a fiend. Um, hold on a second. What's going on with his grip on this gun?
He's this this grip on this gun is like trying to get into the claw of a lobster at red lobster
Like dude, what is this grip?
She's only fainted
His hands going I
a fiend
I feel like that's his hands were made in dreams. I fiend we did not come here as enemies
We came only with friendly intentions to talk to ask your aid our aid
Yes, your aid for the whole universe, but your governments of earth refused even to accept our existence
Even though you've seen us heard our messages you still refuse to accept us
Why is it so important that you want to contact the governments of our earth because of death because all you of earth are idiots
Do you just hold on buster? No, you hold on first was your firecracker a harmless explosive then your hand grenade
They began to kill your own people a few at a time then the bomb then a larger bomb
Many people are killed at one time then your scientist stumbled upon the atom bomb split the atom a larger bomb
Then the hydrogen bomb
Where you actually explode the air itself now brings the total destruction of the entire universe
Served by our sun the only explosion left is the solar night why there's no such thing perhaps to you
But we've known it for centuries your scientists will stumble upon it as they have all the others
But the juvenile lines which you possess will not comprehend its strength until it's too late
You're way above our heads the solar night is a way to explode the actual particles of sunlight why that's impossible
Even now your scientists are working on a way to harness the sun's rays
The rays of sunlight are minute particles
Is it so far from your imagination?
They cannot do as I have suggested why a particle of sunlight can't even be seen or measured
Can you see or measure an atom? Yes, you can explode one a ray of sunlight is made up of many atoms
So, what if we do develop this solar night bomb we'd be even a stronger nation than now stronger you see you see
Your stupid minds stupid stupid. That's all i'm taking from you. Get back here you jack
Let him finish he turns green. He's an alien. He was just projecting different skin
It's because of men like you that all must be destroyed headstrong violent
No use of the mind god gave you you talk of god his red blood
You also think it impossible that we too might think of god you guys celebrate easter you
I do wear the uniform of your country. You see I wear the uniform of my country. Yes
We've had to use drastic eggs and the bunny and shit, but you left us no alternative
When you have the solar night you have nothing nor does the universe you speak of solar range country
What is it take a can of your gasoline say?
This can of gasoline is the sun now you spread a thin line of it to a ball representing the earth
Now the gasoline represents the sunlight the sun particles here
We saturate the ball with the gasoline the sunlight then we put a flame to the ball
The flame will speedily travel around the earth back along the line of gasoline to the can
Or the sun itself just like that gta 5 it will explode this source you play that trevor mission spread to every place that gasoline
Like that sunlight touches explode the sunlight here gentlemen you explode the universe
Explode the sunlight here and a chain reaction will occur
Direct to the sun itself true and to all the planets that sunlight touches to every planet in the universe
This is why you must be stopped
This is why any means must be used to stop you in a friendly manner or as it seems
You want this is a v-sauce video
Mad is it mad that you destroy other people to save yourselves you have done this
Is it mad that one country must destroy another to save themselves?
You have also done this how then is it mad that one planet must destroy another who threatens the very
She's just saying the same shit you were what in my land women are for advancing the race
Not for fighting man's battle. Well in our land gas is worthless right now
So your analogy doesn't make any fucking sense clued is worth like negative 30 dollars bro
Is for the development of our planet back to the graveyard. We always end up here
What happened to you? How come you're all alone?
I asked for lots of help you sounded drunk or something on the radio. I didn't see with my own eyes
I'd never believe it believe what it was horrible and he almost broke my shoulder
Look, what are you trying to say? If you don't make sense, we'll never get to the bottom of this now. Who slugged you?
Inspector clay what it was clay. All right, only not like we remembered him
Well, his leg was busted into I can't even text you tell me you saw skeletons. We did earlier
Now I know you're off your rocker. All of us saw it lieutenant the colonel everybody. Where's lieutenant now?
We've got to find him. Mr. Trenor's gone. I was left here to guard her
But they showed up and put me out of the running and the second time tonight and i'm getting darn tired of it
Which way were they going off that way? Come on. I don't know. I'm a police officer in every movie
I don't know anything then one day it could all be gone one big puff of smoke and ball of fire
All that out there the stars
the planets
All of just an empty void
You two had better come along with us come with you. We're gonna arrest an alien police station
Ha ha ha ha ha
So it seems you think you have the upper hand look out that window jeb jeb
Hey jeb come over here jeb
She is unarmed, but he would kill in seconds if I so choose
I feel like we've crossed this path before yes, we have holy cow. It's the only path in the movie
Same. Oh my god. I can't I can't even watch this anymore
Look there. It's clay. All right. There's no mistaking that
And he's got mrs. Trent
Get your gun ready from all i've seen tonight guns won't do any good clay is dead and we buried him
How are we going to kill somebody that's already dead dead and yet there he stands. Well, no, that doesn't make any sense
He hasn't laughed yet and ruined every skit. He's been in that's the only reason i'm listening to you
Look, i've got an idea heard him or not. We've got to try something
I'm gonna sneak up behind him and walk him over the head that ought to make a move follow me
Even when clay was alive, he couldn't run. He's over there somewhere
Run like lightning in the opposite direction
You think it'll work over anything else to try? Oh my god. This is gonna be so funny
He's gonna have the fucking head
I'll be all right
Why just gently tapping somebody's what your man told the big one was he dubbing her voice
Of anything else to try he was just dubbing her voice idea heard him or not
We've got to try something i'm gonna sneak up behind him and walk him over the head that ought to make a move
Follow me even when clay was alive. He couldn't run fast enough to catch me
It took him an hour and 13 minutes run like lightning hit somebody with a stick. You think it'll work of anything else to try
Oh, i'll be all right, take care of the others that's him doing her voice he's practicing
This could only happen because the electrode ray is off. He'll walk again when I turn it on all that right there
Suppose the lieutenant and the others are in that thing. Well, they're supposedly they're margins or something in there
Let's go
You're under arrest. We're gonna put you
Not really punching
Here's the gun
I'll have a ship in the air in a minute
What is he doing over there he doesn't know what that is jack stop doing that you're dropping the air pressure in the room
Get out of here jeff the ship's on fire
Look at the day
This is like we're talking about garages that's the electrical meter
That's like they just dog it up a little bit. That's the thing the guy comes to your house to see how much electricity you use
They added a couple of
dials to it
Get out of here man. The ship's on fire. Get out of the garage the garage is on fire
Yeah
For some reason we decided to turn our grill on in the garage
We're fucking idiots
You're supposed to use these things outside, man
Tapiano
They're supposed to use charcoal inside
Was it worth it? Was it worth it? I wonder if that's the last we'll see of that. I don't give a shit about your beyond burgers, mike
Yeah, gross
God damn it. You should have been safe. Oh, he's dead
That thing yet?
That's right. There's another ghoul running loose and it's my guess that you'll look like him with the ship and the ray gun gone
They have no control
We gotta hand it to them though. They
They're far ahead of us
Just open up
Can you prove that it didn't happen
Perhaps on your way home
Someone will pass you in the dark and you will never know it for they will be from outer space
Many scientists believe that another world is watching us this moment. We once laughed at the horseless carriage
the airplane
the telephone the electric light
vitamins radio
vitamins radios fiber truck now some of us laugh at outer space in the future
garage in hollywood, usa
It was that was fucking ridiculous
What a stupid movie
Those were two back to back those were those were great
Very much worth watching on stream
I wonder if the next one will hold up the next one could be
Not even close. I don't know
It's worth a shot though. Ah coming up next we have to close this out. This is the longest one
This is santa claus conquers the martians
Uh, this is the longest one. So this is an hour and 20 minutes
and
I don't uh
Another alien themed one. This is gonna be so fucking bad
This one sucks, dude
uh
Well, we're gonna watch it. It's very boring. Uh
How could you have a boring movie if you're santa claus conquering martians? Let's see what happens
I'm willing to give it a try. It's not what you think. It's terrible. It's terrible
veto
Veto i'm veto
What the fuck? Holy shit
This is unbelievable. This is like the most i've ever seen chat agree
Oh my god
Okay
So this is this is bad. Are you sure? Are you sure?
Uh, uh, come along. Mr. Anderson and i'll show you some of the new toys we're turning out. Are you sure?
Okay. Well, uh, are you guys sure? Are you sure about this? Give it a chance?
Give us a chance
Watch the first. All right. Let's we're gonna watch the first 10 minutes
If this don't work out then we're gonna move on to another one
and the other one is
Attack of the giant leeches
Attack of the giant leeches is the one that's up next
That sounds better
But what about the santa claus one
Really? Uh leeches, please. Oh, right
Fine. We're gonna watch 10 minutes of santa first. We're gonna watch santa claus conquers earth
With bombs or whatever. He does. I don't know santa conquers earth. No santa conquers the martians
We're going for it. We're gonna watch 10 minutes of this
If in 10 times two speed fine if in five to 10 minutes, this is not I don't like this
We're gonna move on want it regular speed. No, this is a fucking song in the beginning. Don't think so
Give us 20 minutes
20 minutes
That's what I want
20 minutes if this is not worth watching we're gonna watch attack of the fucking giant slugs
Okay
Look this you just get more content
We start a new movie if this isn't very good
santa claus
Here we go
These movies are free, okay
Oh, you guys have a lot of freedom station. KID tv brings you the special event of the year
A first in television history santa's gonna find a bunch of fucking martians kid tv has standing by
A television crew at santa claus workshop and in just a few seconds our special correspondent andy henderson
Will bring you a person of germa 95 made-up name santa claus himself direct from the north pole stevenson stevens
Anderson temperature is 91 degrees below zero
Come on kids by a telstar andy henderson at the north pole. This is martians. Hi kids. This is andy henderson at the north pole
It's cold up here
From this spot, there's only one direction you can go and that's south
Yeah
Living up here is pretty rough. I don't know if you go north you end up south
Fucking idiot. We've been here. We've eaten nothing but frozen food. At least that's the way it is by the time we get it
And now let's take a look see into santa's workshop
Here we go
20 minutes
relax
Reporting live. I'm sorry santa's workshop
Weeks before christmas and santa and his helpers are working overtime to make sure that there's enough toys for the kids
All over santa's a pretty busy man, but i'm sure
He'd like to say a few words to you kids. I'm not vetoing this yet. Relax. Hello santa. Oh, hello, son
Oh, oh hello boys and girls
Everybody smoked me at a very busy time
Well, well we've never disappointed the kids yet
Tell me is it true that this year there's a rumor that you're going to use a rocket sled
No, sorry
We're going out the good old-fashioned way with my reindeer
rancer and dancer and dunder and blitz and
Donger is not a
But the kids know their names
There you are
We have so much to do and you stand here dawdling talking to this visitor. Mr. Anderson. This is mrs
Mr. Anderson
Television did you say we're on television?
I hate this but i'm 20 minutes
We have 15 more minutes. Don't care
Come along. Mr. Anderson and i'll show you some of the new toys. We're turning out. This is a bazooka
Everything is a okay salad
Winky is in charge of our space
Here here is the latest toy rocket it runs on real
Strange little creature over here
Oh, uh winky made that that's his idea of a martian a martian
Is here on fire i'd hate to meet a creature like that on a dark night
I wonder if there really are people on mars. Well, who knows
Well, if there are I hope they have someone like you up there santa to bring joy and good cheer to all the martian children
Oh, mr. Anderson
Oh
Keep going winky christmas eve is coming soon. Now, mr. Anderson. I want to show you some more
Drop oh you lazy good for nothing. Where are you this sucks drop another garage wake up drop a wake up
We've painted our garage a newcomer
It's a funny ray
Oh, I hate this
Stand up. This is fucking horrible
Stand up stand up
I'm sorry chief keemar, sir drop. Oh, you were the laziest man on mars. Why are you sleeping during working hours?
I wasn't sleeping. I just get back in the room good. Is the master here?
He's in there and keemar is very angry, too
Keemar I bought some new food pills. I hope the children will eat these
We have hamburger
buttered asparagus
Mashed potatoes and a special treat some kind
I was gonna go like 10 minutes in
So that's what the earth people call a city
How primitive look at all those buildings above ground
Why we could destroy that city with one blast of our curie
He's wearing like a beer helmet i'm waiting for the strada going his mouth and to be like, oh those primitive humans
Let's get bad lord tension crew who's driving the plane
When we've landed regna voldar and I will leave the ship to investigate
Hargo lomas and drop. Oh is the guy driving the plane facing the other direction immediate blast off
Let's get bad. He's gone the north pole very well. Come along
Where these kids come from
This morning two children disappeared mysteriously from the vicinity of welch lake
The police have found no clues and it seems as though billy and betty foster have simply vanished into thin air
This appears to be a day when everything is vanishing into thin air while local police are continuing their
No, sir as a matter of fact, I was just looking in there to remind myself never to hide in there again
I bet
I
Want one scene where santa lives
Besides i've always wanted to visit mars mommy and daddy are going to be angry
You think that's something I can just see mrs. Claus now christmas coming and i'm not there. She'll have a fit
Oh me oh my oh me
Come and get it dinner time
Here's drop. Oh, if I can't cheer you up drop. Oh can he always makes me laugh
What does he know?
dinner tonight
or soup and
Beast I love mickey mouse chocolate ice cream
No, thank you. Mickey mouse is so funny
Even when he's an alien guy
Well, is it all right if I have your chocolate ice cream
Oh
After we secured the ship and lower the ladder
Skip
I can't believe it. That's the first time in months. They've gone to sleep without the sleep spray
Santa tomorrow, we'll set up a workshop for you
It won't be exactly the same as the one you have on earth, but i'm sure it'll serve your purpose
All right, what do you want? Hold on. These are our terms first
Destroy the toy machine
Why is there no beard what's going on where's this beard
Merry christmas everybody
You get it attack of the giant leeches attack of the giant leeches incoming here. Cool. This is gonna be probably it might be worse
This one is only one hour long
Vito what?
How am I I we didn't?
I veto this one, too
Oh, we're watching this one
Here we go three. This is attack of the giant leeches
three two
one
crusty
Very crusty
It's crusty
That was a leech or a mountain lion, yeah either one
Oh the saturation, oh great i'll drink to that one
Drink, uh, you know when you're drinking out of an instrument
You're in an old movie
Ken clark jen shepard and michael emmett with these people that I don't feel like reading
Virtual story screenplay by this guy who cares
This looks like garbage bring on the fucking rich brothers. That's what I gotta say
Dick rubbin. Oh, it is dick rubbin
It's rubin rubin relax
It's rubin
Work, but uh, this is fucking crustier than a goddamn burnt piece of toast
Hey, uh, yay
Just who is the second limb miss hold on hold on wait, wait, wait a minute. You hear me girl. What are you playing the piano?
Well, you won't now what is that what are you putting in your mouth don't put it don't put it in your mouth
Take that out of your mouth
Come on. Oh, she's brushing her teeth. That's the weirdest. What how are you?
Nobody brushes their teeth all the way to the back of the throat who the fuck does that she can't do what she's been asking for
I do
You brush your teeth all the way to the back of your esophagus. What the fuck are you talking about?
I'm back there. I'll lay a jug
He'll be doing it
Terrible thing you killed out there at the swamp
I put five slugs into that critter before it went under
This thing I've seen
And regular arms on it like a man
It was sort of different looking
Had had suckers on them
like one of them uh
Like one of them octopuses things
Well, how do you know what okay even like how do you know what an octopus is
Oh, I told you before it was one of those octopuses things
Just take things off
It was an octopus
Oh, sir, and it weren't no freak gator neither
I've been poaching this country for 40 years and I ain't never seen nothing like it
Not too bad. You didn't bring it back steve benton probably pay a fair bounty for whatever it was
bounty
I wouldn't touch that critter for all the money ever made
And if you see that you wouldn't either
You better take it easy on this stuff. You're looking kind of peeking
What am I gonna get some real shit in the public domain? I'm gonna clean my otter. I think about this sometimes
Public domain always has just dog shit
You've been poaching all these years coming back to haunt you frankenstein's the only thing we got
And attack of the giant fucking leeches
You better. I'll see it right quick yourself. It's because of disney
I can't wait to see fucking mickey mouse do all shitty car commercials
It's gonna be fucking crazy
Mickey mouse is gonna be selling insurance
Just wait when they lose that case in 10 years
You made that joke before he's a repeater
And here by the way, here comes the jazz music when uh, there's a lady on the screen and hold on. We might need to
I need to move this forward about 15 seconds. Look
It's not like I want to be mean or anything like that. Liz baby. Okay reputation around here
These folks have no respect slow
Flutes next thing
I just got dressed like an opera singer
This is dick rubbin, okay
All right, did you tell that there might be a female on the screen?
There could be a woman on the screen in 1940
Okay, this is might be a skip scenario touch me you think you're talking to don't touch me
You're my wife. I'll touch you anytime. I feel like it. They're married
Where you going?
This movie sucks
Maybe i'll be back
Maybe I won't
Liz baby, I don't mean nothing listen to me
I know I know i've been really looking like chef boy rd lately, but you know, i'm good for it
You know me
What there was a young one that last trap had to kill it. Oh poor thing. What?
Told you you shouldn't come along
Turn the lights on. I can't see what's happening. This is the movie man watching a wedding dress
Oh when she's not suffering those traps
horrible
These poachers know the swamps like the back of their hands, but i'll catch one of them. Yeah
I'll have to be satisfied confiscating
Trap
These people aren't like other folks, you know, they'll try and get back at you let them try
Steve you're a stranger here. They've lived this way for generations one man isn't going to change them overnight
You're a real worry ward. I'm serious
They can be dangerous
Shut up you drunk. I'll be careful. What?
You just all right
Steve I love you. I love you so much
What was that
Was eating cereal listen benton
What is he eating that beef stew?
As far as this office is concerned at the end of but sure if I can't see whether lem was killed by anything human
I wouldn't need you to tell me my job
And i'm not about to go tromping through the swamp looking for an overgrown gator
Saw your wasn't killed by an alligator. Is that so did you hear that morton game warden benton says it wasn't a gator kill lem
Well, then what was it?
You know, you can't veto movie halfway through it. Dr. Grayson said it's been it's been like two hours
How has it been? Oh sure. How has it been 10 minutes? It's been three hours 30 miles inland living in clear water
Stranger things have happened. I know I care benton
You work for the state
Now, why don't you keep your nose out of county business? Is that clear enough for you? Oh, we're staying
Oh go soak your fat head
What
What was that you said oh go soak your fat head go soak your fat head
Okay, go soak your fat head trouble
And he's sure going to get it
You can bet on that
There's a good thing. He's 11. Otherwise, I would have been really mad at him. The octopi uses its suction discs to hold its prey
Now in itself the disc will not inflict a wound same is true of the squid
Now both creatures have a parrot-like beak as their primary offensive and defensive weapon. Well, maybe the sheriff was right there
Could be a freak or a malformed alligator
No
No, i'm afraid it wasn't
Well, where does that leave us doc?
I wish I knew
You know, i'm beginning to think lem was telling the truth in warper store
He did see something that night
Something that had intelligence enough to seek him out destroy him late. Thanks for the tea
Sorry, I'm going to have killed the thing this guy's jack a dozen rifle bullets. Look at this guy's fucking arms
I've seen that old 44 40 years. Nothing could live after being hit with those slugs
well
Conceiving the possibility of one such creature
We must also concede the possibility of others
Oh, there's one sure way of finding out go in and search every backwater channel and what's button this one if it's there i'll find it
Well, whatever it was it's not here anymore
Do you want some coffee? Yeah. Thanks, son. I know I could hide in here and never be noticed one did
The seminal was on osio in 1830s with the u.s army two years around them up. I remember reading about osio in high school two years
It's only been out of two days and I feel worn out. Well, I might as well keep on looking around
This movie's so bad
What do you want me to do? It's like this is the second movie we tried this is the second finale
This is finale two. I
Want more ritz brothers. I me too. I know I really do
Got an interesting scene. Hold on. Can't you think of anything else? Say stupid? I gotta get this order over miss chauvin
She's one of my better customers
Can't keep awaiting
This is fat han solo
I love you. Are you talking about?
get out
Where are the leeches?
I played half life. I love the physics
It's fun to play with stuff have some trouble day
And you know women cal gotta get the hair down every now and then
You sure don't know an awful lot about females
I gotta hand it to you. Is that all his stuff? I can't stand here. John cal. Yeah
All I got is a few bags of rice a couple of shelves stable
About this time an elbow macaroni. Yeah, it's all my stuff frank ever since limb got itself killed
I don't own anything else to sell out and move into town
Don't you let her bamboozle you dave?
You keep her right here in the store
After all place wouldn't be seen without you around
Thanks. Yeah, I better get going see when I get back
Yeah, i'll be around
Thank you, uh nick for the for the community five communities with so much money coming
Do you guys even give a shit about this movie a ton of money coming?
I mean, this is not a gorilla movie or an aliens movie. So who cares?
Thanks for the five subs nick dub the movie sure you won't send
Uh, would you like some dinner?
Sounds good to me
Hey, look, it's a copy of the bible
Oh, I love the bible. No, I can't do this. No, no, no, I can't do this
I can't do this. I can't do this. I can't do this. No, I can't do this right now
No, I cannot me too. You gotta know your strengths and this is not one of them right now here
No, no, nope
I'm not gonna get that one on me. No
Not drunk enough. No, I know
You gotta know what we're just talking for something. That's why i'm even sure exists
So what do you mean?
You know, we we've covered miles of back channel and haven't come across where are the leeches dude's theory of an alien creature
Not so much as a mutt. I didn't mean anything against you
You
Wait, did he just say that god I wish that was me what god I wish that was me
He didn't
No way
You're wrong wait for the both of you
What oh how get up
Come on, get up
Now look dave. I I know what you're thinking, but I got double. Wait god. I wish that was me
It is you you're making out with this woman. I'm pulling the trigger. It is you
No point getting riled dave
Wasn't my fault
Imagine making out with some girl and going god. I wish it was just was me
Um, it is you. Oh, sorry. I've just been on twitch for so long. I've been writing that
Fucking 12
Come on. Get up. No
No, he killed me. He killed me
Your husband wants to take a look at you
You uh you walk all the way dave one more step and i'll blow your plumbing too
Get over there
I'm not playing that again. I'm not playing it again. What are you gonna do to find out soon enough?
Uh, that's for doing that gun before I get mad and make you eat it
Go ahead and try it cow. Go right ahead and try it
This guy yosemite sam are they where the leech is it's been 25 fucking minutes
It was a leech in the very beginning of the movie. Yeah, the leech is the friends we made along the way
Yeah
You call yourself a man
Get going
You wouldn't you wouldn't get an old friend dave if you don't move i'll tell you where you're staying
Why did he shoot him
That wasn't me he shot him I didn't put that in he shot him come on out of there what he's spamming
Like what he's spamming
God drops to the floor
Eyes pop out of something
That's appeared next to head his steam blows out slams fist on table rattling any plates or bolts
Fireworks
There ain't nothing down here sir
Well i'm getting tired of this
Uh, come on in boys well if there's any bodies out there we'd have found them guys I want some straight answers walter
I want to see the leech. Oh my god. My head hurts
Come on out of there. All right. Yeah, stop stop. Stop. So I read it. I got it. I got it
What is it? I can't see it
Just one of the scaring them bodies are still in there
You can bet some old bull gators got him stuffed in his cave under the bank
Letting him ripen up for a few days. Oh my god. My head hurts from laughing. Yeah. Well
What was it leech some long cypress poles to go man pulled the gator cave
Too far forward how what
It's about two seconds
I'm sorry doc. I can't do it
Wait, who's dead? I had to do it myself wouldn't want to have to arrest you doc
But I will if I find you near the preserve with any explosives. Why is he 5 000 feet away?
Sorry, nan. That's the way it's got to be
He's right, man. It's his job to protect wildlife
What about he's two miles away?
Three people have been killed in that game preserve
Doesn't that mean anything to you?
Nan try to understand if I could be sure something in the swamp was responsible for those deaths. I'm sorry. I didn't mean to
We've been together the last three days was hanging a trace of anything unusual
Not so much as a suggestion of any form of life unknown to us
steve
Shot and killed those people. All right. I'll admit for your death left a lot of questions unanswered
But you can bet your bottom dollar the other two died from dave walker's shotgun
Do you really believe that figure it out psycho walker the cartoon noises that came out of his gun swamps after he found him
How could you trust him after that? He shot them and he tried to place the blame on sawyer's dt's
If sawyer told of seeing a purple giraffes with polka dot tails walker would have claimed they did it
There's one argument against that steve
Dave walker wasn't the kind of a man to hang himself. Not even with two murder charges against him
I talked with dave less than an hour before he killed himself
That man best part of this movie was the dick rubbin name. I've seen frightened men before terrified men
Yeah, i've never seen anything to compare with the horror and the fear in walker's eyes
Well, he realized what he'd done and killed two people. That's the highlight
Oh look doc nan and I were all over that swamp god damn it. Why didn't these monsters attack us?
I've been thinking about that. They're probably night creatures
They can't stand the light they stay down near the bottom during the day
A small charge would stun him bring him to the surface can't buy doc. You're pigheaded steve benton stubborn and pigheaded
You just don't understand do you?
Good night doc. What's that? What what what?
What viewers plummeting i've read one person they said please put parts on and I was like no
But then that one person had power
I can't take this anymore
Uh, well, we can't we can't skip it when I started I started watching I can't oh that's comedy fucking liquor
Boy, that makes me happy
Okay, i'm gonna keep it on
Right unseasonable
So it's funny, huh?
Didn't you notice anything? No, what we've been prodding around you all morning
Ain't run across a single gator
By rights is this fool should be calling with him. So funny. Yeah, that is funny. I like looks
Let's call it day. Well, wait a minute. Wait, we ain't gonna hold around the bend yet
You do what you want. Just get me on dry land and right quick. All right. I know you're getting all hit up. Let's go
A huge canoe, holy shit
Out here
Action
What's normal what's normal wait I think
It's just trash bags
sentient trash bags
tending
Fuck it's kind of fucked up actually
Yes, they're getting eaten actually kind of scary. Yeah actually kind of calling but there's been no answer
Why I just got back what seems to be the trouble haven't you heard? Okay. Kylo Ren relax
Disappeared
Come on inside
You know covis
Nothing would please him more than to have all the swamp people disappear
Swamp trash he calls them
Strange they have about as much regard for him as he has for them
When they're worried enough to go to him
You know something's wrong
Mrs. Reed said the men went searching for cow and mrs walker's bodies and they never returned
Cobra says he'll get up a search party if they don't show up in a couple of days person's name
Doc you and then take your car and get as many volunteers as you can
Tell them to meet me at the old wagon road. I'll call doc evans and have him bring his dogs
Either they're lost or they've had an accident. God damn it so much more. I hope to heaven you're right
Dude veto, please
I've been around here. It's the same scene
Carry that lady
All ladies need to be carried in movies from the 30s through the 60s. They can't even walk
Women can't walk. Did you know that?
From 1930 to 1960 females couldn't walk
There was no time. Wait, is that a wiley coyote explosion machine?
Sure used enough stuff to do the job mike. I used 100 sticks or 40 percent
I'll blow the bottom right out. All right, let her go. Oh, no
I've done enough of your dirty work
Help yourself
But is he presses the button?
Well, the worst part about this jack is that's one lake out of about 16 000 in the united states
We're gonna have to go all over
They're everywhere man. We didn't win shit. This dude is fucking hairy. Whoa
Whoa, i'm this is a serious. Whoa
What?
This dude is fucking hairy
Uh, I'm I mean really like really hair down here on your stomach
Holy shit
I don't have that
What do you mean? That's normal. No, I don't have that shit
I've got a line going from my belly button down to my uh, my brain is
What's that sad? Nothing?
What do you mean manlit?
You have hair here on your obliques. No, you don't
Who has fucking hair on their obliques?
Yes
I don't believe I don't believe you. Oh shit spoilers
But meanwhile at the pentagon in washington dc
All right
Uh, i'm gonna go pee come back and we're gonna watch some three stooges. Hope to see you there. Okay. Hello
We're gonna watch captain alex. Uh, i've already seen captain alex. So I already seen it. All right, so three stooges
What are we gonna watch for the three stooges?
You haven't watched it with us
I mean, that's true. But okay. This is uh, the three stooges punch drunks
I wonder we'll give it a try. This is probably the last thing we do tonight before we just chill and hang out
I gotta ask you though very very important question. Would you hold on?
Hold on. This is the first time we've done this
Do you want to do this again? Would you like to do this again?
With other public domain movies if you'd like to please vote on that poll
If not, then let me know
This is a trial run
Not every week. No, no, no, it'd be like once a month
That's pretty that's a lot
That's 94 percent to six. That's a lot of people
Okay
Uh, so we'll get more ritz brothers movies
I I don't do I have to give the link anymore?
I think
Uh, I don't think you can the nose are gonna climb back
At this point
Uh, this has been a lot of fun though
I'm very very happy with this the first two movies were fucking incredible
And then we played some fart noises, you know
Uh, this is called the three stooges and punch drunks. Let's check this one out and this will take us to the end
Columbia picture
the three stooges
Moe larry and curly in
something fucking comedy
punch drunks with darthi granger
Am I gonna get drunk each time too?
Probably where's our cut from last night's show?
Yeah, the only cut i've got so far is this one over my eye
Sure, help me boys after taking out expenses mouth open
Chew fucking moe disgusting. We're quitting idiot
On a gentleman mugs can't do that to me. I'll be left without any fighters
I got it. I got it
Hello bo bromo. Hi, mr. McGurion
punch him
Squish his nose with your fingers
What the fuck?
Wait a minute. Where have you been out to lunch?
Get over there and wait on those customers. Yes, sir. Oh and when fucking violence to strangers was funny
Four slices of burnt toast and a rotten egg
Point toast and a rotten egg. Yeah, what do you want that for? I got a tapeworm and it's good enough for him
What do you gentlemen have
I got a tapeworm three hamburgers for the mugs three hamburgers
Pardon me stranger
I'm a musician. So what?
Well, I thought if you had some music around the place you might increase business
How much dough do you generally get? Well, I get 250 but for you i'll take 200. I'll give you a bowl of soup
I'll take it if you're good
I hope the soup's good
I want one of these hats
You'll never regret this mister
Larry always looks like he's been electrocuted
15 seconds before every performance
Sorry gentlemen, you can't have any hamburger the meat's too fresh. Oh, yeah
This isn't public domain
This is not public domain
What the fuck are you talking about? What?
Wait, hold on the three stooges
public domain
This is not in the public domain
How it was nice knowing you. What the fuck you what?
Check the website public domain. What the fuck
Did I get one guide? This is called punch drunks
1934 one guy color crazy
rideless groom sing a song of six pants disorder in the court color crazy malice in the palace and
Wait, what am I gonna get in trouble?
Oh
Guys I don't think
I don't
I don't think this is okay
The meat ain't the only fresh thing around here, is it?
Oh give us a break will you fellas i'm a citizen and I
Now you're gonna bring the boys of food
Stop stop
You can't do that
Why is this every single interior gta scene, uh
Am I can I not is this staff around what is this fucking seven million people here staff who's here staff staff?
Can I can I fucking play this movie?
This staff here staff link
Can I play this movie as long as I make fucking comedy references? Can I do this?
Is this okay?
I there's a twitch staff here link. I know you're watching I can see you
As long as I do like oh funny fucking comedy references and how he screams like as long as I fucking
That's fair use. Is that all right? I didn't see it. What do you say?
You said it's okay. You said it's fine. Okay back to the fucking violence against strangers funny
Say you're a born champ. Did I do this?
Sure. Yeah, you did. What's eating you? You're a psycho. Remember?
No
Every time I hear that weasel tune something pops inside of me, then everything goes black
Hey, what's the idea? You're trying to ruin my business. I'm sorry. Look at my customers
I'm a victim of circumstance. What do you think this is a joint? It's that pop the weasel. Hey fiddler. Give us that weasel tune again
Maybe you'll punch this guy
Don't punch this guy
Don't punch the fucking owner of the pasta italiana. He's gone. He's that guy's gone. He's out. He's out of here
What doesn't exist? Look, he's gone. How'd he get up there? It worried shit hands with your new manager
Boy, we're gonna make a lot of money. I need you too. From now on we're a corporation where we're going
We got a lot of training to do
Hey, he's not he's not a fucking like
Uh, that's not like turning on the uh, what's the thing called goddamn jokes? You gotta give jokes
What's the other thing that grinds up food in your uh, a garbage disposal fuck god damn it whatever pretend i'm not here
He's joe biden
The thing that uh the uh the guy the thing there whatever it is
I don't know. I know you had a tough day kid
How do you feel now?
Oh, you're in great shape ko
Where's that what?
How do they get here the lady she said gentlemen besides I always told you boxing and women don't mix
Now that probably hurts
They hurt each other in real life. What can I do for you toots?
I'm in a terrible dilemma
Yeah, I don't care much for these foreign cars either
You don't understand
I'm stuck Honda. Civic's a good car. That's what they all tell me. Sorry
Mo fucking wrong
Yeah, hey kayo don't sit there like a dummy come over here. Give me a hand
Which one get on the bumper? Wait a minute. We need more help. Where's larry?
I can't wait to these guys are fortnight characters. We added skins
Curly mowing larry
Yeah, it's a fine time to go fishing
Here come the leeches
Help me here. Wait a minute in music. They're strength. Yeah, give ko a couple of bars of weasel
Play the music again
This lady's what she's a stock image i'll be with you in a minute on me stock image lady
Uh, we gotta get this guy's foot on it from the car. They'll be in fortnight. Trust me a couple of years
Give it a couple years
I'll be right. That's fine
Don't worry about me dear i'm a man without feelings what I tell you about mixing fighting with women get upstairs
Go on upstairs what's on his what's on his back? See you after the fight. Don't worry now. I won't get hurt
See you toots
Hold on. Hold on
Ah, yes, just people are gonna know the three stooges more as time goes on you fucking moron
Well, you called me a moron. So you're automatically banned from the channel, but uh to address your comment
um
The three what the three stooges are are are
forever
And that person for three weeks
At least all right if if the three stooges get into fortnight, I want fucking 10 000 subs
I'm gonna just let's be clear
You boys make a good clean fight
No holding and hitting and no dirty tactics if they don't
I'll eat a fucking glove
I get two years. I have two years for this to happen a guy sitting on a chair
They're gonna be in fortnight. I'm telling you
sit down
Stop hitting him. Stop it. Why are they always touching each other?
It didn't work. Oh, you broke his strata various. He's gonna lose
Versus mickey the sink
Thanks pal
He's already up
Don't get hit by a car dude
The ref sucks wireless, what do you mean wireless?
Sure
I thought he was gonna do a roundhouse kick
Where's your candy kid?
Why is he getting ready to ring the bell?
I did it before you little shit my rules
What oh we're talking comedy hey, I get it I get it. All right, come on bring it in here larry
All right now beat his ass curly
Uncle dan will tell you how fuzzy bear met jerry pre stump in the woods right next to peter rabbit
All right. Why does everybody from like the 30s have such weird body types? This guy's supposed to be jacked
But he looks like fucking taffy
he's got like a big fat stomach and like weird breasts and
Googly arms like this is not like this. He's not fit
Look at how healthy and jacked this guy is
Oh, by the way, here's a big stomach his arms are small his hands are small
His chest is small, but he's got a big fucking stomach though. I mean he's jacked in the 30s
He has two back muscles
Uh biting is illegal
He's going back to the store
What is going on?
That was good that was pretty good that was funny that was fun
Yeah, that was funny it was come on I suppose you want the afternoon off gta
Now he hasn't driven on the sidewalk and run over 15 people yet
I don't agree
All right
Okay, it's gta
Imagine losing to pop goes the weasel
Your career is fucking over
I knew we do it we put it over
That'll be a tweet that's like a hashtag funny fucking tweet
It's over
Okay. I don't know why I thought that was the land of lakes person. I thought that was the land of lakes butter
Have I lost my fucking mind?
Okay, so the good butter pictures presents more you want more stooges. What about charlie chaplin charlie chaplin?
What's a good charlie chaplin movie?
I mean i'm i'm still good to go buster keaton
Play jump king. What the fuck are you talking about play jump king on public domain movie night?
Jesus christ
Okay, fine
Imagine getting the usb in the slot at the first try. I can't imagine this goddamn software. Let's go
Is this even fucking plugged in? Let's go
Let's go
Vito wait, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Wait, why why I want to show up?
Oh, cuz obs sucks. I forgot obs can't window capture right? Why won't this work plug it in?
Plug it in
What the fuck?
That's not right now
I don't know how to play
Wait, what?
What did I just do? Wait, wait, open it back up open it open open open open open open open open open open open open
Open it open it open open open open open open open open open it open it open it open it open it open the game
Open it open it open the game right now. I just deleted. I deleted the safe. I deleted the whole safe. It's gone
Who cares
Um who cares I I don't
Why still why would delete save?
Be
Why would delete save?
Why would delete safe be right on that menu?
Veto? Yeah, veto this. Give me the fuck out of here. I'm done. I don't care. I'm done. Fuck. Fuck that game.
Fuck everything about that game. Who cares?
Okay. Um, oh, that's it. I'll see you tomorrow.
Oh, whatever. I'll see you in a couple days. See you in a few days. See you on uh, see you on Monday.
Yeah, see you on Monday. I'm done.
The easy bake oven stream. Yeah, hold on. I know that people are waiting for this.
Uh, it turns out something interesting.
A bunch of the recipes that I ordered have not come in yet.
Uh,
I have 15 easy bake oven recipes. They're still shipping. Still.
Um, so we can't do that tomorrow.
I'm sorry to say.
I'm so upset this stream sucks. What?
Ban that person for like a month.
Uh, stream blows. Stream sucks. What? Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. He's right. No, he's not. Get out.
Fuck you, Jerma. Hey.
We're rioting?
It's been four and a half hours. You guys know the fucking costochondritis rules.
I have costochondritis rules.
No stream can be more than four or five hours. You know that, right? Come on. Don't riot.
Chat, you're killing him.
You said four to six.
Yeah, it's been four and a half. I'm gonna spend like half an hour 40 minutes in the hanging out with you guys.
What are you talking about?
Can I ban chat?
Hey, uh, wait, wait, wait. Who said that? Link?
Link, do me a favor. What movies can I watch on stream that don't have to be
on the terrible service that you guys have?
What movies can I watch that aren't on that awful service?
They're like, please watch Jack Ryan
service.
What can I watch?
What can I watch besides please god fucking please god watch Jack Ryan? What can I watch?
Fuck, am I gonna get in trouble? I don't know. Don't ban me. Don't ban me.
That was rude.
Was it?
I want to watch movies and tv shows with my friends.
Are they your friends? Yes. Are you sure? That sounds kind of parasocial.
Quiet.
He's using us. What the fuck? What are you talking about? Uh, but for real, no, no joking around.
That was a lot of fun.
I would love to do that again.
Stream tomorrow. I can't stream tomorrow. I gotta take a bath.
Worst one guy moment all day.
I'll...
Listen, I'll be back on Monday.
Monday, Tuesday, Wednesday, and then probably Thursday and hopefully Easy Bake Oven happens.
Easy Bake Oven.
Amazon doesn't have...
Amazon has like pretend dates that they're sending shit because of the coronavirus.
I ordered shit and it doesn't know when it's gonna come in. That's real. I can't... I don't know what to...
What do I... I don't know what to do.
I didn't say five days a week. I said four. What's today? Friday, Wednesday, Thursday, Friday, Friday, Saturday.
It's been six days in the last seven days. What are you talking about? I didn't say seven days a week.
Six days.
You said more streams, but shorter. Yeah, and it's been... we've streamed like eight in the last ten days.
He's gaslighting us? No, you're gaslighting me. That's literally no. What? Let me see. Let me see.
He's a liar. Let me see if I'm a liar or not. Let me see.
You're my witch. No, you're my twitch. Let's see. He's lying. He's a lying streamer. He's a liar.
I don't think I'm a liar. Let's see.
Shut up, you fucking idiot. All right, let's go to videos.
What was the last week? I streamed like six times the last like seven or eight days, right? Let's find out.
Okay, one, two, three.
Five days ago.
Six, seven days ago. All right, so one, two, three. I've seen six of the last nine days.
What? What the heck?
That's not a lie. That's real.
He's fudging the numbers. I'll be back on Monday. That's two days from now and I think it's gonna be hilarious.
Four out of 20 days? What? What is this?
Oh, that's public domain movie night. That's what we just did.
He's drunk? I... yeah, I kind of am.
What do you want me to lie to you?
No, I'm not. I've had like five vodka cocktails.
Yeah, I have. Yeah, I am.
Yeah, what am I gonna lie to you? Put on the face cam? Sure. The webcam doesn't want to get captured.
Oh, I unplugged it. I can't... I can't get it to load.
This thing sucks.
Oh, wait. No, no, this is another camera.
Okay.
This... I'm here. You look like a villain. That's fine. Greasy teeth?
Ah, they're right. I don't know how you're right, but you are. All right. See you on Monday. I had a ton of fun tonight.
Perfect time for TF2. Why would I... what...
All right, the next game that somebody fucking says in the chat, I'll play it right now. What is it? What is it? Say it!
Oh, fuck. TF2. This is gonna take like two hours to download.
Nah, this is gonna take like three hours to download. Uh, it's not gonna work.
I'm not gonna play jump. No. All right. I'm out of here. I'm gonna take a fucking bath. I'll see you on Monday.
All right. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. I'll see you on Monday.
Uh, for Gotcha Force. Gotcha Force on Monday!
You look greasy. Do...
No, it's the light. The light makes me look fucked up.
You're drunk? No, I'm... yeah, I am. What? I don't know. Yes, I am. Okay. Good night.
Uh, that was so much like for real. No like joking around. That was a ton of fucking fun.
I had so much fucking fun. We will do this again.
Without a doubt. That was a ton of fun. I had a blast. Hope you did too. He's a wine mom. No. Yeah, whatever.
I'm fucking 35 this year. Get over it. Uh, why can't I...
There it is. Let's do the bits!
Why are you so old? How did that happen? I don't know, man. I just did.
It just hap- it fucking happened. I'm 35 this year. I know. It's been 10 years. I've been doing this for 10 years.
That was a lot of fun. Thanks for joining me. I will see you guys on Monday.
For more fucking funny stuff. We're gonna play Gotcha Force.
One of my favorite GameCube games ever.
You'll see why. It was two hundred and fifty dollars. Gotcha Force was
two hundred and fifty fucking dollars. I hope you like it.
Hey, Charlie is okay. Thanks for three dollars. Did someone say movie night? They did. Me and you.
Thank you, Snake Cowboy for the ten community subs. Ten subs. Thank you.
Uh, Orofarynx. Thanks for threes subs. That's not- it's three dollars actually. Thanks to three hundred bits.
I'm recovering from coronavirus. And even though laughing makes my chest worse, your streams have helped me keep my head up.
Thanks for all you do. Hopefully you recover really soon. Take care of yourself. Drink lots of water and stay isolated.
Thanks for the three dollars. Hey, Vic for First Noble. Thanks for five dollars.
If the gorilla is so smart, how come it's a gorilla and not a human?
Because the movie was made in 1939. They didn't fucking understand anything. They knew smoke cigarettes and break walls.
That's what they did. Hey, Banjo Boy. Thanks for two fifty. Fun fact.
Santa Claus Conquers the Martians was the first appearance of Mrs. Claus in any media.
Really? Most people think that the claymation Rudolph holds this title, but no.
Santa Claus Conquers the Martians came out a couple months before. I've watched this movie like 18 times.
I have no idea why. It was fun watching with you though. Thanks for a fun night. We barely watched it, but.
Atlanteus, thanks for ten dollars. Here are your royalties for my use of the Rat Birthday song
when I wash my hands.
Uh, that that song is free. You don't have to pay me money. That song is free, but thanks for the thousand bits.
Hey freak out. Thanks for the five dollars. Jerma, if you want some old dramatic movies,
you should watch Twelve Angry Men for the best years of our lives.
Or if you want something to watch in your personal time, watch a thing that could be porn.
And I'm not going to say it out loud. Thanks for the five dollars. Hey, uh, Uber Morph Point.
Thanks for fifteen dollars, Uber Morph Point. If you do another one of these, you should watch Who Killed Captain Alex?
I've seen it. Uh, Ugandan Action Movie Free on YouTube. I've seen that whole movie. It's fantastic.
I'd like to see things on movie night that I've never seen. Things that I've never seen before. I've seen that one.
Uh, Dr. Zutsu, thanks for the seven dollars. Hey Jerma, glad this stream schedule is coming back together.
Stuff is really wild and stressful for everyone right now, and I'm glad stuff is working out for you enough
that you can stream again. I've been stressed recently since I started school again.
I can't believe I played Jump King for ten seconds and deleted the whole save. That's, that sucks.
Um, since I started school again and my design is one of the 25 finalists in the Terraria Vanity Contest,
if I win and you ever play Terraria again, my design is the TV head outfit.
Thanks for streaming. Thanks for the seven bucks. Terraria is a great game. That'd be fucking cool
if you got some shit in it. Can't believe I deleted my whole save account on Jump King.
Thanks for the seven bucks. Peaceful Haley, 250 from Peaceful Haley. So happy you're doing a movie night.
The riffing makes it even better. Thanks for being entertaining. Good night, Jerma, and chat.
Uh, I think it was a success. I had a lot of fun. I'm having a great time. Like, this has been fucking,
this has been a blast. I hope you had fun.
Thanks for the 350. Bella Lisosy was a master theater and movie actor in the 20s and early 30s,
and extremely popular thanks to his role in Dracula. The Gorilla was filmed in the period
when his career was on the decline and was mostly typecasted and relegated to bit parts.
By the time Plan 9 was filmed, he was destitute and addicted to morphine. Holy shit. He died
halfway through production. By the way, this was fun. Wait, what? He died halfway through production.
That's fucking horrible. Uh, also, I might suggest Freaks. 1932. That's sad and terrible.
That was the guy that used the cape? Oh, I fucking made fun of, that was, oh, I feel bad.
That's why they covered his face. Uh, thanks for the 250, Vrimthral. The Bella with the cape
up against his face is actually a double. Uh, Bella Lisosy died partway through into
filming Plan 9. Plan 9 was also Lisosy's final film. On a lighter note,
this whole stream has been golden. Thanks for the laughs. I'm glad we can come together and
have some fun. I had a few drinks. It's all, it's all good. You know, whatever. I played
Jump King to lead in my save. Embarrassing. What an embarrassing asshole. Uh, Fancy Boots. Thanks for
250. Correction. Plan 9 was technically, technically, Lisosy's final film. It was
released in 1959, but his appearance is comprised of old footage recorded before his passing.
Interesting tip. You're a movie nerd. Uh, Blaine. Blaine's Magmar. Thanks for 250. Uh,
Jerma, as a public health major, I want to say that you were doing a great service
just by making the quarantine more fun. You'll always be my favorite streamer. He has no idea
what the fuck he's saying. What? Yes, I do. I'm not like that far gone. Jesus. Give me some slack.
I've had some drinks. That doesn't mean I'm like fucking stupid. Oh, he's gone. He's,
he didn't have any idea what he's saying. Where is he? He's five. He's a five-year-old.
Give me some slack for Christ's sake. It's been like five hours of drinking. Eh, whatever. Hey,
DarkPyLord. Thanks for the five dollars. Jerma, fun fact about Plan 9 from Outer Space. Every
shot featuring Bella Lugosi was actually unused footage from a different movie Ed Wood had shot
years earlier. That's sad. So much Lugosi lore. I know. I'm laughing at that. No, I'm not. I'm
not laughing at some person. Hmm. Devakity, thanks for 250. In case you didn't know,
the backstory of Plan 9. Bella Lugosi that played the vampire was dead years before the movie.
I know the guy's dead. Okay. I get it. I know. He covered his face because after the actor wasn't
Lugosi, the footage where you see his face is leftover footage. I'm not laughing at that. I'm
laughing at chat being fucking hilarious. Ah, yeah. Bella Lugosi's dead. I know. I, this is like six
messages in a row. I know he's dead. I know. And then he was replaced. Please do The Great
Dictator. Pretty sure it's public domain. It's great. Thank you, Devakity. Oh, okay. I got to
fucking get it together. Hole of one zombie. Thanks for 250. This was amazing. Recommend.
I recommend any early Jackie Chan film in public domain or Ninja Dragon if it's on YouTube.
Not sure if it's public domain. Terribly dubbed Jackie Chan films are brilliant.
I don't think they're public domain. Appreciate it though. Thank you. Femme Enting Dregs. This was
$25. Femme Enting Dregs. Thanks. Thank you for a better movie night than I've seen in the past
five years in the old facilities known as theaters. Here's half the cost of what a movie ticket was
going to in about a year from now the way things were going. If you're keeping going in these times
have a blast. I'm having a blast so far. $25 for a movie ticket. Yeah. Did I read that wrong?
Probably. Thank you for a better movie night than I've seen in the past five years in the old
facilities known as theaters. Here's half the cost of what a movie ticket was going to in about a
year from now the way things were going. Hope you keep these things going. It's been a blast so far.
I did it right. I read that word for word. That's correct. Hey, Evangelion. The room is spinning.
No, it's not. Not even close. Hey, guess what? Plan 9 was actually the last film of Bela Lugosi.
The reason his face is hidden throughout most of the film either by his cape or by filming
is because it's actually a stand-in. The shots that actually show his face were filmed for
unrelated projects and then repurposed for this film. I'm not reading the same bits.
The show, you know, after his death in the order to draw in more of an audience,
they said it was Bela Lugosi's final film. Lugosi likely never met any of the actors in Plan 9.
Any more fun facts? That's so funny. The final actor, Lich, gave $50 fucking dollars and I missed
it, but they said these fucking aliens have space travel and guns that control dead bodies,
but humans have gone too far. Oh my God. Thanks for the huge amount of money.
Hey, Flimflam. $5. I got a burp. I can't mute it. Why? Why can't I mute this? What the fuck?
I tried. What the fuck? Stream Deck. What the fuck? Stream Deck, what are you doing? Mute this.
It won't mute. I don't know why. It sucks. Flimflam, thanks for the $5. Thanks for the stream.
I'd like to recommend The Pink Panther Strikes again for public domain movie night 2,
whenever that may be. Fairly certain it's public domain. If not, then please watch yourself.
If you haven't already, here's the link. Watch yourself? I think we've done that before.
Hey, Jerma, do you know that Bela Lugosi is dead? Stop. That's so easy to make me laugh right now.
Flimflam, another $5. Forgot you turned links off. Just search Uncle Carl, Uncle Earl's
classic TV channel, Pink Panther Strikes again. It's the first link. Uncle Carl's
Pink Panther. What the fuck is happening? I got it. Is this public domain though? I don't think
it is. Gotta be careful. Link is watching. Thanks for the $5. Sticks Renegade, thanks for $2.50.
Press J or L to FF or rewind 10 seconds, please. Plus press left or right on the arrow keys to do
5 seconds. I figured it out. Grizzly Wright, thanks for the $3. I'm making my first ever
Twitch donation to say that Santa is fucking stupid. Friedl Schlitz, thanks for $2.50.
Please make this a reoccurring thing. The stream has made me laugh out loud more than anything else
this month. Movies are more fun when you watch them with 7,000 other people. Also, you should
add Frog to the list. And its sequel, Frogs. They're both on YouTube. Oh, what's that? Another
$5,050 donation that I skipped and didn't even read? From Scripts 3?
Gerald, please. Just put on a Charlie Chaplin movie already. They're all public domain. Put on
the Gold Rush. That's the best one from him. Next time. Next time. Wolf Bowl, thanks for $5.
Did we really think that the ADHD streamer wasn't going to skip scenes and play fart and scream
sound effects? I don't know. I sent the message too early. I meant to say that I wouldn't have
had it any other way. Thank you for taking my fart sound effect suggestion. God damn it.
Abomination Zero, $15. Lots of fucking money. You have to do some Three Stooges shit for
Green Screen 2. I promise. But what about Bela Lugosi? Is he dead? Autumn Dragons, thanks for
the $2.50. Jerma, tonight was really fun. I'm really looking forward to future movie nights.
Call me a boomer, but it's fun to see what comedy was like back in the day. Also, in the future,
if it's possible, can you put on subtitles? It would help a bunch of us out. That's a rag on
your commentary or anything. Much love to everyone here. Congrats on getting to the top $500 on Twitch
as a Christian gamer dad streamer. Thanks. Hey, Snoozencopter, $2.50. Thanks for $2.50.
Today, after watching all these old movies and you making for the Fortnite YouTuber comment thing,
comedy really hasn't progressed at all. Every single YouTube and streamer comedy routine
consists out of making loud, funny, random noises and getting hurt in game. That will exist for the
next thousand years. Sorry to say. A Lars Blood Axe, thanks for $5. Charlie Chaplin made a movie
called Gold Rush in which he consumes a shoe. It's fate must be watched. Jerma put Sun Chips in F
tier, thanks to $2.50. More stream days, less stream hours. Kappa, to ban that person for
fucking 10 years. LM Man, thanks for the $5. Jerma, I wish you were quiet during the gorilla movie.
I really enjoyed it. I was fucking, I didn't, I shut the fuck up. Dr. Zoot Suit, $5. I can't believe
you actually played Jump King. I was kidding. Why did you read that? I'm so sorry. The fucking
stream is over anyways. Who cares? J Ran Cree, thanks for $15. So there's going to be another
Jump King stream where you beat it all over again, right? Hope so. The first time around was the
best. Either way, movie night was great. Let's do it again. I agree. Did I actually delete the whole
fucking thing? So bad. Why would you put that on the menu? Anything Show Official, thanks for $5.
You should do a Red Baron night tomorrow night where you play the old Red Baron games while
eating Red Baron pizza. I don't think so. Kirranj, thanks for $5. I missed about half the stream,
so I'm really excited to watch the VOD, but you have no idea how happy this movie stream idea
makes me. Older movies, mostly sci-fi and horror, also the B movie variety, are a big interest of
mine. So I'm really happy to watch some with everyone. The issue with these bad movies,
if they're really hit or miss, and a lot of slow with gold nuggets in them periodically.
Regardless, it was fun as hell. I think we hit fucking gold the first four hours at the three or
four hours. Those first two movies were perfect. And then I drank too much. And the third movie was
terrible. Pretty much it. LM, man, thanks for the 250. If you're going to play Sam and Max season
three, I won't. Have you ever considered playing Strong Bad's cool games for attractive people?
It's made by Telltale. I will not. I'm not going to play Sam and Max season three. It didn't grab me.
It wasn't a fan. It's just the way it is. Hey, Chimtrees, thanks for $3. I can't wait to see the
giant leeches in Germany. They won't be there. It will be sucked cigar and a waffle. Thanks for $5.
Remember, why did you become so hideous? It's called going past 35 happens to everybody.
Sorry, it happened to me. You posted cringe, bro. Thanks for the 10 bucks. Wait, is it over? I
thought you were watching multiple movies. That's why I'm just now tuning in. Looks like I'm the
clown here. I pay hands. We watched three movies and one three stooges TV show. I don't know when
you got here, but you probably don't hear him in the third movie, dude. We watched. We we watched
three. The leech counts, even though we skipped 30 minutes. It counts blueberry juice. Thanks for 250.
Hey, pal. Hey, pal. I hate to do this to you, especially so I can tell you're having so much
fun, but I'm going to have to write you up for a SUI. That's right. Streaming under the influence.
I mean, we can all have fun here or there, but deleting your save. It's fine if chat does it,
but you're the designated driver of this stream, not us. No, the only way to pay this off is if you
raid rift tracks, you know, considering you basically ripped off, you ripped off their entire
career. Mike Nelson's fucking Mike Nelson's a huge influence on my life. You got it. Are they live?
But we have worried somebody else. I've read it rift tracks like last week. They're fucking
fantastic. They're great guys. Goobery. Thanks for the 250 again. No, that's a lie. It's the same
message. Dr. Clay. Thanks for $5. If you ever do this again, please green screen yourself in the
lower right as a silhouette. That would really be copying Mike Nelson and those MST 3K guys. So I
don't know if I want to do that. Hey, crunch $3 from crunch PS. If we're talking older movies,
uh, not sure if you're into the universal monsters, but in my opinion, the invisible man
from 1933 is the absolute best universal monster movie they put out. I wish it were public domain
because I think it would be a great fun watch with everyone. It's too bad. Regardless, uh,
it's not an obscure recommendation, but I'd still recommend it to everyone who hasn't seen it.
It's one of my favorite movies in general, actually. Thanks again. I wish it was in public
domain. We'd watch it right now. God damn it. Hey hatchet. Thanks for $3. Thanks for the very
fun night. Hope we get to watch some Charlie Chaplin next time. Probably. We watched three
stooges this time. Why not next time? West you'll thousand bits, $10 German. I'm watching this in
VR with my best friends. Why would you watch this in VR? We're all major fans. PS, did you get your
haircut? Doesn't look like Lego hair. No, I smeared it back on the back of my head. It's just greasy
and smeared back. Don't be fooled. Hey Keith King Crimson. Thanks for $2.50. Hey German. Fun fact.
Bella Lugosi is alive and well and he's in my house right now. Okay. Um, I hope you guys have fun.
Hey Joe mount. Thanks for $5. German. Are you excited to be 80 plus years old and streaming
shitty video games? That's not going to happen. That's not going to happen. I can guarantee you.
Hey stream beyond. Thanks for $3. What do you do with bits in this? I'm not going to fucking be
live at 80. I got my golden years guys. Give me a break. What do you do with bits in this stream?
Is it some kind of currency thing? Thanks for the fun stream today and all the laughs you've
brought. Just so you know, the people who made who killed captain Alex made another movie.
That's also free. I've seen that one too. I've seen the sequel. Unfortunately, we can't watch
it here. I've seen it. Uh, cast lion. Thanks for $3. German on the topic of Bella Lugosi. I,
can we stop talking about this guy? You should watch Bella Lugosi meets a Brooklyn gorilla.
No, no, we're not, we're not talking about him anymore. Uh, I own you. I own you. You. Thanks
for $3. German actor died movie. Hey, he X in X. Thanks for $3. Thanks for the free bucks. I
still can't believe you deleted. By the way, I can't believe you. Uh, the whole stream has been
a blast. By the way, Bella Lugosi died. Laugh about it. I can't. Tana King. Thanks for the $15.
Why didn't they need the language computer when talking in person? I don't know. The movie's
terrible. Hey, Sculptor. Thanks for $5. German. You should watch the movie Ed Wood by Tim Burton.
It's a great comedy biopic about Ed Wood's life. In it, you learn that Bella Lugosi actually died
before the movie was completed and they, Bella Lugosi is dead. Yes. Hey, you posted cringe, bro.
Thanks for the thousand bits. Uh, I recommended Little Shop of Horrors for the next one. Although
Vinny might've already watched it on stream. Also F in the chat for Bella Lugosi. Yeah, let's see
him. The guy died like 40 years ago. F in the chat for him, I guess. I don't know. Uh, Medi Miren.
Thanks for the $5. German. It's test time. I hope you've been studying question one.
What happened to Bella Lugosi during plan nine? He died and they filmed it anyways and he's dead.
Thanks for the $5. Uh, Shibururu. Thanks for $3. Chat clearly loves Lugosi. Cheers to him.
I'm sure he'd germ a heart for all the love. Also all the people freaking out about freaks.
That movie's too smart for their little minds, I guess. I didn't say it. He did. Hey, Flimflam.
Thanks for the $5. That website that has the Pink Panther movie states that their public domain.
Gotta get that confirmed before I do that. I would do it. Neuro Gasly. 500 bits from Neuro Gasly. Hey
man, in case you didn't know, Bella Lugosi isn't actually dead. He was pretending I was there. I
was also the gorilla. That's good to know. Thanks for the fucking $5. Uh, Myriad. Thanks for $15.
No message. Just a huge amount of money. Thanks for 15 bucks. Uh, Glumrot. Thanks for $3. German.
I just came from my friend's goth DJ set and he can't get it to work. Can you help him come
to unplug it and plug it back in? If not, then tell him to, uh, just sell it all. Hey, uh, Vibio
game. Thanks for $5. Movie night was an absolute blast. Thanks for so much. Fantastic streams.
I'm semi delirious from laughing. Looking forward to the next time you do this.
Me too. It'll be fun. Uh, thank you. Bella Lugosi's ghost for the $5. Wow. Must've made
that name five seconds ago. Hey, German. I heard you enjoyed my final movie. Hope you can watch
more of them in the future. Cool. Thanks for the $5. Bella Lugosi's ghost guy that made this
fucking username 10 minutes ago. Uh, Spooge. Thanks for $3. Hey, I've been lurking recently
and haven't been super active in chat, but I'm glad to have these streams to keep us all company
during these lockdown hours. Loving it every day. By the way, when's the next FTK stream?
Are you going to play Resident Evil 3? Uh, FTK is currently being developed. It's going to be fun.
This is going to be events. It will return. I promise. I just don't have a date.
Resident Evil 3. Uh, streamer is going to lie to you. Streamer is lying to you. Hey, Evangelion.
Thanks for the $2.50. Did you know Dick Rubin is dead? He did props for 99 movies in his life,
including Sex Kittens Go to College. That's not porn, by the way. Weird title for a not porn movie.
He was responsible for those terrible garbage leeches. IMTV is amazing. Anyway, he's dead.
Isn't that interesting? Oh, and he worked on some Star Trek, I guess. I guess. Thanks for the $2.50.
Uh, thanks Sturdy Bread for the $2.50. Dr. Clay's suggestion was created in sub chat.
There is an MST 3K silhouette of Yu, Shito, and Beanbag Sonic. Jesus Christ. He's in hell.
Don't say that! Worm Club, thanks for $2.50. Hey, Jerma, I love Moominite. You should, yeah.
You and chat seem to like comedies the most. Please consider Buster Keaton's Shurran Jr.
It actually entered public domain this year and is full of Keaton's insane stunts,
one of which almost killed him. Okay. Oh, by the way, Bella Lugosi is dead. I didn't know.
Thanks for asking. Cigar and a waffle, thanks for $5. I can't stop watching your streams,
but I really don't like you. What the fuck are you doing here? Go watch Fucking Breaking Bad.
I don't get out of here. What are you doing here? Jerma put sun chips in F tier and I would again.
Just so you know, thanks for $2.50. I was able to successfully free Bella Lugosi from King Crimson's
home. Please call the cops. I can hear his footsteps behind me and that person. Uh, Alomar
waffle. Thanks for $3. Thanks for the tons of laughs. As always, please look into how public
domain works before you get banned. It's fucking, it's not illegal. What are you talking about?
Hey, you posted cringe, bro. Thanks for five more dollars. Uh, Lella Bogosi was born before
the movie was completed. Funny fucking comment. Hey Johnny, nice mountains. Thanks for $5. Why
are you making a mockery of Bella Lugosi's recent passing? He died like 40 years ago. Thanks for the
$5. Uh, Cthulhu Katamari. Thanks for the $3. Hey Jerma, love the stream. Fun fact, Bella Lugosi
never actually existed. He was just a green screen. Thanks for the three bucks. Uh, Fritz in the house.
Thanks for $6. 66 fucking Satan money. I love the stream. Felt like we were all a part of an episode
of best of the worst. I really like to see more of the mystery films. I love seeing the chat lose
their minds as it played out. Me too. Hey, to address the subs, please. We had some subs here.
We had a lot of subs to dress them. He's drunk. I mean, did you need a fucking scientist to tell
you that one? I could have told you that 10 minutes ago. What are you talking about? Uh,
thanks for the subs, everybody. Appreciate all the continued support. You guys fucking spoil the shit
out of me. Here they come. Thank you. Hope you enjoyed movie night one. Movie night two will
definitely happen. Just not now. That was a ton of fun. I even, I had some drinks. It was a blast.
I would fucking do it all over again. A million times. Thanks for staying around. Thanks for
hanging out. We do have a few more hits to do. Uh, Johnny nice mountains. Thanks for $5. Why are
you making a mockery out of Bela Lugosi's recent passing? I'm not. Uh, I didn't even know he died
30 years ago. Thanks for $5. Uh, I already read that one by the way. Hey, Skizzoy. Thanks for $5.
You should check out the goth band Bajas. Their most popular song is called Bela Lugosi's Dead.
I think you'd like it. Great. Maybe. Hey, Goo Berry Juice. Thanks for $4.50. Sir, this theater
doesn't tolerate noise pollution and drinking, so I'm afraid I have to ask you to leave.
However, I can't believe I deleted the fucking save. We are obligated to give you a movie
fun fact before we evict you from the premises. Bela Lugosi didn't delete his Jump King save file
on stream. Now please take your monthly bath. I'm, yeah, I can't fucking believe I did that.
That's so stupid. I spent like so many hours on that. Hey, Jay Bum Bum. Thanks for the three
fucking Jesus. Germa, I said you were a greasy teen. Not that you had greasy teeth.
I apologize. Your teeth are pristine and perfect. Just like you, babe. This stream was amazing and
I'm excited for the next one. The next movie night I recommend Neil Breen. His movies are all
on YouTube. Sage the Ghost. Thanks for $5. Please will you cut your own hair on stream?
It, they say do it for Lugosi. I don't fucking know who that guy was. I don't, I didn't know him.
Thanks for the five bucks. Hey, $3 from, uh, Peridotty. Thanks for the three bucks. Germa,
me and my boyfriend and watch your streams and vlogs. I gotta get out of here. I gotta get out
of here. I'm out of here. Uh, I just want to say thanks for the laughs. We love you. Also,
can you say hi Chris? Yes. Hi Chris. I'm not going to cut my hair on stream. Oh,
this is fucking funny. Uh, Hey Chris, I'm glad you to watch the streams and one more. No, seriously.
Thank you for watching. Anybody that watches, I fucking thanks a lot. Agent Dark booty. Thanks
for the $5. Streaming goes to theater, gets drunk and rants about Bell Lugosi's death.
I didn't, you did and I read it. Hey, steer, steal, a steal. Thanks for $5. Jeremy,
I've watched you for so long without donating. You are pretty cool for a guy named Jeremy. What's
the fucking, what's that supposed to mean? Steel. What do you mean? You know, are the Jeremy's that
suck. I'm a cool art. I'll see you guys on Monday. Thanks for watching. I had so much fun. I hope you
did too. We're going to raid. It's a, it's a, it's a Friday night. Who are we rating? Not rift tracks.
Give me some names. Give me some names. Name, name, name, name, name, name, name.
That's a bad, that was the front page of Twitch talent. Criken, Criken, Bernie Sanders, critical,
Vinny. Who have we never rated before? I want someone we'd never rated. Never. Who's Greg? I
don't know what the fuck Greg is. What are you talking about? I do a guy with, no, not Bernie's
not live. What are you talking about? I've rated Nova a bunch of times. Nova's awesome. We've rated
critical. Who have we not rated before? Let's say, let's say who's playing games. Who's playing
Nintendo games? I'm a Nintendo streamer guys. Who's playing Nintendo games right now?
See, wait a minute. Wait a minute. Who's playing fucking Mario? I want to, I want a Mario streamer
and that's it. Mario. Who's playing Mario? Mario. Why? Because Sue, I want to, I want to
rate a Super Mario fucking. Somebody's playing Super Mario. Bela Lugosi is dead. I can't rate
him. I can't fucking, can't believe I'm saying this. Okay. We've got, let's take a look down.
Discover list. Nope. Categories. Okay. Minecraft. Nope. Animal Crossing. No, thanks.
Mario Maker 2. No, thanks. I mean, the game's good. Mario Kart 8.
Mario Tennis. Top decision. Mario Tennis. Mario 64. Lugosi streaming Mario right now. Jesus Christ.
Imagine. Mario Galaxy 2. Who's playing Mario Galaxy 2? 24 hour stream. Mizkif is playing Mario.
All right. Here we go. You ready? We're going to raid Mizkif. Let's go. Let's go for it. Let's go.
What do you mean no? What? What are you vetoing? What? I'm getting vetoed. What the fuck is going
on? What? Cancel. What the fuck? Don't do it. I've already done it. What? I'm missing bits.
Where are their bits? Oh, shit, I did. He's playing Mario Galaxy 2. What's the fucking problem? What?
He's currently arguing with people on stream. I feel like I do that too.
What's going on? Read my bits. All right. Holy shit. Skulper. Thanks for $5.
Remember to answer your question to me and my friends. We're watching in VR
so we can hang out while we do it. Also love the stream. Lugosi for Rumble.
I don't even know what he looks like. Johnny. Nice mountains. Thanks for $5.
I saw a picture of you and Bella Lugosi at Comic-Con. You both shaking hands while you stare
creepily into the camera. I don't fucking even know who that is. All right. Go fucking dumped.
Just go tell italics to fuck himself. Let's go. Why is everybody losing their fucking minds over
this? Getting vetoed by the chat. What the fuck? Look at Mario streamers. No, don't do that. He
kills people. What? No, don't actually say go fuck yourself. Just be nice. Do you read chat? I just
read it. All right. I'll see you guys on Monday. Take care. It was a lot of fun. I had a blast.
Thanks for watching, as always. It was a ton of fun. Thanks for participating. Go tell italics
that he's a fucking swell guy. Wait, he's ending the stream? Oh, fuck. He's ending.
Cancel. Cancel. Don't go to italics. Cancel. Don't go to italics stream. We're going to go.
Oh, god damn it. He's ending his stream. What the fuck? All right. Hold on. Who else is streaming?
Go to uber hack zone over. He's a fucking good dude. Let's go. Fucking he's a good dude. Let's go.
He's ending his stream right now. Oh, god. All right. Nova's a good dude. He's funny. You'll
like him. He's doing GTRP. Good night. Goodbye. See you Monday. Same spot. Same exact spot.