I can't put it on here. What the fuck? What the fuck? Oh, hold on. I think I got it.
There we go. All right. All right. Let's do a bread tier list. Look up the ending.
I don't... true endings. I don't need true ending. That doesn't have to be true ending.
All right, let's get it. Bread tier list.
Oh, it's just small. My windows always get so fucked up.
Okay. So this is a very important tier list for a lot of you, I think.
Um, I can see it better. All right, I'm gonna... I'm quitting this. We don't need to be in here
anymore. This is... that game was really cool. It was really like just a chill game.
I liked it a lot. All right, bread tier list. I'm ready. Put on Olive Garden music for this.
Actually kind of a fucking good idea. There's a lot on this list. All right, right there.
That's where it is. All right, let's make it a little bigger. All right, you guys ready?
The quintessential bread tier list. Sourdough's number one.
What the fuck?
Oh my god. No, it's not. I want that person timed out. I actually want you timed out.
Uh, can we make this IRL? I need music though. You're right.
Uh, Garden... Olive Garden music? Olive Garden theme song. Club remix? It's a club remix.
Why is there a club remix of this? This is a club remix. This is Olive Garden?
I don't think this is even the Olive Garden. Okay, here we go. Bagel. That's a straight up A.
Bagel can be used as a sandwich topping. Can be used as a breakfast, as a lunch, as a dinner.
You can do bagels and lox. You can do bagels, eggs, and cheese. You can do bagel tuna sandwich.
Versatility. Hawaiian roll. S. Hawaiian roll S. 100%. No fighting me on that one. Hawaiian rolls
are S. S. If you buy a bag of Hawaiian rolls, you better be ready for that bag to be gone
within a day. Within one day. They don't last long. You will never take a bag of Hawaiian rolls
and turn it like this and go, is that mold? Oh no, there's like eight. There's like how many
slices are in there? One, two, three, four, five. I think that's mold. Nope. Never gonna happen.
It's gone every time. Oatmeal bread. Yeah. Okay. Rye bread. Uh, it's a D. Unless it's with a
Reuben sandwich and then it becomes a B. Brioche? A. Bagels are better. A whole wheat bread? I guess
it's an F. I fucking hate wheat bread. It sucks. I feel... I know. I... When anytime anybody says,
hey, whiter wheat. I go, bro, white every time. Like I don't like wheat bread. I just don't.
It just makes it taste different. It tastes... Bread to me is texture and a little bit of flavor.
Whole wheat bread changes like the flavor of a sandwich. Sure. I don't care. Call me whatever
you want. Banana bread. This is a very close to S. I'm not sure I want to put this in S. I'm gonna
put it in A. It depends. There's really shitty banana bread and there's really great banana bread.
There's banana breads that are dog shit, but if you get a moist, a dense moist banana bread,
wow, that's absolute A+. Cornbread is also the same. There's a lot of really shitty cornbread.
Dry cornbread. If you get the real good stuff, this might level up. Maybe. Depends. I think it's...
I think so. Cinnamon bread. F. I'm sorry. I just don't like it. I am not a fan of cinnamon.
You all know that. Everybody knows that at this point. This channel has been... This channel
started with me hating cinnamon. I don't really like cinnamon as a condiment, as a seasoning. I'm
not a fan. I actually don't think it belongs... These actually probably both don't belong in F,
but... Are people saying quackity? What do you mean quackity? What? Oh, they gifted subs.
What's up, quackity? Anyways, we're doing good takes here. Croissants. Croissants are an S for
flavor, but an F for practicality. Eating a croissant, you have to vacuum your shirt.
What is this song? This is not Olive Garden. Yeah, when you eat croissants, they're delicious,
but you literally have to vacuum your clothes afterwards. Hold on. I'll put it in the right
spot. I need some restaurant music. Here we go. There we go. That's more Olive Garden.
Croissant is F for malleability, mandible ability, whatever it's called.
We're talking flavor only, and I have like a tray underneath that I can catch the croissant
crumbles. I'm going to give it an A. Biscuits. Some biscuits, they're dry as fuck a lot of times,
but you know what? I'm going to have to... People are going to be mad about this,
but I'm going to give it a B. I already know where this is going, so I need to do this now.
Let's get this out of the way, because people are going to be mad. English muffins are horrible.
English muffins just have a bad taste. I don't like it. I don't really... I really don't like
English muffins. English muffins to me taste like somebody made a bagel biscuit, like a biscuit,
and they put a droplet of artificial bread flavoring on it. I don't know. I don't like
the taste. It tastes like baby powder. When I bite into an English muffin, it's like baby powder.
Okay, a McDonald's sausage egg McMuffin. Yeah, I'd eat it. That brings it up to here,
but I really don't like English muffins. I'm sorry. I just don't.
I don't... What is it? What is yeast bread? What is that? Yeast bread? Isn't that just bread? I kind
of don't really know what that is, so I'm going to... What is it? Just bread? Bagels are failed
donuts. They're vile creations. A bagel is amazing. A bagel is versatile. I'm just going to... I don't
know what to put this on. Potato bread. Yes. Potato bread is everything I like about white bread,
but it's not just default shitty white bread, right? But I like default shitty white bread.
I don't think it's better than Hawaiian roll, but I think potato bread is like... If you want
white bread, potato bread is like the cool version. I love potato bread. It's fantastic.
Not only does this have cinnamon in it, it has gross raisins too.
This is going down here. Cinnamon raisin bread. No, I'm just not into it. Where's white bread? Let's
do it. White bread is like a B. No, white bread is like a C. I probably would rather eat white
bread than oatmeal bread though, because what even... What is oatmeal bread? I don't like
cinnamons. I don't like cinnamons, like raisins and shit. I don't like that. Flat bread is... It's
all right. It's good for like little sandwich rolls and everything. Tortilla. Flour tortilla.
Is corn tortilla on here? Well, that wouldn't be bread, would it? Okay, but this is S. I love
tortilla. A good flour tortilla. Cook it on the stove. Oh yeah. Hell yeah. Absolutely. So good.
So good. Sourdough. Sourdough is... I would say it kind of reminds me of
biting into something like... You know why I don't like sourdough bread? Here's why. That's why.
Every piece of sourdough I've ever had feels like that. Oh, wow. Oh, sourdough. Oh my god,
it's so fresh. I can feel it in my mouth. I have to bite down hard. No. The sourdough flavor
is up here. I'm willing to forgive sourdough for being like tough and chewy. Plus too, it still
fucks though. Why are you fucking bread? What are you talking about? I'd say it's... I'm going to
give it a B. I think it tastes good. It's better than white bread. Garlic bread. Oh, garlic bread.
Garlic bread's... But that's just a meme answer though. Do I really think garlic bread's better
than like banana bread? Okay, is garlic bread better than cornbread? I don't think so. I mean,
I love garlic bread, but is it better than like a good moist banana bread? Probably not. Or a good
bagel? Like a fresh bagel. God, if you get a fresh bagel from like a bagel factory, one of those like
bagel factories restaurants where they make the bagels there and they're fresh and you get it hot
right in the morning, I think it's better. I do. French bread is in the same category as croissant.
It's another bread that when you take a bite out of it, you need like a little dirt devil to vacuum
your like crotch because it just gets everywhere, but it's fucking unbelievable. I think it's better
than croissant. I think it's better than brioche too. French bread just like is garlic bread just
with stuff on it. So what is it? Does it really matter where it goes? Whole grain bread is at the
very bottom. I would rather eat cinnamon raisin bread off the ground than eat a piece of whole
grain bread. It's awful. I know. Oh, you're like, you have like a 10 year old's palette.
Whole grain bread sucks and everybody knows it. You don't bite into whole like all like the weird
like nuts and shit. I don't like the plastic tasting things. It's like the big chunks of like
grains and like little like seeds on it. It's like, it's like bird food to me. It's like bird seed
all over it. I don't like it. It's got bird seed all over it. I don't like whole grain bread. I
think it's bad. Pretzel bread is up here. In fact, pretzel bread is better than Hawaiian rolls.
I might come back to that in a minute. I might come back to this in just a moment,
but pretzel bread could be the best thing in the world. Bread-wise, I think. We'll see. I can change
it if I need to. Well, okay, potato bread is not a 10 year old palette. That's like pretty
sophisticated. Hawaiian rolls, that's a sophisticated palette. Pita bread's pretty good. I think it's
like a B. I love gyros, so pita bread's usually pretty fantastic. This with hummus is fantastic.
I don't think I would put it up here though. I mean, breadsticks are fine, but they're fine.
I like breadsticks. I don't think they're better than like a croissant. Actually,
yeah. I probably, okay, do I, would I rather have a breadstick or a pita bread?
Probably a breadstick. I might have to reevaluate this in a minute in a little bit here. We'll see.
All right, this is the bread from Outback. We know where that's going. Up here somewhere.
But okay, pumpernickel bread and croissants are the exact same in my brain. I need to be
in the mood to eat a croissant. I don't just like, oh, you know what? Yeah, I'll have a croissant
today. That'd be a reason why I get it, why I eat it. Pumpernickel is like, I have to have a reason
to eat it. I don't go to the store and go like, oh yeah, yeah, where's the pumpernickel bread?
No, I usually get like potato bread or the stick of white bread or even a wheat bread sometimes.
Is the bread from Outback? Yeah, it is good. That's why it's an A. It's up an A tier. What
are you talking about? Outback bread is white bread painted brown. Is it really? No, it's not.
What is the bread from Outback? It's not pumpernickel? What is the bread at Outback?
What is the bread at Outback made out of? Honey and molasses wheat bread roll.
But no, wheat bread sucks. Wait, that's a honey and molasses. Honey and molasses wheat bread roll.
Not just generic ass wheat bread. No, they're both going down here. Fuck them both.
Fuck them both. Who cares? Non is up at A, high A. To me, a non is like a pita bread, but like
evolved. Pita bread's like the squirtle and non is like the squirrel mo, whatever his name is,
whatever. Non is just like kind of upgraded pita bread. I don't think it's better than garlic,
but it actually might be. Maybe. Pumpernickel, I like pumpernickel. Why is it down here?
It's definitely like up here. It'd be zucchini bread. I don't know. That's some TikTok shit.
I don't want it. Butter bread and butter bread. What is it? What are these? I don't think I've
had these before. I don't think I've eaten butter bread. I don't think I've had it.
Where would I have eaten this? My grandmother makes zucchini bread, dude. That's not TikTok shit.
I don't know. It's zucchini bread? The Chick-fil-A minis are butter bread. I don't, I don't,
I can't think of, I can't remember what it tastes like. What it is like, right? All right, let me
make sure this is correct. Pretzel bread, yep. Wine roll, this is tough. Yeah, this is right.
I think my S tier is right. A good fresh French roll, though. God damn it, it's good. I'm trying
to think of like biting into like a moist, delicious, savory, aromatic piece of banana
bread. You know what I mean? The kind of bread where you can go like this with the bread,
squish it and you let go and it does not come back to form factor. It's squished. It's fucking
squished. Oh, that changed my mind. No, cornbread or flour tortilla. I feel like brioche is just
better than most of these somehow, right? But I don't know. I love bagels so much. I can eat
bagels, breakfast, breakfast, lunch. Why can't I say the K in breakfast? I could eat a bagel,
breakfast, lunch and dinner and be happy about it. Here's the exact same tier list from a year
and a half ago that you did. What? Are you serious? I did this already? This is my list?
I did this already? So what does it look like? Oh, someone's got a screenshot. Here we go. Wait,
hold on. I need to compare. Let's compare it. It's pretty fucking close, guys. It's pretty close.
It's pretty close. It's close, man. Hold on. If I were to stop this right now, right? Let's overlay
it. Yo, this is pretty much the same. This is pretty good. What's not up here? Croissant is
up at S now. Potato bread, potato bread. Pretzel bread, pretzel bread. Croissant. I must have had
a shitty croissant. I must add a shitty croissant. You know, at some point over the last two years,
I probably bit into a croissant and went fuck and got pissed. That is what happened.
Banana bread. Yeah, I must have had a really moist banana bread. Biscuit. Biscuits. Whoa,
it took a nose dive here. Pita bread took a dive. Then flatbread took a dive. Cornbread evolved.
White bread kind of jumped up. Oatmeal bread. Okay, but yeah, but remember, all these things
that are in D, I was afraid to piss off like the bread andies in chat, right? So I couldn't make
them F. Where's garlic bread on this? Wow, garlic bread was a fucking C. I stand by my list. You did
this exact same list already. I'm kind of curious. What does somebody... I did a fast food one.
Are my tastes kind of the same? You were wearing the same shirt. I was? No, I wasn't. You just
did the fast food. What's another one that I've done? What's some of the popular ones? It's like
candy, soda, chips and stuff, right? What's one that I haven't done in a while that I have done
to see if... Because I don't remember. I don't remember anything. Cheese's baby food. You did
fruits before. Pumpkin bread. I don't like it. You did the same grin. You didn't do cookie run
characters yet. All right, so should I... What's another one? This is done. I'm happy with this.
Should I do like soda, candy? Is there a good candy one? I've been eating a shitload of candy
lately. Should I do a candy or something? What do you think? I've been eating a lot of candy. I've
been really into candy lately. Do alcohol? I could do that. I don't even need a tier list. Vodka,
S, everything else fucking like F, besides like whiskey at like an A. Beer, F. Wine, like A. There
you go. Is there a good candy one? You did candy in 2020. Okay, so it's been about two years. I
don't remember what I did. So is there a good candy one? Give me a good candy one. He have two
unusual hats. I don't even know. Guys, I've seen like three unusual hats my whole life. Have you
eaten much candy since then? Yeah, I think so. There's a candy tier list right here. Let's check
it out. Vodka, is that so? Yeah, because vodka goes with like almost everything. That's the only reason
why. I like whiskey too, but vodka is like easier for me to drink. I don't really drink that much
hard alcohol. Usually it's just a wine or like champagne or something, right? Okay, candy.
Let me put it down. Okay, how long is this? This is gonna take like an hour. This is gonna take like
a fucking hour, isn't it? This doesn't feel complete. Is this complete? What do you guys think?
Is there more on here that should be on here? No, this looks pretty complete. Is it the same
one that I did? I think this looks kind of complete. What's it missing? Looks pretty good.
Looks good. Okay, let's start at the with the easy stuff that I know. Um, Reese's Pieces are an A,
although eating more than like what? What's touching my leg? What? I honestly got there was
like a fucking thing on my leg. What was that? Okay, uh, Reese's Pieces are pretty good. I would
say they're A. I would say Twizzlers are D or F. D is fine. We can use it as F. Twizzlers are gross.
There's only one kind of Twizzler I like and it's the ones where you peel, you peel the Twizzlers.
Those are pretty good. Bazooka Gum. If you can find one that isn't as hard as a rock,
that's, I'd say that's pretty solid B. A hundred grand. I remember the commercials where they'd
say, what would you do with a hundred grand? I'd eat it. So that gets a B for like funny commercial.
No, it doesn't. Let's just get this out of the way. Reese's the best candy. Reese's are the best
candy. There's no, I honestly, I don't think there's any argument to be made. There really isn't.
No, there is no argument to make. It's the best candy. It's the best chocolate candy.
You know what else? I'm going to give Reese's a little bit of credit here. They also haven't
changed shit. There's been no new recipe for Reese's. It's the same goddamn shit it was like
50 years ago. Think about it. Remember, think about the things that you think about that go like,
oh man, back in the nineties when like it tasted better and they used like fucking whatever.
It's the same. This has not changed in like fucking 40 years. Sour Patch Kids. Nah,
I don't like these. They're, I like eating like one or two. I like them, but I just, I only want
like two. I really only want like two. I'll keep it in B for now. I know they're good. I like them,
but I just don't, I don't want to eat like a whole bag. Bubble Tape is A. If you can find it,
it's amazing. Although it does have like the weird like baby powder shit on it.
I'll keep it for now. I love it though. Sweet Tarts. Are these the, yep, those are S. Absolutely,
100%. Sweet Tarts are so delicious. They're so yummy. I can eat a Sweet Tart and it's the same
exact thing. Sweet Tarts are Sour Patch Kids, but good. Sweet Tarts are like Sour Candy, Sour Patch
Kids. They're just like a better version in my brain than a Sour Patch Kid. I just feel that way.
Fun Dip is also kind of, I can only do it once or twice. It's good, but I don't know. I'll keep it
in B for now. Mike and Ike's, I don't, there's just no reason to eat them. Original Tootsie Rolls.
These are, they're, they're not, I don't know. They're kind of just the, Heath Bar is like a C
or a B, but if it's part of ice cream, it's S. Like Heath Bar Crunch Ice Cream, S+. I'd say it's
probably, I'm going to give it a high B. I like it. Warheads, again, like I just like Sweet Tarts
better. I don't, I don't know. They're good, but you can, you only eat one. After you eat more than
one, it's like, you're going to fucking, I feel like I'm going to throw up. I'll put it C. Kit Kats
are up high. Come around A. I'll fix it. Andy's Mints, S+, tried and true for like 500 years.
I may have changed my opinion on this. I don't remember what I gave this like two or three years
ago, but Andy's Mints have been tried and true, delicious, perfect. It's a perfect serving size.
You only need like one of them, one or two, just one or two. That's it. And it's completely
satisfying. It's a perfect combination of chocolate, mint. It's perfect. It's S. In fact, now that I
know what's right next to Sweet Tarts here, this is A. This is only for the most prestigious candy.
And Andy's are up there as, as probably, you know what? No, how dare you even get your,
get your hand away from there. How dare you? I like just reached it. I just got like slapped
by like mom going to get like the food. Okay. Three Musketeers. I'm going to shock a lot of you with
this one. This is a high A. The fluffy, the fluffy nougat in the middle. Oh, it's so good.
It's so fluffy and so like just puffy and fluffy. So yummy. So good. I love it. A plus.
It's literally air. What are these? Are these, are these, what are these gummies? What are those?
These are Swedish fish. They are Swedish fish, aren't they? F. I don't get this. I don't think
I ever will. I don't understand why people like these. Don't, I really don't like them at all.
They're just like kind of slimy and like chewy. I don't get it. I just, I honestly just don't get
it. I know that that's the worst take I've had, but man, these are just not good. I just, this is
not good. They're fruity. Yeah, but like I would rather just have gummy bears. The Haribo gummy,
are the Haribo gummy bears on here? Because those, they're just a way better version of these.
Like a hundred times better. I mean like 100 times better. It's like the same thing in my head.
Are they on? There they are. Yeah. Yeah. Haribo gummy bears are, wait, these are big ones. I'm
going to take these as just like the little ones. These are perfect. Yeah. These are like, hey,
these are great. Yeah. Swedish fish, you chew, you chew them up. And then after like 10 to 20
minutes, you realize that you have this like, like weird, like red, like cement paste that's aligning
all of your gums. It's like, no, I don't know. I don't like it. I don't think there's any list
that you'll ever see that has peeps higher than an F4D. If somebody genuinely had peeps up here,
I'm, I'm, I'm, I'm a little concerned. I think I'm concerned about them. I don't think anybody
puts these up here. I could see how people could put them like here, but an S, I mean,
I don't know what you're talking about. How would that be possible? No, I don't think anybody puts
them up there. Peeps are A, yeah, but not S. If you put peeps in S tier, I don't know about that.
Dots F. Okay. All you Swedish fish Andes, what's the difference between dots and fish besides the
squished mold that is the fish mold for the candy? What's the difference? I explained. You all say
dots are the worst candy. Everybody knows dots is the worst candy, but Swedish fish are just like
flattened out dots. Huh? The shape is important. Do you like dinosaur chicken nuggets more than
regular chicken nuggets? What are you talking about? Yes. These also suck. They just, it's just,
it takes forever. I don't like the appeal. They're better than peeps. No, they're not. Actually,
I'd rather eat a peep. It's just, no. Who is going to spit this shit out and eat it later?
Do you rinse it under the sink? After you suck on this thing for like three hours,
do you spit it out and like rinse it under the sink and put it in like a bag? I don't know.
Twix, that's going up here. I've had Twix before that were really like pillowy and delicious,
but I have to be honest. I've had Twix before that were kind of stale. They're like the,
it's just something, something's off. You know what I mean? Something's off. I've had that
experience a few times. Razzlers? Holy shit. I just, I gotta remember these being good. Sweet
tarts. They're on the same level. This is the candy necklace. That's up there too. Pretty like
a high B. York pep man patties. That's up there too. These are phenomenal. It's that perfect like
ice. Okay. I think of, I think of a commercial when you bite into a York pep man patty and it's like,
I hear that. I hear like a, and I think of like snow being around me. It's perfect.
Airheads are all right. They're, I don't know if I put airheads, maybe I put them like here.
I don't think I would rather, I'd rather have a Kit Kat than an airhead. I'm way more chocolate
oriented than I am like sweet fruit sugary kind of oriented. Look at this list with the exception
of like sweet tarts. Like most of my stuff up here is like chocolate mint, chocolate, chocolate,
chocolate, chocolate, chocolate. I, I, it's all right. It's all right. I like it. I don't know.
Why is this even on here? I don't even know what a baby Ruth tastes like. I just noticed a shit
load of peanuts. So I don't, I don't think I've had it. Uh, lifesavers are pretty good. I actually,
it's not on here, I don't think, but I prefer the like mint spear mint lifesavers over the fruity
ones. Can I pretend that these are the mint ones? You know, I talk about the little individually
packaged, um, mint spearmint ones. Oh, that's amazing. This is so good. The mint ones are
better. Okay. I'm just going to pretend these are the mint ones. This is okay. This is that candy
that's in that group of candy that's at every gas station that's in the bags. And it's like just all
the weird oddity like circus shit, right? There's all this, uh, the gas station has this one row of
just like with these weird bag candies. And I'm not a big fan. Circus peanuts. Yeah, circus peanuts
are okay. I actually kind of like eating one and going like, yeah, I remember that's what that is.
And then I never eat another one ever again. I don't think they just, they don't belong down
here. Hmm. Okay. Just general Hershey's bar. I mean, it's part of one of my favorite desserts
ever, which is s'mores, but by itself, like, I mean, there's, there's other things I would rather
have. A Hershey bar is fine. It's fine. But if you have Kit Kat available, that's at the same rack,
I'm going to, I'm going to get Kit Kat. If you have three musketeers and Hershey's right next
to each other, I'm never going to take the Hershey bar ever. But if you were like, Hey man,
do you want some chocolate? I got Hershey's. I'd be like, yeah, sure. That's fine. Sounds good.
That sounds fine. But I don't think it's probably C. Um, hot, hot tamales. This is like the hot, uh,
cinnamon candy. I'd actually probably rather eat this than candy corn. Cinnamon, like can't, no,
thanks. S'mores are the only place Hershey's are good. Yeah. I mean, you're right, but it's one of
the reasons why it's so good, right? What are these? These, are these nerds? S. Nerds are S.
And again, another reason why you're probably seeing a pattern up here.
The nerds formula has never changed. It's the same formula it's been since like a
nineteen fucking hundred, since like 1830 or whatever, when these were invented, they have
never changed. They've been exactly the same and they're really good. They're gross. I like them.
I think they're good. Ring pop is fine. I probably put it over here. It's just like a lollipop,
whatever. It's just, it's a lollipop that's shaped in an interesting way. They're okay. Fireball,
again, gross cinnamon candy. That's like just hot, like cinnamon fireball kind of, you know,
thank you. Milky way is just three musketeer, but way worse, but it's not that bad. It's good.
It's just not, it doesn't even, not even come close to me. Doesn't even come close. Three
musketeers are just like kind of like a whipped up kind of fluffy version and it's way better.
It's pocky. Is that pocky? No, these are candy cigarettes. Okay. These are gross. These are
actually really gross. Have you ever eaten a candy cigarette? It kind of reminds me of like
what plaster would taste like. I think it, you know, I know, no thanks. Pixie sticks. These are
all right. I'm going to put pixie sticks next to Fun Dip because they're literally the exact same
thing. There is no difference besides a stick that you lick. Nothing else is different. I would eat
it though. Some of these are going to be hard to place. I would say Starburst is S, but I don't
know. They kind of fell off for me. They kind of fell way down. Yeah, they fell way down for me.
I don't know why. Something about it. Something, I think, something about it. It's not really,
I don't really care. Smiders are great. I actually really enjoy these. Is it A though? It's probably
B. These are the same to me. I would put Smarties, Candy Necklace, and Pez right next to each other.
They're in the same like genre of video game kind of candy. You know what I mean? They're in the same
exact genre. Where's Pez? There it is. I think Pez is probably the best, but to me they're like,
they're in the same flavor profile. They're the same like movie genre. Like this is Jason, this
is Freddy, and this is like Michael Myers. You know what I mean? It's like they're the, I'm getting
the same thing out of it. Nestle Crunch. I feel like it's been a while, but I do remember eating
it. I'm thinking it was good. I think Crackle might be better. Is Crackle on here? Can I pretend this
is Crackle? I think Crackle actually might be better. What the fuck is Crackle? Crackle?
Is it the red wrapper? I think Crackle is better, but I think this is still good.
I don't think it's better than Kit Kat, but it's close. No it's not. Actually, you know what it is?
Actually it is. I think it is. All right, like Cookie Dough Bites. I don't think I've ever eaten
these. Fruit Gushers. Is this like a candy? Are Gushers candy or are they fruit snack? Right?
Isn't it? It's kind of a difference, isn't there? I don't like think Gushers are candy. I like them a
lot though. I don't like that you open the bag and you go take one out and like you get the like
the like streamer wall. You know what I mean? With all like the hexagons that are like
you get like the like hexagon streamer wall when you pull it out. It's all connected and shit.
I'd like to eat one at a time, but they're good. I'd rather have a gummy bear, but I actually do
like these. I think they're good. I know that's a gross take for a lot of people. They really
don't like that. People think Gushers are gross. When was the last time you had them?
Lemonheads are horrible, aren't they? But they're good. They're like they're here.
It's like this is like the same thing in my brain. Any candy where you put it in your mouth and you
go like like it's like the same thing. The same movie. It's the same like genre. It fits in the
same spot. I think they're okay. They're chewy, aren't they? These are the ones where they're
yellow and then when you like suck all the juice off them they turn into white like chewy little
balls, right? I got it right. After you like suck on them for a little while they turn these little
tiny white like wishy-chewy things. Soft outside, hard inside. I had it backwards. I haven't had
these in a while, but I do remember thinking they were pretty good. Bob Stoppers. I haven't really
had them. Tootsie Pops are like Hershey bars. They're fine. I would rather have something else.
Where are Tootsie Rolls? Did I put them up here? Where is it? There they are. I mean they're like
these are better than Tootsie Rolls because they're Tootsie Pops. So there's like a
there's more complex flavors going on, but I still would rather have something else.
Dolly Ranchers. These are these are up here. I'd say somewhere in A.
Tommy Bears are a little bit depends. What do you want out of your candy experience?
Do you want to just eat something and have it disappear and like that's it? That was delicious.
Move on to the next thing. Or do you want a little bit longer lasting experience? Do you want to eat
something that's going to last you more than one second? 10 seconds? These are the same to me.
This is just like extended delayed release tablets. These are like let's go right now.
Yeah, this is extended release tablets of the same thing. So I like them both.
It depends on how I feel. We got a Blow Pop, which are way better than Tootsie Pops. I can tell you
I have not had one in a long time, but I do remember them being phenomenal. Been a while.
Probably better than Gushers. Charleston Chew. What a legend. Speaking of Charleston Chew,
where the hell is it? Because that's up here. Where's Charleston Chew? Nope. I already know
what this is. It's like a gross coconut thing. Dum Dums. I'd rather have a Dum Dum than a Blow
Pop. They're just easier, quicker. Yeah, Charleston Chews are incredible in the freezer. They have to
be from the freezer though. They have to be. If a Charleston Chew is in the freezer, it's here
somewhere in this area. I don't know exactly where, but it's here. Life service are not that
high. This is going to need some re-combobulating here. Snickers are tried and true. It's kind of
exactly what you're looking for. Test of time. Been around for like 100 years. They've never
changed it. It's always just always good. Yeah, just always good. Especially the little ones.
Oh my god, I almost fell down. The little Snickers, the little individual little squares,
I think are better than the bars because they make sure that in the little squares,
it's the exact ratio of everything you want. It's a perfect singular bite of candy. The bar of Snickers
could, it's kind of, you never know what's going to be in there. You don't know what the ratio is
like. The little ones, oh yeah, you know exactly what you're getting in there. Absolutely. They're
up here. Thinking about making a change here. We'll see. M&Ms, they're all right. They're fine,
but this is just, if they're regular M&Ms, then like, whatever. Peanut butter M&Ms are up here.
Regular M&Ms, they're, they're, they're, they're reliable. They're reliable. Okay, the chocolate
inside of an M&M is better than the chocolate on the Hershey's. Like this, you just get like an
upgraded experience with the candy on the outside. Once you get in there, the chocolate's better,
it's a better chocolate. It tastes better. M&M's minis are S tier. Oh, you better believe it.
You better believe it. I think this is probably around here. Again, these fit in the same category.
Like do I want like the Reese's flavor, or do I want the M&M's flavor? One's not better than
the other for me. Razzlers get out of here. You don't belong up there. Bubble tape doesn't either.
Skittles are like, they fell off. Just like Starburst did. They're actually in the same place for
me. It's just, they kind of fell off for me. I'm not, I'm not a big fan anymore. They're almost like
too sugary. I know that like I have literally pure sugar up here, right? But something about
Skittles, they're almost like too sweet. It's like too sugary. I don't know why. Something about it.
I guess you could say this is like, this is the exact same thing, but even these like taste
different than this. It's like a different kind of sweetness. Uh, I'm gonna just, I don't, I think
these are the same, so I'm gonna put them here. Lifesavers, I'm gonna, where are lifesavers? If
they're in A, it's a mistake. Where are they? Where are they? Didn't I put other lifesavers up here?
Where'd they go? Bottom of A? All right, okay. Uh, wait, we're pretending that these are mint,
right? These are like the spirit ones. That's what we're pretending. Um, these are tropical ones. The
tropical ones are actually pretty good. I would put them somewhere here. They're okay. I would,
they're good. Hershey's Kisses are better than Hershey's. Again, it's, it's like, it's kind of
weird because the chocolate in a Hershey's Kiss tastes better than a Hershey bar. I don't know why
or how. I don't get it. And it's way better somehow. It is way better. Why? Why is that?
I can't give you a reason why. You just said shape doesn't matter. No, I told you that these are the
same thing, just different shapes. I also think they're gross. I don't think these are gross.
I think these are, I think chocolate's good. I think chocolate's good. I think these are gross.
Yeah, they could be different shapes as long as I think they taste good. That's fine.
They belong right here, right in the middle. Probably over-funned. Bazooka, what is Bazooka?
What is this doing up here? Yeah, it's called you chew up the gum for five seconds, read the comic
book and spit it out. Why was this up here? But that was, those comic books, those comics were
fire. How cool was that? A tiny little comic with like three or four, five panels. That's
fucking awesome. What a cool thing. That was really, the wrapper was a comic book. Um, excuse me.
Yeah, I was wrong. Pop rocks are fun for a second where you, you're like, oh yeah, remember these
and you do it and you go, okay, I won't eat these for like another three or four years. They're
all right. You, I don't, you can't put, okay, I know some people are going to put this in S,
but how do you put something in S that you know you're not going to eat more than like once every
two or three decades? You know what I mean? Like sure, they're really cool. It's a crazy experience.
Like it's, wow, look at the pop rocks and it's, oh my God, crunch, crunch. But if I'm only going
to do this like once every fucking five years, why can I put it up here? Like I said, why would
I put it up there? It's, it's cool, but it's not. I, I have eaten these. I mean, I ate like five of
these literally yesterday. So that's why they're up here. Um, this is a funny like experience to
have, but I don't think it's like a great candy to eat all the time. These are the wax bottles.
Again, same deal. You're going to remember that the wax bottles exist. You're going to go, oh dude,
oh my God. Whoa. Oh yeah. Do you remember? Do you remember that? And then you go, both going to go,
okay, we're not doing that for another decade. We're not doing that again. We're not doing that
ever again. Like we're going to do it once and then forget it exists for like another five years
till we remember to do it again. They belong in the same place and they're somehow better than
Starburst and Skittles, but that experience is cooler than, yeah. Yep. I think so. Almond Joy.
Mm. I really don't, I really don't like these. I don't like them. I think they're better. These
are probably better than, yeah, than all this fucking dog shit. You know, it's tough to like
do these. Somebody said earlier, like you're going to, you're ruining sponsorship opportunities.
If like Twizzlers for any reason ever, and I'm not saying this is ever going to happen,
but if any of these companies were ever like, Hey man, we should, you want to like work together?
And all that was here. Wow. These are all dog shit. These are dog shit. You know what I mean?
Like I gotta be careful. These are not weighted to my palate moment. They're all one company.
Don't worry. That's true. True. True. That's true. All right. Laffy Taffy is actually,
holy shit. This is the pink Laffy Taffy. I'm trying to remember what it tastes like. It's like a
creamy, weird, like strawberry fake flavoring. And it's delicious. Isn't it? It's like fantastic.
I like know what this tastes like. Yeah. Hold on. I'm getting it. Hey. Oh yeah. Oh yeah. That's,
that's probably, oh, that's up here. I think so. Yeah. These are really good. I just haven't
had one in a while. Where's uh, like just Saltwater Taffy. That belongs up here in S.
These things are fine. They're, you eat the paper half the time. Whatever. No. Any candy where you
go like this. No, it's like, it's fine. It's, but I don't think it's, I don't, I don't want it all
the time. Uh, jelly beans. I mean, toasted marshmallow jelly beans are up here, but the
fact that they kept popcorn in for this long. I mean, they, well, you go down here like the,
just the fact that these, these people have put popcorn still in here this many years later.
What are you thinking? Like, what are you thinking? Popcorn is the best flavor. What are you thinking?
Popcorn's the best flavor. What are, what drugs I've seeped into you. Popcorn is not the best
flavor. Popcorn tastes like fucking eggs. The popcorn jelly bean tastes like eggs. No, I will,
I'm going to die on this hill. Toasted marshmallow is way up here and watermelon. So you know what,
besides like the egg flavored one, I would probably enjoy this more than Fondue or Lemonheads.
I think it's a solid B. Toasted marshmallow and sucks ass. That's like, they're literally the only
reason to get it. That's why you buy the jelly beans. What are you on about? What are you talking
about? I can't believe somebody's saying that right now. That's crazy to me. Uh, Whoppers kind
of tastes like acid. Uh, Whoppers are good, but they taste like they're fucking something's wrong
with like the something was wrong in the production. But they do have a, they have a very interesting
flavor. And if you're really into it, there's been times where I've looked at the Whoppers kind of
at the movie theater counter or whatever and been like, you know what, go, let's do it. Let's get it.
Let's go for it. And I'm like, oh yeah, these are fine. But they do, they kind of have that weird
like acidic fucking taste. Like there's something, like there was way too much of some ingredient
that you wanted to remove. But I, I think that they're fine. I would, I think they're solid.
But they, they see. I see. In fact, like these are like gimmick fucking things. They should be down
here. They're fine. They taste fine, but they're gimmicks. This is a gimmick. Who's going to be
able to do this at the office? You know what I mean? Who's, this is a gimmick. You're not,
you can't do that at the office. Like these down here, one, two, three, four, five, you can't do
this at the office. But like the guy in the next door and like the office next door, you're going
to do like pop rocks. And you look over, you peek over like the side and he's like, you can't do
that at the office. Why not? It's not for adults. I know. But I'm just saying you can't do that
at the office. We already know where Skittles are. We're going to put them both here.
Milk Duds. Oh, Milk Duds are bad. But why are these in the same space? Why are these
occupying the same part of my brain? They're like chewy and kind of hard, right? Oh, I know Milk
Duds. Milk Duds are the ones that are unbelievably delicious. The chocolate, the like candy chocolate
coating on the outside is fucking so good. It's like chewy and oh, it's so yummy. And then you
spit it out when it gets to like the weird like gum under the desk consistency. Right. Okay. I mean,
these are like A plus in flavor. But when they get to that point, they go all the way down here.
I think I'd probably rather have a whopper. The flavor is phenomenal, though. It really is.
The flavor is phenomenal. What are these dots? These are the cousin of dots. What are these
called? Like dinkels or something? What are these called? What are these gumdrops? Oh,
no, they're they're like we're dots in the same place for me. Okay, hold on.
Let me guess. Let me guess. Is it right? He sees Andy's nerds. Three musketeers. Dork pep and
patties. Snickers. Hearts. I'm gonna move this. I'm gonna move this. Yeah, I think. Wait. Yeah.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Let's move this a little bit here. Remember these are mint. These
are mint. This is I remember this being so good. These are fine. Milky Way. Yeah, that's fine.
Put this up a little higher. Way higher, actually. Actually, you know what? Fuck that.
Oh, fuck that. Yeah, I'd rather have a youth bar. Maybe not more than a gummy bear.
Maybe not. Stupid fucking idiot. Idiot. Oh, yeah. Yeah. I think that's fine. I still think he's an
alien for putting Pocky in trash tier. Actually, Pocky would be up here for me now. I've had a
few flavors that I actually really liked. There's like a mint chocolate Pocky that is up here.
I don't really like any of the other ones. Here's my old list. Okay. Pocky was on there twice.
All right. Let's get my old list. I think I'm happy with this one. What have we got?
All right. What's going on here? Who puts Mr. Goodbar in S tier? Why is Mr. Goodbar in S tier?
Mr. Goodbar? What the fuck am I talking about? Why is Mr. Goodbar on here twice? It's on here
two times. I don't get it. You were pretending it was something else. Does it remember what it was
supposed to be? Why would you ever put Mr. Goodbar in S tier? It's good, but not S tier.
Oh, this is an absolutely brainless take. Gummy bears are in D. Cadbury eggs are in D. M&M's are
in F. What am I talking about? Guys, what am I on about? Is Swedish fish down at F? It better be.
Sweet tarts? All right. Hold on. Let's shrink this down a little. Yeah. All right. Sweet tarts are
fine. Broly is in trash tier. And I would put it there again. I would put it down here again.
Everyone talking about how I have like a palette of a 10-year-old and yet I'm getting all this
flack for trolley gummy worms being down in like D. Excuse me? Gummy worms? No. Broly is S. No,
it's not. It's a gummy worm. Gummy worms are like fucking F. They're like D. I don't like them.
They're down here with like Swedish fucking fish. Wait. Hold on. I'll be fair. I'll be fair. Relax.
Relax. I'll be fair. I've never had a trolley before ever in my life.
It's just gummy worms are for kids, but I just didn't ever, I never bought them.
Eat a trolley on stream. Gummy worms were like, oh, ew. He's got a worm in his mouth that's for
children. I never bought them. Everything that I have besides nerds is an adult beverage of candies.
Okay. It's an adult beverage of candies. Reese's is like the whiskey. No. Reese's is, yeah. Reese's
is like the whiskey. Andy's is like the, like peppermint schnapps. Free Musketeers is like a
really good fucking wine. York peppermint patty. These are, these are, these are like adult beverages.
Snickers bar. Oh, that's like, these are, these are like aged to perfection. Everyone making fun
of my, my 10 year old palette and saying, where's trolley? Where's the gummy worms?
Bubble tape. It's six feet of bubble gum for adults, not kids. I remember the commercial.
Six feet of bubble gum for you, not kids. I saw it a million times. It was on TV all the time.
You're already in mine. Okay. I've never had a trolley. I'll leave the trolley on stream
and I'll change my opinion if it's good. Gummy worms are for men. What? It's not for men? No,
it's not. Why? How's a gummy worm for men? Oh, it's a man sized gummy worm. Gummy worms are for men.
Why are you putting gummy worms in the same category as, as like a fucking like brisket sandwich?
Executives eat trolley. Really? At the office? Really? At the, at the office?
Trolley gummy worms coming out at the office? Really? No, it is coming out. Andy's mints. Andy's
mints. York peppermint patties. Son, would you like a Snickers? Son, how about a three musketeers?
That's coming out of the board meeting. Nobody at the board meeting is, unless it's like one of
those like 90s comedy movies where like the kind of weird funny guy got on the board of directors
and like comes to the office in like a, like a sweatshirt and like glasses and eats gummy worms.
All right. This is not a 90s comedy movie. We're executives and we eat Andy's mints.
CEOs eat trolley. Oh no, they do not. You're a boring adult. Okay, here we go. I will buy a
bag of trolley and I'll eat them on stream. Is there a certain color of trolley that I need to eat
first? Or is it one of those cases where like, no dude, skip all the green ones and yeah, those
are the gross ones. Which, what, which is the one I need to eat? Blue? Make this, you better make
this accurate because you're only getting one chance. Sour trolley? Blue sour trolley. The blue
and pink blue and sour trolley. Blue and blue and pink trolley. Sour. Blue and pink sour trolley.
Okay. All right. Any, any of the blue ones, any of the red ones. Pink. Sour. Okay. Sure. I'm going to
eat a blue sour trolley on stream tomorrow. Tomorrow. We'll do it tomorrow. Any other candies
that I have to have to be a fucking adult? Which ones? I'll give you my real opinion. Tomorrow.
Can you eat, can you eat a review of Papa John's pizza? I'm not going to eat a fucking trolley and
then a Papa John's pizza tomorrow. Why would I do that? Oh, hey dude, now that you're trying candy,
eat a whole Papa John's pepperoni pizza and give us what you thought. Okay. How about this? No,
that's, I don't think I can get that by tomorrow. Should I like go up against my own bullshit and
eat all the things that are in like D, like C and D? Should we do like a face your bullshit stream
where like I eat all these things that I have in a bad category and tell you how I really feel?
And you have to eat them in a suit. Toblerone is S plus. It's not, it can't even fit on this list.
Toblerone is like stratosphere. It's the best candy in the world, but it's just not on here.
It's not fair. It's not fair for Toblerone to be on here. All right. How about this? Let's,
okay. This is what we're going to do. We're going to do a face the bullshit stream.
Can I do it tomorrow? Tomorrow. Okay. Can I, can you give me a day to prepare? I want to make sure
I can like get a bunch of these. I'll do a face the bullshit stream. Let me, give me a little,
give me a day or two to prepare this. Thursday. I think I can get most of these by Thursday.
I don't think I can get it by tomorrow. I'll wear a suit and it will, it'll be called face the
bullshit stream. I'm talking like all the, all like the F tier shit that I've told you about.
We're talking bread? Like I'm going to get wheat bread. Like you know what, what we should do?
Let me, I'm going to go through these and figure out all the, all the things that I fucking said
it would do a gross. You're going to buy every single candy at the store in a suit.
Did they make little versions of this shit? I don't want to like eat one and then like not want it.
You need a popcorn jelly bean. Oh fuck. You can get 95% of these at like Walmart or a gas station.
Okay. All right. All right. We'll, we'll make this work. So I'm, tomorrow I'm going to scour the world
for all these things that I said that I hate or think is gross or think like I, I'm so high and
mighty on and I will give you my real honest opinions on them. I will not fuck around.
I'm going to, and I'm going to do it in a suit. It's going to be like a fucking telephone on the
desk. I'm going to have like an executive table. All I ask is that you don't fuck around. All right.
I'll pull up all, I get, I'll figure it out. But yeah, we'll, we'll open up. If you have any
recommendations, by the way, we have the recommended channel in discord. Maybe I can work with maybe the
mods. We'll, we'll get like a good list of like a bunch of stuff. This is going to be the worst
stream of the year with candlelight. What if he pukes? What if I puke on camera? Can I puke?
Yeah. It's going to be called face the bullshit and a top hat with candles. All right. Let me
just make sure I can even get all this gross stuff. Okay. I'll see you. I'll see you guys on Thursday.
Thursday. We're going to start early on Thursday, not four o'clock. We're going to start Thursday,
probably around like two. You said tomorrow. I got to go. Okay. I don't think I can find
some of these things on the chips list guys. I'm going to have to go to like fucking five
Walmarts. That's not going to happen tomorrow. All the, okay. If he wants to get the F's from
his chip list, I'll do them all. All my tier lists. Maybe besides the fast food ones. Cause
that I don't want to like, all right. Here's what I don't want to do. I don't want to like
buy a bunch of food and like waste a bunch of food. Right. That'll be for like a different day.
And maybe we're talking like shelf stable stuff because even if I don't like it, I can like
roll it up and like eat it over the course of a year. So I, I'm not going to buy like
fucking 30 pieces of fast food and take 10 bites of everything and then throw it all away. I'm
not going to do that. So we'll see. I'll do it on Thursday. Do it on Friday. I can't do it on
Friday. Cause I need to get like all these candies. I need to get all those chips. I need to get all
the sodas and hey, where's the, where's the Pepsi nitro? Where's Pepsi nitro? Where's Pepsi nitro?
Where the fuck is it? I keep seeing commercials for it. Where is it? Where is it? They keep showing
it to me. Where is it? It's bad. I want to try it. I keep seeing it on like television and shit.
And I'm like, I want it. I want to try it. It's so good. It actually looked good. All right.
Those of you that want to follow the sort of what's going to happen here,
all the F tier candies and like maybe some of the D tier candies, all the F tier sodas,
all the F tier chips. I'm going to try to get as many of them as I can. Here we go. And I'm
going to give you, I'm going to give a rating out of 10. That's it. I'll see you. I'll see you
Thursday. And don't forget breads. Don't worry. That's why it's going to take more than, okay.
That's why it's going to take more than like a day. I have to go to like a bunch. I have to like,
I don't think they have all this stuff in one place. Who the fuck has candy corn right now?
Or candy cigarettes? I don't know. Are these even legal anymore? Are these, these are illegal?
Aren't they? I don't think I can buy these. We're going to get these. We're supposed to get that.
Cookie dough bites. Guys, they don't even sell this. You have to go to Spencer's Gifts.
Spencer's. Just go to a movie theater. Oh my God. I'm going to go to a movie theater and just
be like, I'll take, I'll take the Almond Joy. I'll take the Twizzlers. I'll take the Mike and Ikes.
I'll take the cookie dough bites. I'll take the candy cigarettes. The Gobstoppers, the Dots,
and the Peeps. Uh, give me a couple of those too. Oh, enjoy the movie. No, there's no movie.
Bye. Bye, man. Enjoy Spider-Man. That movie sucked. See you later. It did, I'm kidding.
That didn't suck. It was fine. Oh, enjoy Morbius. Oh, dude, it's the fifth time I've seen it.
All right, I'll see you later. I'm going to work on, I'm going to get to work on this now.
I'll see you guys on Thursday, two o'clock Pacific. Yeah. And so the mods over here are talking.
They're saying get some, get what you can reasonably get. Cereal list too. Yep. I have so much
bullshit. I'm going to have a pantry full of shit. I'm never going to have to buy a cereal ever. But
what if I don't like it? I'm going to have to like eat like gross cereal. I mean, I'm going to eat all
this stuff because it's going to be, I don't want to just waste a bunch of food. So if I buy, for
instance, um, what is down here at the very bottom? Like multi-grain Cheerios. Oh, I don't want to eat
those, but I don't want to eat multi-grain Cheerios. Could you donate it? Okay. If I don't get through
everything and yeah, but I mean, I'm going to be opening most of this stuff. I'm going to have to
eat it. So if I, if I can track down the Sour Patch Kids cereal, I'm going to have to open the bag and
eat it. I can't like, I'm not going to, I'm going to have to eventually over the course of like a year
eat that Sour Patch Kids cereal. They're a single serving box. Yeah. I'll make sure to get the small
ones. All right. So I'll see you on Thursday for Face the Bullshit 2 p.m. Might start earlier.
Keep an eye on the sus over the next day or so. Are you looking at like a somewhere between 12
and 2 p.m. start? Not sure yet. Thanks for watching. See you guys later. Thanks for sticking around.
Have a wonderful rest of your night. We'll see you soon. I'm actually excited.
Can I put Bullshit in the title of a stream or is that going to like Twitch flag me?
I don't think I can. I can just, I can just bleep it out. Yeah. It'll be like Face the Bull
S with like did, did, did, did, did. All right. Goodnight guys. See you later.