Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
And tonight, I'm not sure what I'm gonna be playing as, and it doesn't really matter, because this video is not gonna talk about Team Fortress 2.
It's not gonna talk about Smite. I don't know why I just brought up Smite.
There hasn't been a Smite video on this channel in like 70 years, but it's gonna talk about how this whole YouTube thing has truly been the most humbling experience of my entire life.
And this is not a subscriber milestone video. It's not like, thank you for 150,000 subscribers. No, this is not like any video like that.
It's just something I've wanted to do for a long time, is talk about this in a little bit more detail than I ever have.
And I figured it would be a good idea to do it right now, because I'm in the mood to talk about it.
So what am I getting at here? What's the point here? What am I talking about?
I'm talking about when people send me comments or tweets or personal messages. I read them all. I really do, I promise you guys.
I read all the comments, I read all the tweets, I read all the personal messages. It's just too much to ever be able to reply to them.
I think Gabe Newell famously said, I don't reply to them all, but I do read them all, talking about emails.
I'm the same way. I can't reply to them, but I do read them and I do appreciate them.
But why I bring up this topic of comments and people sending me messages is, what I get a lot of times in any of my inboxes
are people telling me that the videos that I make, the content I make, whether it's a comedy video or a discussion video, anything, it helps out their life.
They watch it and they feel better about themselves, they feel better about the world, they're going through depression, they're going through some tough times.
And they watch these videos from just from a YouTuber like me and it helps them out.
And I'm not going to solely say that like, oh, it's just because I'm such a good, it's a lot of different people.
There's a lot of people on this website that make fantastic content, very uplifting, fun, awesome content.
I'm not the only one that makes videos. There's plenty of other people.
But knowing that what I'm doing could potentially be helping somebody else in a much deeper way than I ever could possibly have imagined is life changing.
Being able to directly impact somebody else's life through video content is amazing.
And I really, truly hope that I can help out in any way I can, guys.
If you're watching the videos for fun and then you move on, if you're watching the videos to get away from something, I'm glad I'm here.
I'm glad there's a lot of us here on this site that can help you do that, that can help you through that.
And I mean that from the very bottom of my soul. I really do mean that.
A lot of you guys already know this. I've went through fucking all kinds of depression in the last, you know, 10 years.
I'm not perfect. I'm not a perfect guy. Like, I'm not.
I've gone through plenty of problems in my life. And I've gone through plenty of issues.
And I've gone through plenty of times where I've been like, you know what? Fuck it.
But the more you dwell on stuff like that, the more you're going to bring yourself down into a place you don't want to be.
You don't want to be there. Trust me on that. You do not want to be there.
You want to be up. You want to be high. You want to be on the mountain. You want to be shouting from the mountaintops, baby.
Sawmill. That was a reference to one of Star's videos. But whatever.
You want to be in a position where you're happy.
And if I can help you get there, if I can help you do that with these videos, then god damn it, I'm going to keep doing it.
And I'm going to try my absolute hardest to make the best videos I can.
To make the funniest videos I can. To make the most entertaining videos I can.
That's what I'm all about. That's what this channel is all about.
This channel is not about anything else. That's the number one thing. That's the number two thing.
That's the number three thing. The top three things of my channel are that.
And everything else is underneath.
And the whole purpose of this video, the whole reason why I made this video, why I opened up Audacity, why I started talking in the first place,
is to say thank you to those of you that have watched these videos.
That, you know, it's not a subscriber milestone, like I said in the beginning.
Not like, oh, 200k, no. I just want to say thanks.
Because me making videos that you guys enjoy, or that help out your life in some way, anyway, makes me want to be a better person.
Makes me want to strive to make better content, strive to make better videos, more entertaining things, have more ideas, more experiments.
It's like Dr. Jekyll and Mr. Jerma upstairs in my noggin lately.
Because I got a lot of ideas, and I want to do them.
But we're not going to go into that now.
And to close this video out, I'm only going to take about 30 seconds or so in this video,
because if you're having problems, if you're having real problems, talk to somebody.
You have to. You have to get in touch with somebody.
Because it's not healthy to stay mad, to stay depressed.
It's not a healthy thing. I know. I know.
Take it from me. I know.
You don't want to be sad. You don't want to be depressed about certain things.
You want a good old grandma for Christine to help you.
That's a new character. I don't know who that is.
You want to be happy. So try to get happy.
Try to find ways to make you happy.
And if I can make you happy, like I said, god damn it, I'm going to keep fucking doing it.
So thank you everybody for watching. I really do appreciate it.
I'll see you guys all next time. And of course, take care everybody.