What's up? Didn't expect me today, did you?
Hey. Just like I can delay streams indefinitely.
I can also pull them back.
That's exactly what we're doing.
We'll stream tomorrow, but I think we can go over a few things.
Reverse delay, yeah.
It happens like once a year.
Well, you're here for it!
You're here for it!
The one time every year that I, instead of pushing a stream out, I do it a day or two before.
And it's funny, because this is a mistake on my part.
So I come in a free stream chat, and people are just kind of like,
Hey, what's up, man? What are you doing here?
I'm just like, what do you mean? Let's get ready!
Probably like 3.30.
I thought it was Tuesday.
And I'm just going to go by what I think in my head.
So I'm not just going to get here and be ready, sitting at the desk.
It's like, OK, here we go.
It's time to stream.
And then, no, no, never mind.
I'm coming, but no, I'm here.
I'm ready.
So we're streaming today.
We also are going to play Such Art, which, I don't know, I saw this came out.
This Steel Rising, Dark Souls-like.
We can hear the game when you talk again.
What the fuck, man?
Why is it so hard to stream?
Why does it never...
Why do my settings get reversed every time I turn on my computer?
I'm being serious.
Why is it fixed?
Why do my settings reverse every time I turn my computer on?
What the fuck is this doing?
Oh, God, come on.
OK.
Anyways.
Yeah. All right.
Let's go over a few things.
Let's talk about the week ahead here because there's a few things we need to discuss.
Very important.
I think it's fixed.
Yeah.
All right. So here's the deal.
So what we're going to do this weekend.
Oh, my stop.
Hold on.
This weekend, we're going to do an Omega weekend.
OK.
I'm streaming today.
We'll go for about five to seven hours, depending on how long it takes, depending what we do.
But there's something that I have to do.
There's something that I've been kind of figuring out the last day or so.
It's why I didn't stream yesterday.
I have to get a thousand fucking baseballs signed and shipped because there's a lot of them.
So I have to get that going once for me.
That's right.
You should do it on stream.
No, I don't want to do that.
That's weird.
That's weird to me.
I don't like that at all.
I want to just sit there with a YouTube playlist up for like two to like eight hour days back
to back.
Just put on, you know what I've been really into?
This chemist on YouTube.
I have no idea what the hell he's talking about.
But all his videos, they're like 30 plus minute long videos.
And it just talks about all this chemistry.
Nile Red.
Yeah, that's the one.
So I just watch Nile Red and I just, here's the thing that happens when you watch a Nile
Red video.
By the time you get to the end of the video and the experiment is over, I forgot the whole
video.
I don't even know what happened.
They're awesome though.
They are the best videos just to sit there with your mouth open and just go.
Wow.
I'm learning.
I have no idea what I'm learning.
Stream that straight.
Wait, stream watching Nile Red videos.
I don't know about that.
I'd rather you watch Nile Red videos on Nile Red's channel.
I mean, we could.
All right.
But I want to do that while I'm signing baseballs.
Do you really want me to stream this?
I don't know.
I don't think so.
That's weird to me.
To me, that's like, I don't know.
That feels like an egomaniac stream.
I don't know why it just does.
That feels kind of like an egomaniac thing.
Oh, hey, what's up guys?
Signing baseballs.
Yeah.
I'm going to sign this one too.
Oh, give me that one.
Yeah.
I'm going to sign that one.
That's my name on it, by the way.
I don't know.
Maybe.
I will give you a hard maybe on that one, but I do.
I have to get that sorted.
I got to get shipments.
I got to get, it's a thousand baseballs.
It's a lot of material.
It's a ton to work with.
So my plan is this.
I'm going to stream today and then unless I decide to do an egomaniac megalomania stream,
the next time you see me after tonight will be for the Omega weekend on Friday, Saturday
and Sunday.
We're going to do three days in a row.
I know I've been kind of bouncing around a lot lately.
I've been, you know, it's been like three days, no stream, four days, five days, no
stream.
We're going to do an Omega weekend this weekend.
So get your recommendations in to the discord channel because that's going to build, it's
going to be a doozy of three days in a row.
I promise this is not going to be like a, well, this streams like four hours in a 16
minutes.
No, we're going to do three Omega streams in a row.
We're doing an Omega weekend and I'm going to laugh my ass off if I get like a headache
on Friday afternoon.
But that's the plan.
Guys, we can't do the Omega weekend.
I got to, I need a nap.
I won't.
Don't burn out.
No, I've, I've been taking a lot of time.
So don't worry.
I'll be okay.
It'll be fun.
We'll get a bunch of stuff to do.
You're going to call into sick for work.
No, I'm not going to.
I promise we'll do a bunch of stuff.
We'll play like a 10 different games.
We'll jump around.
We'll be crazy.
But today we're going to play this dark soul.
I stopped saying that because I feel like companies hate to hear that.
Hey guys, we're going to play this thing.
And the only thing that I'm going to tell you is dark souls is awesome.
Okay.
I'm sure that it's like, yeah.
I do.
Dark souls is an awesome game.
Let's play this one called steel rising.
I have no idea.
We're just going to, we're going to give it a try.
You guys ready?
Change the title.
I like that title because everybody calls everything like a souls, ask souls, light,
souls, like souls, ask souls, light, like I think my title is fine.
I should just start calling this stream a rogue light stream because it turns off and
we start over again with like a new game.
Another stream later.
It's kind of like a rogue.
Like, you know, we start over on a different, a different game.
Each stream.
All right.
Let me get this.
I think unplugged here.
I hope this is good.
All right.
Can you guys, you guys can't see this is way too loud for me.
It probably won't be too loud for you though.
And I can confirm.
Yes.
We've confirmed it.
I've confirmed it with you.
We are with a new camera angle.
I have moved it to where I want it permanently.
Do you understand where this is now?
This is a perfect gang.
Perfect angle.
Perfect lighting.
What do you think?
This is better.
Right?
You're right there.
You're literally right there.
Exactly where I wanted you.
It's too orange.
That's, that's my face.
All right.
You guys ready for this?
I'm ready.
This is called Steel Rising.
Why did I laugh?
Oh, God damn it.
I can't.
I just, I'm why am I even live?
Okay.
And why is this funny?
This isn't funny.
Nothing that I'm doing is funny.
I don't understand.
Why am I laughing at this?
What the fuck is going on?
I'm sorry.
What's assist mode?
Okay.
So this makes it easier.
Well, I don't, I don't, I don't, I'm not going to need that for now.
Maybe I'll need it later.
We'll see.
All right.
Here comes the opening cut scene.
Everybody's quiet.
Where's Otto?
I'll show him.
I told you later.
Checkmate.
You know, actually, I think I'm in no mood for games right now.
How much longer are we to be kept here?
We just simply watch as Paris burns from afar.
The rabble of rioting.
This is the price to be paid for spoiling the masses.
Why are they playing chess?
The king sent us here long before the city went up in flames.
He knew what was about to transpire.
If you're a noble, do you have to know chess?
What if you don't?
Does that annoy the other nobles?
True.
He can be misguided and somewhat short tempered at times, but he's no Nero.
Then why have we been given no news for so long?
Place en four, Gabrielle.
The children.
They'll soon be out of harm's way.
I am most certain of it.
Monsieur Clary will take good care of them.
For now, at least, we are safe.
Louder?
Safe.
Vremont?
Where are the Shadow Guards?
We are still protected.
The king just preferred to use a different sort of guard.
R1.
Odds?
Or jailers?
Leave this room, Gabrielle.
The king.
He has lost his mind to grief.
First our darling, Sophie.
Then our beloved son.
My poor sweet angel.
They didn't let me say goodbye.
What character am I?
I wasn't even allowed to see him.
Serephar.
Something inside me is crying out.
Telling me he's still of this world at times.
I think I hear him calling to me.
I'm so afraid.
What do you fear, my dear?
What do you fear, my queen?
Everything, everything horrifies me.
The king's wrath, his army of indefatigable automats that Monsieur de Vaucossot has built
for him, the charlatans.
You're the hair.
Who are now more powerful, more modest.
Did you mean to say heir or hair?
Like her hair?
What happened to my son?
What will happen to the children that God has deigned to leave in my care?
I won't let any harm come to them.
Did you say heir?
This I promise you.
I don't know what you said.
fast but how do you not see that we're prisoners here all is not lost you
forget about the one autumn out that is not hostile to us this new bodyguard of
yours me whoa okay wait are we robot we're a robot yep mmm I don't know I
think it has to be this it has to be right we have to do the George
Washington here okay I like this one okay what's next wait they have to pick
a class bodyguard soldier dancer this is gonna be hard mode or something right
don't ever pick this first when his souls like ask light rogue like ask like
game right you always do do this first wait let me read heavy weapons special
move block ranged attack heavy weapon heavy weapon heavy weapon light weapon
light weapon all right what do all the streamers do because I don't want to do
that one dancer what do all the streamers do I don't want to do with this
the streamer one nobody plays this dancer or the game dancer wait light
weapon block explosive projectile that could ignite an enemy as way I have like
a fan is that a shield what is it dancers are highly resistant and can
chain attacks together in quick succession to immobilize enemies and
inflict critical hits okay is this like decks light weapon weapon is infused
with frost or if you know all right I'll do dancer what if I suck oh fine all
right what about details ah there we go all right so this is all right this is
durability this is tank this is strength heavy weapons this is decks and
this is magic all right we'll do dancer that's gonna be the most minus twos of
the whole year without a doubt well nobody cared nevermind yes but it is
loyal to you that's all that matters if it managed to escape the chateau why
they don't why they stand like that your eyes and ears in Paris that's what I do
when I have a wicked bad burp that has not come out yet what does that stance
the chance the other automats were to go after it you won't attempt anything
foolish I cannot lose you Gabrielle not now that's like that acid reflux pose
like the ages madam that's me the king must be stopped the very kingdom is at
this game suck go and find Vaucosson at his workshop he surely holds the secret
to these tireless automats and perhaps he will know something about the death
of my son how am I to leave the chateau grounds madam okay go to the riverbank
at the far side of the grounds from there you can take a boat to Paris so
that way and take a boat and now we open up the doors to the first area of our
souls like souls ask souls light game if he is the one who is we get to hear it
this unrest get to hear this I can't fucking wait and never mind all right so
how do we play how do I play reach the investigate the dead art what do you
how do you play this oh all right that's my eyes hurt that's a soup that's a huge
frog jump all right it's a dodge all right let's do let's dance okay that's
the charge it's like fans all right cool so I can lock on there excuse me okay
quick access belt how can we look 40 from this angle ban that person all right
consumables on the quick access belt so you can use them at any time go to the
inventory to assign oil for it the belt okay this is a heel it's like an oil can
really so you like that's all right I like that so let's put it on this slot
right here okay well actually why would I have that equipped okay so it's just
repair that's kind of cool looking there's one there's one thing that I
who hold on I'm very curious if I can do this or not I saw it in them options
menu let me go let's just go to the video field of view what does that do
hundred times I'm a million times better I'm gonna say 100 fucking million times
better you know you don't understand a million times better okay hold on there
was something else I might want to do to advanced video if it's in here I'm gonna
be really happy okay that's fine that's fine that's fine ray tracing mm-hmm I
don't see it wait game subtitles camera effects no all right let's go oh you can
grab try explore is it get a full letter grade we'll find out in a second is
there sprint I don't think this is sprint it might be it's a very pretty
game that matters to anybody here all right each weapon has an attacking or
deep special move for the okay so it's like a weapon art I know it's not yeah
whatever what did that do oh it's just a block okay by the way yes it did get
rid of the screen shake I believe so that's a full letter grid all right hold
on wait you can overheat when a just runs out of endurance her gears overheat
and she can no longer perform the following actions attack jump dodge or
sprint what that's not good when you overheated you can trigger rapid
cooling which can instantly restore an amount of endurance depending on your
timing however this inflicts a certain amount of frost damage as shown in the
following gauge wait did he play this before no that's the surge is one of my
least favorite games of all time using it too soon after okay so I gotta be
careful so over let me try this oops so if I overheat okay overheated you have
to do it immediately all right that's kind of insane I'm kidding that that
game is fine I just didn't like it I know that game is it was very cool I
didn't like it whatever do I really I don't need to explain myself I didn't
like it I didn't like it so get out of here leave me alone I wonder what is
there there are no iframes wait are there iframes let's try let's test no
there isn't wait let's try it okay maybe there is I don't have any heels left
now the third you know it was the surge to that I never played the surge one I
actually enjoyed up at the first hour then I backtracked a statement that I
made in front of about 12,000 people to make sure that nobody hates me for
having a video game that I don't like or something so I backtracked and I you
know honestly like if you like what you like who cares enjoy what you enjoy
don't let some dickhead like me tell you that you can't like something because I
didn't that's stupid it's a dumb mindset and you should nobody should have it
I'm gonna die H's light weapons are able to inflict immobilization damages shown
in the immobilization gauge and the gauges build the enemy is temporarily
immobilized leaving them open to a critical hit okay so immobilization
damage did it work that for it oh okay cool ignore the fact that you're
insulting no that clip that was cycling around was a joke and you clipping it
out of context I said it and it was a it was a comedic reference it was a joke I
didn't actually mean it right afterwards I go no no I'm just kidding I need to
heal is there oh there is a sprint okay cool nice PR Andy no I genuinely look if
you like stuff who cares if I don't if we got the people don't like it do you
like it who cares enjoy it I like the venom movie you know throw
fucking eggs at me all right well that obviously can't go in there so I'm
almost dead though what happens when I die cool rusty key wait secrets what
did this game come out essence of spirit I'm livid that you don't share my
opinion you know four days ago oh shit I'm I'm right on time I'm never like
I'm never on time for this I never play a new game when it comes out I feel kind
of accomplished in some way what if I get heels are there crabs in the game
who knows we'll find out I got I'm the first boss is definitely gonna be okay
break stuff ordinary oil but wait hold on is this a heel okay it's a it's a
hot oh this is a bonfire stop saying that okay activating a vestal creates a
checkpoint where eight you know why I'm playing this because I saw the trailer
trailer for um lies of P and I was like oh I want to play like a souls game
again I knew it well whatever what's lies of P no it's I'm not saying it
wrong right it's the fucking Pinocchio game it's the Pinocchio souls like you
understand what I just said go look it up that's so weird to say okay upgrade
attributes by spending so that's essence okay so that's just like souls upgrade
equipment by spending materials and obtain equipment by spending essence so
wait you there's no you have to buy all the stuff you want to find this is a
bonfire that's cool okay upgrades module slots requires three keys weapons all
right I need 1,500 essence to upgrade this and a bronze ingot okay so all the
upgrades are literally on the same screen which is that's that's good that's
cool all right one power one agility what am I what do I want probably
agility right agility or power how do I increase damage power I don't have
souls to do this he hates it I do this feels like a YouTube somehow the YouTube
video kind of like a director's commentary why this is not a director's
commentary what's happening it's the camera angle do I do I have to buy
heels it's the camera angle this is a beautiful angle it's perfect I'm right
in frame it's got my whole head and body it's direct it's not off to the side
what this is director commentary Andy all right we're moving on we're moving on
try buy these is a stupid well maybe it was dumb but I bought four heels oh cool
any hats I'm interested I'm actually interested that seems like a pretty easy
well not easy the wrong word it seems like a pretty it's a good system to put
everything in the same place so I don't have to like go to this bonfire to find
this NPC in the woods that'll teach me how to do a spell right I know that's
cool but I do I do appreciate the like the complete package in the same spot
and I'm a huge fan of the souls games huge fan you all know that especially
Elden Ring but I do appreciate that there did I just can I sneak there's a
lot of staggering this game too seems like oh okay so I do have a heal that
regenerates it's good to know hi where's the where's the tutorial boss
let's go where are you I'm ready for it let's go this way wait did I come from
this way oh shit I'm out of juice oh fuck I don't like that all right we're
good I'm not used to paying attention to that mm-hmm I need I need deadly boss
mods installed do you know I'm saying it needs to scream at me that I'm getting
close how much is this heal to the hole right I actually need something like
DBM feels like a zoom call well whatever what the hell is that wait a minute you
need a tool to break this no stop I can't jump that the boss gets lock on to
a targeted approach slowly ooh okay that's helpful what is considered
that was pretty cool that was pretty cool I have somebody saying this it
seriously feels like a zoom call this is a fake reaction it's not you guys need
to relax I'm not superimposed on top of the video no joke I've missed it the
controller parasocial Andy's zoom call this is like a council meeting I'm so
confused I'm just gonna play oh chat raid one ooh wait you just obtained a
new module you can almost pick my nose on camera you can assign it to a module
slot of the same level from the module menu yeah what's this do increases
health this is oh this is rapid cooling I'm gonna put the health one in like I
could use it this is definitely gonna be something that drops here in no way
right this is definitely like tutorial bosses place I guess not maybe it is
right here elusory walls wasn't supposed to go on a boat this risk art
killed by the automats that replaced them that's kind of an e3 walk what I
just did but you know what I mean all right um this is kind of crazy what's
going on here captain degros governor deafrey confirms that no command was
given to replace your company with a detachment of automats I therefore urge
you until further notice to keep your distance from these machines and to
inform me of any signs of hostility do not engage unless her majesty the Queen
is in danger reinforcements are on route hurdle the back man second in
command oh whatever defeat the unstable automat to activate what I can't even
touch the bonfire until I kill the boss here oh let's go first try Andy I'm so
upset Andy all right let's go let's go first try check it out music all I have
is hot oh that's bad okay wait I'm just resetting it
shit what are you doing what are you doing what are you doing don't overheat
don't overheat no I overheat it first try yeah it was just a story boss come
on module key is this a surge like game you've just obtained a module key Aegis
has several slots for modules that augment her stats and after the
behavior of reading comprehension let me try that again Aegis has several slots
for modules that augment her stats and alter the behavior of certain mechanics
the slots of levels that allow Aegis to fit increasingly powerful modules to
unlock a slot with the module key you just obtained go to the upgrades menu at
the Vestal note you can equip modules at any given time from Aegis I'm not
comprehending this hold on let me read without talking okay so I can upgrade my
modules that was kind of fun that felt that felt pretty that felt clean and
responsive that felt pretty responsive that was fun I enjoyed that let me look
at this okay oh I get it so I can have two modules now what does this get me
though if I do three keys here should I just do the other one you so higher I
know level 2 slot um I'll just do let's just go with this so I can um have two
modules at the same time it makes sense right how many souls do I have oh shit
I can upgrade something what should I do engineering what does it do I'll give
no help menu which in multiplier loot multiplier and armor this is health I'm
assuming and during oh no it's just it's stamina and critical hit multiplier
durability is health and balance power resides but then believe it resides
it's a trick shadow on the wall I don't know how people are actors I would get
halfway through a line like that and be like Jesus you are an actor I think I'm
gonna stay with probably this or durability you're camera shy I'm not
camera shy actually I probably I'd probably be a pretty good dramatic
actor you did have a voice acting gig for that phone game I did you're right I
think I think I could be a pretty good actor if I really wanted to um I don't
know I I don't want to ruin the character so it's just tell me if
somebody helped me should I just do durability I feel like that's safe I
mean I do act on the big event streams right are you come sometimes you know
like I get into character I'm gonna do health because you know whatever that's
gonna be healthier okay cool theater kid that's fine all right so yeah now I can
put these both in so what does this do slightly reduces the internal damage
caused by rapid cooling well it's good just to have them both I'm sure I'll
find more so this system I'm assuming is probably gonna be like Hollow Knight
right it's kind of what it looks like it might be okay cool so now what what is
the alchemy capsule thing what does this do quest items no it's materials no what
is it I keep picking it up where is it it's not a quest item and it's not
materials it's not in my access belt where what is it what is it it's just
souls it is please eat a booger I keep picking it up the multi versus banner is
still there no it's not I took it off didn't I it shouldn't be there is it
hold on everybody relax it's not still there right fuck it is still there all
right we're good we're good why would there ever be a sponsor on this game
from oh I like crashed my game what happened what I do oh I like alt tab
then it did this that reset the area why is this lagging it really does not like
that I alt tabbed restart try to restart the back of the main menu and restart
alt tab again shit um I'm gonna it saves it right here right I'll just reload it
the Devon chat right now help what do I do I'll just restart it that's fine I
think I'm gonna be sick shit what happened I turned multi versus banner
and my game freaked out why is that such a stupid okay um I think I have to reset
the whole game give me one sec restart the whole game I'm interested I'm I'm
still here trust me when I would have stopped by now I would have okay let's
try it again Nvidia GeForce RTX does anybody actually turn that on I have a
3090 and I have I don't think I've ever used it I think we turned it on for one
minute in Resident Evil 8 I don't know I just to me it's just like oh hey RTX is
cool it might like fuck up the whole game though every time I've ever used it
it just slows everything down the chest over here that hurt why is this head
shaped like Stewie Griffin what I have a musket how do I use it wait hold on I
can wait a minute why didn't I do this alchemy damage flame frost and
fulmination when she uses alchemy capsules for each attack alchemical
damage fills a gauge which when full triggers an affliction which lasts and
okay ignite frost full metal alchemist is electrocution so should I have 36
bullets how many bullets do I have 34 does this refill do I have infinite no
I only have 34 okay don't waste it let's try it though what's the range on it
that's fucking way I've rented a money that's actually pretty cool all right
that's cool so you just this is ammo you just pick it up you wasted all your ammo
I didn't I needed to see how it worked before I fought anything a lantern new
zone ran it caught what does this cobblestone do okay there is a jump
attack there's a hover attack too I do like the fact that the dodge when you
dodge an attack you go around them and not just to the side I do enjoy I enjoy
it what happened to my eyebrows what do you mean ooh here flame resistance down
but everything else up let's put it on I thought this hit pog shoes okay
endurance up cool all right let's go this is blocked oh yeah shortcut I think
maybe new enemy type flame well item I thought I dodged it I think the i-frames
are small I don't think they're very big that's fun excuse me what's with the
i-frames that's cuz I alt tab that's annoying I alt tab nice hairline angle I
think it looks fine that's very generous the backstab range on that was I was a
hundred feet away you're dodging into where they attack I know that like when
you first came to this channel you probably didn't see it but it says no
back seating I got a compass oh I can set a waypoint nemesis claws excuse me
already got a new weapon all right hold on this is the scales better with agility
52 this is what about hold on wait is impact all right this is worse but
counter it's any parry that is time just right reverses the effects of the
enemy's attack and deals physical damage how are they they cool like
scarecrow hands so that's a parry I wonder how hard it is to do I try it I
try for a minute somebody else can somebody else to read that I didn't mean
to press that button there would do you're balding I'm almost 40 don't worry
and I know wish you're gonna have you wish you have this here when you're 37
you will wish that you had this fucking hairline when you're almost 40 like me
how do I get up there I can definitely get up there there's a chest up there
how do I get up here it's like an elevator or something maybe the rope I
don't think there's a grab shit shoot the gun and I re-aim the gun I don't
think I can get up there I know maybe later wait shit there's a chest up there
the other rope I don't know if I can get up there I'm just waiting to say the
solution you know being a streamer is great for a few reasons it has you know
has its pros and cons right during a broadcast but it it's great to be able
to just kind of go like this and then go oh what if I uh what if I attack the
ropes and then everyone's like oh he figured it out pog that's the best part
about being a streamer is you just don't know when I just look at chat and read
the answer and that's what we all do it everybody does it if you're a streamer
and you say you don't do that come on Gwen it's it's very subtle it's like the
where do I fucking go guys oh you know what I could try I could try the jumping
twice here all right well I'm just leaving that should not have hurt game
got a lower grade for that why one full letter grade oh this is it I just got
sucked into the game can you fast travel see the bald spot good I don't have a
bald spot all right what about this boutique wait I can just buy this stuff
all right the letter grade came back so I own the compass oh I can sell all
right there's anything can I sell this stuff you look at so I this is just the
crunchies from those other games that we won't we will not compare it to I can
level up again oh I can just use it from here that work oh okay I guess it worked
all right so agility yeah I think that makes sense right I'm weapon that scales
with agility most of my stuff is scaling with agility all right that was cool so
from here I'm trying to figure out what to go from here I gotta check for secret
areas there's probably a secret area behind this rock like that I might that
I'm doing on my own and thinking of yeah like why like I feel like I'm trying to
use my knowledge of the game and everything that there's a secret behind
the rock and it's like a rare weapon it might be I don't know it's possible I'm
pretty I have a lot of game knowledge so ordinary vile all right let's get
another boss I'm using the new weapons all right how do I get them to spin
didn't they go last time how do I get how do I do that didn't they spin am I
out of my mind they spun there it is okay it's the next one I actually like I
kind of like the cause I didn't get anything oh what all right oh I got a
key they put you in a box with a camera this time new enemy type quiet you can
tell that he's not playing the game you know I've thought of before I thought of
hiring somebody that was a true video gamer right and just have them off to
the side while I sit there and we have we have a controller setup where they're
both the controllers are player one you know I mean so we have two controllers
both are player one it's not player one and player two so they would have a
controller here and I would have the same controller and they'd be doing
insane and I can whenever I want just take over and and and just start
playing and hold up the controller and be like the fuck are you talking about
I'm literally doing it and move on my own show me moving with the controller
and everything you would absolutely fall for it because why would you ever think
it wasn't happening destiny to PvP I'll say it again my fair part of that whole
scream was Aaron Aaron I think I think you can actually hear me laugh off like
camera well not off camera but in the call Aaron Aaron it's too good it's
perfect house oh the R2 is actually really good on that I like the R2 make
on house I don't want to get to kill if you could be any dinosaur what would you
want to be pterodactyl they're the only ones who truly survived because they
turned into birds this'll we're getting weapons every five seconds here really
that's another weapon falchion and saber see affinity let me try these are cool
what's the special I was you why would you use a different weapon is there a
reason to use a different item how much more damage does this do 56 this has
yeah he's the he's a better I'll use him for a little while it overheats really
quickly I feel like the move kit is way better I think laws they're okay oh yeah
I'd be a pterodactyl because I essentially every modern dinosaur is a
pterodactyl and when my money modern dinosaur I mean birds and alligators
survive too I mean they're fucking based you know what I mean like of course
they're gonna live catalyst you have enough materials to upgrade the brett
open the upgrades menu at a vestal and use Lavo you see our catalysts to
increase the number of doses okay so this is like a s to splash all right
that's good I do everything over here did I see
everything it's this we need a tool to break this oh oh I do no I don't
got seen that boats gonna take you to Paris uh you sure how do I get back
here unstable lightning ram all right how do I get back here actually don't
remember my god get absolutely fucking decimated get fucking decimated this
guy fucking easy I win do I just have like the perfect build for that that
was not hard that guy was very very much chump that guy I was a test that's the
first time they've ever used this thing it's gonna cut to like the doctor
robotic level of mad scientist over here in some ditch that's hiding with a
remote control being like blasted I can't believe my creation was killed so
easily that's how that's that kind of the level of how bad that was hey I'll
take it I'm happy the first guy was actually pretty hard the first guy was
pretty challenging although I did kind of cheese that so is that really fair
for me to say that this boat will take me to Paris make sure I can't do
anything else I cheese the absolute hell what difficulty is it it's the whatever
the regular one I cheese that app 100% you're going to meet your compact
ancestor on France I'm not French on France wait what is this the do it
territory one of the mods is trying to gaslight me but though pterosaurs lived
among dinosaurs and certainly looked like dinosaurs to the untrained eye the
two groups are not the same okay pterodactyls weren't dinosaurs they were
another species hold on wait it was Paris across the lake that's not where I
came from right is that where I came from that doesn't make any sense they
wouldn't know right I had to go down a hole this uh-huh no I was gonna say you
could have you could have shot my head of a cannon over here in the beginning
of the game I gotta find a vest a vest you'll not a bonfire I don't lose all
those souls right okay what all right I think you went down the river Cian that
goes right through the middle of Paris what where am I I don't even know never
mind he is playing yeah I climb this oh my god you ruined my moment I actually
I'm kind of scared because I where's the I need a safe point this one there but
chest no frost grenade cool I like this area cool I can probably level up a
couple of times oh no you can't go through the gate right how come you can
go through the gate but I can't all right well there's the bonfire yes
whatever it is best still can you do something funny my mom is watching no
go do your homework about I think it's just agility and durability if I can do
both I can crush some crunchies okay is that enough other durability he's 24
I'm gonna hold on to the key you don't know that does the price go up every
time or down every time wait is that how many oh I have 218 of these why am I
buying them okay let's uh stretch out a little a little bit of balm what's the
best salad recipe to learn for a recent grad depends on what you like red
cabbage with Caesar salad I usually don't like Caesar salad to me is just
is not is not a food do I feel is it weird for me to say that I don't feel I
feel like Caesar salad is not a rough food it's not a real food it's like
shredded lettuce croutons and like fucking dressing I genuinely don't find
to be a real food what about chicken well hold on you didn't say chicken
Caesar salad we're talking about just Caesar salad chicken Caesar salad
changes everything is this free spot I didn't even ask this question does this
respawn enemies I don't think it does okay it does okay what was I saying yeah
okay so I Caesar salad to me is well the new listen the nutritional content of
just regular lettuce is really not that high the nutritional content of just
chunks of bread just croutons is really not that high so if you're eating a
Caesar salad lunch you're not really getting very much it's just kind of
nothing a little side of a Caesar salad that's fine but if it's like oh yeah
I'll take a Caesar salad you're not really getting a whole lot of nutritional
value is not but it tastes good you name me a bunch of other things that tastes
good too that much better for you can I get up there lettuce has vitamins okay
lettuce has the vitamins I don't think lettuce has that many vitamins it
depends what kind of lettuce you're talking about spinach yeah you didn't
say spinach was you said lettuce I love spinach spinach is one of my favorite
foods spinach is one of the best things ever what am I good how do I get out of
here how do I get out of here oh okay water flask yeah that's cool you know I
think the problem with salads are or is the problem with a salad for me is when
I'm hungry I don't it's not like oh I'm hungry I can't wait to eat salad I wish
salad was more substantial and I know that you can make salad more substantial
right but eventually you get to a point where there's so much shit in the salad
that it's kind of just like I'm a mess oh god come on what the oh my goodness
that was a long cool down romaine is all right right remains good salad toppers
all right well let me check this way that's a Boston take maybe it is because
on the East Coast and this is completely different on than it is here in Vegas
and on the West Coast I've found I was spoiled rotten with some of the on the
East Coast just has some of the best pizza the best sub shops the best
fucking sandwich places oh you want it you want like a big sub you're the best
in the world is on the East Coast Boston New York Philadelphia I mean I was
spoiled rotten so eating like a big steak and cheese with my grilled onions
on it I don't want to eat the salad with pine nuts like what happened I'm so
jealous I miss it all the time I really do going back to the East Coast going
back to Boston getting pizza from there just hits so different so different a
good nice thin crust just right out of the oven oh my god it's not the same not
here not at all there's decent pizza places around here but I wouldn't call
them good hold on I gotta be quiet this is kind of a hard pull I won't do it
all right we're good the East Coast is terrible for stargazing I'd rather a
steak and cheese sub than stargazing okay on my tier list of location based
things stargazing is way below like a Philly cheese steak it just it just is
but I love Vegas I love it out here so while I lose a lot of my favorite local
awesome sub shops and pizza places I gained Las Vegas which is man there's a
whole lot more to do there's a whole lot more going on out here I gotta put some
stuff in my bar here all right hold on so I go back and this game is fun I
actually like this game I have to be pessimistic Andy every time I open a
video game this is I actually think this is games cute yes it's cute oh wait get
that off I hear something large New Jersey pizza and subs are amazing I know
New York New Jersey don't all right do I got seen Vegas kind of scares me I
went there as a minor and it was and I feel I don't know what he said but Vegas
is a very adult city that's true oh my god just picked up a water flask you
water drink it in front of her five petrification grenades a glass of water
hey I'll bring in the whole boat what else you got in there why am I why is
mod chat haunting me right now a mod right now is posting their pizza that
they got and it's fucking amazing looking what the hell why are you
taunting me that looks so good oh my god I want it I just want that to burn my
face so bad I want to take a bite of that and have like the cheese come off
slide off and hit me right here and and I go I want it so bad I want to be the
first person to do that and everybody else all collectively puts their pieces
down you know I'm saying like we get it there it is oh yeah okay you got a
plate and everybody goes oh all right and we wait we like just talk about like
sports for fucking ten minutes and I go no no that's not ready it's hot hot hot
hot hot hot I point over at the net person that over here hot dude hot it's
hot hot hot and they go oh okay thanks man I feel like I should level up I
don't like this what is that um try to say fucking go I have I only have two
here I got it I got here yeah I got my right I jumped this fence there's a
weirdo over there jump animation jump animation looks like that tick-tock
where they go you know I'm talking about where they go they go like side to side
like this you know what I'm talking about it's where they go like this they
go like some people must have to know what I'm talking about they put their
arms up and it's like boing boing boing boing boomer on tick-tock I don't use
tick-tock I'm just I was trying to relate that to some of you guys know
I'm saying all right there's a there's a fight here so quiet now it was midair
through the frost is so unbelievable in this game it's like a free hit all right
this guy's kind of hard is this a class thing because this is the best class for
sure the only people on tick-tock are influencers I you I don't even you might
need to walk that one back that's not true I feel like I'm close to a boss
all right this is kind of scary it's kind of fucked up I'm gonna pick this
up and something's gonna drop right ah where is it there's something about that
metal boom boom boom boom talk more about lettuce um what do you want me to say
shit all right I'm gonna I'm gonna just gun this person new area oh wait a
minute this is a shortcut or something it's not a shortcut there's just one
there's just one I'll take it flame resistance violet oh there's
definitely gonna be a flame enemy lettuce okay so there's lettuce is um I
love the taste of lettuce and mayo and like like lettuce chicken and mayo
together like that shredded lettuce all right I need to play really cautiously
here no yeah I'm playing like an absolute coward right now there's no
way I'm gonna not guy to do anything there's no diminishing returns on frost
then why I'm gonna just the combo every time oh my god okay I need health fire
chain I can upgrade the weapons can I what should I do which one should I
upgrade I'm running out of ammo shit all right hold on wait wait wait I'm not
going over there yet upgrade the gun the gun is alchemy though hold on great to
stable charging my god I was actually puked okay this is just a pole no all
right flame grenade take that off all right explosive grenade what about the
compass maybe I'll use it and then frost grenade and take this off so what does
the compass do we use it what does it do oh wow oh I can I can just bet all
right that's cool I get to have a quest marker I'll take it that's fine with me
oh thank God I need that right now is it on hard I could I have even so I
don't think I could even selected hard I don't think that was an option I just
played on there whatever the regular mode is I'm gonna sneeze yes shortcut
there's no pop there's no pause oh there is a positive nevermind it's not like
the Voldemort game that we can't say there we go should I do I don't know I
feel like the gun is amazing it's actually incredible and I should have
started with it show Otto I will just not yet no I'm playing this game I don't
think it's power ever engineering engineering is what like a luck stat in
this game how come you're changing your camera angles every stream do you have
ass acne you've never seen a camera from back there no you when that's never
happened maybe a point in there yeah I feel like it's probably a good idea this
is like stamina right yeah I haven't have to do it again all right so how
does this scale wait a second hold on that's a that's a weapon I thought that
was a module so I say whatever you want about this game go ahead and say it but
this is the fifth weapon in an hour in ten minutes what is this all right it's
kind of funky cool and now it's on fire oh yeah that's cool not gonna be using
it though 60 wait 61 plus 25 this is better I guess I mean what do I want to
upgrade this is the highest scaling I'll try it for a few minutes why not wait
can I come on oh my goodness you don't doesn't have to be a side arm that's not
even a side arm this is an actual weapon all right cool well I'll try it for a
little while are you the booger guy oh yeah you probably found me from that
clip of me like I thought the stream was off then the camera was still on it was
pretty dark but I said you know you can still see and I just I just ate a shit
little bit too I was I was eating boogers in the chair for like ten
straight minutes I know everyone's seen the clip by now but whatever yeah that's
fine I'm glad you found the stream I mean without that viral clip I wouldn't
have you know you wouldn't have been here you wouldn't have found it all
right so this is just the three doses oh all right I'll come back and figure this
out later these grenades work pretty well yeah I'm gonna buy many of these I
can look at I can upgrade something so what can I upgrade how come there's still
a you can upgrade thing oh cuz I have keys I'm gonna hold on to him dog I'm
not I want to use him all right let's go so that I opened up the shortcut which
is here now I'm not wearing a hairnet as items cool god damn it everything has
been cool so far I'm going the wrong way I'm definitely going the wrong way
there it is this is the right way right yeah oh shit oh shit oh shit am I going
wrong am I going the wrong way wait is that the wrong way didn't I open up a
shortcut that led right here wait I'm confused oh thanks God I've got the
compass otherwise this would have been a lot harder there it is excellent I am
yes okay we got it I'm so glad that exists hey you know what they could have
done which would have been funny if to turn the compass on it takes souls it's
like 500 souls to turn the compass on so that would be funny and it scales as you
level would have been kind of fun that would have been kind of funny all right
there we go this is what I'm doing don't worry about that this is it all
right let's freaking go the hell was that that's fire looks crazy that
actually looks awesome shit oh now you're on fire we haven't been on fire
this whole time that took a long time to get you there get up there get up go go
go go go go no ammo be drunk be talking about I could be using a yo-yo cuz it's
kind of fun all right the weapons cool but it's a little too slow for me that's
a little too much to lead up very cool though essence of a valiant spirit okay
I gotta go this way wait I already came this way did I look can I open that
what's all those wait where am I compass thank you this up there's no way I
ever would have figured that out that like you kidding me I would never would
have jumped up here for no reason why is the camera get worse every stream this
camera is in a perfect angle it's in a perfect position this is the most in
frame I've ever been in my whole life on stream it's the most in frame this is
the most you've seen me here and I just maybe drink a potion time that person
out for an hour at least an hour endurance and armor yep absolute in
frame this is the most absolutely in frame I've ever been pretty the compass
a like a boss is incoming could be wrong I wonder how much I'm going to
absolutely style on this boss coming up find out I've got a ton where are these
petrification grenades like ten of these this is this immobilizes enemies all
right well let's go look directly into the camera for a little while no why am
I hearing this music I was just throwing rocks oh no can we talk but there's like
what is that how do I talk through the window and I get in I don't think I can
even talk to this person oh no thank you how all right shoot this guy down I
don't know I don't read this fighting people okay now I can read the note on
the ground I don't even why do I want I don't want to read the note what though
oh my god that's really what that was okay that shouldn't hurt by the way I'm
made out of like stainless steel or something why would that hurt I'm a
robot I made out of metal and shit why would a falling five feet off why would
that hurt me it's like driving through a pothole all right that's fair wait
what's over here even at max resolution your cameras off wow that does a lot of
damage they quit work dogs he's ranging he's raging why'd I say
ranging okay okay oh what is it whoo nice okay cool so wait hold on this
game's cute this is cute game oh all right they still streaming tomorrow I am
not I'm well by the way those that are trickling in let's go over it again so
oh I have to I've been trying to figure out I'm gonna do this I have to sign and
ship a thousand baseballs and it's time to do that so what we're doing is we're
doing an Omega weekend this weekend they're the plan was I was gonna do
maybe tomorrow and Wednesday but I said you know what no I'm gonna get this done
I want to get it done I want to actually put real time into it and care so I'm
gonna spend the next couple days signing boxing and shipping a thousand
baseballs so Friday Saturday Sunday we're gonna do an Omega weekend three
days in a row stream the signing that's it's possible but I'm not gonna
guarantee that I'm gonna say that probably won't happen all right do I have
enough stream the signing stream the signing I yeah I don't know I don't it
feels odd to me I don't want to do that I have a lot of these okay I I have a
criticism if the devs are watching I I like it when it goes like this shows the
amount that I added like when it I want it to be like you know what I mean
because when I use one of these in the menu it's just kind of like yeah I used
it it doesn't like show that like on the bottom or something it says like the
amount that's on it but I don't have a real-time calculation they're not
watching you told me they were you literally said that like an hour ago
all right it's time to choose a weapon this would be 60 this would be it's not
this one it's probably this or what would that be 48 is it the claws or is
it the the falchion the claws are gonna have the best scaling but do I like them
better I'll show on or or claws I this move set was better but it scales worse
not that it matters at this early should be the falchion all right get a poll
going because I actually don't know and I'm seeing a lot of both one for
falchion and saber two for claws and we're gonna be upgrading that buddy the
long face because I'm a goofy motherfucker they die do I have to
answer that one or two one is falchion and saber and two is nemesis claws one
two I'm afraid to alt tab so I can't click on it so hopefully you guys can I
get an update of what the percentage is claws have a parry yeah but all right so
this has a parry but this has the cool blade tornado that has a different
damage scale it's interesting falchion is winning by a lot okay oh I didn't we
didn't even look at this yeah all right so there's no way it's coming back
congratulations I'll share and saber enjoyers that's what we're gonna
upgrade and I'm gonna do it right now there we go all right so that I'm gonna
be doing a lot more damage I think looks good very cool other moves that on this
is good as well cool all right I'm ready can you play so much or scare
Saturdays this October we'll do a bunch of horror stuff I'll do a lot of horror
stuff this month coming up we'll get a list so good it takes almost the whole
stamina bar but it kills almost anything in one hit will you do Halloween movie
night if I can find some more public domain horror movies yeah they have to
be public domain all right let's get it where we going here yeah oh that came
out far that move is so good there's a combo with the R2 pretty good you know I
really do wonder I genuinely probably should look into this I wonder just how
much money it would cost what the cost effectiveness kind of ratio there would
be to like how much this cost or how fun we could have on stream for me to just
buy the licensing streaming rights to be able to show a movie on stream for a
night it can't be that expensive some of these old movies right some of these
old old fucking movies there's no way that would be you know how much am I
willing to pay for that a lot more than I think a lot of you guys think actually
go through the rights holders and be like hey can I scream this movie without
you having a problem with it what the fuck you can do that I wonder how far
that could go right I wonder how much money would it take to stream like
gremlins to somebody was saying I wonder what that would cost it's I mean it's
Warner right it's expensive but not that bad I know people that own a retro shit
wait hold on you do wait wait wait wait it I want to all tab but with mods mods
find that person that just said that that they know how that works and and I
would like to question them and you know I mean I want to like talk to them can
we like ask that person some stuff and I want to interrogate that person find
that person because we're gonna interrogate what do you know about
getting the rights to gremlins to what do you know I know people that own a
retro cinema and they do it all the time all right well let's maybe we could
find out some info because I am willing I'm not kidding around I I wish I was
joking when I say this but I'm willing to put thousands and thousands of
dollars and to be to be able to do that I am willing to put up money to be able
to stream some old dumb horror movie that could get the stream shut down
right because they have to be a license pretty much per movie wouldn't that be
fun should we'd be like licensed movie Andy let's do it let's do it I'm gonna
look into it I'm gonna get on the phone with community Jake literally tonight
let's see if it's possible well I will talk to the person that has experience
doing it because that would be really fun oh no what happens if it's too fun
and that's like all I want to do oh well whatever private domain movie night
that's right oh you were over here that doesn't stagger too dark over here I
can't see yeah let's let's buy the licensing rights to a bunch of old horror
movies and maybe who cares movies that aren't horrible I mean I wonder how
much does it cost to stream a licensing deal with like three men and a baby that
possible I mean these movies are old they're really old and they're probably
on streaming services I don't know what about an Amazon watch party see I don't
want to do that because that I that kind of like sucks from my understanding the
way that that works is only certain people from certain regions can do it
there's a very limited amount of shows to watch and it's not me streaming it
right doesn't it like take over the stream and it's not like me hanging out
with like a cam on right it's pretty limited to what you can do with it I
would rather have people be able to hang out and enjoy it they never work either
if it's you and a mini player no no no no I would I would want to buy one night
streaming rights to some of these movies and just do it the way that we would
want to do it the vaude would have to be destroyed too yeah I just wouldn't
turn the vaude on that would be a thing that people knew was gonna happen right
it's hey we're do we're streaming this movie it cost me like $14,000 to buy the
rights to stream this movie for a night you're gonna want to be there alive
because it's not gonna be I'm not gonna have a vaude or whatever like insane
amount of money it costs I'm afraid of this they're a shortcut or something I'm
afraid of going through there oh hello wait hold on just release the audio
recording of your voice that could do that probably get it sponsored I don't
think I would want to do that because I would want us to be able to just say and
have just have fun and not worry about like oh you know the rights holder is
here can't talk about how like shitty that scene was right it's just I'm buying
the rights to stream this that's it unless it was made very clear that the
rights holder that they just didn't care at all they're like you'd literally say
whatever you want you can do whatever you want please do it with Morbius I do
not I do not have the capital to be able to buy the rights to stream Morbius
you're talking about potentially I wanted to take a wild guess it would
probably cost hundreds of thousands of dollars to stream Morbius legally to this
channel can you imagine if I spent like five hundred and like thirty thousand
dollars just just liquidate everything I own to be able to stream Morbius for one
night I mean that would be kind of funny then that would probably get a lot of
press streamer liquidates entire net worth to stream Morbius for one night
just like two thousand one hundred and twenty five people you know what I mean
it would be it would be like that it would be like oh yeah dude Morbius let's
go like two thousand one hundred and and like ten people would show up all
right where's the bonfire that would be so funny though I think to make that
even a reality I'm trying to think of the legal way logistically you would
have to do that I would need to make a business I would have to make a new LLC
or something right and I'm a movie theater it's a oh yes I'm a movie
theater and I'm streaming movies and then buy the rights for my movie theater
to stream to like thirty or forty thousand people with my movie see how
would this even work all right I'm getting lost here where's the I'm talking
about being okay wait wait where am I wait there's a bonfire here somewhere see
if you should contact Warner and see if they would want to do a gremlins movie
night I don't I I don't think okay here we go I don't think that no that's not
gonna happen that would not happen yeah I mean we would there would be a we
would do it and it'd be fun but there's no way it's not possible I'm not I I am a
I am a small fry in the grand scheme of all media that's not gonna happen I'm a
small fry in the grand scheme of things I'm not I cannot get the rights to
gremlins you know what I mean it's not happening
don't anymore crunchies I do have a crunchy so you mean I just used it I
want like a and count on the bottom right I see I'm thinking health or just
keep going with his agility I do another weapon no what do I do
see health can you run out of the compass all right I feel like there's
something going on here yeah I I'm trying to think of how much some of
these old horror movies that no one real I 10 grand 20 grand would be let's be
realistic how much do you think that would really be then if I was gonna buy
the rights to scream for one night like five four or five movies that would be
every a lot I'll be 4k 5k maybe not more than a few thousand I wonder what the
Agra range on this out of here all right let's get this is definitely boss I have
three of these keys I wonder if I should use them yeah cuz something very we talk
about this sometimes something very important to know is if a movie is free
to watch it is not free to stream it to broadcast I don't I don't have
broadcasting rights to some of these properties right there's a huge
difference between this is free to watch and this is free to broadcast be cool
though I'll look into it maybe if you've used one of the platforms that you
stream the ads they'll they won't care no I would need because the way that it
works right on I think on twitch is somebody can just shut the stream down
they can just claim the stream they can be like nope I don't think so and just
turn it off so it would have to be expressed written permission from the
rights holder so no one can just go excuse me turn this off it'd be like no
no no that I've already been in contact with which and the rights holder this is
the screen staying on I'll look into it I really will I don't care scream it
loser we're trying to figure out how risky stupid don't fall off the edge
they can hit each other shit was dumb what the fuck has happened okay we're
good I didn't use any heels streaming but make everything look like a normal
stream have a cover of you gaming a random video game and everything then
just play movies illegally without anyone noticing how does that doesn't
make any sense what's your your thought process on that stream with a game but
then have the movie like what that we switch to so when people say that hey
this twitch staff in chat I hit a button and it goes to me playing steel rising
like we got like mom caught us I mean that would be funny but I would get
banned I don't know how long you can request a stream it for free oh yeah
absolutely you a lot of these talks would be hey can I do this not hey can I
give you $25,000 to stream the gremlins to no it would be like hey can we work
something out that will start there you start at hey can I do this and then it
goes through well I don't think so not unless you decide to pay for the rights
that's when you go negotiator in there me I'll bring that price down how much
was it I was 25 grand best I can do is 16 thousand and then they never they
never answer the phone again does this open ah that's a boss for sure I tried
to dodge I ran a stamina these guys are annoying as you're not over there why
am I looking over there there's no iframes where are the iframes what
happened um I think I just turned on my Xbox this is not connected to the
computer anymore I think I turned I just turned the Xbox on that's in like another
room see it's like still on it's not plugged in well how did I do that Holly
are you watching can you turn the Xbox up can you go in the other room and to
turn the Xbox off I don't know she might not even be here how is that even
possible can I shouldn't I be listed why would that happen I don't think she's
here oh wait no I hope I better not be doing anything on the Xbox what the
fuck is happening oh shit I don't know how to play the keyboard and mouse okay
I I have it's I have I'll be give me a second I'll be right back yeah that's
precisely what happened by the way it was just on somebody said thank you for
your confirmation of a thousand V bucks okay plugging it in okay we're good show
Otto I will before the three events just wait okay we good we're back we want
Otto now are you and he's sleeping like he's leave him alone he's sleeping what
happened what happened right this I feel like I'm sitting in the wrong spot it
feels different oh it's cuz I'm off this thing okay all right let's go did I give
everything in the middle here we go Eugene Dave Van Kansen's workshop
someone hid upstairs I just need to find a way in from the outside I'm on
sure if I'll constant new stuff Diane reaches he's just better and Diane shoes
I mean besides the lightning resistance he's a better I only have one hat okay
on sewer somebody's upstairs well I'm not going that way
you're looking with Bergen worth scum backs
it's not raised that up when you don't even know you don't know what that is if
you don't know what that is then I mean you're watching this game no Bergen
worth not burger boy burger boy burger boy
lot crazed bastard all right I can I have three keys what does this do
because it's I can upgrade this slot is this a bad idea or should I just start
with the four slots first don't do that let's you put a key oh right I have a
tier two I'm doing it okay now what okay so this is tier two all right grade two
stable charging and grade two efficient charging this module moderately
increases balance during charged attacks what does that mean this module
moderately increases the physical damage caused by a successful fully
charged attack what is balance what is that the boys it's like kind of like
super armor balances boys all right I'll keep up I'll try it why not all right
let's go boys all right I feel like there's a boss so let me get rid of the
souls that I don't want to wait can I level up again no so let's spend these
so I don't lose them if I die hold on what about equipment can I buy
something else this is cell right am I crazy yeah no I don't know wait a minute
oh wait wait wait wait wait wait wait what what hold on there's a whole way
that I can there's a whole menu of items what is this glass core batons how come
I didn't see this what is that halberd thank God I don't really care about any
of this although this seems kind of cool what's this thing 15 armor hmm so I
get the hood this is worse re armor yeah these are these are worse but hold on
well I can buy modules this module slightly increases armor and balance
when her health is low but that seems amazing oh that's even better I want
this one I don't know who gives a shit about this more endurance all right let's
do it time let's see if I can beat the boss first try you're looking fresh do
you any favorite insects dragonflies earwigs and what was the question I
don't remember factories I want to go this way first it wants me to go that
way but not yet this is just a shortcut back here you don't really need your
wigs yeah your wigs are cool they get a bad rap they're funny they're cute
they're harmless are they a pest oh they're a pest you're a pest someone
he's aggressive he's getting he's getting aggressive not gonna hit me with
that shit pop up there and deal with this bozo shit hold on all right baby
earwigs eat each other's poop I don't think you know how just how gross a lot
of stuff in the animal kingdom is up that way I think no this way
investigate why hold on there's somebody dead up there wait can I go that way
oh I get up there investigate the death of the dolphin all right oh I climb a
bookcase or something ladders don't work what have I done okay how do I get up
here it has to be a way I didn't in there from somewhere outside right oh
there are worms in your skin there are not some outlandish thing to say that's
truly outlandish just well you're making no sense you can't freak me out with
something like that sorry I can't get up there it looks like that way but I don't
think I can get up there that way yeah look how do I get up there I don't
understand oh cool spend all that time how much for a bottle of your hair oil
100 million dollars in in USD in United States dollars us cash not an IO not an
IOU not like oh I'm gonna do a I'll do a bank transfer no I want it I want it
like two lawyers present and I wanted to be signed and I want a hundred million
dollars US cash money real just money cash in a briefcase type shit how do I
know that you'll give me the oil I'll do it at the meeting I got a lawyer on
my side you get a lawyer on your side and out we'll do it there I hope you
have one for your movie stream I'm gonna figure that out I'm gonna use a law
firm I'm gonna use my trusted law firm gonzo and gonzo it's a funny to get the
rights to have gonzo be my lawyer would probably cost more money than just
without like a shirt on to the meeting and have like sunglasses and have like a
bad sunburn all over me and being like and being a bathing suit and be like
here's 20 grand it would cost more money to do it the other way like it
would cost gonzo as a lawyer would be like a hundred thousand dollars forget
that I can literally just show up without a lawyer and just give them a
check for 20 grand it would be less money why would you have no shirt on
I came to the beach not real why is he getting naked at the beach what are you
talking about I said I said I have no shirt with a bathing suit and like a
sunburn and sunglasses like I just came from the beach like a towel over my
shoulder let's get this deal done man let's go no I'm not naked stop saying
naked that's weird what are you talking about why were you at the beach it was
relaxing before a stressful period I don't know I'm saying like it would be
so casual instead of having to hire gonzo for a 500 grand I used to show up
with a tank top it like it like long socks dad socks how to slide through
there through like the lobby were you at the beach with gonzo no this way I
thought I missed it and I was gonna be pissed whoa don't Mario this okay
nothing else in here wait what's this there are two down here wall two down
here two two two all right I got it got it got it got it got it Jesus didn't I
just make that way more exciting oh what's that this increases health I have
that on nevermind this has got 35 armor why is this so much better than
everything else that endurance game is terrible this thing's so much better
it's 20 it's Lady Dimitri soon I'll put it on just fun I guess this is better
okay cool it's for style I see getting a lot of frame flame resistance stuff
wait am I in that house I am in that house all right oh I got parried that
was a slash-dash and you fucked it up get it off okay I'm not in that house I
will be soon I will be very soon what the fuck dude what was that
oh I think I'm supposed to fall down here I've been unlocking these doors I
have no idea where they go I guess I guess this is a shortcut to okay to
here but what does this do for me I'm going back to the bonfire do I have any
crunchies I do I'm going damage can you react to the Nintendo Direct tomorrow
no I'm sorry it's like 7 a.m. it's 7 a.m. Pacific or something it's way too early
it's 6 to 7 a.m. or something it's not gonna happen I need to sell some stuff
okay I am gonna sell how much do I need like 300 this is probably a bad idea but
whatever shit I have the same problem oh wait a minute uh I can do this right yep
okay so this is more health we want your reaction I don't there's nothing in
that Nintendo's coming out with it I'm I wanted to play I don't think it is
anything I'm I can think of I don't I can't think of it I didn't do the the
summer games thing whatever was our games calm I didn't do that either let me
buy some bullets all right whatever I have to do let's try this again now okay
we're going this way I think I'm close to something I'm not gonna fight we're
just gonna run here the mobile walkway okay sure thing I think it sounds like
it's gonna explode I think chasing me yeah there is why did you chase me this
whole way how do I get over there all this way okay sure okay like the
barnyard PC game I don't know that is shit shit how do I get over here can you
please play sly Cooper that's where I draw the line I'm sorry that's where I
draw the line I don't know where to go this way I was up on that walkway before
I get up there damn it I don't know is this correct I hope so yeah okay so then
from here and go this way right yes yes sorry I was muted um so I think it's
right there weird okay wait what the fuck how do I get over there it's
clearly there's a staircase right there but how do I get over here what the hell
this is confusing I jump out of this how do I get over here okay this takes me
all the way back around again then I don't get this what the hell how am I
lost in a game with a quest marker do you understand that there's there's
literally one fucking way to get over here and it's like up down these stairs
and then down those stairs and then left out of that building and then down those
stairs and then around those stairs and through that door and it's only why it's
not like I can't just walk straight you need to put you in a box with four
buttons to win there are I there are you there are four buttons there's nothing
up here that it right there is that it right there I go in there into the right
prepare the walkway I it's up there is it not there I just got her is the game
good it was feel about 15 minutes ago now this is not right I go down from here
no this is not right it is that door it has to be right what is this this is
that door so let's go through here and then to the through up here I can't get
I can't get away how do I get out of here how do I get out of here sure I'd be
honest how do I get the fuck out of this maze how do I get over there how come
you're doing this to us tell me where to go just tell me where to go how do I go
that way like in this building but I can't how am I supposed to do that I
was already up there no help no no no yes help yes help me go the other way
there is no other there's no other way there's only this way I have to go in
there I have to go in there and up and then straight I have to there's no other
way to go no okay I'm fine and then up up and then across is the only way can I
can't go up from here I have to go down and then otherwise get up there how do I
get up there I'm serious bro somebody help me I genuinely don't understand
how to get up there go to the factory port that door I missed it go to the
port by sliding off the roof okay in the port why you the port that's over here
okay I'm gonna go to the port go to the part we slide off the roof I've slidden
off the fuck off god damn dog this okay let's go this way god I'm trying to the
quest marker actually was a detriment again it's telling me to go it's telling
me to go that way whatever you know it you get it you understand I've been
trying to follow the quest marker this is walking away from the quest marker
you told me oh yeah why you get a quest marker how can you get it wrong there's
a quest marker what's wrong to tell me to go that way I'm thinking I am I'm
trying to traverse that way to go whatever you didn't even see this
everyone was telling me to go in the building you didn't see it either
liars this is no way it was the game's fault it was this was the game's fault
worst gamer moment no it's not please it is absolutely not the worst gamer
moment not even close because I was following instructions I followed
directions how did you get that in here oh you didn't okay
let's come for say yeah okay so how about this yeah you guys like all worst
gamer moment but have a best gamer moment every time I get hit by the boss
I will eat a hot dog each hit from the boss is one hot dog I'm fucking kidding
that's not happening not a not a chance in hell that happens it's not happening
it's too late no I'm sorry I didn't my hand was out and I went like this what
did I pick up what did I pick up how come it's not showing me what I pick up
sometimes yeah I went like this and when you went to shake my hand and I
went sorry you got baited okay I got a lot of bullets so many lies sit up
straight there okay so now I'm not gonna go that way just yet this looks
interesting why are your eyes closer together today they are wait is that a
shortcut I thought I was going in the water okay thank God so where the hell
is this it's a shitty shortcut yeah this shortcut is awful this is a shitty
shortcut no sorry we're not we're not we're not doing like a look at and look
at all these look at all these ball fondler Andes well what's the hot dog
stream mmm yeah all the ball fondler Andes think they're gonna get the
spotlight here sorry nope I'm really trying to get that spotlight out of
context that is a little strange second I'm slowly processing which is
happening all these ball fondler Andes that's out of context that that's a
little strange and it's the hot dog stream all the ball fondler Andes what
is that supposed to mean that I'm I'm I'm confusing myself they think they're
gonna get the spotlight I will have to get to it thank you up let ball fondler
go ball Fondler has been unbanned for almost a month what are you talking
about you're my you have a very rectangular forehead yeah when I go like
gosh it's like a fucking hammerhead okay I made it to the forge oh boss time
oh boss fight the strat still works should have taken the bet should have
taken the bet there's still time for me to shake your hand this weapon is too
good it's so good there's no diminishing returns on this should
have taken that bet she's Andy all right should I not use that anymore it's not
okay it's not fair if I use that anymore that's too good it actually probably
should okay it's probably gonna get patched one hot dog I didn't get hit
once that's gonna get patched that's gonna get that out of the game no when
did I get hit I didn't get it once look at your health it was like that already
it was already at minus like 10% all right I've no more cheese I won't do
any more cheese strats it's just too good I've been I cheese the last two
bosses in a row and that's with no points okay if you play the alchemy
class and you get this weapon you'll just you could literally just kill
everybody I won't cheese the bosses anymore the next boss I will not cheese
that I promise I will fight it regularly hold on is there anything else here that's
gonna get patched what is attacking me from somewhere they'll add some type of
bosses cannot be frozen more than once or twice like in a row or something
right ketchup or mustard mustard harder than the boss am I gonna die what the
fuck is he doing all right did I miss anything down here whoo that way yellow
mustard yeah I don't really like yellow mustard I do like brown mustard kind of
ground mustard very good all right I can upgrade this again I need 3,000 souls
that's a lot brown mustard like ground stone ground mustard I'm not gonna use
this fight or flight physical damage and impact when her health is at its lowest
or I mean that's the frost I'm sorry the children in the chat don't like real
mustard I think a lot of people here do that's part of the secret recipe though
I already did this let's keep going this game's cute all right we are about to
repair the walkway you're a corporate honey Dijon spy I like honey mustard but
I prefer stone ground I think it's I like the little pebbles is this sponsored
no and I would have to tell you I'm just playing because I told you I it looks
fun it is fun I would not play this game for three hours if I didn't think it was
fun that should work I just gotta stop being a cheeseball it's been fight the
bosses for real all right so that opens this I like this game too yes it's fine
it's good I think it's good I think it'll it'll scratch some of that itch oh
wait hello why did you turn around that's pretty good get the free hits
using the op weapon isn't cheese that's just the game yeah but I have okay I
have not dodged a boss's attack in two and a half hours that's that's a fact
increases immobilization oh that's kind of good actually I like what I have
better all right ah this works now just in case I miss an item which I don't
think I'm going to okay we're good my friends watching your stream for the
first time he said stop making Rick and Morty jokes that's not very shwifty of
your friend is it sorry I have 31 frost grenades wait no I'm purchasing well
your friend is now never gonna watch the stream ever again why are you such a dad
you'd like to make chat fringe it's fun it'll be fun mine 60 FPS yeah that's it
oh so peace I was given orders to come here an automatic the talks you don't
gonna have this guy's careful consoles dancer I saw you perform in Versailles
when you were first presented to the Queen wait there all of a sudden there
are dialogue options there are machines wreaking havoc on the Esplanade so I
saw yes and a little too closely for my liking it's a miracle I escaped alive
just by these are valid I saw one take a volley of gunfire hold for an instant
then carry on as if nothing happened but no machine however resilient is
indestructible these automats must have a weakness some vital axle gear that we
can target I don't suppose you would know you who share their nature no blast
that is unfortunate I scoured the workshop hoping to shed some light on the
matter but to no avail there are machines wreaking havoc on the Esplanade
so I saw yes and a little too closely for my liking it's a miracle I escaped
alive just by these are valid I saw one take a volley of gunfire hold for an
instant then carry on as if nothing happened but no machine however resilient is indestructible these automats must have a weakness some vital axle gear that we can target I don't suppose you would know why we doing this again this is okay
no blast that is unfortunate I scoured the workshop hoping to shed some light on the matter wasn't that different dialogue wait that this was different dialogue there are machines oh no
just by this but no these automats some vital I don't suppose you would know no
blast I scared okay it's a little on so I was watching a YouTube video the other
night and that was weird I would cut to you like as if I'm talking to this guy
but whatever we'll just that's fine I was I guess I just don't look at the
screen okay so I was watching a YouTube video the other night and I was I may
have been high I've been relaxing and they've been a little high on THC
marijuana and so this video star I was searching for a gameplay video and I got
a video game video that I was looking for and in the middle like two minutes
into this video there was I hate this I'm gonna go like this two minutes into
this video there was an ad you know like oh by the way this this video is
sponsored by this and it was for a different game so it was it was a video
game video and then it went into this kind of hey here's an ad for another
game and it was so long to me that I was I was like why did I click on this this
game that I don't fucking care about why did I open this video I was so high I
was just like why did I do this this is not the video did I search for this and
I forgot the actual reason why I watched the first video I forgot the reason why
I opened the video in the first place so I just left I was like I don't what's
happening and I and then I forgot the video I wanted to go search for it again
I forgot what I was looking for what a stoner hey you can you can um
I have been sent by the Queen it's called being high yeah I'm just um she's
I was so confused though I really why did I open this video I've done that
well sober well cuz the ad was so long in the video and it was for another
video game on a video game video I just like there's no why am I here
I must find I had to click this I had to search for this secret to the tireless
automats your creator well that makes two of us if only I had listened to the
Albert I must attend to a matter of the I don't know anybody Karen but you can
do it on your playthrough wait somebody died new zone you get to drive the
carriage that would it's a full letter grade okay travel Eugene Dave back on
son's horseless carriage allows ages to travel around Paris in addition thanks
to the equipment on board she can do the same thing she Canada Vestal with
messengers allowing ages to receive and reply to letters from her allies turn
the fucking Xbox on again this on fuck I did I can't unplug it look it's on the
Xbox is far away let me make that clear it is far away it's across the entire
my entire place use a wired controller I'm this is what I'm wired I'm plugged
in with a wire to the computer just unplugged the Xbox oh thank you I think
Holly may have turned it off I'm plugged in with a wire okay there we go all right
travel whoa where should I go what's correspondence oh who cares where should
I go main quest is la city and the tool reese thank you Holly that scared the
shit out of me wait Holly you were you in the room at the the Xbox just turn on
and the TV turn on it was I pressing buttons let's get the shit out of me where
should I go la city or to the risk this game looks kind of good it is I think
it's fun really really the bosses are kind of easy but that's the kind of
character I'm playing I won't if I was a strength character I bet you'd be
having a lot more trouble I kept hearing the little dude dude okay where should I
go take the batteries out of the controller now that's a brilliant idea
that's actually a smart idea mmm honest to God that's the smartest thing I've
ever heard oh wait can I oh does that still work I'm gonna go to la city god
I wish you were real you smoking crack again it's pronounced sit a ooh I like
this area wait let me do the e3 walk it's very specific I almost got it I hope
there's an enemy here yep shit I made the game look like shit I'm sorry don't
fire me I do like this area though it's definitely not yeah do it again with
music less hellies I need souls gonna need to upgrade this weapon
dogs are too fast for that whoa whoa whoa whoa
the other one died oh they explode okay I like the fire effects in this game
my eye tricky area right it you're gonna replay it's secure oh I'd rather punch
myself in the face square in the nose then play through secure again if I had
an option here but you can punch yourself as hard as you can directly in
your face like right here or you have to start a new playthrough of secure Oh and
get to the end and beat the whole game get the true ending I'd go now I do it
now you hate secure oh no I don't hate secure oh it's just fucking impossibly
difficult I've gone back to it before in the last since beating it I just go no
no why am I doing this what's the point of you playing with I cannot come up
with a reason to play secure oh yeah that is the hardest game I've ever played
and yes I had the same thing oh you know what maybe I'll play secure oh again
that sounds kind of like fun yeah it's like really tough and but Perry's I get
that's such a fun game and you get to the first boss fight get to lady
butterfly or the big guy the big drunk guy you go what am I doing here I could
play Mario Party and you know what I mean I could know that I don't want to
do that I could do anything else skill issue that drunk guy fight well you have
to fight like 15 people and him at the same time it's just like what I why am I
why am I playing this there's no reason me to do this right now I've done that
twice all right let me pay attention please before I lose it's kicking my
ass double swing all right I've been hit by you that any of the bosses in the
game all right skill issue let's go quiet up there and I even get up there I
can't so whatever screw it bring us me strong will you get down here so I can
Jesus I dodged the other way they're the me strong playthrough I tell us it's
never gonna happen I just don't think it will because it's one thing okay yeah I
I are taking marijuana off stream and stuff right but I don't I don't know I
feel like that's really that's some kind of endorsement somehow to like dude hey
just like smoke weed and play games man just like play game while you're high
it's so much more fun yeah look at how look at how fun this is it's not yeah I
don't want to if I were to the me strong playthrough I wouldn't say anything it
would be like guys I'm doing me strong today and I wouldn't say anything else
but then people that are just like why is he sucks such as why is he so bad he
has to be making this up that right I get there's gonna be no way to hide that
because it would be undeniable what was going on yeah that's the playthrough
where I make a big caveman guy and put every single point in strength and try
to beat like get through fucking like like Godric's castle think I could do it
yeah every single point has to be in strength let's be a caveman all right
what am I missing something here didn't you stream drunk before yeah I mean
I don't know I to me there's a difference in my brain or oh I'm drinking
on stream versus I'm drunk it's this it's part of the stream is me I'm drunk
I'm drunk scream I'm drunk and I have to play this game trashed right like I could
drink on stream it's not like part of oh yeah it's because the stream is live so
that's why I'm drinking a lot I don't know how do I get up there I don't
know influencer Andy influencer Andy I mean I could just it is you know okay
this is an 18 plus story and whatever mature content warning but still I don't
wanted to make it people think that dude just like fucking get high and like play
Elden ring and it's like what I'm doing you should be that's what I do why don't
you do it too so much cooler this way I don't know it's probably a place to do
it and not be like influencer Andy I genuinely don't know how to get up there
yes it's this way yes it definitely is you're an adult do what you want yeah I
know I know I'm overthinking it I do that a lot though that's Virgo that's a
Virgo behavior I mean it makes me that I'm whatever I have a lot of those
essences it's time to crush them all right there we go are you gonna play
scorn what's scorn they're good the movement looks fun in this game it's
very clean all right however you want to look at this and talk about this a lot
of the Dark Souls kind of clone games they all have the same problem where it
it feels like kind of off somehow and we're like clunky this feels good to
play this feels good I have not had a complaint at all about how the combat
animations are or besides the hitboxes maybe it's very clean it's very polished
put it that way it's a polished game I know I did crash out but you know what
I'm saying oh my god that guy just killed me he's letting the dev down
lightly that's not what's happening I look at how many souls I have what the
hell is going on I have a lot oh my god I'm bad this reminds me of a 360 game in
a good way I know what you mean by that I know what that means damn it I had
enough and I have I just blew it wait how much how many points do I have shit
that was stupid actually I might have enough do I have enough two thousand is
it two or three thousand upgrade the weapon shit three all right I'll just
farm for a sec your face is blocking the souls why did it take you that long for
someone to tell me this I can't all tab though I have two thousand you see that
anywhere how come nobody told me this oh well you're an idiot
what was that guy doing get to 3,000 and I'm gonna turn around okay hold on now
oh that's cool stop blocking me it's not fair I'm out of stamina already
what happened to the hamster stream um to refresh people's memories it's when I
was gonna dress up with like ears and like teeth here and just be in a ball
over there and have like a couple of toys and like a one of those water
durable water things and I was gonna eat seeds and shit and I wasn't gonna say
anything and see how long until I lost like 5,000 subs it was like gonna be
experiment but I said decided against it I was gonna have a tube I could go
through between rooms and stuff and you could give me bits to like drop seeds
down that turned out it was gonna be too expensive all right so I went this way
already this is the way they came right yeah I like the heel animation it's
cool and I would have a bunch of made-up catchphrases when a new sub came in I
go oh I sure wish I had some cheese thank you so and everyone was just spam
laughing and shit even though it was not funny
hamsters don't eat cheese yeah and next I'd be like oh next time give me some
candy and go like like into the camera I wonder how many people would leave
permanently she's to meet you where am I going I never if I if the compass
didn't exist I would never have done that play hamster playground all aboard
the hamster train prepare for cuteness overload relentless training and fierce
rivalry as you and your hamsters take on challenges while traversing the maze and
riding a skateboard with more modes this is an AI somebody this is AI generated
with more modes coming soon be the first to cross the finish line to earn rewards
and yummy treats experiences fierce competition in a laid-back style you
customize your hamster while traversing the maze and riding a skateboard you
know I don't know I I'm like doing this I'm doing it hold on it's a cutscene
hold on oh dude 455 thanks for the bitch I could use some cheese he's taken an
ultimate for his aid to calm you're no more human than the machines that laid
waste to this city there's nothing stranger than that
face just what mission has the marquee entrusted you with I must meet with
Abbe Gaiquah alas you've come too late the Abbott has got it into his head to
go to the palette I can't even get it to stay there he is certain that Monseigneur
de la Far the bishop of Nancy is being held prisoner by the monstrosity that
is wreaking havoc on the Ile de la Cit but how can he possibly hope to free him
the Abbott is a holy man who would lay down his life it's a holy man justice
okay but there isn't one among us who stands the slightest chance against
that thing not the slightest chance I wonder where I go from here though I
can't get it to stay don't look up in them into the I'm just a mirror don't
look up and say here's of cheese my mouth is too watery I can't I'm such a
I'm such a greasy person I can't get my teeth to stay there I missed that whole
thing what I'm oh I gotta turn these in oh that what I looked like what the fuck
what Jesus I look horrible oh my god it looks I hate it I genuinely hate that
image oh it's like triggering a response it's triggering a response I don't I
can't alt tab but those images are triggering a response how are you
supposed to avoid it that well please show it I will before the stream ends
here we go all right I need to upgrade the weapon oh my god
cheese to me oh I I would love some cheese would you guys ironically like
that though I feel like there's a lot of people that would want me to do that
because they would it they go yeah that's that's do it that's funny with
the ratio of the amount of people that leave the community permanently versus
the amount of people that stay and give cheese bits what's the ratio do you
think I would legit call work off of that no you you would not you would fall
out sick from work if I was doing the hamster with the teeth and say cheese
bits and stuff you would call off work I would to be honest those of you that
said the game was not hard enough yeah we'll wait till you get to see the wrong
right let's wait till you get to say hello wherever we are I don't know what
zone this is so unforgiving so unforgiving oh it's brutal this game is
just so unforgiving brutal why we like it though that's why we play them brutal
oh just wait till you get to see an all I'm sorry I have too much fun when I
turn the stream on sometimes I don't I really do I have too much fun the pole
get that shit out of here I'm not that I don't care about whatever that pole says
I'd skip work for it I would unsub only 16 people would unsub but how many
people would sub ready this way I can't afford to sub I skipped work oh shit
shit okay what if you put me on the TV at work that was pretty I don't think I
supposed to even be able to do that but I okay I think I screwed that up but I
win that would be weird as fuck frost catalyst ooh all right I want that I
want the health to though frost is I got the module keys well oh no huh those of
you that said that this game was not too tough just wait till you get to the
fire poker in sienna what just blew by me what's going on oh hi I got a lot of
essences all right so it's like 80% of you would skip work to do that that's
kind of cool my soul count is 1895 2000 leave more stamina I have some okay I
gotta get to a oh wait this doesn't it's blurry this is from wait when did I say
this I have to all tab this is confusing when did I write this I already did this
that I wrote this already how long ago is that no new jokes this is okay this is
gonna scare people oh I hate it I actually hate this
you
hold on can I like do it let me see it looks like a deep fake is it all right
like is it in the right spot is it in the right spot is that correct
huh huh uh-huh uh-huh uh-huh yeah yeah yeah oh oh shit oh shit oh shit there we
go now you can see the souls I have nothing left okay oh is it a thumbnail
now shit well I promise we'll move on in a second this thumbnail looks
ridiculous though this looks like a real face something looks wrong something's
off right that doesn't look like me this is a different person it's just
different enough where if you've watched my stream a bunch of times you'd probably
say what's going on easy clicks let's go easy clicks
I'll get out of here this game's pretty fun I actually don't want to die I have
no health cheese melt back no we don't we we got to move on I'm okay with
having a comedy segment now and again but we just can't it can't be the entire
thing um this is back hold on wait what I've been here already haven't I I've
definitely been yeah I've been here already the other way no fun no fun
plenty of fun where do I go you lost again I know I have to go that way I
wouldn't around why did that how come I didn't grab they guys to go out and
around can't jump from here yeah whatever you lost 400 viewers that's
okay and I know that I you might be a little annoyed by the hamster routine I
understand how the I'm just gonna go back and level up okay whatever hamster
shit is so fucking unfunny move on this person is it the person has the stream
her turned off like the visual part I don't I really don't blame you stop
plotting views all right how do I go from here down here maybe I don't maybe
just walk this gate is closed I can't open this shit lost again he hasn't
smiled once I feel like I've been smiling a shitload this whole time all
right just kill me where am I where am I just go you know I've noticed I haven't
died if once this whole game I don't know what happens what happens when you
die in steel series it was this game called heel heel rising I died
honestly just wanna see what happens okay oh I know you're right I fell down
all right where do I go I have to go this way I opened up a shortcut over
here right over here and then down or left I don't know some reassurance would
be nice you having fun yeah I'm a little confused but I'm having fun wait a minute
speaking of cheeseball now I can't reach it and go here things gonna
explode all right so I don't think I walk I think I have to go this way all
right brew here Ross here stops doing the hamster stuff stop it now what it's a
dead end there's nothing else here don't get it stop harrying me stop okay this
is a dead end okay I came from here I'm wait where am I this person's right
here don't you dare kill me right now let's just back the way I came I don't
get it this is a dead end is this a dead end though like it kind of can't be
where else am I supposed to go there's nothing else down here to open is it's
yeah I have to go back somewhere else I didn't even know this was a door what
this is the first door that ever looked like this that I can open okay well
don't die shit he's gonna follow me that that door just it was the first one
that ever looked like that yeah I don't even I don't care run don't pick up I
don't care I know where to go now whatever the the door that blended in
with everything everyone that's saying mad because bad I want them timed out
do it do it when I get to the next boss it's gonna be sick okay we're good it's
confusing it was really confusing okay then I turned I ran now I can slow it
down oh my god do not die right now I feel like I can't hurt these things okay
I bet it oh there we go oh what how can you have final fantasy if 14 community
energy what's that mean you you were made of neither flesh nor blood you were an
automat like those who committed this massacre I have received no such
command I am carrying out a mission I've been in a weird mood today I'm sorry
your friend on Plas Saint-Marie informed me of your intentions alas I was not
able to reach the Palais de Justice I fear that the soul of Monseigneur de la
Far has lost forever was he killed what has been done to him is a fate worse
than death far worse but I could go no further there were so many bodies so
many innocent strewn about the square he means your cringe and your community is
annoying I felt it I don't think I think that's what you think I don't think
that's what they were saying it's hopeless the streets are teeming with
machines but the machine that is wreaking havoc in the area around the
palace colossal much much larger than yourself what's more the soul of his
excellency the bishop has been imprisoned within this way he dropped
the magic ring how could you not have picked up the magic ring dude he's just
like monologuing and we can just pick it up Bishop of Nancy ask the Lord to
bless this assembly and watch over this meeting of the estates general let us
not turn a blind eye to the misfortunes of a populace who is condemned to the
most abject poverty for there is no greater sin than to ignore the
suffering of one's brethren we're parted way gone straight I feel like I could
play that part pretty well of the court is an insult to the misery that reigns
in our lands in such dark times how can one conceive of hiding away to play
or tinker with clockwork contraptions
okay what you what happened you stop moving I feared you were broke I do not
know I only touched this ring more senior than a fast ring whoever you are
help him please let not that this soul be forever lost make haste I beg of you
defeat the Titan at the Palais de Justice all right we got a Titan to fight
corn dogs are okay I'm not a huge fan of corn dogs or do I have enough to do no I
don't you know I could upgrade though yeah might as well thing is amazing why
not I think I'm good honey I have 123 bullets all right let's do it
let's fight the Titan beat the Titan at the this place all right let's go you
ignored all of us I mean I have to play the game I can't just sit there and spam
whoo I'm doing that that's a more heels right yep you're like I've missed one of
these somewhere I only have three heels it's really not that good wait I'm gonna
buy the other ones I didn't know this and I would it yeah I get four all right
let's go fight this Titan and I'm not gonna cheese this I'm gonna fight it for
real no cheese strats no just shooting it from far away and laughing let me get
my inventory in a place where I want it to all right I got tons of grenades oh
yeah my this this bar is sick all right we're good those things are really good
pretty good we have what impossible oh god whoa you didn't get petrified who is
oh come on all right weird that I'm gonna say this this chat is chaos I mean
somebody just I am yeah it kind of is okay somebody just wrote mozzarella
thoughts like I'm gonna stop the stream and tell you how I feel about the cheese
mozzarella for 10 straight minutes that's like just wait that's what you
want but you did do that yeah but that was on my own terms you can't say all
right mozzarella what do you think it's like hits me that I'm doing something if
I want to talk about mozzarella I'll talk about it on my own terms here we go
not to fight the Titan I want all right I'm not gonna cheese it I'm ready let's
go unstable butcher is that oh I got so greedy there was no reason for me to do
that what are you doing there we go all right there you go I did it without the
gun oh I am dropping frames you're right that's weird I really shouldn't be it's
terrible flame resistant I guess hmm this is way too much armor I mean not
just put it on okay cool that was a mini boss that's not the Titan that was that
was not okay that was not a boss that was a mini boss this chest is locked you
thought I thought that was the Titan now how am I supposed to know that would be
whack if that was I thought that was the Titan um should I go can I even go back
I want to level up again yeah I want to level up what's with the what's with the
issues here it's kind of came out of nowhere
treatment fine for like four plus hours okay so that's death don't do that again
that's like 30,000 souls here thank God and you spare a word about Internet
Explorer shutting down tomorrow it is which would mean shutting down 5k it's
shutting down tomorrow how do I need I have 2,000 I need okay I can let me just
kill a few things wait not you talk about not Microsoft edge you're talking
about Internet Explorer not Microsoft edge who cares yeah I mean I don't use
it I have not opened Internet Explorer in a long time where am I just bit me
head and blew up on me it was I was inside of its mouth I need like another
couple hundred after this this should do it right yeah thirty five hundred that
should be it why is everyone but me so funny what you've definitely probably
said something funny in the chat what do you mean you probably said something
funny why is everybody funny
closer you're not like the others are you you gave them quite a beating what
madam come sooner my share poor children well you're mine
answer the door on the night of a hunt they marched all day on the pond nerve
oh you should have heard them singing as they marched on the plastophene they
were very brave then to hear them you'd think that the king had already handed
over his crown okay I'm gonna go kill a Titan goodbye fuck you lady
thirty nine hundred are you kidding me hold on that's annoying all right 30 is
that enough thirty nine thirty eight I think that's enough right it better be
it's gonna sell something if it's not another point in endurance now damage
all the way all right let's go let's fight the Titan
shouldn't hurt shouldn't hurt a yo German how long you planning on being
live for no however long it takes to fight this boss and kill it and do the
next area or at least see the next area where am I going dude they're still gonna
support edge yeah I mean that would be weird if they didn't right where am I
going where am I going where am I going honest to God where am I going where am
I going oh it's up here all right let's go let's see what the first real boss is
like in this game can't open that chest locked let's do it to feed the type here
we go
what should I eat
we must leave this place boss in you there's no time all right let's do it
see how cool this is oh hell yeah Golden Cross what's that Donald's maybe let me
take a look at my modules all right this is level two first physical damage by a
fully charged attack I feel like that's really hard to get done this one's good
do I have any other slot two slot ones don't I think these are fine all right
here we go Titan it's time for the game to impress us this is the point where
the game could impress everybody I'm curious we've fought a few mini bosses
it seems so far the game could impress us with a really cool boss fight I was I
was a hundred million years away here we go Titan fight almost time how much was
this game uh that's a good question I actually don't remember I bought this
game and then turned the stream on maybe six to seven minutes later I think was
rich Andy no I'm not saying that oh I just bought it I don't even care I just
say I I did I bought it it's like oh that's how much this was when I turned
that I took I got distracted by turning the stream on immediately okay how long
did it take to download I have fiber I know Omega low fiber like I drop frames
sometimes but it's a 1000 down connection so it's a gigabit happens
very quickly I do have a gigabit connection it's not my fault that this
some reason twitch hates my connection to the servers I know flex I mean it
really isn't because this internet costs 75% less than the internet that I had
before it it is it is a almost a hot 200 fucking dollars less expensive than the
one that I had in the other house that I was in what a perfect time I can I just
kill this guy I did this guy's are so annoying it's not why even fight these
guys pretty good frame drop timing yeah for some reason sometimes twitch just
genuinely hates wherever my traffic is coming from and I have to server hop
until I find one that lets me stream on it for a week and then I do it again
bro I pay 90 for gigabit where I am but that's what I mean I used to have to
have like this crazy business internet to get over I believe it was 10 to 20
upload which was fucking unbelievably stupid why do you stream at a low bit
rate if you're paying for fiber is you can't scream to twitch past 6,000 bit
rate they'll literally turn your stream off is the Titan is that the Titan no
it's not that's the thing we've already fought that that's not the Titan right
we just bought that thing take this to the clerk's office at the shadow it's
really wet where he is walking he's walking through like sludge why his shoes
filled with water I got the Bible all right where's this Titan nice all right
it's definitely right here I'll get to you in a minute actually let me buy a
bunch of health potions oh that's interesting you can buy these make sure
you don't lose them that's cool all right I need to buy this what do you
have to say what's wrong be not afraid I am NOT a member of the royal army you
like the game new to the stream I intend to put an end to it yeah I think it's
fun I don't think it's as hard as some of the souls games or some of the other
souls likes but it's definitely enjoyable it's a fun experience I think
good I will not hurt you you can believe me
combat's fun I'm afraid it's too late madam those whose bodies are strewn
about this square paid the ultimate price for their blind trust like me they
believed in their country in the National Guard and they were urged to
join he believed in the marketer Lafayette was to lead them to victory
you're not gonna stream this again so I didn't that's a Titan all right are you
ready let's go it's time for the Titan fight that's a Titan what is inside of
that this gets kind of goofy the Bishop of the city all right let's go first
real fight I've done no damn it I can't hurt him oh you could only hurt the top
all right I get it makes sense now perfect no face to face to okay I got
it um get up what's up how do I get away run what the fuck what do I do about
this oh is that Mr. Hill better not be still on the ground let go let go let
go let go let go of me let go of me let go get off me get out of here wait for
me stop you better not die I have no stamina fuck this guy I'm gonna show
you the real strat why was I I'm gonna kill this guy in fucking ten seconds
watch this I'm gonna kill this guy in ten seconds check this out watch this
this guy's dead watch this I'm gonna kill this guy in enough time for you to go
take a piss and come back sure it's never mind that's your fight oh my god
what am I supposed to do about this honest to goodness that's that's strategy
right there
don't want juice how am I supposed to get away but I have juice what do I do
try to be with my eyes closed I didn't destroy did you come back from peeing
yet that was a long pee that was kind of a fun fight that was a little goofy
though and throwing grenades in random directions though I like this games
funny this gets fun I like it it's fun a little humorous it's clean I think it's
fun this nightmare you were throwing grenades at this guy you owe your
freedom to the good habit I tell you this man is utterly irreplaceable he
has devoted himself body and soul to the mission I entrusted to him
investigating the King's entourage in particular the man who enabled him to
create this ungodly army I just made a YouTube video just cutting at the end of
sentences like dude you took a lot of takes to do that captured monsignor I
was with a big record in plasticine we've gone to speak with the volunteers
we implored them not to take our arms against the King's machines alas they
refused to eat our words and we had to leave in great haste after that
what do you I can't remember a thing those poor people these are automats
were truly made in the mold of their master ruthless to think for just one
simple reproach against the court the king cast me into hell what nightmare
monsignor it was terrible I was shadow we try to move away from the fire that
would be probably good idea has been you put they put you in there 20 minutes
ago there were flames everywhere only been 30-40 minutes
that awaits our immortal source once our time on this earth has ended if this is
true then how are we to go on living with nothing to hope for nothing to
believe it but you the notes what notes monsignor the notes the abbot placed in
my safekeeping those heretics took them I know this heck you can be found oh my
god his neck did you see that to the shuttle a prison was like watch all the
way where will I be safe go and join the Abbott at the society does amy then what
his soul was powering the Titan oh that's cool but you must go quickly more
will be here soon he took right the fuck off there's a hook now whoa okay game
just got five times cooler you do it in the air yes you can all right that's
cool cool we have we got a secure hook and an
Omega chest volley mallet what is that the strength look at this thing what is
it it's such a Looney Tunes weapon whoa it's a shotgun it's strength so I can't
use it that's really cool you know the weapon designs are very good as it
that's definitely an absolute plus one the weapons are really cool all right now
what oh if you get the notes I would have missed that okay
countering module get someone to scream chat messages at you for a stream you
know I thought about turning on TTS for one day I grapple something oh okay over
there don't well okay it would be they'd be the mods would be there and they
would be able to push through and delete stuff they needed to have how many souls
41 I'm almost there no crunchies I can sell yeah I'm gonna sell some stuff
TTS is annoying well I figured I'm not gonna do it I just thought about it
talking about screaming chat messages at somebody I let me sell sell this sell
all these sell these no I'm gonna sell the claws I'm not gonna use them okay I
know don't selling weapons is the dumbest thing don't sell weapons it's
fine endurance all right and I'm gonna buy more heels all right is it a
is it a McDonald's kind of night tonight McDonald's kind of night Taco Bell
Wendy's which one do you think the Chateau-Laye prison is at the other end of the
Pont-en-Chaune this grappling hook will be very useful
ooh we're up here now cool that's where we were before see you later
like go down there we've got to get out of here Taco Bell Taco Bell Taco Bell
maybe I will do Taco Bell these machines have neither heart nor mind no mercy can
be expected time is it
Popeyes that's right well use the hook in combat really what that's pretty cool
what does it use stop being the enemy that I have the most trouble with yeah
what kind of night what kind of night is it first try the next boss or are these
we're not doing that again I do want to play that game again though so I do want
to do that again that game was fun that was a fun game that was a phenomenal
game I want to play it again hmm I get you want me to get the dog is it time
for auto I'm not gonna fight these guys away all right no I haven't been here
have I use me the Grand Chateau-Laye all right this is a good place to stop I'll go
get auto we'll do an auto hangout session for like a minute or two you
want my fine okay my final first impressions of this game that was fun
that was actually a pretty fun game I enjoyed that is it a 10 out of 10 no is
it a 5 out of 10 no is it a 6 out of 10 no it's higher is it an 8 out of 10 not
sure is it a good game yeah that was fun I think it was worth playing I would have
stopped if I didn't think it was good it was pretty fun I liked it I think it
probably gets a little bit more interesting a little bit later maybe is
it a 7 it's like between depending who you are someone between like a 7 and an
8 something I don't give ratings on this stream there's no way that's an 8
come on Gwen I'm I just I didn't say that this is it okay the game with how
do you rate a game the game was clean the animations were clean combat was fun
the bosses are a little easier than I would have liked only saw four of them
though I don't know how long the game is I thought it was fun there's definitely
enough there to be interested this definitely seems like there's enough
weapons the weapons are awesome it kind of remind me of blood-borne where
they're very cool and very different and the difficulty up I could it's pretty
cheeseable yeah but whatever I mean you don't have to play it like that I let
me go get Otto that was steel rising it's on steam was kind of fun I would
say it was worth playing let me go get Otto I'll be right back you guys can see
that Otto exists I'll be right back okay you see what's going on I tell what's
going on I tell you see like we've had turkey neck he was very sleepy be you
tired he was sleeping he hates us he just woke up yeah are you sleepy did I
disturb you he's my special boy is he chunky he's a little chunky it's been
hot it's been like 115 degrees 120 degrees he it's not time for him to be
outside he's a little chunky we're working on it we're working on it he's
a little lumpy yeah but yeah I'll see you guys later that's gonna be the end
well he wasn't sleeping sleeping he was asleep and then kind of woke up a little
while ago and was resting he was a little sleepy all right so I've got to
do I got to sign a thousand baseballs and ship them out I'll see you for the
Omega weekend get your recommendations and we'll get a whole list we're gonna
play like five to ten games this weekend we're gonna do a ton of shit this
weekend I will see you on Friday Friday Saturday Sunday Omega weekend I'm gonna
go do this get this done if I do get it done before then if it doesn't take more
than a couple days to really get this all these things shipped out and signed
and everything and I will let you know but my plan is to come back on Friday
and we're not gonna start at four we'll start up probably around two I'll start
earlier I promise see you next week no this is gonna be on Omega weekend and
more than I say Omega weekend the more that it has to happen right we're gonna
do sorcery we're gonna do some other stuff we're gonna do figure it out
ultra kill maybe we're going to play each one of these games for two to four
hours each all weekend delay Andy will happen delay Andy will not happen no I'm
gonna make sure there's no chance for a delay Andy no you can clip that you can
thanks for watching thanks for hanging out I was in a really weird mood today
this is very odd I'm thinking like the like cheese hamster face thing and I'm
like what was the point of that we've been waiting 15 hundred and seventy nine
days for driver one maybe like three of you have been waiting for that I played
driver one did I played driver one during one of the PlayStation one nights
from like three or four years ago I already played it didn't I I swear to
God I did that was driver two no well I'll look into it maybe we'll do driver
one if I didn't do it check out the driver Twitter why right why does the
driver why does driver have a Twitter driver game is this correct okay what am
I looking at here I'm on driver that is a driver game official updates on the
driver series I'll discuss everything related to the past present and future
of driver my blood what am I looking at not the right account no okay
you're a play driver I all right but I already did I have I swear to you I
already did this I'm gonna go look this up and see what you want to get out of
here after all right I don't want to get out let's go out of all right I see you
guys later see you on Friday have a good rest of your week Omega weekend okay
coming in see you later yeah and call your mother sorry sorry forgot to say it
goodbye