Hello, how are you? Good to see you.
Uh, you know, I was supposed to be live like 10 minutes ago, but I, uh,
all like the Twitch stuff, I lost all my connections with all the stuff that I had connected.
So my like streaming service stuff that I use, I had to like re-log in.
So fuck! How you doing?
Oh, here he is. First stream since the leaks. We have to hear what he has to say.
Well, first of all, I'll tell you, I was, I was just as surprised as probably maybe a lot of you were.
I did not think that I was in that category. I just really didn't.
When I saw that list, I was like, holy shit, wow, look at these top 100 fucking streamers.
And they make a shitload of money. I wonder where I am. I'm 98. What?
Wait, how? What? How? I was very surprised.
He's a billionaire. No, no, no. I'm not gonna, look, I'm not gonna touch too much upon this.
Uh, you guys, I try to be transparent with money with you guys.
Hopefully I have been.
Now you know exactly the amount of money that I have taken in from twitch.tv
in the last like two plus years.
And whatever, I'm just gonna keep using it. That's all there is to it.
Number 98. Pay back your debt. The debt's like billions. I only have whatever it was.
I don't even have that by the way. That's over the last two, two years and one month, two months.
I've been using it. I don't even have it. I don't even have any money.
No, I'm gonna make a really just clear before italics is waiting, but let me make a really
clear statement on this. Um, don't ever give this channel money unless like you absolutely
can afford to. There's literally no reason for you to give this channel more than a sub ever.
I just want to make that really clear. I hope that people don't think they have to give this
channel money. Hopefully I've been clear on that the last five years or so. Um, and I know I don't
want to even, I don't want to talk about this too much because I know anytime you talk about like
money, you're coming like a bunch of primes. I don't want, that's not what this is for.
I'm not even going to address them, but I'm just going to keep trying to do what I can and
use it on the stream. Use it on me too, right? Like I want to make sure that,
because there's another thing that's really worth bringing up too, is I mean, I don't know how long
this is going to last. I don't think anybody does. So I want to make sure that if I'm going to make
this kind of money, I want to have like investments and put it into like accounts that are going to
like be okay in five to 10 years. Cause I have no idea how long this is going to last. But there
are far other people on this platform that are not in the top 100, top 200 that you should probably
be giving your sub to every month. It's probably not me anymore. Let's be honest, right? But we,
I could talk about this for like another four hours. Invest in a proper e-clown car. First,
second, I thought you said proper e-clown. All right. It's Alex is waiting. Let me say hello.
Hey, sorry. I forgot that I haven't addressed the leak since I streamed last. And that happened like
in the middle of the week. Yeah. The leak, the leak, what being like a top 30,000 streamer,
just making a casual average minimum wage on Twitch. What's there to reveal.
All right. We're playing Far Cry 6 today. It's Alex. You don't know who he is. How could you not
at this point? Everybody knows who I am because they're real viewers and gamers.
I think we're already in the game, right? Yeah, we are in the game. I have to run ads. No,
I'm not going to run ads. Like what, you don't understand though. Do you guys get it? Why like,
Oh, maybe he should start running ads. Oh, give us ads, Jerma. What? Are you serious? Why would I,
why would I do that? There's a bunch of people in your chat saying who right now.
Are they? Did you tell them to wear their name tags to the stream today?
I, well, you have your name tag on. Sometimes I feel like I have to wear a name tag.
I feel like they don't know who I am. All right, let's go. Did I even tweet this? Okay. I'm just
going to retweet yours because I'm incredibly lazy. There, that's it. There we go. See? I was
talking about how professional we were like doing the whole tutorial before the stream even started.
Yeah. But I mean, that's something you have to do in, in these games. And by the way,
people are quite curious about the title. I've never sat through an entire Far Cry game. I walk
out of the movie in the first act and I keep seeing the sequels. Don't, I don't know why we
keep doing this. We go to the Far Cry movie. We don't, we get up and leave the movie and you like
effectively showed up late. And I don't mean that as a stream joke. I mean, like you, you,
you got into the seat, you crawled over, the lights are already off. You skipped all the cut
scenes to get here. I got to like explain the plot. Yeah. I actually truly have no fucking idea
what's going on because he did the tutorial last night and I was unaware that, well, he told me,
but I just didn't do it because I'm busy. So he did the tutorial last night. It's about an hour
and he's like, Hey, did you do, did you do the tutorial yet? And I'm like, no, it's like,
can I get through it in like an hour? And he's like, yeah, there's a bunch of cut scenes though.
So I'm not kidding. I wish I had it recorded. I sprinted through every single thing. I
mashed space bar to skip every single cut scene. I don't even know how to crouch. I have no idea.
I just had, I held shift the whole time. But anyways, this is the first segment is like a
stealth section too. I just sprint. I ran right through it. I just ran through it. Somebody said,
I thought you were done playing Ubisoft games. Uh, this isn't an Ubisoft game. This is Far Cry.
It's the same game every time we already played Far Cry four and five. So you can rest assured
this is no different. Yeah. But why do we keep going to the movie? This is like you, okay.
So again, let's say if Far Cry was a movie and you and I went to the movie together
and after like 30 minutes of that movie, we were like, I'm leaving. This movie sucks. Right. And
we leave the movie. Why do we keep going to the sequels? Oh, Hey dude, Hey, Far Cry five just
came out. Oh, we like, didn't really care that much. And we just kind of goofed around for like
three hours in the first. Why do we keep going to the monstrous sequels and leaving boss baby?
You don't, you don't watch the whole movie boss, baby. You watch like 30 seconds and then you skip
like 10 minutes and then you watch like 30 more seconds. This is what we're doing with all the
these movies, trying to see what happens. Oh, you go, you talk about the, uh, the, the skip to the
movie thing. Yeah. I love doing that. I think you have to talk to this person. We need to talk.
Cause this is your, this is your game, not mine. I accept. Hit that slave camp hard.
Okay. I thought she was, she put the gun out. I thought she was going to shoot you.
She was like aiming it at you for a second. Okay. Where do we go? I don't, I have no idea
what's going on, dude. I have absolutely no idea what's happening. I don't know who that person is.
The very first like thing anybody hears in the game is go hit that slave camp hard. That,
you know, that's exactly what we're going to do. I don't even know. I don't even know where we are.
All right, let's go. You could probably like just, I honestly, wait, we haven't,
we have an alligator. Remember that we do. Yes. We have two alligators and you can,
you can press E on the alligator. Isn't that so cute? You feed alligator. I already did this.
They drop like, you drop like a ham sandwich in his mouth. Come here. I want to do that to mine too.
Holy, what the fuck happened? I was just trying to cook the steak. What the hell are you doing?
It was just going to be like a cooked steak joke. I don't know. I thought, I don't know. All right,
let's go. Let's give me do a mission. We start the game even though I already did. I don't know
what's going on. But yeah, welcome guys. This is Far Cry 6. How come you run faster than me?
Hold on. First bug. First bug? First bug. Oh, I thought you said like a beetle or something.
No, do you see this person? I don't see anybody. She is flying like a T-posing Jesus in my game.
I don't see that. I see a gun just sitting here. It's just a floating gun. Can you get on the horse?
Don't please put it away. Can you get it? No, I don't. Look, we have to at least get on the road.
Okay, you need your own horse. Just get a little further downhill. I could jump on that.
Wait, what if you get on the zip line and then land on me?
Easy. I can't. Hold on. That's stupid. Run his ass off. Holy shit. Oh my god, that was horrible.
Are you all right? Yeah, I'm good. All right. So we're going to go in this way.
So there's horses in this game. Why does this feel like it's like 10 FOV? It's going to make
me want to puke. I already changed it. You're probably going to get like leashed back to me.
You can only be so far from me. I have to like keep the like, you know, the backpack
with the child. Are you really that far away? Okay, I got to turn the FOV up. It's like 95.
I have it so high already. It's at 95. Should I put it like 110? I think it's just like small
on the horse. I think when you get on the horse, it just zooms in to like a nauseating level.
Maybe it does. Okay. All right. So we need to go meet Julio. Driving FOV is forced FOV. Okay. I see.
I need to find, we need to find like a vehicle. Otherwise we're going to have to walk everywhere.
Oh, I'm already there. Oh, I'm coming. Characters like get tired in this park, right?
Random. I can't talk to this person though. This is your game. Yes. You're just passing through
and the alligator attack him. I got here way before you did. Yeah. Cause I had to walk the whole way.
All right. I'm coming. Wait, what? Hold. I had it on toggle. What is this bullshit? I did. I swear
to God. What the fuck? Where is it? Okay. There's so many options in this game. How long did it take
you to actually sit here and go through each one of these? Um, I didn't. I just turned off motion
blur. What are you, what are you changing right now? I don't like to hold, uh, aim down sights.
Really? You toggled? Yeah. Toggle gamer? Cause I don't, the pressure with my, uh, Tony. Yes.
The pressure on my middle finger hurts. What do you use middle finger? Middle finger is,
that's right. Click is for middle mouse button. I'm just kidding. I don't use that either. I was
going to say, what are you talking about? All right. Will you talk to this guy?
Finally, I'm not going to bullshit you. I wanted to do this alone, but Clara give me an order.
I can handle myself. Is there a punch? So he should be here right now, but instead I get you.
And I'm supposed to be a Miami, but instead his health bar. I'm stuck here with you.
He can't die. Can he? Enough talk. Step one, we hit the tobacco. Step two, we destroy their
poison supply. Step three, we get the fuck out of there. And Castillo gets a nice pretty
message from you. He uses toggle. Yes, I do. No, I get the horse. That's all right. He's like
running after you. He's like, what are you doing? Wait, would you just teleport it over here? Wait,
what happened? Why is he choking? What's he choking on? What did he eat? All right, let's go. Leave
the horse. We're just doing all the same jokes from the last one. We're watching the same movie.
It's okay to do the same jokes because we're watching the same movie. He's waiting for me.
I don't know. Where's the farm? I don't know. You killed him. You screwed everything up,
I think. He'll protect you from fire. And more importantly, Castillo's fucking poison.
Okay, here we go. So what do we have to do? He gave me some gloves. He gave me oven mitts.
All right, suit up with that gear. All right. Pretty sick. All right, what we got? We need
different gloves. How does this even work? Hazmat? I think I got it on. There it is. What? All right,
did you do the how to change gear tutorial? No, yeah, I did it already. Oh, here it is. You're
not wearing the gloves. Let's put them on. There you go. That's the first time I've seen the inside
of the fucking menu. What is that there for? All right. Are you ready? Let's go get like a car or
something. I don't want to walk 700 miles. Let's go. That's a good horse. Wait, he's going too?
Are we going to the blue? What's the blue mark? It says follow him. So I think you go walk near
him. Oh, okay. But don't run him over though. Is this the walk and talk? It probably is.
We actually do get a flamethrower. That's pretty crazy. If I could change anything,
it would be me dying on that horse. Okay, the horse is just. I wish I had one. And if she
loved you, well, then you could do this. Oh my God. Okay, need to know or challenge complete
Ubisoft Connect XP earning. That's way too huge of a notification. He's almost dead. Did I do that?
Yes. Get it on your skin. It can make you go fucking crazy or sit like deep down. What happens
if he dies though? We probably have to restart it. So let's let's actually try to just get through
the first co-op mission. It's a quarter of the screen. Jeremy's going to shoot and kill the
NPC. No, I'm not. He is. He is proven already that he's the one doing that this spring.
I haven't killed anybody yet. He's still alive. You killed him. I had to revive him. He was just
down. That wasn't dead. That's why he still got half health. Right behind you. Oh, yeah.
Don't we have like cell phone cameras? I actually can't fit the horse through here.
Get over here. All right. Horse is getting abandoned. Okay, so we need to follow him up
to the top. Yeah, but like what happens if you shoot him while he's on the ladder? He's probably
gonna fall off. I don't want to craft anything by the way. I don't even like. Oh, there's
hang on. There's crafting in this game. Of course there is. See the tobacco and the yellow poison
tanks. Okay, so we have to scout. Punch holes in the tanks to let the poison out into the air.
By the way, what kind of iPhone is this where they can get this clear of an image
zooming in this much? It's the kind like, okay, so for context, your side character dies
when a boat gets shot full of holes and they drown. Oh, okay. But on the beach,
the first thing they do is say give me my phone and it's still working even though they just like
washed up on the shore. The phone's like. It's like a super phone. Are you scanning right now?
I'm just I'm looking around at stuff. I don't know how to do that. Oh, hit X. How do I know
that you don't? Oh, because I pushed like the other phone. There's no way you get that kind
of image from this month. Let's make some chaos. Are you fucking kidding me? When I like zoom in
to take a picture of a bee at one foot away, it's still kind of blurry. Are you kidding me? All
right. Well, whatever. He just he went down already, man. It's a video game. No, it's not.
It's real life. Listen, just give iPhone another like seven iterations. They'll have them out in
the next two years and they'll have camera quality like that. They're purposely holding
back camera quality so they have another iPhone to release next year. So I can destroy the yellow
poison tank. What the fuck is the alligator doing? How do you be stealthy with an alligator?
See what I'm talking about? Like what? How is this a stealth game? By the way, did you turn off bars?
Well, what would I do? I shot somebody I wasn't supposed to. I think you just shot a civilian.
What is going on? Destroy the tanks. They've got like poison guns. We have to sabotage. It is so
loud. I can't even get through the door. You're not even listening to this when your compound's
getting like raided by two special agents. How do I get through the door? What's happening?
Who's this guy? I got an enemy. Oops. Oh shit. Hold on. Are we doing the Ubisoft play? All right.
Coming up on your right here. I'm going to need some support. All right. Sure. Calling it an
airdrop airdrop. What do you want it? Where should I put it? Hey, there's a guy shooting at us over
here. Why is it on fire? I got one. I cannot move. I can't fucking move. I can't move the cursor.
I'm giving you some cover fire. Is that going to be right on top of us? Oh, fuck.
No shit. I can right click. Where is this? What am I looking at? You're on your own for a second.
I have to turn this down. It is so loud. How do I get? I can't get off of this. Okay. Wait,
you just say a Spanish swear word. I don't know why some of the gun sounds so much louder than
other ones. Eel. It's because one of them has a silencer on it. Okay. We only did 17%. Oh,
we're going to get this car. Where's the music coming from? Um, how do I drive this? W I get,
why can't I go to the front seat? Oh, are you kidding me? Yeah. Um, I'm taking this thing.
Oh, okay. To sabotage the plantation. Here we go. Yeah. We've only destroyed 20%. I think we
have to like, hang on. Wait a second. Are they doing the like, beginning of the game is the
first question. Sorry. That was scared the shit out of me. I don't know why. What was that? Oh
shit. This guy, like I just exploded into blood. Oh no, it wasn't. I thought he just like turned
into blood mist. It's this guy. Oh my God. All right. Get me out of here. Oh shit. This is bad.
All right. Alligator is okay. Oh my God. What the fuck? He won't let me in.
Okay. Burn the red tobacco plants with my, with my toadster USB stick. All right. We got to burn
these plants and do it. Where's my plan? There. All right. Here we go. Oh shit. It burns.
You think Spanish songs are still DMC able? I think everything is. Wait, collect gasoline.
What do I do with this? Watch out, get out of there. How are you supposed to safely do this without
getting burned? I'm just saying it, but you know, if the DMC people can't understand the lyrics,
then maybe it's an algorithm, man. It's an algorithm. Okay. Where are you right now?
And why are you not helping me burn all this? I, I'm over here burning other farms.
This is co-op. It's cooperative. I don't burn the same farm you're burning. That's redundant.
Oh, back to front. All right. We're at 50%. This was not a stealth mission anyway. No,
this is like a, you destroy everything. 3d movie jumpscare.
Okay. All right. I don't have any more gasoline. It picks them up from a barrel. I have been
even made one weed joke. No, I mean, that's so easy. There are no weed jokes. Can I like,
I can't just like cut this down. I changed my weapon. Does that work? He's just on fire
running through all this. Now I'm on fire. There's still some over here. Do you have any gas left?
I'm trying to shoot the plants to get rid of them. Really? I'm just saying you can destroy
the yellow barrels. Wait, that's where the music's coming from. That's it. Okay. You just get the
shit out of me. I've got a blue friendly icon over my head. This is where the music's coming from.
So you couldn't tell it was me. This is what I see the volume indicator. That's what the music's
coming from. What? I don't know what just happened. Yeah, that was a, oh, that's a good guy.
Okay. Oh shit. What? I have great. Okay. What? Oh, that was, that was my like three and overwatch.
I don't even know what the fuck I just did. First of all, overwatch joke in 2021.
Second of all, it's the only watchers in smite. That's the only, the only two moments.
Well, we did it. We did it. We can, we can go back on my way. Yeah, I think we're good. We can keep
on. We'll both head back to large stone tower. All right. We did it. Make sure you get your,
your, where is this music coming from? I think it's just thematic. It's just there to like,
get you all jazzed up, dude. But I don't, there's no context to where it will be coming from though.
I don't know. We're apparently sticking it to the government by destroying the drugs,
which seems counterintuitive. All right, songs over. But I think they're laced with poison.
Fake raid. Somebody said fake. I don't see a raid, but fake raid.
Vinny just tried to raid you, but accidentally raided a fake germa. What? Hold on. That, that,
is that what happened? Well, hi everybody. That I guess not here. He forgot the nine eight five.
Oh shit. Well, thanks anyways. It's appreciate it. Is this not the large stone tower?
This looks like it. He's over there though. Wait, he's coming this way. He's pathing.
Oops. You're okay. Yeah. He was just walking through like the brush. Oops. Yeah. But thanks
Vinny. If you're watching, that's actually fucking hilarious. Fake germa got a raid.
Uh, but hey guys, welcome playing Far Cry 6 with it's Alex. Are you, is he good? I think he's good.
Shit. You really can hold your own. I don't want to say I told you. Did you do your super move?
Don't fuck around. Don't do that. Stop. What are you throwing at him? This is just the beginning.
What is those? What do you, how do you do that? How do I do that? Stop. Oh yeah. You're telling
me to stop. You're like interrupting the NPC cut scene. How do I do it? Okay. It's a
middle mouse. Yeah. I thought you said it was middle mouse. It is. You have to hit Q
and then mouse over the, uh, the holster and then mouse wheel.
Oh my God. I don't know who it is. Is it him? I'm trying to cut the screams off.
It's then now he's screaming in my game though. All right. If we bring him back,
let's do the screaming stuff. Okay. Holy shit, dude. That was insane. It was just like,
somebody was screaming in my ear. I swear to God. Oh, head back to the tower. All right. You want
to grab a horse? Uh, yeah, we got two horses here. Are you good? Is this streaming? Yeah. I,
apparently it's, apparently we're fine. I still got to talk to him. Hold on. I can't believe you
weren't hearing that. It was like a loud human scream in my ear. And they're going to see the
smoke. We work well together. See, listen, if you were good with it, you did good. Sorry,
I doubted you. See you back at camp. Okay. Now we're good. That was a quick turn. All right.
Oh, nice. Now we both have horses. Awesome. Um, do you want to leave or should I?
Do we have a mission? We should find a car. I mean, this car is back in the, in the drug lab.
Can you do that? What? Apparently not. Oh yeah. There you go. Nice. My horse wasn't professionally
trained. Oh, we're on the phone. I hope you can see the smoke from where you are.
Stop hurting my horse. He's hurting, but okay. I think Lita would be smiling right now.
Danny, there's someone I want you to meet. Oh, new quest. He's a local fisherman,
which means votes for Lieberkant. He lives on the east side of Casas Cove.
Always got nobody's in here. Oh, come on. Really? That would have been really funny.
So I've been following the story so far and basically here's how it works. Literally any
person who has speaking lines gets shot in the head at some point. It happens about five times
in the prologue. Really? Yeah. So, um, basically just violence is the answer, I think.
I mean, I will say the game is, it's, it's very pretty. It's like the, really the graphics are
wild. It's only been, uh, we only have been playing for 20 minutes. You're already making
justifications for your future six out of 10. Okay. Um, I'm, I do. We really, every one of these
is a six out of 10 locked in. It's grayed out. You can't even, you can't even scroll your mouse
over it. It's grayed out. It's locked in six out of 10. Dude, why would you swerve to my right?
Oh, fuck. Oh no. Is he all right? Oh shit. It was random. Is he okay? He's fine. He's all right.
He's all right. He's still moving around. Get out of here. What the fuck? No, I didn't want
that to happen. Hey, don't give me that. I can't. What's that? I can't get off of him.
This guy. I don't know, man. I don't know why I'm riding this guy's ass. You're going too far away
from your partner. Oh shit. I'm going to lose you. You ran over my horse. I'm like running towards
you. Wait, where are you? I'm about to hijack a car. Okay. Good. Good. You have to come to me.
Okay. Is that you? Wait, are you on my? I'm so confused right now. I have no idea what's going
on. Is that, that's you. It's me. Yeah. Can we get the truck? Yeah. Oh, you just knocked the tree
down on top of it, but he's fine. Okay. Let's go. Where are we going? Uh, you're, you're the pilot.
Okay. I'm the pilot. What the fuck did you throw that? That guy say, I know I heard something.
Yeah. There's a, there's a bad guys are in red. That's how you know they're bad.
And the good guys are in there. That's how you know they're good. The ex gorilla at his shipyard. Can
you, um, can you give like a waypoint for us? Oh, it's over here. What the fuck was that?
Just dogs. They just spawned out of nowhere. They live here. Why are you chasing them? I'm going to
the marker. See it's the star thing. My character is bored with you driving. So he's just humming to
himself. You are humming. Are we the questers? I think these are, these are questers. Is this a
fishing? Might be. There was a joke attempt, but you need a little bit more distance.
The best part is he's looking over there because the explosions happened over there.
You're in the big leagues now. It's just the, the sound is what made him us afraid. Not the visual.
Good. Well, you don't have any friends. One just shut up and call for a car. Oh, a car. Okay.
And you don't want to craft. Okay. I actually probably a good idea. I don't. Can we even
craft anything? I think so. Okay. I'm going to do, I'm going to do standard rounds in this
way. No soft target. They stand around the fine, right? I mean, sure. Charms. Oh, this is a
cosmetic. Oh, I have skins. Dude, did you get the ultimate edition with like cyberpunk skins?
Absolutely not. Um, I did all your ride using Q. Okay. Your ride will be delivered to you.
Okay. Is we actually going to get DMCA for these? I don't, I, I don't know. It was maybe,
um, hold on. Are we, are we ghostbusters? This, you can throw fucking baseballs. People,
this game just went, it went a full letter grade. That's what I was doing earlier.
I was doing that 30 minutes ago when you asked me what I was doing. Oh my God. Oh my God. This
got a full letter grade. I thought you were throwing, I thought you were throwing knives
at somebody. I mean, I can do that too. Oh, all right. No stops. So now we have to call our ride.
I don't have that option. You just put, you hold Q. That was a bad guy.
It was a bad guy. Yeah, it was a bad guy. Oh, but you can carry bodies.
Hey, do you, I think, do you have to call a ride? See if you can give you access to a ride.
You're psycho rides on the way. All right. No, don't, you just got this. It's so,
it's so hard to like judge the range. All right. You drive. I'll be the, I'll be the guy that goes
gunk, gunk, gunk, gunk, gunk, gunk, gunk, gunk. Let's see. Oh no, I was wrong. Okay.
Where are we going? I don't know.
Look, anti aircraft cannons. Okay. Secure drives to the right for no reason.
You got all of them, like what the, you, those are bad guys, right? I don't think two of them were.
I think they were just like, just going to desynchronize me. Like assassin's creed.
They were wearing red you can't wear red out here my games lagging. Oh, there we go. I'll switch. Where you going?
I'm trying to drive in a straight line, but unironically it's pulling to the right. He's actually the gas station go
Why is it making the aim over there?
What I think auto-aim just took that over?
All right, let's go. Are you okay? You sold the car. I mean I was
Are you what I'm trying to assess the situation here get
Ghost bus this car. I know what the fuck
Are you hooked on to that car? Yes, are we going? Oh, no, here comes the ghost buster. Oh
Am I kind of scared of what's coming down the road here? How do you turn the radio off? Uh, left slash
Why?
We're all just waiting to see what you do
Me yeah
What what you're in the little car, right? I mean I'm attached to the little car
I'm not gonna ram into you at full speed because that's too easy. No, it was
Minus two. No, that would be a plus two. That'd be a minus two
See I am a person of refined taste and I was just waiting on a better option to arrive
But that that's a better option watch out for the alligator
Well, they can chat loves easy jokes. Somebody just said yeah
I'm the one that died
Not the people other people there me subverted expectations bitch
How did I'm the one that okay? Well, whatever
Let's get back in the let's get back in the ecto cool. Oh switch seat. Okay, so
assassinate
Commandant Rosa Rio
Okay, she's inspecting a military site. We have a lot of random shit to do. All right, let's do it
I'm gonna go to the closest one. She's right here
He drowned. All right, it's right here. Fuck is going on
Hey, the what is great out here
It's right here right there 238
Water's very clean. How the hell did you get from the car to there? I just swam
Okay. Yeah, but you like actually teleported from underwater
Yeah, this only said that took ten seconds for you to do that, but it also keep in mind I
Saved us probably two or three minutes
driving that way, um
Something over on this other side here
Yeah, how do you get up there? Oh, I was just trying to make us that it's screaming
So this is gonna save us time
It's your ass. It is. Yep. Thank you
Why have you done this? You know what?
All right, I'll activate it. Will you just teleport to me and you teleport to me?
Probably oh, it's right here. Okay, you can't ride wild horses. You really can
No, I mean, there's this tame and there's wild horses. I'd be my alligator gonna hang out
Turn on friendly fire. It's already on be careful. Don't go that don't fall. Oh, there you are
Over here where the I'm ready for the mission. Okay, you ready?
Which we're trespassing currently? I think pretty much everything we do in this frame is illegal. Oh
boat
That boats really far and probably not drivable. Oh, is it just an asset?
Is it just like a faraway like JP like whatever the image thing?
There are tanks we can ride too. Okay, so this is what is this?
Well, I think we've just
Who is who somebody talking to me? I think we're supposed to blow this tank up
What happened blue tank up? Oh you fired at me? Okay. All right. There was a tank. Hold on. How do I get you up?
repair
Wait, oh, we're supposed to drive it
Get her
She's getting in the tank. She's getting in the tank. I'm just making you aware. She's in the tank now
She's driving the tank
She's just taking the first
Listen, why does it say repair the tank if they're gonna drive the tank?
Oh, why did you mortar me when I was standing next to it said destroy? I didn't listen
It said blow up the tank. It's fine. We're right here. We're fine. Let's go
Taking care of a commandant a problem for Benito
Find some high ground do some scouting before you alright, I'm stealth
I'm stealth. We're invisible. I'm inside of a flower patch. Oh fuck. I just looked at me. What the fuck off not stuff anymore
Like that guy's running to get in the tank by the way, he definitely is
Okay, he's getting inside the tank he's inside nobody else
somebody else in this tank
What the fuck are you dead somebody's just named the tank of my face oh he was in it
Fire I thought that's the tank you were talking about you were like hiding behind that tank
It was like dude. Look somebody's running to take no now. They're getting in
Oh my god
They saw me and they're running in the tank and I thought you were like setting up for a joke
I mean, I when he turned really slowly to look at me. I kind of wanted him to shoot me point-blank range
I'll be honest. I'll be honest with my voice just do it there. That was weird
popping it
All right, let's just let's get in here
Parachute is still on
Get your parachute off, bro
That's why they can see us
That is so stupid
Get in there and fight him on in there. It's your you're the birthday boy right now
Just to make sure everybody knows who the birthday boy is. Oh my god the tank
Put the phone down you idiot
Hell, what do you mean help? I go. Let's actually for
Your
When they get in the tank, they just got the parachute does fucking the parachute just swept the whole thing up
Okay, it was a major distraction
I killed like eight people. Okay, we have to like go in there and just like sabotage the tanks with mortars and shit
We're gonna okay. All right, look
First of all, what let's just make sure what mission even is this go to the depot and free up the fuel so we can
Survive and kill the commandant. So they think twice about trying again. Okay, this is a major mission. We're about to do
This is rank four. Look, I bet I bet I could do this in stealth by myself. You think so? Yeah, okay
Let's find out. I'll be watching
Okay. Hang on. I'm gonna leave Guapo here. I
Mark them for you. Yeah
Is that actually working? I got this
Birthday boy assassination mission. Nice. Very very nice. Very nice. I think one person's running to me
You've got one person in front of you
We isn't on the mountain directly under you
Yep, they're coming in. I don't think they know of your presence yet. Somebody actually underneath me too. There's two people
Guy you're gonna be right in front of you. Careful. He's aiming his gun down towards the
the outside area
You see him? Okay, are they facing me or away from me? He is facing you and you are
He's like above that lip. If you go if you jump up, he's gonna be right there looking at you
They're actually all coming up there right now. They're like climbing up there. Yes, that guy's climbing the ladder in front of you
What? That guy's climbing up there
There's a guy up here
You're chasing him right now. This guy knows you're chasing him. He's running away from you
Okay, now they're going up that ladder. Why are they all up there? I don't know. I think they heard you
I haven't been spotted yet. They're coming down sliding back down. They're both down. Oh
Oh, you got you got two different people here. Oh here is the commander?
Yeah, the commander's here and there's three people on the other side
Listen, I need some Ubisoft call-outs
sure
Well, watch out on your three three o'clock no nice nice three o'clock
Awesome, dude. Good job
Straight ahead
Watch out watch out
He's this guy's angry. This guy's angry up on your left side. You can see him right there right in front of him
Come on. Give him the booyah. There it is. Nice job. Nice job booyah. They're suspicious
I don't know if you can really get these two
They see the body
The one on the far side is the one
No, it's really hard to not just get out of this binoculars and press V
I tell you how hard it is for me not to do that right now. This guy sees
Uh-oh, you're not two people see oh, they all see now you're in trouble
That guy's true. That guy just threw ice bottle. I got a through like a way. What do you just do? He's really a firework
What the fuck is this guy doing? I got a shot of the layer in the
I just used my best stealth maneuver. Let me help you. Oh
Fuck oh wait, I killed him. Was that you? I just killed that guy. Is there a mortar? Yeah. Wait, hang on
You shot that was me. I shot it from here. You did yours and then I did mine and we did we doubled them
There was not a guy like you just mortared me. That was the only guy left
After that I got a sniper rifle
Okay, so that was cool. Let's get a tank
We actually drive this one enter as driver. Okay, can we both get why did it did it not let us drive?
During the mission
apparently not
If I don't get in this tank, I'm no I'm not going to I
Actually want to roll into the next mission with two tanks and scare the absolute shit out of the like four guards
We have to take down because this is mission number two of the game. Don't do it. No, we have to let's make it work
I I'd literally just looked I have to look where I'm going. The turret just happens to point where I'm looking
Okay, I'm not gonna like always that really we just won the mission. I
I just won the mission
We are so far away from this one. I don't better get going
Which way we have a mission?
It's the other way. It's like behind you. It's it's as far away from the possibly could be map seems kind of small
I wonder if I'm if it opens up later
This is one of the islands. I think there might be more than one. Yeah
This thing actually fucking moves for a tank. Holy shit
This looks driving way too fast for a tank
tanks
Maybe the sense of speed is warped. We're just so used to walking everywhere. They didn't just tell this guy's
1800 this is gonna take so long
Are you shooting the machine? Oh, that's a machine gun
No, don't shoot that tanks are deceptively fast
I think the only reason why is because there any time you see a tank in like a movie or a TV show
it's just going like
Like two miles per hour for some reason you never see tanks moving fast
I I did not know there was a person there. Wait, you you moved the thing you hit him with the stick
You turn you turn and aim you're gonna hit sliding the head
She ducked she actually ducked underneath it. No, don't I think you hit a stick sandwich
It's not you don't run into the road get out of here get out of here get out get out move
this is like when you spawn in the tank in GTA like
like battlefield now, I
Wouldn't surprise if you'd like turned around. It was like just for like green like player number like usernames
You heard a drive
every time
Now they're gonna just back off into a ravine you you killed that guy that was you that did that
Everything is so loud
Would I kill?
Your killing them. I why am I getting dude? You're you're doing dishonorable kills while we're in the same party
I'm getting negative points because of that
We're here to liberate the island. Okay, we use some unconventional means. We're trying to free the people
What
Necessary sacrifice. This is so loud. I
Can't hear anything besides tank sounds. Did they try to spike strip us didn't work
I'm trying to do the thing that I used to do in TF2 or I would just load into like bad water
come out of the spawn and just
Aim the huntsman and just shoot it into the air and hope to God that I hit somebody in the head
I think every single person
Cod like
Throwing nice beginning of match. Yeah
And the thing is it sucks because in like 10 plus years that I played TF2 the hundreds of hours
I probably played Huntsman sniper it never happened. It was that's just disappointing
You think that maybe once in like 5,000 10,000 chances it would work
I mean, that's that's why it took so long to record the videos
All right, so what are we doing here secure gasoline two poles glamour to be we got to secure the gasoline
Really? This is gonna stop a tank a
fucking parking garage
little strip
I
Told you this is we're way over prepared for the second mission of the game. Oh
I think it's both the gas station. I think it's blue gas station
I'm just letting you go first
Alright, don't blow up those tanks
To cure fuel. Alright, we need to secure this bill. I'm gonna get out
Pardon me
That wasn't me that that I haven't done a thing
You just got killed on by the actual regular guys after after getting up on a soapbox and saying how over prepared we were
Hold on. I'm gonna come save him. I would be careful. I'm probably gonna spawn in but in your car
Yeah, I don't think you can get me nice. All right
So security the gas
I said one slow motion. Right? Yeah, did you go slow mo? Um, I just killed that guy. I know
Oh, it was the last it was the last guy. Nice. We got it job
Excuse me
No, excuse me. No alarms sounded like how the radio every single time is like, okay
So what you're gonna want to do is get up on a like high place use your camera spot as many enemies as you can
I'm trying to stay in stealth. I was coming to tanks
Yeah, it said we've didn't sound an alarm we were the alarm
Okay, overcome the regime to become stronger
Stay in the tanks for the whole game. That's kind of no, that's kind of boring. I want to fly around like helicopters on
I'm ready for my new toy. Excuse me developers
Look at how spoiled we really are
The tank was fun to drive around a tank and shoot stuff, but I want something else done with this thing. I'm done with it
Yeah, I want I want I want a helicopter that can go on the water
That shoots missiles out the front and I want to be able to flat fast travel with it
I want to fly and I wanted to go into ground to how come there's no subterranean shit in Far Cry. I'm bored
I'm bored
I see what you're doing. I saw that
That guy is now yeah, you fired you fired guns of his doing on the motorcycle now he's going very fast to get away from you
I'm kind of wedged. Oh nice. Thank you. Why would you drive directly into this? Don't you think it hit the brakes? Oh my god
Did you do that? You did? Yes, you did
Okay, the alligators are cool and shit like them, but what what the hell what are they doing here?
Why are they here? This is like no reason for them to be out here right now. I don't know everybody
Let's stay home. They've run. They don't they don't get in the car. They just run behind us
That seems just so strange. It shouldn't happen. What the hell's going on here?
Who is that? It's like it's like a random event. Okay, I think we need to save this guy
I
Don't I know what you get that I'll get that away. I see what you were doing. I'm not doing any
I'm just yes, you are yeah observing with a with your gun. Okay, look at the clouds. Oh, they're so beautiful
What's he doing? Oh, he's taking the gun. All right night. Can we hang out? Let me hang out this good
I see you what?
Bad guy, this is bad guy. That was a bad. I mean, he's a good guy. I
See you I kind of I want to can this guy be getting the tank with us
See if you can like can you recruit people in like park ride 5? It looks like he's kind of with us
Maybe it was because he picked up a gun if he follows you
Here I go, oh
Did you wait that was you I have I okay is it if you hit right?
I said I know it's one HP
But if you hit right-click does it fire the machine gun till you hit right-click again?
All right. No, you just hold the button down. Let's I
It's toggle because right-click is toggle for me that includes this
Apparently for some reasons is aimed on sites. It's the same thing. Yeah. Yeah, but it's not this is firing
It's not but in the game it is. All right, does he follow us?
You killed him. I didn't I didn't he's alive. Why did you assume he's dead? I don't know cuz I saw an explosion
That guy is a bad guy. I don't know. They just rammed into me with a horse at night
I don't think that's a bad guy. I don't know what he's did he say. Sorry
Where's he going? I feel like we kind of need to see these this guy's story how it plays out
He's gonna have a real short one
All right, where is he? Where'd he go? Where'd he go? He just run him over
No, he's right here. That's not him
Who's this guy? That's not him. That's the that's a different guy. Oh
That's a different guy. Where'd I friend go?
He D. No, he's right here. All right, let's walk. I want to see what this guy goes. We have to see how this plays up
What's he doing? I don't know. Maybe we can't maybe he's not gonna do anything. Why is he down here? I don't know
Guapos in the way. Yeah, I'm trying to move him. Wait. He's found a thing. Do you play it found a place to go?
No, I think I think we've lost this guy's not gonna do anything
Wait, so we expect way too much from this guy. I mean we kind of do
Can you like I don't think we can like tell him to come with us. I almost killed him. I saw the knife
Yeah, that was scary. I don't know. Maybe if we just give him some space he'll wander back to the road. No, I
Wait, he sees something. He does. Yeah, something sees us
Move your guapo. Are you going up? I don't see anything so far. Oh, there's a guy over there
Wait, I hear something that you all right is you okay. All right good
I'm just making sure the road was clear. I can't kill him. He's
Yeah, you can't kill anybody with baseballs
Excuse me. All right, he'll be fine. Let's go. I'm trying so hard not to snipe him with the tank. Oh do it
He might show up later your play resonate before it's like a telltale moment
and when you like rescue the you rescue the dog and they're like in the first 10 minutes of the game and
Then spoil this for as an evil for whatever who cares games like 15 years old
Why did you cuz I want to get in? Oh, I don't think I can I can repair him
There's a there's a gunner seat. Is there I?
Can't sit in it. Oh, there we go. Yeah. All right. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go
You're gonna leave this behind
What oh you I want to like be in the same tank and be free. Oh, yeah, that's that's fine
I try to figure out what you're doing. What are you doing?
In this work. I was the next mission returned if we got to go back to the camp. Is it marked?
I think it's just down the road. All right, let's go
Good. Yeah, I'm good. What? Okay. You're just oddly quiet
Something is very loud. It's okay. We're friends. We just have a quiet road trip. I said, what are you gonna be for Halloween?
The Dark Knight Joker that's what I am every single fucking year
I go I do I go to Halloween every year as the as the Dark Knight Joker
And I like go up to people I go, you know how I got these scars like I just won't drop it
I'm just gonna be like a
Squid. All right, that's cool. Hey, wait, we have a we have something going on over here. What you're gonna wait
I'm a I am in a tank
True that's true. Is this guy see me?
I can't move
Why was he about it looked like he was about to be like a ranger? Oh
Yeah, I'll be eating you if I didn't anymore he's about to do like the nemesis system thing
He just like everything froze and it just looked at him
You got it. Oh shit. All right, we're gonna get a gun
Crisis of birth. Oh, you know, at least it's well gotta be crap. That's it. Whoa. All right. Let's get a Jeep tanks
It's not boring. I want a boring new car
dude
Can we get the person we just rescued in here?
Game's not fun unless there's always a nemesis guy to come up with like we've had
free stinking dies
Am I right? Yeah, it's only it's only funny when you get
What's happening?
That guy's blew his tires why he blows tires
And she I don't want to hit her I can't move can she get in hey
I see them. Well, how do I hunt the horn? It's G
Can we get their crocs in the back seat? Oh, I guess I guess they don't they can't jump in the back. That's kind of weird
Are you going turning around?
Okay. Oh my god. What is what is this?
It's an anti-tank is it underwater fucking landmine
What the hell why oh my god?
But it is D day in case in case somebody tries to invade this little beach inlet
They better not be another one right here. All right heading up this way
We might have to get out and climb
Why would we it's a fact like it's right here. I with I can't I can't drive up there. I don't think
It's it's Claris. Oh, yeah, we're going back to the camp
Maybe they'll give us a toy. I hope so if they don't I'm going to cry in the middle of the toy aisle
Oh, I thought that was an animal. No, just a bag
They use Zonk right now. No
Why should I be?
Here we go. So
We skipping the cutscene or are we gonna watch because I don't know I will try to skip it
How do you skip it? Um, I don't think we can it's just a black screen. Yeah, this is black screen the fire
Oh, there we go
Cinematic with partner, okay
We are the worst like we really are what's the point of like what what's the point of us playing this I mean
We get to the gameplay. Okay, I just drive around cinematic trailers. Okay get to
Gameplay, am I right gamers? I mean, we're just just driving and running people over the cars and I throw grenades and stuff
I guess that's fun, right? It's fun. Just kind of ride around and just drive around and ride around and drive around
Whatever I was saying. All right, let's go. No, we have to get a mission. Oh shit. We probably shouldn't have skipped that
New toy they heard you the developers are listening
I'll make sure my fiery corpse comes down on you. Okay, I'm gonna put on like different clothes because I feel like I should be doing
That right. Do we have different clothes? I think so. Yeah, you have gear. We've gotten some stuff
We've like new weapons. Don't we I have a watch. I have a sniper rifle. I'm putting this thing on
Okay, how's the sniper if I want air support? I'll have to blow it up. All right, we need to uh, there we go
Hmm look like oh shit. Okay, I zoom in
Really was it what's the point of having a scope?
Yes, you saw it too. It's basically just
it's like when it's like when people play shooters that don't have cross airs and
You just tape where the center of the screen is like on the middle of your monitor so that you know
Where to hit fire?
New photos, what are they? Okay, cool. So we have to destroy the
Sam site there are a bunch of horses here
We say we can't ride these if they got a saddle on them you can yeah, these are not wild
That's how you tell the difference from this with a tame horse in a wild horse
I don't know if you knew this but if you see like horses in nature, they don't come prepped with leather saddles
Um, I don't other equipment. I don't have I don't have the ability to go on. Hey, can you climb it?
Why can I not do that? I don't worry
I'm a friend. All right, so we're gonna get that on the map. Where is it over there?
We have to go destroy this shit just like okay, when did far cry become just cause when they made six of them
Hey, we got to go over here and like blow this up. Hold on. We gotta go over there and blow that up
New mission. What are we? What are you blowing up? So is there a difference between I mean, it's like not really
This horse is in this one
Let's go
Do you think that the reason why they keep making far cry games because all the far cry games are independent of each other, right?
You think the reason is because they don't if they came out with this game and it was called like
Into the abyss or something right and it was not a fire crap far cry game people would be like this is just a far cry game
What the fuck are you doing? Like what is this game them numbering these far cry games?
I think gives them some leeway where it's just hey, it's just another far cry game. Don't worry
They don't have to explain like why it's so similar. How do you fish?
We have fishing rod as a reward. It's a known brand. Yeah, they can't make this another game
Be nice horse. How do you fish? I don't know. We got a fishing rod. Yeah
Well, there's like a spot right here on the weapon wheel. Oh shit. Oh, nice. There it is
Okay, look for fishing spots each has opened the tackle box to equip the right fishing gear the right fish and then cast the line
I would toy the tackle box. I didn't get the horse with that, right? Okay. All right tackle box
What are we looking for? We're looking for fish
Okay, let's put on a um, I don't think you actually have to change anything cuz we don't have anything
Yeah, we don't have anything. I'm gonna have to have one. I don't I don't want to catch the alligator
Cast it like okay. See there's a fish right there
All right
Okay, I got one take it out
Do you yeah, you have to actually catch it though. Hang on. I'm gonna catch yours. No get out of here
Doesn't look like you have one to me. I do it's just like I don't know. I'm trying to reel it in
I'm holding right right trigger. I know it's it's right click. Whatever. Come on. Get over here. Hey
You snap the line fuck
Fish I got one. Wait, is it toggled? Is that the problem? Is that all right, please don't tell me that's it's not the problem
Is it cuz I have a toggled?
He's holding right click permanently. You might be no no way, right? Yep. That's what's happening toggle fishing
It's freaking me out because like it's such a far. How far can you cast the line?
No way. Nobody's gonna do it that far
How do you okay? Like I got another one, but I got I see that see the lightning. Yeah, I saw the lightning
How do you get them to actually bite? You got to like lure him in you got to like kind of wait
They'll come over you'll see a little bit of water
Yeah, and then can we get okay? I'm done. This is I fucking hate. This is stupid
I'm fucking done with this stupid ass god damn minigame. It sucks. Put it away. I'm done
I'm done. I don't do this. Oh
What a flop
He struck my lightning speech you give I
Can't put the fishing pole away. I know yeah, I think you have to go into your like actual inventory and like it holds queue
Like me once we blasted through Castillo's blockade
Well neat neither of us catch the fear no, but it's all right you have to um, however the level of skill up
What are they gonna make like gamer mouse that has rumble? Oh
That would be awful
Do you hold desk would vibrate?
It would just be like I
Would shake into your arm and it would shake all through your desk and your monitors
That's why I can't tell when I caught a fish because it was like I couldn't tell the difference between a nibble and bike
Hey, I need rumble on my mouse. We have to blow this stuff up. I still legitimately don't know how to put this fishing route away
Yeah, here we go you hold Q. All right, so we have to be careful because we're we're about to um, I
Don't know if that person sees us or I don't I think that person is hot. Is this hot? No, this is our car. Oh
I was wondering what the hell they were doing
They just like they just like drop the car
In front
Okay, this was a
Do you have anything this guy just has a hat and like a t-shirt and like boots
We need to get this guy like a weapon. He's in the middle of like a car. All right, where are you going?
That's my chance. I need uh, I need help. I need a hero
Dude, thanks work. All right, let's go. We have to destroy that with explosives. You see this guy. I heard that guy
You look I'm gonna lean out and snipe. It's out of here
What's the what are we even supposed to do to destroy the um, like the big auntie? Uh, oh
I shot that guy to another dimension, dude. I had to throw that guy in his right ear. So hard. There's pull them
Okay, we got one. Oh my god
Put out fire what's five
This guy is yours
I got to revive the croc
What do you imagine you get burnt and you're like, oh should I know duct tape that'll do it?
Have you ever seen duct tape burn before?
All right, so I that happened way too quickly you just drove into that exploded and now we have to do another one
Yeah, get the loot though
Could be a toy in here. That's right. There's loot
Edison's if you do you does it like share between us? I don't know. It's a good question
Probably, okay 500 meters that way. How about
We need a boat. I feel like if we swim I'm gonna get you down there. You doomed what?
Sorry
Would you do what did you see five? No, sorry. Yeah, you're close. You were close though. My destroyer is close
Wait, try a little bit closer until you're left. Where what's the plan here? What are you? What are you doing? I'm
What's wrong with me? You just water deeper. This is water toxic. What's going on?
What's wrong with me? Can you see me?
Yeah, what am I doing? Why I'm like, why am I can't breathe?
Hold on. I'm not drowning them up my heads above water. I think I think it's a good time to try the minigame
Yeah, I can stand up here. Why would I be drowning? I can stand here. Nice. All right, that just scared the shit out of me
I thought that was a fucking monster
What was that?
What was that? What was that? Hey gonna get a nibble out here. I don't know what that was, but it was scary
Yeah, I think the eye of Sauron just like looked over here. Hold on. I got something
What is hurting me, huh? Oh
Shit are you drowning?
Get him Guapo
Shark. Oh my god. That was terrifying
Yeah
Guapo was attacking something and I thought he was biting me but there was a shark in here trying to kill me
Hold on. I've got a fish
Wines gonna break Guapo stay with me, please. I need you. Oh what a what a good boy
I'm gonna be the winner. I'm like about to be there. I'm the winner. I got a fish. Did you really?
What kind of fish?
Shark really the big shark. I got a material. Did you actually get a shark?
Yeah, it's huge. Oh
Guapo Guapo Guapo
What is that that was just hacking me what is it? Oh shit Guapo, please
Come here. I just ride him. You just going towards this big boat that we definitely can't
I'm about to be on the surface over here. Oh
Interesting
Guapo, please
Guapo, please help me. I'm so close
That you
Yeah, the throat actually that's a good idea because you're gonna hit whatever's attacking me
Why am I still swimming?
No, but like I was still on my face in like eight inch water
Maybe I hope you had fun out there. It looked it looked pleasant. It's fun
Shoot the light out of the lighthouse
Wild pigs. Oh my god. Yeah, I don't wanna like kill them. I just drinking a cigar. I just like drank a cigar. What was that?
They're they're fighting Guapo
They just killed Guapo what you let them do this
Could they okay Guapo this little pound the bag. Did you say we should shoot the light out?
Yeah, shoot the light out of life. I can't tell this drop on bullets. I saw it done in one of the trailers
Just keep shooting. He's ready. Should I actually do there?
I'm close to Castillo ships
I want to hear
the ships
Like the thon
Okay, I love this comment
What he said
It's the house from the gamma
Correction screen and I know exactly what you're talking about
You know, you know what you get that right like adjust the brightness until you can see this but you can't see that
Yeah, it is the gamma correction screen. Why would you even catch that? What how much perceptive are you? It's crazy
There's a death. I
Shoot somebody from here. All right, we got to go up to the top of the lighthouse thing
Wait a second, but I love that like Far Cry became so famous for jumping puzzles
For tall things that they're like, yeah, fuck it. Let's just have them climb a rope to the top like
Just skip everything. No more climbing just pull
We don't have time for these puzzles anymore
Okay, I thought this is a bad guy look before you leap all right clear the ship of both clear both ships
If Lita was here, I'd kick her ass for keeping your secret. We have to parachute over
We I was gonna just snipe them
You want me to try to give you support over to watch?
I already I already did a stealth mission you it's your turn. You want me to do the stealth mission part. I
Mean dude, whatever. However, you want to do it? Okay, I'll try
You have a sniper rifle. I've got um, okay. Okay, I can like mark waypoints for you. Okay, so
Yeah, I'm gonna try to stealth over there. So we have to clear both ships
Yeah, just do one though. You don't have to do both. I'll come over after you to the closest one
I don't think this I don't think this is enough
Are you hoping W yes
Like I think it's okay because it's a thing to get up over here
Poggle parachute if I'm not gonna attack my shark, that's all I care about. I didn't see anybody on the first boat
There's a camera. There's a guy right here
Ladder I wouldn't go in you. Oh, you found the second ladder. I'm on board
And don't be afraid of using their own weapons against them. That's what I was about to do
Okay, you got a good view
Can you see my waypoints?
Okay, those are yours
Alright, I'm gonna I don't know if I can kill these guys
What do you mean? You don't know if you can kill them. I don't know this like this people everywhere
There guy was a guy over here in the right on your right
No, there's a guy. Um, the guy you dead ahead this guy to his to your left. It's on me
Okay, good job one down
the guy down below and the guy on the roof overlooking and
Three guys in this little boat courtyard trying to dump the person over the edge. They're coming back
I'm trying to throw the guy over the edge. The sun's getting in my eyes. Oh somebody somebody's up top
See you later dickhead
Guessing the stealth part is over. I hear the alarm. That was over. Oh shit
The guys have helicopter. You see the helicopter
No, I'm in my inventory. I was hoping to take care of think I got it taken care of kind of I
Why would you put this here?
Okay, what in God's fucking green earth is this here for this date?
You have a machine gun mounted up here. You're trying to block the view. What would you put this here for? Oh
I see the heli now. What? Oh you down? Yes
Hold on. I got the hero music blocking the mounted guns view. My theme song is on
Thank you. Nice work. I want to grapple blow up. Oh shit
That guy's not even here. He's underground god dammit. I haven't done a single goddamn thing. There we go. All right one clear
Parachute with parachute. Help me. I'm dead everybody. I was trying to parachute down to the guy. I
Wanted to like
parachute and swing down
Where am I?
Inside of like a but I'm like left for dead. I'm inside of one of the like little supply closets
Seriously, oh what? Okay. One. Wait. Why are you here? I just spawn next to you
Yeah, I die if I try to parachute down I died all right
Here comes Robota talent
Should I get we should have had you record stuff for this day?
How we get over the other side? I have a sniper rifle. What am I doing? Yeah, you got a sniper
I mean, it's not like it really matters. I think doesn't really go that far
This is seriously what a place like it was just like pub G
Two people just fucking shooting and missing over and over again. What happened like okay us sitting here sniping is like a shitty prices
Sequel, okay. Somebody is hitting us from somewhere. I don't know
One dude's shooting RPGs from the lighthouse
He's hitting us
Fuck you Danny. He's talking to be talking about us. No, there's still people on this one
Did we clear it yet? I
Think we can parachute out. This is not clear though. It's still somebody on here. Oh, he's over here. I've got a half a power shirt
They forgot to mention that there's about
staff of 150 people per boat
There's too many people
They brought a helicopter
They got him oh my god, how many did you shoot the hell that's our helicopter
It is yeah, I
Think the music has looped at least one fault because we're taking too long. I
swear to God I've heard like
I think we got like the
You know when the music goes like did you yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, we got we got the full loop I think
This is like they hang on hang on hang on. There's actually a boat. Is there a real boat?
I think our friendly helicopters gonna blow it up. Let's get it. Let's get it. All right, shoot
Fuck you. No, what the hell?
I'm just I'm just walking over there, man. I'm just gonna walk over
Okay, I have a really really like campaign
Alex how did the alligator get onto the boat? Does it use the ladder?
Clear clear
Yep
Learn it out more soldiers in
Where are you I'm on the other boat this could be good. It could be good. What do you think?
I've got a I've got a I've got a swing spot. All right
I'm looking at you
Break your legs
Like a shattering sound that was so loud. I
Love how it was like at 14 frames a second. Oh
Hey, wait, here's the bad guy. Here's the bad guy. This guy we have to kill
I'm gonna fucking move this guy
Nuke him. I'm gonna pull it fuck. Where's my how come I can't do this?
Help help
He's dead. Good job
Alright, there can't be that many more. We've probably taken out most of the Navy
What about these guys? Yeah
Hey come a little earlier next time just like the cavalry
Showing up late and claiming all the credit
my game crashed
Did it what's happening? What the fuck is one of the two there's got to be like one guy left
That was okay. That was weird
I'm bored
Okay, it's okay. Where is this last person? I did it just get it
Yeah, we did it both ships clear to soldiers gorilla boats can now escape. Okay, and
Maybe we'll get picked up
Now you gotta wait for the cool down
Oh
I'm alive. Don't worry. What's the joke? How do we get off of this?
Reach Clara's boat. Oh, she's coming. We made it
You know one of these times we're gonna do that in the main characters bodies is gonna be lying on the ground. Oh shit
boat sequence
Holy shit. We just made it out of there to give you credit Clara fucking did it. We did it, Danny
That was the difference. What's your plan? What did she do? She didn't do shit
He came to rescue us for the boat jobs until we could scrape up some money
Open a body shop if the Yankee blockade taught us anything. It's how to keep things running when you got nothing. That's the dream
Sure, the Yankees might pay you to park their cars or pick their fruit, but you'll never be one of them
The American dream doesn't come in our color. Okay, if we're shitting on dreams
What are you going to do if you win? Who are the people in the boats back here?
The next president won't last six months before they are assassinated
Were they on the boat? They're in they're in fisher boats. You ever see Dunkirk? Whoa. Whoa
It's a vision Danny, but I'm not as naive look up
This revolution will free yada, but won't fix it when we take the capital yada will be burning
Will be civil war factions warlords born back in the sky birds
You just wait till birds get smart enough to do this shit and shape into like a like a middle finger or something
Just wait until they get that kind of sentience
That's why we're making drones they're just like birds but you have to do this more control
No one would choose this. No, Danny
Everyone who follows me who joins Libertad chooses this but you know, there's aren't real birds are drones
Fuck you
Maybe a fancy apron leave me out of your fantasies Clara. I
Want to look forward I don't like looking this way
You don't think that was like the camera where like we're doing like the joke where we're gonna crash and would not looking
I like that one. I know but like I don't I want to be in control of that not her. I think we got imprisoned
Oh
This one
Let's watch this one, oh man and a fake it can be hard to see I haven't even seen this actor on screen yet
So I kind of want to
Understands that loyalty country is key to his survival. Not justice not love not even family
loyalty vision that look on themselves
Fake yarn is love to be the outcasts
They are addicted to their surface perversions
Chaos lies like wild dogs, but what dogs can be broken. What's the subtitle? What's going on the subtitle and if
dog
Refuses like the last line goes to the top just in case you read really slow
It's not on the screen right now, it's a lot of words for that sentence
You imagine if you didn't like if you would on a different language
You didn't understand it and you thought this is all they said you would think like, oh wow, that's all they said here. Okay, let's see
Somebody's still saying
And if a dog refuses to break they will be no more steps and if a dog refuses to break
That's how each one of these is starting
Yeah, like the last words of the last sentence start the next line and if a dog refuses to break
That person's dead, you know what I mean? Like they always do that in movies and TV shows
Oh, I'm gonna have the butter the the pistol or the rifle and hit you in the head like 12 times
The person is a club if they're gonna like do that
After I keep my promises Danny you wanted a boat you got a book
It's a beautiful. This is the one subterranean missile launching the helicopter boat. Is it really you two are just gonna let me leave
Bullshit, you could have sold us out a long time ago. All right, so we get we kind of get what happens
I'm driving the book from back here
Yeah, where the engine block is are you trying?
Wait, are you fucking me? Are you actually driving? Are you driving? You're driving. I am you
Military presence increased your horn. I don't think there's a horn. Okay. Well, this was fun, but we'd have to go over here
Don't be okay
We're gonna get some you can respawn it a thousand times. It's
Cars respawn. Don't worry, man. They really cut the budget for this far crime. All right, I mean look at this boat
Wait, where is this? Yeah, he's just dig
Whatever. Wait, let's go over here. Like I swear to God that person is so if I put my mouth to the ground and went like
They'd probably hear us and I could be like
I could put my ear on the ground. They could yell it. I mean, that's how they communicated before cell phones. Oh
See, it's why this concrete nevermind. All right, let's work
All right, let's work
What's the what's the job?
Can you hear this? I don't hear anything. He's only giving the quest to me. Oh
I'm just gonna start taking stuff. Whatever. He said before we can do the next mission
We need to have the achievements for beating Far Cry 5. I'm a weapon too. All right. Look I'll get a new gun here
Let's put it on
attachments
Yeah, it looks good. I want to use this thing. It's what slot is it in?
He also said he needs both of us to do the Voss
definition of insanity line
This is the definition of insanity
Sorry, was that like the Shakespearean interpretation? It was me just saying it to move on and go
Oh, these if we get different supreme. Whoa, what are these weapons EMP pulse to knock over enemies?
Chaos by launching poison gas. I don't need to need to hear anything else. That's not that one. What is this one?
Resolve real quick Britain. I don't know what this thing is. I got the gas one
Which is a gas coffee? Yeah poison gas. Oh poison gas. Okay
Does that just equip no?
Resolver I'm like I want to go look out and see what this thing does which which I'll pick a different one
Which one did you get? I got the one that looks like a wrench
number two
Okay, without was it
Flamethrower. All right. That's the thing. I just got so what's this resolver of weapon? How do we use it?
You probably have to like go into the inventory and equip it in the armory
armory
Have to equip it. Oh
Arsenal
Like in your actual arsenal. Okay. Yeah, I see
What's the other thing do I don't I don't want the flamethrower anymore put this thing on it's a cross
I'm done with you. This might be kind of fun
Sounds like the Ubisoft people playing with the ad, you know what? Whatever
I'm gonna be wicked low fucking energy for the rest of stream. You ready? Okay. Ah
All right, dude, you ready? Let's go. I don't know you sure. Yeah, you really okay. Let's um, I got this cool thing here
So where we gonna go?
Yeah, actually I'm gonna take a shit for like 30 minutes and then I'm gonna go make some dinner
Then I'm gonna take my dog out and then I'm gonna run some errands and then I'll then I'll play co-op with you again
I promise. No, I'm good. I'm good. Um, I'll talk to you later, though
Like I'll talk to you like at some point. Thanks for playing. All right, we're gonna go over here
My was my chat. I can't see anything
Is there any that you can relate to more than?
Getting a co-op game with your friend and you guys play at one time and that you never play it again ever
Once you're back, it's every experience ever
Ammo new believers because you were surprised. Let's keep it that way. We need to know this. This is important
I still controls all of yada with soldados. I like that. They're all scrapbookers. The capital is a stronghold
It's good to have some hobbies. We free you can do when you're waiting for your friends to log on
So they'll play co-op with you again hit military targets like FND bases and checkpoints
This does look like a
Operations that will unite the revolution and make Libertad stronger to do that
I need you to recruit three groups in yada to fight with Libertad each is waging war across
What are these subtitles I should turn these off
Poison lifeline you guys get this game. I hope you enjoy these islands
Other places
This is the demo we're giving you the demo of the game so you can decide if you want to buy it or not
Because you're not gonna see any of these places
Are we going here right now
There's like a leader in each zone
Counter-propaganda campaign and for some reason be like HQ of the resistance is right in the
Was saying this is really confusing
Well, we're not making this any easier. We're skipping every cutscene and run
We're not making it really easy for you to pay attention
But the Montero family is waging war against Jose they hate visitors
But I even tell on a mechanic who has a workshop in Costa del Mar his name is Philly Barca
And he's their gatekeeper. Okay, can we get a helicopter and just fly to the leaders?
I'll be here actioning targeted Libertad strikes against Castillo throughout yada
Hang on. I'm going to get all these groups to sign up to Libertad by myself
How simple you help we're gonna get a change dot org petition going there's a lot of people we have to go get
We're gonna get a lot of these. There's a lot of people here. I send a squad to these groups
I'm an invader. I send a scout then I'm not serious with you
They get my best career without politics and bullshit just help Libertad takes the capital we slid and on throat
We got a pretty good idea. Oh, I try to walk. I tried to skip earlier. Oh, we have a real boat. Oh
Oh
Okay, now we're talking now. We're actually are talking meet the legends, okay
Meet the Monteros. Oh god. This did just open up. All right. We won't go first
Uh, yeah, I think I think we can go wherever extra content now available
You can go up down. What do you think? Hold on. I have a new friend Pete the Elbertson's
Where's my new friend? What do you mean new friend? I have a new buddy somewhere
Oh, we can call for our boats now. Oh, yeah. Okay
Do you want to get in the boat? Just let's go this way. Yeah, what do I have? Okay, hold on
I did you buy this game because I didn't buy it. I did the like Ubisoft
subscription thing for like one month I
What is that?
they you know, like like
EA play yeah, and apparently it
Unlocks like every premium thing so hold on but to show you how ridiculous this shit is what hold on
I'm about to do like a sea of thieves cosmetic
You have like a Kano I hold on it hasn't I haven't even finished yet
How much do you hold on I need you to while you're doing that?
I need you to explain to me very slowly so I can keep up and understand you
You're paying a monthly subscription to Ubisoft to play like three games that come out. No, no, no, you must understand
Dollars so I could play this for one stream and then I'm just gonna unsubscribe
Before the next month charges me. Okay, but but is that what the service is?
It's to like play Ubisoft games like as a subscription. Yeah, that's that seem that's it. That's impossible
I don't believe you. That's what I mean. They gave me the super look at my look at my hand
I have a robot hand. Hold on. Hold on
What is it doing? No, no behind you what?
It has a QR code around its collar really
So it's $15 a month and you get to play any Ubisoft game you want I guess yeah
why are you saying it like we're doing a sponsored segment because I'm trying to understand because
You can get every Ubisoft game that probably ever came out on like sales. Oh, I also apparently unlock like
New weapons. How many new weapons did I get?
This really is like use my cheat code
I'm the guy standing behind the person cooking the food in the infomercial going now. Hold on a second Kathy
You're hold on you're telling me that this can cook rice and can cook chicken at the same time. Explain that to me
I don't understand
What the okay this game sucks, this is stupid. I hate this. I don't like it anymore. I don't like this game anymore
I got a Winchester
Get out of here get it with you or with your Ubisoft subscription character
It's not this stupid not fair. I
Paid $60 for this game. How much did you pay for it again? Explain it again plated scorpion. This was $15
Yeah, I guess I paid three top four times as much as you did for this game
Okay, but I mean nothing stopping you from getting premium currency and just going ahead and buying it to adding these cosmetic items to your game
What the hell that's you could just pay you could just pay more and then you could unlock them permanently
You were supposed to buy the $200 edition. I am so confused. I didn't think that was a thing
Is that why they made their own launcher? Is that why they really like leaned into the like the you play connect thing?
That's probably just because steam takes like 20% of the profit on everything but but didn't we did I bought this?
Oh my god, what happened?
Okay, there are two objects in the ocean that could possibly be hit
Yes, and you have hit both of them
Statistic statistically if you use the whole service area, it's like a zero point zero zero zero one percent chance to hit those boats. I
Am still so fucking I'm floored by this whole Ubisoft thing. I'm sorry. I just am I
Mean you could you could probably access the the you play shop in the game. I bet because you couldn't Assassin's Creed
How many games does Ubisoft think they're gonna release I
Don't I don't know that wasn't even my only costume. I have three how many games is Ubisoft release a year?
three four maybe
The cyberpunk one was pretty this one's gonna make you mad too, but for a different reason
What are you doing more crazy things now
What you get like a cool I?
Get I you get like laser cannons and cool costumes and I get like a fucking crossbow that was made out of a toaster
Okay, let's go
We need a car
Listen, okay. Well, I just want to be clear. We're trying to usurp the government
While also taking part in beautiful capitalism. I don't listen. Look at these look at these beautiful shoes in my watch
Solid gold
Let's go
Listen only the capital is gonna come up with this laser gun with magnetic reload. I just put the magazine
Also that guy doesn't get mad
Hey, why don't you use your like cool new gun on this guy?
That's so I did you is it $15 to get loud I just met this lady
Why do I have the option what is happening?
Why okay, I was so confused your gun is too loud, I don't care how much it cost
Get this lady out here
Get we gotta get with this lady's a fucking menace we gotta get over this wrong person
That's the quest what the hell you're don't I don't like they're too loud
If you paid more money to be louder than me, nobody's louder than me
I'm one of the loudest most annoying streamers on Twitch. Don't you get it?
You know, I don't be able to be badly be a little louder than me. Oh, what does this do?
I don't know. Maybe this is the fact that there was an explosion that happened five feet away from me
We have to make contact with Philly
Shit
Okay, I'll use pay-to-win Robo dog
Okay, are you ready? I just like gassed everybody
I don't know. I don't have a I don't have a horse somehow and that may him
Yeah, I want you want to go get a robot one from the fucking store
It probably is one rockets on its back
Hold on did I get a super rocket too? I
Think we can probably I think we can take this over
There's a helicopter here dude, we have to take this place out. Let's do this slowly and actually methodically. Let's actually do it
Okay, really? There's a helicopter right here
Actually sneak and do this correctly. Okay, I'll uh, I'll do some spying
Sure
That's quite a climb for and claim this is there anybody up on this tower
I don't know. There are a couple people it looks pretty open. There's just guy on the roof
Is there a guy but there's a guy on the roof?
How do I get up on that's not none of the not of that building. There's a guy on the roof
To your right. Let me get up there. Oh
Okay. Yeah, I don't know that that guy just I don't know this guy's doing but
You're asking you about shooting somebody on a ladder. Well, that guy wasn't technically on a ladder
All right, I'm just gonna go over here. I think this they see you getting in the helicopter. I'm gonna try to cover you
It said anti aircraft covers the skies
I'll go up. Oh shit. Don't take a picture with you fucking good. What?
Good doesn't look like it. Oh
You're not good
Damn it. I thought it already blew up. It wasn't exploded yet
How did you even get up there?
On the tower, oh you already that was a named guy
You're this is fucked up. What's going on? Um
Hey guapo is down you
It's guapo didn't pay enough money
I'm having common. I'm going
How do we claim this place we have to go in and like break something or grab something or is it just kill the people?
I
Think this is just a random outpost. I think we can actually do something here, right like turn off. Okay, hold on interact
Here we go. All right access chopper. I
literally pressed Q W P O Q L P O P O Q W 1 2 0 0 5
That's what I pressed. I didn't I don't even know what in buttons
I just pressed random ones about my password in chat after giving up everything that's happened recently
It's connecting
Okay connecting
Alright, is it still connecting? Where's the mouse? Yeah, where's the mouse?
How long is it to connect?
Nobody's coughing in here. All right, let's go through glass. Oh, that's not good. There's a helicopter. I know this is a helicopter
I've been trying to shoot the pilot out. I like hacked this thing, but I don't know if it's doing anything
It says connected. Oh
What's down here? I'm gonna blow up the helicopter before I kill this guy
Um, I just went underground
Wait, where's my pay-to-win sniper?
It's just things I feel like I'm watching the intro of a TV show. So much shit is on the top left of my screen
It's as if it's telling me who like made the game and shit. What it looked like. Are you dead? I went like down. I
Like come collecting like military
Ingredients, I don't know whatever it is. I went down. There's a little building can go in and I went down into the basement
I can't see it's a lot of stuff a single thing. I think I got everything
Well, this is down
Did I
In a are you okay up there? No, no
There's a lot of people
Wait, I got a bunker key card. Hang on
It doesn't pop up on my screen that says if I just put my credit card in right now
I can actually buy a revive. I
Wouldn't be surprised
Bunker key card. Come on. They got me something cool here
There's about six people on my corpse
What the fuck I I'm just coming up. I have no idea. There's a seven people on my body
Okay, I got a key card. Oh, you're dead. Okay, I'm helping. Oh my god. All right, you're any missiles or anything heavy
Hey, hey, what happened? Are you okay?
Use the rocket backpack. I don't have that one. I have the gas. Oh
Shit, we're in trouble. There are two helicopters
Wow
I don't have any heels left either
What the fuck what ammo? I'm dead. Are you still alive?
moment momentarily
There's a nice slide
Yep. All right. I just smoked a cigar and put it out on my hand to kill myself. Oh
I did it. What's happening? Just shut the pilot finally. Oh, you got you got pilot. Nice. I
Knocked the helmet off
No, not Robo dog. All right, I got Robo dog
All right, but what always what are we doing here? I got like a key card. Did we haven't liberated the place?
Objective telling you where to go
Nagging you. Oh, you have to just kill everybody. So where's the anti-air that like shoots the helicopters down?
I think we just claimed it. Maybe when this cycles back, we'll get access to the helicopter
helicopter
Come on, please. Oh
Yeah, we got it. What do we we did? Oh
Helicopter inbound. Oh
Hell yeah, finally
The guilt finally caught up with me you buying more
No, I've just been using
I've just been using the ones that I already had
This is restricted airspace, so we have to get the hell out of here fast
It's we just captured it. It's ours. Apparently it's not a bear. I guess not
Wait, can you are you over here? Can you get in here? Yeah, one sec
Nice. All right, where someone's noticing us. How do you fly?
We've been seen by
Nope
Just trying to get out of the airspace. All right. Hell. Yeah, that's kind of sad that our
guapos are
They'll catch up running
All right, let me get the controls here
So it's just forward back left right and then it's space control
Kate 9000 just died. So I guess they weren't fine. How do I turn? Oh, I have to actually be okay
I'm gonna get a free look. All right, let's go. Let's fly to the mission. Let's try not to break this
You look you just went to a rave. I do you look like you just went to like Burning Man. I
Don't know why I thought that said e exit vehicle slash freak out I'm gonna try to do this very carefully
What kind of person works in a place like this? Oh
I didn't get it landed. Where's he just a fucking lose it
Exactly what I would have done. I like this character
Really said she was seen at the tobacco plantation. All right, let's go. What what happened to the chopper? I don't know
It's apparently gone. It's not to make do with this
If you bring this vehicle to a pickup point, you can call it in whenever you want. I can use can you slash DMCA?
The plane
Or on to the next toy, that's all we care about. Oh wow a toy we both get in this
This is back. You're in the back. You're yeah, you're the pie. I'm facing backwards
Okay, how do I fly it?
restricted airspace is on your radar
Accelerate the accelerate. Yeah, and then pitch. Um, I don't know what that does
Holy fucking smokes, dude. Are you kidding me?
We actually just do that
from a takeoff
This is a vertical takeoff and landing
Itch and yaw, what's this? I'm trying
Now is a plantation
Press E to shoot who is she after? Oh fuck we're gonna get fired. I didn't mean to do that. I'm sorry
I'm sorry. That was it. That was a full-on painful. Yeah, that was a big one
Yes, I do I am I am Iron Man one. Oh
My god, that's all it does. Oh, what is that? Oh
Whose plane is this?
Okay, I'm out of ammo. We got him. No. Oh
They're coming back
What was that?
Hold on. I've got like booby traps
Plane is just freaking out up there. This plane is freaking me out. I
Out or something
Well plane is gone
Plane just did a flip. Okay, we'll get another one planes actually upside down. Well done
There's a supply drop whoever is in that plane right now is and puked their guts out like five times
It's no way you're gonna keep doing that. So what is this another outpost or just like I think this is another outpost
This is a good person. I'm pretty sure the laser. Oh
Okay, I don't know. I thought that was a friendly. It's like a bunker
No, this is like a little bunker like we probably claim it though. Do we have to destroy stuff?
didn't the thing said destroy things and you'll I
Swear to god. I was like destroy. I'll try to machete the likes
That's a good question just break shit
Clearly looks like we can take this it does but I don't think there's anything here. Oh
That was a UFO. I wasn't even playing guided missile. All right. Well, I guess we have to go over here
Oh lower it
I'm pulling like glass out of my body. Lower your crock lower your crocodile now
No guapo
Are we back in the in the like tobacco field? I gotta get guapo. Yeah, we're back in the tobacco places
Come on guapo. Wait, who are you?
This person have five hundred thousand help maybe a little overkill
Yeah, you get over here I'm okay
Well, I was all right. All right guapo. You're good. Where are my other gadgets? There's a really weird sound that just came out of your dog
It's some like grease in his joints. I bet you he gets struck by lightning
Nope another helicopter person. I cannot kill. Okay, like I'm in dress pants doing this like
It's like a thousand dollar suit and you just slide around
Hey, is there like a player three in here because these guys are all already dead
I feel like we did this already like when we are thanks for burning me with your cool
Jetpack that will never happen. By the way, there will never be a jetpack
Ever never gonna happen. Oh, I get to do boosts and you leave a wake of fire behind you that's hurting us
We talked about like Oh flying cars jetpacks. Nope. No when you add the other axis
Not just left and right but up and down and for you know, they understand how insane that would be if they were flying cars
People would be able to use the Y & Z axis to pass you on the road, which is in the air
There'd be a car there would be a flying car accident every like there'd be 50,000 flying car accidents every one second
If you think that that like dick behind you that is just riding your ass while you're going the speed limit on the highway
If you don't think that the fat guy has a Y & Z axis
He's not gonna fucking crash with this first time he drives that car you get twice as many lanes though
Instead of just horizontal you get vertical lanes. So they got more space. They have more room
When there's 50,000 cars on the road think of how many cars are in the highway?
Yeah, but it's like are there more people in this timeline or the same amount of people
This same amount of people think about when you drive down the road how many cars you are around?
Imagine if they could just be anywhere in the sky
Listen to me that sounds like you're stifling progress people said that about cars to it
They're like, you know, there's so many horses. What if a lot of people added like cars to this?
They're gonna run over the horses
We're all still on the same axis though. You're not adding an axis by having a horse to a car
Hey, they wouldn't they share the same plane
Skip that skip it now
Sounds like James Gunn worked hard on this
Rehired and that's the best he could do
Circumstances with all the mental anguish. Oh
Here we go
fight fight
Well run does
They're all
Is the game too loud? I feel like they was excruciatingly loud. It's louder now. I feel like right now. Yeah, it definitely got louder
I can't aim this gun that far. Why are they attacking this?
What did you see that?
No, I was too busy spinning gas over there. What happened? I just traveled like 15 feet for that knife kill like
Take out the soldiers. All right, there's only I think there's only one more. I think it's still getting loud
It's that definitely is getting louder. Where's this last person? Oh, here comes a helicopter, of course
Helicopter coming in
I'm gonna throw an explosive barrel at the helicopter and you shoot it in nevermind
Oh, I just put gas out here this guy's taking off. He's like I'm out of here
Did you do that? Yeah, why did the car 15 times? I don't know
Watch out
Come on. Let me snipe him. Come on
Is it bulletproof? I was thinking earlier. I think it is
Yeah, this shit's bulletproof. I can't hear
You're gonna land I feel like he's going to land I was he hovering like
What about the mounted guns? Can you aim mount a gun that high? Yes. Whoa. He had more health than the helicopter
Just lying on the ground
Shield
What is this game? Okay, this one's actually not fatal it doesn't work
I shot right through it. It's a piece of cardboard
Hold that shield up. I want to see so hold on. Hold on. It doesn't actually work. It does it actually works
Listen, these are the same developers that made rainbow six, you know all the clips you see on Twitter
It's always the shield guy. He just walks into a room holds the shield up for 30 straight seconds. Everybody laughs
Josh you feet though
Hey, remember when like I played rainbow six season. I thought I was gonna like it
No, I was that might have been like the the game that I would hate the most. I remember rainbow siege
Rainbow six siege. Why are we saying rainbow siege rainbow six siege in
Alpha had forced open mic lobbies. Oh, yeah
That's so bad. You're okay. So everyone who was streaming it you just go into a lobby
It was like alright, they've got a guy in the next room. Yep. I'm gonna go ahead and put up my shield
Hey, hey, can we get some grenades in there?
Ah
It was actually the Ubisoft trailers. It really was the Ubisoft trailers people just talking
Yeah, people don't talk when they play co-op games. Usually I don't want people to hear me unrecorded
I've listened like but back when I would like used to make YouTube videos, right?
you did you'd record a bunch of stuff for like hours and hours at a time and
I don't know why I do this shit
But I just go like this when I know when no one's in the room and I'm just alone and like I'm not even aware
of it, I just go like this like
I just like sniff
every like two to three minutes, I'll just do like a
I don't I don't get it. I don't know why it just happens
I will listen to whole parts of recordings that were like 20 minutes of silence and beginning like gameplay and you just hear like
I feel like I'm now I'm sniffing right?
Yeah, see you just like it you were now on manual sniffing. I
Don't know what it is. It's like maybe it's like breathing in to like get up to
Stable my breath to shoot it something. I don't know. It's like weird
Yeah, I gotta go in and then it comes out
No, it's not like an irritation or like I have allergies or something in the room is bothering me or at my stuffy nose
No, it's just I just make a loud
Inhale noise every like few minutes
I
Think is kind of like an echo location for humans
It's like hey, I'm in this room. I was in your chat right now. I would be doing triple question marks in the chat
I think everybody's already used to it. It's like it's not it's actually not
Echolocation sniffing really loud to like
Yeah, so I let someone know you're coming
So if you're like walking down the hall and you think someone may not know that you're coming it's like, you know, like hey
I'm I'm on my way
Whatever you're doing in here better not be weird
Better not be weird embarrassing cuz here I come
That's so funny cuz like that's like I have no idea what you're talking
That was I actually he's right. Yeah true. Oh
That's so funny
But I can you know part of you probably is that is probably correct is you hear people kind of like
Mouth breathing and stuff when they're walking or you'll hear like
So that makes sense, yeah
Just not coming around that Dachshund I saw a doctor there is a doctor in this game with
Third we are in third person. I'm trying to capitalize on third person. This is a really weird build camp facilities
Okay, just like they can follow up for frame rates like worse than third person
I really don't think we're supposed to be in third person. I made contact with the motoros
Well Carlos wants nothing to do with me, but I get along with his daughter. I think she's my way in
You need to understand them
First step is understanding this camp
You need to become one of them
Yes, sorry coming here with my $4,000 suit try not to get my shoes dirty
Could you guys put me in the right direction to overthrow the revolution? I want the I want the Dachshund pet
I
Feel like this would be a really you would have an alligator right here next to like a Dachshund
This is like seems really bad
He's he's got a quest. It says who's a good boy. I can't even touch him
Philly's furry friend fancies a fantastic feast. Look at this perfect little sausage
I've got to find him a yummy treat a meal fit for a puppy prince on his special day reward a hundred XP
You shoot me in the head. I
Stuck I don't speak bark amigo. I'm stuck in third person
Yeah, I'm stuck in third person too. Oh, you still are because I can't interact with anything
This is my world. You're just passing through no
Only in the camp, okay, I love this little thing little wheels
All right, I guess we're gonna um build a gorilla camp I think you have to do that
Would you rather have access to a wingsuit and
Hide out locations for fast travel. Mm-hmm, or
No, the other one sucks. What is it? You can't just say but you know, yeah
What if I want that one's a fishing hut and we've already tried that
Didn't go so well. Mm-hmm, and then visit a cantina and trade animal and fish meat for
Meals that grant temporary buffs like in that one Capcom game that everybody likes. You're the new face
Yeah, that's cool. Well, we'll do the um, the wingsuit one. Why would you pick the other one on stream?
That's like the streamer one. You have to pick that one. Oh
There are lots of big crocs search for a park west end of Cortina River has a great hunting spot a
Lot of quests now. Yeah
There's that's we don't even have the main quest or the side quest. I said mustard here. I don't have mustard on my back
water
It's a vacuum cleaner that I've turned into a put on reverse and put in your reason to connect into that into a tank
Which then it goes a little thing that goes into my mouth from the top of that and it's water
I turn the vacuum on reverse and I can drink it
I have a leader and recruits
I'm assigning. Wait a second. Are these passive missions? I think I was what did you do?
I just walked over here and put us on a cutscene
Lost tourist listen Carlos, I mean kind of was
She sent and I don't blame you have no history here again, I we just don't ever
Any way that we can get right to the fly the plane around is
What we are doing right now
In the beginning we talked about like the movie
We keep watching the far cry movie and leaving in the first act and why do we keep watching the movies?
It's got it's gotten even worse. We are not only leaving in the first act of every far cry movie
We are looking up the Wikipedia page of the movie and just reading the spoilers. We don't even care
This is how like IGN always has a walkthrough guide every single time a game launches
It's probably just like one guy who skips every single cutscene and rushes through the missions to be the first person to have like the
Google search engine optimization
like walkthrough page up
You and I are just sitting in the movie theater right now we both have our phones up
Ten minutes in the movie has gone by we're both on the Wikipedia page for that movie and we're like nudging each other
Oh, hey, man. Hey and like in like an hour or two, I guess I guess like this main character like dies
Oh, yeah, it's crazy
And we believe
Then there's the reverse the person who doesn't care about any gameplay and just watches the like cutscene YouTube compilation
Just to skip through the Lord. Oh, you can do that afterwards
You're saying it's super loud. So everyone's hearing you
Yeah, we're broadcasting it. We are broadcasting us sitting in
Okay, all right
We're broadcasting us sitting in the theater reading the Wikipedia page really loudly and we leave after an hour of the movie
The horse is too smart won't do it
You shoot
Compound over here. How did I miss that? It's impossible. I can't do this fov. It is too low
Why would you drive a gas truck here?
I guess oh shit. Oh shit. I'm done
3,000 IQ like
Suicide bomb play I guess they like island would be rid of us
Just sacrificing two people in a gas tank. That's not smoke the cigar
Anytime a character in a game smokes a cigar
Doesn't matter what game it is. You want one? No
What I was going to say is I did
It's over. I can't say it
you
Okay, you know a metal gear solid when you smoke the cigar and you hear the
I can't I'm not gonna try the bomb there
Who dropped the smoke made where's what is where's that? Yeah
Holy shit, but that was what that was a civilian
They're a combat now, I mean that was very very fine
Destroy the poison
It's a tank. There's a tank where I need help. He knows Hank. He knows. Where's our tank? Oh
That's a tank
Eat shit mother fucker. I get him. I don't think so
Now you now you're doing the same thing. I was doing. All right. Well, he's very clearly he's it right now
He's like, oh fuck. I can't do anything. You can't can you hijack these? I don't think so
I think this guy homemade with the tank. Yeah
If I stand up will he shoot me in the head?
Yep, well, they shoot me with I want to get shot with this thing though. No, don't blame
Like Burnham and do shit press V
Strategy was not to play
Fell on me he knew he's like, you know, I last I sit here long enough these two fucking dickheads
They're gonna just die. I heard on the radio what they've been doing
I'm completely safe here. How do you do wingsuit and you
shift
Doesn't do anything
That's how you go
We're like doing all this really important. We're like liberating all these places. We're doing all this stuff
We're like and you just hit your head on a wall from the wingsuit. Like why would we even use these?
What a fucking stupid idea
frying pan Joe
I can't deploy a wingsuit. Are you the only one that has it?
Maybe you can't there's no like shift button. I can't do it. I think you're the only one that has it
You might be able to pick it up at the camp
Well, I try to fly into somebody
If you can fly directly into somebody and just like Superman superhero tackle them I see you engineer
Where'd the people go? There's nobody here. Oh
Yeah, you gotta you gotta slide tackle you gotta tackle lieutenant Alfonso
I gotta walk all the way up the hills just to reset the joke. This feels like a YouTube video. Oh
We've been spotted I do with that information that you need to we've been spotted
That you freaked that guy out that guy is backing away he's terrified
He can't believe what you did. I need them to be like standing still
The 10th
Okay, this guy your dog is killing the guy we have to kill. He just completed the mission for us. Where are you?
It's good because I miss it's not there's no way
Perfectly still
This is a guy there's a guy said fuck
There's a friendly civilian in there fighting for us. What? Yeah, the guy with the blue dot
Well
He's dead now
What did you just throw?
All right, I need stuff like watching the video and play the actual game here. We did
I'll be with like one of these mounted guns
He actually is trying to run you over
Rosie
I'm distracting him. I
Mean smoke right now. I can't see anything. I
Need some backup
No, he's getting closer
Hey, hey luckily. He forgot he has a forward mounted like explosive their motors somewhere over here if they fight like they have to me
I think we're supposed to hang out. Hang on. Can we just like hot-swap the backpack to Rockets?
Can you hot like just swap it out? Oh
Yeah, I have to make him dizzy fucker. What are you talking about?
Get away from me done. How'd you do that? I just changed back to rocket pack
Okay, to be careful. My jetpack wasn't doing anything
Your dog needs help
Okay
He's fine. He's good. Okay
Whatever. Oh, yeah, don't shoot the horses. Don't shoot the horses. Why do they just keep walking down this hill?
I think the alarm raised
The horses bark. Okay, this is like they've got they've got horses mobility
Long-range guns. This is like in John Wick
When all of the enemies are the bad guys for some reason enter like gun food
Right so that he can disarm them and like throw them to the ground
And you forgot about the music that place
that like
We're gonna move
We have to destroy the poison containers that's a mission we're on right now
Forget oh my god such an opportunity such an opportunity
Dropping in oh you shooting it. I've sniped him like five times. What the fuck?
Like I can't be alive
Why do they always get the fun helicopters? What's my dog on fire? Oh
War crime Andy what what are you talking about? Hey, I'm dying helping
What me too? Oh
The helicopter did it it's cuz you were shooting the guy parachuting that's it. Oh, oh shit. Oh shit
Okay, right. You know what if they didn't want to get shot, then they should have teardrop somewhere else
before crime
Well, I they're poisoning people. I have no defense. I have no defense
Well, why are we here? I don't know they put us all the way back here
Were we just at one of the two objectives? Yeah, but we died
Let's say let's take a look at the map for a second because we I feel like we're just running around like morons
Clear the air. So now the pole now we have to poison his troops. No, wait
Now he's poisoning his troops is killing us take out the crow
Yeah, crop dusters yellow tankers fumigators as what we're doing if we take out the anti-air gun, then we can fly which is
Here right next to the oh, I got an idea which one you want to do first
My idea is driving away wait coming back
This is the poison trucks. What the fuck? Holy shit. Oh my god
Okay. Well, we got it. Is this what you wanted? Yeah, are you in the car? No, I'm coming. Alright, so what was your plan?
I don't it's like put c4 on this and it's like driving in the middle of thing and then go full speed and dive out and blow it
up
Do we have c4?
Not really, but I mean if we could just shoot it fast enough afterward
Be fine. Oh, couldn't we also just shoot the car and it would explode and do the same thing. That's what I just said
Yeah, yeah, but we're not when forget about the c4
Yeah, that's what I that's what I said. Oh, you just said that we have c4 and I just said yeah
We could just dive out and if we can shoot the car fast enough, then it'll explode
Oh, I thought you said oh what if we just shoot the car and skip the c4 like it was your own idea
No, I was I was corroborating your idea because I thought you said that we could get c4 and shoot the c4
German never listens to the plan. Yeah, that's why they call me the wild car
That's you crazy stuff like this
In my friend group, I'm the wild one
Are you dead? Oh fuck
Hey, thanks. Oh, that's a spill-in
Hey
Plane is here. Oh
We have to take out those prop disaster thingy
We have to take out the crop duster thingies up there
How are we supposed to actually get rid of that?
We need our own helicopter. This guy just has such an advantage. I give rockets or something
I don't have any rockets or anything. No
We just have to shoot the pilot. I mean you make that sound like that's a simple thing to do. I have this thing
Damnit going up top. I just popped an entire bottle of pills. Oh
What happened the crash into me did the plane crash into me
Did you get a good view of that? Oh, I hope so cuz I want to see that later
What the fuck?
I'm coming. Oh my god
But yeah, it would straight it. Okay. Hang on. Hang on. Stay up here
Find like a find me like a target. Okay, that's not directly below us not directly below us. Okay, that's gonna be tricky
All right, do you see this civilian over here?
where
There you know, let me see. Okay. I
Yes, I see that for what what are you doing?
Opportunity we're gonna sit here all day until you do this. I don't care how long it takes
I don't care how long it takes you this wingsuit. You get back up here this instant and and we do this
I
Get her
Know
Like my body's right next to her. How did that not hit? I guess it didn't hit
she's
Deceptively like you gotta like drop. All right. This is this is the one
Training will be complete. Oh
She's moving
You got it
Like 15 feet
And she's still alive still alive. Yeah, she killed me. She killed you
That's so stupid. Oh
It's still just there. I just did I died is her missiles. I just heard missiles fire
What are you firing over here? Oh, hi
Yeah, don't do that to my camera. I think you heard her leg. She's holding her waiting
I already hit her. I'm just watching because it looks like you heard her leg her leg is hurt
What are you doing? Somebody said everything is funnier when it's far away. You know what? That's actually true
I think you're missing you just I'm just a core challenge. You just did an achievement
Okay, that was just
Okay, um
What you want to deal with the the hazmat suit guy?
Just go for it. You just went to kick the guy and you just went to do a huge kick on that guy
It looks like you kicked him K 9,000 already won. Okay, that was fun. That was fun
Man, that was actually pretty fun
Okay, now say it enough times. It'll be true
Wait, here's the people feel POV of the plane. I need to see this. Come on. We have to watch this
We've to watch italics is POV for a sec
Hold on. This is really important
Okay, let's take a look this is your POV
Yes
All right. That was awesome. I'll see without you shooting it. It looked like he was gonna just drive into it
It was going to be pretty close. Yeah, it may have actually rammed into you possibly you just made sure it was gonna happen
Yeah, that was actually awesome. All right back to it. What were we doing?
New gun. Did you get that gun? Yeah, do you have to loot everything that I lose? I think you know, I got the gun
There's no that there's still point is it poison inside so there's still shit to do. Yeah the hell
Just I was just giving you a moment to regroup. Okay
Let's go
Poison we used to get rid of the poison containers and shit. Okay. I
Will this looks like poison container over here. This looks pretty poisonous doesn't it? Yeah, you can't just walking in the poison
What's the origin of it? It's a guy in the watchtower. He's climbing down to come to us
It was the last thing he's ever saw he ever saw I fucked it up a bad one-liner
Okay, so it's just everywhere over here
That's so goddamn loud
All right here poison barrels. Okay, destroy them. Yep. They are
Danger close
All right, that one's gone. I think we can I can I can Captain America these people you have like what you cool power moves
This is not the premium gun, this is just the one that I picked
Did you equip the guns you picked from like the the last thing we did? I yeah, I have the crossbow thing
Hang on my dog's in the front seat
He's in the front seat. Yeah, I
I'm not cool enough. This is motion sickness. That's bad. So what's it?
What are we supposed to blow up? We got 49% Yeah, because the two gold indicators are where we have to go
Wait, are you sure?
No, I don't think so. I think we got them all here. Okay, see it's like oh, it's just poisoning quest
That's like the next objective is 800 meters away. Yeah, I'm pretty sure that is spread out along all these
Indicators, he's bad at piloting every vehicle. I'm not driving this one
All right, I'll try driver he stepped out of the vehicle. All right, let's get it
Whoa, there's people
People Oh help. Thank you. Yeah, I thought there are people that's why you were in the good
All right, what we get something in here something in here interact. Ooh, we got metal
I thought it was gonna be like I thought they were carrying like another vehicle not
Crafting materials. That's bad. That's a bad guy. Oh shit
Okay new car new plan
Okay, I thought they were hauling like a motorcycle or something. Cool. All right, get us somewhere and get us somewhere quick
Get us there
No, not from my perspective not from my perspective. Oh wait, yeah, you're not okay. Let me help you. Okay, I can hear the like
It's time for you to play the same game
Get in the backseat and it is the game is
Quite the urge to shoot your friend while he's driving the car. Yeah, we didn't you didn't get
You weren't in the car
Okay, I thought you were behind me I thought there's a baseball I'm sorry
Hostiles
You're in yeah, all right good we heal first
This is like our get to do the armored truck you actually in the car
We got the Far Cry 5 trucks that have like the back doors that open for some reason
All right, you drive. I can't be held responsible
I tried driving last time it didn't work out so well for me
Can't shoot this guy. Oh, he's got a hazmat suit on shit
Oh
So I guess the guy in front of the car I was trying to just drive forward I
Ran over him and he exploded and like caught the engine block on fire. Oh
Okay, and exploded. All right. I'm tired of watching
My companion get destroyed. Oh
I'm calling a new friend. Okay, so
Hmm who you calling in
Hold on. I'm getting my I'm equipping my like cheat codes. Oh, this is good. You're gonna like this one
I'm not hitting him. Am I you got a new something good something new?
I threw a baseball and you guys are starting to fire again. He's gone. That's it
What are these guys doing? Oh shit, he's back
No
We like a kitty now
old chain
That's not the one you're gonna whoa. I want a cat. Well, then you should have gotten the premium Wow mount
Okay, anyway
What? All right get
Okay, it's too many people. All right. We just it's too smooth to make distractions. They're way too many distractions. Let's go
There's so many distractions. Okay
I think I know what I need to do. Oh god. This guy's behind us now. Wait, which way
We have to go to the gold any one of those two will do. All right, but I gotta try this first. Okay
Do you have like?
Um, I think I can get out there. No, it's it's like a different one. Oh
Hold on this front thing on the car supposed to do something that has potential
Okay
Wait, we're going back the way we just came from yeah, I'm just looking for a car
He's fine, whatever we'll put a pin on this. Oh my goodness
All right, we're fine. Ah
Ah
Look out. Oh, no
No bar
Yeah, turn this fucking game down man. Are you dry? I'm gonna turn the game down. It's just so loud
I'm gonna hear this game in my fucking dreams
um, I
Well, we made it. I guess we've made it
Did you do it cars? I?
Can get out you're gonna make me fucking puke. I gotta get out of here. Oh
Why am I wow, oh
That was embarrassing. That was really embarrassing. All right banded you you're on your own. I'm dead. Oh, you're dead
I have one HP. I unloaded a clip into this guy's chest and he just super kicks me and killed me
Are you gonna have to revive?
Wait, I was picking you up. I was in animation picking you up. How are you still down?
I guess he must have shot me the second that I came up
How come guapa doesn't have one of those things that those dogs have that the rescue dogs with like little things around the neck
I mean old like cartoons and stuff
You know, we're like that like the dogs the big with the collar. They had like water in it and stuff
Yeah, I mean a flask a cask. Yeah, it was booze
It was brandy. It wasn't water. What it was alcohol
It was booze to warm you up
What why was it not water?
Where you going by the way, but fucking gatorade in that thing. All right, go this way water would freeze. Oh
That's right. What so what are you? What are you even talking about?
Okay, like I remember like watching old TV shows and movies away
There's a huge like st. Bernard and had this thing around its neck and it was like with a big group of like adventurers
And like they would drink out of the like that like the canteen around like the dog's neck. It was in Beethoven
No, it wasn't in Beethoven. Oh
It was from Looney Tunes. I don't know. It was from some cartoon or some movie. Oh my god. I'm down again
I'm so bad at this game. I'm I'm on my way. It was booze to make you feel warmer
Yeah, well, you know what I'm saying. Pirates of the Caribbean. It was like it was like a flask. Oh shit
Sorry punch you it wasn't big. It was pretty small
Yeah, it was alcohol shit. You're right. Never mind
There's another helicopter. I feel like okay, we're doing this so wrong, man. I don't even know it was okay
We're running into second of all
Alone legend a cask of liquor around a dog called a warm-up travelers. No historical records exist of this talk of this practice
So did like the Looney Tunes just make this shit up. Why do I have that thing?
Why am I thinking that did you keep bringing me up? I keep dying instantly. It was milk
Am I hitting this guy? All right. Where are you? Just don't you just just forget about me
I I will die if I have to
There's a helicopter flying dangerously low to the ground by the way right above you
You look at sword and shield you look like such an idiot
I'm trying to level my paladin
Okay
Papa boy, that's not guapo still equally as important get up. I'm doing like the e3 trailer right now. Holy shit
Okay, I was you're right. Okay, I'm coming
What's aiming at me? Why is that aiming at me? What the fuck is that thing? Why isn't it?
There's nobody control what this robotic controllers what there's like two guys left then it was a turret there
Okay, we're not supposed to be doing it like that
We have to be tactical. I mean, but we have to blow them up. So they got it. How can you can't do this in stealth, right?
Well, okay, he sent us a photo
Okay, I'm just gonna snipe okay you snipe I'll go in it's nice to meet I snipe them in your hands
All right, you good. Oh
He got the alarm off through the alarm. Did they come instantly? They're already here
These guys I
I'm sorry dog attacked. Oh, there are there are attack dogs. I don't know where the enemies are
Shit come on. Let's go. I think we're okay. We're good. All right, we're good. We're good. We're just gonna kill them
Screw all the stuff
You're are you dead? No, I'm good. That person's body evaporated
Also, I need to blow up the barrels right next to you. Yeah, let me run another way
First back. I think that's it. That looks like it's it. No, there's one more. Wait a minute. What's in it?
Okay, we got this dog tank boy
Let's talk out. Let's talk out
My pet is down. I hear loud sounds. Oh
I think we cleared it though. Yeah, I think we're good. I think we can move on to the next one
Jesus
Yeah, we gotta get out of here
Come to me. Oh
Why would you ever pick the passenger seat is what I'm wondering
Why would you ever do that? Oh, you're right. Oh
No, oh
No, he's turning it to me
Oh
He missed
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No
Yeah
All right. Where's the last one? Yeah. Yes
That was 400 meters to your right. I can't drive through that. I try I thought I could I know but whatever right we're trespassing
Oh
Okay, the turret sinking in this game is better than the battlefield 2042 alpha. Mm-hmm
It's pretty clean
Okay, how about we just stay out and just from a distance, right? Why do we have to go in?
We don't have to go inside
We're just surrounding ourselves with people. I think that person's shooting a mortar. Ow
Alright, I'm going it. Why is it fire over here? They just called for backup
Jesus who is shooting me? It's god. Damn it. I could even I didn't see that guy if I bleed out and you're alive
I'll just spawn right next to you, right? Oh, wait. Are you hang on? Are you dead? Yeah, but I think I'll just spawn right next to you
You better believe fast
Smothered when he said we have you tried playing with you monitor turned on. Oh shit. Hold on. What the fuck? That's right
I was wondering why I was just sitting there was like a just a glare of like look at my face. Look like a mirror
Hey, hang on. Are you still on the contrast screen?
No, no, I just like I didn't have the monitor on I was wondering I was like this looks like me sitting here
Yeah, you have to turn the brightness up enough where you can just barely see the line. Mm-hmm
Cuz I heard like I heard the sounds and stuff, but I didn't know
Didn't know where they were coming from. All right, where are we at? How we still not done this because we just died
We're still on this mission, right? 94%
We just have to destroy more tobacco things
Really come on
99%
He's telling us to shoot the planes. But what he's not telling us is how what we need better weapons
We can't just shoot at the planes. We did that already
Didn't do anything. All right, just look for a yellow barrel. Shoot it harder
Arrows you craft the right bullets. You need armor piercing rounds for those planes. It's guys fishing
Okay, I killed that guy and we did it. It's complete. It's done. Did you do it?
Yeah, apparently
Someone you chat just said is this game co-op? Um, yes
We're just but we're both playing single-player at the same time
We just like talking to each other. This guy's trying to come. I'm just literally waiting in the car for you
I'm gonna try and make it for you. I didn't do anything and these guys are attacking me
Yeah, yeah, we just went to like the convenience store and I like didn't feel like getting out of the car
My phone. Oh my god. Sorry. I bumped you. Wait, what? I just like I punch like the mic. Sorry. I punched the bike
I think you meant you bumped the car
And that's why we exploded. All right. Well, we have a main mission over here
I want to go to like the workbench and look at stuff, right? I don't want to just shoot the same bullets
I do. Yeah
Yeah, maybe you should pay premium and you could have all the guns I have to play with I'm not gonna do that
We can't why did we just clear?
Why did you put us in a trespassing area?
It's both it spawned us in the trespass
You're a diablo 2 character
I
Alright, I what whatever I don't think you can get on this
You can
You are on it. Yeah, i'm here. The back of your head is right in front of my barrel
Psycho
We're going the wrong way that one lived you're a menace i'm just practicing
I love you said cover me. I'm reloading
All right. This is a bad guy right here. Not those this one
You didn't hit a single you're just gonna leave them
Yeah, I mean them
This is chaos
Okay, we didn't even aggro those guys. No, they're just driving by shooting at us
This is the part of the fucking comedy movie where I go hold on to your seats
And you close your eyes you cover both eyes with both hands and you go. Oh
No
You're gonna you're gonna have to go faster
Really build up the drama
That uh go differently in your head. Yeah, are you drowning?
But your head just went up all above the water. That's not fair
Hold on you get air
I'm gonna live that's not fair
That's unfair
the best laid jokes
Why am I i'm sinking further than I think I should be
This is this deep
Uh, how deep is this? This is deep fucking water. What's going on?
Let that be a lesson kids. Okay, don't try and cross real rivers just because it looks shallow
This river is like 700 feet deep
Probably died on the oregon trail and in the crusades
Where are you? I am 5 000 feet underneath this water. Okay that
Actually, you're right. Let that be a lesson
You are uh, you just gotta watch dogs. I think that's what happened. Oh deep is this actually
Okay, so you were under the map
Yeah, okay. This is literally like five six feet deep. Not even like four feet deep
That was really weird unless there's this one like giant sinkhole thing
I think I think what happened was I was still on the back of the buggy
And you spawned on me, but since I was like facing up behind me was like under
the soil
Oh, I see
Oh, this is nice
Don't you dare i'll be very mad at you if you shoot that thing
Okay, no not that up
No the goat I
Don't kill it. Don't kill it
I don't even see a goat it ran by us and it was cute and this thing just no it's not gonna leave us alone
Leave us alone
what
Where's guapo? Oh shit. Oh, no guapo
What are you doing? Oh my god
What the hell?
Oh
Oh my okay, this is like fucking brutal. I don't like this. I don't like this. I don't like this anymore
I don't like this anymore
They killed my cat
Holy shit
Oh, dude, we got some coyote meat. We could probably trade that for a new rocket launcher. That was a death roll. Yeah, that was brutal
There are people
out here
Yeah, that was a road
these
These guys are in like different what happened?
This lady
What happened?
I swear to god every time a lady comes over with an atv the screen explodes. I don't know what's happening here
It's better if you don't know we actually we need a vehicle. We need something
I don't who
Is it you I thought that was you
Who is he what are you eating drop it drop that drop it
Yeah, don't do that drop it. Thank you. Okay. I think we're okay now
No, no, no, no, no more atv people. No people on atvs. They cause they cause problems
And started honking
What is he sprinting after
Yeah, we get keep going we gotta keep we're gonna follow this this is this is like an uh
We gotta have the camera out for this. I just saw blood. I don't know who's it was
What is this lady's problem?
Yarring traffic, am I right?
Hey, I think it's another atv is for people going faster the speed limit
Okay, eventually
Is that blood or mud? I don't know
What are you looking at the horse?
Oh god
I don't know what to point my camera
There she is her car is smoking
I'm trying to protect her channel seven news
Making sure she's okay
All right
Did a plane just crash?
This is i'm feeling i'm holding down the cinematic button in gta
Why do you keep crashing into shit?
No, we're gonna lose her
I just got shot in the head
Why is it pulling me off the road?
Oh my god, we are the worst at trailing somebody
That's how every assassin's creed trailing mission ends they they got it down to his science
Okay
Going well
This is dash cam footage
Imagine bringing this to like court
the amount of insane shit going on
Judges just put his hands up and be like I don't even I don't know what the fuck is happening in your dash cam
It was 56 car accidents in 15 seconds
Who's at fault? Did you have the right away? I have no idea. You're all just going to jail
I guess I have absolutely no fucking idea what to do with this
No
Oh god, no
He doesn't know oh that hit us. That was a direct hit
I don't think that was him. Was it him?
Why is he still driving down the road?
I gotta get this on camera
Bye. Okay. Good. Yeah
Hey, why did it? Okay. So I I was just
Oh
Okay
Oh, i'm just thinking of like this judge looking at this video
Oh, by the way, I i'm not even sure those cats are legal to own
Whose cat is that?
An alligator and his so you get something to roll back. Oh
This guy's just vibing. Oh
Why did he i've stood in the road before and no one's ran into me like that
I'm just sitting there with the camera up and he stroked. He didn't even care
What are you doing?
Okay. Um
Uh-huh. I had a moment there. I'm sorry
Welcome back. I missed him. Thank you
What's the mission again? We're okay. We have to go this way. I don't think we have one
I think we can do whatever we want
We could just look at the map to go somewhere
um
We could just keep fighting in the middle of this
All right. I'm just gonna is that a good guy? I think that's a good. I think it's a good guy
Okay. Thanks for the help
Where are you?
Where are you on the roof?
Well, you're on the roof of this car. Okay. Yeah
Can you like open the back door or anything like what happens if you hit x x?
It's raining though. No, nothing turns them when the windshield wipers are on
You hit the rain button apparently so
We could do the good boy mission
Let's think. Oh, okay
Let's just get back there and see what we can even do
Uh, let's do
Oh the the good boy mission is collect crocodile. Oh, okay
So can you get that mark one marker for us?
Uh, I think it's like just follows the road
Okay
I'm playing paper boy. I don't know what i'm doing
Does paper boy usually drive a truck?
I don't know
Yeah
Nobody knows what paper boy is
Yes, they do. Come on. That's like that's what's saying. You don't know what pac-man is
I mean paper boy isn't a isn't a smash bros character. So should have been
Still going this way
I still think I don't think i'm holy fuck. I must flip that person. Uh, yeah, it's actually behind us now
Actually, you could just take this road again. Okay
to the left
Do you actually have it barked?
Okay. Yeah, okay you pass the road this this one works
Dave
We're actually isn't on the mini map. Oh, I see. Uh, it's the big gold star like 500 meters away
Did she just scream really loud? I i'm wondering if the cat
No
Oh, no, she's like, yeah, she's like saying yes, dude, just fast travel. I got the bird
We can uh, we can press f in the mini map or on the big map
Where'd the bird go?
Hey, uh hit up the map fast travel to the big blue. There we go. Much faster
Oh, do you have a solid state drive? Yeah, I do
Am I still loading?
Yeah
39 to you omegalo
uh
That doesn't compute data
But you know keep flexing. Yeah
What a sellout, but I bought no it's called I got scammed
I'm one of the people that built their computer like
Seven months ago eight months ago and graphics cards. You couldn't get them. It was so hard to get I have some bad news for you
but you still can't
Oh really? Oh shit, but I I ended up like I needed a graphics card
I've waited and waited and waited and waited and we tried over and over again to get something that wasn't a 30 90
And it was like all right. Well, I need to get a graphics card
I don't even care you paid 50 000 for 30 90. No, I did not this is taking a very long time
I will say though. Yeah, I think it's uh, i'm gonna say game probably crashed in the loading screen
30 90 but no 1080p stream metallics. I would let you take this one. Would you like to explain that? Um, sure
See you have to get approved by twitch to have more than six megabit per second up for 1080p to look good
Why does 1080p not look good at 6 000 up? Could you explain that for the audience, please?
because bitrate
sucks and uh
cox cox the internet but also
I got error coded. Oh, no
All right. Well, we have to wait. Hopefully this is script the whole game. Is that gonna mess the game up?
Oh shit, you host it though, right? So we should do your game
I am trying to load back in I will never fast travel ever again
That was the problem, you know, you know how every single video game always says never close your game during like a loading screen
And our game just crashed during a loading screen. That's a lot of bullshit
And i'm I press continue to like continue my game and i'm in another loading screen
I'm just gonna force quit the game. I'm in the process of force quitting. Oh, i'm right. Wait, you got in i'm not
Yeah, because you have to join me, but i'm still stuck in the loading screen. Oh, yeah, you've got to force quit then
I'm still hearing the game's audio and the game is force quit
I'm very upset right now. Why is this the game three people?
Yeah, there is no ubisoft game open right now and i'm still I still hear the music of the loading menu
Why does it is it just me or does it sound like i'm like witcher music you still have them?
This is weird. I've closed everything it says farcar6 is running right now. What? Okay. I need to like give me a sec
Force quit the application, but it's already closed
2021 triple a release. Oh megalo. You know what I mean?
Come back in triple a doesn't exist anymore. What's your favorite game of all time?
Uh nights of the old republic tied with uh teenage mutant ninja turtles turtles in time, of course, that's good
It's a good pick. All right
Uh, I should be ready to be invited momentarily here once this fucking actually open the game
What's your favorite game of all time besides?
mario rpg or team fortress
If I had to say that was a real softball. I mean it is it just is okay
I gauge how much
I like a game based on how much time I put into a game. So
I've put the most time
Into like team fortress into like world of warcraft
Although I would say world of warcraft should be on that list up until like wrath of the lich king
That's it. Wow doesn't exist in my brain really
Until after wrath of the lich king. All right. I'm ready for an invite if you can
Give one to me
um
Zero hold on. Uh, all right. Well
Menu next continue game new game add-ons store options
Quit to desktop quit to desktop. Okay, you ready?
Continue menu narration is disabled. All right. I'm ready. How do I exit? Oh, right. Did you send me one?
I did. Yeah, why do I not see it? Oh, I turned off notification. Wouldn't it be here? Uh, should be yeah core challenge completed
Did you join? Okay, try to re-invite me. Um, why am I not getting it?
Uh, I just did it again. What the hell?
What the hell can you um, just right click on
My name from like the friend list and then right click. There we are. I found it worst stream 2021
Get that bandit. Thanks for your input and thanks for your feedback. Thank you. Appreciate it
I take all feedback and I process it and I put it in and I process it. Thank you
Okay, can I make a can I make like a mean stream joke? No, okay. Can I do it? Anyway, why you want to be mean?
Don't be mean. It's all right. It's not really mean. It's like it's like appeals to the chat at the expense of you
Oh, yeah, sure. Go on. Let's hear it. Oh worst stream of 2021
Uh number 10 out of 10. Is that what you're saying? He said there's been 10 bad streams this year
No, there's been 10 streams this year. Oh
That's not true
That's not true. All right, let's do that. We're doing crocodile meat. These can't be trusted. Okay me
Yeah, you just fired at that guy. Why did you just just what did you shoot turkey? What is that?
He was a pelican by the way, he'll be soft. What is going on here? Really? What's wrong with you? My
Controls got reset. Okay. Well now I have to do this. I have to like disable this again
You feel like sending me messages. Hold on. Let me turn off notifications
Oh this fuck. Oh who fucking has that? It was me. Did you leak me? Did you leak me?
You got listen, oh you leaked me I got some bad news 120 gigabytes of my computer have leaked
onto the bit torrent
No, you don't no. No, I don't know. No, no more leaks
All right. I'm ready, but no when I try to invite you from the in-game menu it popped up
Oh, I don't care
Uh, I don't care. It's it's my epic games launcher account. I'm not i'm not concerned about it. Fuck you, bro
Listen, I think we can all just blame ubisoft
Can see their shitty overlay inside games well you can you can actually blame ubisoft for
Having ubisoft connect in the first place
All right
So we don't fast travel but we have to go all the way down here
I haven't mocked so like getting in the car and like turning the radio off
feels like
Getting an uber on quiet mode like they're like jamming out in the car. But then since you asked for like silence
They pick you up and they turn it off
That's an option yeah
although
Sometimes you will pick that option and they probably just don't even like
Okay. Um, just trying to did you get out? No, I mean i'm here. I'm just watching. Who's the blip on the map?
um
I mean you ran over a guy
Yeah, i've picked quiet ride before
He's like, all right, let's have a quiet ride
And you get picked up and the person just like hey arty. How are you? How you doing stranger? It's just like oh shit
So what are you up to in town?
I'm just like, oh wait, I guess you didn't look at the thing that I clicked
And I wonder if sometimes do you
It's alex do you think do you think that people look at that after they get picked up like if you get picked up
And you know that you were talking
Do you think you get really pissed off at yourself after seeing that afterwards?
Are you like, oh
Oh my god, that person wanted me to shut the fuck up and I talked for for 30 straight minutes
See, that's what I that's what I did when I got in here, but I just didn't want to say anything
I feel like that's a really really scary moment where you're just like, all right. See you later. Have a wonderful trip
It's been a great time having you in the car. You look over and you see like in the settings they picked quiet ride
That's what I that's what I said, I picked quiet ride, but anyway, thank thank you. Thank you. It's been fun
Um, i'll be sure to leave a five-star review
And i'm changing my tip right now. No
That's what you were doing
All right. So we have we have this quest, but what does he want us to go? Is that the meat one?
uh, this is a
main quest the meat one is
We have to find
Crocodiles also are we gonna are we gonna do the meme?
What's the meme?
This is the meme. What do you do?
Well, if uh, if the menu didn't come up this would have done it
So it was going to happen regardless because you're also on this screen. I don't understand
Uh, you have to you have to press you have to talk to this guy and press ready
Do we play can you like speak to this dude? I can't talk to this guy. Um, how come i'm ready and you're not
Oh, what the fuck this guy
You're gonna jump in the ring yourself go check out that box next to the arena
It's not even my name. That's somebody else's never did anything for you. That's a fake name
Somebody would have you need to find and pick at least one rooster. Oh, we don't have a we don't have one
Uh, there's one in a box like around I picked one up. I don't get it roosters. It's a rooster
Uh, there was one inside of like a crate
Do I have a two I think because you picked it up you uh, maybe maybe since I picked it up both of us got it
I guess some new faces
Muy bien, just as i'm ready. This sport is not for the faint of heart. What is this? Well, who am I inviting?
Are we in a game?
Yeah, I don't how do you start this? How do you start this here? Let me okay. There we go. Choose your fight. Wait, oh
What the fuck is this bet? Why is there a character select screen for this?
You know italics has the secret dlc box. I actually aren't any dlc cups. What the fuck
Wait, we're actually gonna do this
It's like street fighter
Uh, how do you I don't know how to do this
What?
How do you fight? I don't know
What's the let's see attack buttons?
e
I'm pressing like every button
I can't there's no like attack. Yeah, there is no
This is like every new fighting game. Wait, wait back up back up. I'm just gonna practice some combos over here in the quarter
mouse one
Yeah, yeah, don't fight me yet
jkl
Shit
Oh
This is kind of fucked up don't you think?
like before before after we um
murdered all the civilians
Yeah
You have to build meter
This is it. There was okay. First of all, there's like
25 characters in this
Okay, how do you block?
I don't think there is a block
There is meter. Yeah, there's meter left control
Did you do super what the fuck how do you just it was left control
Come on
They spent like way too much time on this
This is i'm like i'm like getting sweaty right now
And then flap right over your head
What dude we're like holding it like oh good a good job like petting the the the chicken
What?
the fuck
Oh, dude
What
All right. Well that that you can unlock uh, 25 different chickens that you can um, you can fight with them
You can yeah
now let's go back to playing the other game that I think is
Significantly more tasteful where my attack dog can rip the throat out of the people that I have trained it to
And then go back to running over civilians with tractors and shooting people mindlessly in the head
I think that's a little bit more tasteful guys
All right, let's go
Do we have to go to the road?
good point
So where's this? Where's this? Do you have it something map? I don't have this on my map
That I saw them down at the road
in
Here we go. Uh, well we have options. Oh, okay, we can do this
we can do
Whatever this purple quest is
Why don't you give us a give us something cool to do while I spawn a plane?
The biggest map is actually pretty large
Uh, we'd like just got to the main island. Yeah, but if it's anything like any of the other ubisoft games
Um, it's probably just a copy and paste of this five times
Assassin's creed valhalla was actually too big
It was unplayed. It was like no there's no way to finish
Yeah
As we go into the next generation of video games
I don't a settling point for a game is not how big a map is right? I feel like that people are still on that
Yeah, there's no reason to make a game like a like a adventure action game like 300 hours
Well, all you do is pop in and out of cover to shoot your enemies and listen to cutscenes. Sorry red dead
Just wait, you just talked shit about red dead
Yeah, it was a baiting switch. You thought I was talking about ubisoft game
Really? I was talking about red dead too you
Oh, I I just fucking threw up for a second. You just what'd you say?
But what'd you say about red dead being you don't like it? What'd you say that again?
I just said it was like too long. How could you possibly finish it?
Is I love that game it's alexis based no, I am i'm based i'm the base one stop saying that
No, you're cringe
It's true. Okay odds of you turning abruptly and ramming this directly into the mountain zero
I have to move
I freaked out
I could just feel it coming on. Yeah, I didn't do that on purpose
I think that was self-fulfilling prophecy level of destiny where like I created the scenario
I think so
Well, the thing just starts beeping in my ear and it's like
It's the person says a missile is gonna hit us. I'm gonna try to freak out
Okay, we can hang on. Let me pick a different mission
We can um
steal some spurs
we can
Steal a military truck. We need to do the
Don't meet a guy
Both of our chats are not going to be happy if we don't do the dachshund quest. We both have dachshunds
carrizo charrizo
charrizo the dachshund
All right helicopter you drive at this. I'm not I don't want you know, what's gonna happen if I do
Says there are lots of crocs
Try searching serpentino park. Where's serpentino park?
Uh serpentino park, okay, I see a spot is it in the same area we are in that's pretty close
It's like almost walking distance. Do you do you not have a wingsuit still?
No, unless it's like in my inventory and I have to equip it or something. Did you have to equip it?
Uh, no, I just built a like camp building come talk to this foreman and see maybe I'll just give it to me
Uh, maybe
The crocodiles are down there. Did you mark them? Yeah, only player one gets the wingsuit. Oh
Really really you have to play single player in order to unlock it because you're you're the co-op partner
Oh, so your character doesn't like so wait. Do I not exist? Is this one of those games?
Yeah, I think it's I think it's one of those uh, anything that happens only happens in my game
You know, it's really really really annoying about all that if that's true
They push the fact that this whole campaign can be played in co-op if you're gonna make that a huge part
Of your selling point for the game and again the whole campaign is playable in co-op grab a friend
But don't let him leave drop out
Don't let your fucking friend leave at least give me like the major like plot points or something
So I don't have to do the whole thing
Because like I could definitely do this
You get to have the fun. Bye. I think I got you at once didn't I you hit me once
Well, she could be as cool as me with all my premium guns my suit skin
Hold on while i'm waiting for you to come i'm gonna equip one of my new premium skins
All right. Let's see how much I care about this. Is it on?
Well, I just saw the curtain pull back from the game that just spawned in
I have cowboy boots
And a hat
It's not gonna shoot us, right?
Put your gun away put your gun away
Yeah, nice
They can't they can't see through your disguise you
budget-tier
Pyro cosplay, I guess they're unhappy
I think they've noticed that we
Look extremely suspicious
Oh my arm, how are you supposed to deal with tanks?
I think you're just supposed to avoid them
All right, get in the car
I have no heels
Who is that standing in the what who is somebody standing in the middle of the road? Who is this person?
Oh
I'm down
That escalates very quickly. You just had you got we can't avoid the tanks. We stood there for too long
Has jerma ever played a video game back in like the late 80s? I played mario 1 and 2 and stuff
I haven't played since anything since probably like mario 3
Uh, we played pong recently. All right, we're gonna stay on the road. We're not gonna stop for anything
We're not gonna shoot anybody. I'm just gonna drive on the road. We're gonna go where we're supposed to go
Are you in loading screen? Yes, I am. We're currently stuck in here again
Uh-oh, when are you gonna stream cubert? What are they gonna give bomb moms their own game?
Like how come toad gets one?
How come games made by like one person?
Like don't have you like get disconnected their loading screen
They spent a lot of money on this loading screen. This was a high tier commission
Like there are games right now that were made by like three people and they run like flawlessly
Uh, I just got booted
out of the game
He hates the game. No
I actually think it's fun. These games are all fun. They're all six out of tens, but they're fun to play
Maybe more fun if uh, we didn't have to reload in because the game crashes on a loading screen. Yeah
Yeah, i'm just gonna uh hard restart how long we've been streaming for I feel like it's been a while i'm flies when you're having fun
All right, i'm gonna force quit the game again
Hey, he hates the game. I don't hate the game. How long we've been streaming for i'm just
No, it's different. It's not what you think. Okay force quit again. It's still it's not even all my
Six out of ten. Is that the number of times that the game loads back in after you die?
I I okay. Thank god. I thought I was gonna have to restart my computer. All right strike three strike three and you're up
Ubisoft i'm telling you right now strike three and you're up coming back. Just don't die forehead
Which is yeah, we we just have to like not die and just run to where we need to go
And hey we did me and it's alex talked about playing this and we even said what did we say?
Let's wait like a week or so
So like the maybe they'll iron out the connection problem stuff, right?
You think there will be a patch in the first week? No, I don't know
It's been it was running fine for like four hours. That's what I don't understand
Maybe I should have done a full hard reset of my game too. It's only been three days
Has it really how that's been like five
Uh, can you just join off me or do I need to invite you? Uh, let me say I can join you
This is another one of those games that has like 12 splash screens before you get to the game
All right, can I join off of you? Let's find out
When the game is working
There's actually probably fewer bugs than far cry 5 had
Uh, i'm apparently i'm offline somehow. Let me see if I can just join you
but also I was basically playing with um with training weights because i've been playing the battlefield beta and uh come like
I have a total misconception of what constitutes like a buggy game after playing that because
All right, um, I I can go my friends list and I have I have three icons
One of them is a controller one of them is a chat bubble and one of them is the three dots
I don't know what any of them do i'm gonna try to press them
I think I can invite you but I can't join you. I think you're gonna have to invite me again
Resident sleeper. Yeah, I would be too. I I am right now actually that I am resident sleeper right now
Launcher on your desktop. It says you're offline for me. I don't know why you get that
I got that but I don't know why it says you're offline. All right, here we go
As i'm online i'm mine rack your knuckles. Let's go
Okay
Okay, cool. We're back. I'm in a plane. Are you in the plane?
I guess i'm just I don't think this is a good idea because how we gotta we gotta come we gotta like just
Abandon the plane before we both crash. No, no, no, he's gonna reset the game get in the plane
I'm gonna fly we're gonna jump out of our parachutes and get out
Good idea. I like that idea. Okay
The plane bit no, this is not gonna wait i'm not even driving you are just get us close enough
Once we're in the red area with the red zone. We're gonna jump out and just float
nice
Very nice. Very nice. How do you turn like the view angle?
I don't think so
How low do you think I could fly without?
Okay, and it's time for us to get out. I'm up
Did you get out?
No, let me know i'm still in the plane where you're going too far from your partner
Wait, why did you put me back in the plane? I don't want to be in the plane. I want to get out of the plane
Don't get out of the plane. No
Okay
No, don't pull me back in the plane. It's gonna pull me back in the plane
You're too far
I want one of us to survive so we don't have to have the how are you? Wait, you're alive. You're fine. Yeah, everything's chill
I'm not sure why you're in such a panic because we were in the red zone
Yeah, but there's an actual pilot
Right this time who doesn't just crash
Into the mountain at the first beep in his ear. I'm here some composure. This is what we have and uh, get respect safety
We have to go here
You got us to our destination. You did a good job
You all right
Yeah, i'm here
In fact, i'm here first
Oh, yeah
You're welcome. See imagine if we both bailed out the first time we'd be in the jungle lost
And uh, we'd have to walk like 500 meters
So I just saved the stream like, uh
12 minutes of of aimlessly wandering while we're trying to scramble for something entertaining to say
That's true to try to get a laugh in order to distract the resident sleepers in chat. That's true
Yeah, that's right. You got it. You know what you're talking about
All right. Here we go
to steal favorite spurs
Would be stealthed. I don't know why this quest is
Yeah, why are we I thought we're doing the dachshund quest
They're supposed to be crocodiles like in the area above
No, I think he's or alligators
Well, we can do both. What's the difference?
I actually don't know which ones are native to america
Lots of stuff to collect
Getting hurt that was a new rooster fighter
What's hurting us? I keep oh
Something's bumping into us or hurting us
No
My character's making sounds like I was getting hurt
Fine
Where's all the like throw the weapons from far cry five if roosters start coming out of the walls
They took out they took out throw weapons and they took out the car with the back doors that could open and trap helicopters in them
Why is windows telling me to switch my language?
I just changed my input language
what
Smith's something going on down here
Is this like a turkey over here? There's a there's like a big rooster turkey chicken over here
Oh, good luck king rooster
Do we have to fight it?
The animals are angry
I'm trying to get this a good cinematic angle
oh what was
That was uh, anticlimactic
oh
My cat just kind of unceremoniously wait
um
Escape the bunker. Yeah, there was a bunch of them
My familiar has taken this quest
Objectives you've got to pay to win cat. That's not fair
I think this is supposed to be
Intense. No, I think this is supposed to be a horror
hallway parody
Yeah, that was kind of funny. Let's go
Dps press v. No, not in here
It smells like shit get out get out get out get out man get out
Okay, I think um
Don't leave me in here
Dude, get him. Watch out
All right, we did it
nice work
Let's head back to very very dramatic music
Okay objective complete
Place
shit birds everywhere
This must be crocodiles here though a chicken put a bullet in me
That's 2 000 meters away. Oh my god
That's not
That's just the turning
So where's the the alligators are right here somewhere, right?
Like it. Yeah
I found chorizo's recipe. They should be well try and make it for him. No, they're down here
Uh, i'm not insignificant distance away that's very far that's further than oh my god, it's so far
I don't know how this I feel like i'm driving the car. Okay, uh
Your mark my worst ass
Oh, sorry
that better
Careful with your
I'm good. I think they're gonna spike strip us. I think so
Oh
It worked
emerging gameplay
Pick up the goddamn purse. What the hell? All right
I am guarding the alarm. I think we're okay now
The alarm should be broken now, right?
Uh, I think so
Is it like one more guy?
I think that's it
I think if we kill all the guys we control the checkpoint
Oh something in here
We got
Gun powder. I think gunpowder lets you make guns
Oh, all right. It's probably just like crafting the tank again
I'm just hiding
He's hiding here
Let's just do the left for dead strategy where everyone goes in the bathroom
And everyone aims out the door with auto shotguns
I don't think he knows
Is he leaving he's investigating sort of and also crashing
Maybe becoming stuck
Looks like he's stuck. I think we can go
Yeah, he's stuck. All right, let's get out of here
I mean I can steal the horse, but let's get the car. I missed whatever
Take this one. Oh
Don't just keep driving
I don't just keep driving
You're just rolling up
This thing doesn't do shit
All right movie, uh, you you can jump on the roof of mine. I gotta get the shot. Come on
All right. I agree a movie scene has to play out here
A movie scene you're expecting a lot
Hey, let's go to do a movie scene in front of the camera. Hey, uh
Do something funny
Oh, that's a great shot great angle actually perfect shot right here. Okay. I got an idea nice and tight right there
That actually scared the shit out of me that startled me. I thought he crashed into like a wall
Cut yeah, good shot. Good scene
On to the crocodile meat
You drive. Okay. Thank you italics. Now we don't have to do that for an hour
X is gun. Oh cool
Uh, you kind of put this in a ditch here
I mean I dove out of the car. It just went where it was going to go
I think we may need a new one. No, we're okay
The scooper on front is supposed to flip cars, but it doesn't seem to work
I don't this happened. You just came to a complete stop. Why?
Instantly the engine just fell out of the car
I think i'm hitting you
I think i'm running into you my power as host is simply too great. It might be your shield
Wait, I didn't want to hit all those chickens
That's actually a good idea. What if I what if you run to me at full speed while I have a shield equipped?
You block it
I don't know. That's what I wanted to find out your uh legs are doing lots of interesting things
You want to try it?
Now you get all the hold your shield up and put it right in front of the car
It works
Are you serious? Are you kidding me?
No, it does not hang on. I wonder if it works with the tank
This i'm fine
That shouldn't work
You dodged the horse good job. I did I don't want to hit the horse
This marvel movie is whack
parried a truck
Uh, we gotta try like a
airplane
I I know but it blocks explosions
Oh if I flew into you with an airplane, would you block it? That's a good idea
It's a really good idea
Let's try that in a little bit
What happens if I hit v while you're driving?
It'll probably blow the car up and we'll have to get to a loading screen and be mad at the area
I can
You got hit by a barrel
All right, uh go fast or
Yeah, we gotta go this way
All right, go fast
Yeah, i'm just gonna hit v
going fast
You're still on the car. It works
Uh newton's law of physics says that a perpetual motion something will be in motion until it is out of motion
When I was a young boy and what I played with trains, I sure did love them
My sister was a very interesting person. That's the first 15 seconds of young sheldon. Thank you very much
It was literally the first like 30 seconds of young sheldon episode 1 pilot
Yeah, but it sounded like the right man in the wrong place can make all the different
stuff
They're just dropping like paratroopers down here. Are they firing at us?
I'm very confused who they're shooting at. Yeah, they're shooting at us. Why what happened?
We're just here. We exist
They don't need a reason
Well, what the heck?
I have a shield. Why don't you get one?
Come on. Heal. Heal. Heal. Heal. Heal. Heal. Heal
heal
Got him get the helicopter get the helicopter might be able to fly that out
Give me this fucking thing right now. Come on. Does it let you jump in? No
What if we get a what if we get a boat and push it?
Why is it so hard to get a helicopter in this game?
I mean the way we have access to them is just yeah, they're in weird places shitty one. This is the big one
So we're looking for um
crocodiles here
This one
Do we are we supposed to kill them?
What's this look like to you?
Um, I was I don't know. I was videoing it. I was hoping he was gonna kill you
I was hoping he was gonna kill you and I was gonna have like a picture of you getting eaten by a crocodile
But that didn't happen. I got you. Who's this? Oh, dude, there's rats. They're rats
No, it's not. This is a gopher. Oh shit. Can you can they be friends?
What is this? How do we uh, can we like press e or anything?
Like a beaver. I don't think that's like a beaver
All right. So now we're gonna bring the treat back to auto
Or midas either one
Hang on both. Hang on. I just got the option to feed
Really?
Yeah, but I can't see it again because they're like scared
Holy shit
Damn it
Maybe we need to sneak up
I don't know. It definitely said feed
There's more up ahead. See if you can get the ones, uh, that haven't been like spooked yet. Yeah
All right. Let's let's let's creep up. Okay. That's a jack rabbits. Why are we like we're like hurting them?
No, I don't think so. We're trying to feed them. No like h e hard like uh, oh I see like protecting them
I really hope this doesn't lead to a street
Pretty game. They're just so squeaky. Oh, here we go. Here's uh, oh, it's a that's a rabbit. Damn it
Okay. Well, we tried. Oh wait right here right here. Can you feed it? I did it
And they're just so hungry. Oh my god. Do it again, please. You have to you have to like um,
Crouch up to them. What are we feeding them? Uh
pellets
Uh-oh, we have a there's a predator over there. Oh, there is a wolf just walking around
Can you feed the wolf if you just like walk up? Can you be hand out? Don't try to feed wolves
Help help. I don't know what to do
Run to the water into the water run to the water. He's got my arm. Let's get in the water
Shooting a gun into the water. He won't go in the water
Okay
Yeah, I guess you're right
Okay, uh new toy we have a new toy there is a new toy
Also, they're fighting the wolf and it's not going well when he's fighting the wolf they threw three molotovs
Ah, yes, there is a new toy old toy
uh
Where are we gonna go?
That's a great question, but we're gonna go somewhere. We'll go somewhere
Yeah, fuck that dock. Who cares? How do I get out of here? He's all dead ends. I think they're all dead ends
Give me a marker
You're just vlogging
All right. Yeah, all right. I'll give you a marker. Um, we have to go this way
Hold on
honeymoon video
And i'll be honest with you
Put the phone down right like okay. Oh brothers. We're having so much fun. I'm gonna record this
No, don't just like enjoy the vacation right here
Where's the marker? There are designated things to take pictures of don't bring your phone into the water. What is that? Oh, it's an alligator
Uh, we should just be able to go backwards
Oh shit
What's wrong? The alligators. Oh, whoa
I kind of like want to see what it'll do. Honey. They're getting so close
Wow
The wildlife are here is really interesting. I love being in nature
I want to be out. I want to be outside all the time
I want to be camping. I want to be hiking
I want to just sunbathe. I want to go swimming
My camera's like broken. Oh, what's this over here? What this is?
Uh, I don't know
Let's go to like a safe
distance right here
I don't think they even care. They're stuck. Do you want to go help them?
Can you get on their boat and will they even care I well depends on if they notice me, I guess
Try to stealth up there. I think you can stealth up there and take the guy out with
See if you can wait see if you can go on the boat and like just sit on with them
What if I can do one of the like swimming machete animations where you like there's got to be one to pull a guy off the boat
Right. I would hope so
He's aiming the gun around the boat at you he doesn't want to get off
I see that
You're having your camera
Yeah, come over to this side around this thing. See if you can get him to like point around his left shoulder
Like they're just grooving
I feel like i'm taking a picture of you like filming a movie or doing like a photo shoot
Okay, they see me when I get like
There if I go if I go up there they can see too. So I can't will he fire the gun?
It's actually a good question
If you were to stand up like around the left side of the boat. All right about to get detected. Let's find out
I can't jump
Too i'm too puny. He can definitely fire if he wanted to right now go stand right next to him
I can't even like get up here. All right. Give me one sec to reset my uh
Stealth meter. Okay, i'm filming you i'm filming you
Okay, you're up there. Nice
very cool
That didn't do anything
Nothing killed me. What the fuck?
Uh-oh. Uh-oh. What happened? I did like a backflip off the I hope this loads please load. Come on. We're not done yet
Yes
You're going you're going on facebook. Can we like eat these?
I don't think so. All right, let's go feed the uh, feed the dog. Let's actually finish that
Like you said I said then yep. I'm gonna call in a car
That would probably be useful when do I get to like call in other cars?
You probably have to set it find in a warehouse at the fnd storage facility complete any grand
Premio race or go to a chop shop. Okay. Oh my gosh. Look at this. Oh, I thought he's biting this whatever it was
Hey, thanks. All right, you want to drive?
Uh, do you okay? Yeah, you can drive. I've been driving a lot. Why is he pissed?
Is he yeah, he didn't he just brought the car to us and he was mad because he has to walk
This is unfair. Why can't oh, why can't that guy just not be in the car with us and you drop him off?
I don't know what happened. Yeah, there's no like other no familiar people in this game like we you can like
Get followers. It seems really unfair
What?
Why would you run her or she could have gotten in the car? I thought she was bad
She's not bad. Is this guy bad?
Yeah, he's bad
All right, pick up pick her up and let her get in the car
All right, let's go
this way
In the cop
Point your phone out the window like a hipster vlog
She's not getting in the car
Can I lean out?
Okay, let's just go take you out
Good. Excellent
Can you do a selfie? I don't think so
put away zoom toggle ui
No, you can't
What happened there?
Why is there a skull flying around in the sky?
There's a skull in the sky. I think that means there's like a
It's not a new sea of thieves event. I don't know. I never played it
Probably where jack black is
I said, I wouldn't be surprised if this is just the last game flipped upside down
Well, they just like flip horizontally every asset
They broke my tires
Where's the other guy I don't see anybody where are they anybody marked?
No, I don't we're not are we marking people
They got planes do if we we just gotta leave because they got the alarm run run run out. There's gonna be more people
It's only gonna get exacerbated. I'm good. It is explosives back here. Just be aware of that be careful. I have almost zero health
I'm dead
I can't get out of the fucking back seat of this car
I'm just running. I'm sorry. You'll spawn on me. All right, i'm out. Oh, there's a spectator bug
All right, I got away
I wonder if when you do you you probably just spawn right on me
And we're
Back. Yeah, that's a much better idea
What the fuck is this thing?
ferret
Why is it mad?
What did I do?
Because humans have corrupted their natural environments
There's a mongoose
What are you shooting at?
What's even down there? I'm just gonna get a car
Found one hold on this guy have a quest
Holy shit
No, don't shoot me
All right, I get it. I'm in. All right, let's head. We're just trying to feed the goddamn dachshund. Okay
Helicopter you turn it around of course a tank
He's aiming
He ain't gonna hit him. He's not he's aiming
I'd be surprised he literally just disappeared off the map. We're good
They tend to do that
Are you yet? No, I
Oh
I just I did the waypoints wrong
I was trying to cut through here because the waypoint is taking us somewhere else
Look at the this is the wrong way. We need to put the waypoint waypoint
Okay, i'll give you some waypoints because i'm driving towards this waypoint here. You see my waypoint
Yeah, it's it
So now we have to go this way
All right, the moment that everyone's been waiting for
It's finally among us
Why why?
I can't say two words that are very common together
without it being
A video game everybody likes. I don't think it contextually even made sense
You know, you're probably right
What am I doing?
Excuse me
Why did this happen?
Okay. Well, let's go feed the dog
I am so ready for this
feeding the dog
Crocodile steak
Are you okay? Are you gonna be able to see it? I think so
As long as i'm close probably, right?
So hard for my god
Should be enough to make us amigos, right? We did it. He's so hungry
He's no you have to eat the rest of the food
I he doesn't want to buy you the good stuff. You have to eat the rest of it
but
Not hungry. It's okay
Wait
um
Chorizo has something to show you. Where is it? What is it? I should follow him to find out really
What are you doing? You want me to okay? Oh, let's go
What you got there now for me? Oh shit
diamonds
Keep following him. Yeah, he navigates this uh ramp pretty well
Dogs been stealing shit through the whole community and like burying it in corners
Even more well that wasn't really hidden
It was just on the counter serious key
Okay, but like what if he was one of the attack companions?
He's so funny
He just moves this slowly around is messing around he's walking around
He is
Now he's not
He probably helped you steal this shit
I think this is the beginning of a beautiful friendship. He's got a name tag
Really?
Yeah, so you can equip his name tag
That way you remember him anywhere you go
Just put like a cute dachshund in your game and everyone won't care about
Just connecting with their friend like two times in a row
Very nice. Oh shit
It's real really hold on. How do you do it? Hang on. Where is he? This is pet. I can't do it
It's his pet chorizo
Where is he?
I don't see him yet
Pepe laugh co-op. Are you kidding me?
Oh, it's on cooldown. I can't even get the dog
I'm just like trapped. I'm trapped like in a mirror or something. Like I know here's what it is. Um
You're holding the controller that's not plugged
And pretending like you're playing while i'm playing
What the fuck?
All right, let's keep going. How are you doing? You're you doing good. You're right. I'm good
I just I just got our our little friend who actually exists
Here he is. Oh my goodness. I can't believe it
I can't believe you can actually you but but
what if he gets like
Attacked he's gonna get like a you're gonna throw a grenade and it's gonna be bad. Just go to sleep in the puddle
He's sleeping inside of the mud puddle. We have to protect
This dog at all costs
All right, bring the spurs back. All right, where's the crafting bench? Let's make some new toys. We'll complete this first
because we we've had this
Pretty much completed for like an hour
I just can't stand the idea
Now you did us a favor and I trust you but if you say anything to anyone
I'll fuck you up a challenger approaches
What's my reward
Give my quest reward
You think I did that the goodest of my heart?
We got it right there. Look gonna be rank four
Okay, new weapons and gear at arms daily, let's go look at some new weapons
Uh, we should be able to craft some shit
Well, you should be able to craft some shit in your cool game that you have
No, you can't anybody can craft stuff. We just gotta find the crafting table. No, I can't I know I can't I can't I can't
I can't I don't even want to look mentally. No, I can't I don't even want to look it's stupid. I can't do it
I actually don't think I can
I can go I can can I talk to this guy?
Listen i'll just I could throw one of my weapons on the ground and you can pick it up
Uh, it's all right, man. I just uh, that's fine. It's cool
As I can't do it. I genuinely don't even know where the crafting bench is
Yeah, just make a bunch of like shit. Whatever. It's fine. I don't care. Yeah, you know what? Um
um
It is it is more fun with my 15 game
All right, that means fucking it's like low low price of 15 dollars, you know, it's pretty good deal
Sorry, just make something fucking whatever
Yeah
Oh fucking probably uh
I'm building my i'm building my base. Yeah. Hang on. I gotta wait for your approval though. You said no
You need uh, you need my approval. Okay, let me um, let me deliberate on this
Oh, this is I thought this was gonna sell weapons. They sell clothes clothes
I'll give you one sec
Got a raid from uh chibli. Thanks for the raid chibli
What's going on everybody? Thanks for joining
Playing far cry six my buddy italics. How are you guys doing?
I have italics muted in deafens and he probably doesn't know what's going on. But thanks for the raid. Welcome everybody. So um,
Where do you want to go from here? What would you like to do?
uh
I'll let you choose because I feel like um, you know, my my game's kind of better than yours
I've got the the dachshund dog pet. Um, I got a premium weapons. I've got the
Awesome clothes. Yeah, I mean it's it's a better game mary guy. It's a cooler game
But I think like we can do what you kind of feel like because you're the one that has to be the quarterback here
Yeah, you do have a point. I mean anything we do really doesn't impact your save at all
Um, even though you own the game and uh, I technically i'm renting it. So
No, let's go do uh, let's go. I want to fly a plane. I want to be in a plane
Somebody just somebody just throw a glass at the dog
Who the fuck just did that who did that? All right, let's go fly a plane spawn a plane and I want to fly it
Okay
just
What's this controller icon?
I don't wait. What is it? Yeah indirect. Oh
It's uh their dlc aren't these just characters from the other games?
Yeah, I think that for some reason is somehow the also you okay if you don't move
I literally can't finish the game like if you went afk right here. Yeah, I am 100% boxed in
Really
There's no jumping in this mug you just stuck you just you just put me in a minecraft like dirt
Dark hut while I was uh using the bathroom. Oh, all right. Let's get in the plane
What time is right now? When do we start too? I got like another 40 minutes in me. Let's get let's get some new vehicles and weapons
We gotta get new toys. I'm I like I can't there's a crafting bench in there somewhere
I don't know where it is
There's a helicopter now or there was then but there is now too and we have two can we have two different vehicles
Okay, so uh you you want the plane?
Why don't we know I want the helicopter? Okay, well pick pick one. Oh, no. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Let's try the shield thing. That's a good idea. How are we gonna do this?
Where are you gonna be? I'm just gonna go to the end of the runway
I have to like pitch this down then all right. The plane is currently moving so I can't really stop it
All right, just accelerate. All right. Here we go
Not bad time didn't save me that time. I'm all right
Spawn in here. Yeah
Like round you up. All right, where to can't you like a grapple onto stuff?
That's the grapple still in the game. That's just cause
No, no, no, that's far cry five was we were doing like a grapple onto the helicopter. Remember we were trying to like um
Do the physics bounce?
Oh, I don't know. Maybe if the helicopter blades probably have to unlock it
So i'm going to a waypoint right now. What's this waypoint for?
I don't I don't know what to do. I'm panicking. I actually don't I like forgot how to drive the fucking plane. I don't know what to do
Why can't I not move my mouth? I can't move my mouth
Just get out just get out just get out
You're good
Yes
Did you shoot at me? How are you so much higher than me? All right, try and shoot this
I can't look down
There you are. I'm gonna try to i'm gonna try and make a cool landing in front of you. Okay?
Okay, just stay still we get this on camera, right? Like pull out your camera. All right, here we come
That's it. It doesn't look like you're going towards me. I am I never vibe me. That was fun
I was gonna try to land on your camera lens, but that would have been really really probably impossible to do
I I didn't even have the camera out
And what happened there?
He just walked right into my trap
I set that up like I was waiting for you to like land there so I could blow you up when you when you landed
But since you didn't land there
I had to leave the trap out so that then you just ran right over it. I couldn't pass up the opportunity
Yeah
I had to salvage it. It's okay. I made sure chorizo was oh my the explosion. I got blood
Oh, no, that's disgusting. I've got the blood all over my hands. That's gross. He's healing the wounds
All right. What do you want to do for the last like 30 40 minutes to an hour or something? Uh,
Let's take a look. We're gonna we're gonna give ourselves an objective. I don't think we even have one
How do okay?
We need to figure out how to build the gorilla garrison because like everything fun is locked behind the gorilla garrison
There's we got there's rocket launchers
There's bows
There's like seven shotguns four sniper rifles like every single thing is tied to that
Okay, but do we have any indicator where to go for that?
Uh, I think it's supposed to be in the camp, but I probably already like I don't know what's down here
You can find them in military out installations, too
Because there's this cortina weather station military target vehicle pickup points
There is this one over here, which is the tobacco factory military target there's a town over here
You can't turn the stream off until you get on an airplane and try to just fly to the bad guy's hq to kill him
Um, we'll try that alex you up for a challenge to like just fly
Across to the to rank eight and try to kill the guy with like a sniper headshot in the head fly to rank eight
Yeah, just fly across. Okay. Sure. Where's the guy? All right, so hit go to your map. Uh-huh
Uh, oh like the top. Yeah, just go fly to his like compound. Um
El presidente we'll just get in a plane. You're gonna drive because you're much better than I am. Okay fly across this
This is gonna be like day z level travel time. I mean we could try it
Maybe we can maybe if we fly like out of bounds or something we can fly around and land
Okay, try it. I didn't mean to click that. All right. Well, how do we get how do we get a plane?
Yeah, that's restricted airspace
But can we like avoid the restricted airspace by flying like around the ocean or something?
I think we probably need to fast travel. What about like a um, what about like a jet ski? That might work
Yeah, maybe a jet ski might do it if we go to the dock here
You actually might be onto something seriously if we go around the entire map here
Okay, let's go west to that marker. I'll call in just like a regular car
And then the marker there's like a dock there could be a boat
Okay, this is kind of stupid turn around run down this hill and slide like down down the slope and just hold
Well, that's fun
You can almost do the entire go. Okay. Let's go
You guys are gonna stop the whole war
I mean, we're gonna see what happens. It's worth a shot a few good minutes
Why does it always end up like this?
It always ends up like this
okay, and
I'm kind of just hoping that there is a boat of some kind right? Yeah spike strips
This car is not doing very well
But nice job dodges. I just dodged the spike strips
Smoking a little bit though for some did we get shot?
I think we may have
Is there a third person view? I don't think so only in the camp
That guy spawned and you killed him
Okay, it just occurred to me that little chorizo I spoke turn little chorizo is like following us
Yeah, just running on the road
If you can like do a wheelie on the slopes
Very nice
That's a cowl
I thought that was a routine bison
Those windshield wipers are sure helping us right now
Keeping the smoke down
Just to flip
I was okay. I didn't realize there was a ditch. I was just trying to cut across the grass
All right, we're almost at water. We're almost there. Oh
We just to make it to the water
And oh jesus
Uh-oh
Uh, hey come come look at me. All right
All right. Here's your this is your opportunity go go to the rank eight area and die
Your body is gone, but your arms are still there
And you if you swim this way
You're gonna drown
No, I my head's above water right now. Is it?
Yeah
I could I could be here as long as actually there may not be a way out except drowning
I'm gonna help you under water though. But if I go under water
It's a boat over here
Hang on. I might be able to there's a boat right here. Hold on
What happened? I'm swimming back up. Are you dying?
I got a boat. I'm
Uh-oh now i'm gonna drown
All right, it's fine. You uh, we're gonna repair this shit
I'm just under the world
Grasping for air like a horror movie like I can see reality fourth dimensional
Through the bookcases and I can see you in the boat having fun and i'm like struggling to get to you
Alex this boat has a machine gun
Really? We need to be very aware of that
Whoa, I think we're gonna be able to get out. I think I think this is the one. It's actually a good boat
It's really good boat
And we got to go
I'm right i'm here
Okay, we're gonna
I hate you
So you're gonna go right we're gonna hit an invisible wall
Follow the coastline
We're gonna hit an invisible wall. I think
Am I going straight here self-defense you go right outside the this little opening
Somebody just had a sailboat out here. I don't think that's a sailboat. I think they're like coming to get us
Are they?
The guy on the left is the guy on the left is
Hey, you gotta you got a gun
I do
You gotta go you gotta drive. I'm going
There's too much smoke. Oh shit. There's a lot of machine gun boats out here
There are yeah, this is their way to make it so you don't come over here
So how far do we need to go?
Oh, I mean you just keep going
There's almost no end in sight. I can't look at my map. All right
Oh, Jesus. Okay
I'll set a marker for
I actually can't set markers. I don't think you can no no
It's like this is an illegal zone
We're we're beyond the veil at this point as long as we can just trace the outside. I think we'd be fine
I hope they've run into a destroyer and get vaporized. Hey
We're doing the uh, what's that rpg where you can win the game?
like in the in the opening segments like
Gothic or something. Yeah, something like that
Whether you just like sprint as fast you can to this one town and like kill the guy
All right, if we can actually kill the
Boss
I don't think he'll even be on the map
Do even like because we know what region he's in but do we know like we know what his house is. Yeah
It's probably gonna be a big building it's probably gonna be very clear
What do you think the odds are that they um?
Have something that's even better than tanks and choppers probably pretty high right?
You're about to drive a into an island and b into the bad guys into an island. I got plenty of room
I got plenty of room. I'm fine
Just confirm with me that i'm going the right way. I mean they'll look the ai beached their boat
I'm just saying anything's possible. Okay
What?
What what?
What are you talking about? No get out and push what?
Just push it. We'll be fine. We can push a little bit more. I think that's okay
I think we're good
How did you board this from the edges?
Where are we? We are actually way closer than I thought we were gonna be we're almost there
We're like halfway there. Yeah
Are you gonna are you gonna take the right and go through a little inlet like the little um?
Oh god, no, we're going that way. Yeah, go around go around tall side. Can you move?
Yeah, okay, because you're
An asshole kill him kill him kill him kill this guy
I
Beeped at him and he fucking whatever
He'll just got to kill that guy
Nice good good work
Okay, but like boating accidents actually happen like that
Wow like this you have so much space you go anywhere
And you're the only other
Like oil tanker spills
All right, we're almost there
Look, we have to we have to be really tactical. We have to be really stealthy too
No bullshit. No like flying laugh out loud helicopters into the walls or whatever
No, we're gonna get there and we're gonna sneak to this guy's compound and
One of us is gonna snipe rival in the head
All right. I'm gonna I see like a haze on the horizon
You should probably like veer right a little bit so we don't hit some like water wall
Do they know dude that guy's got a better gun. That's a better boat
Far away or is it the same one? Is this same boat or almost sir? I was gonna go. It's just right away
All right, just keep going
All right. So you guide me a little bit here because I don't know exactly where i'm going. Okay, you're gonna go. Um
just kind of
turn
To the right side of that island and just kind of follow like this way. Yeah, just follow that
It's gonna be an lol laughing about a moment
I know
So, okay rank is just
How hard it is relative to your equipment? I believe so
They they kind of like turned to far cry into an rpg
Weirdly, we're not supposed to be in this zone
Yeah, like you have to have okay you have to have the right like
Level up guns like health bars and all that shit
All right. So this looks like
this zone on the right here, I think is
Zone
You think it's just that tall building that like kind of cathedral looking building right there
It actually probably is. Yeah, I assume right
One of them is a is like a huge hotel
Okay, so you watch like the first big few
push
It's it's the only
Piece of land here. Of course it is
There are sharks everywhere. So just be
Oh my god, we'll go push it. Push it a lot push it. Push it. Push it. Push it. This is bad
Is this drivable yet? Oh not yet
Can you drive it? Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god. I can't get him
I can't get in
Take their boat take their boat take their I mean i've already shot the hell it's sinking. No, it's not like me
You can repair it
There's those sharks are are everywhere. This I mean, I think this one will drive
You can repair this one
This is a sure thing. This is absolutely a sure thing. Do I hear a dog a dog?
Uh, they're like raw
Why is a baby dog in the waters paddle doing the doggy paddle? He's just in the water. Yeah, he's just in the water
Ammo
Get this thing out of here. All right, come to my boat. It's in a good spot. I will protect you
I'll make sure I shoot the sharks that come near you
Okay, i'm on your boat. Very good. All right
Be careful. We don't want to hit the same piece of land
Very nice. All right. Good. What was that?
Uh, apparently there is a vehicle weapon
so much smoke
Left are we smoking? Hold on. I have to repair this
Uh boat dealt with I can't get back on the gunner's seat
The sharks are gonna eat me the sharks are gonna eat me go back
Don't kill me don't kill me
Okay, holy shit
Wait, wait, wait slow down slow down. I need to I need to sit down
You good? Okay. I'm good
I just road killed a shark
And we got the meat for it. He's definitely in that big tower over there
Okay, so
Uh, once we get in here
Because they're like the highest level enemies in the entire game
If they don't one shot us, we're just gonna no fighting like only run
Yeah, just just try to get where just try to get what we're trying to get to
That guy's the guy was on our team. How was I supposed to know that? I'm just look every everything's a threat right now
We're trying to get to the guy the last guy in the game
Kind of yeah, no, it's just a seawall. Uh
boat explosion
Watch out for the buoy watch out for the buoy
That wasn't mine
What do you mean abandoned ship?
Oh, fuck. No, we're okay. Hold on. How do you uh, those are those are mines?
No
What happened you ran into a mine?
Yeah, but like uh, we were stationary. I didn't expect it to explode twice. Where's this gonna put us? Oh, no
Shit, I I should have I should have jumped. I was trying to get the other boat the people off the other boat
Okay, what if we get on a plane and we take that same route around that'll be faster, right?
We need like okay, uh, we need to get a plane that has a gun. I think the game crashed
Um, I think we're just so far away from anywhere that it wants to spawn us that it's loading in the game again for the first
Time but also it it may also bug. Yeah, but
Oh
I don't what what exploded the second time?
I don't think it was a mine. I think they like fired an explosive round. I think the boat was on fire
From the boat my piloting has a grenade launcher
So if they had one of those like aimed at us, they could just shoot a grenade launcher. Oh, we were so close
We were so close
And also it may have crashed. I think we're I think we're dead in the water here
Yeah
Yeah, i'll give it till it completes the circle, but that's it
And we're out
Oh
It got disconnected
Is far cry six good? No
Is far cry six worth playing? Yes. Hope that answers your question
15 for the premium edition on you play
Far cry six playing it like we are right now
Is a absolute blast
Does a six out of ten rating still stand? Yeah, it's not a bad game. It's just
More exactly what you've played probably three or four times now
Yeah, it's fun. I seem to remember, uh
I feel like there's maybe more stuff in this game, but there's more like locked stuff
Far cry five. I remember we streamed it twice because there was like more stuff to do
Yeah, I mean granted we are we are not
Playing the game the way that it may have been intended to be played to be clear. I'm at like stream shit
Yeah, yeah
All right. Do you want to try the plane strategy once see if it works? Yeah. Um, um, it's up to you
Yeah, let's let's try playing strat one time worth a shot. I'm loading back in here. It's definitely fun
Like not every game that comes out has to be
like a masterpiece
It's just fun to play. It's not I mean, it's just good. I guess kind of
Really pretty looking game seems to be well acted
But you kind of it would just we you're just playing the same game
You've already played just kind of more stuff to do since but since like far cry four, right?
It's sort of every far cry has been like a dlc for far cry four. Is that accurate? Yeah, pretty much
There's only so much new stuff you can add once you've got like yeah
helicopters planes
Uh jet skis boats with guns on them boats with the grenade launchers on them. You got a black screen. Yeah, it's it's loading
What is this warm up pso cash thing? I've never seen that before all right
We're gonna play try to plane strat see what happens. What was the one you you play? Uh, what far cry primal?
yeah, that was like the um, uh, that was that was the
One with the dinosaurs and the mammoths. I wonder if that one's fun. I never played it
All right. I'm ready for an invite. Okay. I'm currently connecting to the far cry servers
Please wait
How do you feel about sorb being in smash? What are your thoughts?
Uh, what are my thoughts on sora being in smash?
well
Where to begin first I need to go ahead and show you guys the prologue
This is the lore for kingdom hearts one
And i'm trying to figure out how to canonically connect the sora in smash brothers with the other 17 kingdom hearts games
So if you guys would all just uh, go ahead and sit down get a snack pay attention
We're gonna watch all the lore videos for all the kingdom hearts games back to back in order to understand
Why sakurai decided to do this and go ahead and extend the kingdom hearts lore into the smash universe thereby
Putting every single smash character potentially in the next kingdom hearts game you say can I have an invite?
Yeah, I already sent you one. Let's see. What the heck that was pretty good. Uh explainer
It says I don't have one from you. It said I don't have a I don't have one. I sent another one
got it, um,
one of the things that I heard or that I was looking at is that
Sora has been they wanted to put him in the game like a year or two ago, right?
but like
It took like three years of like lawyers all yelling at each other before they finally agreed to put him in the game or something
Because I was confused. Okay, if you're gonna have banjo kazooie
Don't you think you want banjo kazooie to be to be the last character?
And then so why wouldn't sora have come out during when kingdom hearts three was relevant?
you want to know the real reason the real reason is because
Uh, coincidentally
Sora is announced for smash at the same time that the kingdom hearts games are announced to be coming to nintendo platforms
And there it is. He's got it. There it is. You got you found the smoke and gun
It's just a brand deal like nintendo doesn't give a shit to the last character
They were just like what major uh franchise can we bring to switch because people are complaining
There's not enough third party games on our platform and they're just they're just playing
Uh pokemon snap for like 30 minutes and then putting the switch down like I don't understand
There it is
He's got to get some long ass games that will take 150 hours for gamers to complete and sell it in a big bundle
So they can buy the bundle and I guess we'll get a new character and smash at the same time. There it is
Nailing it there it is. Um
Okay, let's go to the plane joke
Where is the plane joke from here?
Uh, I was looking for the oh they're looking for the craft image. There it is. There it is
Okay, I got an idea
What if we both take a plane that way if one of us crashes the other one's alive? That's that's brilliant
I wonder if we can summon two at once which i'll say i'll have to say close
So you don't like yeah, because i'm gonna port into yours and then my plane's gonna explode
Okay, so you just drive like a few feet down the runway
Yeah, you go first
I'm just gonna be honest. I i need to follow you not the other way around
Trust me on this one. Okay. I'm just gonna set like a marker a helicopter is probably better right now
But plane but it's slow. It is slow. You're right. Okay, what happens if you call for two planes?
Just says ride cannot be delivered. Let's see if we can even spawn two planes in
Well, how about this you just go i'll try to spawn one. It's gonna teleport me into your plane anyways
So that should be fine
Vehicle currently in use so no just go so just me just you are you in if you fly?
I'll just be teleported to the backseat
Why are things exploding on the side you ran over? Oh, I got 15 trees. Oh what?
I got you with that. No, I didn't
I did not hit you with that. Did I no way
What the fuck I can't believe that hit you. Okay. Um, just fly away fly to are you
In or not? No, not yet. I'm just I can still see you now. I'm in okay
So theoretically here if you go to the ocean, maybe the right should we go fly to the ocean?
If you fly straight ahead from here, just fly straight. Oh, hang on. Oh wait
I'm looking at the wrong person here. Yeah, you gotta turn around fly towards the ocean
You will not hit any other room here. We're about to be in some very heavily restricted airspace
I'm gonna fly with this mountain. There are places where we can fly. It's just the entire zone that he's in we cannot you like your
Oh flying north
Are we upside down?
Uh to try to get out of restricted airspace
I am okay. I need to go west or what which direction I need to go. So you need to go north
fly north and
North is the restricted airspace though, is it I don't know
Okay, both of our curses are on top of each other and I can't tell who's pointing who
Okay, no turn right turn right if you pull right and just kind of i'm already committed
What are you talking about? You're already committed. I'm already in what are you doing? No, don't be in
What are you doing? Don't be in
We're going down just pressed e
What just hit you i'm still alive. All right, it didn't work. Whatever. They're you sniping at me?
Different man for himself now
I keep pushing this button
Okay, look, it's fine. We actually are
Almost halfway there. No, we're we get where I
We're almost halfway there. Hold on. I got an idea. This helicopter is just chasing me
It's okay. You're gonna come to me. I'm trying to come to you without being killed
The helicopter i'm coming
You will
Spawn me into your car. Okay, i'm coming
I don't think are you just gonna try to just drive there on the road a gta strat
We're gonna go to uh, we're gonna go to the airfield
And then steal a vehicle from the airfield
It's where it is right there
I told you we're not we're really not that far. Oh, we're really not
Like god, I hope I just throw a grenade in his room
Oh that didn't work out
Gotta go around the spikes
All right
We're in rank seven
Why do we have people behind us? Hey, it's all right. What rank are we we're gonna get like triple experience
Oh double xp weekend and far cry six pretty much what we're doing
Right click on italics his head then left click. Oh, I wonder what that does
Okay before we dive do you actually is there a plane available?
In this the senate
Um, I didn't mean to shoot. I don't know. That's very good question. You just alerted every
I alerted the pig zona
Oh
I mean if there's going to be a plane there it's this one right there
There is in fact a plane here
straight ahead
Move. Oh guard. Hang on. I can take him out. Let's go. This one has a machine gun on it. Why wasn't he dying?
Oh, there is a machine gun on this one
Okay, yup, you be I mean I did crash the last plane so I can't really talk. Hey, fly plane quick. Tell me
How do you fly? How do you fly? How do you fly? How do you fly?
How do you fly? How do you fly? How do you fly? How do you fly? Okay
We have nothing else. Just head to the ocean ocean fast
We're about to get
No, sorry get a boat get a boat get a boat get a boat
I'm still alive. You are I'm alive. I have one HP. Okay. Wait say hello. I'm gonna spawn on you in a second
I'm on you. All right, we need a boat. It's right there, dude
We have to overwhelm the fuck out of somebody over here boat. Oh, we gotta go to the same boat
We have to overwhelm whoever's on it because they're gonna be people with machine guns and stuff on fire. I think so
God oh
Shit they get to the boat really hard. I will take I'm just bait right now
I have two of them three of them on me right there's more. I can't heal in here. Just stay alive
I'm gonna try to bait all of them. Okay. I'm gonna get to this boat. I just got killed. They're on you
I made it to the fiery boat. Excellent currently repairing excellent. Oh excellent
No dinner today, huh
Okay, okay repaired I'm gonna drive we gotta go guy in the water I think there is fuck him look here's
All right
Perfect. This is exactly where we were last time. We just have to get over here
Can you stop for a sec so I can get in the gunner?
All right, you go. All right. There are mines here. We have to be aware of going for that building over there here
Did they don't want us out here?
So I'm thinking once I get in here, I'm gonna take a right
Let's see. We could we could like you should be able to see him. They're like
Floating in the water. So should I bang?
Should I go right just bang it right here and just we'll go in there or should I wrap around further?
Cuz I feel like it's right there. That's his like big hideout or something, right? Yeah
Like we exploded just in front of his head towards the seawall to the right
All right. I see the mines. Oh, there you go. Yeah, the big big red bubbles
Can I shoot him? I?
Would you're alerting people to our presence?
Okay, so if we get up here
See this spot right here
Right where the wall is clear in a path. The question is do I get how far in is this place?
From where we are right now
Should we jump over here and just kind of start a sneak into the house
We're gonna have to go through the whole city
What about is there a better place of me extremely restrictive you have to fly into it
You'll be shot down to die immediately, but we're not flying it
What are we going for this building? Like I would say the big one. Yeah
Like the one with the red the red light at the top
Yeah, I feel like that's a big isn't that the hotel or is that his like actual hideout? Well, he's got we got
square
Park or a del Leon
Where the where the spoilers in chat? Well, we have to get out of here. Anyways, so let's just get out
We can't take the boat over here. It's a mansion
Okay, this is probably the good time to like actually change to usable guns poor daily own is the hideout. So we need to go
There was that okay, we have toro did alone dating on the law. Yeah, whatever. It's marked. We have to be very careful
Okay, I'm just changing load out. There's a car right here. Looks like there's nobody around that is that
Is that gonna be should we put all our eggs?
I feel like we should do not split out to be in this. Yeah, like not split up but like he separated
I said the respawn points are too valuable
Well, I'm gonna slowly just kind of start moving around void this all the all the red gas shit. That's the enemy side
Yeah, there's a lot of Emmys down there. Honestly, I would just get in the car for now because there's no enemies down
Almost away from their suspicion. There we go. Okay. Yeah, I would just get in the car right now
Until we find a new car is in the event that you could you get detected? I we can just get out of here
All right, let's do it. I'm just avoiding all the red circles dead ahead
And the houses too
Why does this feel like dying light? Oh wait for the car to pass
Just like running over shit, okay, this is we can go this way now
It's a roadblock up ahead. There is but there's nobody here. I think they're in the guard tower. Oh fuck
Are we gonna get through this? Uh, I think it's very purpose-built to not allow this
I think we're gonna have to go on foot to be honest
All right, let's sneak just put this holster your gun. Maybe it'll buy us more time. Yeah, go for stealth stab kills
Where are you going?
Restricted areas
Blue marker, no, no the the white one
Make it again
Yeah, the one I'm looking at is this one here or Deleon is where he is. Oh, it's blue for me. Okay
What is that as a stork? I feed the stork. I
Thought the stork made that noise
It's like the period just ended in like a hockey game
Pelican. All right, let's go this way. Hang on. Hang on
We have a silenced gun, but it probably does no damage to like level eight
No, the only I would only gonna be able to stealth kill these guys
It says one there's a guy scary guy there. No, that's a dog
It's a dog and a scary guy about this way an idea. That's a slow take it easy
We're not in a rush
Yeah, we if we are literally dead on site now
This is actually this gameplay right here is is kind of what Deathloop is sort of
Oh
Alright
Nobody's here. Are we good? Can we yeah. Yeah, we're good. Does it hurt? Oh
There's a crafting table here, I think those are good guys on the right are they a new fast travel open location. Oh
Dude, oh dude. There's no way the dude is here. Oh, he's here. Oh, he wasn't my voice to hear that
I want to be able to shoot him in the head once and kill him
That's definitely not gonna happen. I want sir slightly reduced
weapon noise
No, that's it. That's getting rid of no. No, I don't want range. I don't want to do that. Maybe I do
Optical socket. Okay, I want I haven't unlocked any others armor piercing. I've got a I've got a decent weapon with a silencer now
I do armor piercing without no I can't it's locked item missing. All right, what are the weapons? Can we do here?
Sniper I mean there's also the theory that mean if we can just run on his front door and just hold the fucking fire
Dang down. They just don't just wm1 pyro his house
It's possible. Yeah, you could do you could go
Flamethrower just if you're gonna do flamethrower put the like fire gloves on see don't burn yourself
I'm gonna put flamethrower on I'm gonna put this new
How do you unlock new utility like throwables cuz there's like grenades and stuff that's a great question
Okay, I've got level three Captain America shield what you're seeing is democracy
Absolute. Oh, that's a good headlock there, sir. You know your judo. Well
Get your hand off of my penis
classic
Okay, they're they're on this road
His voice is getting louder
He's on the mic right now. Yes
Okay, what about if we go down this alley this way over here?
What is the charm a meal a succulent Chinese meal
Ta-ta and farewell you can use the grapple to on
Is there is there a grapple point? I mean it probably is. Oh, there is a grapple point
Can't see it from here
Damn it. I keep thinking that
Like they've seen us. Yeah, that's like a you've been spotted
Why why be careful be careful be careful why oh, it's to the grapple from below, okay?
It's fine, there's nobody down here. All right, well, there's like a perfectly cut scream clip possibly
Right, there's the child there's people to the left here
I'm thinking down this yeah down this alleyway
What happened what happened to you all right?
All right, we're gonna make it through here. I thought there was a guy's head and closer all right easy
The dog over here. This is a dog. This is dog. What do we do?
Where do we go this way? Oh shit? Oh wait. We just got so laying people out
I think I think we that's probably a better way to go though. Don't you think?
That person is an RPG
Which can run to his house run to his house they do have an RPG
Holy shit, he's in the face of the RPG. Oh
Again, oh
My god. Oh my god. Oh my god. I'm gonna hide in the corner
All right, I got mine taken care of there's like three this down that hallway straight in front of you down that alleyway
There's two people with rocket launchers
Alright, I'm gonna avoid them and my heel back. I don't think they could possibly know where I am
I wonder can I get the rocket launcher from that guy if I kill him? I wonder if I can get him
You shooting yep. Oh you need help. Here's it. Oh my god
I'm sorry dog. I'm so sorry I
They have rocket launchers that guy very tanky
We've got to shoot in the head that's very important watch out guys. I don't know what that guy
All right helicopter. We gotta like hide from the chopper. Where's it? Oh shit. Oh more guards. Really? Yep
I'm gonna retreat back turn back dead. Oh the chopper is what scares me
Check watch it. Watch it dead. Is he dead? All right, let's go
oceans minus two oh
Shit, we're getting close man. Uh
We are getting close what's gonna happen when we get there, I don't know
I'm gonna run over the flame throw and hold it down
As long as look just me and you are the last people there's two other people that are left in pub G
It's you and me just play like your life depends on it. Okay, they're across the street someone someone's over there that can see us
Okay, let me I can I snipe them
Very important playing pub GPC or mobile
Yeah, there's a guy right there I think I can get him
Dead roof. I shot him in the head
Keep it. Um, there's a lot of people on this street. All right, just left for dead time left left for dead
Bathroom until they leave us long. This guy just ziplined. I guess not. Oh shit. Oh fuck. Oh fuck
Why not hitting this guy?
I'm gonna stealth kill the mortar guy
Wow, I can't help you I have zero health this one guy down here
All right, you just stay alive because I have zero HP. Okay, I'm healing. I don't know who can see me
Somebody can see me. All right. I got I got my health back my heel back. See if I can pop this guy
I have no bullets in this gun. What am I? What the hell are you doing? Jeremy? Oh
Shit, we need ammo
He's focusing on you
I'm alive down here. If you need to die, go for it. All right. All right. I'm gonna come and cover. I'm sorry doggy
I'm sorry. I have to get ammo. I guess I'm like a pistol ammo. You should give me a break
Hey, I think we have to run. This is totally walled off over here. Is this
Shit, what about down this way? Oh
I'm down that hurt. I'm just gonna die so I can spawn on top with you. Okay, just stay in a safe place
I feel pretty safe here. I gotta switch weapons about to spawn on you in like 10 seconds
Okay rank up to stand up to stronger soldiers. That's fine. I'm coming on you. Here we are
I need to change weapons. Don't stand up by the way, if you stand on the guy
To the north he made they may have seen but I don't know if they can get up here
Somebody can see us when we stand. Yeah
That 352 this way. All right, we just gonna keep going this way. Yeah, but that that way's a super wall
Is it super walls completely? What if we go to the light might be able to parachute over it? You think so?
Like getting on top of this
There's a bad place for yeah, we definitely gonna get over there from here on the roof. We gotta move
We gotta move. We gotta move. Gotta move
Fuck the parachute didn't go off. Don't jump. Don't don't wait. What do we both die?
It wasn't high enough to deploy the parachute. Oh, come on
That was a classic fall joke. Oh, all right now that we got a fast travel point though, didn't we?
Let's see if it works
It it yeah, apparently I can't believe we both didn't get the parachutes up
I think it was just too hot too high, but too low too high to live too low to parachute
All right, let's go I didn't even see Teresa the entire time somebody said you might be able to wing suit
We have to go to like a real well, I might be able to and then pull you pull you in
Yeah, dude, what if we just okay, hold on hear me out here
Let's go all the way up to the top of this building and then you just wing suit and fly over there
Everybody sees us here
Okay, I can't hurt these guys at all. We need armor piercing bolts. Oh shit. Oh, I have soft ammo on
Soft ammo I need the other gun, but I can't I don't have time to switch to it. Oh, that was you shit
That was me. I can't even
Know
Bird motherfucker, how dare you
Oh
Okay, I need let me do hold on let me change my ammo dude if it is a bench this thing sucks
Me like give me this thing and I won't change the ammo on it
Armor piercings on it. That's good. I gotta put armor piercing on this thing, too
It's no ammo on this thing. I think you unlock more at the workbench. Is that you?
What this is I'm at the workbench. Oh, there we go. There's a guy. Okay, just put armor piercing on every gun
Yeah, you don't have to be the workman's you can do it anyway. Yeah, you can do it anywhere. Okay
One mod available to install it workbench. Oh, come on. Okay. Here we go. You put armor piercing on your flamethrower
I
Can't switch it out. I don't think I have it. Yeah, you have to be at a workbench
Oh
What the fuck why?
All right. So hey look
See that grapple point over there. We need to get on top of this building. That's high enough for you to wingsuit across the town
Uh-huh, but you can't die though. Like is there a way can you safely land the wingsuit somehow?
parachute
We have to get we have to get higher. Yeah, we actually do need to get higher. Hold on. I got an idea
There's a workbench right there. Yeah, I know it's too late though. Are you gonna try to like worms?
Ninja rope up to another platform
Yeah, but I can't I can't like any more anymore slack. You're gonna hit the wall
Slow it down. I see you're gonna try to go up here
You actually might be able to do this if you can grab on top of where that moss is
This is difficult and it's not going anywhere
Any more space
Okay, except this person throwing grenades up here. We got to get across to it. Let's go across three
Okay, you first tell us you don't have parachutes. That's why that's what's going on. We don't have parachutes. It's grayed out
It's not that we're not deploying them fast enough where it's too low or too high. We don't have them
Maybe I don't have a wingsuit either. Okay, so there's another tall building. Yep that we can climb
You you lead you're the one that has the suit. Hopefully you still have it. Do I have the suit?
Find out. Oh
Back turn around. No
Add
Wait, are you alive? Yeah. Oh, yeah
Who's this then except my dog all the way back there? I think so
Yeah, there's like there's like four or five guards on the street. Okay
Hmm. All right. I see. Yep. We gotta take these guys out
All right, you stay up there then
That guy's got a lot of armor. Do you think a human body can block a rocket behind you behind you behind you behind you?
Why are you behind you behind you? I'm trying to shoot him. I'm
Okay, is that it I
Think that's it on this street helicopter coming in
Chopper is here. Oh
We got impacts wax. I feel like this is probably good. There's like high-level gear. Where are you over here?
in the building
Helicopters here now tension coming this way. Yeah, there is. All right. What if we go? I'm really sorry. I'm sorry
We have we need clear road
Does the chopper know where we are? I don't know
Probably. Okay, so I'm just gonna go for this alley dead ahead. Um, is this person on the ladder? Oh
It's not that person off the ladder
They're freaking out down there. All right, we have to move. Oh shit. Yeah, we're gonna move. Where are we going from here?
I need to get to the top of a really tall building to see if I can ring suit
There's too many fucking people there. This is the street from last time. Is that a friendly dog? Oh, thank God
Okay, so we know how this ends
The chopper is just chasing me, but I'm behind you
He the chopper is gonna be overhead in a second. It's here. Oh
What happened that hurt?
Sucks, what about that alley straight ahead to your right? Oh
Fuck bad. Very bad
Hiding I'm just hiding that somehow. I am technically still alive. I'm gonna reload guns
Who sees me who sees me who sees me who sees me who sees me?
Just hang over there I'll hang over here. I can't hang over. I can't hang over there anymore. I got an idea
I'm almost I'm out of ammo for a lot of whips. Oh
This is bad. Okay. I'm gonna go for something here
Okay, fixing my broken ow, I kind of went around to the right side
I'm gonna see if there's anything over here we can do
Have they sounded the alarm already? I
Think so like on the roof
Damn it. They really don't want you to go over there. Yeah
Like e1 is super off-limits manhole manhole. There's a manhole
Where is it dude come to me? Holy shit. This is the way in
Actually the way in where are you? I would just throw yourself off a building. I have no idea how I got here
There is no wingsuit. Yeah, no wingsuit
Not permitted at this location. All right, I'm dead. So don't die. It's gonna hide. I gotta switch guns to these armor
25% damn it. What does he like the metal gear solid death sound?
I'm here. Okay, take a look at this
interesting, huh, oh
God don't do what I did. Don't do what I did. Don't do what I did
Nice and slow. Oh, we got flash game flashlights and everything. Isn't this the tutorial sewer?
Yeah
There are alligators down here. You're gonna turn into one
They've hostile. Let's not find out
Are we gonna like a pop-up in his bathroom like in his toilet? There's a I mean at that
We could but we would just be copying. All right. I'm not gonna go out yet because George are Martin
You might put your head out and die. Is it safe? There's a tank out here. Okay
There's a hang on if we stay safe crouched completely hidden
There's a chance we might if they're not in the tank already. We might be able to get the tank. Oh
Bro, okay. That sounds like a great idea ready. I don't have a silencer
There's a guy right to your left right to your left literally right next to us. You'll see that
Okay, I'm taking a shot. What about the guy right here?
Take care of the alarm. I will shoot the alarm
Did you get it?
No, he got it. Oh, yes. Oh, no, I don't know what to do. I don't know what to do
I don't know what to do. I'm freezing in panic. I'm gonna go this way
I'm gonna go. I don't know what to do. Where do I go? I'm gonna go this way. I think I'm running over here. Oh
Just run just run just run just run run run run run back in the sewer. Hey, can you get back?
Oh
He went into the tank
Yeah, like he okay. It's like his animation started
Or I could like shoot him to get out of it. Damn it. Oh
He wouldn't he just started speeding I freaked I don't know where to go
I didn't know if I was gonna run into a bunch of enemies. All right, last try one more try. Let's go for it
Hey last try. Let's try. Let's try going different route. I'm gonna put armor piercing on every single weapon you have
Let's try taking a different path. I don't know that for sure that if I was allowed to take the tank
I there was no prompt. Yeah, can you how do you craft ammo? Can you craft ammo?
some guns you
Pick like primary weapon, whatever then the gun. It should be the first attachment mod
I really don't have enough to do armor piercing for um, it's annoying
You have to EMP a tank to steal it. You actually can have an EMP really to disable vehicles
But I don't know how to get it now you up you change your backpack. Oh, they're here. What do you mean?
They're here stun grenade smoke grenades
Dynamite I don't have we don't have EMPs. I don't think there's a perception grenade. I don't know what that is
EMP sticky EMP grenade blast grenade EMP acquire Supremo from Juan's office or his arms dealers
We have to do it first. Yeah. Well, um, go right in the sewers this time. It'll lead you to the compound
Okay, good. No, no armor piercing. I can't come on
There's uh, if you if you look at your pack your Supremo pack. Hmm, and then mods
There's one for like minor armor piercing protection and there's also one for just run faster
Sharp sure to kill streak poison powered
Nobody what that's actually a really good idea. Dude. What are we thinking? This person's brilliant. I want that person to be
I'm going to time them up for 10 seconds. Just let people know who it was
Somebody said that I should just hide in the sewer and be your spawn point
Well, you just try to get into the compound good. That's a great idea
Okay. All right. You ready? Hold on
classic halo stretch
Dude, halo one. That's what you do to play halo on legendary
Somebody is the spawn we grapple this we're gonna get back to that sewer. All right back to that sewer
I don't remember where it was. It's that eyeball on the map. Holy shit. They've all
They were all just about to collapse on us
Luckily, I put armor piercing rounds on my
Well, that saves us some time rifle here
Okay, good
You know six hours to beat halo one on legendary. How do every good joke is plus five, dude, how the fuck did we?
Oh right here. Um
Follow the eyes. Nobody remembers a plus five minus five
What happened? What happened you good? I broke my arm. Are you going this way? By the way? I don't know
We need to get to that. Um that eyeball the eyeball
eyeball on the map
Where are these guys coming from?
Are they shooting the dog? I don't know
chorizo's getting them
really
Well, this is clearing them out. This is good. Yeah, but don't they just respond do they?
All right, we got to get this way. Okay, chorizo
Where's guapo I don't know what happened to guapo I think I gotta go heal chorizo
I didn't do it long enough. I didn't do it long enough
Wait, here's guapo. What is the whole time?
All right, let's go. I don't know where you were going before but you went in a full circle and we're just killing people
I do I don't I don't know how I got to that eye see the eyeball on the map the mini map
That's where the sewer is. That's where we need to go
But it like I think we have to go this way see the blue marker
Oh, actually, I think we can go down here to take a right
See the little blue map down here
I hate that I hate that I hate that I just had to do that
Yeah, this is the right way now we go through here, huh, and then we go
This way this way. Oh my god that guy fucking exploded. Oh
My god and this way
He's dead, okay, okay gamer moments now we need the sewer
Which where the fuck is it?
Shit
It's definitely okay. I think it was this way
Ignore these guys and then it was to the right. Actually, I don't know I teleported to you
No, this is the wrong way. Hold on. We need to go. This is where I went before I died
Yeah, I don't have no idea straight and then right straight and right right there straight and right
I think it actually could be this way. Just walk through this like checkpoint thing. Uh-huh. Holy shit
Yep, bingo. Don't three though
Whisk woppo. All right. There you go. All right. So now I said in the sewer go right
All right
Oh god, oh don't die. What the fuck one are you dead? Nope almost though
Oh
Are you petting him if you die right now, I'm going to die you understand
Did you stop to pet chorizo while they want they while they were coming around the corner?
Yes, I could have just gone in the sewer. I it's too much pressure fighting people like 10 levels higher than us
Guys, I have the same gear I got from the tutorial
All right, we get there in five seconds if we don't go on a loop, all right, let's go go go go go go I
Was I was curious to see if you had invincibility frames if you pet one of the animals because it would have been huge
All right, where did you go down? Yeah
I'm here. It's a lot of guys down there that it holy. Oh my god is he's bad. He's a bad guy too over here
That was a great throw. Oh
Fuck be careful
Yeah, we should just wait to get in the sewer all we all that matters is the sir
Just exactly where we just were. Okay, you fucking stupid ass game
I don't know how I seeing all this and you're not seeing any of it. I'm just trying to stay alive, man
I don't know. I'm just trying to live
They're doing some insane shit
Here right behind. All right, let's go. I
Died like six times. Okay hard, right?
Watch out that guy's got a bomb
Did somebody set us up where you going just come here. Where are you going? This guy's a rocket launcher turn around. He's fine
I'm just trying to be like erratic. So he doesn't shoot. He doesn't kill us. All right, they're coming through the checkpoint though
Dammit, where are they shooting us from both? I don't I'm dead. I'm done. I have no idea who was shooting me
I think it's up top. He's up top. Okay, let's just go through it. We're gonna go I
Got shield. I'll lead the way
I'm so glad you think I'm so glad you're in front John wick
Here's a rocket launcher. This guy's got a rocket launcher. Did the edible kicked in like fucking ten minutes ago?
And I am like so glad you're in front of me. Oh, no, you're on fire. Don't spread it over me
All right. I'm just going to the fucking sewer to be your spawn point for the love of God
All right, we're good because I'm about to die he's got a flamethrower I just fine I'm in the I'm your spawn point I'm here
I just you he's just chasing you
Oh you change guns if you just die it will be fine there's just so much fire I can't kill one guy
Hopefully he kills you your time to shine
Everybody's coming down here, right? Why does he look like he's why does it? He looks like he's coming to get me
He's thinking about it. Why do I hear bullets being shot? Oh, just guapo. I got
Okay
We're good. Somebody said go right in the sewer and it gets to the compound
I was like 80 meters away from whatever the objective was
Really?
But I may have set the objective marker way too close
There you are, okay
I'm running out of ammo, but I'm here. Yeah me too
Res go
Okay, I'm not gonna use in the sewer not gonna res guapo, sorry
Good very good. Well done. I would not go up there. I
This person alive
They're dead now
Okay, guapos back combat's over. Actually is it okay? Are you gonna go?
We get a clean clean slate. Are you just gonna check and see if you can just walk into the compound?
I'm just gonna go back. Remember that we ran to the um
The tank yeah, I feel like that's kind of where we're going right think so
Wait, did we come from this way or are we going?
We are going kind of that way
Hang on are you back there? How'd you go? I'm in the sewer man. I'm not leaving the sewer
I'm like on the street level
You're gonna have to catch up to me though, right? I mean should I just go from the city you can go this way
You can go up to me at least you want to come up to you
Are you sure you won't I sure I'm gonna cuz we're gonna get we're gonna I could I could just keep going until
I teleport you I guess that's true. I
We certain that you'll be able to
That means people saying stay in the sewer people saying so we're sewer sewer you have to do the sewer sewer is the only
Way apparently people saying sewer is the only way. Oh, okay. Well, then maybe I'm just going in a circle then
Or maybe chat just really wants you to stay in a sewer just to see how long you'll do it
That's fine. You go you got to tank through the sewer stay in the sewer
What are you doing down here? There's somebody down here. Okay, I'm gonna die so I can respawn on you in the sewer
Yeah, who killed Guapo? What am I doing down here? He was the protagonist of a different story. You better not die
Don't do anything stupid. I am standing still. I'm not going anywhere
Don't get surprised by a crocodile. I won't there's no crocodiles down here. There's a pretty good side character POV
That's fine. I just want to make sure we are we are alive. Okay, here we go. I'm here
All right, so people are saying to go straight and then go right
You say that we got we got bad guys in the rear. I think we can outpace them. They'll go, right?
So I'm assuming this means right
How do we die down here the first time?
Jump or something
This goes out of the sewer. I'm I'm staying here
This is a tank again, yeah, this is other way wrong way other way other way apparently it's the other side
Yeah, we're on I'm on the wrong side here. He said there were people down here, right? Yep. They're right here
They said hug, right? It's crocodiles here now, too. I guess still shooting me and you were right in front of him
Yeah, I have a shield. Would you shoot the shield guy?
so left
instead of right I
Guess it's a secret. It's just a secret back here
It's wrong secret helmet
We have to go here. We have to get here. Okay. Well, well, I guess we've just go through where the tank is
Yeah, what the heck? Well, you guys are helping us
The shotgun is like god-tier powerful the pistol shotgun shield combo
Okay. Well, we're gonna try watch over the dog this dog right next to you
And a mean one it is. Yeah, why is he not attacking you? How safe is it if I come up?
20% he knows they like kind of know I'm here. Yeah, they know I'm here now. Sorry dog. Okay, you
Walk was down. I'm going for tank. All right, you'd go for tank. Do you want me to help suppressing fire?
I'm in you're in the tank. I'm in the tank. Oh hell. Yeah. All right
But they have RPGs and shit. This is gonna be a short-lived adventure. Do you think so?
Both I don't think you should get in on the mounted turret. That's for sure
I'm just gonna try moving but we need to go like that way kind of like right. Can we go right from here?
Can you repair me if you come back down if you come this way? Yeah, I don't want to go too far out
Hang on. Hang on. I'm just gonna hop out and try to repair
Where is this person that keeps seeing me? I don't know where they are. You're right there. Okay full help
Like I just tried to shoot a rocket on me at me. I think he's still looking at me
Press V. No, I know what V does
I don't want to do it right now. I don't I can't get in your tank though. You can but then we'll just both die
That's true. There is there there is a gunner seat though. I don't know who keeps seeing me. There's somebody right across the way
I don't like I'm on fire
Alright, what about can we go down that can that road that's right next to you? Can you go down that this really doesn't take that much?
Oh shit, I shouldn't have gotten out. Did you pop up? Yeah fight or run. What the fuck?
I think special forces are about to arrive
Wanted
We have to move. I'm moving if we go down. Can we go right? Can we go down this way?
I'm stuck. I wonder this way we can go
Back in the sewer because this is blocked off. We have to go left
But we can't we have to go eventually we are we supposed to go that way
So we're chat. How do they keep getting up like on the roof?
Alright, there's a space. There's a place we can go down here. It's a little alleyway
Okay, is there anywhere? I don't think we can go anywhere. I can't this thing doesn't turn like a tank should follow the blue line
Yeah, I'm trying to see where it even we go. We have to go that way, but
What if we jumped on your tank to jump over the wall?
that work
Watch out. I'm trying to repair you
Looking good. Oh, why are you going to circle because everything's blocked off
We're trying to find a place that we can like get over one of the walls
Somebody behind us. I only see guapo and my poor pup is just lying on the ground riding
We can't go this way kill my dog
Like how do we?
Maybe through here. I can't shoot
All right, Guapo. Help me out. Is there a grapple?
It's a grapple up here
Chirijo
You know Jeremy, maybe the area isn't available to you actually reach the point in this story
What is up here? Is that an explosive?
I guess not. What is it? It's like a beacon on top of this place. Oh shit crackle and pop machine gun
LMG what happened by machine gun might actually be good here. I just may be very good
um oh
This is where we tried to jump over. Hey, can you come to me? Oh, you're really far away
It's no grapple hook all clear
Where is it? I have a door stuck situation. You've got a door stuck scenario. Yeah
Oh, I might actually be stuck here. I feel like I can make it
Fight or run there now. Yeah, we know that I'm coming back to you. Oh
You're very far away
Cuz I'm kind of just going in a circle cuz we don't know how to get into the center cuz I don't know
I don't think we can get in there's one way. There's still one way. What is it if I can actually okay?
I wonder if you start wingsuiting from just outside of the city limits if it'll kill your wingsuit when you get in
Probably you can but this I think the sewer is south of the tower area. Oh
Dude we've been in the wrong place the whole time we need to wait we need to be like here
We've been running around in the sewers up here. We need to be down here. Let's see these blue tunnels
shit
Yeah, I'm just heading towards the new marker
Finger so
How have we
If you look at the map, we've just been really far northwest
We we're supposed to be down south of that area to see the blue lines. I think that's the sewers
We were getting like sewer directions for the wrong sewers
Yeah
Whatever. It's okay. I have a car or we'll have a car
Teresa those guys
Oh
Why did they all run towards it? Yeah. Thank you chopper chopper gameplay
Hold on gotta get closer
Nice
What a shot
Almost there. Okay. Oh
I was this car still here. This thing's insane. By the way, what this car?
Now the car that I
Alright get us to that sewer. We gotta find the manhole that's down here. I think this guy knows it
I'm going to your marker. I know go to that one. That's where we have to go
He knows we're doing this. Yeah, we should get out
What is right here? There's a sewer right here. This is the sewer that we need to get it to get into the compound
This is the secret sewer we got the all clear
Don't do what I did. That kills you. Be very careful. Good fault joke. All right, so now we have to just go from here
This sure ways
We gotta go we gotta go left. Yeah, go left. This will take us through
Yep, this way. I don't know about this
Sewer looks awfully similar thing on this. It's just free stuff. Oh, I get it all even if you if I don't pick it up
Yeah, we're about to be in his compound
This is the do or die right here. It's either we do it or we don't so
We're in like another just kind of tell now he did straight ahead that building is his tower
There any people think these are civilians. Yeah, we just holster. No, we're not supposed to be here
We're gonna kill on site the sleepy alien people are just standing outside yawning your front door
This is like it is like in the movie when the bad guy
Tricks the good guy into thinking it was easy to get to this point
You know and then like the lights come on and they were expecting them to break in the entire time
Yeah, I don't can we go in here. This looks totally blocked. Yes. Okay. Okay, we're in. All right
We're in we're in that guy was
Extremely surprised. All right
No panicking. No panicking. We're gonna get through this. We're gonna go up all the way up the stairs
We need to play this together cover each other
There's no guards yet, okay
New shotgun wait, hold on. Let me look let me equip that cover me cover you we got where are you?
Oh, there you are. We had dogs in coming. I'm getting a shotgun equipped. Okay shotguns equipped
Nice and easy. Can you go that way? No
Hopefully there's this anyway to go. Can we not go anyway?
Cuz I'm looking at the enemy dog that's trying to get us in it. They're just like pathing around. I
would assume
He's not open. There's a I see a grapple point, but it's like kind of outside
We can't go up
Here somebody's Oh
Grapple on roof in big room shit
Hmm like I see that I see that too is that maybe that's outside
Definitely not available from here. Oh my god
Come on here
The grapple looks like it was on this side. It was definitely like inside but also
Not on the first floor
Yeah, it's like it's like right there shit
They've protected it. I don't think we can get in there an impenetrable locked door
Damnit, we can't get up there. I don't think um
I don't think you can fly anything here. No, you know, it's probably it's probably like it loads the area. Probably
It's probably story locked
Dogs like attacking me while I'm like smoking a cigar. I'm sorry dog, but I'm gonna die
I don't think there's any other place we can go. Hi. Is there is there a helicopter around here?
I mean we could look if there is I don't know where it would be
Wait, that's a good dog. Oh
I think the dog barking at us and attacking. That's not a good dog
You can't slight tackle them. They're running into the building. Um, I don't I don't think there's a I don't think I think I think
We're screwed. I
Think we're probably screwed too
Hang out wait for him to leave and go to a restaurant or something
But I cleared the street
Use the vent
German vent German vent German vent. This is an among us thing
Probably come out and face us
Alright. Well, that was fun. I don't think we're getting in here. At least we made it in here. We did make it here though
What I'm getting hit markers someone someone has held up there
Oh, that was me dying. Oops
All right. Oh, that's it
Yeah, I'm just giving it one last look see I would assume that this area changes when you're supposed to come here
I'm it probably does. Where are you? Oh, you're in that building
I was just saying if there's a way to like
Like that it's not it's not really like a jet pack. This thing only has like a little boost
We would need like a helicopter or plane or something
Okay, well played. So maybe I could like
Yeah, it's alright that was fun though, yeah climb up his leg like a kitten
Hey, so we just find where the helicopter spawns are
This is a long stream. Um, it's long. I mean look we're having fun
All right the shotgun. All right turns people to stone help. I'm bleeding here. I'm my body's on fire
Are you loving in games when the shotgun shoots and it like rips to the right like this?
Yeah, what's up with that recoil? Oh
See the recoil on this look at this
It's a lot. This little pistols really
Powerful Jesus
Is your shotgun do that
Look at decent do you see how the how crazy the recoil is though, right?
I can barely even like aim it on my screen. It's like this guy sucks. It's uh, the L Ruby. Yeah
There's fun
Everybody this was far cry 6. This is italics. Let me shoot this guy. Let me let me get the kill
That's fun
If you don't know italics, this is Alex and he screams got a good scream
Yeah, it was fun
Make an objective make objectives for yourself. It's fun
Okay, so hey
The first part of the movies over we know what we did is we went actually up to the projector room and we
Fast-forwarded the movie with everyone still in there just being like what the fuck is going on
Why we fast-forwarding like the end, you know, you might be able to do that for the other guys
Maybe not, but that'd be pretty cool. All right. I'll talk to you later. Thanks for playing. Yeah
Somebody said I'll see you next year. Oh
Interesting you'll see me next year. How about um, are we are we doing the other thing the man of a damn?
Yeah, we're doing man of a damn. Yeah, that's man of a damn three, right? Or is it man of a damn four?
That's like that's like in two weeks. Oh shit. Look at that. I gotta play man of a damn with it's Alex
That's how it works. Can't get rid of me that easy
Thought I wish I could
Got to try harder
Yeah, well, we'll see it talks again in a couple weeks or a man of a damn that's not the name of the game
That's just what the only one I could remember
All right, I'll tell you soon dude. I don't know if you're still streaming or not
But if not, no and I'll talk to you soon. I'm done. But thanks for playing. Yeah, it was
very enjoyable in in of itself just being shitty but also
You know just having some good laugh out loud moment. Yeah, and look far cry. Look the great out six out of ten
That's fine. But it's it's fun to play with friends. This is yeah, it is a co-op game. We'll see you later
Thanks a lot, dude. Bye. Bye night German chat
He's gone. Yeah, we'll do the um, oh what what my computer just crashed my computer crashing. Hello. Can anybody hear me?
Hello. Hello. Can you hear? Oh, okay. No, we can hear you. All right
My computer just crashed. I lost the access to my other monitor
Everything went on to my main screen. Everything was black for like 10 straight seconds. I have no audio
Say 50 in the chat if you can hear me. I need to know. Okay. All right, good
That was really weird. I have my left monitor is like dead. I think my graphics card crashed when I exited the game. All right
Thanks for watching everybody. We'll see you again. Probably some point in the middle of the week. I'm probably gonna stream on
Maybe Thursday Tuesday Thursday or Thursday, maybe Wednesday. Keep an eye on the on the sauce. It's gonna be some point midweek
And you're probably asking what are we gonna play? I you know, I have no idea
I was thinking about maybe yeah, what are people saying in the chat smite smite smite one place smite smite smite
I mean, that's a fun one. That's all right
Oh, I mean a lot of people in the chat are saying it a lot of people are saying it. That's interesting
Yeah, well, maybe we'll play smite. We said fuck you. Come on. Just relax man. There's no need for that kind of vulgarity
What about the Nickelodeon all-star bra? Oh that did come out. That's not a bad idea
We'll figure out something some of the look just keep an eye on the sauce
I got some stuff to do this week
You'll get something midweek and then we'll back on the
Weekend at some point as well. I'll see you guys midweek. Thanks for watching everybody. That was Far Cry 6
It was a doozy. Have a great rest of your evening
Pray rest of your day
Thanks a lot guys. Good night. Goodbye
Take care of yourself. Thanks for the subs as always and I'm gonna reiterate this one more time
Money on this stream it sees a lot
Tried to be pretty transparent about how much money this stream takes in
There's no you don't need to like give this stream a shitload of money. Please don't
If you give this channel five dollars a month, it's more than enough way more than enough
It realistically should nobody should really be ever giving this channel more than that amount per month. I
can't like stop people from doing that but I
You know, you guys know how much good guy 98
I'm not trying to like be well, you know, I'm like I'm like a good guy. I
Just don't want people to think I'm taking all this shit for granted
Because I'm not I just hope people know that I don't
Don't think so much as I need to say
I'm just trying to do trying to do what I'm doing
Yeah, good night guys. I'll see you guys later. Have a great rest of your evening. Goodbye
See you in the middle of the week. Keep an eye on the sus
I'm gonna leave before a sub train happens because I'm not I'm gonna make sure that doesn't happen. I
See you later. Bye. Bye