Hey, what's happening? How you doing? Honest to goodness, let's game. Yeah, more, I mean, you,
you know what we're doing. I don't gotta tell you. You know, I don't gotta tell you what we're doing.
You already know. Dark and Darker again tonight. Gonna be playing with a few different groups.
Gonna be jumping around. First group, we got...
Italics. Italics is here tonight. Permission to swag out. Yeah, sure, I guess. And then,
the other participant in the group for group one. Gonna be poke. Poke, poke, poke, poke, poke, poke.
Can we, can everybody yell, please? And then a little bit later, we're gonna maybe get
criken in here. And then later, I'm gonna play with Will Neff. I'm gonna be jumping around all
over the place tonight. So, but we'll start here. Trying to play with as many people as I can,
because it's obviously over in a few days. Promise not to germa this up this time.
I was not responsible for even half of those deaths. I was not responsible for half of our wipes.
You're talking about people, people were like paying money to kill me in the game. Like,
that's not, I don't think anybody was trying very particularly hard a couple days ago. I don't think
that's the case. But yeah, that's the plan tonight. After today, I'm not going to be streaming this
game again. I, this is the last night you'll see it. I'm gonna probably stream for a little
bit tonight. I don't know how long, but you know, we'll see. Because this weekend, on Sunday,
Ster and I are gonna do Elden Ring mods again. So, I gotta, I gotta move on to something else
at some point, right? And then after that, at some point next week, maybe that's when I'll tap back
into like sorcery. Breath of the Wild, maybe. I gotta finish some of this stuff, right? So,
we'll probably do that too. Maybe Frog Detective as well. Just gonna wait. Hylics. Yeah,
that's probably where you'll see that. The new randomizer seed. I think we're doing different
mods. I think we're doing randomizer with other stuff on it to make it even more ridiculous.
And I cannot promise that that we're going to beat the game again. But we're gonna at least play it
again and do one final just kind of mayhem run and just see what happens. So, I don't know,
we'll see. I am not promising we're going to play another like 30 hours of Elden Ring. But I don't
know what Ster has in store for us. Because Ster is the one that is putting it together. So, he's
putting all these mods together. So, he's, I'm just, he's just like, hey, I'll give, I'll give
you the folders when I need to. Or I'll tell you what to download when, when, when we're ready.
So, I don't know what it could be anything. Yeah, more dark and darker. I think I talked to Poke,
talked to Italics. Italics is currently in the call. But he is, I think, starting to stream
doing his intro. So, we're just gonna hang out. Seven Hour Visual Novel Mod Pack. Visual Novel
Elden Ring. How am I doing? I'm doing pretty good. I'm doing pretty good. Hope you're doing good.
Do you like circus peanuts? No, so you say this dude loves circus peanuts. I don't know where
you're getting that from. I like biting into a circus peanut. I like, the texture of a circus
peanut is very interesting to me. After that, it gets a little weird, I think. You can, I can
really only eat one circus peanut. And then I don't want another one for a year. But I, I don't,
I enjoy that one circus peanut. It's pretty cool. Texture, bro. This ain't Minecraft. Why is
something, why is texture Minecraft to you? It's not, everything's not Minecraft. Texture is a
word to describe tech. Oh my god, whatever. What the fuck? They've got a point. Texture,
everything has to be Minecraft. All right, let's see if we've got, let's see. Yeah, I'm gonna add
Poke, I think, right now. And let's get Poke in here. Poke and I have a very interesting
relationship. Poke and I were part of a team. Oh, I'll wait till Poke gets in here. Talk about
our Smite World Championship prospects. Hold on. There we go. Oh, whoops. Uh, I'll just call
Italics back. I made a different group. That's my fault. I forgot. I'm right now, I'm gonna call
with Italics and he's getting a call from me again. How does that work? Hey, what's up? How
you doing? Are you ready to get some dubs? Hey, are you ready to get a potential Smite World
Championship? Oh, there you are. What's up? Hey, what's up? Yeah, sorry. I had to, I called again.
I'm an idiot and I made two groups. That's all good. You sound the same. Oh, hey, what's up,
everybody? Hey, how are you? You sound the same, just nicer. Hey, what's up? Oh, hey, everybody.
How are you? Yo, I'm Poke. What's up, German Poke? No, it's been a while, Poke. It's been a while.
Played Smite, right? Yeah, and we were best friends. I retweeted that. That was really fun.
That was fun. We broke up, but we got over it and we're here. All right, so Italics does not
really know how to play the game, so I hope you're not ready to try really hard. I've got two. I'm
really good at teaching people how to play. Good, good, good, good, good. I do have some credentials.
Okay, I played a bunch of Tarkov. I played a bunch of Mountain Blade and I played a bunch
of Chivalry and this is just those games. He's fucking good too. He was one of the best fucking
Tarkov players I've ever seen in my life. Okay, you're good then. He's only seen one.
All right, let's do it. We'll poke. What's your name in the game? My name is Movie. It's okay.
I love that name. Just Movie. Yeah, I got lucky. That's actually pretty lucky. I was there when
the game just came up and I just put random names. I got Movie, I got Music, I got... That's like
putting David in. I also got Carl, just Carl. I was gonna say, yeah, I had to put a one on mine.
Carl has got fucked over, but I got all the Carl's. Carl one, Carl two, Carl three, Carl four.
This is the next one. I don't see your invite. URL Gold Rush. You can sell those on eBay now.
I allow your invite. You can invite me now. There we go. I got it. Yo. So you play fighter? Yeah,
I play fighter. Do you want me to roll something else? I'll swap, I'll swap. I have like... Oh,
fighter meta? I'm gonna try this. All right, what do I have? I'm bringing up Carl. Should I bring my
Zwayander for this one? No, not first match. That would be stupid. What the hell am I talking
about? Did you just ask if you want to bring like your most valuable weapon into my basically first
game? I'm likely to just friendly fire you at the first portal and just take it off your body and
then escape. Yeah, all right. I'm bringing you a weapon. Oh. Aetalics. Aetalics. My friends call me
E. No, you should say E-tal. E-tal. E. I got you, bro. Did you just call him Elm? Were you gonna call him Elm Tree?
Elm Tree? I thought you said Elm, like you were gonna call him Elm Tree. No, no, I'm gonna call
him E. But I got you a weapon. That's perfect. I got you a Z... No, no, no. Zwayander. My friends call me E. My
loved ones call me Biggie, so your choice. Oh, shit. All right. All right, you guys ready? Yeah.
All right, ready up. E. The game asked me if I wanted to check my loadout and I was like, no, I'm going
in naked. You don't have anything, do you? I know. All right, I gotta put headphones in. Polk, have you
done any of the red dungeons? Yeah, I've done a lot for this game. Are they hard? Yeah, it's hard.
I mean, it's kind of hard, yeah. Have you done High Roller? It's really hard. Have you done High Roller?
No, I'm terrified. I'm too much of a wuss. Let's get 100 bucks and go just for fun. Polk, I have a
lot of money. Like, my whole stash is gold coins and I'm just like scared to use them. Do the stashes
continue through demos or like wipe per demo? Yeah, it's gonna be all gone soon. You have to spend it.
No. You have to. Here, take the sword. I need to rebind Effany. Wait, where's it? Which one? I gave
it to him. I gave it to him, not you, sorry. What the fuck? Oh, I thought you have money. No,
I got one, yeah. All right, so, Taleks, here's how you click to swing. Oh, really? Let's fucking go.
Wow, great teacher. You ever played Mordhau? Yeah. Chivalry counts, hopefully? Yeah, yeah,
it's like that. Are we moving through this door or are you scouting? I'm sorry. I was moving,
I had to move something. Hey, by the way, Taleks, bugs kill, so be aware. Okay, do I have like,
is there an overhand, like an overhead swing or am I just cleaving everybody? Oh, no, yeah.
Third attack or a second attack, like a combo, like swing and then swing. That's right click.
Okay. But you can swing twice. Swing and then boom. Yeah, it's a three combo for everybody,
right? Yeah, just every weapon has a different animation, so. This game is so fun. All right.
Yeah. Oh my god. I'm sure I'm safe corner. There's shit everywhere, there's loot everywhere,
you have to get it. Oh, enemies, enemies. Where? I'm gonna fireball him. I got him,
direct hit. Nice shot. I'm gonna get him again. Did you just kill that person? No,
he got away though. All right, I'm so bad at this. It's a jumping puzzle at the beginning of the map.
This is a big tip E. E? Press X on holster and then to make this jump. I made a jump crouch.
Yeah, make sure you don't have anything in your hands, it's very hard. It actually,
nobody laugh at it if it doesn't make it. Oh my gosh. No, that was actually pretty impressive.
Oh, okay. Yeah. Yeah. Well, yeah, you got it done. I won't say anything else. I'm going back to dome.
Oh, what was that? Where are they? Oh, okay. Are you alone? Oh, hey, I'm talking, communicating.
Yeah. Yeah. Oh, that's right. You did shoot two. Why am I acting like a meteor? You fucking attacked
them. I'm sorry. I thought you were a monster. I won't shoot you. He thought you were a monster
and he, that's why that happened. Don't worry. You're trapped. There's a trap here. You lied.
I'm fucking dead. We got an archer back there too. It's the last thing you hear. I'm dead.
You have to kill him. I'm hasting you. I'm going to go this door. I'm going to bounce off the walls.
They're trying to go. I hasted. I'm giving you invisibility. You're invisible.
Oh, that's actually a good strat lying on the internet. Yeah. What the fuck is going on here?
All right, Carl. I'm going in. Oh, got one in the head. Oh, I'm going in. One hit. Impressive.
Oh my God. It's how it's fucking gigachad. Nice, man. All right. Okay. I'm going to take
Jerma's soul. Okay. Yeah. So should I be looting right now? You loot. I'll go heal.
So there were two, just two. It looks like it was three. Yeah. But then we killed a third,
is what I'm asking. Yeah, they're all dead. Okay. They put a trap down on the door.
My last words were you lied. What a shitty way to go. I was trying to disarm it. Oh,
you right click to loot fast. Okay. So I just leave white gear. Yeah. Unless it can replace,
if you have nothing in it, if you have no boots or no, having something is better than nothing,
obviously. Yeah. It's going to take some white gear at home now. If you have nothing. Yeah. I
just beat those guys with no armor. Yeah. Well, you are barbarian. Barbarian is kind of.
Don't take this from me. Okay. It's all I have. Okay. Well, what you did was very good. Can you
help me out, please? I need to help my friend. Oh, not me. Can you please help me out? Should
I be going over there? I just need to get to my friend, heal and arrest my friend. Are you good?
Everybody's so full of shit in this game. It's so funny. Yeah. Please don't hurt me. I'm very,
I have nothing. I have nothing. I have nothing. Yes. One of them is naked. Here,
you guys can have this. What did you give him? It's getting. What did you do? There's a heel
right here. Listen, E. Yeah. You got to hide. I got to hide. Okay. Yeah. You kind of. Or something.
Yeah. Figure it out. You got you guys kind of opposite directions right now. Yeah. We're on
like other side of that room. I'm looping around. I'm looping around. You got to. Oh, should I use
a bandage or something? Yeah. If you have any heels, definitely use them. That's the craziest
spider ever. It's still behind you. Not bad. Not bad. That did nothing. Okay. Yeah. The bandages
are pretty awful, but they're better than nothing. Healing potions are instant and they're kind of a
hot. It's like Diablo 2. Everything in this game is Diablo 2. Just imagine. Did one of these guys
have a heal potion? What is this? Yep. Pick that up. That's a heal potion. Oh, that's mine. Yeah.
Take that. Whoops. There's a resin here, but it's so. Oh no, it's going to be way too hard.
I can try. Is that a red bat too? Okay. Um, what should I do now? You, you should probably try to
find him. I think the walls closing in from the West. Oh yeah. You want to, uh, Alex, you want to
try to get to the sort of middle of bottom right of the circle. Are you okay over there? I'm being
shot at by your friends. I think. Oh yeah. I ran past them. Yeah. They're evil. Oh no, this is an
evil mob. Yeah. Oh, I'm screwed. Red. If the, if the skeleton is red or the monster is red,
it means they're an elite version and they're, they're horrible. Okay. Yeah. I'm dead guys.
Oh, you guys want to backseat game me? You're the one with the kills. Yeah, but I have no concept
of space or location other than there's apparently a wall here. Yeah. It's essentially what you're
looking for right now, Alex, is you're just trying to get out. So you're looking for a blue podium,
a blue podium. It's going to go and it's, it's kind of textured. Oh, Minecraft. It's textured.
So you'll know what it looks. It's blue, bright blue. Red goes to a different dungeon. So you
don't want to go to the red one. Blue. You're looking for that's a trap, right? That's a trap.
Yeah. Don't go there. Okay. But if the only other way to go, there's like three guys, I think you'll
live. No, no, you'll be fine. Yeah. If you just play it slow here. Well, yeah, play it slow and
just, you're just looking for a portal. There's at least three here somewhere in the circle. So
there's like three minutes left in the match. Yeah. Bottom right. Okay. You are just trying
to hear that. Yeah. Where's that coming from? That's that's that direction. That is a portal
coming up through the ground. It could be a red one though. I think it's a red one because you
can see the kill feed pop up, right? It's a three down portal portal. It's a red one. I think so.
This game sucks. Oh, yeah. Crouch here. Crouch. Yeah. Oh, right. Forgot. Yeah. This stuff that
shoots out of the walls. And it's almost impossible to tell. So when you're going through a little
hallway like this crouch, there's damage coming from nowhere. Okay. Is it it's okay to be like
walking around with a torch, right? Like, yeah. I mean, you're just trying to find a way out right
now and try to leave with whatever you picked up. Listen, I hear footsteps to my left. I think it's
behind you. There's another one. Did you hear that? Like, are you quieter when you're crouching? Like
in Tarkov? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Are these invisible walls? Like, what is this? Yeah. You hit him five
times. Don't tell him. Can I sacrifice you to the great old ones? There it is. You need that. Yep.
Hitty. And just get out of here. It's the second it comes up. Well, the answer to that question
is no. How is he better than us? Hey, we're out. Easy game. I understand what the problem is.
Here's the thing. I was a distraction, right? So if I didn't stand in that trap, then they may
have been like, oh shit, like we got somebody and then they killed me and they were just really not
prepared for the next part. I claim about 20% of that victory. Well, I retired Carl and now I'm on,
I couldn't get the other names. I'm on Tom Guy Peter. It's my Ranger. Your names are like,
they're awesome. Can I show you my wizard? Yeah. There. Ice and frost. And fire. And, you know,
everything else. Et cetera, et cetera. All right. So, you understand the game now. You get it. Now
we're going to try as hard as we can now. Yeah, we were just acting for that one. But important,
folk, we have to make sure that he understands this. You just, did you have, do you have anything,
you have like stuff in your inventory right now? Yeah. Oh yeah. I need to put in stash, huh? Or
sell it. Because if you picked up anything that's a chalice or a- Oh yeah. You go to merchants and
like the chalice stuff is the collector. Yeah. So- What did you say was fast transfer hotkey?
Is it like a- Oh, shift click is to go from wherever you want to the
sell window and shift right click puts it in your stash. Ah, shift right click. I was trying to
shift left click. So if you have any of those little trinkets, you want to sell them because
that's the way you make gold. That's how you, you sell anything to make money. It's one of the only
ways, unless you find it or- Okay. I don't want you guys to have to like wait longer. So I'll just
do the selling stuff. Oh, I'm fine. No, we're good. We're good. Jeremy, you got money, right?
I've got, yeah, I got money. Go to the goblin merchant. Um, but hold on. I, I'm going to give
you some guilt armor. If, uh, I stole this from somebody and I have to get rid of it. So I'm going
to put the sin on you now. What is it? What kind of armor is it? It's purple, uh, ranger armor.
Okay. Thank you. Yeah. I stole it from somebody and I'm just going to, I'm just moving the guilt
to you. Okay. Are you okay with that? Yes. All right, cool. Yeah, that's cool. Thank you. Okay.
I'm going to actually, I'm going to, I'm going to have a good sword this time. I dare you to gamble
one time. Okay. At the goblin merchant. Does he have anything for sale for you? Yeah, he's got like
gloves. Uh, I'll try gloves. Do it. I'm not doing that ever again. Oh, okay. Well, I'm ready. Sorry.
I got like a fucking, like default gloves. Poke, you said that it was going to be awesome. There's
a chance. Okay. Hold on. So Jim's ceremonial, anything blue? Blue is, is very good. I mean,
no, no, no, no, sorry. Blue background. That's like, that's like vendor trash. That's stuff you
can wear. Red background. Like, uh, Jim rings, bangles, goblets, uh, candle holders. Yeah,
that's the collector. Yeah. The collector, the vendors are spread out in a way where like the,
you have to sell the gear that would sell to that person. So you can't sell a sword to the guy that
takes, um, trinkets. It's, uh, okay. Yeah. You have to do it into the right vendor. It'll be like,
Oh, that vendor doesn't want that item. All right. How do you get rid of like actual trash?
Just throw it down at the ground. Um, at the end of the, at the beginning of the match.
Okay. Like if it's, if it's like a gray that is not even worth anything, then you just throw it
away. You can even sell it to, and it'll just be sell for zero. All right, let's do it. Okay.
Got something cool for you. Yay. Hey, if you lose it, I'm going to be pissed off by the way.
Okay. I'm sorry. I'm already sorry. I'm always sorry. All right, let's go. I brought a decent
weapon this time, so I don't want to, I don't want to blow it. Please get gold bags from the treasure.
No, I want to, I want it out. I like looking at the coins. Uh, once again,
I brought no bandages, no potions. I think I'll just take them from your dead body again.
We worked last time, so that's a good tried and true strap. All right, poke.
Yo, I got this for you. Look at that. Oh, wait, that's really good. Wow. Don't, don't pick that
up. Don't pick that up either. It's my old self. All right. Begin the looting. So just break ship
break, whatever you can break, touch, whatever you can touch, open up, whatever you can open
the game is, is just pick up everything. Okay. So I'm going to have to, oh, Barians and doors is
like an awful combo. Yeah. Yeah. No, it's just the weapon you, once you get a felling axe.
Okay. That's like the best weapon. It's like two zombies, three zombies. Yeah. Some of these,
some rooms are actually awful. So sometimes they're best to be avoided. We should go straight here.
We should go straight here. Yeah. I've started down there plenty of times and you just die.
It just sucks being down there. Oh, this is the worst place. Who can break doors?
Barbarians. You can eventually, I think you can eventually. But yeah, even like the basic enemies
are terrifying to me right now. As they should be. Go through here. We go here. That's where we came
from. Yeah. But we go down. Is it, is it good to like shut doors behind you or? Yeah. Usually.
Yeah. Oh, careful poke. This guy farts. Oh yeah. He sure does. Is it poison or does it hurt?
It just hurts when you're in it. That's good. At least I almost just took that in the face.
Oh, I hear somebody. I'm, I'm being overly cautious right now. Above, above, above.
Is there somebody in here? I heard somebody. Who's in there? Thank you. Good job. Well done team.
Ooh. All right. Good call. Good call. Okay. So right click is pretty good in these like narrow
hallways, I guess. Oh, I hear him. I hear him. Yeah. Wizard. What do you guys, what do you guys
want to do? I don't know. I'm kind of just like charging unless you guys have stuff to lose that
run away. Are they up or down? They're up. They're up. Okay. Up mid I think. We can, we can go across
this. Go for it. Straight ahead behind this big pillar. Uh, west, west, west. Yep. Okay. Are you
guys friendly? He's doing a fireball. Uh oh. I think the answer is no. You guys want to trade?
There's people up top though as well. You guys want to trade? Ooh, that hurt. Yeah, that stung.
Yeah. Watch out. Fireballs hurt. Nice. Got one. One more down here. One guy. Nice. Got two. Got one guy.
There's missiles coming in from the east. I'm just trying to run around them. I'm going up top.
I stepped on them. Oh nice. Is there fall damage? Nope. No. All right. That was pretty good. Pretty
good. One guy, one guy was hiding in this room. He died. Oh, he died? He just died and I killed him.
No, that's so sad. Oh shit. They had a lot of stuff. All right. We're gonna, all right. I'm not
gonna. A lot of dead bodies over here. I'm gonna switch those. Hold on. There's like that, there's
blue axes and shit. Yeah. Can I take the potions? Yeah. So like the best stat on a weapon or anything
is like all attributes. That's like the god stat. That's like the plus one to all skills for Diablo
2, right? Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Um, so like just leave white weapons or just something's better than
nothing, I guess? Something is always better than nothing, but if you have, if your inventory is
full, then you start dropping, you know, grays and all that shit. Trinkets are always worth holding,
but if you, if you, if you could fit more chalices in your backpack, get rid of like a white weapon,
right? Yeah. I don't pick up the gray stuff. Usually. All right. I am kind of hurt, but we
should probably start to. I'm gonna drop some heals right here. Actually I'll use a campfire.
That's a good idea. Right here. Oh, this is a great time to explain a new mechanic.
They, they, they buffed campfires, didn't they? Yeah. All right. Come here fast and you press F on
it and it heals you. Oh, sweet. What a beautiful little camping spot. This is just wait till
somebody just buries an ax in the back of your head while you're doing this. Okay. What's the
worst thing that could happen to us right then? Like, is there, is there like a AOE that would
one shot? I mean, a barbarian with a felling ax, just turning the corner and hitting you once in
the head. Yeah. Or like a geared mage fireballs. All right. Watch out for this, uh, like, uh,
E you can use these right here or use a, use a health pot. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, you guys hear that?
Yep. Skeleton up here. I feel like somebody's skeleton here. Nice. Ooh. Who could even use
this right now? Blue quarterstaff plus one to all attributes. Maybe it's Alex. Maybe. Oh,
I don't know what any one, any one of you on this, uh, skeleton. Let's take a look at this. Let me
see. It's a quarterstaff. So it's kind of, they're really, really strong, but they're kind of weird
to use. Right. Yeah. I haven't really tried it. I heard something over back by me. Sounded
mechanical. Yeah. It might be a skeleton archer, but let's see. Um, like one 35 just like Diablo
bat chest. Hey, it's Alex. Do you remember, do you remember Diablo two? Oh, Diablo two. You're
going to freaking love this game. I remember the greatest ARPG that's ever been made and never been
duplicated except by the remaster Diablo two. I loved it too. It's probably one of the best games
of all time. The blue portal. Ooh. All right. Who wants to get out of here? Oh, you got the, that
purple and, but Alex, what do you got? Um, my best is a, the blue quarterstaff and a green Marauder
outfit. And that's it. I just hover near it. Wait for three. Yeah. You should definitely take it
though, because you, you, you probably have the least amount of stuff and money. Are you saying
I'm poor? I, yeah, I would definitely take it. You should just get out of here. Why, why the lights
off here? Hey, wait, wait, wait. Actually, before you go there, like just honestly, like just take
all this. Oh dude, money. Just take everything and then get out, get the hell out of here. You
know what? Fucking take this too. You know what? Just take everything. I don't have that much
space. Just fucking take everything I want. Go, go, get out of here. Hurry. Oh, someone's here. Hey,
are you friendly? You gotta, you gotta get out of here. I'm going. Hey, we can talk. I'm not gonna
hurt you. People are getting naked in here. I could have killed you right there. I'm friendly, man. Hey,
what's up? What's going on? Hey, watch out. Watch out for the trap, man. Watch out. There's a trap
here. I want the goblet. Someone's coming. This game is crazy, man. Did you not put any of your
armor back on? No. Okay. Who's taking it? I, it should be you. I have literally nothing.
I gave everything to italics and he left. No. No? We find two. We find two? No, you know,
you get out of here. Right here, right here. Are you good? Did you make it? No, I'm gonna find one.
No, no, you have way better stuff than I do. I threw all my stuff to italics. I'm already,
I'm already there. All right, I'm going in. Oh, there's a, I didn't realize there was actually
like a kill feed. Oh, there's one down the hall. Oak, you have to survive with the guilt armor.
That's true. He's eating beef jerky. Oh, damn. Oh, that was close. Well, that was fun, though.
I have a lot of weapons. I want to get rid of it. Hey, that was guilt armor anyways. Hey, I'm,
I'm two for two, but that's only because you let me go this time. So now honestly, being able to
leave and make a little bit of money is just, you can buy potions and ban it. You, you're going to
need it. Stash is coming together here. Yep. Can you, uh, sell the merchants directly from the stash?
I don't know. Oh yeah. You can sell, you don't have to put it in your stash. You can just sell
it from your bag too. Yeah. But like, if you have stuff in your stash, can you sell from that?
Yeah, you can. Well, you, you can just sell right from your stash. I didn't know that. That's cool.
You mean just like from the stash window or no? You have to like actually be in the merchant window.
I meant like, uh, be in the merchant window, but stash open. Yeah. On the right side, you can see
little stash button. Oh yeah. You can play stuff in stash. Blue throwing axes. Is that even worth,
like you can't, can you recover thrown weapons? Nope. They are, they are just a consumable,
but they're very, very good if you get good ones. All right. I'm good to just to rock back in when
you guys are ready. I'm in. Okay. One second. Should I, should I like buy, um, like heal potion
or anything? It's good practice to have and don't get scammed because there is, there's two versions
that come in batches of three. One is insanely expensive for not very much more healing. That's
only due to that if you're very wealthy, but like the, the cheaper one that's three is usually good
to have. Oh, what perk do you have E? Um, I just got level two. So can I pick a perk? Yeah. Go to,
go to class and Perk and Skill. So 18 gold for the three stack is good, uh, potions? Uh, yeah. It's
not bad. It's always a good practice to have three of the default potion and three bandages if you
can afford it. Okay. So, um, I'm on the perk page. Yeah. You go to perk and skill and then you,
you see that available perk you have, or the one perk you have on? Oh yeah. Two-handed weapon
expert. Yeah. Maybe you should just get the, um, the one that lets you break through walls and shit.
I like that one. That's like the best perk in my opinion. Uh, smash unreinforced doors and containers
and defeat blocks and parries. Yeah. You should get that one. Just get that one. And I'm going to
bring you, I'm going to bring you a, just a, just a normal axe. You'll have a lot more fun with it.
Yeah. Barbarian with the axe is, uh, barbarian with an axe is disgusting. It's fun just bopping
people in the head with, um, two shots. Especially if you get like a purple
felling axe or something. It's just, you can kill somebody in one hit. I got him a white one for now.
Yep. So you can have what, like four perks at a time at level 15? Yeah. Okay. Oh, and you should,
I'm just the question asker on the, I am like the audience POV. Like people, people are like tuning
into the streams and be like, I don't know what this game is. And I'm them. I'm just asking questions
for them. Hey, you have to learn somewhere. You should replace your second ability with the
battle shout one or the one that like, uh, fears everything. That one is really good.
You keep the one that gives you strength and the one that gives you the fear. Uh,
7.5 meter radius physical damage. Yeah. That one, that one's bussing. It's super good.
Yeah. That one, it's like a stun almost essentially. Yeah. You just walk in a room
and anything that hits you, like the mobs, you just stop them. It's really good. Okay. I'm ready.
Is war cry any good? Uh, the max HP buff? Uh, I think the ability, I think the attack bar one's
better. Yeah. The one that gives you strength is good. Okay. All right. Let's go. And by the way,
to all the stream snipers, three, two, one, let's go for it. That's very kind of you. Yeah. So you
said there's like three maps right now in the demo. There's a solo map. There's a team map. And then
is the high roller map a different map or is that the same as the regular map, but just harder?
Yeah. The same as, uh, the same one, but harder. I'm willing to pay for it if we want to do it.
We should do it. It's fun. It's hard. Okay. Yeah. We should do it. All right. Here's your acts.
Yo, did this acts like, Oh, wait, you, you got out. Oh no. Wait, what? I forgot. You didn't die.
Yeah. I didn't die. Yeah. But just try that one. You'll love it. But what about the greens?
See what you like. Honestly, like swings down, not side to side. So it's easier. It's so much
better that, Oh, yeah. Yeah. Oh no. You're not using the acts for the felling one. The felling
one is like the felling one. Yeah. Yeah. It's like, I give you, I give you a felling acts.
That one is like, this is what I just picked up off the ground. Oh, I just got hit by that.
Shit. I didn't give you a, wait, what is it? This is the acts that I was dropped.
This apparently I gave you the wrong battle. Like you're, you just tried to like scam me,
like gaslighting you beautiful acts. I'll give it to you for the little price of a hundred gold.
It's a felling acts. Did I really buy a white ass? Wait, you bought, you bought that? No, no, no.
It was like 20 bucks. Oh, it's that bad. Oh, I'm so sorry. That's okay. Oh, we got people. Oh,
people up there. Um, let me squeeze in here and fart people on top of us. And there's a,
there's an archer. There's a, there's multiple skeleton archers and they're awful. They don't
miss. And the regular archer shooting. And the trick is you crouch before they hit you.
I just hold the shield up like archers coming down and archers trying to shoot me.
Oh, this, oh, the skeleton archer. Yeah. There's an archer up top on the, on the balcony though.
Yeah. He ran away. He closed the door. Nice. Good. So there, there are like cleaves in this game,
right? Yeah. You can, yeah, you can, you can swing and hit everything. Okay. I'm, I'm asking more
for friendly fire than for anything else. Yeah. You can, you can hit people with a huge, it's like
180 degrees in front of you essentially if you hold it down. Oops. These little bats, these bats
are my favorite to kill because they drop, uh, amulets and stuff. I hear arrows. Oh, this is
yours. Uh, there is a green, uh, armor here. Resourcefulness. Who should, who strength and
resourcefulness? Uh, Alex, you should take these. These are green. They got strength and resourcefulness
on them. I'm going to drop them for you over here. Probably best in your hands. Okay. On the ground
in front of me. Got them. Yeah. The hardest part right now is just learning like weapon range
and, uh, where the tip of the, you know, a lot of random shit. I found one for you.
What do you got? Look at that. Head down, ass up. Everybody loot. Same time. Let's go. Oh,
shit. Yeah. Hey, E. Hey, what up? Hey, E. Hey, what up? Oh, and here, uh, German for your head,
your haircut. Oh, wow. A warm all. Does that mean my haircut's bad? Talk later. Is this
your haircut? So there's like a three attack progression for every weapon. Yeah. Everything
has a three chain. Uh, I think so. When do you queue up the second swing? I know it's just stupid.
Uh, hold it. Baby questions. You just hold it. If it's not in a row, it will not chain together.
Okay. So you could do click and then click, or you could just hold. Holding is probably a little
easier because then you can let it go when you don't want to swing it third time. This campfire
for us. I'm a campfire for us. Why not? So what did they change with the campfire? This heals more
or something. I think it's just longer. Oh, come over here. Yeah, I'm coming. Movement.
Oh, movement. Oh, shit. Behind me. Behind me. Ah. Up the stairs as well. Stairs. Behind you.
Folk behind you. Okay. I'm running back a little bit. They flanked us. Yeah, they did. They come
through. They come through. Oh, that hurt. Oh, I almost just hit you guys. He's gotta be low.
Oh, the archer got me. The archer got me. That, that, the, the, the two hitters probably low.
Fighters probably low. He's coming in with a peeling potion. I'm almost dead. Yeah. I can't
hit shit with this mall. I'm so afraid of that archer. This is so Scott. The archer will kill,
the archer will kill. Yo. Oh, I thought I killed him. Fuck. I can't hit. The range on this mall is
dog shit. Yeah. Oh my God. I had healing potions in my fucking inventory. I didn't even, I forgot
I bought them. I thought, oh shit. I'm an idiot. Don't even blame yourself. The mall is just like
the axe. I'll buy you one right now. I got you a felling axe. Okay. I had every swing. I had six
potions and I didn't even drink one. I did drink a potion, but they heal like 10%. Hey, we're just
warming up. We're warming up. Come on. That was my first death in this game. You know what? You know
what it is? A lot of times I don't buy anything because I go, no, no, no, no, no. I don't want to
fucking lose it. I'm not buying shit. I'm just going for it. And then when you actually do buy shit,
it's, you just forget that you did that. Okay. I'm going to remember, I'm buying it. I'm buying it
right now. This is like fighting in a dream. You're like stuck in quicksand. You can't move.
Everything's heavy. Shit. I take the L on that one. I could have fucking healed. No, no, no, no,
I tricked us with the food. I was working for them. Bye. You know what? I don't even care if I lose
it. I'm bringing out the big, I'm bringing out the big gun. How's the, um, the quarterstaff?
Quarterstaff is fun to use. It's just, it has like a swing down, then you swing the bottom part up.
So it has like a swing down animation, then like a swing up animation. All right. Put,
put a value on like just the average green or blue or like higher quality in terms of like gold.
Blues are worth a lot more than, than greens, I would say. Like you talk about like, like how
much it, like to sell it. Yeah. Like, uh, like whether or not you want to, ooh, should I go
win with this and risk losing it? Like what's, what's the gold value of? I mean, the blues are
gonna, they, they can carry you through a run. If you have like a good blue weapon or like a good
three or four blues on for equipment, you're going to take a lot less damage. Yeah. But if you like
die with one, how much money did you lose? Oh, like maybe 40 gold, 30 gold for like a couple of
items. Maybe they sell for like what? 10 to 20, a lot of times 15. Okay. I got you a weapon. Okay.
I got you weapon E. It's good. Sick. All right. I'm coming in with my purple sword. I got a purple
and I am not around this time. I am so angry. Oh, get, get pissed off. Get angry. Cause this is how
we're going to, I'm so mad. I'm ready. You don't sound that mad to me. I don't know if we can do
it. I'm buying some potions. Get angry. I'm tense. How do you swap between, um, number four? Uh,
you just hit four. All right. I'm ready. I'm going to, if I lose my purple, I lose my purple boat.
I'm not going to, cause we're going to destroy. I'm going to find you purples. We're going to
find purples. I'm just glad I haven't killed either of you yet. Outside of not killing the
guys who killed you first. Hey, what'd you say? Did you hear the voice in the loading screen?
I was at you. Yeah. Oh, I like how you can still talk in the loading screen like a little bit.
All right. I'm trying as hard as I can now. You say you brought a purple in.
I have a purple weapon. I can kill Mo. If I hit somebody in the head, I can kill them in one or
two hits. All right. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Yeah. Boom. Boom. Now that attack
animation is good as hell. Heck hell. Try it out. Yep. Uh, poke. I, I, you might, you probably
didn't know. I, I don't really, like if you're going to say like a swear or something, can you
say like, like a crap or, Oh, I know. I was pretending I couldn't. Oh, that stinks. Like you
should have, I don't know. I just, maybe next time just be better about it if you can. Oh,
okay. Sorry about that. Yeah. It's all right. Just, you know, so there's, you know, is the
felling acts like a single attack? Yeah. Okay. Just hit their heads. Yep. Click on heads. Oh,
fountain of speed. Yeah. I don't want to hit you with this. So this just makes you run faster,
right? What does fountain of speed? Yeah, it does. You should probably take this shit then.
Yeah. Um, Alex, you take grief. Oh, me trying protection. I'll take this. Oh, that,
what am I supposed to take this little fountain? Oh, that's my, yeah, the speed, the speed fountain
because it makes you run faster. You should take that. I am slow as shit. What do you think we
should go this way? I guess so. Should I just be using abilities more often? Like you want to run
in the middle there right there and use your E, go in the middle there, use your E or your other Q
or your, your other one. Oh, people there, people across. Yep. Mage behind me. Mage. Yep. He needs
like one hit. Got one. Got one. This guy's really low running away. Oh, there's a guy, 195. Oh,
that's, you do play those games. Oh my God. Thank you for saying that. Yeah. He's like, he's not,
he's really hurt. I got him. I got him. He's dead. Okay. Let's go. Good shit guys. All right. I
didn't kill shit, but I got one call out. So I'll take the assist. Anybody need health? Uh,
I can. Hey, we won that fight. Yeah, it was good. All right. Good fight. Good fight. Nice job.
Listen, I'm at a disadvantage. I have to do a new weapon every game. So I'm learning every single,
uh, I think you're doing great. Do you want some, uh, some advantages or healing potions to Alex?
Uh, I got two left and there's three on this guy. Yeah. You should take, you should take one.
Yeah. You always want to be topped off. Yeah. You want to be close to like 90%
can be because it's so easy to die from like one hit in the head that if you could survive too,
then you might kill the other person bandages versus potions. Just bandages are small potions.
Basically. Yeah. Just use a potion and then use a bandage on after that. I got a campfire as well.
We need it also potion of protection. Like these right here, I'm dropping one. You always want to
pop that before a fight. It's like, it's really, really helpful. Uh, there's a tracker box just
30. Oh, fine. Oh yeah. It's two, two people. We both just did the same thing. Trying to throw
axes. Okay. There he goes. His buddy's over here somewhere at a 15 down the hall. West is the other
one. Yep. He's got a potion. I killed this guy. Yep. This guy's just way throwing his old stuff.
Careful. Uh, don't engage too much, which we're all here cause he could just hit you once in the head.
He's got that potion. Nice. Oh, that's barely. Mine came down a half second before his.
I'm gonna use a campfire right here. Okay. Yeah. For you guys. Now it's good to take them both.
Use your heals guys. These are solo. I just drank one. Drank one bandaging. Drop that health pot for
you too. That's two different groups. We're doing all right. We are rolling right now. We are rolling
them. I killed the archer too. Grab that potion. Yep. Yeah. You got the archer too. That's huge.
Getting skunked off these potions right now. I dropped another health pot for you guys.
Oh my God. This morning star. No cleric though. Make sure you guys fully heal and then move
forward. I'm just trying to take a shoot on this. There's a pendant on them too. There's a good
pendant on them. Oh, physical healing. Cool. I'll take it. All right. I got the killing blow. I
don't have any, I'm taking the loot. Yeah. Take as much of that as you want. Go crazy. I'm just
kidding. I don't, I don't really care. We gotta go crazy. Go crazy man. We gotta move too. We gotta
move. Okay. Those are good. Those are good. Helmet. Good. Circles coming. Also as a barbarian,
you have these like throwing axes. Yeah. They're really good. It slows them too. It's really good.
Did you get the morning star off that person? Uh. I'm gonna. Oh, you got it? Yeah. No,
just sell it. You can just sell it. All right. Let's move. All right. Oil lanterns explode.
Oil lanterns sell for a shit load of money by the way. Yeah, I sell them. It's good money.
They sell for like 25 gold each. Can't move. I am. I think I've bugged my character.
What's wrong? Never mind. Never mind. Never mind. There's an F to cancel so you don't throw.
Oh yeah. You have to like. You can't like switch weapons or do anything else. The game is a little
buggy. Sometimes you'll swing and you won't swing and sometimes you'll just keep swinging for no
reason. Yeah. Happens to me a lot. We should probably start to look for a way out. Like we
should probably generally try to get out of here. Yeah. It should be popping up now. Kind of good.
Oh, shoes for you if you want those shoes. Oh shit. Those are good.
Should go this way. Okay. It's sneak to the right here. Don't do aggro.
Yeah. This room is hell. Yep. Yeah. This room seriously is where it's like so many people die.
That Wraith that that's like a boss. Yeah. I see green eye entities. Yep. That's a more confidence
room. I don't know if we have that at the moment. I got to get used to the range on these.
This Y hander really was like training weights in terms of reach. Yeah. Watch out through the
hole here on the right. Oh my God. I'm sad. I don't want to swing because it's a horizontal
swing and I will hit one of you in the head with this insanely powerful weapon. Yeah.
I would feel so awful about it. So I'm just not going to do it. It'd be funny though.
It would. I would be very, very funny. All right. Shit's on his weight around here.
Spun up soon. Oh, be careful here. Whoa. What was that? What happened? What happened?
You got hit in the back by the pendulum. Oh, I thought there were only two.
Oh, shit. What the fuck is happening? I thought it was only three heels. I got heels. I think
I thought it was three. I didn't even know the other one was moving.
I've never seen four. I've only seen three. Oh, God. Escape at the end of it.
There's one there. Hey, hey, boys. I'm just saying I'm fucking out of here. Yeah, go for it.
Here, take the shit. I'll open it for you. Appreciate it. All right. Yeah. Here's something else.
Good luck. Have fun. We should be able to find one right here.
Just in case there's a fight. I just want to make sure. All right. Good luck. Be careful here.
All right. Take it before I do. Yeah. I've dropped those on the ground.
I dropped healing on the ground for you. Oh, there's three next to me. Oh, nice. Yeah.
Get out, get out, get out. Oh, nice. One of them's slightly more dangerous. I'll take the
I'll take the dangerous one already. Hell yeah. That was a good one. That's a clean one. Nice.
Good job, guys. Oh, yeah. And we killed like two groups also when we got looted.
Yeah, that worked out pretty well. I feel good about that one. Okay. Since we're cocky as hell,
we should do a high roller for fun. All right. Yeah. No, no, no, no, no. It's very scary.
Yeah. So whatever, the ship wipes in two days anyway. Yeah. For just let's go to labs.
Do we all have to pay for it? It's a hundred. So collect a hundred, get a lot of heals,
just get a lot of the cheap heals, get the healing potions and the alchemist, the bandages. Okay.
We got this. Okay. All right. Let's get scary. It's going to be scary. Yeah. Let's take a second.
Make sure you got all your shit or you got what you want. We'll go for it. Okay. Let me do this.
I just wanted to say that thanks to you, I have a seventy five percent survival
rate in this game, which I think is you're really going to mess up our matchmaking.
I don't think there even is matchmaking. Cool. All right. So, okay. So collector is all the
goblets and stuff. I don't even know who all the merchants are and buy a shitload of potions.
Oh, how much would you how much should we get? How many stacks of potions like three? I think
I'm going to fill an entire slot with potions. Oh, I can't buy that. Any of you guys need gloves?
I don't have a hundred gold yet, but hold on. If you sell everything, I'm working on it.
Yeah. I'm buying this whole stock of potions. Is that stupid? The thing was I'm so poor that
I spent thirty six gold just on like heals in the last two counters. We can do one more normal
if you want. I think I'm ready for it. Let's let's go. Let's do a high roll. Let's do it.
By the way, oil lanterns really do sell for twenty. I don't know why they sell for so much.
That's crazy. How do you stack? Is it like a is it like a wallet? Yes. You buy the gold coin
purses and then go. Oh, of course. So should I just be selling like all the extra armor and weapons
and stuff vendor or like should I save those for player market or what? Anything that you. Yeah.
Anything that you get that's like blue or better, especially if it's purple,
if it's for the wrong class. I mean, trading it is how you I mean, selling it was probably
not a great idea because you can just trade it to another player. But I mean, at this stage in the
demo, I would just just sell everything and keep some stuff. If you have another character you
want to play with, then you can do sort of the oh, I'm going to go in a game and drop this on
the ground. Please give it to my ranger when I make it right. But I haven't done any trading or
anything. I'm just kind of playing. I am going to do this, though. I gambled again. You said oil
lanterns are pretty good to sell. Yep. They were twenty three. Who's the who's the weapon guy?
The weapon guy. OK. Yeah. OK. I am. OK. I am ready to try this hard mode.
Got a ton of heels. I got a full set of gear. It's pretty good stuff. I think I'm ready. All
right. I'm ready. How do you get the high roller ticket or what do you have to do to get in? I
think I just have to pay for it. Oh, OK. So it's like, are we ready to fight robots? We all take
a hundred. Everybody has to pay. Do you have a hundred gold? I just got. Yeah, I just traded up
to it. How about this? We die. If we die, we go into the normal with nothing and go zero to hero.
Yeah, that's good. I think I have like one hundred and thirty eight gold and some silver. Perfect.
All right, let's do it. You ready? Everybody get your money. Get you get your wallet out.
We're splitting this check three ways. OK, if you bring a second weapon, does that like weigh you
down like you're slower? I think it's only if you've equipped. OK, so like a primary secondary is
fine to have. Yeah, if you have primaries, but I just make sure it's not equipped. If you don't
remind me to ignore you earlier, I had to go pee, but I didn't want to say I want to have to go pee.
You know what I'm saying? When you ignored me, when did you ignore me? Yeah, I didn't. I'm so sorry.
You didn't do it. You didn't do anything in this stream. What do you call it? I'm ready.
You don't have to apologize for anything. You didn't do anything wrong. All right. You ready?
I won't do it again. I just read your message. Yeah, whatever you're doing. Yeah. What?
All right. I'm president. Oh, here we go. So like with the felling axe, I feel like I have
to get danger close to anything to hit. Kind of. But it hits the head really hard, though. OK.
You know what I'm saying? Yeah, just got to click on the head faster. But how do we close the gap
when they're faster than me? So there's like, I rebind my holster to like mouse button.
That's a good idea. I just, I holster all the time when I'm running to people. And if you jump
and holster in the air, you like, there's like some tech to it. You know what I'm saying? Yeah,
yeah. Like CS, CS go jumping. Oh, we got, we got gambler. Yeah, yeah, yeah. All right. So we got,
we got some, we got gambler. If only, if one of us survives, people are betting on it. All right.
Let's see. Only one of us has to survive this. Good luck, believers and non-believers, except
non-believers, you fucked up. I'm just saying you fucked up. I'm a high roller. I didn't get it in
time. Oh, they heard that. Oh, they did. Yeah, they heard nothing but, oh fuck. I don't even have a
torso piece. I'm, I'm, I'm taking this to the next level here. So is this a different map poke or is
this the same one, but just everything's harder? There's a chance to get a Colosseum map, but
usually it's the same map. Okay. Um, the rebind didn't work. Okay. No, listen, listen, listen. Oh
God, every monster moves faster and they're scary. What? Oh my God. It does move so fast. I missed.
Okay. We did that. That was so fast. Ooh. Oh my God. I had a ring. The loot is a lot better. Wow.
All right. This is cool. All right. I'm just going to follow you. Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay. Okay. Okay. I learned this today. Yeah. Listen, there's a way to kill this boss without
taking damage. So I'm going to try it. Okay. Oh, I'm going this way. I'm going this way. Wish me luck.
High roller. Let's go without taking any damage. Oh, people across. They're coming. Get the, get
out of here, buddy. Are you friendly? Oh, okay. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Oh,
nevermind. Run, run, run. This guy aggroed the whole world. Oh, you do. You aggroed everything.
What are you doing? We're high rollers. In this door. Oh my God. He just brought everything over
here. Close them out. Close, close, close, close, close. State your name. We're good. We're good.
State your name. What's your, what's your name? Name is Ethan. I'm Ethan. Okay. Ethan, you look
like you got a lot of good shit. No, I'm, I came in here with grace. I came in here with grace.
Okay. All right. You can live. Hey, it's better to have four than three. Which one do you use?
Huh? Shout out the substream. Shout out the substream. It's for you. This is for you.
Oh, okay. Now I see his name. If Poke just couldn't take the shout out, he couldn't take like the
fucking shout out. No, no, no. I thought he was going to say something bad or something.
He's like, I got my moment. Oh, you thought, you thought he was going to just start screaming
wicked awful shit. Oh, that's true. All right. Yeah. You met. Yep. Yep. Which one's Jerma?
I was like, wait, what? That's true. That's true. I got scared. It's like, I don't know. I don't
know. Oh my God. Uh, you know what? Like, like good on you though. Like appreciate it looking
out. I'm sorry. You're looking out for us. That's, that's good. Sorry, Ethan. Yeah. He thought, he
thought you're going to scream a bunch of terrible things into the mic. The developer just messaged
me and said, we can't group up with four or so. All right. Hard jump. Uh huh. I missed it.
God damn it. I'm actually so fucking mad because I'm dead down here. Do not be like me. Make that
jump. I'll make it over. There's a boss following me. Yeah. Oh wait, you can jump up here. Other
players, other players coming across. No, they're not friendly. What do I go from here? I forget
this whole map. Uh, you gotta come back. We're friendly. We're friendly. Come. Who the fuck is
this guy? That's like, he's in the party with the guy you just said is friendly. All right. We're
good. Wait, is this your, are you all teammates? Who is this? Who are you? Yes. You a high roller?
I am your communion. Drink from me. Are you a high roller or are you, what are you? I'm like stuck.
Here comes the wall. What did he say? He said, I am your communion. Drink from me.
All right. Hey, you need to relax. Um, the wall. Yeah, we got to get out of here. We have to leave.
Jump past these guys. Ready? You're gonna. Oh Jesus. Oh God. We're not going that way.
Oh, you're not that way. I think I'm with you. No. Yep. We, we wrapped back around. Yeah. Okay.
We're good. We're good. Who's this guy? You're friendly. Okay. Like seven or eight friendlies
here. Yeah. It's the whole dungeon is friendly apparently. I feel bad for Ethan. That's, that
was so funny. All guys just looted up. I know just met six. Hey, why not? Oh, look at all these
heels. A lot of stuff here. All been looted. We should probably make our way towards the circle
though. Yeah. Watch out for this. Okay. All right. Watch out for the thing you said to watch out for
you. Yeah. I jumped it. I fucking, I'm an idiot. So if we find food and we don't know what it is,
are you guys going to test it to make sure it's not poisonous? I think there'll be people here.
There's a lot of people. We have like an entire Warcraft raid. I think we're going to be all right.
We have a whole five man Warcraft dungeon group. People's people coughing in here.
I can't breathe. That shit's making me choke. How long does it take to die in there? Like one. Oh
my God. It's chasing me. Okay. This is the way the developers intended the game to be played.
Actually kind of true. I hear fighting going on. We're good. Kill this archer. I'm starting to
forget who is friendly. We have to, there's too many people claiming to be friendly that I'm going
to turn around and kill somebody. If I had a Zwei hander, that's basically what I would do.
I would just do a big wide swing. Ow. So many fucking spiders. Uh oh. That guy is getting
chased by four different entities. Okay. We're good. We're good. Oh my God. I almost just hit you
twice. I don't know how. Thank you. Uh huh. I did something. Yeah. Just like loot up for sure.
Just pick up everything. Yeah. You guys did as much as you can. Even the boxes are like
barrels. I said, Hey, can you please do a world record bong hit? Um, no, I'm good. Not right now.
Actually, uh, talk to you. Take this shrine. We're okay. I'm here reporting. This is a power shrine.
You'll hit for way more. You did one earlier. Yeah. I mean, I already, I broke the world record
earlier. I have to do it again. Like shut up. Is it true that you swing faster if you duck in the
middle of a felling acts? Well, I don't know that speed. Oh, did you get the smash perk?
You can break walls and stuff. Yeah. Oh, you can break doors. I didn't tell you break a door
and you can break chests. Yeah. With the felling acts, even chests. Oh, bad guys. Uh, there's a
party in here, like a different party, like two parties. Actually, I'm shooting at them.
There's one to our left. Let's go. I think there's an invisible guy at like one 95 rogue. All right.
They're getting to be too many people around. I don't know who's friendly,
so just be aware of that. I don't know. You might die from, I might accidentally hit you.
Oh, is this the guy that has to play among us in every game? That's too hard of a decision.
Send your minions to fight these guys. Hey, go fight those people.
Hey, send your minions. I'm playing a necromancer. It's all fun and games until
there's only one portal for all nine of us. Yeah. When there's one portal left, I'm sorry,
but I'm just swinging this down there guys. It's right here. The bad guy. That's a bad guy.
Are you friendly? All right. Well, then it looks like you looks like you and I are going to have a
one V one of one of my minions. Oh no. Let me do this. Yeah. This guy had gear. Get him,
get him, kill him. I demand it right here. Right here. Guys, on this body right here.
Uh, come get this weapon. This guy right here. Oh my fucking God. Get this shit off my character.
This is my portal. Wait, is yours? Okay. Where's mine? The one there's a guy up there finding one
for you. Oh, okay. You go up there. I really don't have much shit. So if I die, it's all good.
You know, you need to make shit. No, you need to make some shit though. Yeah. But I haven't been
looting anything because there's nine people in our party. Uh, so it's like locusts. Just kill them
all. There's only red portals up here. It's only red portals. Uh, did they take the, oh no, we can't
go. No, there's one portal here. I got one here. Oh no, I got one here. Alex, be, be good. Uh,
I'm being chased by a mimic. I'm just leaving. I have to go in the red. I have to go in the red.
Oh, you went wait. I'm the last man standing. You have to get up here. Oh, you have to get
up here. Go on the red, go on the red, go on the red. It's all good. Yeah, but no, but it's,
you go to the next dungeon. Like you guys going to go to the next one. You're good. It's not,
you can make it. You might not. I'm one with the darkness. Oh shit. Oh, I'm sorry. You guys
gotta explain this shit before the critical moment. I thought there'd be more portals, but
that was unlucky. Well, to be fair on that round, there were like nine people.
It was kind of an interesting one. Is it time to watch poke clear this whole dungeon? No, I'm just
going to die. Oh, are you dead too? No, he's in the next dungeon. Oh, he took red and you took
blue. Yeah. I just left. I thought we were just leaving. Sorry. Poke is going to literally kill
the boss right now. No, I'm extracting or something. No, no, no. I honestly want to watch. Yeah. Oh,
I can't see anything guys. Smart. Smart. Somebody said, I swear poking through a blue portal. Yeah,
I thought you did leave poke. Oh my God. What the fuck is that? Is that a person that just ran
there? Someone ran there and died. Look at these strats. I took your portal. I did. Oh, I thought
you were just kind of, you just were gone. Oops. This is big brain. Yeah, it is. What do you have
for a bow? Let me see. That's pretty good. Oh, you can look at the inventory. Oh yeah. Hit tab. You
got some, you got some good shit in here poke. Yeah. I want to get out. Oh no. Has a reflective
shield. It hurts you. Did this standing on the light post is this is, this is working out really
well. So like, you're going to get out of here. No, it's infinite arrows, but you do have to reload.
Okay. I think if you play it safe, I think you actually will get out of here. I don't think,
I don't think anybody else is even in here or did anybody else take it? How can you take, can you
tell? Someone ran here and just died over there. Oh yeah, they did. So they might've dropped all
their shit from the last. Okay. You did the movie thing where you only hit the bars, you know,
like when the villain is shooting like an automatic weapon and the hero's running on
like a catwalk and every bullet just inexplicably sparks off of the side rail. That's what you just
did. Like and they're always putting their hands up kind of like that's somehow protecting them
from the bolts. Yeah. If you cover your face and you don't look at the sparks, you're safer. Yeah.
And then they're never, they're never firing back. They're always like running. You gotta outrun the
bullets. Yep. You just, you just run out, run no matter, even the bullets are hitting where you
are. Some good loot. What do you have? I'm gonna look at your inventory. So purples probably are
down here like crazy then in here in high roller, I would imagine. I like these pants. I just found
these frock or just see that. That's real. Plus two physical power plus two healing. Good for a
cleric. Oh no. What is that? It's a centaur. There are centaurs. Yeah. Good luck with that.
This is a, this is a boss room. I figured what boss this is. That looks like a boss. Yeah. I,
I don't know. I think you just get out of here. They try to run there. Open the door.
Is this the only avenue? Oh, nice. Do the skeletons fight the boss? I don't think so. No,
something killed the skeletons in there. Maybe they were summons. Hey, this is my buddy, Eric.
Oh, when you get far enough away, he unsummons the skeletons. He's like a necromancer. I enjoy
the lore of the necromancer who waits thousands of years for you to come through. But like when
you leave his section of the park, he, um, he gets sad. His animatronic turns off. Oh,
he has to go through his like Freddy Fazbear routine. Oh, okay. You can open the door in the
right. Right. It's like watching a, it's like watching a little movie. I love this. Yeah. Oh
God folk. They move so fast. You weren't kidding. Good shit in here. No, sorry for holding you guys
up, man. No, it's no, I like watching this. Yeah. I, I, this is good to see what's going on in here.
Oh my God. Oh man. Oh, no way. Is this going to work? My friend. Oh, that was a noble sacrifice.
That was a noble sacrifice. I got out. Nice. Nice. That's huge. Hey, I'll get you one of you guys
pants. That is really good. I like pants. I got a, I got a lot of blue. I got both of you pants.
You guys bring your pants at home. I got y'all pants. Yeah. Just leave your pants. Yeah. Already
done. I got a few. Can't believe I got out. High roller red place is really hard. No. Yeah. That's
awesome. You can, you got like a purple too. Yeah. You got the, you didn't get the best experience
though for high roller. You had to fight like 10 Ethan's 10 Ethan encounters. Let's call them
Ethan though. Yeah. An Ethan encounter did show up a few times here. Guys, no more Ethan's. Okay.
Yeah. When you show up, you show up with blood lust. Yeah. Fight us. No more Ethan's. Oh man.
All right. Let's go. Like if you're going to snipe, like try to scare us and make it like funny, like
try to kill us. Actually, Ethan was really funny because you thought Ethan was going to like scream
a bunch of bad words. So that was actually my moment. That was a pretty great moment. That was
a great moment. Okay. I assume we're not recueing for that because I am broke. Yeah. We'll go normal.
Yeah. We'll do a normal one. Uh, I'll bring you a gray felling X just for now. Okay. I'll take it.
It's so funny just how much that wiped out my bank account though. It's like, it was almost two rows,
like two, almost a whole, like a whole row. We'll get stuff down. I'm ready. All right. I just want
to make sure I don't, I just want to bring, you know, I don't want to bring anything good. All
right. I'm happy with this. I'm happy with that. I got my long sword. Shit looks pretty good. All
right. I'm good to go. Everybody ready? Yep. Should be good. Go. Oh shit. I forgot I was wearing this.
What do you have? I got nothing, dude. Oh shit. What do you mean? What do you have? That was,
you took me into the high roller in my fifth game. I lost it all. Hey, but now you have experience
there. We did a, we did a $100 max bat single spin. Yeah. And then accidentally ran into like
eight other people in the same slot. Yeah. There were like 10 people at the same slot machine,
all like reaching for the max bet. Ooh, trying to get a grasp of like armor ratings. Oh, I was
muted. Talking to myself. Sorry about that. Okay. I'm ready. Fuck. Wait. Unarmed the builds. Here,
someone take this pants. Shit. I didn't bring any torches. I'm an idiot. I got one. I got an extra
torch here. Oh, awesome. Uh, I'll take these pants. Why not? And I'll take that torch. All right.
Nice. Collect. All right. You can stand here in the middle and cleave them all. Wait, who or
anything? You gave me a felling axe. He can cleave. Maybe I can't. I don't know if you can. I can't
on my third swing. All right. Okay. There's been such a massive debate on this. How do you open a,
how do you do the lockpicking? It seems impossible. How would you, how do you do it? This one's not,
but it usually is. You press space when it hits it. It's okay. I thought it was like, like it's space.
Yeah, it's space. Is there a lockpicking minigame? Yeah. And does it have to be in the yellow or the
red? Yellow. I don't know what the red does. I'll be honest. Yeah. It says space on the screen. Yeah,
but it's on the, that shit's on the screen for like a 10th of a second. Is smashing the chest
better than picking them? Do you like lose any loot? Uh, no, it's better to kill. I think someone's
here. Oh, people here. Are you friendly? I thought we were. Oh, bad guys. I think he's scary. Okay.
Do we want to get out of this hallway? Is it a mage? It was a skeleton. Oh,
you'll see what I mean. Go look at them. Let's see. Okay. Nobody here. Something. You're right.
Nobody's here. Somebody here. Oh, people come through the door right now. Spider.
Oh, no. Yep. I'm watching her. Six. Oh, they're doing the same thing. Be careful. They're shooting
through the hole too. I hit him. I killed him. I killed him. What? Holy shit. Did you really?
Yeah. Who's this guy? I killed that guy. I killed that guy. Oh, there's another guy. What the fuck
is this? It's a rogue. Yes. One more guy. One more guy in here. He's low. He's low. He's low. He's low.
He ran to the right. Get it. Go get him. I don't know. Down. Maybe he closes his door. I'm pretty
sure we should loot. Hey, go loot. Go loot. So rogues can just be invisible. Yeah. It's like a
cool down. It's like for like 30 seconds. Yeah. You can't do it for that long. Okay. I didn't kill
the cleric. He got away. Dude, that skeleton skin is seriously complete. It's so that's OP.
You I just think that you're an enemy in the game. Yeah. That's crazy. Okay. Okay. Let's keep running.
Are we good? Yeah. If you got some potions. Good potions. Gloves right here. I just have a potion
of protection. That's it. Here. Take these two and use them. We use one at least. I also picked
up a campfire off one of them. I wonder where they are. I have no idea. You guys see anybody?
No. Yeah. That that person got away and it's really interesting that they did because if we
ever if we ever saw them that would be bad for them. It would be awful for them. Let's just keep
going then. Top it up. Must have been the wind. Just remember we'll let you live today. I put a
trap. We're just like waiting for the comedy moment to happen right now. You're just sitting there.
Just ready. He doesn't even have the voice on. He just like okay whatever. All I'm saying if
he gets in a portal at the end I'm gonna be pissed. He's gonna take our portal. That's what I mean.
We gotta get out this way. Where the hell are you guys going? I've been back and forth across
this guy's hallway. There's guys up there. I think we were just waiting to see what this guy was
gonna do. What are you doing over there? You're not gonna kill me. What are you doing? Oh you
killed me. That hurt a lot. I'm dead. I just killed you. Oh I'm dead but I got three hits on
him. Uh oh. Wait the friend. Where's the friend? The cleric friend. Where's the cleric friend?
Where's the cleric friend? I didn't know that does that. What was that? Oh Jerm I'm so sorry
you walked into my bullet. That was so. No dude don't worry about it. I'm an idiot. I got hit.
No it was me. Damn it. As long as it was funny. And hey why don't we spectate our um cleric friend?
Well. This is them right here right? Why indeed. Where are they? Sorry. No dude this game is
fucking a mess. Yeah it's all good. I was gonna die anyways. I was gonna take one more hit and
I was gonna die anyways. I'm just glad you killed him before I killed him. I love how you went to
punch him in the face though. That was funny. Your last dying wish was to just punch in the face.
That cleric we saved should have helped us. I don't know where they went. He just maybe he
took an opportunity. He's probably not even. That's narrative set up and payoff. That person's
probably not even on voice chat like you said and they just probably like oh my god three people.
They're letting me live. And then just kind of went on with their day. You save a guy in act one
he doesn't show up for act three. What do you mean saved him? I mean I don't know. Well we killed.
Okay is it technically did we technically save him or do we yeah that's that's a weird way to say
that but if we didn't we killed we killed him we killed him from ourselves yes we spared him that's
better yeah we killed his two friends and spared him i see all right oh my rogue now poke is going
poke is going uh oh oh and you got one of those be a skeleton skin yeah you go to shop top right
and you collect points every time you extract very cool very cool so you're gonna be scary
you're gonna scare the okay good i like that you're gonna scare people yeah all right i'm
bringing uh i'm gonna bring this blue halberd and let's go i have a sweet hander anyone want one
actually i i will take that i'll take this render i'll bring two of them then i have two of them is
the birdish good uh is yours white yeah it's just white i'll bring you i'll bring you weapon
okay rogue i like your name thank you okay you said you said you are you are bringing a weapon
yeah i'm bringing you guys two sweet handers i don't like them though they're not that good
they're kind of annoying to use because you can only use them you can't use them in a hallway
yeah you have to use like the right click which is okay but um i don't think the upswing like
hits anything vital like the head yeah it's not worth it what's your favorite what's your favorite
class what's like you think is the best one um i really like i like playing rogue i think they're
fun to fuck around with i would have guessed that from the jumping onto the chalice strat you can do
fun stuff was as rogue you can get like a thing where you fast right yeah you're fast and you
could stealth and move like 10 seconds uh 10 steps in stealth then you could like outplay them
trick them you know yeah it's this game's fun i like it a lot i'm ready all right let's go for it
i love this game it's a really good game yeah it makes a strong first impression i'm just looking
forward to more just like pve stuff more like maps i think it it has a lot of potential for sure
just hope that they get it at the right get it the right way how would elmo play this game
elmo's not old enough to play this like what what a what a dumb question are you trying to
get a voice yeah is it elmo like 50 yeah almost like in his like mid 40s wait that's right no
isn't elmo like four how old is elmo he's three yeah no he elmo is supposed to be three years old
oh yeah just oh nice nice nice yeah you take the blue i'll take the green oh this is an annoying
room nice i'm really strong okay we have to take turns not killing you yeah i i don't i'm
i don't want to swing because i'm gonna kill somebody nice oh what do you have let me i can't
expect you but you probably have some cool shit on this character oh yeah i'm really really really
yeah real strong what the you just went like a golf club who i was trying to figure out what the
hell it was hitting a wizard sword oh great two archers yeah now let's go yeah i don't like that
route that route stinks you could break the door yeah but the fucking weapon it just try it again
no get you got to get it i have to do it from this angle i thought you were going to get me
with the backstroke for a second there oh lockpick yeah so how do you is do you have any lockpicks on
you no do you do you have the perk to do i have it you got it oh my god uh yeah battle axe oh yeah
kind of kind of junk that barefoot sound yeah the penguin slap you just scared the shit out of me
by the way i saw a person walk up in my peripheral and i freaked out trying to dodge all the spike
traps there's a double axe in here is that good for barbarian probably right it's just a gray
yeah it's how to get take this uh this battle axe in here 50 damage you probably would like it maybe
more than that if you if you don't like this way under i like the range of the this sword
yeah it's just i can't figure out why the upswing is like hitting something it's weird it doesn't
have a weird swing all right we're gonna make our way out of here you know this spot right here
oh secret this takes you all the way across okay that's that's good to know i think i've done this
accident like once or twice but it's good to know that it's here this game is kind of like
minecraft with guns i mean i that's that's what i said earlier but people are like you're a
fucking idiot and stuff and i don't know it's like i feel pretty validated somebody else said that
it's like annoying when people say i'm stupid about it i feel you yeah more terraria but
whatever this leads to the same place i'd give it like a eight out of ten well it's not even out
yet so you can't you can't give it a rating i mean that was a thought you were making an ig in joke
oh is that is that what that actually is originally from wasn't wasn't ig in the skyrim with guns
quote oh yeah that was okay shit oh man oops did i don't did i hit you no i'm good okay okay is
this uh is this iron north when you craft with this that's an exquisite ruby oh my goodness you
need to get a mining pick and i don't know if anyone upstairs upstairs upstairs yeah i'm at like
half health already friendly friendly i'm down to be not friendly friendly friendly i don't know if
they're friendly they did i can just run up to the killer i'm trying to do it i'm seeing i'm seeing
some ad a yeah the 80 80 80 they do to 80 80 80 80 okay i may have hit you too you did
but i did hit him in the head i did and i said bro what i was a team effort we got him he looked
like a skeleton to me this shit on all right we should probably try to get out of here now
oh it's crazy how strong i am it's so it's it's dumb you think it's rain this guy this guy here
oh these pants holy shit actually uh talc you take these these are like these things pants oh no you
can't only fighter damn this is good okay hold on oh my goodness this guy's got such crazy shit
i'm taking this whole outfit this dude was decked out my headshots are 70 damage
the stab holy shit that's amazing wait did i i'm all right let's go insane anybody have any potions
on them i don't think they did uh i have health bars yet i just drained them let's just get
bandages you know drop uh all right we gotta oh my goodness thank you oh i have a campfire actually
oh we should we probably we gotta move yeah we gotta get out of here that's a nice job though
good work we go this way i think i missed the ring three times oh shit i'm an idiot how good was
that ring uh it's like one strength you want to break these things this spawns the spiders
oh okay so what is minecraft with guns yeah i got these monsters if you go right under it the
little bees they can't hit you little bees or uh the dragonflies oh boots um spell cat spell
capacity bonus and buff duration blue boots on the ground right here blue boots yeah they're
just blue and they're nice but it's like spell shit are we in a high roller this is i feel like
we're getting a ton of good shit e are you looting uh yeah i'm still loot i'm uh pretty full but i
could probably part with some low quality stuff pull it up fuck i keep getting e because it's me
this chalice is cracked bro yeah make sure bro oh it's i mean there's a blue one over there
there's a there is a right across there's a threads here should we do it no probably dumb
i would say so we got one more yeah i hear noise you should take this one you should get out of
here with the with the stuff you have people here people here i'm gonna say go yeah definitely
you should just get out of here run through that stick around for fight probably not you have some
great stuff kill the one kill him try the scale all right i'm out oh my god close quarters is
another one in there no he's dead okay there's a wizard okay we gotta get in the zone oh one here
and another one there all right oh you take that take that one hell yeah oh hopefully this guy
does not doesn't really matter you good yep all right gg nice job you get some good shit out of
that too yeah i'm fully looted this game's pretty sick oh are you spectating my weapons and shit
yeah i'm looking at it right now you got this ron this rondell dagger is crazy like do you see
how everything has plus damage yeah it's just um i'm so dumb stupid not strong physical magical
nice stab him in the face these are some pretty great runs i'm telling you right now
this is this is good shit all right sell this stuff i'm bringing the uh beginner's luck
to the party i love that feeling when you have a full inventory of trinkets and you just
don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't don't and it all turns into money that's
worth a lot how much is this worth actually exquisite ruby it's like 30 am nice is your shoes
good uh germa yep i got blues okay cool i got strength uh magic penetration boots and doesn't
really do anything but it's all good i got a lot of money there yeah like 300 bucks you got 300
holy shit yeah it feels like 300 bucks yeah damn i actually think i'm gonna take these off for now
yeah all right i'm gonna roll with some goofy shit because i don't want to lose this stuff yet
are you goofy stance i think i'm going goofy right now oh rock this for now okay hold on all
right how about uh okay you got time for one more oh of course because we got um i'm trying
to cycle in his bunch of people today all right i'll do one more let's do it right dude if you if
you keep playing this are you playing and playing this like long term yeah i play a lot because hey
should fucking play again gotta get back into like organizing stash mentality for this game
i know hold on what's done we gotta get uh me you and stir i used to play a lot with stir
yeah stir uh i don't know if i don't know if that's gonna uh stir is hey he enjoyed his time in the
game he enjoyed his time in the case this game i didn't say that i said he enjoyed his time in
the game he had a lot of fun in he hates it i don't think stir hates the game he had his he had fun
in the game when we played it two days ago i'll try to convince them yeah maybe you can all right
sorry i'm just buying potions this is a lot to take in you're doing great you're owning
now honest to god you're doing fantastically literally installing the game my secret is letting
you go through the door first he said on his stream that he hates it okay well i didn't say
that so he leaked it himself we are ready to go i think those stir hatings the game like this
is actually directly proportional to how much he actually enjoys it um i think he he liked it but
he didn't really love it but that means he loves it possibly although me him and i had a huge
vampire survivor's argument so i don't know i tried to convince him for like an hour straight
on stream one time and it just didn't work why isn't like that game too no he could probably tell
you every reason why he's he's very opinionated he's very opinionated aren't we all yeah we are
that's all right oh shit i don't know what's what who i don't know who's doing that but that's cool
what there's a chest in there oh there's a there's a secret
there was a trinket oh okay yeah that's like a boss peace if you if you're under him he can't
hit you wow this is actually working holy shit that thing is usually a horrendous thing to deal
with oh horseman's axe okay do you want to try a one-hander me yeah uh i don't know i like the
range of this but i can i can just hear it out take a look it's not a bad one too
trader can barbarians put on a shield or no no one hitter probably pretty bad then
just yeah this is okay watch out oh my goodness the bonk weapon it's good for the hallways and
the doors that was so like masterfully done poke oh thank you there's like you still use all the
purple all the dodging all the strafing i would have died in this room these mobs drop like
amulets and stuff they're really good oh bunny hopping is actually in the game okay you should
do a weld uh i don't want to do weld right now rain behind you alex yeah i just can't you are
opening this chest you can finish it thank you so much cleric um helmet plus one will yeah i want
to try a different class soon but going back to level one i'm almost level five it's easy to level
yeah it's it's the leveling is i know it's like oh shit like level five level 10 level 20 the
difference is almost nothing it's just being able to pick another perk it's it's really everybody's
literally just at zero it's all gear yeah oh people here oh never mind oh i think there is
a person at 150 back by me see there is skeleton peeping in the door i just i swung and i know
that's what that wasn't me oh oh god run this way people cross i think there might be somebody back
here oh my god i can't get through the door yep this wizard shooting shit at us from across the
way okay do you see the room at like 150 i saw like a head through there a minute ago would you
smoke usually open would you smoke a blunt with poke yeah what do we have it's almost here i'll
get on stuffing in oh that was oh find us behind us killed good good good good i'm just like my
whole goal is to try to avoid hitting the both of you that one hander just saved my life so uh
thanks for dropping that they were all up in my face there's some other shit on here i don't want
to take it all use your right click yeah but even it's like uh uh yeah but still i feel like
okay when i do the wind up does that hit don't blame me i don't know what the fuck you could
have done honestly if i if i participated in that fight we would have lost yeah everyone
here i'll use the campfire for you oh okay yeah that'd be good wait do you have a surgical kit
i got i got heels too if you want them i have a campfire kit extra i got three potions on the
ground right here for you right here by me just just chug them well don't chug them but after
each other do you have to wait some guys some loot for money like before you drink another
potion do you have to wait till the bar stops flashing yes oh yeah there's uh some more
trinkets on here so i've seen a golden chest before but i couldn't open it is there have you
ever opened a golden chest book yeah it's nothing crazy oh oh those guys back there yeah i think
that's probably who i saw they were in this room we just went through and then they ran that way
and then got killed oh you jumped down all right we uh oh watch out a lot of shit i don't think you
did never mind never mind oh we got the whole room coming oh yeah i see across across person
is concerning me mage we should just leave this yeah it's this it's never it's always bad yeah
is there is there a tier of item rarity over purple oh legendary so that and that's in the
play test right now is that orange yeah oh man i don't even know how you'd find one of those
i bet someone would give you one right now you have but to ask i definitely don't want that
yeah i feel you ruins the magic honestly if somebody came into a lobby and just dropped
like a legendary on the ground i just wouldn't even pick it up i'd throw it away so i'll take
it and hide it oh that was a lot of money on this one don't shoot me god damn it circles coming in
this thing is hard to use i forgot so how often does the circle close uh often is there like a
timer before it moves or it just randomly starts all people here in the middle it's probably every
couple minutes are we two or three minutes are we fighting somebody dead here i think they're
they're in trouble i think there's no one died here on the left just one looks like maybe two
a lot of enemies behind them though i killed them got one and there's a zombie's with me
i'm just i was trying to get rid of the zombie there's too much gas on there
unfortunately the guy died in an awkward spot for loot oh my god oh i know he did
okay okay uh-oh more people no just i think i'm i went to go loot this guy and i separated myself
from you guys oh are you down in that hallway still yeah yeah yeah come to me here to your left
just turn left and then turn left again okay hold on i gotta check his weapon
this is coming it's coming for you right now right where left and then left so like that way
and then turn left hey there you are oh he had a blue ring this way then left i'm excited about
any rarity of loot at this stage we could try a red portal we could we could i have campfires
i have two heals i mean what point right here all right let's do it yeah cool two red portals
and a blue two blues why do i not have pants off i haven't i haven't had pants on this whole
dungeon there's a blue in this room you guys take these okay you guys take the blues out there
hell yeah hell yeah oh three in here oh wow this is easy let's get out of here wait okay i got
pretty much i got a portal over here let's make sure there's nothing else no he doesn't want to
do red i mean let's get out of here we could someone else here someone else you gotta decide
all right yeah go go get out get out get out get out i'll cover you just yeah get up all right
talks you got up yeah i'm out nice okay we're good yeah you gotta make a decision that was fun
that was ggs honestly poke that's like three in a row where i've collected like a hundred bucks
or at least worth of stuff hell yeah if you want to collect more we play next time yeah yeah if you
if you plan on keep playing it i mean i i don't know if i'm gonna be streaming it but i'm definitely
gonna be playing it and stuff so just let me know thanks uh thanks for the rundown sorry for asking
so many questions but you handled it expertly and i um i enjoyed myself guys poke put pokes um
twitch in the chat please all right yeah let's let's play some more seriously it's um no for sure
you're you're a good shit so but you too man and you too e nice to meet you etalux hey nice
meeting you too dude all right see you guys yeah goodbye that was that was good shit i only died
like two times so you said oh you said you're a good shit i did i meant like that was good
shit like that was fun right yeah you're one of the good shits i did that was just like a slip
it's all right now poke is awesome follow poke and um yeah i think there's a couple people we're
gonna be cycling in no no that yeah no i think that that's that that makes sense that term makes
sense isn't it you're a good shit i think criken's gonna come in yeah no that's a what that's a term
i think we're gonna get criken in here okay bring in the beautiful boy
um well i figure out how who to sell all this good shit too those are those are great rounds
he was uh he was very he was very good criken's name is jeff jerf jerf oh they're okay criken is
gonna be in character i think and then they put in parentheses sorry okay uh i think we need to make
a new lobby exit party here we go yeah yeah thanks blind poke we'll probably play again 100
all right uh i'm looking for jerf jerf you say and then you again and your name was what was it
again um should i play a different class you can do yeah whatever you want to definitely play with
what you think you want to try um i kind of want to see what who's do you know what criken's going
to be criken is a barbarian so okay yeah i'll switch um i want to try cleric or something like
that clerics fun clerics about just kind of buffs and support and heals but you also have like a
mace in your moves it's just kind of like dnd your heels hurt undead enemies oh okay yeah so like do
you have a um a limited number of casts for those you do so you have like correct me if i'm wrong
but there is charges how does the cleric get the charges back if is there a meditate let me add
i gotta come up with a new character name criken's coming in oh wait criken's talking in the lobby
hello hey hello hey oh no no no sorry sorry hey hey hey hey jerf hey yeah what's up
jerf how are you is that jerf i'm good how are you guys doing pretty good pretty good
so thanks for having me on the show yeah 100 so jerf um how strong would you say you are
on a scale of 110 of five that's such an honest answer all right my character name is um bripple
yep b-r-i-p-p-l-e i'm jerf uh you've gotta be in the lobby b-r-i-p-p-l-e
yeah i'm here there you are all right oh my god i have so much shit i have to sell
uh do you want anything i got three candy oh i actually have enough candy i won't
bore you all with that though i'll do that later i'm not bored i need to sell this stuff
leather cap oh wait wait you uh talc you're gonna be a cleric i will hold on to the cleric hat
i will hold on to the morning star okay but like the blue morning star should i take that
yes that was the cleric weapon of choice besides maybe a book i think stashes are different per
character yes you do not share a stash you cannot just trade weapons to yourself unless you want to
give it to me on a different character and then i drop it for you as the clerk should i i mean
are you saying i should do that or um it's not like a huge deal you can do it we do later okay
okay let me just clear out some shit i'm just gonna give you this stuff that i have
oh there's a there's a spell wheel i'll do this later i'll just do it now while i thinking about
it where's my diamond uh right okay sorry all right sorry sorry sorry no i did the wrong thing
again okay i'm just a goddamn idiot aren't we all all right you're having fun right it's very fun
very yeah much all right okay i'm almost ready i promise how long have you been a barbarian uh two
days all right ripple invite come on ripple uh-huh um oh yeah i have to okay so i have to leave
the first party yeah you're gonna exit the first one i bet this guy's just been sitting at a table
with me like uh staring off into space for the last five minutes or so i said gerf is very very
likable i wasn't talking about gerf it's not about you no but but people are saying gerf is
incredibly likable they like love gerf okay thanks that means a lot guys uh i'm just doing my best
that's all you can do especially with the job is uh high turnover as barbarian
got that right but i die almost every game first all right um are we all ready sure want me to bring
uh some candy or a potion i have i have quite a few items that i think i'm good with i appreciate
it though thank you is that your voice doing a thing because i mean might as well do a thing
if we might have to do that too i like it yeah are you like a like a potion seller
no i'm an adventure i must i must i must i must i must i must a little bit of everything i would
say wow i'm just sure i'm ready up please gentlemen sorry you got ready oh pete alex
there's a lot of negative energy going around the table right now i apologize i
i just got my spell book in the mail and i was parsing through it before this journey
oh they're getting into character right let's have let's have a good clean game out there
excuse me as i uh awkwardly flip between the pages and try to find the correct spell and
the heat of combat is very stressful very difficult indeed i would say so what part
of the world are you from uh jerephine just meeting you for the first time north the north
was cold at the way where is everyone as you know we where is everyone oh i say that's sort of
strange that we've not been spawned in the same area are you doing a nigel thornberry sort of uh
it says i'm alone in the party yes me as well hey guys please don't kill jerk don't kill me
i brought my best stuff um i forgot about this let me try and make it out this is really interesting
okay so what uh where are you guys on the map uh i'm in book book book land book book land
book i am in like the temp i'm in the point there's a bunch of pointy pyramid pieces there's
people over here let's see if i can make some friends take that bastard oh i got spider
oh foolish mummy trying to kill me oh good day how are you hello good morrow sir can you help me
mate please strangely enough i've been i have been displaced from my party is it possible that we
could potentially become friends and you can lead me to my other friends party yes yeah where are
you all right let's be friends all right i'm just gonna mute because i'm gonna ruin your guys
like just talking to me i'm sorry are we are we doing this or are we should we just die and leave
because i don't have any good loot i have to go this way basic as it comes i got some uh i
got some bangles what if we run into each other the trap everywhere trap right there oh shit trap
behind you mate oh just be careful while you're walking there's two this i feel like i'm in the
goblin one that you've warned me about yeah i i don't know i don't know what happened so many
people here i'm gonna mute for two minutes just i'm gonna try to find you guys but i'm in hold on
i'm in bookland morrow oh i are you out of course i'm following i don't know why why did we not get
into the same room dear lord please bless us don't not say skeleton ahead i start a skeleton
can you heal yourself as cleric yeah you just gotta uh do the doremi move we might whisper
they have accidentally stopped you like i just don't i hear here's some way to focus here
there's some feet slapping one which invests you oh it's very tricky i'm a trader by trade so of
course i can't swing a sword correctly oh oh if i die i will haunt you forever we need to find
each other this is stupid unfortunately my cleric book did not have an instruction page
oh you know i have just a quick question for you if you could i'm going to turn around and could
you put an arrow in the back of my head and just take all of my things because i've lost my team
and i don't know and i think we're going to requeue so i'm going to turn around and i please uh
gentleman if you could uh put the arrow directly into the back of my skull and please take all of
my things and use them because they're probably worth a little bit maybe they could get you a few
coins if you could just and all i i have a few last words i'd like to say just give me one
you see through your eyes that's not me i was i was muting the discord so i didn't
all right i'm i am now spectating i'm just gonna come find where you guys are and watch
i i am also dead okay let's watch a jerk for a few minutes we are in the same game though
ostensibly i have never seen that happen before that was very weird the the dungeon master split
up the party in the first the first quest what kind of person doesn't have a mute keybind
guys i'm sorry i lost holy shit you i just looked over in the discord you are like
you are a barbarian in real life you're streaming your webcam in here
i'm sure sorry you're broadcasting that to us too that i love that i turn it off no no no i
i love it all right let's let's try this again maybe we maybe we won't have the same problem
oh uh that was all my loot oh wait no i got one axe left happy day sure if i actually can
bring you some stuff probably hold on oh don't worry about it sure if i have a blue barbarian
helm that's plus one strength plus four armor rating and it's pretty good i think i'm going
to give it to you i also have a blue halberd this thing is disgusting plus two to all attributes
plus two to agility this thing is disgusting go away all right uh i'll see if i can trade
and i just want to make sure you know that that is for me because you can't equip it i just want
you to know how cool it was um i apologize i do have a purple swayander how are you with those
i've never used one before it's fun it's i think it could be kind of fun would you like to try a
purple swayander uh if you trust me with it i don't want to i want to mess up it's all right
sure yeah i don't matter beta ends in three days i'm gonna i'm gonna go in with nothing
in that case i'm thinking about saving that all right i'm sorry jerk no i get it you don't trust
your yet you know i need to get your out there yeah wait jerk has to prove to me sure is is good
should i say jerk all right let me get it sure jerk jerk jerk jerk apologize to jerk right now
i i'm sorry i didn't mean that all right so um talks what was you said yeah trying learning
about spell memory yes it if you have it's a it's amount of spells you can attune and
you can only do a certain amount before you're kind of like over encumbered or something right
is that how it works jerk if you could please you have any idea think of it it's like the number of
words you can know yeah i think that that makes sense do you have any favorite words uh yeah what's
your favorite word jerf um well i it's kind of like a joke what do you call a piece of dried
jerf jerfy jerf jerfy yeah yeah like like beef jerky yeah yeah jerfy pretty cool beef jerfy my
favorite word is mayonnaise that's an interesting one why why because it's kind of it's a lot of
syllables and it's i like it a lot yeah because it's either it's mayonnaise it'd be like four or
mayonnaise weird how it can be multiple syllables depending on how you say it very interesting
word like you could say jerk like jerk or like sure to try to drag it out yeah you can drag it
out this turned into a thing but i was just trying to ask uh which spells do you think i should
equip definitely the heel like you know there there is a a heel that only heals you it's not
a group hill well there's one that heals a target unless there's no target and then it heals you
okay yeah so that that's the one yeah yeah i got that one i got uh protection shield yep that's a
good one like the little bubble it's like it's like power shield i've got increased damage by 10
hell yeah oh and hell yeah and any other special requests i think that sounds pretty good to me
i think there's is there one that does uh holy damage uh there is a i'm trying to see if my
glasses it's just holy damage on that italics there's a there's holy light yeah 30 hp heal or
100 undead damage be liberal with the spells okay you guys ready let's go for it let's do it
surf it up your idea what your perks are there's a smell emanating from over your direction oh yeah
it's the jerky in my my back pocket that's what that is i was gonna say i didn't want to but it
sounded rude to bring it up but it's helpful in case we come across hounds like this one auto
right here all right let's hope we're in the same game this time and not across the whole
world from each other that's weird you said brother we're just simply too powerful when united
they split us up at the start somebody said jerf you look constipated uh how you doing down there
we are we are split up again what the f**k damn something's wrong what's all right we need to
breathe all right just i'm just gonna i'm just gonna just yell at people and then have them kill
did i bring anything expensive kind of oh well yeah hope you didn't bring that axe free gear
free gear on i have free a free uh this free gear on me they're gonna get that ass i mean axe
they're gonna get this axe i didn't bring the axe thing thankfully free stuff on me i'm just a free
i'm a free kill i actually am that i know you might think that i'm saying that i have a group
of two other people but we can't get in the same game together for some reason so free gear on me
i'm dying by enemies free gear over here free gear right here you just killed two innocents
they were so so young just kidding the rangers okay i'm dead that was fast well i just i just
died and i figured we'd just reload i think that's a great idea but i'm gonna cast a practice spell
first where are you i wonder why this is weird why is this happening yeah i don't know maybe if we
just all exit kind of reload let's remake the party yeah yeah you got it oh oh heck oh no wait
i think i heard you die there was a spike sound yeah that that'd be me oh no jurf is dead good one
jurf classic classic jurf classic jurf peripheral vision with this helmet all right so yeah actually
take this opportunity to practice because i can't i can't cast a spell how do you cast a spell
right let's uh you hold right click i think right and that charges it and you cannot move when you
cast it that's correct you healed the zombie oh no is it not a zombie is not undead well that's a
mummy well that's a that's a mummy are mummies not undead i believe um isn't that by definition
i think that's correct yeah they should be dead classic classic ripple apparently i'm fine this
is literally bugleberry yeah it kind of is this is the haircut heels do not damage enemies
apparently so i was completely wrong when i said that to you but it that was the mimic that killed
me i was running from that thing when i ran to the spike oh yeah there's a spike down there watch
it found you oh that's the one oh there it is all right so what that's the one that one
undead that one hurts undead yes okay you gotta whisper too there's a big aoe around you i think
make sure you loot it oh it's not dead i think it is the stick the best thing you got
he's not dead jerma can you please get this haircut maybe that would be kind of funny
this haircut is seriously just okay so casting can you can anybody pull this haircut off i feel
like it's really hard to but anyways he's casting it go ahead holy purification there you go good
job i figured it out okay and it's like the zone's coming does a ton of damage by the way it hurts
a lot oh no that move is incredible zone if you if you um if you run around and grab like two or
three people and they're chasing you you can almost kill everything and just one huge aoe like that
it hurts a lot it's like 70 plus damage i think watch out the bugs are eating you my god dude
so bad what was that it was awful you didn't even like attack so bad oh make a lot
you were so bad all right let's let's exit game and try this again yeah nice playing with you guys
it's really fun to play with the jerk um yeah but we're like hopping around cycling people in so
like yeah see you later it was fun okay yeah maybe next time yeah good just good games all around
all right let's leave this party let's try this again should we just exit the game or should we
leave i wonder if we should just all restart i'm just gonna do that i just restarted yeah
yeah yeah yep yep that's smart start reset and it again uh this is the first time i've
ever experienced this bug this is weird let's try it again uh what'd you recommend for um
for a weapon felling axe if you can get one everybody loves felling axes what do you think
they call him that um probably the guy that invented it like tripped over it oh he wouldn't
they call trip axes then but it ain't that he fell all right invites going up i get it what's
your name ripple ripples it's ripple oh i what i say ripples okay all right can this let's come
on this needs to work i'm okay i'm not bringing any items because if this doesn't work again then
what the heck that's why i was gonna say i'm glad that this has just been not super try hard
because i don't have anything to lose anyway yeah either way the spell that i used is it has the
same description as my the perk that did kill the mummy maybe it is i don't know i haven't played
any clerk i'm gonna like switch it and then like switch it again okay we're on we're in a team
and i just did it all right let's do it ready up because one of them says holy purification
the aoe does undead monster damage and then holy light does just undead target damage
they just have more than 100 hp okay oh i'm sorry all right it's all right we're good don't
jerk don't worry about it okay okay i see our names down there yeah hey ripple goodbye jeff
i hope to see you on the other side and okay thinking it's thinking
hmm yay that's sure sure sure sure sure sure sure hold on everyone sure sure sure yeah we
can't do it i get it all right how well can you swing a sword well i don't have a sword i got an
axe okay okay you said be liberal with the spells but what's the what's the baseline
i'm sorry there's a more than more than like two two bad guys maybe use a spell yeah on individual
just single enemies not really but if we have like more than one or two then yeah like should i
already be healing you i just took a potion so i'm okay but eventually yes i've just my brain just
farted for a second so i couldn't hit that thing hey secret area oh get in there and pick up
whatever you want hey you're a fighter right mm-hmm oh thank you very nice sure sure oh oh
jerk is this a smurf scenario where you replace words with jerk or is it a you like do you just
what's the scenario here the smurf mom jerk right but okay do you understand what i say when i say
oh man that was that was jerfing crazy yeah okay just again there is a magic staff here i don't
know if it's better than what you have hey uh jerk for there any uh there any jerfettes around
here you know i'm saying oh i have to jerk i'm single why are you looking you're looking to
jerk looking to jerk down that's a horrible room i don't like that room we're not going in it
right yeah this room is also horrible whatever there's people in here at this bathroom all right
go in there uh 20 seconds of protection you can also good do your prayer spell yep they don't
know we're coming they don't know we're here there's people here and now they see us oh they're
screaming get ready to jerk your maker what does that mean i forgot how to cast a spell
they're running you think we should chase uh nah we gotta get through the circle anyways oh they
left one behind they did it was a little wizard oh no oh no he turned oh it's a cleric that's even
worse that was so where'd they go i don't know if they caught was this person alone oops oh this
person may have been alone but they feel a little bad if they were they were swinging at you though
yeah they did swing once with a stick yeah that was aggression yeah that's provocation i thought
i was casting protection on you uh that was a self-cast you can also very protected you can
give it to enemies too by the way like you can heal enemies oh good so if you cast a healing spell
and you do it to another player they will get healed there's some comedy there oh yeah that's
funny i did also like the part where he said it's jurfing time yeah that's your i'm about to jurf
off i'm kidding i'm kidding i'm not doing that oh god oh my god oh my god is that the most annoying
way you can say that there's death in here whoa you're not kidding somebody was here that was a
good movie quote like there is death in here there's there's death in here we should all go
to read that line together we should all split up hey you know if we make it out here alive
let's go to the let's go get some hey i'll share a pint of ale with you for real yeah can i get my
own too yeah wow thanks i think there's something going on here i just saw a corpse yeah let me just
that's weird someone just got killed by the pendulums pendulum all right we're kind of
getting into the area where we're gonna have to fight oh there's a heal already oh a falchion
like that better casting speed magic damage i haven't looted anything i just realized oh you
haven't looted anything ripple get to loot but i'll i'll go over you it happens though it does
you get kind of stuck in though like i'm looking at my spells and no it happens okay those are
invulnerable i'm concerned with being ready to give you guys like a shield jurf there is a jurf
and a pair of giraffes in here and if you want to jurf here i would jurf this oh can we just all
jurfed here wow i mean thanks all right we're careful oh hey spell book uh after we clear this
obviously but we might get collapsed on actually oh good spell there i was ready nice good job
everybody have any lock picks uh uh yeah i don't have a lock pick classic jurf jurf just sounds
like a really nice guy you know what i mean just sounds like a like a like a nice like good
presence to be around oh thanks it's a good there's a good aura yeah uh it's alex on the ground
is a spell book which is going to help your spells who would have thought do what i mean that's i
think you have to have it instead of snaf is it better than staff it might be seems like it it has
like plus magic damage or something it should i don't know how it works really i don't play
the casters uh we gotta move oh maybe this way a little closer to the zone a little peak
all this back the way we came jurf you sound like a really swell canadian guy
thanks i think it's like this is it's that last sentence uh players south coming through the door
south all right in position okay um it was the way you said the last word i love it all right are we
ready yeah i mean there's players are we running at them all right we're hostile we're hostile we're
hostile we're hostile behind me oh watch out i almost got you oh boy get them jerks oh they're
all pretty low i got one that that fighter right there is pretty low they're chasing i have to
imagine he's probably one hit wow we really jerked at the end there didn't we dude did that dude have
i thought i hit that dude like four times i hit him twice dude he missed a lot he but he oh that
was so sad he just literally bopped you in the head you know that was uh yelp in my bed there
all right i'm bringing items this time i'm going in i would bring items if i had items
god we got really just i would say royally jerked i'm gonna drop all my money on this one i'm done
drifting around yeah let's let's go for it just gonna i'm just gonna fill out a little
want some good shit i'm bringing my halberd i'm i'm i'm ready to rock now what's my best
offense outside of healing you in like a player encounter your mace yeah your mace i think that's
what bopped us at the end there i wonder if he had a really good base probably he must have had
some good buy some potions i have nothing and therefore i will bring nothing all right i'm
actually i'm going to try as hard as i can mode this time to let you know all right all right all
right yeah this time i'm gonna let her rip you know i'm saying oh yeah gonna die instantly no
we're gonna be fine it won't be instant that's exaggeration these fools need to have an what's
that an economy round i got plenty of money every round's an economy round for me number can only
go up right now i got a blue halberd i'm ready this is gonna go directly into somebody's forehead
it's going to crush their skull in one hand i get it get it did you say get it
yes i did not know that i didn't know that get it was in jerk's vocabulary oh no oh no
what is happening right now oh we're losing to him wait why was we couldn't take the
oh did i get a heal purple yeah i was pointing at you and it healed me instead oh thanks man
oh uh barred itch barred itch yeah barred itch here which is pretty good how barbarian much
mana do i have i think you have charges don't you hey burple help us for you yeah i have one
charge left oh sure if you were real jerk you know that you're welcome uh there's much just
random shit here the crossbows do a lot of damage oh yeah good work everyone i kind of nothing on
any of these people almost got me what are these like glowing what's the altar of sacrifice is it
is it as the name implies um so kind of what it means is you can rip you can revive them there
yeah so if somebody uh if somebody dies then you can all right if somebody dies then you can
turf them you know what was that just all right if somebody dies you take their soul and then you go
to that altar and it brings them back naked you take their soul yep every player when they're
dead they have a soul that you can everyone's got a soul under their shirt hey what the got you
hey the spiders all come out of uh a pot yep you gotta smash the pot nice what's in the tomb
do i have an aoe hill you don't know do you do i don't know if you have it can you equip it yet
is it a perk i know that you have like a big like aoe hot i can heal someone for 30 pretty
terrible items all right there's a lot of shit in here but there's a bunch of you know monsters and
just be careful just just you're telling me it's called sanctuary is the heel oh what happened
i'm all right oh gerf hold on gerf be careful i got one i almost just hit you gerf oh that's
that's my bad oh good all right uh nice nice mark actually nice work there's a healing shrine over
there too oh there is uh ripple you should definitely take that healing shrine because
you're the healer and we want you to stay alive yeah how do i get more charges that i actually
do not know the answer of is the healing shrine the blue one or the the green one this is speed
over here i might just you know we got a lockpick i don't unfortunately oh beans uh the campfire by
the way is how you can get more charges oh that's a big one this is a big one we got it though
maybe gerf should take the heal now i've got a still got the chunk heal i got four charges of
30 yeah can i get a little piece of that thing yeah that's probably good it's a pretty good
heal too oh that's good thanks do you want another one oh i don't want to impose yeah
yeah if you stay alive i stay alive there if you are canadian yeah you think so
there's that nice canadian hospitality oh that was a much weaker one no offense it's my first day
on the job watch out everyone hide archer sometimes they shoot twice in a row and it's very bad all
right we got another archer across the way did you actually shoot me with that you did hit me with
a damn oh come on dude a lot of stuff to loot in here but this is where a lot of people are
going to come oh i got an archer on me a human one human human human human human oh he's coming
oh you're off where are you he's up across jumping down yep there oh boy he came and found me
coming we're coming oh they got me guys watch your behind behind behind i'm dead i got killed from
behind what the fuck just happened i died instantly i was a head shot with a longbow what
it was a good one holy shit how much health did i have he just ambushed us i was at one i was at
100 hp i died in one headshot i had a helmet on too holy shit yeah i had full health and i had armor
oh my goodness i was at 100 hp jesus well it's unfortunate oh we just gotta just gotta get lucky
sorry do we have time for a bathroom break i think we do take a quick break i took a hit from the
fighter too it must have been at the same time because it was just like all right i'm very back
let's go pee yep i gotta take the dog out too what if i don't gotta then um just just put your both
your head to put both your hands on the table and just sit there and pray internally but both of
your hands over your asshole so you don't need to all right okay all right we're back i have returned
oh hi we uh we good to go i think he's still pooping he's what is he also oh all right in the
meantime i'm gonna figure out is there a long law i like the long sort of the best okay
jeref what's your favorite item what do you like to use um stick big old jerv stick
the old jerv quarterstaff stick a big old jerv stick uh what do you what do you call uh
uh well have you had an impossible burger yet no let's try it's impossible it's just you should
give it a try i feel like it'd be interesting you think jerv specifically would enjoy an
impossible burger actually jerv would probably take a bite of the impossible burger and then
kill me with his axe because i suggested it in the first place so it's not good i mean i'm
getting mixed signals here okay that's like a jerv bites this his eyes turn red he grabs the axe
and he just kills me jerv they're pretty good though you probably like it am i killing you or
am i liking it it depends on um i don't know it depends on how you how you are i'm bringing this
oh i am i don't know like i don't know what what jerv's preferences are in regards to food
i feel like there's a pretty large middle ground between killing you and liking it
it might be okay all right we good yeah um yeah i'm gonna go jerv jerv jerv jerv jerv jerv jerv
jerv jerv hi everybody that's the last thing some of them will hear the last thing i might hear
wow i know pretty deep you would want yourself to be the last thing you hear you egotistical streamer
wait mayonnaise not anymore i said your favorite word you did that word has too much power you did
that was cool yeah you're welcome i like you a little bit more now jerv oh thanks how do you
go more than a 10 out of 10 11 at 10 all right watch out i'll step on that
hurry up oh these people are already people let's do it let's get them let's get them they're hurt
bottom healing oh oh skeleton got me okay i can't heal you anymore oh jerv they're all dead but
there's a very mean red skeleton here hey good job very mean red skeleton oh no jerv is dead
tell him to stop moving yeah i think jerv's little soul and put in a little little sacrifice spot
we're gonna try um jerv i i mean um um whatever your name is just pick it up excuse me i don't
i'm just starting to saying jerv it's like in my it's like earwormed into my answer to jerv all
right i got jerv soul we can bring jerv back yes okay i don't have a resurrection spell no it's
okay we just find a shrine okay there's one more body was there anyone else then really i mean
there was literally level one nobody has anything uh they have bandages i'll take those i didn't pick
it up wait what do you mean wait what's going on i don't have it why not wait what wait where's
uh here's jerv oh yeah i saw that you left his soul i put it in his inventory what i left my uh my
soul back at home it's in my other pair of pants can you imagine taking a soul out of somebody's
body and like just putting it in their pocket and leaving that seems okay how do we um we should
probably just hang out over here this one archer it's two now just be careful stay behind me get
this uh bait this over here you've been blessed that's very helpful how did that even hit me i
will never know i think you put down your shield the second he attacked is that what happened
i didn't want to say anything but i did anyway i'm sorry do you want me to heal you or do you have
potions uh i i would love a heal okay thank you all right this guy's gonna be annoying
and you oh you can cancel watch out yeah make sure you stay right behind me because these things
hurt a lot they're very annoying to kill oh i think it's good okay height is a good strategy
it is actually was it better than what i was that scary sound you guys hear that
somebody's coming in here right now no that's you opening that it's okay we're good now we
need to find a shrine nothing here all right there's gonna be a lot of people in this area
so just be careful should i focus on support or offense if we run into other people if we run into
one or two people focus on healing me because that's what they're going to be doing if it's
the similar setup uh take that say a prayer for jerk okay um oh thanks yep crouch through this
don't do do not do not go don't not just don't go up there what do you call it so i get hurt i
distracted you know we're just gonna do like a what do you call what are you doing you're about
to do a what do you call it something something joke weren't you yeah i was i'm sorry yeah you
were it's not the time well let's hear it we we need we gotta hear it now uh we we called uh i
forgot it i'm gonna talk you off okay i think there's people here how did it go to me i think
that one is only for you i think no it's um heals a target i was pointing right at you i know this
i remember i know there's one that i know this one that only heals you okay hold on okay that
was your footsteps but it's all right wait i was just watching you like make sure no cars were
coming yeah that's what it feels like seriously i just i want i want somebody to explain what
happened i i don't know if somebody's had my screen open i don't know how many people are
watching my screen right now but what happened i don't know i don't know you're if that's the
giraffe what happened i don't know it went through the shield it went through the shield
this is like um i feel like when we do that it's sean of the dead with the brooms
yeah yeah what's in here what do you call uh the longest necked mammal on the earth if it was
giraffe in its name giraffe oh no giraffe giraffe giraffe yeah all right i just got
fucking hit in the face i'm sorry for distracting you i'm playing out of mana i'm playing sesame
street with giraffe right now hold on uh circles moving in like now yeah we got we we can get out
i got two holy heels left here's one yeah please let me have it okay and then two strength agility
will blessings movement maybe sounds like a skeleton maybe is this a crouch hallway
yep any hallway that's like well actually yeah any hallway that's like this narrow
let's do it okay this is this is ugly this is like kind of ugly up here we're not going that way
yeah do we go in a circle or is this just like a symmetrical map i think it's just looks similar
watch out for the traps that are oh these are just shitty pants but you can probably use them
all right you say you just shit your pants you guys just go on a bathroom break
i'm kidding all right we need to bang a left here oh nope uh you want to get out what do you
got any what do you got for stuff there's an exit right there less than you you think so yeah i got
one green and that's it all right well let's just go through here uh just don't fight just make it
through here you only got one green do you want to take it and just take some money
hold on yeah let's kill this and then you take it because you need to make some cash
okay so here take take all take all this shit on the ground right now okay uh i'm out of spice
all right so just play tetris so don't get out no just go just leave you take up whatever's left
just go i'm out all right good good job i gotta get off that level one grind does the shield on
your back actually protect i don't think so because that would be pretty cool all right let
me see if i can get out of here what do you have three arrows oh never mind i got a jerk soul i
think that's worth probably something can i get out this way all right please don't sell my soul
um how am i gonna get out of here to the right jerk soul is like uh the treasure chest at the end
of the rainbow what's the best way to get out of here how do i get the fuck out of here you gotta
go up you gotta go up yeah you're just going deeper into the abyss yeah up that way and then
like you gotta hang a left oh no oh oh my god not this is not gonna hey there's a way out
yeah there is but there's also that uh oh you gotta kite him around good good dodge oh oh
no oh fuck you get stuck get stuck get stuck get stuck get stuck get stuck get stuck get stuck
you can do it what why did i not go in why did i not go in i was waiting to one second why did i
not go in it was up it was there what you were there you died so that i you gotta you gotta
live you gotta wait the one like i thought it was all the way open i think you got blocked by the
skeleton yeah good try that's worth it I don't really have anything I just
wanted to do it for the because you gave it all to me I'm gonna do it it was just
it was open I just didn't touch it I feel like I did I think the animation
wasn't quite done but I had to I had to go for it you forgot to you forgot the
animation skip yeah I mean it you can't go in until like it's all the way open
and then sits there for about a half a second but I thought I could make it
okay all right you guys ready for another one yeah yeah I'm gonna put on
some decent stuff this time it's not that though yeah I want to know not that
yep yeah it's here another joke what would you what do you call your civic
duty if Jeff was a government and you were summoned to court a it's a juror
you have to get to serve on the jury free I don't want to say it you can say
it's a Murphy duty yeah you got it yeah I got it yeah oh cool I just bring this
way under all right I go all in here just this once I'm going all in oh that
means I need something better than this though oh I'll see if I can buy anything
uh I can buy the I can buy this late armor yeah figure out who to sell
everything to grab bunch of random shit that's yeah okay let's go make sure you
buy potions and stuff too do I need to buy potions if I can just heal myself
yeah you definitely want at least a stack if we're going for real and it's
not like oh we're gonna run around and be a dickhead I just made my first 50
gold and I'm gonna spend a third of that on potions it's there unfortunately
that's the way it is all right okay okay hold on one second please okay I
actually have I am like stacked right now so if I really if I lose it's then
this is very sad but I'm gonna play for I'm gonna play my heart out here potions
help you live and living gets you money that's true also I want to check this
real quick another is weander I don't really want that got a mole how are we
doing are we ready yeah I'm ready I am also ready all right I am stacked out I
am decked out this is I like I could if I am just I gotta play well I could kill
people probably one hit to their head I'm getting better with the spells oh
yeah there's a learning curve everybody just stand up come on now stand up
everybody's put your hands up come on just stand up hmm okay you need me want
some audience participation for this one yes okay put your hands up okay we're
too we are gonna just live okay I want to live so that's good hit this oh you
are decked out oh I think I am NOT messing around you got spurs on your
boots careful I got a campfire kid if we need to take it take a five that's
actually really helpful thank you turf yeah did you take that have a scary room
but watch over the bats you want some protection it'll be pretty sweet saw
yours he's like one hit all right let's get in there oh there's a mage on I got
this the tunic over there green these vans oh I almost hit you we got him good
job oh I got a I got clothes for you Burpee did you call me burpee burpee
I did here whoo a mystic Raymond I will dream out of my frock now yeah there's
a tunic there's a green tunic over in the other than that hallway we just came
from it's a green I recommend somebody pick it up I'm gonna heal myself the
old-fashioned way just loot it up loot I don't know what that means there's a
there's a green tunic over here a tunic on this zombie right here yeah you take
that back and you can use it if you die I'm just putting it on the but I just
heard a bow and arrow okay wait who's shooting yes there's a bow and arrow
okay it's up top to be careful they can snipe really easily how did he hit me
he's still afraid we're okay they come the red on I can do this a lot of people
here okay hit nice hey good job thank you thank you I've been practicing for
that one whoa sorry did you get I got a purple quarterstaff did you really yeah
all right that's actually huge you want to live hold still I got I can't know
what else should have used a stronger heal on you hey Jerry I'm gonna trade
you something here take that it's amazing I want to make sure you have
something good too because that's a strength and it's good for you and yep
Wow thank you you guys are the best I was picking this first dips got my
jerk stick my naughty little jerk you were faster that's actually pretty good
too all right let me so if corpses have a gray name they've been looted or no I
actually don't know this question we should avoid fighting you know just in
general yeah well like with the people because we're kind of bad at that it
seems like oh suddenly someone has a purple in the party and we're yeah let's
get out of here let's just hide in the corner until the escapes come up see now
is the time for you to come out of the giraffe character and be like hey guys
let's actually like the fuck out of here what do we need character for that for
thanks burpee I am an exercise of the mouth but honestly um yeah we both want
to get out of here because I have a purple weapon on right now I don't want
to lose this so I'm there with you I will do my best to keep you alive just
gonna get that Luke get that money and have a good time people across all
people across wizard that's barbarian Barb wizard and I'm gonna get this door
open yeah let's get spiders it means there is a pot in the corner somewhere
it was a lot back up behind me I can take these out with like one swing player
dead ahead north whoa fireball well there's a whole team like they're
coming in what did you get some heal they are miss moving around what do you
think should we back get that if they're fighting something though we could back
off we could back off if we could go in well they're fighting another team
they're fighting other team okay oh wait wait we don't want to fight in here
you guys I got you oh I can't go first cuz I got to heal you anybody else oh
they closed this off oh are you bastards oh watch out watch out you can cast
through this hey another group over here left let's not get surrounded I think we
should leave yeah let's go this way this person in here there was there was
somebody right here they might follow us big scary room I close the door big
scary room somebody in here could have multiple attacks that need to happen
they're gonna come behind us I heard him he just broke the door down all right I
wouldn't start the spot get a spot they come I got the wizard one down we got
them we got them all I missed all right let's heal up but I got a campfire I'm
gonna put a little campfire down heal up take a bunch of shit they got a lot of
diamonds and shit they got a lot of stuff well I'm dropping a little campfire
a little rest I was good I was doing protection I was doing blessings yeah
that was sick yeah when I landed those shots yeah they were great here all right
everyone take a fire all right I will I will watch over you after well no you
should sit down too you almost killed him no I didn't I made sure I saw the
opportunity to accidentally hit him and I didn't that's really big of you thank
you do you guys heal more if I sit here with you hi sure always like having your
company pendant yeah let me get up and get the pendant well that's great yeah
yeah I think the fire gives your skills back to okay there was a couple people
that died make sure you lose them this is on the right bar I didn't even use my
heel myself feel this is this is working out pretty well all right we should
probably try to get out because the circle is here a lot of people dead or
shield yeah we got all the bodies right here are they like spread out there this
is all kind of here all right okay oh wait don't have any like dumb bullshit
that I don't want really I heard other footsteps I mean my nasty little grippers
slapping on the pavement it might be okay all right we need we got we got to
get out here I am we gonna my portal we got to get a look at me well that scared
a lot of things I have the least amount of both so just don't get killed there's
an escape portal right behind you two guys one more one more wizard oh I'm
gonna beat him up got nice yes all right we got out out out out out this one here
get that portal going oh one right next to you oh yeah get out get out get out
get out get out get out one out nice job that's good sorry yeah sorry I may have
killed you it's Alex I don't know if I did or not but it may have been me wait
did because I was blocking the daggers I think they might have poked around the
daggers I don't know I I had like a few greens I did it's check the kill feed it
was me was it a good job over there it was in the kill feed sorry dude there's
a lot going on and it's a huge arc and I think I may have hit you directly in the
back of like the spine you can't kill my healer only I can kill my healer but I
will bring you something nice because I did get some nice stuff yeah me too yeah
we're going back in there with the purples or you think we're gonna take
it easy of her own if I win with a purple I put it back in the box oh yeah
yeah you know I mean yeah back to graze for me well that's not necessarily true
oh you hear that oh I I have at least a cool shield for you I want to look at my
perks I have at least I have a cool shield and I've got cool boots for you
too you're gonna be just fine should I change from the AOE the PvE AOE to
different like player skill um the AOE is real the AOE heal is very good but I
don't know I don't really know cleric that well I can't really help you I don't
think the judge there's a judgment skill but it seems very specific like it looks
like reading the Terms of Service on the website because it says after focusing
for point five seconds immediately deal 35 magic damage and reduce targets
movement speed for two seconds but can only be cast when the crosshair targets
an enemy within four point five meters hmm yeah that sounds like a lot there's a
lot hmm I got boots for you I don't know if I want to take them I'm gonna okay
I'm keeping at least okay this is the new plan I want to keep some good shit
here I'll bring you these boots because this is gonna be good for you I'll bring
you this I have a blue pair of boots for you
and I have a nice shield with plus one attributes it's gonna be nice okay trying
to decide whether to do the PvE or PvP skill PvP is probably the way to go if
you're in a group of three oh you can also like not memorize spells and just
take two skills I guess yeah you can I think there's a weird way because it's
like the memory slots right mm-hmm yeah PvP is probably better not fine pants
not concerned about it someone said our PvP is terrible right after two of you
guys just made it out with purple items after killing multiple team groups I
mean that we we were the victor on at least three separate team fights there
were we not yeah I think we're doing just fine
everyone's voting for a derma throw oh actually you should take this ring to
this plus one spell capacity I'm actually gonna get because this is buff
durations too I don't know maybe you should take them both wait I got a I got
a necklace a piece for you to agility the jelly will help him a lot right I
know that's just moving speed now I'll keep that on for me the ring though it's
gonna help you with spell capacity and a little bit more strength I have an AOE
spell I'm feeling pretty good after that after the last one that was good yeah no
that was good we had that we actually did very well I'm happy with it oh there
is an AOE spell would you guys rather have I feel like I can't do both bless
and protection would you rather have 20 physical damage blocked or plus three to
strength agility and will for 30 seconds the idea I like the agility that
movement speed agility is movement speed and attack speed it's huge still I'm
going to give you these boots probably better for you magic pen versus item
equipped speed or magic pen this magic pen work for a clerk what would that do
um is that yes doesn't make your heels more potent casting agility on your
melee teammate makes them ten times better yeah I'm just gonna keep my load
out the way it is still learning the spells I have mm-hmm all right you guys
ready mm-hmm oh yeah go for it doing it do a high
roll around dude oh thanks poke just carried us through that he's got this
he's just like jumping around he's like jumping up here and yeah yeah he was he
was a he was a rock star for that that was like your third game that was like
your second or third game ever right yeah you guys are like let's do high
roller after I think it was game four ever yeah poke was cracked out he was
here are all these things I would like for you to take oh yeah here take this
necklace oh my god so nice it's for me burpee ooh I wonder what that is heater
shield a necklace oh a piece yeah I think when I hit when I look at it by the way
there's no excuse if you die new jerk yeah you're geared now okay big leaks
wait where's your pants need oh I didn't bring any oops I actually just
didn't realize that there's nothing like fighting in a dream yeah I'll find a
pair in a second what does willpower do in this game will power no power yep
bigger heels bigger damage sure fee John's nice that's right you better run
oh oh oh oh oh man that's one of the best pendants I've ever seen this is
plus two will plus three attributes you're gonna want you need to take this
and you need to get it at home oh you me burpee oh yeah whatever you burp what
burple burpee what's your name what I don't know if I don't your name you
can call me you don't call me okay anyway right here uh-huh you want to pick
this up oh I'm following the wrong person yeah full that is plus three
attributes busted that is like an L mega pendant for you you could probably
sell it on the auction house I will I will actually take that probably as
mines buff duration and agility what is all right necklace of pieces down there
are you regifting my gift array try to keep the agility on I'm trying to
recycle the package things awesome too here you know what take this back oh my
god I do it been recycled twice blue sapphire as a gift maybe your gift just
actually got regifted twice that's sad but hey it was good to start with
Seinfeld moment oh I missed that's okay as long as you missed me too huh yeah
Wow bring a survival that's great long sword seriously is my favorite weapon
I it's too bad that I have his weander it's purple long sword is so versatile
let's check out this way gang got the forward stab then a little side stab and
then it's got the overhead it's so it's like the best items it is well I'm gonna
try and get that potion oh that I could I smelled that you just put that so
close to my face I could smell it back swing oh this is a house close is a
white morning star in this coffin over here I don't know if you're it's worse
or better than what you have probably better because what I've got right now
is garbage would grab it was that noise oh boy the zones coming it is we need to
we need to run this way and then bang a left it's bang Edelman this is democracy
manifest okay I got blessing ready queued up whoa hey someone's been here
yeah I'm red alert got my jerk face on they didn't loot this yes they did
nevermind why did you assume they didn't because that there was a secret little
space and we said how have I bail of destruction in their wake I've been
pretty good hope you're doing well hey hope you're doing good too thanks for
asking appreciate all bar ditch you guys want a shrine of protection or does it
slow you down oh you should take that I took the other one it doesn't I got it
already oh someone someone's been here someone's been here they're probably
still here hot on their trail oh look a shrine of power actually jerk you should
take that all right whoa don't mind me just up pondering my little my little
trying to find one drink oh they found me what oh players
that's a lot of candy on them candy is insanely important does anybody want it
somebody should take that candy Wow that really just
no nothing no audio no talking I think he was trying to figure out a way to
communicate but it was so he did you not hear that he said something he said oh
hey are you friendly I saw you crouch and I said yeah I'm sure the funny
thing is a guy he got bit once and the spiders very much damage is he the one
that just died over here it was a spider it actually was a spider and you can
check the logs
there's a lot of us here
can you I can do protection spell on these guys yeah you can remember me you
hit me in the face just I'm trying to get them to come out I'm trying to get
them to come they can't possibly think there's five people here that's gonna
fight them right well there's arrows in our friends so you probably should go in
otherwise we're gonna have to fight them by ourselves all right everybody rush
three two one go how did that go to me good fight good fight good fight wait our
friends dead I don't know I don't know I'm just taking everything I think
everyone died I got as much as I could they they've left you this
a cream okay I don't feel guilty we uh we actually should just keep running
because we need to find a way out of here how does the dude the accuracy is
like this has been a really surreal round left and then left I don't know
where to go here we just go left here it's not there it's fake it's not real
all right over here and then left again and then right I heard one I heard one
hey hey all right who's who's got a lot of good shit not me I got plenty of
space though if you guys have stuff to I guess I'm pretty I got some good stuff
here Alex just take take a ton of this shit I took this guy's kettle hat
sorry but on his shirt somebody's coming somebody's coming no wait all right
Alex pick up all that shit on the ground that's right under me pick it up a ton
of shit and then get it in the portal just take it my and everything take
literally everything I couldn't take I couldn't take some of it all right well
it's all right we were okay we're okay bang left on here all right let's get
out of here one of the friends lived and then Jerma killed them what that didn't
happen that's that's what chat says we have players we're not really gonna
fight over a red portal are we nice first hit one oh they got sure I need a
spot can I get out oh is enough time to loot everybody I have to right I have to
loot everybody you can't you're closing no I don't have anything no you don't
have anything I don't have any items I lost all my stuff oh man oh geez okay
little stings that's too bad I would have tried I had time I don't think I had
time I think it would have been dead by the time I went in I got it I got a good
amount of stuff thank you technically we got out with everything so that's okay
why did I drop all that stuff I talks got 95% of it yeah I've got some stuff
remember italics does not have an inventory full of gold coins I can I can
correct you italics does not have an inventory right I got a raid right from
Jack's films actually I made it out with the blue plate boots playing some dark
and darker appreciate it you found welcome everybody blue sapphire yeah you're
looking to just kind of money money money money you just want to build up
some cash or you can afford stuff I mean that's that's how I stream usually as
money money money you know yeah money money money money money money all right
so oh I did get something nice okay that's kind of good I'll hold on to this
I did get some nice shit okay I didn't leave empty-handed um do either one of
you want a quarter stuff do you like using it right now um I wouldn't mind
like trying it out yeah cuz I don't really not really using the shield right
now I don't need it to this round but yeah you should give it a shot oh press
the wrong button the pendant is worth 500 gold easy yeah maybe put that in your
stash yeah that's in that's in the snatch honestly that's that's one of the best
items I think I've seen so far for playing it's just it's all about stats
especially the just having plus three to all stats it's just it does is a cracked
item save that for the next two days and then in the last day equip it and
just run into a fucking door let me just I'm gonna bring this for you get rid of
this other stuff molotovs are actually kind of fun I'll keep it you just sell
all gemstones yeah that's it's just for money what about what about you said
candy is important can't so go to merchants and go all the way the right
top right Valentine it's all purples oh oh it's a currency it's a currency and I
just found the weapon that I'm going to use and not use to put it in the
inventory holy shit it's a purple longsword I just used my candy I've been
saving it but yeah this is really good shit there it's just like a good way to
get a purple over time though those little candies the little hard candies
they're kind of hard to find they're not like common yeah it just seems like an
exchange for epic okay kind of filling out here so you're gonna bring the the
staff yes I'll bring the core stuff for you okay I'm gonna look at my spells
again I do want to buy okay pants pants pants I yeah I will the eight so the AOE
healed that won't heal enemy players right or will it oh yeah I will it will
be real friendly beings but they may they're not friendly you know use the
purple sword no no and when I lose this I might if for it to heal them I think
that they should have to say I'm friendly yeah in proximity yeah that was
a good round though we actually that we did we played very well it's a six cost
is the problem ooh maybe maybe get rid of weapon damage it's hard to cast all
the buffs at the same time like it's priority is this thing's fucking awesome
too we got protection bless and divine strike did you like the bar ditch the
the big axe yeah did you like using the bar ditch I don't remember using it
really I'm not on your barbarian I'm thinking
jerk do you like the bar do you like barges you can't hear you right now
bless is the weakest I'll buy this one I want to get confirmation because I will
buy it and he just pay me back like he'll just drop 160 gold from me you
have to give up so much to get sanctuary and the other I guess you can get rid of
the thick heel but then that's the best one for PvP like it's too expensive it
is very expensive sanctuary is a six cost another raid there's another raid
from beta 64 also dag nail earlier to thanks welcome welcome Raiders here
there's the balls that's what just happened to the guy with the spider want
to see the clip his perspective really sad yeah I actually I got a great view
of it I was sitting there just watching the whole time I'm gonna go with this I
had like a cinematic view of that whole scenario yeah there's also a
resurrection spell it's true there is it is a cost Wow so that would be two
thirds of my spell memory with no extra gear helping no way it was a real
terrific moment so in another couple levels Alex you're gonna be able to get
a another perk yeah the second one will be nice because right now it's just
there's some good ones yeah I can get as drunk as I want with no detrimental
side effects I wonder what happens when you drink booze in this game like pain
oh okay so that's right people do like brewmaster clerk because if I drink then
my screen gets all fucked up and it's hard to swing you are not affected by
drunkenness in the game so you could effectively just buy like a shitload of
booze and just be pounding it and just get only the stat bonus when you want it
and not the negative people do brewmaster clerk bonus is good yeah it's
like plus 10 strength or something or plus 15 agility it's something like
that it's huge people do it I think you're committing to melee cleric at
that point right and beer is very cheap yeah so if you wanted to put like a mace
on and really not really cast many spells and just drink potions get plus
10 strength and just go absolutely crazy you could your increases strength HP
damage etc our strength increases HP damage yeah yeah it's HP and image
look I'm staff do wielding oh nice dual welding yeah dude aim for the head why
didn't anyone tell me that like the first thing I told you all right this is
for you oh don't be wait ah that was that was a big torch that was a very
big torch it still technically is was a torch I did I thought I had torches in
my first lot but no I did not it was a cocktail well that's unfortunate but
okay Wow all this place sucks don't go here yeah yeah gee whiz he sure is good
at this game dude how dare you this one is yeah wait there's a wraith over there
maybe not that room nice bandage it's not what they said they didn't oh I
apologize oh that room other players across the hall at W is a mage let's
skirt around I don't know we need to get in the circle and this is a dangerous
room anyways they're there for the hostile by the way I just had a fireball
go right by my head hostile the store open they are they're incoming right now
and going for it trying to kill us are we wait I don't know I'm following I I
think it's just one person just went in this room I get some heal it's just we're
gonna stay with the group there's group just one wizard we can come get us you
know you're looking I have to go to bed in an hour you moved if I didn't have to
go to have dinner in ten minutes you'd be dead I only I only have two big heels
left next time I'll say hold still whoa you didn't say oh well that was a small
heel there was less risk involved my mom said that I can play for an extra ten
minutes so you better hope we don't see each other in the next lobby I wasn't
holding down be sorry you know let this guy go man it's really in your head
you're lucky I have church in the morning now I'm gonna do a lot of shit
there's really nothing here you don't want gray pants I like to call it gray
pants grants about blue pants that's way better hmm okay I don't much crap plus
magic pen plus willpower plus knowledge do you like dual wielding uh it's my
first time it's kind of wonky no complaints so far are we go which way
we going ah just probably go towards the middle but not quite the middle
because that's where all the gamers are gonna be maybe let's check these side
rooms yeah good idea well back it up yeah back it up whoa you said it right
fuck germa what I said it right once I feel like people get mad if I say it
wrong which one do welding camp down here little camp room dual welding I
say dual welding I also call it a tomb instead of a tome but there are tombs
give it like a like a book tome tome tome tome you want a shield please call
them Derek I was like I don't know what that would bit that is hey do you want
to shield Derek Derek I'm using a quarter staff but yes I mean you get you can
call me really whatever you want burpee Derek Oh Darryl is their old game
they're all good okay but jerk jerk yeah I did say I answered a jerk we
should probably go the other way all right I also I mean he Brad just
whatever really I don't really have much so I don't have like any blues I have a
couple of greens but anybody has anything good I would say you should
probably leave if we find a portal yeah I got nothing either
oh goodness always gets me those things it's just scary it's real ooh this is one
of those I'll still jerk this is a huge item call this is a two-handed shield
maybe I'll try it one day is there a range on bind points seven five second
stun oh players south oh yeah should we go around over here maybe sneak up on
them we could see they're coming this way yeah we could sneak I think yeah
they're going the same way they're chasing us I think we're gonna meet them
in the middle here I think like well at some point give us some light the circle
is gonna push us back out it is maybe let's not go here it is oh wait there's
a little secret passage here we use a hidden little passage don't let them
thought that three combo was gonna do it no okay well there's a green armant in
there want that right here guys left me in the dark stock and I want the green
arm that no don't shoot me a green one the green arm that sure don't worry
about healing me I got it we need to go Ross bro we're gonna go there's oh we're
really this is the wrong way here really get troubled out oh oh it all fell apart
right now uh-huh so drop baby drop down and go right oh I'm about I'm dropping
down and going this way I don't know where I'm going I don't know that I
don't I don't know I haven't the map has not been burnt in my memory we were too
busy just taking around I don't know is it this is the way right up here right
just right up here chug potions if you need to get that thing open burpee quick
come on burp oh man oh this burp burp do you have any heels I'm just let me get
to the light okay hey we're fine we're just as we're just as messed up as you
we're just as messed up as you were just trying to live yeah really yeah man this
is a lie I think can't heal yourself whoa this is a lie I think no it's not
all right I am gonna try to I'm following our new friend I was trying to
make money I got no more holy light I got a surgical kit and oh yeah okay I
have a full heel uh-huh I got one more potion of these I got two more potions
okay this is where it gets ugly though wait I could have killed him but I let
him go he it's all right it's all right we just got to defend here sure do you
have a drink no here take this is my last potion oh yeah all right I'll look
for another portal over here here I really don't have them this is I have a
surgical kit the strategic hit on the ground here what does that what does
that do it's a full heel oh so but it makes I see one there's two here guys
turf needs it yeah somebody actually oh jerk get over here oh don't worry about
the heel there's a portal if someone needs it look at that on here well I
luck boys I'm out I'm all alone you guys should take my stuff first at least
jerk take this or be yeah bye is there one more it might be one more I mean I
think that there's I think it's all darkness oh no is there not one more
goodbye okay well oh it was we made it though we did it that counts as a win
that counts as a win I'm sorry I should I should kill that guy hey everything's
good the only reason why I really wanted to leave is because I wanted to keep
this shield it's a two-handed shield I'm curious how it works Burpee sacrifice
that blood is on your hands it is yeah put it on the ground and it blocks the
way and gives cover really I kind of want to just try it I might this might be a
naked run for me I'm just curious how this works to bring out that heater
shield back in for you all right bud sell I'll take 60 bucks that sounds
pretty good rain campfire too or maybe just kill a
ranger and take his yeah just just kill somebody else and take their stuff hmm
do you and I'll just sell it let's get the money for it why not yeah whatever
take this off keep that that's fine this I don't want to bring this this is just
I'm just gonna die so it's all right all right huge shield maybe I'll take like a
short sword or something yeah in case it will buy some potions yeah I'm ready to
try this weapon let's do it we are you ready a ripple can I ask where the name
ripple come from okay I was taking a sip let's drink I was taking that time to
eat some some liquid you eat liquid mm-hmm well you drink liquid oh yeah I
I'm sorry I thought I was speaking but it was in my mind oh that's called
thinking my forefather before me was Fripple and his father triple I am
ripple oh cool okay let me try this can I swing with it and I like attack okay
so you can I can set it down and we can block a door with it it's weird yeah
they'll get him with it over zones coming in you block a door they eat them
by scarabs yeah good plan okay so then what about just holding okay I can just
hold it in front of us like I'm just in scroll flood really um jerk I was just
wondering if you ever consider having children if you would name you know name
them similar to your own like jerk jerk like for example dirt birth wait I was
gonna name one sir and then make him be a surfer I think I hold this or a peasant
uh-huh get it so uh that hurt oh no I don't know how you just what the fuck is
going through the shield the arrows are all right can you guys kill them from
here I hope we're all the flesh oh shit so I'm gonna move forward okay here we
go what was that wrong fire you're on fire just okay hold still for one second
you just saved my life okay so it was I holding it wrong okay I've used almost
half of my heels in the first encounter so we'll need that's yeah that's my
fault try and find some other antidotes just leave it on your back huh well it
actually block if it's off my back you look like a turtle when you get that on
it does all right that's kind of cool trying to find the practical way to use
that thing well I'm just getting real jerked up right now
jerk you okay jerk better I have potions you would like them you want potions
maybe maybe one there just take it I got it I can help I've managed I've also got
an extra potion very cool on the floor you guys are too kind nobody open to
this campfire will restore your spells and I have a campfire I could let me
just put it down now just use the spells on jerk then I'll get back the potions
campfire well there's only one I think so how many does it bring back I'm
healed now maybe I shouldn't do the campfire well I just used because the
campfire will restore your charges I got one big heel in two small heels how
about yeah maybe say yeah we're good next room we can use it and maybe if we
need it let's go just open that door because it's cool uh where's the circle
we're in it but where is it slowly starting to recognize rooms mm-hmm I
help you're doing great oh nevermind oh we need a lockpick oh yeah that's what I
just oh nevermind a spell book here magical damage to I don't know who
matters for you but it's right there gray spellbook oh so I there's a portal
portal just open somewhere over here somewhere oh you heard it yep I don't
know exactly where but one did just spawn oh here it is right here
anybody want to get out I don't have anything let's maybe clear out this room
yeah we can just keep this one in the pocket okay um what was that oh okay
girl girl banged up no you're a little roughed up I don't honestly I want to
die because I want I want this shield did I don't never want to equip this
ever again healers don't get any loot oh wait I got that heater shield for you
get over your ripple coming so you didn't get away out last time so I
think we should give to ripple yep hey wait ripple oh I already have a green
shield but thank you for a second one take this take this yeah ripple take
this take this take this take this take this yeah I think you're gonna need that
actually you throw this away no you can sell it you can sell it take my garbage
wait why am I picking that up the shield is so big hold on I'm gonna hop down
here and kill some skeletons oh there's more than I thought oh jerk jerk I come
back towards the middle I can give you some spells from here sure if I have to
I'm gonna come and help you but I don't oh my god there's a lot you're right I
wasn't jerk around it's a red skeleton too I'm just gonna go ahead and have
this portal open just in case I get sneaked up on I would say that's a good
idea all right I got before it before I leave come to the middle for a heels oh
I'm just getting real chipped up can you throw me a heel burpee oh yeah that's
the stuff hold on I got another one I'm gonna laugh if you turn around the
portals gone somebody ran in it it's so great having a cleric thanks burpee
another one I heard all right I'm out peace take care if that's run of power
you've got the power right Wowie here I go another I heard it again I heard it
somebody's waiting right I think they heard us I think oh yeah they're gonna
come mm-hmm oh but you know what oh oh shit I thought I could get out I thought
I could jump over his head there was so many bats oh god oh no nice nice nice
you can do it you can do it Wow Wow Wow Oh so close I should got in closer I
don't like that shield turns up I only only YouTube can escape and I'm
I die or only I escape and you two die yeah next time let's kill you first so
we get out I'm gonna I'll bring some okay stuff this time that was a joke
guys I didn't mean it you're welcome to try whoa that was cool but look at this
stuff is good I'll take this hey you want me to bring you a blue long sword
need man I would actually love a blue long sword all right you got it it's
yours if you're gonna bring a blue long sword then I kind of want yeah I want
to make sure I get some decent stuff on I'm gonna get me a gift that's nice no
yeah I can I can give you something I just said that cuz it sounded like
that's what you're gonna say yeah I can give you so you're gonna say ah yeah I
can give you you don't have to I sound like you're about to say that so I was
like thanks okay I'm just saying trot try try try I'm giving you a purple
oh right yeah I'm gonna I'll try so this is a this is an opportunity for you to
like you know go for it really show your stuff yeah if you're gonna give me a
blue long sword that because this is I don't really like this way under I'm not
a big fan I'm gonna give it my best yeah you you will okay I am almost ready I am
ready and by the time you're ready I will be back from this brief pee break
okay I'm even gonna bring a camp kit I gave a camp kit to one of you before I
think Alex got it I bring anything else you know what spend it I have a can't
yeah maybe I'll bring up I'll bring a campfire kit to I'll bring this shit to
and then I'm gonna go I'm gonna buy just some shitty stuff yeah waiting for I
hope you I wish you well with this way under it's very hard to use why is it's
a gigantic 180 degree swing in front of you whoa if you have friends prepare to
kill them oh I'm ready are you prepared to die be prepared huh you're ready to
die yes already then what are the stats on the blue long sword uh plus five
additional physical damage okay that's really good plus one and a half move
speed bonus what do you call a jerk with a beard and a top hat uh a jerk
Thomas Jefferson okay um there's something in your throat all right you're
ready for the purple joy under are you ready to get hit by a purple sway lander
yeah but it'll be fun that's all that matters okay there it is there it is
sorry I thought I had to say it too you're all doing it all right this thing's
actually very good I very pretty much appreciate it yeah let's really give it
all right let's go for it let's play let's play our hearts out I want you to
get out of here let's play our hearts out hey let's play that's where that
phrase comes from great to use it here it comes miss all right there jump a
little bit there I got 30% of my health gone but I'll be fine oh only would you
like a healer would you like to drink something I came prepared so I'm going
to just drink a potion or two I came very prepared I knew this was
Gervs first time with this way under and won't happen again you know I was
prepared Archer two archers got a blessing on
jerk I'm one shot in them yeah no it's disgusting if you hit him in the head oh
oh we boo 33 um is your helmet any good because it's green helmet on the ground
here thanks they keep doing the drop on ground button he's asked hey I'm
confused is criken using a voice builder I swear he didn't sound like this I'm
getting him mixed up with somebody else thinking a jerk yeah you're thinking a
jerk the jerk is yeah that's always sounded what do you call a expensive
dinner at Red Lobster jerk I don't know I jerk and turf oh wait
and jerk and jerk yeah I would be the way or surf and jerk stop you you would
cripple you stop as well up here stop what we're stopping for are we doing
Morse code I'm hitting I'm hitting the next person in the head that does a
jerk pun I'll have for protection spells so good luck
you can't stop me from being who I am age you guys want to be topped off wow this
is my favorite room driver the mage library majors casting of the help just
out I just got it there we go oh I thought it was a real age oh it's too
close I lose yeah it's actually annoying it's annoying all right this is a sick
room to loot so run around and get everything get those spider jars first
ready to get flanked get them spider jars who's with me I'm spider help where
are you would you go he's too close I lose I lose losing that's a lot of
spiders all right we're good you're good you're safe
jars over here good job good job against those fighters well done
oh pick up everything they should only leave it I'm jerk this guy's impossible
Oh got him protection spells a little late there I'm gonna hit you I'm loose
well maybe it's not too late hold still you're the best thanks mm-hmm there it
jar yeah okay all right loot city the loot loot loot this is a great room for
trinkets make sure you pick up as many as you can
there's all the shelves on all the shelves book what happens if you
activate this book opens up a secret passage yeah oh okay forget it's pretty
neat secrets one whole potion back here did you loot the skeleton yeah you just
had one potion yeah all right we should probably leave you think we got it all
there we pretty much got I would say everything oh yeah people are gonna come
into this room they're gonna be like oh I love this room and then they're gonna
be pissed off that they missed out it's a lot of us I guess this way and down or
down our downs where we safer I don't know okay this is my first time in this
room so take the lead I think there's also another secret area here yeah
jerk one secrets do you want to look for I don't remember oh no regard oh no
yeah this was the secret yeah there be a book yeah we pulled it I think there's
another one two secrets how come mom what nevermind all right I am moving
south yellow shimmy I've ever had actually mead no what what is mead even
what even it's like a weird it's like a honey beer honey yeah honey ale is it
any good I wonder if I would if you're a bee I'm kidding holy shit that's good I
will take that I would this why was this not looted everything in here is I
everything in here is dead holy shit that's better than what I have on right
now hold on a second what's up jerk he's gonna go through here things amazing
let's do it I'll go first I need a shield though if anybody finds even that
piece of crap shield let me know I miss old I'm just staying far enough back yeah
just just I'll handle it but yeah but you just take the swings and judging by
the kill feed there things are going down out there yeah that's good we're in
here we're at we're in a great spot we're in a great spot you're gonna get
some pants yeah yeah oh hey ah sure hey hey someone coming up behind us party
party party the hell is that guy was chasing that guy I don't know who's
chasing I don't know this is like a this is like a loony tune I guess he got him
one dead one dead I don't think he fought back at all I think three more
three more three more that hurts that guy hurts a lot that guy hurts a lot
that guy hurts a lot he almost killed me in one swing we have to go this way
though no wait let's wrap around that guy's got a really good weapon I think
who's in full purple gear oh no this we enter oh no oh goodbye yeah it's gone
sorry take the other one we gotta get the fuck out of here opening it I'm gonna
wait till you are safe it's open and goodbye sorry sorry jerk all right I
feel bad about this we enter but that guy was real jerked up that guy was
pretty jerked up he almost killed me in one hit look at his gear hold on actually
not too I may have buffed him the half second before his last swing oh yeah
yeah oh he's got a lot of pure physical damage increases that would do it oh the
whole all of it yeah Wow oops oh I got a perks long I kind of I don't know why
it sounds I feel like you're like lying down in bed I'm playing on my laptop
right now guys all right I can't be too loud that was like very exciting and I
feel like your head is down lying down with a laptop and it like it's really
hot on your legs and you don't want to be I don't know you know you got like a
roommate or something you don't want to wake up or yeah I don't want to wake him
up the other people in the jerk kingdom wherever you are parents asleep it was
it was just that last sentence it was like very low and very it was very calm
even though that was very crazy what happened okay that was fucking funny I
can give you an item oh you already gave me one one whole item I can buy you some
gear what do you like to play with my jerk stick can you buy me a little jerk
stick yeah I think I can figure that out you don't like the one you already have
oh I could use that I do have the purple one I'm afraid to use it if I die these
are really cheap Jesus the little throwing axe itself for a lot too can't
wake mom it's past his jerk you hey what do you call what do you call a
disgusting little rodent pet you keep in your room I did say I was gonna hit
somebody in the head if they do that you're full mom what a jerk full I
hate you in the head let me start I waited till we're in the around the
little dinner tables he couldn't can't get me can't get me all right weapons
let's see what do you like ooh I can get a bear ditch
belling axe are you a belling axe belling axe yeah that sounds great yep
yep yep yep okay I'm gonna put on my axe both okay also I just got the smash
perk so I can open doors with my axe that's pretty good that's good I'm gonna
open and I say here's turf this is a nice magic resistance very scary be on
the other side of that yeah don't worry you won't be on the other side don't say it too
loud though all right yeah I know I won't watch in the other room she said
she said I should I lights out by 9 we got 15 or minutes this laptop really
really smarts man yes please should put the vents on this thing stop spamming
the chat stop spamming the chat guys please my mom just bought with this new
laptop but it burns whenever it goes to the chat goes by so fast okay I need I'm
wearing shorts cuz it's so hot I gotta let it breathe I need there's only one
tiny little shitty buckler here okay well I have to buy it all right I am
whenever I am ready to go in three two one punching first wait is that what is
that true what they say that laptops kill your sperm count asking for a
friend probably you'll never jerk the same way again oh no I wonder my little
this ugly son I know what came over this ugly son of a goblin is banging super
hot barbarians and basically you're stupid find out how that's in trade chat
right now apparently that's in apparently that's in trade chat oh boy
what'd you get for me I got you this oh you're the best well you a white felling
axe hmm it's probably better than what you had all right this area sucks
absolute ass just beware we probably lose the worst I got him yeah you got a
protection spell for 20 seconds yep jerk here's a bless oh yeah that's great
hey like in that axe I love it you're the best yep are you liking it I look I
just said I love it all right that's right you just answered forgot where are
you where are we going jerk up here yeah we are growing every everything is
aggroed jerk you may have just jerked us here I'm getting us this door open oh
hey but wait can you punch me in the face real quick what all right here I go
yours jerk oh there's people in here you're kind of jerked up man it worked
it worked it worked it worked it fucking worked we're fine we're safe we're safe
bugs though I got like traps a lot of bugs intimidation check to be fair if I
come back right I don't know I would I don't know if I'd want to come back and
fight that group yeah that freaked me out and I'm on your team that was a
Scooby-Doo monster I guess Scooby-Doo oh god damn it I'm like laughing oh my
goodness this thing is so small I got a heel why am I trying to walk with this
thing I'll do this you have a good dinner plate oh thank you oh are you
doing that what I don't know why just going to start going oh because I was
using a bandage and you healed me and I almost finished but I got the cancel
okay good good good animation cancel my goodness
fine the spawner got it nice job oh brother sure protection all right I'm
getting in there all powered up the guy's blessing that's free behind you
zombie behind you spider all right good good good is that it there's a lot of
people over behind your I can't wait can I stab I don't think I can I can't
cheese it does anybody have a stab like a like a poke through the gate that
works yeah Oh lock picks that's just not something we do we don't lock pick
stuff around here roads have lock picks otherwise we got to find them this is
I'm kind of scared to open this door look at you with a protection spell you
got 20 damage in the tank go hmm I got two protection spells two blessings
here I'm gonna help out actually kind of helped thank you
Wowie we need a little bit of light that'll be great oh oh oh let's get it
together actually they gave me it and then you take this one I have a lock
pick I okay does anybody actually know how to do it there's a secret passage
down there oh yeah you have this space when it does it right the timing thing
okay I'll try it look there's a secret down here I got a secret I've never done
that before what excuse me what the fuck excuse I did I did it twice in the you
saw that freeze freeze frame that shit freeze frame that shit what happened
freeze frame that shit I did it I actually did do it what happened freeze
frame that what oh yeah good job oh a golden chest hey did you get that pick
would you guys go there's a golden chest down here I never seen that before you
just need a pick and we can get open there's a is a pick reusable your rogue
it is can you guys point me in a direct I can I can hear you walking we're below
we're down I even down how'd you get down oh they were secret oh there is a
secret yeah I did it but it was I don't know I did it twice did it what happened
what the hell somebody break these for me thank you
another one you hit the red I don't think I did did you freeze frame it flip
it put it on your fridge yeah seriously oh no a tunic can't wear that you hit
the gritty it was a cool it'd look good stuck can't you break chests oh yeah
true oh neat we're gonna have to call somebody to come get us out of here they
can shoot through this easily if you want to open that that gate I can go get
writers whoo work oh jeez oh jeez oh wow help losing oh my god no no no no
this is way more important than anything else anything you have to say
you're if I need to say that golden chest I need you to say something I would
like for you to say the same way you've been talking the whole time hi kids
we're home early fuck just hit me oh are you gonna are you gonna record it and
then replay your spy no later we just need to hear it my kids were home early
that was perfect couldn't have gone any better well what did I do that for we
got you now I don't know if you want to hear it you could hear it I can't play
it through the mic but I just played it through stream okay you know the talk
boy the talk boy it was on home alone oh yeah oh my god I thought we were on
the same team oh my god okay there's a bird there's a gate right there there's
a gate right there I was so distracted there's like there's a gate right there
I'm dead oh my god I was just so distracted talking about talk boy and
shit I wasn't even looking I thought it was just that we were all hanging out
down here come on you can do it oh brother nice oh god you got this you got
this oh good hit he's in the darkness so dark Jesus oh how is he alive how are
you alive I don't like five times oh that was so fucking hard you did so well
though you did so good you really did I couldn't see shit except like something
was glowing red and I was just aiming for the thing that was glowing red
I'm sorry I just like I we were just kind of hanging out down there yeah we
were just kind of chilling and I just I was it was really dark and I saw a
portal and I was like oh portal opened for us and then I a person that I didn't
recognize was right in front of me I was like wait and it took a second for that
person to realize that too it was like wait oh shit this is a okay fight
because it was really dark that was funny that's all right that's what I'm
punished for not having an offensive perk you had when you died you were in
there and you did kind of like a long jump like the Olympic style like both
your legs went out as if you're just getting pure maximum distance somebody
in chat we got ultimate one guide there that was a one guy I'm sorry that's my
fault you confused somebody you confused another mom at the grocery store yeah
yeah as as my mom yeah wait you what I thought he saw his mom but it was not
and she killed in the wrong car but like looks like your car no it's just I can't
even explain it it was just dark you guys were moving and I was queuing up a
video and playing it for stream and then I thought we were in the same room was
pitch black and then I like walked to this other group that I thought was my
group and then they attacked me and it turned out it wasn't and that mom killed
me all right I'm using the halberd hey can I get you anything Burpee sounds
bad you know I'm you played that it's Alex you played that really well I
could have killed him with one more hit yeah like one hit but in the dark like
that you played that he had a shitload armor you played that perfectly do not
I think that's the only reason I lived I had like a green helmet and green
chess piece and I also had like damage mitigation by three as a perk don't you
dare be upset by that you played that very well here's you doing I forgot to
use judge I see they everyone wants us to do a red portal if we can I don't
mean good luck fine one why did you stare at the skeleton and wonder why it
hit you okay I was all I was all tabbed clicking on a video to play the talk
back joke from okay from my perspective I don't whatever it is a skeleton was
walking towards you for like 30 seconds you said everyone stop playing I have
something important to say it's all right it doesn't matter okay cool you
guys ready for to rock and roll yeah I am ready to rock and roll I am NOT okay
then why did you say that because I was making sure that you were ready in we go
okay thing has so much range I always forget that I'm so used to using the
regular swords it's the Morningstar just the mace but the Morningstar the same
like attack I believe so you know what you should say when you had someone with
your mace you're dead good morning star I'm kicking you from the lobby a heater
shield I'm gonna let that one just fly by all right look uh-huh oh brother no I
should we go down here yes absolutely just work oh probably not my goodness we
all just hit that at the same time we all almost hit each other he's so done so
good morning star star or you could name your child star you can say good
morning star why would I name my child that when I could name my child instead
I'm so glad I did not land on the spikes I was desperately trying to injure it
does have a ring to it what is going on here is this dead what it was very weird
oh hello oh excuse me excuse me excuse you dodging all the traps oh it's red
that's why okay oh my god animals killed you please don't do this shit
everywhere all right up I got some sweet pants all right we can take a
second here junk oh I think this thing's coming for me it's coming for me
Oh P you bad okay I got you hold still oh ooh nice fancy heel thank you
well this thing go away so I can get the loot back there'll take a minute to
disaparate there's a hidden wall here if there's a lever somewhere or a book or
something you you can have a jerk am I doing oh a lever yep all that oh she
could ooh a green arm it do you want that something right next to the sink
club oh my goodness really that was so what this was absolute bait oh no other
stores other source locked um okay well weird we need another lever here me got
this for you need you get me see what that is all right I got baby heels one
big heel all right you know how to get through here there's a guy with it was
an archer yeah look for another lever I guess I think I can room I might be able
to get it through tricky I'm trying to do my second attack and go through like
that hold on I got it well yeah you could probably just pray at them right
thoughts and prayers everyone my face please I just laughed like wildly by the
way that was like what was that have I ever laughed like that before you know
really getting goofed on by this Ranger actually if you just keep distracting
them because I can loot this chest oh okay worth it okay all right let's we
gotta move a bangle that was my only bandage I didn't I forgot to bring
potions cuz I died I got you potion on the ground right now
let's watch over the traps all right where do we want to go down yeah we gotta
check these barrels out when you're done oh wait the lever waiting go back I'll
use the lever again maybe it'll open the other side yeah let's go we'll just spin
the whole match here until the circle can get in there go on burpee no go in
where oh in here you use the lever now oh yeah hey great idea no no you okay
yeah they do but we have to survive nothing's that my shields on fire but
other than that you think you think a guy that's gonna walk over a trap right
there and take no we're not gonna be able to do that wrong I don't even know
why I walked over here what was the point of me coming over I just try okay
I'm hold on oh dude sick you open up the secret passage wait did I all right wait
we need to wait no no no it's a we know no leave here leave this play don't
hear me don't hear me don't hear me I just took a question cancel it please
move I need to check the lever we have to leave do we though oh look at in here
oh a very good bandage I was a lever where would I be one two three I'm gonna
solve this puzzle all right I mean oh you're normal I can see you
jerk yeah what you're what are you doing trying to try to solve the puzzle oh we
remind this is the picked lock all right time to go someone's gonna walk in on us
like yeah we haven't gotten any loot have I okay I heard a portal opened
somewhere but we got it let's just keep we got to play the game all right let's
go how do we get the hell out of here the devs put the puzzle there and we
have to solve it mmm the treasure is behind the waterfall
another secret yep there's got to be a lever around here somewhere gotta be a
lever around here mmm wonder I think we just spawned something just say it like
that here comes the yeah all right we got to get out of here that's red put
we're gonna actually gonna die down here we have to get out we have to go do I
don't you leave I don't know I don't know how to leave I genuinely don't know
how to get out of here how do you go up is there stairs how do we get up there's
a staircase where's the staircase oh did anybody know where the staircase is I
center of the room center of the room right here right here right here oh
sure follow me oh shit okay good oh we made it behind you burpee all right I
got him all right I'm gonna give you a small baby heel okay mmm I told you
that was dangerous don't spend it all in one place hey we have to just keep going
because we're way far away from the circle okay fine dude you're bald yeah
what of it an issue with that character is actually bald you got a you got a
problem with me I don't have a problem oh you're you check this out is this cool
very cool yeah no kill the boss room now kill the guy in the middle I don't want
to do that anymore we kind of have to go over there at some point though brother
you're not kidding all right let's trade let's hug the wall we could probably
kill this boss if we really wanted to lose we don't really have anything to
really lose let's try to fight this thing if we can get it alone it's not
about stuff to lose no no like this the skeleton well we have to go in here so
let's fight whatever is in here we're gonna be careful don't aggro the whole
room but we just did oh slowly take care of it slowly can't see this fire in my
face there's two portals to leave there are two portals to leave guarded by the
rain you guys are doing nothing with the protection spell that's okay look you
can't you if you do this all right we can kill it we can kill it we can kill
it oh both here both here focus on the right oh they're shooting me focus on
the right first all right I got him with a speed debuff jerk if you come towards
me I can give you a big kill ouch ouch ouch okay nice got you with the heel can
you heal jerk yeah I got the right okay all right focus focus focus focus we
don't want to lose this if you something on it take it if it's purple get the
hell out of here okay okay I'm out of heels all right well I got one more I
got one left I got right I hope you have aggro I'm gonna open the portals yeah
ouch oh boy oh boy just go to skeleton okay okay okay I got the next one was
there anything good on the Wraith I'm not really got you guys with protection
spells we got more Skelly's coming in I haven't looted shit okay start looting
are looting we got a little bit we got a minute here just make sure we don't get
ninja all right we need to leave either we have to kill in the darkness until
your health runs out yeah we got we got to focus this focus this thing we're
gonna kill us oh we don't have to just take a portal oh okay okay okay I got
aggro oh yeah bye bye I'm down on you it's coming for you it's coming for you
least amount oh you've already got a portal that thing's gonna kill you are
open yeah just take what you can all right good luck I didn't get shit all
right let's go hey we all made it out hey nice stash I got whoo oh hey good work
everyone we could have killed that boss we could have killed it we killed the
way of escaping alive so the rate didn't have anything did it even have like a
green it had a green cleric chest which I'm gonna bring for you I'm just
whispering now I got three of these you know it's really funny I was just being
stuck and lost in that space is what made us able to live and leave because we
were like everyone else was dead I think everybody else is dead literally
everybody because you meant you commented on how the kill feed yeah was
very busy that's exactly what happened almost 400 gold on Jerv mmm nice anyone
want a present I do like I got you a rope I might let's go long so actually
you need a rope because my best one I lost when the one before this about you
need you want a present I'm going kind of try hard mode this time I'm putting
on a good sword really good pants bunch of heels I got a right I got a pretty
decent setup keeping the boys alive I am a loot goblin or whoever wants to kill
me but I think it's time to go for a try hard one let me see if there's
anything better I can buy no much let's see I've almost got 300 gold that's good
that's a good start that's pretty good almost as much as Jerv I have 750 I had
almost a thousand playing some support okay so there's like gear that lets you
memorize more spells there is because that would be pretty sweet you guys want
to go down to the under area the under area yeah yeah we should if we spawn
near it hmm see like sanctuary would have been awesome for that last
encounter I mean we did pretty good we managed agro on two different bosses yeah
it was pretty good yeah it was pretty good by the way I yes I'm doing the
swords by height so relax I'm bringing a drink for you just because I it's been
in my inventory for like a week all right how is everybody doing sure it's
good yeah why not buy money bags um I could but I don't I mean there's no
reason to have them right now until I get more gear I'd rather just keep the
money it's five bucks per bag right why would I spend five bucks when I don't
even look at I got all this empty space it looks nicer I like the gold coins I
think looks cool all right we good to go uh everybody ready it oh ripple you have
another perk to put on oh yeah level 5 you get another perk uh I actually put
one on yeah oh yeah damage reduction in a small after that encounter where I
died I put the like five percent bonus damage I don't know if that's enough but
you're pretty good to win the next fight okay let me just let's go for it how
many charges of sanctuary do you get I I don't know is it more than one in my
because it's a really really amazing heal to just a gigantic AOE heal you get
to probably get rid of the light heal hmm but I've been enjoying running what
I've got so far it's been working we're staying alive we are staying alive and
I've got really good gear on so I'm going to try this round I'm not gonna do
anything dumb like a like a tuna can a tuna can yeah like a tuna tin can mm-hmm
yeah you're getting you're getting quieter like a mob boss oh yeah you're
right it's just so late yeah that you wanna do it again on the day of my
daughter's wedding try to I'll try to pep it up for this one here oh here's
your robes hey can you please pep it up a little place sorry boss thank you don't
want to be annoyed about anything but what the fuck are you going oh boy how
do you were so far from the zone right now behind you what what a bad start
fine got you healed oh I missed oh I missed again watch out oh I saved your
ass cross there has no target so if I pointed someone and they have their
shield up it doesn't count as targeting them water staff right here green tons of
damage I'll take them decent boots um oh those are good no no trade me trade me
well here trade me Wow I actually think minor better for me ah yeah let's take
the quarter staff for later here you can have him I guess give me the other ones
back yes boss give me the other ones back sir thank you I thought you just put
them on the ground and walked away okay make sure you look at the on the shelf
the cement shelves is usually random little trinkets alright let's get out of
her skeletons coming dear oh oh geez oh no okay begin the loot the loot oh wow
normal is way under which is there a skeleton yep yep yep yep watch out
he's right behind me isn't he um green boots they're kind of dumpy but they're
they're here anybody wants them dumpy they're kind of crappy they're not
really that great not that good jerk yeah good oh yeah it's this room again
thanks you'll see this heal for after we go it's this room again mm-hmm yeah
that's what I just said me too oh that's so cool and maybe we'll find that pick
this time I think I may have hit you with that second part of that swing ooh
wizard shoes good luck in there jerk okay oh there's more there are more who
is oh there's a spider fighter very good very good all right now loot it's loot
time resurrection thing right here let me get that a lot of crap I accidentally
I'm so pissed I didn't I grabbed my mouse weirdly and I pressed thumb
button for and I just used my 50% heal for no reason what a disaster give me a
break you got protection bubble I'll get them have a little blessing too okay
that went to me put a little light on here for you thanks you're the best oh
okay oh are they come on aggro to me they're aggroed to you guys somehow I
don't know how you guys are full floor below me oh was that your torch did you
sort of go down nope that's other people other people okay incoming here I come
maybe we don't do we want to engage or not we're gonna have to move very
quickly maybe let's go to the zone instead okay how do you you can just
throw torches to like rooms you hold right click and then you let it go let
go right click to throw you have three towards you can pick it right back up to
pretty useful all right let's go it's good to know this is a bad door you
guys are going through different doors we are okay we'll go back all right let's
go you both thought you were leading this way oh there's a portal there's a
portal already open it looks like a trap kind of does that look that somebody is
trying to trap you ready oh they just took it portal portal over here guys
portal portal oh somebody went in it oh what oh boy I'm moving quick now yeah
you are moving fast now I just did that in case we get ambushed here and kind of
terrible gear oh hey found a guy like a real guy yeah well not fake oh you got
to be a little bit more yeah he's got our candy our candy on this one good
hat art candy as well somebody's definitely grab it isn't this shit this
shit going on down here downstairs yes well they have to come up here to get
to the portal or the third thing so be careful fighting in this yeah it's got
20 seconds of protection if you want to go look I think they went a different
way yeah they did shit I pre potted too oops
footsteps north yep they're in this room just healed yeah there's at least two I
just want to make it so we can see better in fighting it's I think that's
like a good thing to do oh brother all right let's go get them those spiders oh
that's weird can't shut this behind your they're kind of like shadowing us yeah
I think we're gonna meet over this way oh it's the mommy room oh yep it's the
mommy room so we're at all falls apart here we can either watch this or we can
push in what do you think I go go just be careful we don't get stuffed in a
hallway when stuff's jerk in a corner oh there's so much loot okay across the
way oh yeah there are two Rangers yeah let's go for it shit oh yeah run run you
little you'll devils I'm coming for you I'm gonna jerk have a max range yeah
that's right get into the scarabs and run right back up don't need to chase
them Rangers oh got me fine fine fine fine fine by don't let this person get
it oh fuck it's gonna protect you okay for what end Jeff god damn it ah there's
multiple parties in here now try to find another portal all right bud oh there's
there's three parties they set me on on for sure you guys are okay you guys are
all right I would just try to get together I don't know who this oh you
ripple it's just you I I was trying to jump around the portal I jumped in it I
actually messed up I'm sorry you can do it they're gonna fuck up and hit each
other don't worry oh boy there's a lot of people I want to see what happens
there's a lot of people yeah I killed the like you did the like guy opens a
portal it's a mess you just you just did like the spider-man into the spider
verse with like the port you just went into the into the portal yeah there are
so many people alive yeah those mummies are gonna eat him oh I already back
this guy's dead oh no way no way oh my god I can't believe you got out um yes
I'm all Rangers they're all the guy that I killed is probably so pissed oh yeah he
opened the portal and you killed him and then instantly yeah it just it the
animation just was in the right spot and I hit him with one hit and I died and I
went in whatever and yeah it is Ranger versus Ranger wait no there's one um
there's one clerk well Purvis ain't gonna make it so I thought clerics
aren't that great um when their party is gone yeah hey five people died to the
darks I uh should have been there a little longer um I'll get wait yeah I'll
get you some stuff Alex I gave you some stuff don't worry I'm good I just need
to figure out like my screen was especially dark I know it's called dark
and darker but it was more so than usual yeah I mean it is called dark and
darker but I went into the options and it did a turn screen brightness up and
brighter I see I put I literally put it up all the way and no one's seen that
yet but you know what I don't even care if you see it bright and brighter kind
of yeah ah that's good to know yeah it's in the game it's not met it's not
fucking with anything it's in the game the developers have put it in there so I
put it up all the way I see yep so unless they take that out in the game
people saying omega low high settings high settings yeah because I mean on
epic I think I get little frame drops I'm gonna roll with the same thing I
think I'll get you some what do you if you had a perfect item Alex what would
it be well I just lost my green shirt my green pants and my green shield okay
just armor is good like you can never go wrong with I mean I take a weapon I
guess armor say any anything's good because I am actually out of everything
except one blue plate of boots I do have money though I have like 300 gold this
thing is really good but I don't know if I want to give it to you it's just like
it's like way too expensive for you have what I'm getting for it um let me see
anything in the merchant what do I have in my stash I can give you boots and I
can give you I can just become like drunk battle monk well I'll buy you a
beer sure does it do you matter do you care if it's a one one gold beer just
whatever's on tap yeah it's the cheap stuff get to do the same place yeah Wow all
right let's try again shucks I it's not really anything I can buy for you let's
go I did get front row seats to that switcheroo that you did so it's pretty
very cool I will say the first day I played this I was playing alone but I
think I only made it out like four times in eight hours there's an ale oh yeah
I didn't take isn't it there's an ale and there's also a heater shield it's
not great but I try I gambled for you and I lost bone here see I thought we
were doing a bet and I didn't take the battle suboptimal hit me did not hit me
just seriously oh brother oh I wrote on him for a second you see that oops okay
when when you have too many potions around your hip yeah you're you're kind
of you stand out Christmas tree yeah it's beautiful Christmas tree we're going
down or we're going back I think we should uh that God it's this room yeah
it's this one last time we were down there we lost okay I'm gonna give one
I can get both of you a protection spell you jump down you clear it easy look I
made it go this way I'm not gonna make it there you go
thank you you got it there you go good jump actually can I wear these whoa why
did you break makeup look this for you all right we are safe whatever direction
you want to go that's the way they'll go it's just like following behind you guys
picking up the scraps that you don't want in an equipping them hey far I've
gotten pants from you gloves from you that's the way it is yeah I'm getting
the hand me downs from big brother well also remember we both survived last
time you didn't yeah so you're essentially starting it with nothing on
right hey boots you get what you want over here burpee boots boots oh boots
um this is a helmet right here it's it kind of stinks but you know the helmet
I don't think you can wear it's like a play down with a green arm it had you
want that one is there epic um like chalices and stuff I don't think I've
seen a purple one I have they're like 80 gold awesome
spooky if this for you coming not you burpee coming anyway thing I have is
better but I appreciate it all right let's make it another life let's make a
decision the decision I think that is circled this way or we already in it we
are in it but we should get out of this tiny little hallways this is a trap
hallway yep careful be careful red spiders I'll go get the thing duck and
cover it just duck I miss where is he I got it god damn it
I'm so I can't even kill him in two hits I'm too weak I'm too weak and this is
someone shooting arrows yeah sounds like there's a fight yep there well it's
gonna come to ground now oh my god there's this watch out this is trap
right there I'm gonna heal don't worry about me bless
okay very good was the sacrifice oh whoa excellent something I heard the trap
behind us go off I mine are better better wait wait for weapon damage yeah
you're right wait a minute yeah yeah the trap behind us is going off um here it's
Alex take these these are actually it's take the blue pants that I just got I
mean I I was wearing those before but those are better this is better for me
as I tried to say a lot of words at once and it just wasn't working
watch out potential yep there's a trap right here
God I do so little much oh you cleaved yeah I did all right we're in a good
spot the last time you guys jumped down there things went really bad it did we
should probably not do that although this oh yeah this is that horrible room
we're here pretty early though so we might actually be okay
expert be birdie oh my god and I forgot that it was even there yeah I guess
someone's fighting down below in the hole sure we're like in that distance I
do hear something me typing that just get the shit out of me
hurry type faster oh yeah he's just raging on his keyboard
rar oh this room yeah this is a lot of loot in it though yeah I know this place
is awesome especially in here there's like a mage NPC oh I just protected you
right before that fireball good job oh no it's got immunity oh my god what was I
thinking you know what just don't go over there you're topped off the mage is
down there still about to a fireball oh look at him
we're are good watch out for that thing oh man I was just gonna loot all this
stuff jerk jerk don't heal me thank you I got two more of those and one more
lesser heal great oh should we go back this way should we go back yeah I don't
know what's up for the traps I almost forgot this way we just said hey dude I
was gonna say you should play with Kraken and it's taking me 30 minutes to
realize that this is Kraken which yeah yeah maybe maybe another time this
jerk oh trying to power what a fine let's all crowd in here we have to see
what loot is all right weird question seven minutes in heaven should you be
smashing those are we losing loot because you're breaking them no it's just
faster and kind of cool and sometimes it's a mimic and then you are one hit
ahead yeah well there's a way out oh wow all right do you want to go this time
ripple here takes him but ripple you just you get out of here like all day
you all can't wait wait wait take take take a few fucking things you know I
mean like Jesus Christ come on cripple we need to get you out of here I rub
your little head I rub it more blah blah you'd like that take this like that take
this yeah yeah you like that don't you now get out of here all right is that
enough all right take it like have a nice heaven yep yep yep come on
cripple go I don't I don't want you anymore get out someone's gonna snipe
this somebody snipe it we gotta leave all right we gotta know we gotta fight
oh no we have to leave I like okay all right we're gonna go good everything's
fine no I'm not gonna go in the portal it's Alex has not been able to take a
gear for like four matches in a row monks historically have been taken care
of by the church okay well they just live in the monastery hey what do they
call a church somebody coming everybody coming sure uh is somebody there's a
barbarian here somewhere he's in the room with you mm-hmm more okay I'll get
this one you go for that one okay all right oh yep where's the lever to open
this it's on the wall we're on the wall I can't find it where the hell is it
I'm gonna do I'll do it for you it's right here is it oh it's right there okay
just go go go get out get out get out go ahead and get out oh it's okay I'll wait
for you don't get and get out fuck there's no portals here this is stupid
this game is so bad I don't understand this good there's no portals in this
room like if anyone was listening that don't know fucking here I'm looting up a
storm I didn't want somebody to run in oh you're still here yeah good job
everyone nice work I think we were the only three people in that making yeah
that was just a full PvE experience it works it works I got time for one more
I'm loaded I got time for I got time for one more and then I'm gonna jump in
to another group sounds good that means you guys keep playing yeah it's past
your sped time too so I you know I don't know how much longer I got either but
definitely down for at least one more you do sound sleepy giraffe oh yeah
barely keeping these lids open especially with the warmth of the laptop
yeah it's lulling me right to bed are you cracking are you taking off after
this I got I don't know I won't go that much longer though as we can somebody in
the group anybody want to attack you want to keep playing uh let me let me
ask will cuz I normally stop streaming around like 10 to 11 anyways okay yeah
yeah I'm cool calling it after this one too okay just selling all of my vendor
gear I got some good stuff especially the blue pants you dropped yeah those
are way better for you anyways hey we're doing it yeah let's do gear up let's go
in for real oh shoot yeah I was I was already for real but now I'm gonna be
more for real yeah deck yourself out get prepared bring in the jerk stick I'm
gonna bring yeah let's do this no I'm not I'm not gonna do it hmm should I
yeah why not why shouldn't I eat why shouldn't I take every potion all right
okay let's go for it let's do it this is gonna be a big one I've got over 400
gold now very good wow that's great all right this is the big one I'm taking my
blue pendant too I would definitely take yep and that thing is worth like
millions so just like you were it's gonna be erased on the end of the demo
anyways you know what you're right I'm taking my purple sword okay let's go
I'm taking my purple stick let's freaking yeah no let's go let's go this
is this one's for real this is let's go purple so in that case I'm buying
potions yeah be ready this round is about to be flawless we call that called
jerk fixed high roller I don't know if we should do high roller no thanks we
don't have poke here to kill every single enemy on the farm I'm bringing
lock picks even though I'm not very good at it actually you know what let me do
this I'm gonna be ready we got to be ready you know what I mean okay I think I'm
ready all right go this is this is a big one let's hope we don't lose in the
first ten seconds everything's fine except my weapon I wasn't it's like the
most important part my weapon is yeah if you start healing then it's not that
bad I got the jerk stick so it's gonna get real is it sweaty in that mask oh
yeah it's like an oven I was gonna say keep you having to lick my lips here we
go yeah this is this is the we are not messing around round who's boss in
here there's a boss in here and we are going to run away we're not gonna fight
it I thought about it I thought about it for a second but no that would that
would be a bad place to lose I got a purple purple of my arms I don't want
to lose it her job oh wait I remember this room how is he hitting me well
afraid I don't get it he was fletching out kind of oh gosh oh no
you're a heel thanks bud all right there's an annoying Archer over here
careful they're very good there any other kind of human are just really kind
of beefing it I don't do my kill why not right down here there's usually stuff
there's there's a mage across the way lots of enemies across would you be
better served with 30 heel or 15 heel at the current present probably 15 would do
you got a lot of people around you be careful uh I got a yeah a green shield
for you if he is better than what you have ripple okay okay green shield on
the ground right next to me that's a gorgeous shield there but do you think
wearing a mask IRL nope he is all right it's like it has a mask on right now
what do you love I love this game what are you trying to say about his face
dude aren't we all wearing masks all time three physical this is amazing is
it better than what I have right now yeah it is it's just a bunch of physical
power one will one knowledge this one's all right um Alex come over here for a
second uh-huh hold on green gloves if they're better than what you have right
I'm sure they are thank you it was a little underwhelming this time just a
little I'm doing pretty good whoa this is our time to shine let's kill it all
right protection on mead oh wow protection on jerk you guys can take 20
for free there's a heel for jerk slow on the boss 35 damage and that is when we
take a look and that is when holy shit I'll pick Bard each do you want the
Bard each I think that's all you know that's for you that's blue man oh rock
and roll I'll take the bow I mean I also got two lock picks all right we're good
that were that thing is usually so hard to kill you know where you guys are
putting out a lot of damage we're doing it we are doing it he has a base filter
on what's that a base filter his voice is always that deep that's just turf
yeah if you got a nice base filter can you give us like a
blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah blah I can't do it too loud
because of the parents sleeping all right yeah something went down in here
I think oh brother maybe not know where the first people are oh hell yeah
blessing for you we need to clear this quick because people are gonna collapse
lesson for you behind you eat yeah don't worry about healing me Wow good moves
good moves lock picks in the middle oh wait that's really good I found and also
irony it's called necklace a piece and it gives additional physical damage
yeah loot loot loot and we have to get out of her whatever you can get pick up
all this lock ready should be like everyone good luck you can do it sure
don't jerk it up that do not mess it up I fruit it up one I got two though I'm
too guys I want to break it to you but I did it goofed it twice okay let's get
out of here was you up to the right that seems like safe okay we have a compass I
know but just imagine just translate that how you need to I was looking
backwards so all right this room is awful I all in favor to just run through
this like to the right yeah okay I don't like that door open there's another
party right here party right here they're shooting through the door right
now hope give us a shield and we'll go that's just a blessing I only have two
protection careful careful that's on me two are just three it's three archers
it's three archers that's three that's bad leave let's not do this no fuck
this are you committed okay got one I'm in trouble I'm in trouble trouble I need
a hill once dead how do these miss be careful if you're alone there's no
middle ground there's one dead oh they hired three arrows at once watch out
back it up oh brother I'm out of protection I'm out of blessings I'm out
of big heels I got one little heal in a bind hold right here for a sec I think
they got my jerk stick I think they did go this way actually even no no no let's
go let's go let's go let's go fuck it let's go yeah they're waiting they live
they were they're waiting yeah I can lead with the shield you any protection
potions maybe start with that the blue potions well that hurts doesn't it there's
an invisible guy where he's over there with the other one I'm just gonna run
up I'm closing the gap with the shield shit that's a slow back up back up back
up back up purple door we don't want that they're waiting all right this is
what we're not gonna win this it's gonna check if the jerk stick is still there
yeah where's your body that's right on the left not that one I know but this
jewels and gems on this one oh my god hold on all right I'm fine all right we
gotta get the fuck out of here all right loot loot I'll block for you but they
might have grabbed my stick oh maybe not looks like it's still there oh it's
there it's there all right run this way oh he's in front I hate Rangers fucking
archers it hide in here where's in here behind behind jump over oh this is
there's a little windows that can shoot from yes they can I'm gonna heal they're
in the windows yep they are let them let them think that let them think that
something okay wait wait wait portal where it's out there with another you're
gonna try to leave fuck I tried to jump on them there's one more here maybe try
to get the rest of the stuff and then look for another portal this way there's
one right there yeah there's a different party I think you can guard that no
problem watch out watch out he's shooting shooting no no I want to heal
I want to heal one just died just one Ranger left portal and you can go yep
just keep keep going keep going keep block block block block block there's
another portal down there for you burpee burpee is going for it
good luck you gotta stop them you're gonna have to do you watch how this is
sculpted behind you I wouldn't have left you but I have his I got the staff
oh shit yeah sorry burpee it's okay I have I'm used to it I wouldn't have
wanted to run away so quickly but I did have you've got his stuff yeah that was
and all I had was what I was able to scavenge the three Rangers nothing three
Rangers that was crazy they were they were a kill squad I do want to trade
this back to you well we'd have to go another one then no like we can just
trade oh can you yeah if you go into the trade just go to like like
miscellaneous trade one team there go to miscellaneous trade one and then I'm
gonna say like hi yeah I'm gonna say hi and miscellaneous trade one and then you
need to click by name or right click it and say like hey hey and then I'm gonna
go like this he was jerk and then I'm gonna go like this oh wow the jerk stick
I got I got a real play it out or it's not real um anything you want for me no
I just want to make sure you get this back here oh I'll take some I'll take
some crunchies that's all I got oh my god no that's way too much you don't
you know keep those all right jerfy keep those you you gave me this stick as a
gift Jeffy keep those that you just jerfy you I almost want to give you one
more so you can buy another one that's just a fun like out of every single
spell back against the wall still managed to sneak over get the loot
survive your fee take those away your fee you keep accepting it but you're
telling me to take it away what which one is it no keep the crunchies they're
actually you they're useful use it what's the crunchies take the card you
can't sell the trade sorry you can't sell the trade can you do it again I
didn't I was trying you can't sell the trade I didn't mean to cancel the trade
stop bracing do it again please his mom's gonna hear you through his head
yeah it's really loud for me I don't have headphones and speakers oh my
oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god oh my god I just gave
that to some random fucking person wait what I gave your that I gave your thing
to a random person I thought that was you I just clicked yes I didn't realize
that people were right-clicking me I just gave that to a random fucking
person I forgot I was a streamer I forgot I was I forgot I was a streamer
for literally 10 seconds I just want that person to know that they wouldn't
have that item now if I didn't hold the shield wall up hi you want wait we want
to give it back oh you're gonna save the day here here I'll give you this I'll
give you diamond oh my god you are so wow are you here no like here here like
come on like that's so nice of you I'm so stupid oh my god thank god all right
we're good all right let's do that again sure figure it out I'm sure yeah
I'm gonna say I'm gonna say hi again you got it back because Jerf's mom lint in
that I know she was gonna be pissed what a hero what an actual hero thank you so
much no you can't thank somebody who scammed you out of it in the first no
no I don't think they were trying to I think they were just like this guy's so
stupid how is he that's stupid or is this you there's so many people adding
me that I don't know if this is you it says Jerf went by the name that's how
you can tell is this you yeah yep okay it's all my money oh boy I got the
jerk stick back yippee I I just didn't realize okay thank you so much this is
the best day of my life okay we did that we're good I'm supposed to rate you
guys thumbs down on the karma report oh my god prices inverted yeah yeah give
us a good rating purple oh you have to earn karma reports oh I only got one
oops sorry ripple well sorry jerk to Shay hey clobber no seriously that like
that was really nice you didn't even have to do that it was really funny that
that happened but that was criken staff and I'm glad you gave it to me it's not
a staff it's a stick different there's no magic just real sturdy sturdy wood hey
there's still hey there's still good people in the world come on yeah all
right um I'm gonna have you you guys done you said yeah I think I'm all done
but yeah I think that was a good a good taste I think darkness I learned what it
meant to be a true support when you run out of heels you have to give your own
HP Wow true bestie for that being your actual first time playing the game you
did you did very very well you know you're doing better than me and I've
played this game for like 30 40 50 hours it was fun playing both sides cuz like
the first half was two-handed cleaving and the second half was trying to like
do heels and buffs and stuff yeah but it's it's really fun like it's got good
versatility between all the six classes yeah nice job I want to play mage mage is
really fun yeah they're fine all right guys thanks for playing tallax and what
was a jerk again we have to ask at this point if you know criken just I feel
like I thought I was playing the criken today but I don't maybe he's missed my
DMs or something I don't know if you can maybe talk to him or something you
know I'll beat him up with my jerv stick I'll say you answer those DMs naughty
boy and smack him all right thanks for playing tallax good to see you again
and that's how we're ending no thanks for having me guys I had a lot of fun
playing with you guys good to see you guys all right take it easy bye everyone
by jerk yep that is the tallax by the way if you're not following tallax me
yeah see you soon dude by tallax by jerfa yeah tallax follow tallax if you
don't long long a long time known as tallax and of course criken not
cracking for a long time too both swell individuals but now I'm going to move
on to one final party and that is with will neff me and will have been talking
for the last three four days oh snuffy raided holy smokes thank you snuffy for
the raid welcome everybody kind of jumping around from spot to spot group
to group a lot of people were playing it so just jumping around thanks for the
raid thanks enough of you saying you've been playing this to who you wanted to
it's very hard but it's very fun it's it's okay to lose over and over again
yeah welcome and I'm gonna tell will I am ready to rock and roll that was a
pretty good one to go out on three archers though I don't know how you plan
there is crying coming in oh criken is here now this is like a double raid well
thanks cracking good to hang out with you good to see again welcome all the
jerk all the jerk fanatics we're gonna call you welcome welcome welcome welcome
welcome I'll show you quickly my inventory doesn't want to know well I
just chill I've got some good stuff I'm thankfully was able to keep this let's
do a little bit of upkeep why not all right there we go okay I do have one
purple I had two purples but I kind of screwed it up I'm not gonna use this
though I'm gonna use I have every single version of the long sword I'm
gonna buy potions that'll get ready can't put it there why why can I not oh
this one's better okay I see yeah I'll leave it still playing yep I'm gonna be
joining Will Neff and I think somebody else I'm not sure who it is should be
fun I'm just chilling until then I have to do some inventory management mmm I
think I'm all right for now with this on yeah I will buy some potions though
okay I'm happy with this now no more gambling I think that looks alright I'm
just gonna bring the green what Charlie um Charlie plane hey spy plane is he in
a full group yeah Charlie's play yes he's good group like this yeah he already
has one yeah yeah no no that's all good there are a lot of people playing this
right now a lot of people kind of jumping around a lot of people getting
groups part of the reason too that I had the three groups kind of blocked out
is to try to jump around so I'm not looking I've got a group so I'm not
like really looking for one I think this is clean offline okay I was like who is
this in the lobby right now sure I'm gonna exit I'm kind of scared that if I
don't then the same problem is gonna happen it's gonna restart the game
does anyone know how this runs on DX 11 because there's an option to start it
with dips DX 11 I imagine it's probably not very good you know it's so weird
about all the new graphics all the new DirectX versions it feels like
everything after DX 10 just kind of sucks is that weird to say like
everything I feel like it's all kind of broken after like 10 or 11 like it's
like oh yeah you could you could run it on like DX 12 but or DX 11 but don't do
that oh here we go I'm getting in fly like an eagle that was beautiful to come
into oh thank you yo hello German this is Nessua Nessua this is
Jerma I think you guys have met I can't remember I can't what's up what's up
go on oh this is the finest gaming force ever assembled I am so ready to play
yeah I've been playing all day really have you been dominating a little no
sounds like he's been dominating the answer is absolutely no I am ready to be
hard-carried and just walk around and pick up stuff as well what do you play
fighter oh I hear no one does that is like you do though nobody does nobody
does now let me get let me make sure I get my volume am I my good volume for
you guys yeah you're good okay let me see how I am is good I'm just loading in
I gotta let you know I'm new but I can aim no that's good it doesn't matter it
really doesn't matter this game is such a mess it really doesn't matter yeah
this game is it's pretty easy to pick up if you've played like Tarkov I never
played easier it's like an easier Tarkov but like this is my first BR besides
pubg mobile against bots oh really oh wow not much overlap from PUBG what's
your name Jerma in game my name in game is mead one mead M E D M E A D one like
the beer me mm-hmm oh you're level 20 let's go and what was the name of your
ranger Ness this is as well I love you in E s got it yeah yeah can you
re-invite oh yeah you got it yeah I I had it turned off yep okay here we go
the mead one mead one you are you are Lady Godiva yes yep oh dude you're
looking suited I like pretty sick look pretty sick hey look at this like this
out uh-huh yeah I got a you mean one of these I got a purple oh you got a
purple yeah pretty low level here I'm not gonna use it cuz I'm terrified and I
feel like I'll break it and I'll die and I don't want to get it but we'll go in
with basic loot this time I got wait oh you don't me go on my good stuff yeah I
mean I'm going in with decent stuff I got greens I got blues I'm ready to
rock and roll let's send it let's go so how much have you guys played a lot
probably right I'm at like 25 hours yeah I've seen some of your gameplay you are
absolutely nuts you know it's funny is like this is the only game that I'm nuts
at usually Nessua here carries me and everything mm-hmm so it feels good to
have a game that I'm actually like halfway decent at all right let's run it
I hear you're the best at dodging axes in the world though I really am maybe
stop hitting me huh the damage carries over did you even know that does it no
that'd be so funny you just spawn dead if you do magic in there though you do
lose charges I did not really yep if you're if you're a mage you will lose
charges if you cast spells randomly up in the clubbing kind of sucks all right I
thought it was like a practice waiting room all right lead fighting for us oh
yeah potions hey there's potions like everywhere good start good stop
whoo oh yeah oh zombie oh god don't be buying oh god I'm hearing him there you
go oh my goodness Oh Nessua be careful of the uh there's there's traps on the
ground did he have any good shit on him can you get my loot from I started dude
dude I could like leave now with all this gear back your head what oh there's
a yeah there's a there's an arrow okay that's a it's a tough start for us boys
guys that's yeah I want to spectate anyway it's fine yeah Ness had to eat
hey well the good thing is if we make it out I can literally just drop your
entire loadout on the ground next time we'll get a rez off I believe oh yeah
you can rise in this game can't you healing all right oh you're gonna get
up oh wow is it okay I love how like nice derma was about it he's like um
there's there's trap that there's a trap well I didn't want to be like yeah
there's just a trap underneath you oh I think this is a red room oh no there's a
healing trying to hear I mean we just met I don't want to just be screaming at
you listen together listen I just did an hour on the stair master I'm not you
know I'm not with it that's actually this room is kind of hectic I'm gonna go
drop those skeletons oh my god look at you this is just yeah he's he's carry oh
my god look at him okay you are cracked a little bit watch out is a red so I
don't know if you put this together but the three tiers of difficulty for any
mob are like the base coloring then there's red or sorry red and then
there's gray and gray are like is great wait there's a there's a great will
fuck your head well yeah great you don't really see outside a high roller all
that much but so who could mine by the way I see are you just gonna buy a
pickaxe tips oh this sniper is annoying I didn't know that you had to like train
it or not yesterday and great open your lock back oh no it doesn't need it oh we
need a did we get we get his soul I thought you grabbed it all right no I
didn't I took all of his stuff are you sure it might be in your no I definitely
don't have it I took all of this gear I took literally all of his gear and that
was it all I want is the bow back all I need all right you stabbed me I'm gonna
kill up real quick then we'll go back for a soul hey hey look look look I got
something for you yeah that's for stabbing you thank you oh oh shit
there's a team here all right oh god I'm in he's tasting it's a wizard he's
invising I bet he's going this way it's probably going towards wash down there
wash down there he might hit the cup back yeah oh that's a lot of damage we
gotta back off he's by himself you backing up yeah ideal all right he's I
don't know I don't know if he's coming up he'll up he's coming don't both take
this oh you're fucking gone are you him okay what do they have oh dude five
bucks oh five healing shrine what a bastard all right I'm gonna go back for
NASA soul yeah I actually just forgot that's how you did it do you even know
we're gonna hear people what a terrible time for a fight it's okay you don't
need to revive man I would at least like the option we could try true that's true
plus you're right here right my crazy didn't go that far it was where that
spike trap is after you guys just killed an old man it took me five bucks for
the spike trap yeah this is a different guy what is this that's my brother who
the fuck is that guy that's my brother we all died yeah we just died who are you
okay they need to know we're not the brightest dude I don't know this map at
all I played have you played the solo yeah it's it's bad it's so hard bad yeah
actually where are you I don't know I don't know this map oh boy okay we don't
know where he is let's not go in it's yeah it's fine I believe in you boys you
got this that gives me PTSD drink some wicked babies actually you know what
screw this we're gonna do this oh you're doing a campfire a little campfire
action that's okay there is a person in the lobby named fart smeller who's
killing everybody yeah we have to be very aware of fart smeller he's a rogue
you'll classic fart smeller watch out for fart smeller fart smell like fart
smell it just so load fart smell it just so load a whole group I think you're
right do you like my bacon potato combo how'd you get that oh somebody can leave
it's true what does the campfire do it heals and resets charges of spells I
should probably leave to make sure I get out because I want to and we're getting
shot at so go ahead and get out of here I have his entire loadout so yes thank
God cuz I wasn't ready for those traps oh my god is that fart smeller yeah
that's that's someone that's a three stack yep I feel about this I believe in
well but I don't know if I believe in a 1v3 that's a tight that's it that's a
tough tight scenario yeah I do believe in you will leave but I wonder they
might be fighting that might be two different teams it doesn't tell me how
you how many are left right I think where the timer is counting down I think
that's the amount of people that are still here the gray right the gray
notches oh I don't know no the gray notches are how much time is left oh I've
been reading that completely wrong for a whole fucking week it's like the entire
lobby is alive this circle is so small I can't believe I got that right actually
a whole week thought it was notches for people I have a feeling they're gonna
come out right here I'm gonna go Batman books I'm gonna give them the old where's
Rachel I think they moved in you think they dipped they might be dead I mean I
don't hear anybody I think they were just kind of murdering their way through
well I need healing stuff anyway yeah where did they go oh man has a potion
potion good shot well I oh god this is dark I feel like a rogue turned out the
lights over here fuck this I'm gonna go around you have a torch dude I don't I
don't want that smoke well I have an idea that's a fart smeller super setup
right there I feel like you and I could probably execute this pretty well well
what's that I want to fill my inventory with gold yeah and I want to run around
and just be dropping it when people hit me and just be a loot goblin for people
that I love this I have 2,000 gold that I can make that happen with oh my god
that's a lot of gold just be running around being like you never get all
right you just leprechauns yeah just run around here just every time it
hits us we drop like four or five stacks and run yeah leave a trail every like
ten steps leave a trail walk walk walk leave walk walk walk leave just wait
till somebody finds us boy he's candy it's gonna get a little weird yeah hey
I've been where I died I was the other guy you guys like me someone set a
fucking trap what the what do you do oh you have to like disarm it it's kind of
how do I get out of here oh oh there you go you're going the wrong way oh wait
there's a portal right there yeah you might be the only person left has
anybody even left I think that you're the only one I don't know it'll say the
dark grows darker if I get out and it's over let's see yeah last one your last
version so they all died yeah I think they all died I think fart smeller
killed everybody I think fart smeller found them and yeah yeah fart smeller
killed me too old fart smeller mm-hmm I yeah I have your entire loadout so
pretty much ready thank you so I'm just gonna go in with this all right I'll go
in with nothing well let me put my go back let me get a little bandaid we buy
more visions your strongest passions when do you want to do treasure goblin
um I was probably to end I because that I mean the game is gonna wipe in two
days but I would like to be able to buy stuff now oh yes yeah you might also
want to buy that skeleton skin and just run around completely nude oh that's
true do I like I have enough for it all right ready up I have enough let me just
buy one more thing my passions are too strong for you to try I'm ready this is
the run okay this is the run that I will not die to trap conspiring against all
right I was before we go anywhere please put your eyes to the ground yes you're
in everything you've ever owned is about to be on the ground all right let's get
some big loot well have you found a unique an orange uh yeah you got to beat
the bosses for those are they just are they just ridiculous I'm not gonna lie
the bosses are absurdly difficult and you they're like different raid phases
yeah thank you yeah I saw you do the ghost one they kind of bugged out he
yeah he bugged out one time we got lucky because he has a he has like a pure one
shot where he like flies up and if you if you don't jump at the right time you
just die that sounds like hell right the other boss also has a one shot that's
like really weird it's like this very slow traveling orb there's one that
summons skeletons too right that's the lich yeah that one looks pretty awful
yeah nice yeah they'll all have gems the mummies well they have a good flute
trash yeah let's freaking go take that boom so the fighters like a like a tank
right the fighter can use all equipment so all of the stuff is based on like old
school D&D stuff they're adding more classes to I think right yeah they're
adding the bard that's gonna be wild I just need you guys the front line get
these on the bar they already are good circle incoming go Oh candy our game
team team team team team team team over running looks like to try and get on
the back line first if we can I need my my Ranger I'm gonna stay to the left
there oh yep start start clipping them yeah push him we have the room push
through the choke they hit each other they're terrible
drop one drop two let's go all right what do they got what do they got what
do they got what do they got and this is booty tickler 420 the fighter actually
have some stuff you might like on them mmm really yep I'm gonna build a fire
loot this room I'm really nervous you guys in front of me is like I don't want
to hit you I got I mean it's yeah it's better we got about 10 seconds till the
fires up yeah did you have anything else pop off and come on all right let's go
camaraderie oh my I'm I didn't even know you had this nice double-heel yeah I
mean like when you're past half health it's it's good just a fireplace because
you otherwise you burn so many consumables trying to get back to full
health efficiency indeed indeed this game is cool this game is so fun it's way
funner with people I played solo the first night I played it and I think I
lost 95 I played probably 20 to 30 games and I lost every single one I won like
maybe two out of like the 30 I bled all right this has been looted but they
didn't kill this area for some reason so be really careful because if they get up
top it's really hard to win a fight in here all right we got the mage oh red
skeleton you play rogue or something it's a little easier I don't like this
boy up holy shit he's mad at me okay he's red because I'm a giga Chad are you
good at it can you get it there's a there's a fighter barbarian helm here
those corpse green though oh you got it nice there's another one right here can
you do too big loot big big schlute and it's fighter loot come here Jerma what
look at this what is it look at that and then this one's for my ranger oh wow
that's actually fucking awesome that's huge for me you are welcome boys all
right skeleton you have my bow and my absolute him they usually have some
pretty good schlute yep um magical damage bonus magic pen it's not really
it's blue that's not really for me I would grab blues no regardless just grab
it just for like yeah didn't know if anybody could use it or anything we can
yeah oh shit the skeleton on the stairs is red I'm gonna grab him first put them
down nice wait am I doing more damage to this
helm holy shit yeah you should be so Rangers when they get kidded they do so
much and uh it was pretty good yeah I have been almost one shot in the head by
a good Ranger before PvP put away your weapons wq with me right here you don't
want to get caught on this choke just jump across with me three two one jump
he doesn't know we're here I am the only barbarian he's gone I'm low got a ship
good I have to heal him up boys all right let's go good good yeah you guys
are gonna low yeah yeah it's got a soul heart I don't that is soul heart what the
fuck is that oh that's it that's the thing I didn't take from you when you
died oh we could resurrect this person and kill him again sounds great people
oh you can't be where the footsteps I heard footsteps this direction peek
through here open it yeah it's just a mom we go back across did they have a
campfire no I really would be swell oh just keep pumping happens if you fall
right there there's like a whole fucking fucked up
there's no fall damage right no there's no fall damage but there's traps all
over the ground in there yeah it can get ugly especially you'll you'll aggro
everything down there it's a mess it is always it's awful we want to go there I
am out of healing oh but there is a healing shrine in here fuck yeah I'm
back to oh there's a team over there spider behind he's got a bow
chillies god damn spider have three I need to snipe in him that's the thing
I'll take care of the spiders hit him yep you do more damage than he does hit
him yep he's running yeah I'm opening the door I got hit he's still fighting
snipe him snipe him he's running I need his consumables watch out there's access
right there access right there if you have torches throw them I got it
actually I'm gonna snipe him with a throwing axe my god these axes are
brutal oh you're just going through I'm going in get him baby I hit him can't
hit him here that he said and when I hit him is that oh you got him all right
loot up oh shit you got big shit oh no I don't know I don't know why I
encouraged the cowardly dog bro you're a big dick into those axes I was like I'm
like don't know if I follow you oh shit okay I'm here I'm here I'm here I'm
gonna come hurry up hurry up all right I made it in another healing potion watch
out I have a lot of shit yeah we're kind of in bad shape though
wish we had a campfire we got to get out of here you're there I don't know if I
should lead all you guys lead I'm dropping a couple of these take take
take make sure you got one I'm all protected oh this is on looted the main
treasure room is on looted go crazy oh dear fears out bowing bowing them party
party party party at 330 330 already at 330 okay keep your distance play
defensive we have only one mob left drink protection potions it's just one
person he's fucking lit up no it's a whole team it's a cleric I let him up
get together guys are we going out guys we got to make sure we push it at the
same target we got to get that cleric first gonna push on we got to get that
cleric I might just make a play and die let's go I'm gonna make a play don't
let him collapse on me we have their fighter alone just beat their fighters
got the cleric got the cleric dead nice got him once it is once it is yep I'll
keep eyes up loot fast we don't have much time we're on last portal I got I
guys got 10 seconds so we got about all right we're gonna get a bounce now we
had a bounce now we have like 45 seconds left on the map oh my god that's down
portal cook that I'm coming cook that right away my loot sucks just get germ
out all right really are you sure what about yes so do you have you have some
good shit sure yeah go now yeah that's what that's what yeah yeah yeah fucked
up there another one I just heard another one there's one that was in
biz remember there's still like one left I'm gonna just get out look at her
portal I heard one is there gonna be another portal no no you got to get out
you got to get out there's ten seconds left on the map till the till the map
collapses yeah there's no more portals no more portals yeah shit but it's all
right you got out you get out oh my god I thought we would all get out that's
no you had a purple shield yeah that's why I told him that's why I said to get
him out oh right I forgot I even equipped it it was too much going on
it's all right it's all right I've got to make you got to make life or death
splits in my brain nest were like you just installed this right yeah so it's
like I'll get you some money so you can buy I it's all right very sweet of you
and I got I got I got money I got I got like a thousand bucks I'm good I'm good
I'm sorry I'm bringing you a helm Jerma I'm gonna check my
merchants real quick yeah I'd rather lose the purple and you'll be able to
buy shit I'm not gonna lie I only took the portal because I thought we were
German do you cast anything as a fighter I don't think so you don't have any
abilities you cast I have a heel and I have a sprint I don't think it I don't
think magic power these are all kind of poopy I mean I would that was still a
win we still won that Lobby oh yeah like everybody I lost a good chance
it's wiping in two days anyways sorry I'm gonna buy way more consumables this
time we were ass out that was crazy all right how's this let me see make some
money all right German I'm bringing you a helm and I'm gonna bring you a warm
all have you ever used a warm all but oh have you ever used those by hander
before I've dude I love the fuck was way under I'm gonna bring you a Z and er
Ness we need to get you a bow or else you're basically kind of use I have a
blue bow oh yeah chalk that I get rid of it no you know use that use I was like
that's what I'm using um oh yeah you got out wait a minute yeah hey I've got a
I've got a bow I have a blue bow you want it I mean sure I have one but
weapon damage 36 free strength 39 I think mine's better though I keep it in
like a Rangers and them yeah but if you lose it for some reason I got that one
you know yeah I don't know we were kind of we were kind of dunking on them
that's bringing you some basic stuff all right let's cook it let's go for it
wait how do you just shift wait make sure you buy a bunch of shit merchants
oh yeah I'm bringing two campfires this time I'm not no weapons I'm ready yeah
I'm not bringing uh let's get a weapon for me I'm bringing some nice stuff for
whoo dude I I killed that cleric and like two headshots yeah you dropped them
it's crazy how fast like the shitty thing is like they they shouldn't have
just taken that fight I like yeah because that was just like that was like
a mutually assured destruction fight because we had no time just wonder where
the Invis guy went probably died nobody's probably get stuck just died
dead yeah he's probably dead yeah right he's sleeping with the fishes he escaped
oh he portal during the fight oh okay oh my oh well oh my goodness that's that
is it let's do this oh okay let's get some amulets boys I'm missing
everything nope I hit that way all right loot it up loot it up loot all
those like bats too because they have the highest drop percentage for amulets
and rings yeah like a throwing weapon here like a green throwing weapon
Jeremiah got some basic gloves for you oh hell yeah did this just their their
yeah that's fine where are they up oh I threw them over there my bad old shoes
right here right here okay yeah just put those old shoes on just a fighter on
hard times shoes on his hands yeah honestly if I saw a pair of old like
beat-up-ass shoes like that I think I'm just gonna stay with bare feet I don't
think I'm putting them on it's like that bit the Simpsons I think you make less
noise or something yeah all right here we go I'm gonna gather them all up and
then fear them just go crazy
wait this guy behind us oh there's a friend this person okay so long story
short I accidentally traded the epic to this person and they gave it back and
they were very sweet and they were very nice so you can now friend oh prove your
friendship I take me your pants off take them off oh this guy likes to party
doesn't have a long stick I did not get the job at truth hey we'll loot up
there's a really good anybody have a lockpick no where do you get lock picks
I think you never I can never open those and I find them all the time that's an
incredible ring one will to resourcefulness three point seven spell
capacity this is like a crazy ring blue and we want it maybe I mean I mean take
it I can't use it I just dropped it here my ground what is it the ring and I mean
it's on the ground coming and it's somewhere on the ground somewhere here
I'm sure right there is it where did it go I think he took it where is it oh
thank you oh there it is yep yes they're trying to find a contact I don't know if
it's really good for me but hey I think it I know you're in love with wearing
shoes on your hands but take those oh my goodness
somebody's just like asking for help oh shit that scared me is someone trying to
honey dick us someone invented the honey dick in this game someone in need of
assistance honey dick yeah honey dick in home you send one of your teammates to
seduce the other party and then you stab them up shooting at us oh yeah are you
oh yeah oh look at you how that hurt yeah he's right across the oh I can't
he's dead no I had a lot of purples I was in the middle of drinking a potion
this guy cross there's a bow guy cross shooting at us I'm trying to kill him I
take his drink of a potion and he stabs me 15 times the head you got your German
you're having a dude no I got I got honey dicked he got a honey dick I got
oh god there's another honey dick er yeah yeah avenge me where's this guy
across the way I'm gonna fuck I can't see him make sure you loot me I had a
ton of good shit on oh he's sanctuary killed him I killed him oh you got him
yeah I got make sure to loop me loop me I had like I already looted you oh you
did I got it did you lose this guy too no it's yeah that was a rogue just I was
in the middle of drinking animation and a rogue was just popped up and got me
good boots I'll take that I take everything all right let's go thank you
clerk do you have pants Ness yeah why wait let me see yeah I do my pants suck
I have pants they have good stuff just remembered that I should take wait why
is everybody saying like clobber betrayed you how he might have accidentally hit
you ready hit you it was not it was not his intention not is it intentions
matter guys yeah that was not come on look when I'm holding down voice chat and
going people are gonna freak out like it's yeah nobody knows what the hell's
going on at that point you got a honey dick yeah you heard someone asking for
help I knew it was gonna be someone you just can't beat you can't be on voice
chat going I don't know where I'm going I don't know what I'm doing help me help
me help me like when you told me I was staying on a trap yeah dude I believe
you're standing on a trap so if I'm another player and I hear somebody
going hey dude don't stand in the trap don't stand in the trap move you are
running as fast as you can to that group to kill them all I'm taking care of the
little buggies goodness all right we're we're getting out this time yeah yeah
you guys should be good where we going this way okay all right there's two
escape portals I've spawned feel like I'm still playing you guys still have me I'm
just still there holding a staff now oh wait there's a rez over there I feel
your presence Jerma hey I heard footsteps it gives me strength oh yeah I
see I see some on the ground actually Jerma you're back oh I see some on the
ground by the way nice so where do I spawn on the altar here
yeah checking for you spawn naked and afraid you have no health and you're
completely nude really you don't even have any you have zero HP and stuff too
yeah it's awful oh no I saw some traps here you go here you go here you go here
you go oh my goodness and then here you go there are bandages go crazy here feet
oh I have a campfire too yeah I'm actually gonna make one of those looks
like such a weirdo oh wait Ness you cook the campfire you're much faster you have
much faster action speed cook it and I do it okay yeah making oh hell yeah and I
don't know if you can rest in a campfire with us but try it because it'll be
funny camaraderie camaraderie um rest Jerma yes tell me a story I didn't I
didn't mean to hit you with my weapon it was an accident okay just make sure it
doesn't happen again long stick sorry all right we're getting out this only has
one soul I'm gonna actually you know it's the base head thing to do Jerma has
no pants this is um is to go down and fight the boss with our fourth person
actually probably a good idea no although I'm just potions I'm not that
confident I'm scared well where'd you go yes well we need you um I'm looking for
because of that how I don't I don't have any torches cuz I'm well I'm level 20
still don't know that we I still don't know the map will level 20 about 50
hours in the game don't know where I'm going oh I can't I found down portals
we're going I think we have to go like this way I lied I don't know where I'm
going I forget oh I found an out portal out portal yeah there's also there's a
there is a down portal yeah yeah yeah over here over here what is the down
portal oh you haven't been to hell yet no we could do the red for more out
portals I don't see him all right should I just go we're going down we're going
down let's go to our all right friend go find either get out or go find your own
down portal because we're going down there's a there's a team down be good
there's a team down here where we don't have time we don't have time we're gonna
get the honey dick again no shit another for any dick come over here where are we
going over here we got to cook these down portals okay see those portals go
cook them you're the fastest okay okay I am one is cooked oh my god I gotta cook
cook cook cook cook cook cook cook oh please please please please cook don't
come and then come down all right cook that one okay okay and as soon as we get
in we're gonna make up we're gonna make two fires I almost died oh my god oh I
just read the potion listen how many times have you done hell Jerma don't
use any of your healing right now don't use any of your healing right now we're
gonna camp I okay I have a little bit of experience here I've watched someone do
it once okay this is a whole different kettle of fish okay the things down here
they want to hurt you real bad they're sick but there's okay now I'm dropping a
fire do we have any porches anybody anybody have any can I have one yeah
nothing without a torch all right get the get the full rep off this you up I
like your boots you know Jerma doesn't have pants that's a we are we are very
under he has no pants but potions I got potions that I'm gonna make it out I
think we'll be all right that'd be fine okay cook this fire too I just dropped
another one we're gonna be okay good guy clobber it you know I'm saying he
might be down here it's possible right when you said that are you down here no
no it might be well bird all right do you guys have any consumables I have I
have three potions and three bandages I have potions of protection that's about
an advantage okay oh leggings leggings for you Jerma oh thank goodness you
won't be naked anyone casting spells I think it's him I think you hate it do you
make it that have well bird well bird well bird he's here I'm devastated right
now oh I saw him and then I saw the skill to just kill them no pick his
body he's got he would have wanted yeah he's got some stuff take that tunic yeah
I I think I gotta I guess it's better wanted it that way yeah all right
tighten up I'm gonna open a door he was the best of us okay okay I fucked up
there are a lot of red skeletons fucked up zone them zone them kill him
oh my god what's this one moving weirdly I'm backing up okay okay we're good we're
good we're good heal up and loot up oh my god I got a blue quarter staff oh
shit hold on anybody want a blue quarter staff uh I think I'm all right I don't
use them so I got a rogue's cowl but it's green do we have any more fires here
here's a blue shield take that so I have three potions and I've got any more
bandages I've got bandages just start bandaging yourself we have to move we
have to move right now drink a potion we got to move moving I think this is a
room that's like a puzzle room hey clobbered soul oh god it's dogs oh my
god I'm fearing they don't have much health I
need arrows in his ass right now I'm airing his asshole what did I just swing
it my character swing my character I didn't press that but I'm telling you
right now I didn't press the button it didn't a fucking specter did it I swear
to god hit me I don't think that was you okay we gotta move we gotta move I
didn't press the button I promise that's I think that was a good it could never
be there we're gonna move we're gonna move I just started I could never be my
I don't believe it I don't believe this is gonna get really fucked up in here
all right I think there's birds and there's dogs I can snipe those birds
and dogs get out of my way oh oh I thought you died fine am I telling I
spring panic okay don't move damage down there I take damage okay guide me
direction oh oh I'm panicking it's killing me don't hit me don't hit me am I
taking damage here dude that thing will stack poison you gotta shoot it where's
the fuck I'm reloading okay you summon another skeleton do not panic I see if I
see him I see him I see a king a shy little I'm a little bit of assholes am
I killing it I took an invisibility potion okay I'm sorry boys you're on
your own okay I don't know how to get out of here I just saved we gotta get
my torch work I want my torch up here what the my torch well I can't have my
torch out there's no more healing okay I'm gonna go like this oh I have healing
is it can you guys is there any way for me to go up is there a lever I you're
just gonna have I I can help you I'll snipe from above all right we gotta push
this is a lever by the door it's a fucking mage nest my god I don't know
right fucking now I don't know where to go he needs me German hold on yeah just
go just go I don't know what I'm doing he's gonna kill please please I've never
been out here for it's terrifying daddy's daddy's that okay I can help you
Jeremy just keep you got this I don't know where the lever is did anybody
where the lever is listen your body is telling you to panic you just cannot
panic I try I don't know what I'm trying to find a lever near the door lever oh
my god there's gotta be a lever other side of the door portal over there it's
it's pitch black oh my god thank you Jesus it's pitch black wait it's through
the door I can see it I can see it all right I'm gonna go just go go go go go
go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go in
your body are telling you to panic panic I'm coming I'm coming I can't see
anything well behind you behind you oh well behind you fuck I made it I'm here
happening okay you're mine your body are telling you to panic well but you can do
this you can fucking do this okay you fear here you know god I missed the jump
okay dude I didn't even I'm sorry don't miss the jump well okay okay there was
just get out for me okay okay oh okay I didn't know you made it up I look behind
you are dead man okay okay things are really bad things are really fucking
bad how are you still alive it's not possible that you're still like I took
your head off I took you up there Jerma I was like what the oh I'm gonna swung and
took my head off I your head your head is still rolling I haven't it's still
wrong I it's I don't know where it's at I was my adrenaline was just up really
high and I just kind of yeah I was like where did my HP go I'd literally I was
hard well I'm here in the fucking disaster DPS DP I'm like I'm the DPS
I'm getting in there and I just killed him instantly yeah no he it turns out
Rangers have no HP oh my god I'm just I'm just gonna buy a fire and we'll go oh
man that dude mate may have that bow my fucking head hurts that was that we may
have that bow we all know Jerma has extra bow yeah I do I got I got an extra
I'll be right back I gotta pee I'm not saying you owe it to me but it's the
way hander yeah that's why you don't give me this way hander I need I need a
weapon I need a long sword only yeah shit I how'd you even get up there I
didn't know how you got up there I could through the wall I could press the
lever it was just far enough away where I could through the wall I could do it
and then I got up there and then I was kind of in panic mode yeah I hear will
shouting all his orders and I'm like okay he knows what he's doing DPS DPS
so yeah I didn't then people started running there was a dog behind me and
then I took your head off oh my goodness so I'll see what what did you swing at
there was two zombies coming through the door and oh this we enter swings in an
180 degree are kind of I backed up into you I think that this we enter seriously
it has like a hundred and eighty degree arc in front of you it's huge yeah I
think I back to the top ten anime betrayal for sure yeah yeah but you know
what I think we learned a whole lot about each other today would not leave
germ I was like I'm gonna stay here I'm just sitting down in the burning depths
down there screaming asking you guys to help me it's like what we gotta go we
gotta go you wait for me that's super great super great yeah mates yeah I
kind of blew that big time I was I was helping will and then I was like we got
to get germa and I don't know how you got up there I was like what the it was
kind of impressive it was impressive how I it was impressive how I got up there
but that's where it ended yeah did you fall I never I'd never been there before
it was scary yeah yeah it was pretty scary to be fair all right we go again
okay I got my I got at least I have a wedding the bow yeah I'll bring the
welfare oh my goodness that was funny I'm gonna hit her it's that was I that's
pretty fun the down portal everybody is saying that club clobber dying was the
catalyst to that going so wrong completely wrong yeah when clobber it
died that was just a bad omen I think I believe he found us across the yeah map
is huge isn't it yeah I saw clobber peek the door there and then he got clobbered
by the fucking skeleton and it was like a one-shot it was he didn't even get a
chance that was definitely worst gamer moment of two twenty twenty three world
record for cringe sorry I'll be in the Guinness Book of World Records
cringiest thing ever hey you know what we go again it's fine take this bow this
will work I don't know if strength works on me but uh we'll make it work
right he's angry very good remote nice oh that's a super bandage oh one of you
take this you're gonna use it you'll use it way better than I will it's a like
blue bandage 25 health okay I also have healing mice I have a ability heals me
too though oh yeah you should be the one staying alive though for sure I'll make
any barrels in this room because it just spawns more skeletons yeah honestly
will if you had been in that area I would have killed you both at the same
time well that would have been just oh I don't even know what I would have done
you know what I would rather die to you German than anyone else no well thank
you anybody cast or no so I see these shrine of protections you never get them
is it just not worth it or what they don't last long it kind of takes a long
time to activate yeah and they only last like 30 seconds or something oh really
that's trash listen we're going with not much loot but I think we're gonna get
big loot I mean anything we pick up is good another shrine to their spawning
all over the place Zombo yeah just only give me a long sword because there's
only one point where I can hit somebody not a hundred and eighty degrees in front
of me this is my answer I just surprise you one shot at me that's what blew my
mind it was a purple zviander is why yeah yeah it like just one shot me I
didn't get to react oh money things all right whatever you do do not go in that
cage down there no why there's a nice and I want to and it drops all the bosses
and at once what yeah I feel like yeah I've been in there before and I got
scared I think you're right yeah no guys I'm not gonna do it why would I oh oh
no no hey go do that oh I just I just team wiped us I'm not gonna you're not
gonna know nobody can Palpatine me right now do it do it and you need to do it
yeah do it main room okay I get looted and suited if we sack up hmm did I hear
the pitter-patter of little feet maybe maybe I can't believe we're not finding
now it's been pretty pretty trash pretty bad we gotta find some players oh
leather gloves oh I would love that I think we could still out place some
people we're gonna go get this healing shrine for me yeah oh my god oh my god
oh wait how do you get through this it's like a Mario level I'm bad at Mario
how come I can't drink this I like me actually got me something's wrong my
game something's wrong with my game that's why there's like I don't know my
my game is bugged your your guys game isn't I think oh that's why I took that
damage that makes sense my death did feel like a bug gloves for someone my
chest they better than what I have yes there crappy boots for someone listen
I'll take it and get right now yeah this is all really bad I have some
anything is better than like here I got some fighter boots hmm yeah they're
green they're green here thank you whoo these are nice strength yep I get
spiders what a damn all right now the main room is usually where shit goes
down down it usually does you do goofing baby
holy shit never been here on our left there's a yeah I'm euro stepping him
okay try and not pull the elites in the middle of the room really cuz I'm
killing them right now you are you clicking on heads yeah you can show the
horns and we can bring them in you may ship yeah but you're gonna have to shoot
him a lot oh I shoot him through the holes in the door you can break the
skinny can you do that yep yep I can't even see him hello sir I move away he
usually breaks the door he smashes through it doesn't he yeah there you
go behind behind behind behind behind group behind team behind team behind he
smashed through oh god Jesus is really bad this is the worst timing this is bad
back up this way just follow me we go for this yeah it takes a lot of damage
they're trying to kill you guys in the back are they the waste that they're
coming at us they're coming at us I love it I love this oh my god he killed me in
one hit all right we got this Nessie I don't know what he has but that thing is
fucking disgusting too I hate a shield off damage on the elite damage on the
he's coming for me right now sandwich nice he's low he's low as fuck oh my god
whatever he has loot all that shit and get the hell out of here yeah I got a
fucking he's got an Omega axe loot up like crazy loot up all that shit
whatever it is he had not really anything good really check the other
barbarian in one ring but where's the other one this is this one he had a
hatchet it's a regular hatchet yeah they didn't really have that great stuff
all right loot the elite loot the elite yeah the elite will have something good
oh he had a long bow I'll take that he did have something good nice like a blue
long bow okay you're low on time yeah the elite will have something pretty
pretty good I'd love to take them off me very nice very nice okay I had blue
gloves portal coffee there's a portal right here too I died right there yeah
put him on you yep right behind you right behind you in the room yep yeah
you're gonna get hurt oh that was a good pistol run boys I think it was good I
think it was a good run we went in there with nothing it's hard when you're
fighting a fucking elite and there's yeah that was just really shitty timing and the fact that he like busted
through the door like the Kool-Aid man right as they shoot yeah dude I got purple
pants nice job kind of sit job good job good job I'm gonna buy some stuff what's
spell capacity that's like how many times they can cast so it's good for
wizards and clerics oh so it's not really that great for me now I'm ready
whenever I'm pistol running again I'm just getting I'll just save them if
someone wants them I don't know I'll keep this long bow wait is this long bow
better oh god as long as better they might be more or less arrows too they
might shoot faster or something oh how do you tell I don't think you can I give
to equip it okay well it hits harder but it's okay all right I'm not gonna bring
two too much I just want a little bit yeah let me just clear my inventory out
oh thanks J Dilla appreciate you bud we're having a good night man getting
potions our shuns very cool long bow is five arrows recurve is six and survival
is seven they shoot faster in that increasing order thank you chat member
long bows the best okay I think I'm ready all right send it that's pretty
fun around yeah that was a great run that was a scab run basically yeah we
went in there with like nothing term of this is games not really for you you
should go back to family guy the quest for stuff not true you're natural what
is that I didn't get after the way I saw you kill Nassau on this is this is your
I felt it dude I want shower in that yeah yeah what's your what's your guys
family guy quest for stuff towns look like they big as big as mine I got to
admit I don't think I've played family guy I'm not played that one is it
pretty fun don't don't oh oh in fact we are just I'm just like advertising this
game I know what I do not play that so how much did Seth McFarlane play you
yeah I was kind of wanted the same thing I got I got hit you oh there's a trap
there careful guys there's a trap hold on but I've outsmarted the trap here
this chap right in the middle here thanks the boots careful oh I almost
walked into it I'm glad you said I don't wait I don't want you to end up like me
okay mm-hmm actually yeah all right we're just busting through doors let's
go this is a scary door room I'm just gonna run right at this mage take care
of the archers for me mm-hmm oh fuck oh we got the bubble off that what that is
why is he shooting at me you were you had threat Jesus oh is it threat this
game is there actually I was just had me convinced I was being confidently
incorrect yeah you had me convinced right there I was just yes ending I just
guess what I'm gaslit and murdered my own team I'm just like though it's
harder but it's slower hmm I don't know is it I guess I hit my shots it's fine
very cool I almost hit you will no problem felt the wind off that one all
right I just do have a taunt that's right I do hear it yeah I think they're over
here wait I get see through this little thing yep the window I hear them too do we
want to be in here I see them I see them I see them they don't see me for that
outside this window yep yeah they say this is frantically bandaging they're
closing the door I'm gonna wait right here he's trying to shoot me through
this I'm gonna see if I get an angle on them boys how do you open doors how do
you open doors I don't know how move back move back watch this they got a they
got a wizard they're trying to flank on this side they're gonna try and come
through this door he's opening this up surprise motherfucker up it's a mage I'm
gonna wrap around watch that prank I'll watch this flank it's coming in you
smited me I did a lot of damage careful the windows cuz yep there's one out all
the wizards in the room Jesus fuck I'm down oh shit oh god I'm dead aren't I I
just missed a couple times I just I don't use the halberd really ever it's
okay wow I had to do a lot of you know something oh that sucks shit it's all
right it's all right I'm gearing up don't worry cuz I have another bow I got
to stick with a weapon and use it cuz all the attack pattern we're using a
halberd I have a good halberd I'm gonna try it is this the attack I tried the
other attack pattern and I kind of screwed me up and you tried like the
maces I you know the arming swords probably my favorite arming sword and
long sword I'm gonna roll it on a longbow for you I fucking okay it's not
good ready no wait wait wait let me buy more stuff doesn't sound good yeah it
was not we're not the droids we were looking for so we got this boys some
runs are not gonna be perfect all right we got this I got loot this time ready
up all right this one of these all right on okay all right let's go I'm trying as
hard as I can this time yeah we're sweating I'm literally an inch away from
my monitor I see everything I'm not I'm not gonna miss a single arrow oh I see
a looted up cleric okay they'll probably die first so will what do you what do
you got on I just I'm running a hatchet tax which is like max damage I went out
with a little bit of I went with the bow you gave me it's about it I lost that
other bow unfortunately I have a I have a long bow for you it's crap but it's
probably better than what you have but there take that all right it's not
better but you know what it's a thought that counts how the fuck do we get out
of here little exit here maybe a little thing oh it was a bug got it lots of
zombies over here yeah we got a lot of zombies coming that wide swing with that
halberd it is a little scary how is he alive don't open that chest it's a mimic
oh how did you know he was sparkling oh that okay I didn't know if there was a
way to tell so when I shout me it all the things that I shouted sparkle
afterward and oh even see them sparkle after a shout oh that's cool I did not
know that do we loot these um pants yes try to grab whatever you can oh Ness I
got you baby you got me nice survival bow mm-hmm that's that's the shit I do
like very cool oh these trials really quick actually green
trousers on them anybody wants them here take those put those on okay do you get
those blue pants yep I'm on oh god galley Lord skeletal watch out for that
watch out for that trap nice mm-hmm there's a trap how do I get around this
thing better oh and I just go through it yeah you might have to just take it how
good is your halberd wait did you not take damage I did not my Halberd is blue
53 damage to strength to weapon damage oh that's you can jump over the present
present those oh like you are a saint thank you
light up nice mmm spy is in this corner over I did not get it I see it yeah yeah
oh goblit many goblets ooh team yep clear this mob real quick and with the
euro step where do you see the team over here in the corner we're gonna push him
fishing yep I see oh yeah I'm W King he down that hall I can't tell shooting at
something careful we're aggroing he doesn't know I'm here he's gone kill this
thing nice okay I have his footsteps I killed him oh you did oh gee all right
nice okay I'm not fucking around anymore shoes for someone probably an ass other
shoes well it's showing God gamer mode I mean look at this guy's face plan in the
wall you see he's seen some shit yeah myrtle yeah man what a honey dick oh
we honey do you know honey dick this isn't cleared yet and there's a down
portal or an out portal oh thank you mm-hmm this is scary oh my god these
scary do anything or is that team yeah there's a team at this door oh fuck I
gotta heal give me a second I think that is yeah baby I'm gonna heal they don't
know I'm here bring them back to this corner they are coming at me with full
force I got this corner I got back up I got back up I just got one hit I'm going
to see me I'm good the wizard oh I got murdered one down wizard left I'm gonna
heal up an archer yep I'm hitting them with the euro set up some for the wizard
the archer is probably really low he's got haste he's got hasted oh you cornered
this guy's on yep yep I got I watch you I watch you got behind that door maybe
kiss over here will the Rangers still live yeah Rangers still live at that door
behind you I have a surge kit I'm gonna surge just protect me yo I got ran down
that Rangers shooting you through that door you shouldn't get you through the door don't give me
anything to shoot at we'll take some of these I'm surging I'm surging yeah but
well but afterwards you're you're you got way more used to that than me all
right we got w key he's looting his buddy close that door motherfucker go for
it okay he's gonna shoot me through the door
oh you do a lot of damage well all right he's gone loot his friend yep you have
an invisibility potion uh I do I do drop that yep where's his buddy
fucker did you get you almost oh oh fuck I got a really dumb idea oh my god he
trapped me he trapped me oh yeah dodge you can't get me no I got a really dumb
idea I'm sorry I just saw a bit no Jarba fuck I did it all right avenge me I
forgot they even had those shit yeah he outplayed me so bad I didn't even know
he had it oh no how much health was he at I hit him twice oh one HP I just like
no it wasn't I was in what HP damn it oh we we played that all right too it's
just I chased him down I didn't wait for you I got ran down by all of them I just
get I just my brain just goes full-on panic mode it's okay my heart goes like
this that's that's how it's supposed to go no my god that's how it's supposed to
go tiny Tina raid is that a Tina Kitten raid
okay oh my god the TK that was a good play by that Ranger seriously yeah okay
I hit him to that door but they went through and they ran through if I get
caught in that what's the play you got to look down at it and press F so you I
can get I can pull I can pull myself out yeah you have to decide yeah oh fuck you
had the right idea they're like you you were dodging while he was like trying to
headshot you okay okay just really good I almost got him at the end you really
did yeah I hit one HP I should have waited for you that was my fault that's
all right okay it was that a wizard like one shot me that was a good fight
though we we killed that pretty much the whole team it's just the um that Ranger
just knew what he was doing I lived we would have won 100% I just died like too
quickly it's good to know that I can take it off I just didn't really think
about it I probably if I got it all right full health to how long does it
take to disarm like 10 seconds thank you tiny T for the rainbow it's like three
seconds oh it's quick I thought I was gonna be long too shit gamer knowledge
what the heck you'll know next time it's also like a panic thing like all of a
sudden yeah I go fuck all the reason goes out the door I think that's the
first time I've been in a Ranger trap too I think that's why like I just was
not expecting it that's the first time it's ever happened practice just a
little practice bandage all right we going in yeah oh sure suck let's not go
that way secret secret room secret room
I'll search we're taking combat we're taking it off they don't know I'm here
fucking headshot got him drop one just the Ranger I'm getting an angle on him
he's lit he's lit yep he pulled aggro too I got an angle on him sorry
enforcer you didn't get the job done drop on him I've shot this motherfucker
like ten times got him he's gone okay clear the archers archers all right let's
click let's clear the room and we'll do I'm bumping into I hope this Ranger has
I'm taking so much Barbie there's another person there oh shit oh yeah fuck
this friend you're in a res room just win this and you can res me back after
my back officer man yes oh my god he's almost gone he's almost got a reload I
gotta reload just run a lot of hits watch out there's a there yeah there is
there was a bandage on my body and they're obviously while killing there's
in there healing I'm getting your soul every load you won't be able to res me
you don't have enough health but he can okay you know do you have anything on
you know no such a hills total um all right here you take it as can I drop
your soul on the ground yeah okay here so you take the soul all right me yeah
cuz I think you have you yeah I can't do it I don't know he doesn't have enough
health to res me oh do you take your health take these bandages too okay
where's the soul I don't know he's full health you need those bandages baby
all right I'll take them go res me it's right in the middle of the room all right
middle room got you coming there we go boys we're back dude I ran up on that
cleric your allies oh do I have to put where do I put it I you put it in your
your quick bar like an item and then you do it oh I'm praying oh well I'm gonna
give you these bandages because you're gonna be naked and yeah this is a shit
load of bandages on the ground hopefully this barbarian was looted too that
ranger was looted wasn't he oh and I think there's still pretty good where
the hell that barbarian die I have a ton of potions do you guys was my under
here Jeremy I got some potions yeah I'm just taking the stuff I'm looting the
other guy over here yeah I'm gonna drop it right behind you oh nice old shoes
rare thank you guys I need healing I dropped a bunch of bandages on the
ground over here right behind you he had a campfire we're okay
don't read that cleric okay he's got the red skeleton skin uh it at all plus
two strength leather helmet and then we'll take take these bandages we're
gonna campfire it's okay okay well perspective you ripped off your shirt
they whipped out his heart and started praying that's how I do it that's the
only way you can bring will back any random ass weapons rip your shirt off
and pray okay I'm gonna campfire right here
Jeremy you're gonna need this yeah get your bacon and potatoes ready bacon and
potatoes oh that sounds delicious boys that was clean except for us not
noticing that there's a third person that was not just always kind of soon
there's gonna be one that was not very pog you're right that was what happens I
get these diamonds and there's Ruby in this camaraderie that you camaraderie
camaraderie hey does anything happen if I take this statues no rip those
eyeballs out oh I'm bad I have a diamond all right we go this way open this door
and we gotta start moving yep yep oh yeah oh snap I thought that a voice is
will oh yeah we got the will nef in the building right now and that's a lot so
and that's a lot don't forget I'm sorry oh my goodness you're too kind I knows
what I know you got spider on you German you got two spiders on you hey I know a
will nef that's pretty darn good too yeah old coin oh god it's my hand I get
the spider spawner this is looted I'm trying to find where the spawner even is
bro this is money guys what does this book activate do don't touch it in some
secret room it's demonic I mean I'm kind of scared
I think there's traps in there be careful there's definitely spider
spawner yeah and this potion is in the ground I can kill the uncle a jar that
is one right here maybe as a more heels I might my god I'm right behind you why
won't he die let's get this shit oh we got to get out of here we do yep gotta
go all right I will I do yep you should also heal yeah I'm currently got one
going right now I'm good it hurts I can't see oh watch out fighters come
through very nice very nice very good oh mega golden chest but it's a lockpick
whoa let's go into the main room advantage ain't room over here boys how
we get over there oh yeah go there's a golden chest over here I don't know if
it's worth anything but we can't really stick around there might be another team
here I'm coming oh come on watch out for that trap on the wall yep what wall
they just everywhere her wait the main rooms this way sorry I fucked up now do
we just have to go under this way well do you want a bench those just going did
well I have potions if you need them yeah yeah I'm clearing this let me drop
them yeah portal oh god wait why is this archer just oh Jesus oh we aggro'd we
all right fall back here fall back here oh we aggro big time pull it back here
pull back here Jerma Jerma has come back here I didn't I didn't do it I didn't I
swear I swear I think it's all you no no no I didn't I swear okay we aggro'd both
bosses I swear to God I didn't a fucking we can go we can go we can move I can't
survive if they hit me oh my god I'm trying to pull aggro from the rave
there's no shot I pulled aggro from the rave and now he's killing me oh I'm
running back this way I'm reloading hang a left get back into the main room
there's down portals I'm gonna cook one cook one up another one across the way
in them right now down portal across the way I'm coming coming coming coming
coming coming coming no where'd you go this is so bad turn turn turn to me I'm
just cooking the outs oh you are stuck in here get in the main room I have a portal for you
all right you're dead okay they're they're on their way so we should get
that we should get out of here now they're they're chasing you just take
that portal and get out are they oh my god wait hold on oh yeah yeah well one
runs for one there's one open for you yep just be there get they're coming in
right now got it okay nice bro I ran into a dead end and they ran in that
fucking room there was no shot I got trapped I promise I didn't aggro them
both no I yeah I don't think you I promise that wasn't you know I think hey
you know sometimes sometimes you just I grew the bosses hey well we believe in
anyways that's our I feel like I need a bow now you can use a crossbow right
yeah I have one I guess oh damn it I'll use a crossbow tried to gamble for you I
got you a good never never gamble I know stupid all right let's go again okay
this is a we going for a real deal run I mean I only have a crossbow yeah pink
ward I'll definitely take that I died real deal run I I'll put my purple long
sword on I'm in misc oh if you're gonna carry me I'd listen my man pink ward
coming through gigantic well are you taking anything good or is this pistol
run pink ward just gave me a fucking sick axe so I'll gear up all right let's
go for it I only have a crossbow we buy a couple
potions and I'll be good man that sucks I got some pretty good stuff too last
room yeah you got just locked in that room I know I thought I was like running
to you guys but I ran that dead end and I was like oh I let's send it thank you
pink ward shout out pink ward don't lose it in your first run okay dude listen
you know there's no problem I can't make there are things we've done we've been
through it is your crossbow 50 damage or how what's your damage or any crossbow
oh my god yeah it's like I got armor for you I've never used a crossbow this is
terrible oh my god does it stink yeah cuz you only shoot one at a time they
have to reload that that's a boy that's just funny what's the axe you have is it
is it crazy it's suited oh it's real good all right all right I'm trying as
hard as I can I got armor for you too take this German oh thank you don't take
that axe that's uh the one I was using before all right here we go oh this thing
is fucking godly who read the pyramid room what why do I have to reload
already single shot crossbow oh my god I have this only gonna take your vote 15
minutes don't worry guys I have these bats don't worry at one point my shot
will land mm-hmm oh he's starting to believe I hit it most got me let's got
me well oh it's a necklace knowledge yeah yeah you were right will be these
things drop yeah this is the best loot room yeah it's trying a little light be
nice yeah the light sees lockpick where are you
Ness this pendants for you there you go dropped it oh shit he's a torch did you
drop it in the there's a door open on this side that makes me very nervous
uh-huh I'm trying to find this thing you dropped oh god I think it's gone
zombies yeah let me help you oh that is not helping me that's although that was
mage setting me on fire well Ranger outfit oh right here green put that on
good stuff I'm take it all right let's go to the main loot room this way a kettle
hat oh here's that rogue where I'm W King drawn in there's only be two others
probably oh he's yelling in VoIP oh he just ghosted yeah I turn boy bond not if
I tell you first came to the wrong neighborhood mother fucker
there is yes I'm nice hello Kelly Ness oh god you're right yeah yeah oh god oh
Ranger this is how stupid I am I saw his footprints right there like where he had
stealth he has a bunch of potions to here bunch of potions on the ground
my god my euro step socks wait necklace that was you have a necklace you don't
have much I'll take movement speed is good yeah I saw his footprints and I was
like see right here and then he came out just fucking started wailing on me he
actually was killed me we gotta get we gotta get you something besides that
rubber band shooter yeah it's not my I don't do much this is a scary room I'm
just here for the ride scary room oceans and shit oh I hit it oh that's take
these help I can't kill it drop gloves for you
yeah taking gloves you know all this loot yeah I'm getting loot all right so
what's the play here we are we sticking it over here we gonna we are right in
the center of the circle that we are destroyed heavy boots all right I'm
gonna give you these Ness just drop green boots for you got a lot of stuff
move speed I like move speed I got a I got some extra bandages they're taking
up space I have too many for me they're about by me top off jump across team
over here he's trying to cook an out portal I'm gonna kill him oh my god that
guy went the guy ran ran through the door this door yep see his footprints
hmm yep yep yep I'd be self I'm following the footprints we're going the
right direction and down here you went up here yeah I'm gonna take the speed
trying in case we find him I feel like I'm here I feel like I like I feel like
I bumped into him in here that was weird like I lagged but I don't know if there's
portal there's a portal there's a wizard here oh yep he's that's read from is so
much they are oh you got they're in a lot of trouble he's hitting the portal
he's hitting the portal I shot him I'm shooting him shoot him he took the
portal god damn it he actually get through it yeah the Wizards not though
the Wizards fucked the wizard went through the right he said he's still
there the Wizards still there yeah we don't need to push that we need to go
back to this one oh I hit him yeah we're gonna get hit by all these little
spiders yeah we're gonna get the hell out of here there's someone over here oh my
god kill those fucking spider on me I'm going to lose my mind come through
cover right behind you where's Rachel are you on potions I'm all right I'm
here I'm gonna should I cook this all right motherfucker you want to play it
like that talking it I'm shooting in your back nice nice oh my god all right
who should take this one of us should I'm gonna get out with this axe yeah
open good luck boys take care I be well all right we need to find another one
pushing up down here a wizard still left by that yeah I don't know do we go up or
oh yeah I go that way I hear somebody in the trap room I reload those my weapons
we go up I'll be back where the hell does this go person all right loot loot quick and then
oh geez oh geez make sure you duck he has a campfire oh really yeah take all
this shit I don't think we need to use it though do I know but I mean did I
just what do you yeah be careful there's all right we gotta move this way we got
up yeah crouch this whole time crouching all right how do we get it's gotta be a
portal here right I hear someone all right I don't see anybody on something
oh there's a scape here you take it I think you have more than me I got a
little bit do you have any purples here's someone I'm gonna run in just be
careful it's coming it's coming you want to kill yeah you see you got this he's
coming I gotta watch this baby if somebody comes from behind me I'm gonna
I'm running in this portal yeah there's a potion I do not I guess I try I do I'm
just gonna go in yeah you just go this shit's all right now I gotta find a way
out cuz you know oh perfect there's definitely one person there clean yep
very clean that guy nice axes that's pretty big I made it out with a lot of
loot dude all right I I've been live for about eight hours I maybe one more call
it maybe one or two more all right and then I'm probably gonna go to bed there
enough but that was a good one yeah maybe like two or three more you want you
to treasure goblin RP uh yeah might as well all right not why not I need I need
some like goblin shit goblin what's like goblin any like a I don't know like a
maybe a skeleton I was gonna just have a shitload of potions I was gonna have my
inventory open and just be running and dropping stuff I'm gonna bring it just a
bunch of ten golds mm-hmm yeah I am too I don't want to burn through all of your
money for the stupid joke I it's gonna go one of two ways I'm gonna die
immediately and I'm free money for somebody or say you should just break it
up and drop a coin I will I will just bring a sledgehammer ten you just drop
like one at a time and I'm bringing invisibility potions to I have my coins
all right D loot get your goblin on are we all gonna do loop out the loop goblin
oh yeah okay so let me go to the tailor and just get some extra bitch just be
naked who cares oh yeah that's wrong boy oh that's on they might not see the it
yeah and we have to be very much like oh our treasures no one will get our
treasure treasure I'm actually not I'm gonna bring my precious any weapon so I
don't go threatening I can't even take these pants off I'm gonna buy potions
though oh we're not even gonna be able to fight mobs somebody should bring a
sword oh I'm bringing I'm bringing my shit don't worry dude I'm bringing my
crossbow all right you're in you want to protect us yeah I got you guys I'll
bring an axe just so I can break doors okay it's gonna be to be okay all right
let's get it okay let's go all right so we're just avoiding mobs avoid mobs it
but slowly is anybody think they can get our treasure I wonder no one will get
our treasure yeah we do have to try to actually survive to find just do the do
the riddle that you a League of Legends character just run there was some
adventurers somewhere in this vicinity let me get what I have we have too many
these questions three let's the other side okay I can't protect all oh my god
this is so many just no we're just W King we're just running okay watch out for
traps I'm jumping I'm jumping if you can answer that riddles now oh any
adventurers around if only there was somebody that could potentially to
probably gonna die we're just looking for main rooms looking for adventurers
anywhere all right did I hear the birds fighting someone oh no no you're on
your own yeah that's all this has been looted
no way
the riddles
even know we have any gold to do two or three people died during that that
wasn't just us killed two people without fighting oh I guess you get ten coins
oh shit I have I have no money anymore no I have like two hundred they didn't
even have Voipon probably I don't think that boy buddy there and I really tried
to give those guys some riddles oh yeah there were a dozen opportunities for
riddles and they just did not they were not yeah you don't even fight back
please no please stop hurting me you're stabbing me I'm bleeding no but what
about my riddles just give just give the guy one riddle please make his life
I'm gonna sell some stuff just so I have individual coins hold on yeah I'm gonna
yeah I'm gonna I'm gonna can you split up your my silver I like I can I is there
were to split stacks or no I don't know if you can take them out of the bags
unfortunately oh man riddles I was just throwing coins out too they just didn't
we weren't paying attention hey they just wanted to murder you I got some good
coins oh yeah I'll click and drag does it have to turn on Voip wait what's the
key for Voip be you hold be be the funniest part about that seriously will
is while you I died pretty early while you were running in circles they were
being killed by minions yeah they were what was happening was so abnormal that
I don't know we may have actually that was not that was not a bad trade all
right my inventory is just laden with coins I'll throw my other stuff out all
right let's go again I'm just putting silver coins in my
inventory oh one by one silver silver sometimes it can be better than gold oh
I didn't bring any money hold on in the lobby we just have to scream about you
know come find us if you want a quest I'm just saying they get the riddle
wrong they're probably gonna murder us that's when we get punchy exactly I feel
they're gonna get really mad when they don't get the riddle right all right I
am ready in one second okay Jack hook up some good riddles for us I got some
already this you guys are gonna be a nightmare to loot that's true you have
to take every individual come find us adventurers if you want to play a little
game coin it will be had oh I doubt anybody they're definitely too stupid I
think we got him does my boy work I don't think I heard you it's weird yeah
you have to activate like twice I was only just finds our three dead I wonder
if they went to our bodies and realized like they just wanted to ask us we made
somebody very rich all right drop all your stuff thing you got to be naked
yep okay remember break doors and keep running and I'll fear so that we can
just keep moving
keep moving you will be rewarded for a riddle and one answer to my river and no
one is smart enough to be able to answer your riddle the trap room it'll be this
little me that who's afraid afraid of that big bad bad oh this is the worst
room oh fuck but people spawn here usually okay I see smoke clouds we're
gonna go up this side and go around would anyone like to answer that
devilish riddles I see like a funny foot I have a little for you
you can answer it this way this way don't attack attack we have riddles you
don't care what to tell her it goes can you good luck eluding me good luck
please what has to be broken before you can use that stitch you know what you
know the smart thing to do here is we ran I'm gonna go follow him this it's
just free money kind of mean you have an arrow in your head will we've broken the
door I am friendly we have riddles we have riddles you answer them with
words you killed this guy there's 50 people running behind him he is so
screwed oh god I can't get through this I'll come back well we made a few people
really rich if they come across our bodies there's still one riddler oh I
have a red door for you you have murdered my other two riddlers but you
would not murder me this is the problem until you don't swing at me are you in
a VR headset like come on like you can't hear he's playing VR games I won't dodge
these arrows and tell you a riddle did anybody okay I want to cycle through I
want someone to find our bodies why don't they don't they don't want to
I want to see what they do when they find will if they find your body with like
fucking up to grand in it or whatever it is oh my god it's a funny no one cares
that's so funny I just nobody has VoIP on or what's going on I thought maybe I
don't know I feel like that guy's gonna die to like the 20 mobs we outrode just
to tell him a riddle hey well they they missed out on hundreds and hundreds of
gold all right are we done or we want to riddle once more I have no more items
to riddle I have money I have money how do I we gotta try to get at least one
like one group that actually has to like yeah answer the riddle surely surely
really all right oh that's so funny though I would bring ten more coins all
right I'm gonna I'm gonna go back to the lobby I have I'll bring extra gold for
okay cool yeah even if you bring like a few stacks and I'll just split it up all
you need is ten coins I even tried to get him to talk it's so funny just how
much this game is so hard think about how difficult it is to actually play
this game and if you just had had played along and answered a riddle you would
have made like 500 fucking gold yeah instead they murdered I bring in two
stacks of gold for you ready up they use someone will answer our riddles I can
feel it I can feel it it'll have one is someone is gonna appreciate our brand of
humor looking for someone to answer riddles oh enough time we are the
Riddler's Guild to be fair you were dragging a horde of mobs behind you but
we also had a horde of riddles these mobs did not want to answer our riddles
all right here's the 20 gold oh my god it's under the helmet fuck okay all
right naked naked is the night you know I'm gonna I'm gonna hold on to this
she oh no I can't oh yeah let's go I'm just holding the shield I'm gonna carry
a torch oh I think I see someone for you a riddle there are monsters if you can
help us we were our monsters now we have riddles if you can kill them we are the
Riddler's Guild we are Huey Huey and Louie we're not in no relation to those
ducks we are Huey Louie and Louie yes that is your first riddle that's your
first riddle excellent question a question for a coin baby perhaps a coin
well answered you have a coin a coin for you look at the crowd adventurers we
have many wells nothing but money for you
this sir is furious as our riddles he's making it I have a riddle I if you take
things away from me I grow larger I am darkness if you find me make sure you
don't fall in whatever this is my favorite riddle this is one of our
favorite riddles surely you can get this I stop for no one no only I grow only
larger I'm never ending yes where are you about to answer our riddle yes here's
honestly could barely hear the riddles oh you eat the riddle yeah we repeat the
riddle I don't remember it you got it wrong that's wrong I have another riddle
though what is your security number that's that's I think that's identity
this coins on the ground adventure for free I don't understand what is so fun
what is always in front of you but you can't be seen we need some fucking
riddles we don't have any riddles in front of you but can't be seen yes I
remember this one no the future I have a real good I am flat but we will give
you more chances I am flat and will only show you yourself I am you I am flat
fuck I'm a very good at this what am I I am you I am flat and I am sparkly what
am I yes and I only show you your true self what am I yes there's more
ventures hey we have riddles we have riddles hey would you guys like to answer some riddles no we have riddles fuck you fuck all of you
we have riddles we have riddles please riddle squad who come please no violence the riddles oh you bastard Dewey you killed Dewey why are you doing this
will your huey please please please please I have a riddle oh my god no one wants to answer our riddles he threw a malt off and got probably a thousand damage on all of us I'm
coming back to give you a riddle it's so funny we don't we want to tell riddles
but like I don't really know very I don't really know any riddles do you know any
riddles that poor party of clerics got destroyed even if you never pick it up
or touch it you don't answer with your weapons you answer with words no I have
god damn it your mirror riddle was so bad no I'm trying to think what the fuck to
even say when you tell me repeat your riddle I don't even remember what you
know he said I didn't hear I am you I have a lot I am shiny I'm sparkly okay I
don't know yeah going in his god yeah we went in his riddlers and we didn't have
any riddles planned I had I had a couple we're just three people on drugs that we
didn't even have anything planned my riddles turned into me trying to do
identity you're like what is your social security number what are those funny
digits on the back of your card looking for a load oh my god all right I think
I'm gonna call it there yeah I'm gonna get some sleep we riddled I think we
riddle our butts off as a team of three men trying to murder us they murdered
all those clerics we just confused it everybody they were trying to figure out
what we were doing is almost like we were speaking a different language they
were like what's happening what happened here I think everybody's been so
traumatized by the yeah oh man that's what I think we kind of got the murdered
it'd be fair they were slaughtered it was watered they were thinking about our
riddles and they were slaughtered all right well I think the the playtest
will be like another few days so maybe I'm gonna try another riddle yeah no
that was awesome it was fun thanks thanks for um hitting me up
it was really that was so much fun thanks for playing with us yeah good
games good games you guys are you gonna keep streaming yeah are you gonna keep
playing no I'm gonna send my audience your way but hey let's double it up
we'll double it up oh double it up double it up that's all have a wonderful
night guys thank you good night everybody that's a will neff by the way
and Nessa whoa we're gonna we're gonna raid call me nest yep all right nice
night all right good night y'all have a good weekend I meet you bye bye yeah
take her that was very fun my my face hurts from the whole evening uh what are
the riddles I think we were just confusing everybody yeah follow up
will neff obviously you're gonna I'm gonna dump you all on on nest right now
will is a will is awesome super funny super cool if you don't follow will neff
what are you doing so let's uh say our goodbye the next time you see me will be
Sunday stir and I are gonna do some more Elden ring randomizer and a bunch of
other mods I don't even know what they are we're gonna figure that out probably
tomorrow that was awesome thanks for hanging out I know they've been pretty
late but I really like the late night streams the stream on Sunday is not
going to be at 6 p.m. stir does not do that schedule so it'll be pulled back at
least probably two or three hours so I think he wants to start a little later
than normal so just keep an eye on the suss I'll figure it out tomorrow maybe
four or five maybe I don't think it's gonna be sick there'll be probably an
hour or two and let's queue up a raid or necessary is it twitch TV slash just
Nessua awesome all right thank you so much everybody get some sleep it's been
a lot of fun I've been having a ton of fun lately on stream we keep going go say
hello go give your best be nice and I'll see you guys on Sunday they carry
selves those are all that you know what that's why I want to really play with a
bunch of people because a game like this you just jump in and people are just so
fun like poke and italics poke was fucking awesome
talics obviously good to see him again criken oh sorry sure obviously will as
well it's just a lot of fun I'm having a blast hopefully it translates to stream
but all good people alright everybody take care of yourselves see you later
have a great night have a good rest of the well you belong the weekend's
probably starting for some of you where it's finishing on Sunday so see you
Sunday good night goodbye take care see you soon have a great one call your
mother