Now, thanks to Myth for setting that up. Go follow Myth on YouTube. He's a really good dude.
That was a lot of fun. I wish I played a little better, but I was okay. Whatever.
You got popular on FPS games. That's, guys, go back and watch my scout tutorial where I explain
what A and D does. You understand? That's what I mean when I'm saying there was boogers coming
out of my nose. Like, okay, so A and D is a stray, right? That's, we're talking, it was a different
world 10 years ago. Okay. More? How do I spell this? Should I make my title Morty? Mortuary Morty?
I think I wanted that. I think I wanted that. I think it has to be that, right? Yeah. I don't
care. Yeah. It's going to be like, Morty. Mortuary. What do you think? Is that bad? Should I change it?
Dude, this is so bright in my fucking face. It's way too bright. Lights off too? Lights off? Well,
this looks like shit. Why does it look so bad? Why do I look like I'm on a VHS tape? Does this
game suck? There we go. That's better. No, it's not. Is that better? That's good, right? Is that like
that? A little bit worse? I think that's fine. That's fine. All right. Mortuary Assistant. I know,
like, I hate Rick and Morty, but don't leave because you don't like the joke. Leave because
that was terrible at Call of Duty and you were, like, expecting something else. All right. Let's
go. Season six is coming soon. Why is this on my other monitor over here? Why is this over here?
This monitor. How do I change that? I don't want it on this monitor. I want it over here.
How do I do that? Hey, what the fuck? Win, shift, and arrow. Win, shift, and arrow. I didn't do
anything. I took it off full screen. There we go. All right. Can you see it? There we go. All right.
How does it look for settings? Is this fine? VSync 120. Let's go. This is probably fine.
Tutorial tips. Yeah. Ultra HD. High quality. I'll turn it up a little. Hopefully this is not,
like, a lot of screamers or something. All right. Okay. Move. Okay. Let's go. New shift.
Invert Y. It fixes a bug. Subtitles on. All right. Let's fucking go. New shift.
What happened to the POG content? I want to see Call of Duty. You missed it.
I'm so glad. Thank you. I'll never understand why you chose such a macabre field. There's nothing
disturbing about it. It's just that... I thought that was real actors.
They actually have everyone they need, but my old teacher, Mr. Delver, transferred me to his office
to finalize my internship there. Oh, well, that's good. I remember you mentioning him.
Where's he located? Are you moving away from me? No. It feels like an AI-generated scene.
He's actually located around here. Like, oh, in Blender. This is what's going to happen.
I don't like that. Grandma. Even I've heard things about that place.
Just be worried about you. Don't make up stories. Death is a scary thing to a lot of people,
and we try to explain things we don't understand, and we want comfort when we lose someone we love.
I mean, no one's embalming any ghost bodies or whatever. It's fine. Right, right. I'm sorry.
Bring!
Shit, that title is so bad. People are going to hate me. I'm actually regretting that title.
If I want that, just take it, please. It should be yours anyway. Thanks. All right.
Enough spooky stuff. I'm so proud of you. When is all this happening? When do you start?
I've actually been there for a few weeks now. My review is tomorrow.
What is happening? All right. Okay. I was like, what's going on? First day. Riverfield Mortuary.
This is loud. All right. Here we go. I feel like I'm playing Call of Duty again. Hold on.
That did not work. I guess it's just the way it is. That's different now. That's better. Better
getting better. Halfway. Halfway. Halfway. All right. There we go. Okay. So what do we do?
We can't break the vase. Okay. Rebecca, one last thing I forgot to give to you. Please grab a
pencil from my desk and sign it. Thanks. From Zoe. Good luck. Use to sign the paperwork on the
door. Access Quick Inventory and choose the item you wish to use. Most but not all places where
the I okay. That's the right mouse button. I can't use that here. Signed. All right.
Great. Perfect timing. I just finished with Mr. Dalton here. You're just sitting here? Please wheel
him back to cold storage and bring us Mrs. Page. Moving the deceased. Use the gurney by standing
behind it and pressing the gurney interact key and walk backwards with the gurney down the hall.
All right. Oh, where was there? Bring a body in or out of cold storage. Open the bay with the
body's name. Pull out the rack and then move the cart over to it. Okay. Oswald Dalton. Oh. Oh,
shit. Okay. Jesus. Okay. Get in there. Wait, is he just floating? How do I push him in? What happened?
Oh, shit. No, get over here. Come back. Come back. How do I? What do I do? How do I push him in?
What's what's going on? I don't understand what's going on here. He's he's he's literally stuck.
What? Okay. Pull this out. Then you put him in. He goes up. And then we put we put we what do we do?
I push him from here, right? Use the gurney. Get it out of the way and push him in. Dude, I tried.
That's literally what I tried doing before and it didn't work. He was frozen. Okay. I was clicking
and dragging. I swear to God. I was trying to find a sprint. Okay. All right. I'm just finishing
up something here. So why don't you grab the clipboard and start recording identifying marks.
I'll get out of your way when you're done and let you hop in here. Clipboard used for forms
and keeping track of mortuary tasks. All right. Okay. Record any distinguishing marks. Enter
markings into computer. Inspecting a body. Hover the cursor over unique markings such as moles,
scratches, bruises and interact with them to record them. Okay. All right. What do we got?
Got a ball here. All right. There's a mole. Wait. There's another one here.
Okay. Back up. Got a bruise. That's it. What about the head? These old windows never stay latched.
Nothing on the head. Wait. Keep going all the way. Bruise. Bruise. Great. Bruising. Climb on in
here and put everything into the record system. Don't forget to take the printout to the front
desk so Zo can add it to the packet for the family. After that, we'll get started. Okay.
Click the record system icon to open the program. What was that? I didn't say anything. You all
right? Yeah. I'm fine. Sorry. Okay. That was what a weirdo. All right. Click the record system icon
to open the program. Match the sections on your clipboard to the corresponding sections on the
computer. Once all findings have been entered into the system, click submit. Print out involving
records and file the records in whatever. All right. So he's going to match the system. Let's go.
Name. I don't... What's the name? Dorothy Page. Age. 87. Head. There was a...
On the right leg, there was a contusion. On the left leg, there was a rash. There was a contusion
on the left arm. There was a contusion on the right arm. On the right shoulder, there was a mole
and that and that's it. Submit it. Okay. Where'd it go? Why were there clues over here?
Where did it print out from? I need to get it from the printer. Where's the printer?
Oh. All right. So I got to file up front so they are available if requested. All right. So we
got to file this. Okay. Time to embalm. All right. I've set everything out so you can just go ahead
and get started. I'll be monitoring. Everything's on your list there if you need it. Pizza's burning.
There's no pizza in the oven. Okay. I'm ready to... So where do we do that? I'm missing something.
Setting the face. Oh. What? Oh. Moisturizing wipe. Injector. I can't hold anything else.
Okay. I can only carry two large items at a time. Okay. So I need to use the injector, right?
I'm missing something. So I have in my... I don't need these... I don't need a moisturizing wipe.
Use for injecting cavity fluid directly into organs. Artery forceps. Scalpel. Just take
everything. Setting needles. Eye caps. IV reservoir bag. I can't hold anything else.
Okay. So I got to get this started, right? Oh. All right. Wire Josh up with needle
injector and settings needles. Am I doing this right? Holy shit. What did I just do?
Oh. Wait. Do I double click it? There we go. Insert eye caps. Are they in? All right.
Okay. Mix embalming fluid. Gatorade, menthol, humectant, and formaldehyde.
Okay. Where is that? Okay. Cavity fluid. Mix embalming fluid and pump. Is it already in there?
No. Okay. Here it is. Okay. Take it. I can't hold anything else.
Really? How do I... How do I... How do I put this wipe down? How do I drop shit?
I can't hold anything else. Really? Get it back.
Sometimes we get chemicals that haven't been stored properly and it can make them pop like that.
Backpack. Just keep doing your thing. I'll get it.
I can't hold anything else. That was not normal.
I can't hold anything else. That sounded fucked up.
All right. We'll put this shit in first. Okay. Hire the audio guy. I am. I genuinely am.
I am genuinely hiring an audio magician to give me... I don't care how much it costs.
It's not the noise gate. If I turn the noise gate off and scream, it'll still happen. It's
this microphone. Okay. I tested it with the noise gate off. I tested with no settings on it all.
Just the mic plugged right into the computer. All right. So now I have to... How do I plug it in?
Make an incision in the cartoided artery and jugular vein. Okay.
Okay. So some items need to be used. What do I need to do with this?
Did I try to put the clipboard in her neck? I'm missing something.
Use forceps to clamp tubing to both veins. I need tubing. Where do I get the tubing?
Where are the forceps? Do I have the forceps? No. Where are the... Are the forceps already in there?
Where's the tube? The window? Window. Stop pretending. I don't... On the window sill.
Oh, this is a bag. This is like a... Okay. This is like a baggie.
I thought it was going to be like a big like snaked up thing. All right. Okay.
Now engage pump and let the body drain. So subway for lunch. Turn it off.
Wait, I didn't know I had to turn it off. I didn't know I had to turn it off. Please help.
Okay. Turn off pump. Remove tubes and close the incision.
Fill an empty reservoir bag with cavity fluid. Okay. Then... Then insert the trocar into the
cavity. Insert the trocar until it stops to begin the flow of embalming fluid.
Once that cavity is full, hold the trocar back and rotate it. Then reinsert whatever.
Oh! I don't want anyone to do this to me. I don't want anyone to do this to me.
Shoot me out of a cannon. Just... Okay. Put me in a cannon and during... I have like a big celebration
where everybody's here. Like I've got family and friends. Load me into a gonzo cannon from the
Muppets and just have it be like tie a bunch of fireworks to me and just shoot me in the space
and everyone just cheer. I don't... I don't want anyone to do this to me. No. High enough where
it's not going to be a problem. I'm talking about like... And I'm like in the stratosphere
and they just get to watch like this big and have it... I don't know. Have like a cool
display. Into orbit. No, not into orbit. Shoot me out of a fucking cannon. Don't do this to me.
Mix cleaners in bathroom closet to create tank cleaner. Okay. Cleaner base. Uh, more...
I can't hold anything else. I can't hold anything else. Is that it? Tank cleaner. What do I do?
Mix cleaners in bathroom closet to create tank cleaner. Then pour into the embalming pump.
I need an embalming pump. Where do I get that? You did it. How do I... That's not it. You just
used it. Turn it on. How do I turn it on? Drop the thing. You got the tank. Oh, okay. All right. I see
what you mean. And then what am I doing? And then pour into the embalming pump. Okay. Apply
moisturizer. Does it get more red? Okay. Moisturizer. Apply moisturizer. Okay. Yeah.
Wipe the face. Tell you what. Why don't you go ahead and head out? I'll take over from here.
Are you sure? I just got here. Don't worry. You're doing great. I'll get the last of your paperwork
sorted today and call you in for your first shift. All right. I'm ready. See you later.
That wasn't moisturizer. That was acid. It was just really weird. So some stuff fell over.
That's not a big deal. No, I know. It wasn't even my fault, but he sent me home right after that.
I'm just really worried. He was supposed to finalize my stuff today. And he said he would,
right? TV goes on top of that, right? You don't. That's where it places the TV. That's a good thing.
Yeah. It just didn't feel like he meant it. Like he just said it to get me out of the building.
Wait a sec. I have another call. Hello? Hey, Rebecca. It's Raymond. Oh, hi, Mr. Delver. Look,
if I did anything wrong today, just- No, no. What's this guy's problem? Yeah. Are you sure?
I mean, of course. Yeah. I don't want people sucking juices out of my body.
I'm on my way right now. I hope you feel better. Bye. Holy shit. That was him. He signed me on.
He needs me to come in tonight. Thanks. I have to go like right now. I'll talk to you later.
All right. Let's go. First day. First day of work. Okay. The sensitivity got worse.
You see that? That's scary. That's some scary shit. Why did it change that on me? And why is
there a microwave here? Why is there a microwave on the ground? This is an insane place for this.
Okay, let's go. Wolfios? Keys. All right. Temporary items do not take up space in your inventory.
All right. Morty. Morty. We're going to play more than one song, Morty. No, we're going to play more
than one song. That's not how it works, Morty. All right. Let's go. Holy fuck. Minus two. Yeah.
Look at the title. And everybody's talking shit about Rick and Morty. Like, you laugh at that
show. I know you do. You sit there with the iPad sitting on your chest, and they get into some
crazy hijinks, and you kind of go, all right. Okay. And then you slam the iPad shut because
you hear somebody come into the room. You don't want anyone to think you're watching it for some
reason. Who cares? What happened? I stubbed my toe. I'm telling you. I'm armed. Don't come in. I'm
armed. Mr. Delver. I need help. Someone's outside the mortuary. What? This is very sudden. But
listen to me. You have to start right away. He's on the phone. It's him. Sorry. He's going like that.
Oh, earbuds. This isn't funny. Stop. You need to take this seriously.
This is insane. I'll just leave. I'll just fucking leave. You can't leave, Rebecca. I can't allow
that for you or for others. It's far too dangerous. What am I supposed to do then?
Most bodies I work with at night are fine. So we stay. What happened to my chat? I can't read the
chat. The embalm. File the paperwork. Stay. I left some things for you on the desk. I'll call again
when you get to the embalm. All right. This is where I'm going to go like this. No, wait. This is insane.
Oh, that's supposed to be him. I was going to just go like this, like jump at him. This is so stupid.
It's just some hazing for the new girl or something. Just turn that back. Turn that back on.
What are you doing? And do your job. Oh, what the fuck? You're right. The ghost is here. You're
right. You should definitely come in here. It's fucked up in here, man. And then when it comes in,
club them with the fucking bowling pin. All right, let's go. Key, key, save recorder. Okay. How do I
get? That's not it. Quitting tomorrow. I'm going to break through the windows. I'm sorry, but this
entire thing is extremely unprofessional. If this is how you treat new hires, I don't think I can
work for you. Don't trust the phones. Anything can be manipulated. Burn the correct body.
What? In this cabinet? This is insane. Just be a professional one. Grab a body and get started.
This is the part where I take the tennis ball and I just don't know what to do.
So I sit over there in the corner and I go like, can't go, can't go. Fucking demons. Can't go.
Somewhere. I just sit there for like 10 minutes. He could have just stayed on the phone.
Oh, shit. That was important.
The further you are from possession, the more time you have. The closer you are,
the more the demon will find the demon's name. All right, find the demon's name.
Allowing you information to guess its name and the body. It's about the only way.
Fucking Eric. It's Eric. Don't think of just scribble.
Notice anything strange? It's starting to go past the pencil in the desk.
Checking from time to time can give an idea. It's Eric.
Just burn them all. Yeah, what's stopping me from just burning all of them and being like, hey,
I just burned them all. I got the demon. Wait, should I not be doing this? Just burn them all.
No, no, you're supposed to listen to all the tapes. No, you know, you're not doing it right.
Hey, Mr. Dover.
He's like, you didn't play my game. What the fuck? Is it over? That was it. Do I have a save?
Oh, God damn it. All right. All right. Don't just be an idiot. Keys. Let's go. All right. Let's go.
I'm not messing around right now. Doesn't he call? I thought he doesn't. He calls. Doesn't he call?
What's the code? This one's got like Cheeto dust on it. It's this one.
Okay. Okay. Where did he say that was? I forgot immediately. Instantly. I forgot what he said.
My ID is. Where is it? He said my ID is the drawer or something.
Think about just script. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, get away from me.
If you notice anything strange, it's starting to take hold. Okay. What are you? There's a notepad
and a pencil on desk. Checking from time to time. Okay. Embalm each body with a special
regent from the cabinet. Use the leading strips from the cabinet to attempt to reveal demonic
sigils. Okay. So we got to get a body out. Okay. All right. So we got to get a body
and we just have to do the process of embalming. All right. It's not. Oh, it's a different name.
Robert Hood. Nothing. Cordell Armstrong. Dorothy Vaughn. Okay. Dorothy Vaughn. Come on out.
Yeah. It's random. All right. Okay. Just leave. I'm not gonna just leave. All right. Here we go.
We need to do. All right. You've got something going on. Do I need to do this?
Head bruise. A couple of head bruises. All right. What about the arm? Yep. All right. Nothing here.
Anything here? Nope. Somebody just tapped on the window. What? Is that it? I think that's it.
That's it, right? Okay. Name. Age 22. Contusion in the head. Right shoulder. There's a problem.
Rash on the arm. And that's it. Submit it. Let's go. Okay. Give me the cabinet. What the fuck is this?
What is this?
Location. You will need to uncover these sigils to use them.
Hold a letting strip up while wandering the mortuary. If it begins to smolder and burn,
you're close. When the paper will bust. It's here. It's right in front of me.
What? This thing's fucking burning. Ow. Where is it? Are you out here? Use the night shift database
to decide what reagent. Am I getting close? I don't wait. I don't get it.
This is. Ow. What? I don't understand. What? How would it just happen? This person's a demon.
Sigil revealed. Where? Look for the mark now. Mark of Satan. Where's the mark? No, no, no, no, no,
no. Turn the lights off. I don't see anything on the furniture in the room on the furniture
on the wall. Can it just be anywhere? Like that? It was just like, oh,
right here, right? It burnt up like right here. It can be, it can be anywhere.
It's near, it has to be near where it burned, right? It blew up right here.
Stop. Where is it? Look on the wall. Dude, I'm looking at the wall. I'm looking at the wall right
now. Sink. Please stop pretending. I have no idea what this wants me to do. I lifted up the thing.
It burnt. It exploded right here. And I'm so. Oh my fucking God. I thought this was a clock.
OK, so that's that's the sigil. So OK, now I have that. So let's go over here.
So what is now? What? What mark is that? This one here?
It's like, yeah, it's like the L. OK, so I have to get I got to get four of these.
Load it, hurry. OK, in invidious emulation, desolation.
OK, so we've got Baraketh. Who else has an L? T-Shack. I need I need more.
Let's go. Let's go light some more papers. All right.
All right. Let's light a paper and let's go find a something.
Let's go. I need more progress first. All right. Let's start.
All right. So I need to. All right. Enter markings into computer.
Didn't I already do that? Yeah, this is already submitted. I got I got to file it.
It's time to involve.
Why are you saying that that like it was a superpower you were activating?
Like that was weird. Time to embalm missing something.
All right. I need to do the. Where is all this shit?
OK, wire, needle injector and setting needles.
I don't know where all this stuff even is. Needle injector.
Are the lights off in here? No. All right. Where the needles?
It's not a tutorial anymore. Moisturizers here, right?
These needles. What the fuck is this? Oh, the glass cabinet. OK.
Needle injector. All right. Setting needles. Let's do it.
OK. Well, I got to be honest. What is the point of doing this?
What's the point of doing this? Why? Why? What's it for?
Why? Why do that? Why? Why are the person's jaw shut?
It keeps the mouth closed so they don't have their mouths open.
All right. I need eye caps. Why did you let me die?
What the fuck is this? This is all your fault.
At every second with you, time is running out, Rebecca.
OK. Insert eye caps. Where are the eye caps?
I don't really know. Eye caps. They weren't in here.
Scalpel. I'm going to pick it up just to have it. Little scissors.
Eye caps. Yeah. All right. Let's go. Put them on.
I can't use that here. Put them on.
You have to click the eyes. Oh, OK.
All right. Now we do the embalming fluid, which is all the chemicals.
This is humectant, hydrogen, whatever. No, no, no.
They don't put that in. I can't hold anything else.
God, why? OK. Formaldehyde.
The other stuff over here. One of those.
What? And then what's the last one?
Glutaraldehyde. OK. Where's the Glutaraldehyde?
Mix it up. Oh, wait. I need a reagent in the old cabinet.
OK. And now we're going to connect. Yep.
I'm missing something. I need the tube.
All right. Let's go. Turn it on.
Oh, hey, Satan. Where is it? Oh, Satan.
OK. That's like a big three right here. All right.
So we've got three L. What's three L?
L. Looking for L3. L3. L3. No.
L3. No. It's going to be emulation.
L3. L. Ah, it's. I know. I know their name.
I know your name. I know. I know. It's Anek.
It's Anek. Look right there. Anek.
All right. So what do I do? How do I say their name?
So now I know it's Anek. Oh, I have to put it in the thing.
OK. L3. T9. L3. T9.
Wait, it's going to be the right order.
It's L3. T9. L3. T9.
L3. T9. Like that, right?
L3. T9. Take it. Now what do I do with this?
Wait, attach it to body somehow, then burn it after?
You have to put it on the correct body, though.
Oh, OK. Why is this body possessed?
You're right. OK, I don't know, but I know it's that one.
All right. So now this is embalmed.
Fill an empty reservoir bag with cavity fluid. OK.
Hold anything else? Yes, you can.
Oh, my God, by this way. Put it back.
OK, then this goes in here. Start scribbling.
Where? Where do I write this down?
Where? Where? Where? Where? Write anything.
How do I write something down? On a desk?
That's nothing. I left a coffee mug on a piece of wood.
But that doesn't do anything. C. OK, keep this up.
There we go. OK, now mix cleaner in the bathroom.
I'm scared. Where's the bathroom? Right here, right?
Where's the bathroom? This is not the bathroom.
Where's the bathroom? Oh, it's right here.
OK, I got it. Any weird shit? Just a double check, right?
What was that? OK, apply moisturizer.
Right. Return body to cold storage.
OK, there's only two more bodies. What's that?
That's just a square. OK, let's go.
All right, who's next? All right, Cordell Armstrong.
Come on out. Let's go.
It starts with a C. It does start with a C, you're right.
That's true. OK, it's definitely this guy.
Without a doubt. It's 100% this guy.
This guy's smiling. Yeah, it's definitely this guy.
That hit? The head. OK, got it all.
All right, put it in the computer. Entry two.
This is Cordell Armstrong, age 53, head.
Got that thing on it. Right shoulder.
We've got these left arm, lemmishes, right arm, curatolas, right leg.
Got a mole. Submit. Hey, let's go.
OK, let's do it again. Oh, it's this guy.
It's this fucking guy. Look at this.
I'm going to put the thing in his mouth and he's.
There we go. OK, then it's eye caps.
Does it down here? What's after eye caps?
Embalming fluid. Let's just get this done now.
All right. OK, embalming fluid.
It's this shit, this shit.
And then it's this shit. And then it's this shit.
Where is it? That's turning into something else now.
Menthol. Where's menthol? Where's that menthol?
Where's that menthol? No, where is it?
I forget where it is. Over here?
Yep. OK, it's on the shelf. I remember that.
And the other chemical right here.
OK, now we're going to attach the tubing, which is here.
I need the stabbers, scalpel, or sips tubing.
That tube is over here. Isn't it?
Yeah. No, you're not.
You're fine. All right.
Turn it on. Quick scribble, scribble.
Input system error. Action acid cannot be found.
If you're experiencing this error for the first time,
locate a poisonous material, ingest and wait for heart rate to slow.
Your flesh is wasted. Give it to me.
Let me in. My glorious pleasures ache to flood your veins.
As you rot in torment for your sin, there is no hope, Rebecca.
You will see me, Rebecca.
It's a very odd Windows blue screen. OK.
Drink poison? Where's poison? I gotta drink it.
Where's poison? Drink poison quick.
Hey, what the fuck was that thing?
It's an Enderman. Where's poison?
What do I do? Wait, what's that?
Heroin kit. Wait, heroin? I'm going to do heroin?
Grab the keys. Nothing on this table is interactable.
No keys here. I just leave.
Oh, that's not good. Jesus.
Oh, yeah. Where are you?
Oh, yep. We got the right one.
Absolutely got the right one.
Yep. No way. It's not the right one.
It's anic. That's absolutely anic.
Yep. L3T9. We got it.
L3T9. That's it.
But is this the right person?
How can we tell if it's the right person, though?
If I put it on. Oh, what if I if I put it on?
Will it start to like burn? Wait, pump them.
You're right. OK. So what's that?
It's like a U. Is it a D or a G?
Shut up. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up.
OK. Turn. Remove the tubes.
Close the incision.
Now we need to do the reservoir bag with cavity fluid, which is over here.
Check the computer again. There we go.
OK. I'll check the computer.
OK. History. Identifying demonic tenacity.
Well, learning the name of the demonic entity is more about waiting.
Identifying which body is experiencing demonic tenacity
requires paying close attention.
While any of the bodies can be manipulated,
it is far easier for the entity to control its own vessel.
Sudden movements, large or small, can be a sign of tenacity.
If a body appears to be more active than others, a strange markings start to appear.
OK. The appearance of new markings on the body.
Sudden movements. Repeat movements.
Sudden movements.
This working? Yeah, this thing is huge.
I guess, um, this is David.
Raymond, this feels insane, but I think you were right.
This has happened a few times now, but let me see if I can get in here.
All right. Shut up. Shut up.
Whatever.
I'm going to burn this guy. I'm burning this guy.
Oh, my God. Oh, my God. Oh, my God.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. Circle. Circle.
You sure?
Well, this is dark in here. Right on.
All right. Clean the bathroom.
See? Oh, I mean, it's definitely see.
Oh, see, this is this guy named like corn something smiling.
It's definitely this guy missing something.
I'm putting this on his head. Is it not you?
When to be sure this is. Oh, yeah, absolutely.
Yeah, 100 percent. Let's go.
You're going in the fucking toilet and wherever you're going.
I'm missing something. OK, it's this guy for real.
Well, we're going to moisturize the face.
Because that's we have to finish that right.
I can't use that here. All right.
What if it's don't trust yourself?
OK. All right. Back into the freezer.
Of course, it's this guy. It's this.
Are you serious? It's this guy.
It's this guy. I got to burn him.
How do I burn him? What do I do?
Do I have any holy water?
I thought there's the eyes looking at me.
Those are red eyes. Get over here.
I get. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I got to put the thing on you.
I can't use that here.
Mark them. Mark them. Mark them quick.
How do I get them in here?
I can't move them. Why not?
Bye. See you later.
Annec. Your name is Annec.
Back to the shadow demon realm with you.
Your name is Annec. Your name is Annec.
What? Why is he still alive?
I got him. No, I got him.
It doesn't end here from now on.
There is always a chance this will happen again.
No matter where you are.
I don't want this. I just want to leave.
By the way. Yes, it is.
It is eight dollars an hour.
So what? You're waging some selfless holy war.
It's not a war. It's survival.
And I'd hardly call it selfless.
We're caught at the front line of something larger.
But I don't do this for some greater good.
We either face it or fall to it.
I wish I could claim to be someone better.
Suffering hell to save us all.
But I simply want to live another day just like everyone else.
So did I win?
When I first experienced this, I had to make a choice.
I could run and spend the rest of my days in fear.
Or I could learn to face it and keep some semblance of a normal life.
That was pretty cool.
It's not a life I would want for anyone.
But choosing between a life of fear or control.
You're the first person I've met to face this hell and survive.
So there are five endings.
Different kind of job.
Let's go work the night shift.
Learn what I know.
Give yourself a chance at a life beyond fear.
I don't know what you experienced, but I know it uses the worst parts of you against yourself.
The more things happen, the more you'll confront the darkest parts of your life.
But through it, you'll become unbreakable.
I'm offering the tools to take control.
The choice is yours.
Hope you come back.
This game's cool.
It was not really what I was expecting, but it was kind of what I was expecting.
Time's possessed.
Wait, so that was when I was in the apartment?
Oh, okay.
That's cool.
Should I do one more?
I'll do one more.
Now that I understand how the game works, I'll try to do one a little cleaner.
And then I'll take off after this.
I'll be live tomorrow.
Tomorrow we're going to play Two Point Campus.
All right, let's go.
So I get it now.
I know how it works.
What time tomorrow?
Um, I'll probably be starting.
I want to say maybe two or three, maybe.
I'll put the steps what I want.
Maybe two o'clock, three o'clock.
All right, let's make this quicker.
Let's get to it.
Who do we got?
We have Brandy Cooper, Nick Darlington, and Rufus Harrell.
Let's do Rufus first.
When is baseball?
Baseball is August 19th at 6 30 p.m.
Oh, no, sorry.
At 4 30 p.m.
Yeah, sorry.
I had it wrong.
I don't know why I said six.
It's 4 30 p.m.
Not 6 30, 4 30.
What am I stuck on?
Get out of the way.
Yeah, 4 30 p.m.
Pacific.
Why can't this not move?
I don't have my clipboard.
I have to go in backwards?
4 30 p.m.
Pacific.
All right, come on out.
Let's get lucky and have a B first try here.
All right, let's go.
What do you got?
I only need my clipboard.
At least I can keep track of things.
Am I laughing?
You heard it.
Somebody just came in.
Wait, this is scratch.
There we go.
All right.
This is Rufus 35.
Flemish's leg.
We got nothing.
Show right.
This right left shoulder.
Nothing left arm is a mole.
Right arm contusion.
Right leg abrasion.
Anything weird in here already?
All right, start it.
All right, we need the wiring.
I already forgot where all the tools are.
They're down here or something, right?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Is anybody eating to this stream?
I feel like it'd be hard.
There we go.
Eye caps.
I mean, actually, pizza would be pretty easy.
Yeah, I could do pizza.
You could eat pizza no matter what.
You can't get grossed out while you're eating pizza.
All right.
All right, we need all the embalming fluid now here.
You've used that one already.
That one sucks.
Start fires.
Start moving other shit besides knocking on the door.
What a shitty ghost.
What a terrible ghost.
Oh, I'm knocking on the door.
Yeah.
What amateur bullshit that is.
Start breaking glass and then we'll talk.
Oh, this one.
I need the notepad.
Notepad's in the other room.
It's him.
It's you.
I need my fucking notepad so I can write that shit down.
Where's the...
I always forget where this one is.
Over here.
Oh, shit.
Write something besides a scribble, dude.
You can't do anything else but that?
That was me in there.
That was fucked up.
All right.
All right, turn the machine on.
Oh, no.
I mean, I need the magical stuff.
Okay.
Put that away.
Let's go ahead and cut this.
I need the pipe.
I'm missing something.
Give me a note.
Something in here, right?
Come on.
Yeah.
Where you at?
Okay.
It's a Z.
We need another one.
We can't go off of that one.
All right.
Get the tubes out.
You got another thing for me already?
Actually, it's Zed.
That's fine.
Okay.
Now we need to do the reservoir bag.
Is it over here?
And then that goes into the...
Oh, yeah.
This thing was here.
You got something to say?
All right.
Where is it?
Z?
A bird?
It looks like a bird.
Let's take a look.
Oh, come on.
What's the password?
9187.
Okay.
It's...
What was it?
What were the two symbols?
Bird and...
Bird and Z.
All right.
It could be...
Baldmet.
Wait.
Is that the right one?
The wrong Z?
Could be...
Shadat?
That's the right one, right?
Bird and Z.
Okay.
Shadat?
I think it's that one.
Let's check the other ones.
Shadat?
Yep.
Shadat.
This one here.
NVIDIUS.
Shadat.
We just got to confirm that with a three
and another little symbol here.
So wait.
Let me get this right.
So there's bird, Z on the left.
Okay.
All right.
Something happened.
Something happened here.
What's left?
I have to...
Oh, yeah.
This thing.
I was doing this.
C.
There we go.
Okay.
Then mix the cleaners in the bathroom
and then do the face moisturizer.
Can we move?
I can't use that here.
Why not?
Hurry up.
All right.
Let's go.
I can't make it.
I can't.
I don't know.
It could be...
It could be.
He was looking at himself though.
His eyes just opened.
His eyes are just...
His eyes are opened.
Wait.
Did they?
His eyes opened.
This is Rufus.
It's...
Yeah.
It's definitely this guy.
Well, let's...
We'll confirm it.
He's got scratches, man.
It's definitely this guy.
I'm just gonna...
I think I'm just gonna go for it.
I'll try one more person.
But I really...
I actually think it really is him.
Is it you?
Brandy?
She's waiting and looking for movements.
Hey.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey.
Easy.
What's your problem?
Stop.
What's your...
There we go.
That's it, huh?
Okay.
Let's get it in the computer.
Brash on the head.
That's it.
All right.
How come your face is a different color than your body?
A combination of bad lighting,
a bunch of blood in my face,
and I don't know.
Weird lighting.
And the white balance is fucked up.
I'm playing a scary game.
What are you talking about?
It's intense.
My face is full of blood and fluids.
All right.
Let's start it.
There we go.
Eyecaps.
All right.
Now we do this stuff in the neck.
Okay.
And the last one is right here.
What the fuck was that?
I'm gonna be able to get out of here.
No, nothing.
Okay.
Keep going.
I really do think it's the first guy, though.
I need tubing.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my goodness.
Okay.
All right, all right, all right, all right, all right.
Stop, stop, stop.
That's different now.
That's a circle.
Oh, oh, oh.
Can't hold anything up.
Oh, please.
Take the tube.
Okay.
I can't make an incision.
I need this.
Oh, I need a scalpel.
Scalpel.
Let's go.
I can't use that here.
What's going on?
Did I not put this in?
I can't hold anything else.
I didn't put the menthol in?
God damn it.
Okay.
I'm missing something.
All right.
Let's go.
I can't use that here.
Begin.
That felt weird when I walked in the room.
Do you know what I mean?
Like something about I felt weird.
I felt off walking in here.
I don't know why I just did.
I told you.
What did I fucking told you?
Something was weird.
I told you so.
I got bad vibes when I opened the door.
I could feel it.
Jesus.
Okay.
Um, now we've got to do the wait.
Let me check this.
All right.
We got to, um, okay.
The abdominal cavity and clean the bathroom.
Write it down.
If you could.
Holy shit.
44.
Estimated 44.
If S 44, S 44, S 40, S 44.
I can't hold anything else.
I can't use that here.
Why not?
I can't hold anything else.
Oh, goodness.
Where is it?
Excuse me.
Where?
That's who it is.
All right.
I know it.
Let's get it on there.
Should that it's down and then bird Z down three.
Like that, right?
I can't hold anything else.
Okay.
I want to put it on you.
What do you do?
I'm going to drop this shit.
I'm missing something.
What are you talking about?
Give me the.
I already, I already have one of those.
What?
Oh my God.
Fuck that guy.
That was fucking horrible.
Holy shit.
Oh my God.
That was awful.
It was awful.
Write it down.
Jesus.
Okay.
I know who it is, but I don't think it's her.
I think it's the guy.
There we go.
Okay.
Cleaner from the bathroom.
I got to.
Are you serious?
Can I just pour it in?
Who cares?
It's it's should that it's should that.
Okay.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Okay.
All right.
Give me the thing.
If I put this on you, what do you do?
Are you sure this is the right?
Yep.
Oh, yes, I am.
I'm missing something.
I actually don't know.
Okay.
All right.
Moisture.
I've got places to be.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Moisturize.
All right.
Let's go.
I think it's the first guy.
You know what?
I'm going to take the third person out and put this on them.
Hey, it's you.
I think.
Get over here.
You know what?
Just stay right here for a second.
I can't use that here.
He's got scratches.
Move him.
There we go.
Stop.
I want to go back.
No.
Left leg.
Left arm.
That's it.
Where's my thing?
Where's my thing that I?
Okay.
It's on it right here.
Hurry, hurry, hurry.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
I can't hold any.
I can't hold anything else.
Stupid thing back then.
Everyone's saying, hey, calm down, calm down.
I mean, I don't have to go fast because I'm going to get possessed
and I'm losing my mind, right?
The fuck?
There we go.
Okay.
Eye caps.
All right.
Mix the fluid.
Don't.
I know there's something probably going to be in here in a second.
Come on.
You know, close this door.
Close the door.
I don't want anyone to see me in here.
Close this door.
Thank you.
All right.
Let's fill it up.
Okay.
Now it's the incision with scalpel forceps.
Joy.
And then I need the tube.
What is that?
Oh, shit.
It's going to.
Does that say going to say 44?
Say something.
I'm missing something.
Shit.
23.
Does he have new scratches?
Does he?
Where?
It's the first guy.
Yeah.
Fuck it.
I'm not spinning.
I'm not waiting.
It's the first guy.
Without a doubt.
Without a doubt in my mind.
I'm missing something.
It's the guy out here.
It's the first guy.
Get him off this thing.
I think I have to finish it.
Yeah, I do, don't I?
I can't.
I can't hold anything else.
Don't you love your grandma?
It's so cold out here.
Leave me the fuck alone.
Get the fuck out of here, you bitch.
Grandma.
My goodness.
Watch your language.
All right.
Finish it, please.
Before I get in.
Okay.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm missing something.
I got to finish this.
That's the first guy.
I'm missing something.
Give me the bag.
Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick.
Where is it?
Right here.
Let me in.
There we go.
All right.
You're done.
Clean the bathroom.
There's no more cleaner.
What do I do?
I dropped it somewhere.
Oh, fuck.
Come on.
Don't do this to me now.
Where is it?
Where did I drop it?
There are more than one shelf.
Why is it quiet?
What?
Hey.
I'm not.
I'm still kind of alive here.
All right.
What did I do?
It was heroin, right?
What the fuck do I do?
No, don't look at that.
Get tubing by.
I'm sorry, guys.
I just have so locked in.
All right.
Get tubing, needle, and lighter.
Tubing by the bed.
Tubing, needle, and lighter.
Tubing.
Where's the needle?
Needle, bathroom, spoon from the coffee table.
That's not it.
That's the spoon, right?
I don't get it.
Needle from the bathroom.
I can't see a needle.
Needle.
Where?
Find a lighter.
Find a full baggie.
Encounter.
Lighter.
Spoon from the coffee table.
Dude, the spoon is right there.
I can't click it.
That's the spoon right here.
In order?
Why does it be in order?
Find a lighter.
You see a lighter?
Lighter.
You looked in the same two spots.
I mean, look.
It's dark as shit in here.
I can't see anything.
What are you talking?
I can't see a goddamn thing.
It's right there.
It's dark.
What the fuck?
Close the door.
Sound like a laugh track?
No, it didn't, dude.
That does not sound like a laugh track.
All right.
I got to get this motherfucker out of here.
Moisturizer.
And then it's the first guy.
It's the first one.
Oh, goodness.
It's here.
Wait.
There are new scratches on this person.
Scratches, scratches, scratches.
Right there.
Were they there before?
I don't think they were.
All right.
Let's moisturize their face.
OK.
Which one of you idiots is it?
It's the first one.
Yeah, no doubt.
You know, you can just stay here.
I don't even care.
Wait, I need the gurney.
Are you sure this is the first one?
Shit, it was this guy.
I was like trying to clean up the place.
I was trying to clean it up.
How is this guy out?
This is weird.
It's this guy.
Look at how fucking weird that is.
Yes.
Gotcha.
Is it the same ending?
Same ending.
So how do I get it to be a different ending?
Come a long way.
It's nice not to be the...
No, this is different.
Mr. Dover?
Oh, no.
I think you can just call me Raymond at this point.
Do you always just pass out and wake up on the floor?
It takes a lot out of you.
I've never simply walked out of here after.
You get used to it.
I'll be sure to clean the floors better.
Raymond, will this ever end?
I honestly don't know.
I've been doing this a long time, Rebecca.
I've traveled all over, learning everything I can.
I've never found anything that could put a stop to it.
You've got to iron that shirt, bro.
So no, I don't think it does.
So we're just like this forever?
It was hard for me, too.
But this is the life we get.
We have to face our worst selves constantly.
Stand around until you die in the next one?
Let's try that.
We are.
Why don't you head home?
Get some rest.
Just die?
Who knows what's coming tonight?
Do another one and burn the first guy?
I already...
I did that already.
No, that's a different ending.
I burnt the...
Remember, I just picked somebody up and burnt them?
So how do I get...
You're just saying just don't do anything.
Just stand still.
Just let this sigil form and get possessed.
I'll do a possessed ending.
Death and decay.
Don't leave the apartment.
Embalm.
Look about the history of preservation.
Oh, shit.
It's grandma.
Nothing in there.
Nothing.
Check under the TV.
Under the TV?
Try to cook.
I don't have any...
Do I have any food?
Do heroin.
No.
Nothing in here.
Oh, no.
I just yawed.
Oh, what's this?
My dad's necklace.
Love you, dad.
My sobriety coin?
My dad's sobriety coin.
Okay.
So I have these items?
Should I go now?
Where are my keys?
All right.
It's getting kind of late.
What do you think?
One more...
Just try to lose.
Just get scared.
All right.
Let's just do everything wrong.
Get the body out but do the name wrong.
All right.
Timothy Sharp.
Just do everything wrong.
Okay.
Am I doing that or is he doing that?
Get the secret ending?
Do everything right with the coins
and get the secret ending.
Wait, this is my work badge.
Wait, what?
Oh, I'm like an actual employee now.
I don't need a password anymore.
Oh, no.
Why am I so tired?
Scare me.
Scream at me or something.
This dude thought he could handle
the McDonald's order.
That's it.
All right.
Left leg.
Yep.
Right shoulder.
Left shoulder.
Yep.
Left arm.
Right arm.
Nothing.
Right leg.
Yep.
Left leg.
Submit.
Oh, man.
That was bad.
I'm awake.
I woke up.
I'm good.
I'm awake.
Come on.
Where's the light?
All right.
We need this stuff.
Eye caps.
Everything I need right now.
Yeah.
Yep.
Okay.
Fluid time.
Fluid.
It's time to make some delicious fluid.
I'm missing something.
Yes, I am.
Tubes.
Clay tablet in the center is called a mark.
Placing the smaller pieces in the correct configuration
will spell the demon's name.
Second, the bottles on the top shelf are a special reagent
that will react to the mark.
Add a bottle to the embalming mixture during the process.
When the mark is placed on the correct body,
the reagent inside it will force the demon to become
bound to it.
Pay attention to signs that you have chosen
correct, obvious, or extremely subtle.
Once you are certain that the demon is bound to its vessel,
describe the sigils of its name in our world
to begin the evocation.
You will need to uncover these sigils to use them.
Hold a letting strip up while wandering the mortuary.
If it begins to smolder and burn, your clothes...
Who the fuck are you?
...when the paper combusts, the sigil
has been revealed somewhere in that area.
Can we turn off the Disney World line audio?
Stop!
And remember, the most important rule.
Have fun on Splash Mountain.
1970, the year of arrival of the House of Death.
What the heck?
Come on, where is it?
I don't need this job.
See you later.
All right, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go, let's go.
All right, that's about...
I'm going to call that a...
I don't know, a Hearthstone symbol.
Did you move?
Oh, we need the bathroom cleaner.
And then we got to, um, moisturize.
And then I don't know, I'm not getting anything from this guy.
I'm not getting anything from this guy.
I don't think it's him.
All right, we know it's this one, right?
Hearthstone symbol.
I'm missing something.
Don't do it right.
Put the wrong...
Oh, okay, right.
Wrong symbol.
No, get it right.
Don't get it right.
Do not get it right.
Secret ending.
Do it right.
Well, I mean, I don't...
It's not this guy.
So that's...
I know that pretty much for a fact.
It's not this guy.
Who's there?
Yeah, let's do a poll.
All right, run a poll.
Do you want me to get it right?
Or do you want me to get it wrong on purpose and get a different ending?
I need to get it twisted.
Okay.
Are you moving?
I'll get it.
Hello?
It's you.
Leave all the windows open?
No, the bugs will get in.
I don't want to do that.
Wait.
There we go.
Okay, those are some scrapes.
Those are scrapes.
Do it right.
Okay.
This scrapes all over.
Rebecca?
Oh, damn it.
Rebecca, come here.
Mom, you stupid bitch.
Hate me all you want.
He's dead because of you.
You should be the one here.
All right, leave.
Give it to me.
You bitch.
Let me in.
I love that voice.
Let me in your house.
Let me in.
I can't move.
Okay.
All right.
So, where were we?
Oh, right.
Did I not print it?
Wait.
No, I didn't.
Okay, I did.
Let me in your house.
All right, now we got to do this shit.
I already have one of those.
Okay, well, let's do it then.
There we go.
I'm missing something.
Okay.
All right.
Now, let's begin this.
We need the fluid.
I just made a warhead.
It was so sour.
Why the fuck did we fill this shit?
Why did we put this in people?
Who was the first person that was like,
oh, you know what?
I have an idea.
Let's pump this person full of formaldehyde.
Why would somebody?
What for what?
Who decided to do that?
Oh, shit.
Hold on.
Yeah, where is it?
Pi.
All right, we got Pi.
Okay, who could it be?
What's my code?
Do I have a code?
I don't have a code, do I?
I'm so confused, didn't I?
This was my ID in here before.
Two, four, six, three, three.
Okay, Pi and Hearthstone.
No.
Okay, it could be Telduck.
Telduck?
No, it's probably Telduck.
Telduck.
All right, what's Telduck?
Pi, Hearthstone, Bong, and J.
So we need to find...
So it's Bong and J.
So that's definitely it.
Bong is at the top, right?
Bong, Hearthstone, Pi, J.
Okay.
I can't hold anything else.
So that's done.
Right, incision.
Don't scare me, idiot.
I need a scalpel.
I already have one of those.
Oh, I forgot to put...
Okay.
I already have one of those.
What are you talking about?
Oh.
Tube.
Let's pump.
Where do I go from here?
Okay, turn it off.
Turn that off.
Close it up.
What's wrong?
Something does feel weird.
I feel like I've been permanently changed.
Okay, let's go back here.
Don't even do it.
Don't do it.
Okay, the AC just turned on
and I felt something touch my arm
and I almost puked.
There we go.
Okay, bathroom.
Oh.
No, close those.
I don't want this open.
Oh, my God.
That's a...
Has somebody shot me with a gun?
We're getting some really good tuber reactions.
Yeah, you really are today.
All right, I'm going to put this on...
Let's see what happens here.
I don't think it's her either.
Are you sure this is the right...
No, I don't think it's you either.
I can't hold anything else.
Is it really...
This is a huge tuber stream?
Yeah, it is.
Dude, why is Holly behind you with a mask on?
Fucking terrifying.
Okay.
I'm missing something.
Oh, right.
Oysterizer.
All right.
Hey, Josh.
What's that?
It's definitely you.
It's definitely this guy.
There's nothing weird happening with these ones.
Let's see if something weird happens with you.
Yeah.
I mean, come on.
Look at...
Do we even really need to do this
or should I just burn him?
It's definitely this guy.
We don't even...
I'm just going to burn him now.
Let's go, buddy.
How dare you smile?
No, no.
I want to take him out.
I can't.
Oh, I can't move him now?
Oh, fine.
There we go.
So you're saying I'm holding these coins and shit, right?
Five-year coin, ten-year coin, necklace.
You're saying that I can...
This is the secret end if I get this all.
If I do this.
You have to get it right, okay?
I have to use the items correctly.
There's going to be some stupid right here.
Missing something.
Look at...
He's like...
His smile's even bigger now.
It's definitely this guy.
There's no doubt.
There we go.
All right.
I can feel something coming.
I knew it.
I'm not even checking.
It's just...
You're going to...
You're slamming the thing.
Doesn't matter.
This wasn't here before.
Oh, my God.
Come here, bitch.
Oh, that's bad.
Wait, four.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Last lot, four.
First, one.
First lot, one.
Last lot, four.
Second, last lot, four.
One, something, something, something, four, four.
One, four, four.
Four, four.
One, and then something in four, four.
I can't see this one.
One, something, four, four, four.
One, something, seven, something, four, four.
One, seven, something, four, four.
One, something, seven, zero, four, four.
One, one, nine, seven, zero, four, four.
Got it.
One, nine, seven, zero, four, four.
What's the, I can, what's the, how do I,
what do I punch the code?
One, one, seven, one, nine, seven, zero, four.
How would I punch it in?
What do I punch the code in?
One, nine, seven, zero, four, four.
Give me the fuck out of here.
Whose mouth did I not open?
Give me that key.
Bye.
Here, come here.
I'm gonna go left.
I make my own way.
David Whitlow, December 8th, 1949.
Oh, somebody said Abraham Lincoln.
Um, what?
Jesus, what the hell was that?
How do I get in there?
All right, there was a keypad under a thing here, right?
I remember, where I was like, what is this for?
It's like down here, right?
Yep.
One, nine, seven, zero, four, four.
Key to the hatch.
Let's go.
Oh God.
Just coming to get a refill, man.
I'm missing something.
Shit, it's too much.
Give me a TLDR.
Somebody just give me a TL...
Just somebody read it for me.
Okay.
The raging is the blood of the possessed.
What the fuck?
Thanks for the...
Yeah.
Spoilers, by the way.
Thanks, guys.
Oh, here we go.
Good.
I don't have to read it.
I'm missing something.
It'll just tell it to me.
Oh, shit.
So he's a demon.
Turned him on me?
Whoa.
The heck, dude?
What the fuck?
Okay.
No, they're not personal pizzas.
What?
Did that guy get up?
Open the door?
I don't...
I can't.
There's another...
There's an old key in the drawer with the ID in it.
Are you shitting me?
Oh, man.
Wait.
How do I pick it up?
Mr. Delva's extra keys.
How do I use them?
Why can't I pick them up?
Okay.
Well, let's go.
Yeah, fuck that guy.
Who cares?
What the hell?
Can't you hear me?
Wait.
That's a...
That's TTT9.
You!
Is Raymond here?
Do you see what he's doing?
Do this to someone.
I think you should let me out.
You ain't going anywhere.
Shut up.
I want wishes.
I want wishes or you ain't going anywhere.
You'll be here soon.
I want wishes and I'll let you out.
Three of them.
It's a simple trade.
I let you out?
You give me three wishes.
You give me whatever I want.
But you have to promise not to kill me when you get out.
That's my...
That's what I have to say.
I know every time that in a movie when this happens,
it's typically,
oh, I summoned fucking Voldemort.
Whatever.
And they just like the second they get out,
they kill the first person,
which is usually the person that summoned them, right?
And why is that?
That's fucked up.
Can we go over this just very quickly?
Every time that in any video game,
in any movie,
any TV show,
the guy that spends his entire lifetime summoning
or bringing back the ultimate bad guy
is the first person for the ultimate bad guy to kill.
It's unfair.
That's absolutely not fair.
Do you know how hard it was to bring you back?
That's unfair.
I'll mark this one down as maybe.
Maybe we'll come back.
What about Peter Pettigrew?
All right.
All I remember from Peter Pettigrew is this.
That's it.
That's all I remember.
All right.
So now what?
It's this guy smiling.
Go get her blood.
Wait, go get her blood?
Get the blood.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
You mean go get the blood that was next to her and use it here?
Where should I use it?
The bottles of her blood.
All the reagents are her blood.
Yeah, that's what I'm imagining.
Yeah, this is all her.
Yeah, it's all this is all her.
I already have it.
Yeah, that's scary.
All right.
Where was I?
Right.
We have to do this.
That was scary.
All right.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Let me.
Okay.
Come on.
Fine.
I gotta get back into this before I die.
Get the tubes.
And let's pump.
What's wrong?
You already did this.
Wait, here comes.
Let me in, you bitch.
All right, this is it.
No, no, I didn't want to let you in.
Don't you miss me?
Maybe you could slit your wrist for me.
Just a little cut.
What's wrong?
I ain't ever inviting grandma to Christmas ever again.
Sorry.
That was weird.
I was like, why can't I not press the button?
All right.
Pump.
Turn off pump.
Remove tubes and fill.
How do I?
Somebody said, go kill the basement lady.
I don't know how.
How do I do that?
Oh, shit.
Something's going to happen.
Something's about to happen.
I'm sitting in the corner.
Her mark.
Oh, wait, it was tear, tear, parka, parka, tear, parka, parka, tear.
I can't do it.
What?
Yeah, I can't.
It's three T's.
There's tiles in the basement.
Whatever.
What is it again?
Such YouTuber reactions.
All right.
Who was this?
It was Tell Duck, right?
Bong, Hearthstone, Pi, Jay.
All right.
Why does the thunder scare you?
I don't know, because it's just sudden.
All right.
Yeah, I get it.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Stop it.
I'm fine.
There we go.
Okay.
Let's put you.
Oh, I don't want to leave.
I don't want to go back in here because the grandma's here.
Uh-oh.
Oh, don't you want to say hi and hello to your grandmother?
I'm so scared.
Don't you want to say hi to your grandmother?
No, don't you want to say hi to your grandmother?
It's definitely you.
Burn, I've got the coins, right?
All right.
Okay, it's time.
It's time.
Let's put it on.
So you're saying if I do this now, I get a super ending.
Do you think it's the wrong one?
I wonder if it's the right one.
Okay.
So now I'm going to get a secret ending.
I have 10 year coin, five year coin and the necklace.
Am I good?
Surely.
Double check your stuff.
Yeah, I got my coins and I got the necklace, right?
See you later.
What?
What are you talking about?
Um, what?
Where's the fucking power?
Where's the power?
Oh, no.
It's gonna get up.
Oh, I just fell.
I just literally tripped.
There was nothing scary.
I just tripped on the rug.
How do I turn it on?
What?
I need the tiles from the basement.
I don't want to go back in the fucking basement.
Dude, where?
Oh, you were full of shit.
Okay, nevermind.
I think it might be bugged.
It didn't moisturize.
Yeah, it did look.
What the hell?
I have to put him back in?
What?
Uh, why won't he go on?
You didn't finish all the...
That's the last one.
I did it all.
There's a fourth body and there's none.
Um, what?
It's...
It bugged out?
Yeah, I tried the fuse box in the bathroom.
It didn't do anything.
Um, I think this is screwed up.
Check your tablet.
There are no tiles in it.
Yeah, there is.
No, that's correct.
I think it's screwed up.
Um, I just reload the game.
Okay, return body to cold storage.
So, we're back.
This is it right here.
Take the mark.
Here we go.
Yep, looks good.
Come with me.
All right, we're back in cold storage.
Is that good?
Oh.
Burn.
There we go.
All right, let's go for it.
I got the coins, right?
Yep.
Who's knocking?
Got it.
Ow.
So, this is a secret ending?
It's not a secret ending.
It's not a secret.
A secret Raymond ending.
Down there, right now, just suffering for no reason.
Valerie is not down there.
She's been gone for years.
You don't know that.
You're just gonna let her stay there.
You don't know what she's feeling.
You are torturing her.
She's helping me survive.
She's helping us survive.
Without her, there's no reagent.
Without the reagent, we have nothing.
You want to have a chance at life, it comes with a cost.
This cost.
You have to make a choice, just like I did.
What choice?
Keep her alive to just bleed her over and over again to save ourselves?
She can't be saved.
End the torture.
She's down there suffering for your own gain.
My gain?
You used her too.
It didn't stop you from finishing the job.
You used her blood anyway.
When it came down to it, you chose survival.
Actually, you never told me that.
I did not come with a context of what was necessary to know that.
No, you drank it too.
I've seen many experience what you did.
None have survived.
I've watched them degrade and suffer until they're no longer themselves.
I didn't know what else to do and just let them suffer.
I searched for years to find a way to reverse it.
All I found was the way to prevent more.
Isn't that better than nothing?
I killed them all, Rebecca.
It was the only thing I could do.
So yes, I am a monster.
But this one horrible thing has prevented me from having to take any more life.
I would choose that again and again.
I can't live with any more death than I already do.
I've made peace with it.
The choice is yours if you can too.
I'll see you tomorrow.
Ending four of five?
Wouldn't that have been three?
Wait, have I done this four times?
All right, that was fun.
Oh, okay, I see.
You messed up the coin ending.
You need to get the coins and necklace from the apartment
then pick up two more coins from the drawer in the mortuary.
Oh, well, whatever.
All right, get the possessed ending.
No, I gotta go.
I'm hungry and I've been sitting here for a while.
I know it doesn't seem that long but I'm still dealing with some problems.
It's because you're scared.
This is great.
The scares were really interesting.
Turning the corner and just kind of seeing a person just standing there.
It's just weird.
It's creepy.
This is fun.
Mortuary assistant.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
Tomorrow we're going to play Two Point Campus and maybe something else.
Pulted Lamb is out too, right?
Maybe I'll do that.
Two Point Campus is going to be sponsored
and I'm thinking about playing it so that's awesome.
The sponsor streams have been amazing by the way.
It's just stuff that I want to play.
Stuff that I'm really interested in playing.
I'm already interested so that's been great.
Pulted Lamb is not sponsored.
Yeah, I would just be playing it.
So I'm really happy about it so far.
I hope the sponsor streams have been good.
You know, I obviously want to play games that people would probably want to watch.
Pulted Lamb is a 10 out of 10.
Maybe I'll open with that.
Play that for like two or three hours and then do Two Point Campus for a few hours.
We'll figure it out.
The sponsor streams feel like a normal stream.
That's really what I'm looking for.
All right, cool.
I'll see you guys tomorrow.
I'm going to start probably around like 2?
2 PM? 3 PM?
We'll make it 3 just in case.
Thanks for watching everybody.
The Call of Duty tournament was really fun.
It's cool to hang out.
Play with Myth.
It's like, who knows?
I want to get these guys over to multiverses.
You know what I mean?
It's like, who played multiverses the other day?
Yesterday or whatever.
I love that game.
Let's play the game I'm good at.
All right, let's see you tomorrow.
Thanks again.
If you're still here from Connor.
A little bit late.
Started late though.
Green Screen Part 2 is going to be on Sunday.
That'll be the last real stream that you see here until baseball.
Because we're probably going to do just a little hangout session before baseball.
Kind of like Dollhouse.
I'm not going to be giving that much info because it's not as elaborate as Dollhouse was.
Where you need to know about the game being played in the background.
I had to kind of explain that before the stream.
But we'll hang out.
I'll talk about it.
Try to hype it up a little bit.
This is not the right music by the way.
This music is scary.
You need to explain the rules of baseball to chat.
August 19th.
430 p.m. Pacific.
Be here.
The German Baseball Association.
That's in the middle of the season so.
Good night guys.
Call your mother.
Take care of yourselves.
Have a great day.
Have a great night.
And goodbye.