Do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
will be up on YouTube. This whole thing.
Again, because I didn't check that.
Where from Massachusetts am I from?
I am from Boston. I guess I'm not
really from Boston. I'm kind of
from a suburb of Boston, but
I'm close enough where I can say I'm from Boston, I guess.
Let's get a zero out of
chart 24.
Any zero out of 32? There it is.
Alright, how about this one?
Here's the IP. I know what Redding is.
I have family members in Redding.
That's pretty cool. Alright, the
IP is going in the chat right now.
Make sure I get in there first. There you go.
What's going on, guys?
Bad water basin. Let's fill this server up, huh?
Come on, let's go.
I don't got all day.
Who am I kidding? I got plenty of time.
I got all the time in the world.
That's not really that true.
Zero to zero. Where is everybody?
I'm the only person. Did I give the right server?
I think I did, didn't I? Hope I did.
I hope I gave the right server.
Let me make sure I did.
This is the one, right? Yeah, okay.
Copy. Yeah, I'm going to put it in there again
just in case. Just in case.
Alright, it looks like that was the right server.
I hope so.
Like you won't fight off.
I like your hat, Nimby. You get a cool hat.
First time in my stream because you are
six hours ahead. It is late for you.
You are a late dweller.
That guy's lagging. I don't want to kill him.
I feel bad. That guy was slow motion.
Got my lemonade over here on the left.
It has been really nice out.
I don't know what it's been like for you guys
wherever you live, but
my goodness, it has been so beautiful out here lately.
It's been 75 degrees,
80 degrees every single day.
And I've been going outside a lot.
I've been taking my new dog for walks.
You know that deal. Oh, I actually killed him.
Oh, that's a spy.
Oh, nice shot, dude. Nice shooting, Tex.
Funny spots.
Alright, what have we got here?
Ooh, good dodging.
Jump into it.
Damn. How long did the stream go? I just started.
I literally just started like
five minutes ago. Oh, boy, that's death.
Oh, come on. Pyro versus Pyro.
Oh, I didn't kill him.
Oh, I thought he was going to go to the...
I'm going to die. He knows how much health I have.
Oh, run away. Dead.
Aquafire 102. What's up, dude?
No demo, man. I'll change the setup.
Oh, by the way, if anybody has noticed,
I'm not sure if you've noticed. Oh, God, there's that spray again.
But, my...
I changed my FOV. I made it bigger.
I'll show you what I did.
I didn't make it too huge, but
here's my FOV now.
I changed it to like 30% more,
and I made my
weapon view model like 30% more.
So, if you've noticed that, I know a lot of people were saying,
please change that.
So, I did.
And it actually is a little bit better.
Easier to see things.
I got a healer now. Alright. That guy's got a buff of Vienna.
Oh, I didn't kill him. He walked right over it, too.
What? Where did he come from?
Where did he even come from?
Was he the medic? No, the medic was healing me.
Like, that medic behind me was healing me.
He just came out of legit nowhere.
Dear Engi, I sapped your sentries. See you again soon,
lol, spy.
Spray over.
That's a nice spray, though. What? That's how he gets in here.
He's still alive.
Don't let him get me. Don't let him get me.
Oh, he's got nowhere to go now. How did he get that?
He's gonna get me.
He's doing a side stab.
He's gonna move. Yeah.
There we go. Dear Engi, I sapped your sentries.
Oh, and I'll move that.
That's mean.
We're getting rolled right now.
Oh my god, I haven't done anything.
Why do I only have like one kill?
Oh, you're making me waste my stuff, scout.
Oh, come on. How did I not hit him?
Let's get him out of here.
He's not dead. He is not dead. He is definitely still alive.
Alright, let's go for a super spam shot here, dude.
Come on, walk over that.
Oh my god.
Chaos.
What do I have crits for?
What a waste.
Let me get the medic at least.
Thank goodness. If I didn't kill that medic, I would have been so upset with myself.
Do I like Twitch or do I like YouTube better?
I mean, YouTube has a lot of problems right now.
There's a lot of glitches with YouTube.
There's a lot of bugs and stuff.
And it's in beta. I can understand that.
But I would definitely say the process is much easier on Twitch.
That's what I will just say at least.
The YouTube stream is better quality though.
Because I'm partnered on YouTube and I'm partnered through Machinima.
So the YouTube stream will look better.
But, I don't know.
Hopefully they fix up some of their bugs.
I'm confident they will.
Whoa. Somebody walked through there.
Medic!
Yeah, I'll go combat engine next.
Look at all these people. My goodness.
Oh, don't get yourself killed.
Oh man.
Oh, come on. Kill somebody.
Oh, I got the medic. Good.
Oh, keep coming. Oh no!
Come on, give me the health.
What? Uber! What? Escape! Escape!
Damn.
Thought I was going to escape. But I didn't.
Boom. Yeah, after this round I'm going to go combat engine.
Oh, there's a crit dude right there.
Oh no, give me away.
Where's the spy? Oh, he's up top there.
He's going up this way. Get him!
Why am I stuck on the staircase?
Is that another spy?
Yeah, there he is.
Everyone's running frantically around chasing this spy.
Oh, I'll walk over that, please.
Somebody go to the left side.
Come on. Dare you.
I double dog dare you.
Anybody up there? I'll leave that there.
That can be the defense spam.
Oh god. Anybody in the car?
No, not yet. Get away from me.
Yeah, come on. Get on the car now.
Come step on that car. You know you want to.
Somebody get on that car. I want to blow it up.
I need to get healed.
Wait, is there a spy up at spawn?
I might have to go deal with that. Hold on.
Oh, I just launched myself into nowhere.
What? What is going on?
Why? Why are they bouncing?
Where's the spy?
He's freaking me out. Was that a sniper?
No. Yikes.
The IP, I linked it a while ago.
I'm going to be changing servers after this anyways.
Get more people into the game.
There's a lot of people in this room.
There's definitely a lot of people still in here.
Oh, crits. Oh, I didn't get anybody.
Come on, damn.
A soldier? Hold on. I've got to deal with this.
Oh!
That's a spy.
That's definitely a spy. No way. Maybe not.
No, it's not a spy.
Oh my god.
I was not ready for this, but I'm going to do it anyways. Let's do it.
Oh, come on. There may be something over here.
I can blow people up. Come on. Die, you bastard.
Jerma is a wizard. Official.
Let's go. Woohoo.
Oh, man. Look at all those people.
How am I doing?
Not that bad.
No 720 here.
I'm not partnered on Twitch.
It's over. I owe gaming.
Register today.
I killed myself. Damn.
I want to start live streaming soon.
Any advice on how to get started? Oh, yeah.
Most important thing is your internet needs to be able to handle it.
That's, I'd say, the number one thing.
Go to speedtest.net
and run a speed test.
I'd say if you upload speed,
if your upload speed is less than one,
like 1.0,
one megabit per second up,
I'd say it might be difficult for you to stream
in good quality.
But if you're higher than one or two
megs up,
you should be fine to stream.
I mean, you guys have been here before when I've had problems
streaming. I mean, I have 10 up connection.
Oh my god.
Somebody run over that. There we go.
Yes. Yes, yes, yes. That's what I wanted.
Run. But you guys have been to streams before
where it's been unwatchable from lag.
And I have a 10 up connection.
It's just weird.
The internet is a weird place.
And also I'd also say you need a pretty good processor
and video card because essentially your computer's
doing kind of like double work.
Oh, no, I got crit rocket.
Oh, I got two cats, man. I love cats.
I love any animal.
The only animal that I could probably say I don't like
is, I don't know,
maybe like, this is a hard
question. The only animal that I don't think
I would like to... Oh my god, another Uber.
This is ridiculous. I'd like
the Uber machine tonight.
Oh,
that was crazy.
Anyways, probably an animal
big enough that will like literally kill me
if I go near it. So
probably something like that. Oh, yeah, four up
is fine. You'll be fine with four up.
Here we go. Oh, boy.
God, I feel like the other team's
getting neglected. Spread the Ubers around.
I don't need them all. No, I'm just kidding.
We're going up top here. Or I could
just apparently not detonate the
mine. What's going on here? What's going on
here? So many people. So
many people to spam. This is
chaos. Oh, this is absolute chaos.
Oh my god. This is
ridiculous. 32 player servers
are insanity. Yeah, this...
Oh my god. Yeah, there's a
full group in here, man.
Yeah, right after this round ends, I'm
gonna hop on a new server. Oh,
fly. Oh, that's a double.
That's a double. Let's go up here.
Hey. Hey, you. Oh, you're real.
I was going to high five
him.
Oh, you want to high five? Oh, sure, I'll
high five you and then just explode
myself. Wow,
that was pretty
unintelligent of me. But yeah,
that's what I do.
All right, new server. I'm gonna say new
server. Oh, you want to high...
See, my brain. A lot of you guys already know
this. Sometimes I just don't think.
It happens quite often, actually.
All right, let's see. Let's see
here. Hmm. I would say
let's play a randomizer server, but
for my streams, I like to
get a lot of people into the games.
As many people as I possibly can that are
watching. So, I don't
want to just, you know, because most of the randomizer
and arena mod type servers, they're
always full. They always have, you know,
23 out of 24, so I would be the only
one that would be able to get in. So, I
like to have people from the stream get priority
and come and play and stuff like that. So,
let's find another server. This
one was 32. All right, oh my god,
there's so many loading. Looking for
32. High tower, got a bunch of bots,
eh. Will I ever do a workout
video? I've
thrown it around. I was gonna do it a long time
ago, but it's just, I
don't know if people would even watch it.
I know that there would be a very small
group of people that would probably watch it,
but I don't know if, like, how
it would be received. I think a lot of people
would be like, what the hell are you doing?
Why are you, like, lifting weights?
24, 25, 32.
Uh, okay.
Well, here we go. Good old fashioned dust ball.
Here is the IP.
Oh, and everyone's always asking about
Enlighten, the new Enlighten.
I'm working on it right now. So,
there will be a new Enlighten in the next couple
of days. Working on it right now.
Yeah, I'll probably do
another one of those videos where I give advice,
and I'll probably do, like, maybe a one or two minute
a vlog type thing where I show you
some stuff, but I'm not sure I would do, like,
a 20 minute workout video.
Like, okay, then up, then down,
then up, then left. I think that would
just be odd. I mean, I think that would be very
weird. Let's go blue. I was red last time.
Let's go blue. Boom. Boom. Boom.
What do I want to use? Oh, the new PDA.
What's gonna be? Oh my god!
And up,
and down, and left, and
egg.
And egg.
Alright, let me say this.
Would you guys watch an egg workout
video? Like, if it was the egg.
What do I want to even play with?
I'll stay with this. I'll stick with this. Why not?
Boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
This server's like...
Does this server look weird?
I'm like, lagging. Oh, I'm trying. I tried to high-five them.
Oh wait, you can just hold your hand like that?
Oh yeah. High five,
baby. Alright, and I don't know
if it's the server or not, but is everybody
all jumpy? Because they are on my screen.
Like, lookit. Does anybody else see that?
We'll go... I don't wanna...
We'll go for one or two rounds like this.
Oh, high five! Here we go!
Swooping!
Yeah, I mean...
Oh god, everyone's like jumping all over the place for me.
Oh!
Sentra, damn!
Hey! Hey!
Hey!
What do you think you're doing?
Oh, I forgot I was gonna answer that question.
The reason why I don't do auto-reload is cause it...
Is somebody in here?
Like, the ghost of the pyro is just in that room with me.
Oh no!
Oh god, what do I do?
Alright, well here we are!
Oh, I'll block your way out.
You can't get out!
You're a dead ringer!
I got you blocked in!
Hey!
There's a tip right there.
If you shoot a dead ringer and you know he's a dead ringer,
just stand in the middle of the hallway.
And he can't get by you.
At least... At least sometimes.
Oh.
Dispatch are going up.
Up here.
I don't know why I decided to put them here.
This is a bad idea.
Oh jeez!
Where is my mini Sentra?
Why is it still alive?
Oh my god.
Getting distracted.
I get distracted.
I have ADD, man.
Wow, we already won?
My goodness.
Oh my goodness.
FG Spidey.
Betcha I can say your name.
I betcha a dollar I can say your name.
32-man Dustbowl is chaos.
I'm gonna go Huntsman Sniper.
If you want to throw me a duel, I'll absolutely do you.
Ah!
Oh, now I got a...
Oh, let me say it.
I got a Cyanagosa.
I think that's how you say it.
Cyanagosa.
And oh, by the way, if you're watching this on YouTube,
because I'm gonna upload this to YouTube afterwards,
yes, I am responding to people in the chat,
so don't just think I have some kind of weird disorder
where I just say random words.
Like I said that last time, too.
Oh, come on, this guy's gonna get headshot.
Right now.
Right now, here we go, ready?
I don't think you know, I don't think you understand.
I don't think you understand, here it comes.
Oh my god, he killed me.
Oh no, a different guy did.
Eggs.
Look at this egg.
Man, this server is lagging for me.
I'll tell you right now.
Oh, look at this double spy collateral.
Oh no, run away.
Oh, attack!
I can't even aim at people.
My screen is like, take a jellyfish.
Oh, he got me.
Oh, look at this server.
I don't think this server was designed
to have this many people in it.
Oh, what, you wanna get covered in Jirardi?
Is that what you're saying?
You want me to come smash you?
Is that what you just said?
You want me to come smash your face in?
I got him.
Fan of Kid Icarus, I never played it.
Not even the original, and I'm an old bastard,
and I didn't even play the original.
Oh, that would've been sick.
I hurt somebody.
God, I love to kill somebody, finally.
I got my first kill ever.
Whoa, did you see where I shot?
If you're watching this on YouTube,
please rewind that and look at where I shot.
I shot like five feet over that guy's head,
and I still killed him.
No, oh God.
Let's just, all right, let's do it.
Oh, there was no way I was gonna get out of there.
A good, affordable graphics card.
That's a good one.
I'd say probably the GTX 550 or the 560.
I think those are both under 200 bucks, I think.
I don't know, under 100.
I think the 550 is, I don't know, the 550 Ti,
I think it's called.
I don't even remember.
Boom.
Oh, I missed him.
Oh God.
I think eggs should be a weapon.
I don't know how well they'd work.
Oh, SimSass, you got the 550?
Is the, how much is the 550?
And follow-up, is it a good graphics card?
Did you, did you, did you, did you, did you?
Oh my God.
Hey, what's going on?
Just hiding over here, away from you.
No, no, please don't kill me, please.
Did you buy the 550 or did it come with your computer?
I'm still like thinking.
Medic, cover me.
Oh, I didn't get him.
Okay, yeah.
So the 550 is only like 130 bucks.
I'd say that's a good graphics card
to be able to save a little bit of money.
Because the 580 is, geez, what, like $500?
Something like that.
I know it's up there.
And they're already working on the 600, aren't they?
The 600 series.
Is that?
Okay, you're real.
You're the real deal.
I got you.
Oh, I'll cover them all.
Okay, okay.
Did I even get, no.
Get this one guy, come on.
The 680 is out now?
Oh dear Lord, what is that?
Like $900?
Can only imagine.
Woo!
I don't think we're going to win this.
Oh God, there's people over there too.
All right, I'm going this way.
Nobody up here?
We almost just got it.
Oh, he's still alive, he's still alive.
Hey, he's turned around, he's behind you.
Oh my God.
Dude, you just like crushed that guy.
Geez.
Oh, forget that, I'm going this way.
Oh my God.
What's my favorite movie?
Hmm, I don't know.
Probably Ghostbusters, or Memento, or The Dark Knight,
or one of the Muppet movies,
or there's a lot of movies I've watched that I like.
I'm not a big movie watcher though.
I'm not even a big TV watcher either.
Oh my God, I just missed his head.
Oh, this guy could be toast.
Oh my God.
They're all here for me.
Oh, this guy doesn't even know I'm here.
Damn it.
Fight Club is also a good one, Ari.
Fight Club is a good one.
I remember the first time I watched Fight Club.
I was so confused.
I think I was like 16, or like 17.
When did that movie come out?
Somebody do a quick research and find out
when did Fight Club release it?
When did it come out in theaters?
Get somebody right in the foot, ready?
Right in the toe.
Aw.
Oh my God, hide.
Hey, you wanna see if like grandpa can beat box?
I don't think he can.
I would assume grandpa could not beat box.
1999, okay.
Oh, so that means I was.
So 10 years ago was 2009, so 10, 11, 12.
So that was 13 years ago.
I was, hmm.
So I'm 26, 16, 15, 14, 13.
I definitely didn't watch it when I was 13.
I don't think my parents would have let me do that.
I mean, once I watched it,
I think the first time I watched it
when I was like 15 or 16, something like that,
and I was confused.
I was absolutely confused.
Office Space is a good movie, too.
The thing is, I've seen a lot of movies,
but I don't watch a lot of movies.
If that makes any sense to anybody,
then oh my God, I just accidentally got that guy.
Greetings from Chile.
Greetings from East Coast, USA, dude.
It's either very early or very late for you.
I'm not sure.
Actually, no, I think we're in the same time zone.
We're close, the same time zone.
Oh my God.
All right, time to play Scout.
My real name is Jeremy.
It's Jeremy, J-E-R-E-M-Y.
Look at all these people he's blowing out.
Look at this good pyro right here.
Just running around blowing all the teammates out.
You get a gold star.
No, it's not Jeremiah.
It's just Jeremy.
Oh, there's a lot of people right there.
Hmm, watch it, watch it, watch it.
All right, Scout's not gonna work.
I'll go medic.
Do I like Irish people?
I do, I am Irish.
I am Irish, so.
Look at this server.
All right, I'm gonna change servers after I die next
just because this server is very laggy.
Look at this guy.
It looks like he's part of a claymation.
Look at this claymation server we're on.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, this is why I like the quick fix
because you can just do this and it makes sense.
Oh my God, that was the guy I just healed.
New server.
That new server, what's this?
Oh yeah, he defeated me.
Probably hop on one more server
and try some Tribes of Sen
because that game is really cool.
Let's go zero out of 24 this time
just to keep the lag factor down a little.
King of the Hill Sawmill, no.
King of the Hill Nucleus, that could be good.
Mm-mm, no.
King of the Hill, no.
High tower, eh.
I'm torn, guys, I don't know where to go.
You are garbage, Jerva, why?
What did I do?
Badwater Mountain Lab, a day in the life of Jerva.
Where I just eat like Cheetos and take a bath.
All right, we're gonna go here.
We're gonna go to Viaduct.
Coth Viaduct, there's the IP.
I put the IP right in the chat.
Should say a little camera next to my name.
Oh, let's go.
Let's go spy.
This is a very weird load-up.
I'm not sure what I was trying to do here.
Oh, I got the strange dead ringer.
The server's full, the server's full.
Sermer, what am I talking about?
If you can't get in or you're trying to get in,
I do apologize.
I think I do have a strange, oh, death.
Thanks for pointing that out.
Well, it's gonna belong to somebody else pretty soon,
so might as well rack up as many kills on it as I can, right?
Hey, look, I'm an engineer walking at you
from the other side.
Oh, you got me.
Damn, how dare you kill me like that.
If I could go pro at any sport, baseball.
I've always wanted to be a baseball player.
Not exactly sure why, but I just have.
Used to play baseball when I was younger.
Into high school, then I stopped in high school.
Oh, my death.
So that way, now they're gonna all know
that I just dead rung.
Dead rung, is that even like a word?
Oh, let's protect this point.
I'm a pyro, I do that the best.
That was just a scared chaos stab right there.
Now, what are you wearing?
Oh, the team is still trickling in.
Well, look, I'm just coming out of spawn myself.
Hey, look, so let's get out of spawn together.
What did, what?
Oh, Jerma, I'm cheating.
I'm watching your stream.
Is my name even Jerma right now yet?
Oh, Scrumpadump, Harvey Hamburger, George Bumberson.
I go by a lot of different titles.
I won't get out of my way.
Oh, you son of a B.
Well, that's like five million deaths in a row.
Is a spy, time to change something else.
Low FPS.
Oh, what am I even using?
Okay, I'll rock with this.
I'll roll with this, I'm cool with that.
Thought there was a spy.
Oh, what just happened?
Oh, my brain.
There was a soldier right there?
Oh, I just killed that medic.
I'm sorry, dude.
I don't think I've ever had a embarrassing name.
Oh, my preferred breakfast food?
Oh, are you kidding me?
Eggs, I had to say.
What do we got here?
No more fooling around.
Let's get some kills.
Let's kill some bastards.
Get on this point.
Boys and girls.
Oh, where is he?
You are a spy.
Yep, because you're invisible now.
Well, that was a total not good idea.
Oh, what was, what?
Did I jump in the air?
Did I, what just happened to me?
I don't even understand how that happened.
Maybe I did jump.
That's a buzz veered.
Kill Jerma, nice name.
Well, at least I got one kill.
Tad around.
Boink, boink, boink.
How do you open console?
It's the tilde key, the thing under escape.
Oh, I gotta do some expert rocket jumping, guys.
Here we go.
Expert rocket jumper.
Check me out.
I'll be on, I don't even know what the name of the site is.
So wait, why would I give up TF2?
I thought I made this explicitly clear that I never was.
TF2 is a huge part of my existence.
Otto, Otto.
Where is Otto?
That's a good question.
That's a sniper and he's gonna, no, he's not.
What is that?
God, that was awful.
Here we go.
Can I get like a string of two and three in a row here?
And you, at least I'm killing people now.
Oh, my Liberty Launcher is now a new rank.
Yeah, I understand that phenomenal.
But to be honest, the items that I have
in my backpack right now, I mean,
I know I can understand like,
oh, he's giving away his whole backpack, he's gonna quit.
I understand that, but I mean,
I have a lot of friends in Team Fortress
and a lot of people that, oh God, hold on.
Oh God, I just totally ruined that bush.
Oh my God.
But I got a lot of friends in Team Fortress
and I have a lot of people that support me with this channel.
So any item that I ever wanna use, I can just get it back.
It might not be strange, it might not be genuine,
but that's, I don't care.
I figured because, like I said in the video,
I started with Team Fortress 2
and I got all the support from you guys from Team Fortress,
a lot of you guys are Team Fortress guys,
and that was a decent, decent shot.
And that's why I felt like doing it,
you know, just something I felt like doing.
And mine's made up, there's no going back now,
so it's gonna happen.
And let's see if I can, no, there's a mini sentry.
All right, after this round, go to one more server
and then I'm gonna hop and drive to send.
Boing, boing.
No, that was laggy.
Oh, I didn't wanna do that.
Oh my God, what is going on with that guy?
That guy was just skydiving right there.
Oh, I'm dead, I am so dead.
Diddy, diddy, diddy, diddy, diddy.
Oh, you lagged out, yeah.
Boom, mission ends in 60 seconds.
Oh, how did I not hit him?
Mini sentry, get out of here.
Oh, there's a sniper, good to know.
Oh, this is where we get in trouble.
Somebody snip us, he's still alive.
Watch the spawn, Optimus Prime is on the loose.
No, you're real, where could he be?
Gotta get on that point, get on it, there we go.
Everyone just stop on here right now, there we go.
All right, one minute 40 seconds, we got this.
Hmm, you gotta back up.
Damn, every time I shoot a crit rocket,
it just goes right by everybody.
Oh, boom, oh, no, no, no.
No, I just ruined this again.
Oh, I'm sorry medic, I'm an idiot.
Aw, yeah, Tribes is a free-to-play game right now.
I would suggest everyone to go get it.
If you play Team Fortress, you'll probably like Tribes.
It's just another one of those kind of fast-paced,
you know, projectile-based, crazy fun games.
FPS, it's first person shooter.
All right, so let's add a new server, new server.
All right, we'll do one more server here,
then I'm gonna hop into Tribes
for probably like a half an hour or so.
So we have 32, okay, let's go to,
we got, this one is open and it's Dustbowl.
Huh, we just did, we already did Dustbowl.
Busytown, what the hell is Busytown?
This one's well, we can do well.
Actually, no, no, no, no, that server might not be able to.
All right, we'll go to this one, CTF well.
And there you are, everyone join it.
Empty randomizer?
Um, I mean, eh, I mean, randomizer, is it really empty?
So those servers are like legit empty right now?
No, okay, next week we'll do randomizer.
We'll do some randomizer next week.
I'm gonna use the shortstop.
And I'm gonna put on the whole set.
Why not, right?
Why not?
Boom, boom, boom, boom.
Oh, the round's not even started, I'm gonna get a kill.
No, I'm not, too bad, woohoo.
Oh, I'm gonna sneeze, I gotta sneeze
and there's nothing I can do about it.
Oh, I'm gonna sneeze, here it comes.
No, no, false alarm.
No, oh man, sorry.
There's no button I can press to mute me.
Are we getting spawn trapped?
What's going on?
Thank you.
Mark, get me in here.
Oh god, they're gonna get crits.
Damn, itsy bitsy spider went up the water spout.
Down came the rain and wiped out that god damn spider.
I just bumped into a spy, but I don't care.
Oh, get away from me, oh man.
No, you are not, you are real.
Well, is, he's still alive.
No, he's not, wait, what?
How is that, unless I actually really just killed him,
I don't think I did though.
Go up top, there's the health, that's what I wanted.
Oh god, no, this just bounced off the door
and came back at me in the face.
Oh, come on away, give me my milk, give me my milk.
Oh, all right, seven level, thanks for coming, man.
Will they ever do more duel commentaries?
Oh, hell yeah, I just did one the other night
on CSGO with MLC stealth.
Oh, just jump over everybody,
try and get around.
Oh, I was gonna get hit by the train.
Get me out of here, get me away from me.
Come on, just give me the stupid intelligence.
D-A-M-M, damn, damn.
Oh, what just, oh, I got backstabbed.
Dang it, do do do, do do do, special delivery.
All right, do do do, was this in the lower right?
Jerma sucks at TF2.
Oh, we got a troll, we got a troll.
All right, one more round of this.
I'm gonna go pyro this time.
Hmm, I always do not, I don't put on, let's go, yeah.
All right, last round,
then I'm gonna hop over to tribes, ascend, damn, ah.
All right, I gotta appear offline.
We can't have any spam coming at me,
especially when it has bad, bad things.
Do do do do do do, oh, no, no, no, no, no.
Is somebody behind us still?
Oh, there he is.
No, God, I turned and saw the goddamn train.
Oh, I don't think I even have the hat,
but the degreaser said, to be honest.
Nah, I don't have the hat.
You know, I saw, I thought I could get by,
and then I turned and scared the crap out of myself.
Oh my God, they have crits, shoot at me.
Come on, all right, don't get hit by the train again.
Oh, oh, I almost got hit by the train again.
No, I'm gonna whack you.
Oh, damn it, where is Burger Boy?
Where is Burger Boy?
How am I not letting him on fire?
Oh, does that mean we're gonna play
tribes, ascend with Burger Boy?
Special guest appearance from Burger Boy?
God damn it, Burger Boy, reveal yourself.
He has?
Burger Boy, Burger Boy's been in videos.
Oh, I'm out of ammo, oh, oh God.
Oh, my power jack, would I get one kill with it?
All right, train, me versus you.
What do you say, buddy, let's do this.
I lost.
Oh, we got crits.
Yes, I just wanna crit fire somebody.
Yeah, feels good to crit fire.
It feels good to crit fire.
All right, we're going sniper.
No, we're not, I'm going heavy.
Run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run.
Get away, oh, come on, right when I get out of spawn.
B-U-L-L-S-H-I-T,
with six exclamation points after that.
Wait, why do I have the Natasha equipped?
Okay, whatever, I'm so scared.
All right, I killed the spy from like 5,000 feet away.
Where is this guy?
Oh, my God, he's on the roof.
I thought he was to the right.
All right, take this stupid thing off.
Give me the regular minigun.
All right, I gotta like really watch my back now.
Playing heavy, like probably the worst idea
I could have ever done.
I'm gonna be on fire, die, die, die, die, get away, get away.
Oh, thank you so much.
Oh, no, here comes another dude.
How are you still alive?
What?
I get hit by the train again.
Of course I get hit by the train again.
That would absolutely happen.
Oh, for the love of God.
Hey, we're gonna get crits, I think.
I hope we get crits right now.
Oh, my God, of course.
We get crits and I die and I'm dead.
Ugh.
Take that, take this, take that.
How are you still alive?
I knew it, I knew there was a guy behind me.
You got 32 person servers that are just like ridiculous.
They are like insane, insanity.
It's like you walk out the door and it's just like,
oh, where is this guy?
I'm so scared of the spy just backstabbing me.
It's definitely gonna happen, like right now.
Yo, I'll get hit by the train again.
Oh, we won?
How did we win?
How am I in the number two right now?
All right, well, good night if you're leaving, man.
Thanks for coming.
So now I'm gonna head on to tribes.
Send time dudes and dudettes.
Thanks for playing, everybody.
All right, so I think I might invite a few people
into the call that have tribes.
Let's see how that goes.
I gotta change this to say,
I might actually do that in a minute.
Let me open up tribes.
The screen might go black for a second, guys.
So I apologize.
Screen is going to go black.
So bear with me for one second.
While I load up tribes, send.
Oh, I have ADHD, crazy bad.
I have really bad ADHD.
Jerma is dead.
I'm still here.
Darkness, it's all I see.
I already did a setup video, Hannibal.
Go to my 4,000 subscriber video.
It should be there.
Don't go into the light.
Now, my children, let me tell you something.
I am God coming to you from the black screen.
Let me tell you, all you need to do
to have a good, fun, interesting life
is to crash, because that's what I think I just did.
Oh, no, no, I'm just, I'm here.
Okay, okay, hold on.
I really thought I just hard crashed right there.
That would have been bad.
All right, let me get into the game.
Screen should come back in about 10 seconds, guys.
Settings, audio, yeah, that's fine.
Video, window, come on, let's go window, windowed.
All right, now I'm coming back.
Change the resolution.
All righty, let me just add this game
as a source into XSplit, and we should be good to go.
Game, hello.
Is that gonna fit?
Does that work?
Let's see, I think that fits, pretty sure at least.
Get that out of the way.
What's with the double screen?
That's weird.
Hmm, hold on a second, guys.
I'm gonna change this.
This is a little glitchy.
I'm just gonna add the screen region.
That should be better.
Okay, yeah, there we go.
All right, so that should be better.
All right, so I think we're gonna get some people in here
talk while we play.
Those of you that have never played this game,
please, my goodness, please go download it.
It is an unbelievable game, and it's free.
What other reason do you need?
Move this, it's not in the way.
To the left, to the left, to the right, to the right.
It needs to be moved a little bit.
All right, looks like it's centered,
at least on my screen.
So are we gonna get anybody in this call?
Maybe, what happened to the audio?
Audio's still here?
Yeah, it's here, I can hear it.
All right, somebody call me on Skype
so we can start a call.
Boo, or Stealth, or Burger Boy,
whichever one of you guys wants to do this thing,
and then just join off being home.
They might have already been calling.
Yeah, they are.
What up?
Oh, what's up, Burger Boy?
Oh, Burger Boy, now Burger Boy's calling me.
Get outta here.
Oh, I'm inviting them this one.
Is Boo around?
I was first.
What about, where's Italics?
Maybe Italics will play.
Boo's offline.
He might be doing a band thing right now.
Oh, hey, everyone.
Oh, what's up, Burger Boy?
Make sure you guys are turning up.
Oh, I was trying to stream off the game.
If somebody else wants to join,
can you guys monitor, or Stealth, can you monitor,
just in case I'm in the game?
Yeah, do it.
What's happening?
I'm just saying, when I alt tab in a window,
it just like explodes,
so I can't really alt tab anymore.
But I wanna play the game.
I mean, you could play the game,
just every 10 seconds, just check this.
So if you want, it's gonna be difficult
to join the game off me right now,
because the way this game works is you have to have,
I don't know how many friends you can have
to be honest, I really don't know.
But I'm gonna go Pathfinder.
I'm gonna turn this up.
Stream is under control.
No one's spamming you.
Stream is under control, and I gotta turn this up.
Turn this up.
Can't hear it.
All right, I think we're good.
Boo's still with sound on the stream?
Should be.
Hey, Burger Boy, do you have frogs in the sun?
Oh, he's got it.
He's absolutely got it.
So this game, if you don't know what this is,
if you're like, what the hell are you doing right now?
This game is pretty much,
think of Team Fortress meets Quake meets skiing
meets ski free meets Windows 95 meets Windows 98.
I'm not sure if that made any sense,
but this game is just, look at this, it's just chaos.
Pretty much think of this game as you play as a soldier,
like a Liberty Launcher soldier,
and that's pretty much what everyone is using.
Then you ski around like 100 miles per hour,
it's all about momentum,
and we just apparently won the game.
Yeah, that's a good way to put it.
This game is Halo with speed hacks
and cooler mechanics, in my opinion.
The music is cool.
I agree with what Jarvis said.
All right, let's change.
You go to a new map, but it's not really Halo.
It's like a, it's cooler than Halo, in my opinion,
just because I never really played Halo, so.
Because you never had an Xbox, you never could play.
I had an Xbox, I had a 360.
When?
Two or three years ago was the last time I had one.
Oh, what's going on?
Why am I like stuck here?
I'm like stuck in this like lobby area.
There we go.
So it was lagging right there, screen was lagging.
You kidding me?
Let me know if it keeps happening, guys.
Try this again.
Because if it keeps happening, I might restart it.
Just change a couple settings.
But yeah, once you get like, on a,
this game is so satisfying.
I'm going Blood Eagle, by the way.
You can get some real satisfying kills within this game.
Especially because it's all about long range,
just long ranging people, it's awesome.
Oh, did you quit and join a different game?
I did, just join off me.
Oh, come on.
Yeah, it like, kicks me out.
Oh, sure it did.
No!
It took so long to key up.
Because Burger Boy is like, not allowed to play.
How do I not kill that guy?
Here we go.
This is a beta, this is a beta.
Here's another kill.
It's free though, it's open.
Open beta.
Oh, he was in the air.
Why didn't you probably order a zerg shooter
and get that free crit?
You get three shots.
Pretty much, the path finders like the scout,
you move around really fast,
and soldiers like the soldier, I guess.
There's like, I think, nine classes in this game.
I'm pretty sure there is.
This is just team deathmatch.
And essentially, what the, why do we, what the hell?
I keep joining a game, we keep just winning.
Don't go home.
Don't quit.
All right, do not quit this one.
Keep staying, stay in this one.
Down, down.
But you see this up here, this 2700 XP.
Pretty much, if you don't wanna buy the game,
the game doesn't cost any money,
but it's kinda like in Team Fortress
where there's an economy where you can buy items
if you don't wanna wait and unlock them.
It's kinda like that.
So if you wanna spend money, you can,
but if you don't, it takes a long time
to get all the items and all the classes and everything, so.
And it's like an exaggerated long time.
Yeah.
Like 90 hours of game time to unlock a new class.
Yeah, you start with three classes
when you just get the game free.
You can spend 10, 20 bucks and you'll unlock everything,
pretty much.
What's gonna go in German?
I'm gonna go Blood Eagle, Pathfinder again.
I'm gonna turn the graphics down a tiny bit
just because I think people were saying it was lagging.
Burger Boy, you went on the other team.
Oh, Burger Boy.
What?
Oh, how do I switch teams in this game?
Did you just press escape?
Yeah, you're gonna escape and then switch teams?
Oh, this guy's toast down here.
This guy's toast, guys.
Oh, get him!
Right shot.
And let's just do it off.
There it is.
All right, so as you can see, I got a shotgun.
You pretty much only have two weapons.
I have grenades, too, but I don't really use them.
I mean, I know I should, but.
And see the top, the middle top, 97, 92?
This is team deathmatch, and essentially how this works
is when you die, one point gets taken off
your side of the team, but if your team has the flag,
or if their team has the flag, kills count as two.
So we have the flag right now, so any time we kill somebody
on their team, it's gonna count as two points
taken down from their score.
Oh, I just got nailed.
So it's lagging, huh?
No, let me see what the hell's going on here.
Wasn't doing this on Team Fortress, was it?
No, it wasn't.
Let's find out what the hell is going on.
It's too graphic with a management string.
No, that's my flag.
Shouldn't be.
I'm watching.
By the way, are you still on the terrorist thing?
Yeah.
Oh, you're still on CT?
Oh yeah, I got the flag, come get me.
Okay.
Oh, you're on the enemy team, huh?
Come get me, okay.
Destroyed.
Oh, come on, let's go 1v1, baby.
Oh, I got me, damn, got me.
It looks okay on my end.
When I'm watching the stream right now, it looks okay.
Maybe it was just like a little issue, I don't know,
not sure, but yeah.
Look at all those people in that.
Oh, I could play a sniper rifle.
Yeah, but see, when you go down,
look at the left and right of my screen.
See how I have that like power meter,
that's how fast I'm going when I ski.
The entire time you're gonna be holding down space,
essentially, in this game.
There's the flag.
All right.
Time to pull off something.
Oh, get him with an air shot, come on now.
I didn't get that guy.
Oh, killed people, go with people going for the flag.
You gotta get rid of these people, there we go.
All right, pick up the flag, pick up the flag.
I got it, I got it.
Oh, protect me.
Oh, Italics is in this game.
Drag him in the call.
Requisite?
Yeah.
Idiot drama.
Drag Italics in here.
Oh!
That was you?
I'm not impressed with him.
Oh, well, why aren't you not impressed with him?
Italics just blew me to hell, and I blew him to hell.
There we go.
Look at all these people right here.
Grenade, grenade.
Grenades are whack in this game.
Oh, there's a flag.
Give me the flag, where am I?
No, that was a snipe flag right there.
I just totally sniped that flag.
Oh, I'm losing momentum.
Gotta go, gotta go, gotta go.
I tried to Sentinel before, but I'm not very good at it.
God, I'm being chased by like a mob of people.
Well, press Z and all the people will start following you.
What?
I promise.
Yeah, because I'm gonna drop the flag.
Still got it.
Oh, maybe not anymore.
Protect me, stealth.
Oh, they got me.
Let me drag its Alex under here.
All right, he's coming.
There it is.
One more of those.
Yeah, baby.
You can get that flag.
One more of those.
Oh, one more of those, baby.
Hey, guys, what is going on?
What's up, man?
What's up, Alex?
Playing the flag, man, like I do.
Yeah, we got some good flag control.
Too bad, like, Burger Boy's terrible at this game.
He could really do something right now.
Can't even figure out how to switch teams.
It hit a scheme.
It did, and then what?
And then go to change...
And then you press,
I don't wanna be on this team anymore.
Oh, I think the MLC stealth just lied to you.
Yeah.
No, that's absolutely true.
I just did it.
Oh, wait, you pressed P.
Awesome.
That's what I meant to say.
Okay, good.
Oh, I can't, there's not enough people on that team.
Oh, this guy is so toast right now.
Oh, here we go.
Well, I can't switch.
Come on, get him with those shots.
Oh, fine, whatever, I'll go with this thing.
There's just a swarm of red upside down triangles
around that flag.
Oh, stealth, you got the flag, all right.
I sure do.
All right, let's do a little bit of teamwork here.
I'm a pro skier, watch how I go.
Yeah, if we're still playing already,
definitely, I'll get you in here.
Oh, there's Burger Boy.
Oh, Burger Boy.
Where are you?
Oh, right there, huh?
Oh, Burger Boy.
I'll switch here.
I think the teams are even.
Oh, no, no, yeah, you're, no, you didn't, not yet.
It depends on the auto balance moves, I guess.
Yeah, well, this game's almost over.
We're almost going to lose.
Oh, but I have a flag, that's good.
That means we're gonna win.
All right, so do not die.
Nobody die and we might win.
No, we won't.
That's gonna be a long range.
I'm gonna get rid of this guy.
Then I'll see, you were flying around the map right now.
I've been chasing you for so long.
I'm dead.
Like shooting Burger Boy from behind,
he's just like right behind me.
Oh, watch out, Burger Boy's gonna take us all on.
Somebody took him out, I don't know who.
Got an assist.
Burger Boy.
I can't even catch up with stealth.
And I'm on his team.
I know, really, right?
Spams, rocket spams.
Oh, we lost.
All right, try and get on his team.
I'm out looking for phone.
Try and get on his team, Burger Boy, the insensitive one.
All right, let's see if any of us
made it into the MVP statistics.
No, we sure didn't.
Yeah, you got the MLC stealth flag held top accolade.
You got like a top medal, you didn't get a MVP.
Actually, you got two, you got two medals.
Flag held and flag killer.
Top accolades.
This thing is.
My most flag held medals is 41.
And that's because I got the flag
right when the game started
and I skied around for 10 minutes and didn't get hit.
Why am I?
I didn't kill anybody either.
Why am I not logged into my own stream right now?
I just typed something, how's that possible?
So it says, oh, playing Team Fortress 2
when I'm absolutely not.
People might believe you.
What are you doing, Blood Eagle?
Yeah, go right when you can.
Is that Burger Boy just like click spamming?
Yeah, I'm trying to get in that Blood Eagle.
Now's your best chance.
Oh no.
Are we gonna get split up here?
Click faster.
I think we might get split up here.
Whatever, I'll catch you guys.
Oh, I just made it.
Oh, Burger Boy.
You could have still got nine.
Oh, he does, yeah.
He just waited.
You made it?
Oh, you made it.
Yeah, enemy has a flag.
No, I gotta change this.
It's just to say I'm playing tribes.
Tribes descend, here we go.
Broadcast updated successfully.
Uh-oh, got the flag.
Probably not for long.
No, I'm gonna go soldier this time.
I think that's the best idea.
Wow, there is no one on my team over here at all.
Try and italics, they're all behind you though.
Oh man, nice air shot.
Oh, Burger Boy made it on my team.
Oh yeah.
Oh, Burger Boy made it, that's good.
All right, let's keep going.
I got killed by an arx buster, whatever that is.
It's probably stupid.
Oh, you bastard, what are you doing?
Oh, that was a sweep under the bridge flight right there.
Oh, you wanna go assault rifle on assault rifle or something?
Oh yeah.
Oh, this guy needs one hit and he's dead.
Oh, come on, fine, thump up.
There we go, there we go.
All right, who's got the flag gun?
Uh-oh, uh-oh, they're gonna catch me now.
I ran into the border of the edge of the map over here.
Do we get the flogged estimator flag?
Yeah, we do.
And italics has two evil men chasing him.
All right, let's get over there.
Got some ninjas flying around behind me
trying to kill me.
I feel one dude chasing it.
Oh, italics' voice is smooth.
It is.
Somebody just said that.
Smooth like an erection.
Hey, this is a PG-13 stream.
I was like, I don't even know what that meant.
I was about to ask.
Oh, air shot, no, that guy just got me.
This thing doesn't go very far, I forget that sometimes.
I'm just kind of doing my best on the map right now.
I'm doing a lapse right behind you.
John Lance, where is he?
Uh-oh, uh-oh.
Trying to go faster than this.
Oh, God.
Not enough jet pack.
I'm trying to prove I'm a better skier.
Well, the classes have a lot of impact on that as well.
We'll pass you.
I'm back on you.
Yeah, if you're like the fastest class.
What are you?
Oh, damn.
I am a raider.
Yeah, this is tribe system.
You've got somebody behind you,
so I'll slow down a little bit until I'm done.
That should, this game is the person that just asked.
This game is free, and it's in open beta.
You can just play it.
You can play it as much as you want, whenever you want,
and it's a game about skiing, momentum, and fun.
It's a ski simulation game.
Yes.
Oh, this guy's smart.
What do I do with a smart guy?
Wait till he lands.
I can't believe I've been carrying
the flag this entire time.
I really can't.
We're taking care of our team here.
Wow, son of a.
Uh-oh, are we gonna get to see
some real raw Burger Boy rage?
Remember, Burger Boy, you can't say any
like wicked, horrible swears.
Oh, I'm about to run into a wall.
Oh, I ran into a wall.
It's over.
I see you, John.
Up deck here.
This is the zombie's deck.
Oh, you wanna go with this?
Boom.
Oh, nice, nice, nice.
It was a good run.
Very nice, very nice.
Burger Boy's in first place.
Burger Boy, there you go.
Oh, yeah.
Somebody get that flag.
All right, one of our guys got the flag.
Gotta get better aim.
Come on, land.
Oh, I got no ammo on this thing.
What am I doing?
I gotta get to an ammo supply.
Not doing so well right this second.
No, that's not, not doing so hot right there.
I just granated myself.
I'm like, as fast as you move in this game,
that is nearly impossible.
Yeah, I know, right?
That's crazy.
I got that guy on the couple of shots.
All right, Zephack, give me some speed.
I'll get this guy.
I'll thump this guy.
Oh, Tumblr's better than Thumpus.
Tumblr's better than Thumpus.
No, not high enough.
Wait, the flag has dropped.
I had the flag on my back.
Get out of the tower.
I got it, I got it.
I blew that guy away from you guys, nice.
Protect the Taleks.
Or I could just like sit down here alone
by myself like an idiot.
Awesome, what are you doing?
Oh, I just got air shot.
Damn.
Oh, losing momentum here.
Just got mad air shot.
I'm dead.
I don't know how I dropped these.
I see a flag, it's mine.
Well, we're doing.
I believe there are some grenades
that can make you drop stuff, like the flag.
Well, that's lame.
Actually, that's pretty cool.
Land on that.
I gotta get more, I gotta.
Oh, this guy's done.
Get out of town.
Just got killed by a blue fatty.
Somebody just said.
Juggernaut, yeah, that's a juggernaut probably.
I might wanna pull out the.
No, I might kill him.
One more shot, come on.
This is the one, this is the one right here.
Oh, no, he's not dead.
There we go.
I need to go to resupply big time.
Oh, Shibby's got a new video.
Reserve shooter.
Sick.
It's like a challenge based on your video.
Oh yeah, flag down baby.
Shibay.
All right, we're beating them by like,
we have like a 100% lead on them right now.
This guy off.
Trying to get like hit markers on him.
But man, I tell you right now, this game is a lot of fun.
I probably wouldn't have even started playing this game
if it was not for italics.
Thank you, sir, thank you.
I was like, you've got to play this game.
You're like, eh, whatever.
I was like, I'll give it a try, whatever.
It probably sucks, no.
This game is very, very good.
I saw it before a long time ago,
like months ago when people were first
starting talking about it.
And I was like, eh, it looks okay,
but this game is very addicting and very fun.
Somebody's behind me, but I don't care to turn around.
And it's free.
Yeah.
That's a huge plus right there.
I usually don't buy games that are like 10 bucks, so.
Yeah, Burger Boy doesn't buy video games
until they are $10.
And we're talking like Skyrim,
but it's like Sky, dude, you're never gonna get that game.
Oh, I'm not gonna get Skyrim three years from now.
Yeah, yeah, you're gonna get Skyrim
when you're like 35.
10 bucks yet?
Is it 10 bucks yet?
That's always, that's the Burger Boy quote.
I'll be like, oh, hey dude, you know,
Diablo 3 just came out.
10 bucks yet?
Like, no, it's not.
It's like 60.
Oh, well, I'm not blind until it's like 10 bucks.
I'm gonna try and help you with this dude.
Nice. Yep.
He was getting on you pretty good.
Yeah.
Agent 13, I thought.
Yeah, all right, let me know when...
All right, that was a joke, nobody was saved.
Wait, what did you just say?
I really just didn't even pay attention to a word you said.
Oh, I need to get up here.
I'm dead.
I'm so dead.
Yeah, absolutely.
Oh, top-fragging like a vile.
Got the guy for ya.
Nice.
Let's see if I can get a spike area with this airstrike.
Let's see if he walks right into it.
Oh, no, you almost got him.
He was in the air.
At least it looked close from over here.
I'm trying to get him in the air.
Not shooting far enough ahead of him.
Nope, still not shooting far enough ahead of him.
Oh, that could have been an air shot.
Come on now.
Mother may I.
All right, I need to wait.
I gotta recharge my stuff here.
Oh, God.
Eat that, Margo.
Eat that, Vlad.
Here we go.
Victory.
All right, let's get Ahri in here.
First one of the day.
Oh, no.
There he is.
Oh, Burger Boy with 12 kills, holy crap.
Did Burger Boy, nice.
I would not buy Team Fortress Classic.
The only reason why I say that is because it's just,
it's very, and now it's just so difficult to play.
This grenade spam is, it's,
unless it's like $5, don't buy it.
I'll put it that way.
Winner, winner, chicken dinner.
I think this is the first time I've ever gotten first place
in anything in tribes.
Oh, really?
In tribes.
That is an achievement in and of itself for me.
Not even first in the whole game.
Just first in my team.
That's good enough.
All right, quick, blood eagle.
Blood eagle.
Everybody click.
Click it.
Yes.
Go back to Pathfinder.
Oh, there's a guy right here.
Air shot, nope.
Get the first kill.
That gives you that flag, yeah.
It does?
Yep.
Oh, it's like Team Defender on Call of Duty?
You've never played Team Defender on Call of Duty?
Hey, watch it.
I can't believe that, oh, he's gonna kill me.
No, Germany, you have to get the first kill,
not first death.
I'm gonna be the first death if I don't get Lord Chaos.
I'm the first damn death.
Wow, that was the luckiest kill I've ever had.
Yeah, I'll probably do videos for tribes.
Eventually, I gotta get familiar with it, get good at it,
but I'll probably do a few videos, at least,
because this game is really awesome.
Boom.
The otter, boom, the otter.
Where am I?
I'm going the absolute wrong direction.
Gonna get some speed here.
Pickin' up speed, pickin' up speed.
Got him, and then someone got me.
Oh, we gotta get that flag.
You got it, somebody on our team got it.
MLC stealth is gonna die.
Look at that chaos, grenade into the chaos.
Oh, I thought I got that guy.
We're good, bye.
My game is just updating,
it's doing some really weird stuff right now.
Hey, when we installed it on Burger Boy's computer,
it was like all his fans turned on.
His computer almost like broke.
Explode, just randomly, I would be surprised.
That is like awesome computer I have.
Nice shot.
That guy got a really good shot.
We've had issues with Borderlands, Burger Boy.
We've had issues.
Burger Boy, Borderlands.
So Ari, how many times have you heard Burger Boy
swear and say horrible things in Borderlands?
Oh, oh God.
Basically, he did remap his keys for his special ability,
and every time he wanted to pick up an item,
he decided to activate his special ability.
And playing his break,
he was just screaming constantly
for the entire three hours that we played at a time.
Worst tank ever.
Oh, Burger Boy, come on.
You can like do better than that.
Oh, let's go, Shottie.
I don't have any momentum.
I'm like walking around the map.
Oh, I still have.
Hey, you.
I'm gonna waste this grenade.
Let's get this guy, double team.
Oh, I missed, there we go.
Another guy right there.
Two guys, 770, that's a direct shot.
Oh, that guy fell in the lava.
Oh, this guy, oh, he knew it.
Wow, that was awesome.
Come here, flag boy.
Holy crap, that was awesome.
Yes.
I just tried to get a resupply,
and a guy threw a grenade right into my feet
when I went over there and got me.
Touche, my friend, that was great, woo.
So Jerma, what classes do you have unlocked so far?
Just the sniper sentinel.
That's it.
The nice thing about, like yesterday,
we were talking about the ones
that don't detonate on impact.
They bounce around.
I have the grenade launcher right now,
and I've noticed that if you get a direct hit,
it's like the demo man, you know,
it'll just explode, it'll just pop.
Oh, really?
Immediately.
Wow.
And the nice thing about them also
is that they usually do a lot more damage
and have a bigger radius than like the spin fuses.
Yeah, I've noticed the explosion's huge.
You just get a massive damage spike right there.
Going in the lava, I keep falling in the lava
like an idiot.
Hey, stop it.
I can't help it.
Does anybody else feel like they're playing Star Wars?
Or we are on like that map.
Yeah.
What's that map called?
I don't know.
I mean, even the noise is like the,
I feel like the,
it sounds like Star Wars.
Oh, dang it.
So what are you guys' favorite classes
with the game so far?
Pathfinder.
I like moving fast and having zero health.
Yeah, I'd probably say the Pathfinder too.
Just get the shock on a solid key.
Break the trend, break the trend.
I would say Raider or Infiltrator.
See, I don't even, I gotta get those guys.
I'm not very good with the Infiltrator yet.
Never been good with stealthy classes in any game.
But it's still fun.
Yeah, so you can cloak?
Oh yeah, you can cloak.
That's crazy.
And instead of using your energy for your jet pack,
it'll use it for your stealth.
Oh, okay, that's a good trade-off.
That's not like overpowered or anything.
That's cool.
And there's a few items and like perks.
Maybe not perks,
but I know there's at least one or two items
that can like detect stealth people.
Oh, really?
I don't have any of those yet.
There's a lot of people here.
I'm so dead.
Yeah, there's like 10 people around me.
Skate down here.
Oh, Tony Hawk presents Tribes Ascent.
Do a kickflip.
All right, I'm gonna do like a shaky 200,
oh, that's like 25 points.
All right, I gotta get some speed.
Yeah, I cannot catch up to the flag carrier.
Oh, shut down his screen.
I'll try and cut him off.
Hey, Burger Boy, your phone.
How did you know it was him?
How did you know he was right there?
Hey, call you right back, I'm gonna make a stream.
I know Jerma's ringtone,
and I'm pretty sure Burger Boy's the only one
who is gonna have his phone on him right now.
What if Vitalik's has his phone on him?
I don't think he would.
I thought that was more of a Burger Boy thing,
to have his phone on him.
What that means about you, I don't know.
Give me that, give me that.
Oh yeah, I got the flag.
Hey, we're losing.
Yeah, I got the flag, just protect me.
All right, I'll lay you off.
I'll do what I want, what I want.
Oh, I'm gonna lose speed right now.
I'm gonna be sitting ducking two seconds.
I'm gonna be your body shield.
Oh my God, there's a whole crew just following you.
Did I kill that guy?
Ah, finally, jeez.
Oh my God.
Oh yeah, I got one of them for you.
Oh, I'm dead, I gotta kill though.
I got another kill?
I think another planet died.
Oh, I'm gonna land right on top
of everybody that's right there.
Oh no, give me that flag.
Oh, I ran right by it.
Oh no, oh, that bastard got it.
No, no, give the shotgun up.
Oh, damn.
Shotgun, best weapon in this game.
Yeah, I didn't pull it out early enough.
I should have pulled it out way earlier.
Oh, Vitalik's don't die.
I got him, I got him, man.
Almost died.
I have 13 health.
My streak.
I don't see you destroying 16 kills, man.
I think I just blew that guy's grenade up
in midair in front of him.
I think that's actually what just happened.
Where is the flag?
I don't know, we don't have it though.
It's a pretty much, it's a pretty close game right now.
We can't lose this.
Melee kill.
Oh, I just totally stole that from you, Burger Boy.
Melee is so tough, but so satisfying when you get it.
I only do it like on AFK people, or like snipers.
Someone just asked.
Especially when you're an infiltrator.
Someone asked me, are there hats in this game?
I don't think so.
I wouldn't, don't put it past him, man.
This game could have a lot of items in the coming future.
He's got it with a freaking crossbow.
I got the flag guy.
All right, you got the flag?
We're gonna lose.
We're absolutely gonna lose.
Try and cut this flag guy off.
Yeah, we're gonna lose.
Oh, cut him off.
It's a done deal.
Cut him off.
It's not over yet, guys.
That guy's out of speed, that guy's out of speed.
Seven to 24, I think it's over.
Five.
Oh yeah.
Oh yeah, it's absolutely over.
Somebody call in the nuke.
Oh.
Wait, no, I had 10,000 credits,
but I called in an inventory station instead.
MLC has killed me 15 times in a row,
that's how many he's said.
Well, I feel like a retard.
I was supposed to call in an orbital strike,
but I called in the inventory station.
Sorry, does nobody die?
Give me that flag.
Oh, all right, I think probably one more round, maybe.
You guys wanna play CTF, or just keep doing this?
I don't know, CTF can be very, very long,
so I'm just supposed to do one more of this.
Are you in here yet, or are you game-loaded?
45 seconds, apparently.
He says 20 minutes ago.
Well, no worries, I mean.
I got this game when Beta first was announced for this.
I signed up for this, like this,
and Firefall I signed up for like years ago.
Yeah.
And Firefall is incredible.
I got the Beta for that as well.
I'm so jealous.
It's only two times a week, though.
You can only delve on in those two periods,
one for Europe and one for US, but it is insane.
It's looking like an incredible game
if you get a chance to get it.
What is Firefall, what is it?
It's another free-to-play game coming out,
and it was like the highlight,
one of the highlights of E3 the past year.
It's, how can you describe it?
How can you describe it, Alex?
What is it called?
Firefall.
Well, I thought someone said 5-4.
That's what I did just say.
Oh, okay.
Oh, when are you gonna get it?
5-4-3-2-1.
He's saying Fire as in it burns you,
and then Fall as in falling.
Sorry, the English accent,
but he's gonna come across great.
Well, no, I'm just an idiot, so.
Firefall is like, okay, imagine.
Oh, oh, Firefall.
We played that at Tax East last year.
Yeah, that's the one, yeah.
5-4-3-2-1.
It looks like Borderlands with an MMO,
and then open world, and then awesome art style.
It is, the art style is absolutely beautiful.
It's one of the most stunning games I've seen in beta.
Like, it looks good as it is.
Yeah, right, now that's cool.
Oh, this guy's gonna land on that.
No, he's not.
Oh, I'm getting blasted, come on.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, I'm actually a shooter.
Anybody else over here with me and the flag guy?
I'm going after this dude down here.
Flag, come on, do you need help?
I'm playing Juggernaut, I'm not good with Juggernaut.
I'm okay, I gotta get better with him.
Oh, come on, walk into that.
This guy is standing still.
Oh, I just got that guy mid-air with a grenade in his back.
Did anyone else do that?
Yeah, I did, I was watching him come out.
I was like 15 feet above the guy.
I just like looked in front of him
and just like popped the grenade right on his back,
and he dropped the flag.
That was amazing.
You gotta chase him right behind you, Tellix.
Oh, he's dead now.
Somebody behind me now, I think.
Is AFK guy?
Get him?
Oh, he's not AFK anymore, is he?
Oh, no, he's AFK.
Haley.
Oh boy, come on, land, land.
Oh, nice shot, dude.
It's like a ballet of death right there, Juggernaut.
Juggernaut, I'm being chased.
I'm dead, nothing I can do about it.
You're right next to me.
What?
Oh, well, where is he?
Oh, okay.
I need to add you guys to my friends list
so I can see you.
So we can see like names, I know.
Yeah.
I'm trying to get him to walk into this grenade.
Oh, he's going too fast.
Where'd he go?
I just launched him somewhere.
Great, where the hell is he?
Oh, of course.
He's right next to me.
You got like two people behind you, Juggernaut.
Yeah, I'm trying to go for the suppressing.
Oh, I'm stuck.
I'm stuck, I'm gonna die.
I'm so dead.
I'm like on the ground.
Nope, nope, you've still got it, you've still got it.
Oh, my God.
Oh, you just saved my life right there.
What's my graphics card?
I use a GTX 470 in video.
It's good.
I wouldn't really recommend,
if you're gonna get a new graphics card,
don't get the 400 series.
There's the 400 series, at least the 470 and the 480.
They heat up way too much.
They are not recommended.
They're very, they're good cards,
but they can get to be like 80, 90 degrees Celsius,
and it's not really that good for your computer.
York, I did play Global Agenda.
I have something like 700 hours,
I think, clocked in on that game.
On Global Agenda?
Yeah, oh God.
I used to play, both me and Zeus used to play
like seriously, like two years ago.
Global Agenda is a different path.
I thought you meant Global Offensive.
No, no, Global Agenda.
That was before it was free.
Like we bought it and we played it,
and oh God, like we put in hours into that game,
and then it all kind of went downhill after a while
when they went free,
and they built Tribes Ascent instead.
They took all their money out of Global Agenda
and put it into Tribes instead.
That's pretty, and that's cool.
What was Global Agenda?
Was it like a similar game?
Yeah, it was third person,
then you could also get into first person
when you aimed down sight and things like that.
It was a really good concept,
just it needed to be made by a bigger company,
if that makes sense.
Yeah, it does.
Like APB, I guess.
APB could have been.
Auto Balance, don't die.
Or I don't know how to treat it.
APB went into the crapper, didn't it?
Cause like they ran out of money or something?
Oh yeah, they were in so much debt in the end.
EA was just like, oh, free game, we'll buy you.
They just made it free for everybody.
It just went downhill from then on in.
Yeah, there is no health kit, by the way.
There is no health kits in this game.
Oh, shit, so.
I think we're gonna win, absolutely, by the way.
I've had the flag the entire game.
That guy's just been stumbling me with this fucking air shot.
That's a sniper coming at me.
Oh, that was beautiful.
Air walking shot, gorgeous.
Gorgeous, yeah, this guy's, let's get him.
There we go.
Nice, yeah buddy.
Oh, I got it.
If I don't need it, I just.
Oh, that was an air shot.
That was a pretty close air shot, though.
I don't know if I would really count that.
I have to get some more ammo and come back to fight.
Oh, I'll blow up.
I got a four core quad core.
Four cores.
Oh, that was interesting, I guess, what I just did.
The spin fuser.
Are you still carrying the flag, MLC?
Yeah, this guy just walked right,
he just like flew right by you.
He's like, eh, whatever.
I'm gonna, I'm gonna chase you.
Actually, I'm gonna come back to you.
Are you all right?
Are you dead or what are you doing still?
Just floating around the map.
Yeah, I've, probably my fourth map around the map.
Oh, you gotta do, oh, you got people on you now.
Oh, did they finally figure out how this game was played?
If I could not be such a slog, I would come over there.
Sorry, they're not gonna be able to catch me.
Juggernaut, why do you forsake me?
Oh, you're a juggernaut?
No wonder you can't keep up.
I'm pretty much like in molasses right now.
No, he's dead.
Oh, they're trying to snipe me.
Yeah, they got a couple of snipers, actually, to be honest.
All right, let's get some effing speed here.
Whoa, we're alive.
Oh, look at that slug.
Ah, I missed him.
I can't even go chase him either.
I'm like the heavy weapons guy.
No, that's your character in Sword War.
No, that's right.
Oh, I finally died.
Oh, am I actually gonna move more
than like two miles per hour now?
Oh, somebody else picked up the flag.
Oh, great, I'm going in the opposite direction
that everybody is.
All right, that's enough.
I'm changing the pathfinder.
Time to commit suicide.
That didn't even kill me.
Oh, what's that?
It's a big bouncing blue-green ball.
Oh, Burger Boy, is that you in the flying?
No, that's the quay.
Oh, so beautiful.
I'm going this way.
MLG Grandpa is on an off season right now.
He'll be back in probably a couple weeks, I'm assuming.
I'm gonna go help protect the flag carrier.
Woo-hoo!
Hey, if you hit one of those water guys
who's when they're going off,
it'll actually give you like a ton of air.
Really?
Yeah, I just got going.
I don't know if you see them,
they're going off on the mountains.
The best two maps are this one
and the one we're gonna play next.
And the worst one's that lava one
that we just got done playing.
That's my opinion.
I like the castle on the best.
What did you, what just hit me?
That guy just got a, ugh, that's on top.
Yeah, sweet, sweet grenade bliss.
Germo, you have 10,000 credits.
Use your super duper.
Okay.
How do you use that thing?
Three, four, five.
Yeah, three, four, five.
I'm just gonna shoot it randomly over here.
Let's see if I end the game.
I don't even, how big is the orbital strike?
Oh, yeah.
I think I ended it with my strike.
Orbital strike's huge.
Yeah, it's huge.
When I use it, I got like four or five kills of them.
Hey, 31 fly tailed medals.
Sick.
Simpsons 999, yes, italics is on that server.
Yeah.
Oh, all right though, I think that's,
that's gonna be it for the stream.
First place, second place, third place, fifth place.
Cool.
That's pretty legit.
Yeah, it's almost too legit, I'm gonna say.
Almost.
Yeah, sorry, Ari, if you didn't get it in time.
Sorry, I didn't get it in time, Ari.
Let's do it for next time.
Yeah, I know, I'm getting it for next time.
Yeah, thanks everybody for coming, appreciate it.
Are you gonna play QWOP to end the stream by yourself?
To end the stream by myself, I am.
I'm probably gonna go get some butter toast
because I just woke up and it's like 5 p.m.
All right, well, for bandwidth purposes,
I'm gonna just end the call.
No, I'm gonna end the call because I'm the host.
All right, well, thanks for coming to the stream, guys.
All right, see you next time.
Take care.
That is.
All right, let's play a little QWOP.
If you missed it, I'm gonna upload this whole thing
to YouTube, by the way.
So the whole thing will be on YouTube
if you missed the beginning.
Make sure this is even lined up.
Oh, what's this big annoying ad over here?
Oh my God, I'm refreshing this.
That's gonna give me a seizure.
Here we go, let's do it.
All right, I'm gonna really take my time with this.
See if I can get into slug mode again.
Yeah, thank you if you guys are taking off.
Thank you so much for coming.
If you missed the beginning of the stream,
it's gonna be on YouTube in the next probably couple hours.
Whenever YouTube decides to process it,
who knows how long that's gonna take.
But yeah, it's ended on this one last one.
Come on, now I'm going backwards.
Going backwards, that's not what I wanna do.
Uh, uh, dang.
If I get 10 meters, I'll be happy.
That's all I care about.
Oh yeah, I feel like I'm doing a dance move.
Like stick your left leg out, pull your left leg down.
That's gonna be the, oh my God.
I can't go forward.
My right leg is always the leg that I can never use.
I don't know why.
It just always ends up like that.
And that's when we fall backwards.
Ah, but yeah, thank you so much guys.
I'm gonna end it with that.
I am tired.
But yeah, I'll catch you guys later.
Thanks again for coming.
This will be on YouTube again, like I said.
So peace guys.
Oh, I'm getting some acid reflux.
But yeah, peace guys.
Thank you so much for coming.
Take care guys.
Bye.