First thing I say when I look over here is,
Jeremiah, I'm so disappointed in you. Why? I didn't even have a chance to turn in my homework.
I just, okay, it was Saturday and Sunday went by. You were running school. You're the teacher.
I come into class. It's been, it's Saturday and Sunday. It's Monday morning at school.
I have my backpack. I've got my textbooks. I sit down in the seat at Math 103.
Teacher looks at me and goes, Jeremiah, I'm incredibly disappointed with you.
I didn't even have a chance to do anything. I just sat down. I was ready to learn.
30 months up. That's a long time. God damn, you guys are fast.
This is not going to be relaxing. Yes, it is. Imagine not being in Math 104 in 2019.
Back seating stream? No, it's not. I know what I'm doing in Picross.
By the way, sorry to disappoint all 10,000 of you that just came to the stream right now.
But today we're going to play Picross with Chad. This was a democracy. It was voted on.
I didn't pick this. I mean, I put, I made it available.
This was a pre-stream vote that came down to it.
And we're going to hang out and just relax. Everyone's going to be calm and collected.
We're going to do some Picross puzzles. We're going to hang out.
We're going to have, you know, resident sleeper waiting room for Sims 4 mods tomorrow.
I'm sure I'll see that a thousand times because that's what's happening tomorrow.
No, this is going to be fun. Look, I've had, the VR has been so intense
that I got to shut off for a little while. So I'm going to play Picross,
this Twitch integration. Are you really playing? Oh yeah, that's tomorrow.
There's a first-person mod for the Sims 4 that I want to try.
There's also a couple of other things that I have not enabled,
but I need to play first-person Sims. He's never going to play Seaman. Yes, I will.
Can you please beat the Abyss Watchers in Sims 4?
We don't talk about that stream. We, we bury that.
God, that's the most fucked up I've ever been.
That's the most, I was just like mentally fucking all over the place for that stream.
Puzzle streams will never be relaxing. Just you wait.
So I don't know what time it is where you are. I don't know what you're doing right now,
but you made it here. I'm going to take that opportunity to fill in squares on a grid.
I will explain it. I will tell you step-by-step instructions.
So like get in bed with your iPhone or your iPad, scrunch your neck down and your chin into
your chest, lying on your back because that's fucking impossible. Can somebody please invent
something to watch TV in bed? And I'm not talking about one of those giant pillows you put with the
chair pillows. Why is there no device that attaches to your neck, like locks around your
neck like a collar and mechanically like lifts your fucking head up and there's like pulls it
up like out of its socket almost. And then there's a crane arm that has your iPhone or
your iPad attached to it up around like almost like a desk lamp in front of your face.
Hi, nobody's made that yet. You're yelling. This is supposed to be real. I'm sorry.
I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. We're supposed to be chill. I don't know. Okay. Let me,
I'm going to give you, I'm going to give you a real reality of something that happened today.
Okay. I don't know why I did this, but this is real. This is not a joke.
Picross stream. I drank a 12 ounce of Red Bull before this stream and I don't fucking drink
that shit. I don't know why I decided to do that today. Forget about all the intent shit
that all the VR streams. No, today is the day that I decide to drink a fucking Red Bull.
That's not how you relax. It has, okay, it had Pac-Man on it. That's why I was like,
I have to drink this. I'm already like fucking, my hands are moving and stuff.
I'm going to have to relax. I don't know why I did that. I don't know why, but I have no reason.
I just want to make sure everyone's very clear before I get started here.
Some of you might be expecting this. This is probably a joke. Oh, and that's like a funny
bit. Like what are we actually doing today? No, this is what we're doing today. I just
want to make that clear. I need that. I have to make that clear. There it is. You can tell
by the Super Mario blocks. Is there audio here? And again, I'm going to, I'm telling you,
I'm going to go, shit, what did I just do? No, everybody relax. You know, don't make me do it.
I'll do it. We talked about it in the pre-stream chat. I'll do it. You guys that were here
before the stream started, you know what I'm talking about. I don't, don't test me here.
I'll put on four and a half hour slow mode. So you only get one message for the whole
stream. Yeah, I'm going to force you to relax. Two messages. Ah, that's right. That's right.
I'm automatically putting a limit here of a four and a half hour stream. I know nobody said that.
We're doing nobody photos for this. I had an extreme elimination, pre-stream elimination
tournament. So let's, let's do it. Everybody just chill out. Welcome to the stream. And
if you're like, fuck this guy, see you tomorrow. That's fine. I'll see you tomorrow
for the Sims 4 mods. But no, I bet you this is, you know what, you know, I bet you this is going
to be one of my most viewed streams this year. Anyone want to raise their hand and take that
fucking auction? Cause I kind of don't. Anyways, so here we go. By the way, there is Twitch
integration and I don't know how it works yet. Let's see. Does it work? Big Bits just came
in right now from Great Canadian Fuck Club. Thank you Great Canadian for the $50. Appreciate
it. No, you can't. Don't get out of bed. Stay in bed. I'm getting a little heated right now.
I'm supposed to be relaxing. Great Canadian. Thank you so much. I'm not going to bed and you
can't make me dad. This Twitch integration. I don't know how it works. I think you can do
like exclamation point. Oh, I got to, but let's get through the tutorial. Let me explain
how this works. Okay. I don't need to read any of this shit down here. Cause I can tell you
how it works, but great Canadian. Thank you so much for the $50. All right. Relax everybody.
It's not cues. Ready? Let me explain how this works. As you said that I got out of my bed.
All right. That's enough. All right. All right. All right. Everything relax.
How this I see the chat and I can't even fucking relax. It's hard to relax with this.
Like a bunch of fucking noises over here. Okay. So pick Ross guys, this is how this works.
You get a grid. It could be five by five. It could be 10 by 10 and people are,
this is Twitch integration right here. How'd you guys figure, how'd you guys do that?
Is this you guys down here? Why is it only two people? Yeah. You guys don't think I got a
secure password. That's fucking 86 characters long. Good luck. All right. Here you go. Here
are your chat commands. I guess I can see them down there. Maybe you can check the commands.
Maybe. Oh Jesus. Oh no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. This is not a good,
this is not relaxing. This is spam. This is spam. This is not relaxing at all.
Anyways, let me, I'm not going to turn that off. All right. Don't before, no,
goodbye. All of you. Don't stop. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. Stop with the
integration shit. It doesn't mean anything yet. Let me tell you how to play the game.
Okay. So you got a grid. It's a five by five grid.
Okay. You have a five by five grid. Stop it. Okay. I'm turning it off. No,
not six hour slow mode. Do it. Don't do it yet. Don't do it yet. I'm kidding.
So how you, you got a grid. There's numbers as you see on the top and on the left,
you know, this is for you guys, not for me. So the grid,
I can't relax. I can't do this. I'm such a fucked up person. I'm never going to be
able to do this stream. You understand? It's like, I'm fucking tied down in a chair right
now and I'm like turning into the Hulk and I just want to explode out of the chair.
All right. We're good. So what you have to do, what you have to do is like, no, no, no,
no, no. That's not right. Okay. I need to relax. So the numbers corresponding on the,
I have to close the chat. I have to, I minimize the chat right now. I can't see
what you guys are saying. I would be so bad under pressure. I could never work for the CIA.
Okay. If I was working for the CIA and they had to like get me to say something or do something
or I was going to crack this, put up a fucking Twitch chat next to my face, ask me questions,
and then watch like the fail fishes and LULs that I see out of the corner of my eye.
I wouldn't be able to do it. I'd crack in a second. You could like rip my fingernails off
and I would be like, I'll never tell. I'll never talk motherfucker. You put like a
Twitch chat into the left of my eyes and they're doing LULs. I'll be like, okay, so,
okay. So, uh, are they laughing at me or, uh, okay. So, uh, the base is about at coordinates
four 95, but anyways, so you get a grid here. There are numbers at the top, numbers at the
left. You fill in squares. See how I'm doing this? Not that one. Not that one.
The numbers on the top and the left, this is how many squares you need to fill in,
in this column here. Same thing on this side. So there are five
squares that need to be filled in here and there's only five spaces. So deducing with
deduction technology, we've deduced that all five squares need to be filled in.
Take a look over here on the left. Only one square on this row needs to be filled in. And
guess what? It was filled in by us doing this five. We've logically deduced
that this is the only one. So therefore it is now grayed out. Take a look at over here.
This says zero. As you are well aware, zero means none. So there are no squares to fill in here.
Got it? So therefore there are three that need to be filled in here. There's one here already.
So guess what? One, two, three. That's where it goes. Notice how now we have our three.
We've deducted with our technological brains. Same thing here. See one and one. You're
probably asking, what the heck's going on with the two ones? Well, just relax. I'll tell
you. This means that there is a space of at least one square between these two numbers. So
as you see, we have one here. So this is one of the ones. It's probably the second one,
considering that this is already filled in. No more squares are allowed to be here.
So our one space one, there has to be at least one empty space. Same thing with this
one. So you got one, one solved our first puzzle. Now I can bring the chat back up so you know,
and that's F for the string, right? Everyone's going to like say F like rip string.
Okay. So now we can bring the chat back. First thing I see is this is shit. Will you relax?
So now that you know how this works, let me show you how a master does it.
You didn't, did you even get to blink? That's a coffee cup. This game is called
PictoPix. You get the relaxing music. They get hard. They're not easy. I'll let you guys do one
in a minute. Don't worry. When do we get to start relaxing? You can right now. So remember,
we've got five here, five, five again. Just imagine you're at like a lounge. So here's
another thing. You can actually stop yourself from accidentally filling in squares. So see how
we're done here. I'm going to put some X's to make sure that I don't accidentally. Oh wait,
hold on a second. So I don't click down here. This is stressing me out. This shouldn't be
stressing you out at all. This should be relaxing. We had five community cubs just come in
from Fitty. Thank you, Fitty for the five community subs. It's not stressful. This
game was fun when I was in kindergarten. You didn't play this in kindergarten. I can
guarantee it. I 100% guarantee you did not play this in kindergarten. You weren't smart enough
for it. Look, that's like a, that's a fucking like Legend of Zelda sword. See, now we have
some more spaces. It's getting more complicated. $100 just came in. Where? What are you talking
about? I'm not going to do this yet. You guys need to understand how the game is played
and I'm getting a vibe that you don't. It was $125 in gifted subs. Five tier. Wait,
those were tier three subs? Oh shit. I, okay. Those are, why would you give, why would you
give some tier three subs? Oh my God. Fitty gave five tier three subs. That's a shit
load of money. Well, congratulations to the people that got the tier three sub.
We know how to play idiot. That guy's not relaxing on what I'm permanently been.
Uh, thank you. That's fucking hot. Like what? Hundreds of dollars or something. 100 and like
50, 200. How much money is that? Is this on steam? It is on steam. I think it's like,
they might be packs you have to buy. I'm making that up. I don't know, but it's like
seven bucks. You can also get these for free online, but this one had the Twitch
integration. So I was like, you know what, why don't I like ignore everybody down here
that's pressing buttons and you know, give it a try. So as you see, we've got the five
filled in here and we have our one. Now remember, I want you all to remember
you're not remembering. Excuse me. Listen, there has to be a space here.
I'm not relaxed. See three, one, this is the one. So therefore there has to be at least
one space between all of these. I'm trying. I know. I, I, I'm sorry. And look, take a
look here. What do you got? What's that? Zero five. There's only three spaces left.
So fill it in. Same thing with this one. Only three spaces left. Same with this one.
Only three spaces left. The one, one, one up here is already done. See one three,
but, but Jerma, I don't get it. If there's one and three, I see one, two, three. I don't
get it. No, no, no, no. Relax. This is one. There's your space. There it is. Therefore,
deduce with your brains. One, two, three. That has to be three in a row.
Bingo. Same thing over here. Right. What's the deal with this one? Can you guys help?
Can I get some help on this one? This one is the reverse of the other one. Take
a look at that. Has to be three space one. There it is. That's how many followers and subs I'm
going to lose a minute on this stream. You just didn't know. Do it yourself. Stupid. Sure.
I think a friend of mine has this tattooed on their chest and they think it means strength
in Chinese. I swear to God, that's not, I'm not making that up. It's not me. I don't
have any tattoos. What are you talking about? All right. Let's see. We got, let's use our
minds here. So, lock in. I'm not going to click these yet. Not until we get harder.
I'm going to have a panic attack. Well, relax because here comes a quick one.
We got, okay. So, nothing here. We got all one there. See? Same thing over here. Same thing here.
So, guess what? Has to be bingo. Bingo. That takes up the two. You got three. It's done.
Mind sweeper. This is not mind sweeper. Did it too slow. Who is this guy? My name is
Jerma. If you are a puzzle enthusiast, you may have found this stream because you're
like a puzzle enthusiast. I am too. And what we like to do in this stream is we check out
new puzzle games and we try new mind kind of brain training games. I do, I stream seven days
a week and I stream 10 hours a day and we do, we, I check out new mind brain training
exercises every day. Zero, right? Take a look. There's you four. Only can be four.
Now, wait a minute here. This is where it gets tricky because look at this.
Okay. So, how are we supposed to know what the heck's going on here? I'll tell you how
because see, there's a space here. It can't be here. It can't be here. This is the one.
So, there has to be a space. Two, you got it filled in. Guess what? The two is down here.
Has to be right there. And then your three spot is there. Your two spot is over here.
It's a baby. Yep. You must have been a cool substitute teacher. Nobody gets it. What
do you mean nobody gets it? No, there's no way. How do you not get it? You don't get it. Okay.
Like, I'll try it again. Let's, let's, let's, shh, relax. Some people don't get it. Ignores
the nice comment. Was there a nice comment? The nice comment was, was it the bits that just
came in? C4G, two, thanks for the 250. Canceled my last bits. I changed my mind
on the pit cross hype. That wasn't a nice message. I've never been less relaxed. Just
lean back in your chair. Go make popcorn or something. When was the last time you had
popcorn? Probably been a long time. No, I'm supposed to, I'm supposed to explain this to
people. Listen. Okay. Here you go. For those of you that have no idea what's going on,
welcome to the stream. My name is Jerma. I do puzzle games. I stream seven days a week,
10 hours a day. I've been at this for about 10 years now. I have my own puzzle
games that I make too. And they involve, you know, mind teasers, brain teasers,
and little twisties inside your head there. But for, what was that? I was like,
explain this. Okay. So, all right. Um, how do you, uh, okay. I got, I have to get the CIA
chat thing out of my way for a second. Okay. Good. All the material. I'd hit the fast forward
on this part. No, you wouldn't. You would sit here and watch it. All right. Listen, relax.
So pit cross is a game where this is a lie that people are trolling me. They know how
this works, but I'm going to do it again, just because a shitload of people did show up
after I started talking about it. Y'all fast forward, huh? Fast forward, fast forward,
fast forward. Interesting. Okay. You want to fast forward? So what you are going to do
is when you take, I'm not really sure how to explain this, but you see all this channel,
we are a puzzle enthusiast stream. And as you, is the voice changer working? No. Hold on. It's
not. Oh God. So what we do on this stream is we are a puzzle enthusiast. As you see here,
the five is five, one, two, three, four, five in a row. What you do is you pull it,
each consecutive circle until the whole thing is filled. As you see there. Did I tell you
guys the funny thing that happened to me yesterday at the drive-through? Wow. You're going to laugh
so hard at me. So I'm in the drive-through and someone behind me decided to beep. I got out of
the car and got hit in the face with an ice cream. And after, do you guys understand this?
I think I'm going to have to re-explain it. So as you see here. Yeah. How's that? Can you hear
me? Can you guys hear me? Fucking relax. So, but really though, sadly, yes, you take that
back right now or I'm going to anti-relax. I love how people are still doing this. I wish you were
mute. You don't actually wish that. Don't say something like that. You know, that hurts my
feelings when you say that. Think about it. You're talking to the streamer. Okay. I wish
the streamer was muted. Okay. You understand? Okay. Get a life. It's Minecraft cheese. Now,
you guys want to play? You guys want to play? Let's see if you've learned anything. Okay.
Good luck. Let's see if you've learned a damn thing. Let's see. Okay. Good. Good. But no,
no, no, no, no, no, no. That's not good. You didn't do that right. You didn't deduce that
correctly. That's not correct. How would you know that this was here? One and one. All you
know is that one is in this row and one's in this column. You can't deduce that logically
here. Okay. Somebody gets it. Thankfully. Think about it here. What is absolutely,
completely yes. Okay. Something that you 100% know to be true. Three. Therefore,
you have to have a space. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I mean, that's true, but you had,
you had, oh no, that's right. Nevermind. I'll move back. What the hell was that? Why did
I just like spam a shitload of stuff? I just dumped like, why am I dumping shit in chat here?
I'm spamming the stream right now. Did you guys remove something? Yes. Very good.
Because see, notice how you got this one right. This one could not have been possible.
It's been doing that the whole stream.
Careful here, guys. I don't think so about that. Think about this. Okay. The chat hurts
my eyes. You did a pretty good job. You deduced it pretty well. Nice work. You made
an anchor. Okay. Now it's my turn. Yes. These are still fairly simple. No, no, no, no. Auto play.
All right. So here we go. I'll show you one too. So let's take a look here. Remember,
you might be saying, oh boy, how am I going to do this? You're probably like
gnawing at your fingernails. They're just breaking off like cartoon, like
Rocco's modern life, just fucking flying everywhere when you move your
corn on the cobbing, your fingernails. Listen, relax. How you deduced this
is take a look. You got one, one, one, right? But I don't, I don't know. Just wait a minute.
Hold on. One space, one space, one. It fills in the whole entire. Now you do this.
If you, later on, it's going to be like 10, eight, 12, 15, four. They get huge. Count
these numbers here. One, two, three, right? How many spaces are in between here? At least
one, at least two. Therefore one, two, three, four, five. It has to fill the whole row.
We get it. No, you don't. At least 200 people have DMed me on Twitter and they're just like,
Jerma, I don't understand. Can you explain that the spaces thing again? I'm like,
I'm trying to help you. Two space, two. So now we have this completely deduced.
You can fill these in. We don't know exactly where these are, but we do because take a look
here. Two, two, two, two. It's as simple as that. Three, because it's got to be in the middle and
there you go. Bingo, bingo. This is second grade shit. We're warming up. Mom said it's my turn
on the pick, Ross. No, you're going to have to wait. One, three. Uh-huh. You got your three
here. You got your one, two. Can we stop the stream until everyone understands? No, we cannot.
Can we stop the stream until everyone? How am I supposed to decide if that's happening or not?
Can we stop the stream? No. Play binaural beats? No, you guys, you guys want to,
if you don't, if people don't start relaxing here, I'm going to play a like a 17 hertz
sound effect on, on YouTube. That's like the fear scary sound that makes you like,
like feel horrible. I will put that on full blast. All right. There you go. We got our
middle here. So we got two in here. We got one and one. So remember it can't be over on one
of these sides. And obviously these, the three has to be one, two, three, one, two, three,
has to be in the middle here. Play binaural beats. I'm not going to play binaural beats.
Why would I play binaural beats? It's going to hurt my head. I can't do binaural. Fine.
I'll try it. Not yet. In a minute. You need to relax. People are going to leave
because of that shit. That's like painful. Okay. So, uh, no, I fucked that whole thing up.
It has to be three here. It's probably this. Fuck. This is easy. You guys are in my head.
I can do like 20 by 20 and I'm like fucked up now. I sit in bed and play this like three
nights a week at like 30 by 30 grid. I can say things that I can't prove too. Just wait.
I like, I got lost. This is so easy. No, it can't be that. Why am I? I did like a 30 by 30
last night in preparation. He's pretending for views. I don't, I can't, I cannot believe that
I can't do this. I can't relax. I can't do it. I seriously like, I don't know what it is.
I'll do the next one. I'll do the next 10 in 30 seconds each. I guarantee it. I fucking 100%
guarantee it. Like I, I don't know what happened. I got stuck in like a, I got stuck in like a
fucking tunnel and like traffic at work. My brain ran into itself like a thousand times
because I had, I'm trying to just watch. Ready? Bingo. Say like, I don't know what the fuck
happened. I don't know what happened. I was pretending for views. Just pretend. Pretend I
was pretending for views. Honest to God, pretend I was just pretending. Derm of 12 D
chest. Yeah. I was pretending for views. I was trying to get some like views in here.
20 seconds left. I'm telling you, I'm fine. So let's see the down or up. It's down here.
Kind of has to be. And then one, one, it could be one, one. I know one, one. It's no, there
it is. So then here's your two, one. It can't be down there. You got two, one. And there's
your two, one. Lame stream guy acts like he's bad. It's so obvious that he's acting and his
fans still can't tell. Stop it. Now we get real. Okay. Forget about all the dumb shit
that just happened. I need to relax. I need to go drink another Red Bull and calm down.
There you see the Maka S. That's fine. We know we got zeros over here.
This like fucking 1900s piano music I have to get rid of. No, no, not that. Just relax.
All right. So we got nine here. And those of you that are wondering, wait a minute,
this is a 10 by 10 grid. What the heck's going on here? Well, it's very simple. You just fill in
the ones that you know are certain, right? So for instance, this is zero. This is also zero,
making it a smaller, smaller area. So we know we only have to work in here.
Guess what? This has to be filled in here. Has to be. Because think about it, right?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine. One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine. These have to be filled in. I don't know if it's here yet or I don't know
if it's here yet, but we're going to try to deduce that. Anyways, we've got one, one.
Those of you that know, we've got the spaces here so we can mark and make sure we know that
we don't have to touch these because there has to be a space either here or here.
This is done. And so is this one. Pretty cool shit. You know what I mean?
So take a look here. Guess what? Four, one, two, three. Doesn't work there,
but guess what works here? One, two, three, four. Oh, I see. It's a penis. It's not a penis.
If it is, I will, if this is a penis, I will give a thousand community subs to myself,
but it has to say penis, like penis. A thousand community subs. I'm hoping there's
not something like developer troll in here because that would be bad. Anyways, so we've
got three this way, two already filled in, four this way as well. So two, we can't figure this
out yet. Four, one, two, three, four, one, two, three, four could be in either one of these
spaces, but it's not because look here, see two, that doesn't work because it has to be,
has to be here because that's impossible for it to be anywhere else. Four now is absolutely
has to be down there. Got the three already done now. Let's take a look at that. Four
has to be two in a row. So it could be either here. It's not here because there's the three
and then look at this perfectly lined up. Don't you just love that fucking satisfying,
hyper satisfying one, two, it's all it could be. No, it's not. Yes, it is. Wait, what? This,
this has to be here. Oh, fuck. It's not satisfying. What did we go wrong? What did I,
hold on. What did I go wrong? This has to be there. Oh, okay. Okay. No, I got it. No,
no, no, no. It's just so, it's hyper satisfying when you get it. Now we've got two.
So this is filled in. So there's your two and nine has to be there. No, nine has to be here.
Imagine being this smart. Imagine never being able to speak in my channel ever again,
as of right now mods, you know what to do. Power, power, power, power, power, power.
All right. I almost just passed out. Relax. Play mind show. No, I'm taking a VR break.
I didn't even tell you the story of what happened when I got done with VR. Did I
tell you this? What happened here? You know, the reason why I'm not doing VR
is because my skin was peeling off. Last night, the skin on my forehead, if I rubbed
gently, skin was coming off of my forehead. I have to stop playing VR for a little while.
That's normal. Yeah. Is it though? I don't think so. It's laying eggs in my head. Skin peeling off
my forehead. Yeah. The valve is laying fucking half, half eggs in my head. All right, let's go.
So we got some two, two, one. Let's see. Two space, one space. Okay. So the two definitely
has to be here because it's impossible to be here. So the two has to be there. Moisturize
more and clean your headset. I clean my headset every time. You know how much I clean
that headset every single time. All right, so it has to be one here somewhere. One, two, three,
four. One, two, three, four. So it has to be here. All right, in the middle there.
Don't know if it's up or down. We got a two and a two. We got a one.
Didn't he say, didn't he moisturize? I moisturize every day. If you don't moisturize
every day, you got, I mean, you kind of have some issues there. You have to moisturize.
All right, I deduced it had to be here because there's no way you can do four down
here. So there's your two. The whole bottom is done. So we got two here though. Do we get to play
it? You guys can do the next one. All right, we got two, maybe this way. There's also one,
one and two are here. So two has to be one, two space, one. I want to play. You can play
a minute. One, two, three, four. One, two, three, four. So we got one, two, three, four.
One, two, three, four. Okay, there's your one and your one. There's your two. So that leaves
us with a one and with them. That's not right. Not right. Not right. How do I undo? Why are you
guys doing question marks? Now I can see because it's one, two, three, four. One, two, three,
four. It has to be these two. The four has to be in these two spots. It has to be.
It's impossible for it not to be. And that's one space, two, two. This is correct.
So then maybe this is wrong. Oh, let me just see what it looks like here.
Four. No, that's correct. It has to be there. So then, yeah, this has to be over this way.
There's no way. Yeah, that's correct. What did I... I fucked up something somehow.
Yeah, that has to be. Ah, shit. Where the fuck is this then? How do I fuck that up?
So maybe it has to be here. But then what the fuck happens here? No, I'll go back a little
bit. I fucked it up somewhere in the very beginning. This is... How do I restart it?
Let me just restart it. Yeah, restart it. Restart it. I need to look at it again.
Because, yeah, I don't know what the hell I screwed up in the beginning here.
Okay. So, yeah, one, two, three, four. One, two, three, four. Okay. There's your two and
your two. Okay, that's what I fucked up. That's what fucked up in the beginning. You're
doing a bad job, not gonna lie. Sorry, you can be banned for life too. So one, two, one,
two, three, four. One, two, three, four. Has to be here. One, two, three, four. One, two, three,
four. One, two, three, four. So then two can go either way. Can I be banned too?
Depends. Is there anything that you'd like to say about how stupid I am?
Huh? Anything else you'd like to say? Anything else you want to add?
You're doing a great job, not gonna lie. Thank you. Now the one thing about Picross that's
if you mess up one tile, it throws your whole brain off. That's why I'm trying to... Once you
like see it, you're like, oh fuck, okay, now I get it. It has to be in here somewhere.
So this was one. If one was here, then it has to be here. Because what are you gonna do?
One and then two? No, that doesn't work. Has to be right there. Now the one on the other hand,
I don't know. Same thing with this one. This is one, two, two. So it could be two. Yeah,
has to be that. Or it could be here. Only knows that one's down here and that's it for this.
So this is where I fucked up last time. This is correct. Because this is the only way this
can work. You know why? It's because I think for some reason this was the same thing.
I thought it was one, one, two, one, one, two. That's what happened last time. What's with all
the question marks? Why? What did I do? I'm getting like a shitload of question marks.
Okay, so two, two has to be two, two. There can't be anything else.
That leaves us with one, one, two. This is done. No, it's not. Shit. What am I doing
wrong here? It can't be anything else. One, one, two, one, two, one. It's not that. Am I
actually reading this wrong? How? One, one, two, one, two, two. These two are right. They're
absolutely correct. So this has to be filled in like this then because this is the only
place I can be. I fucked it all up somehow. Okay, there we go. There's the other two
and there's the four. All right. It was it's a question. That's why everybody's doing question
mark. That's why you're doing that. Now I understand. Oh my god. Oh my god. That's why
everyone was doing that. Oh, oh, rely. Oh, I thought everyone was being just mean
and being like question mark. Holy shit. Is he this dumb? Just wait.
Seven, two, there are seven, eight, nine, ten. So it's going to be one, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, space two. Same deal right here. Let's see five, six, seven, eight,
nine. Not quite enough, but we got one, two, three, four, five, six. Same thing right here.
Okay, cool. That leads us to here. So these are done. Two, that's done. And two is done.
I think we pretty much already figured this whole thing out because three has to be
right here. Five is one, two three, four, five. This whole top section is done. Two and then two,
look at where it has to be. Take a look. That's done. Four has to be right here. One,
two, three, four, five. One, one, one one three. It's a key. It's a penis key.
turn off hints you're embarrassing yourself what hints turn off hints oh
yeah no I don't need that that's okay I don't need those to be on I haven't I
have not even been using those one two three zero I haven't been I didn't
even know that was on I used to do the shit in the papers mom said it's
your turn to play mom can see HM anyone know what that means oh I love when it
happens when this happens shut her mouth I said s HM I love when this happens
ready listen see HM he's pretending for views he's pretending for views I love
when people say that shit because like I can I could be like yeah I mean
whatever you know I'm trying to like come on all right five this is this is
amazing when this happens for those of you know pick Ross enthusiast when you
get a full row every one of these numbers has to start from here all of
them so one two three four five done one block it one block it one block
it one block it one block it one block it five done see HM stop torture
I'm having a good time I tell you this is gonna be my most viewed stream of
the last two years there's only 3600 people here I'm talking vaude too
this is gonna have 40,000 views on the Vaude okay so we get seven here so
this is one two three four five six seven easy enough then that completes
this one two one up here and close both of these down then we have to
two two close this down pretty cool close this one down as well and we got
one two three four five six nice this one is done too leave this with four we
can only go this way and we can only go this way and it is a it's a like
exit the game it is exit all right you guys want to play one you want me
you want to play one all right I'm gonna let you guys play you can have
turn go on turn off slow mode so we can play uh yeah just kill slow mode for
the for the purpose of this no hey yeah what's going on here you guys already
this is zero row here this is zero column what you guys doing it has to
be a space one space one and you've already got a zero here you guys have
got to do some undoing shut up boomer let us handle it I'm trying I love
watching I love being able to watch and see now I get to be the person that
says yeah yeah yeah the first thing you got you got to clear all the zeros
guys oh my god they don't know they don't know it's a penis it's not
I can assure you wait why is that there that's a flora no that's
cheating it shouldn't be there yeah huh I mean how do you know that's
there you don't have any way to know that and let's have more one two
three four five one two three four five okay I see where you're going with this
one I wouldn't have started there but that's okay this is gonna take you
guys ages you're gonna just fill in this isn't this was so easy this was
a really easy one I should have given you guys the last one two times ago
turn the counter down I don't think I can even I don't think I can you
look at how easy this one with it's just one one one one okay that's the
correct that's the correct place to do that before going with the uh with the
sex I confused all this works I'll explain it for you so what you have
here is a series of numbers okay for instance one one one one one what are
you guys doing yeah good job deducing this one how is that how you gonna
figure that out why is he so mean no I'm giving you the chat experience
you're you get to be the streamer now okay now excuse me I'll take care of
this for you so you guys don't have to do that I'll take care of that I can't
remove these which ones with it was okay those those ones good luck I just
like pushed you out of the way and was like god damn it filled it in
for you this is our project in the waiting room Sims 4 mod waiting room
they are this is take forever all right you guys did a good job
congratulations you did fantastic you made a piece of paper that you put into
a piano so it auto plays the song good don't talk all right I won't touch it
and this is what it's like to watch this stream no I go faster than this
even though I make mistakes no it's not I go faster than this I don't go
glasses one see what it is the minecraft one two three four five
minecraft creepers all right my turn smoke the herb no you guys did a good
job nice job seriously good work you guys deserve the win you do so it's
got to be in the middle here cool let's see what we got three and then
two mm-hmm so three again then there's two and two no there's just one two
okay this is two two two this four and a half there's nothing else has to be
there there's your other two and is your last two sick so slow relax relax
calm down you guys are breathing on my neck one two three four five six
one two three four five six one two three four five six one two three four
five six okay there's two two one two two one it's just one there we also have
two and then two it has no yeah it does because that's done they both done
two and then two two and two and that should be three and then two two
and then two one two three four five this is two and this is two and this is
one two three four five and then that's two and then that's two is a blue of
green crab alien don't clap on camera I'm not on camera I'm on audio now
they're throwing in three numbers you ever wish you were playing a
different game I'm just curious if we have the same wishes you mean like
for right now I want to be playing this I'm liking this I'm having this is I
think this is a fun stream I'm having a good time I'm having a good time right
I just have a good time we aren't this you are I have analytics that
tell me so much data is coming through on my dashboard right now I have
an 88% approval rating on this stream and I have analytics that say that so
you can like type and troll in the chat oh this sucks I got like your
approval rating here on my dashboard alright so we got that done three block
it up two three block it up there's a seven one two three four five six seven
block it up one two three four five six seven block it up three block it
up two this is two here block it up two block it up two and then one two
three four five six seven get it locked down three block it up and then I'm not
sure here so then we got two has to be right here and that leads us to two and
then four one two three four block it up two block it up that's it for
that one five so that's block that one up one two three four five block it
up and that's it for that too because that's three two no no no no
no no no no no no no no no no no no no stop stop stop stop stop stop don't
touch anything there we go okay three two one seven one thank you two four three
two it's all I know he ruined it I know that's that's it for that two four
that has to be that lock it up two one two three four five six seven got
that good okay this is one two three four five two three done one two three
four look it's you guys it's you guys that's mood I told you I had analytics
it died this is integrated through twitch it pulled that in doesn't think I
dug I don't have the analytics I just proved it to you on string guys
sometimes we just gotta dial it back and I got to play a game like this
but we can just hang out just chill you know not every stream has to be fucking
crazy you know sometimes you just want to hang out with your friends your
best friends by the way 40 people just left right when I said that my
fucking analytics reminding me one two one two three four five six seven
eight one two three four five six seven eight one two three four five
six seven eight one two three four five six seven eight yep yep yep yep has to
be there I'm flying the chat is my friend let's see four five six seven
eight nine ten is it both just are done okay that's already two there lock
it up lock that up to the whole middle row can be locked up actually
and then we already know what this is two two two two two this one was
very easy at least that was can't believe he's still playing this this is
what everybody voted for they were like four options you know like this is
everybody voted for this I'm going by the democratic process of what people
voted for one two three okay one two three and people wanted it just to
hang out chill stream and that's good that leaves just a little bit down
here and let's see one two three four five six seven eight people can make
choices they regret enact emergency powers and change the game no all
right we I voted for this I'm sorry why would you say sorry this is
interesting do a 100 by 100 already do a 50 by 50 this is lame we have to
work our way up I think this is gonna happen but I'm having a good
time I'm having a swell time thank you dear all right yeah that's it I'm
putting on the fucking fear hurts I'm putting on the 17 Hertz fucking scary
thing 17 Hertz fear noise 17 Hertz infrasound for anxiety uneasiness and
extreme sorrow I don't think I want to play this this is gonna skip I
think I guess it gonna cause me a problem I don't want to do this no
it's six hours of this why would you put your headphones on listen to
six hours of that I'm not doing it about binaural beats okay this one is
called super intelligence music improve focus all right I'm gonna put on the
super intelligence music let's get this off okay super intelligence music okay
I got both headphones in play the brown noise and I'm not gonna do that okay
it's working holy shit this works this works I'm not turning it off this
makes me want to puke it's working I can feel it like going into my brain and
telling me how to do things I'm not putting on the brown noise why would
I do that damn holy shit I mean I didn't even do that I didn't do that
give us the brown note no I'm not gonna give you the brown note I'm not
going to do that that's gonna hurt somebody I'm not gonna be responsible
for somebody shitting their pants it's not even real I don't want to shit
my pants make sense because it can't be yep no wait a minute don't know that
yet this game can't do more damage than the brown note brown noise is
anxiety and stress reducing reducing static it's not shit your pants
frequency shut up not a lie oh yeah they call it the brown note the
brown noise it's just releases anxiety why is it called the brown noise it's
good self-parked minute episode on it fucked it up I fucked it up I'm
talking about the brown noise and I fucked the whole thing up has to be
played at 150 decibels yeah you know what that's not the sound doing that
that's the amount of noise force hitting you in the stomach making you
shit your pants it's nothing to do with this it has to do with the
force of the sound coming out hold on a second here three here six versus here
I fucked this whole thing up god damn it I fucked it all up
hopefully I could hit the undo button like a thousand times shit what did I
get wrong here I'm gonna start over damn it well the IQ music works I
just turned over and I was like shitting pooping music poopoo music and
I stopped paying attention three three this maybe this doesn't go here
to be here there's no way it could be over here so then this shit has to go
away because it can't be there no way two three but what the hell I have is
doing fine this is no this is incorrect I scry I have to do it all
over again restart I have to do it again you got it you got to throw the
whole thing in the trash sometimes you just do yeah okay now I'm not
gonna talk about like shitting my pants I'm gonna listen to the binaural sound
intelligence beats all right relax I'm gonna I just did it I know I just
got a key one two three four five six one two three four five six three two
two block it block it block it block it okay this is done now four three
here it's impossible for it to be anywhere else two has to be here
impossible for it to be anywhere else six does not need to be right here one
two three four five six that's all I know three and then three has to be
right here impossible for it to be anywhere else two and then two this is
where it gets tricky can't be down here can't be this has to be right
can't be anywhere else this is not done two and then two has to be right here it
cannot be anywhere else feel the music three has to be here cannot be anywhere
else two three three could be here it's possible this is so exciting I just
shit my pants that's on you one two three four five six where's the joke
there's no joke stop looking at the chat room and get this one done so it cannot
be up here no no no no no never get I get me anywhere else that's three so
one two three four five six got it that's where we screwed up before I had
one two three four five six that's where it went so wrong before okay the
question is three four five six I'm not gonna brute force it one two three
three there's nothing it can't be just down to this last little quadrant here
one two three four five six got it and then two it has to be there which
leads you to two which leads you to clear which leads you to two which
leads you to two which leads you to one anybody getting smarter it's a
chat's getting bored it's okay it's okay it's okay two three four five six seven
I'm not bored I'm really are you sure you're bored and you aren't relaxed
that's a really good question okay I was about to play the brown noise in
the background but I'm actually gonna get in trouble guys if I play the
brown noise and even one of you has like a direct complaint to twitch I
could get in trouble I play like and like three of you get a headache I could
get like suspended I'm not doing that that's not correct one two three four
five six one two three four five six so it's right there block off those
ones I'm gonna report you that's what I'm saying I don't I don't want to
hurt anybody I don't want to cause anybody a fucking like diarrhea headache
that's not relaxing it's right here one two three four five six seven eight one
two three four five six seven eight melt into your bed and if you have the
computer if you have a chair that can recline recline back put the
headphones in and just look at the corner of your eye on the screen you
don't need to see much this is not ASMR my bed is swallowing me yeah
you're gonna like melt into your bed the covers are gonna you're gonna go
down the covers are gonna come fold up over you you know you're gonna sink back
you're gonna lie oh I'm like sinking this is so relaxing and then your
eyes are gonna fucking rip open and you're like buried alive in a casket
you're the fuck out of here just relax you'll feel it I'm gonna send a
complaint no that's not that I that was me making up a funny scenario whatever
one one so it has to be one spay or one spay has been a lot of marks I need
to make hold on you want to speak to my manager sure I'll go get him yeah
you're speaking to him can I help you I got a complaint oh okay and I
get up on top of the fucking counter and I bend over and I do the
Jim Carrey like asshole thing what is your complaint sir where am I here okay
hey I got it yeah my favorite part is if people down here that are like can
you please put it into a three I did I'm not removing those one two three
four so slow I'm going like he's gonna say the same thing like over
and over again that's the joke it's too not it has to be there I knew
it was a joke no it's not though no that works that works one two three
four five same bill over here five and then one two three four we've got two
five and then one two five one these are done very cool everything's done
over here let's see one two three at least it's eight one two three four
five six eight right nice one and then one this is three and then you got one
two five eight I got a couple more to do here which is this one and look at
that remember the good old days of German when he was known for his
Picross streams yeah I'm just going back to where I started a lot of
people think it was team fortress too no if you go back to my channel my
first two to three hundred videos were Picross and tips and strategies and
stuff but before I got any sort of viewers I deleted them all because I
was like I don't think people want to watch this I deleted all of them I was
gonna leave some up but and you were right to delete them his brown nose
video yeah yeah we're I had like 200 Picross videos and like 60 brown
nose videos why would you put the German craft copypasta here we're not
even it's like completely irrelevant it's still there all right I'm gonna
get yelled at for going too slow one two three four five six seven space
one this is all filled in two and then five one two three one two three
don't know that yet that's some good cider maybe I'm gonna maybe I'll go get a
session mom should I just like start drinking no no no no no bad idea
I'm not gonna start drinking if I start drinking I'm gonna have to take like
tomorrow off let me tell you something about being over 35 under 35 by
like a year or two if I drink now if I have like three drinks four drinks
I literally have to take an entire day the next day lying in my bed
screaming it sucks no I like autos got to go to the vet in like two days so
I'm streaming tomorrow I don't have like a hangover tomorrow I don't get
like hangovers really but I do I don't know I'm hydrating right now no
autos fine Otto has to go to the vet for a very very basic routine
procedure he's completely fine don't worry that's that for that row
closing in I love it when you get that shit done and you can just you
smell it one two three four five one two three four five nice can't deduce
where that is though what's with you and shitting tonight it's not me okay
it's you guys that have this issue you guys telling me to play the brown
noise you guys telling me to go like poo my pants and stuff I don't know
what you guys are on tonight but it's not me I'm just reacting to it
because I'm looking over and I'm like what is going on over here it's
cuz you drank a Red Bull I know no it's not I didn't drink anything now he's
flipping us off all right let me finish this so I get five right here good
three it's done my question is one I still don't have this one somehow you
three here let's see one two three four five yeah it's probably these two
because it can't really no I could be any one of these they're all five
this is two five where's that one over here probably yes well how you can what
what's the hashtag guess mmm it could be either one of these because it's
two is one and then two one two three one two well it has to be one of
these so that's this one one two three four five block it off got it so
this has to be two here done therefore that's one two three four five
therefore that has to be like that therefore here's your one there's your
two in theory that makes two as well there's your one which makes that
three which then turns into here it's a grenade I'm gonna get bigger we're
getting close how was my day my day's been pretty good how was your day
that's more important how was your day try just get shit face today and like
we'll stream like in two days sometimes no it's not gonna fit do a poll I'm not
gonna do a poll that's stupid one there's you one there's you one there's
you one there's you one that means so one two look at that oh it's perfect
you see that did you even see what I did I don't think you did you were
paying attention this music sucks I'll do another one then okay how about that
this is super intelligence this is accelerated learning gamma waves for
focus that was from the gamma waves one there's a game okay wait hold on
wait oh wait I'm afraid of this is game wages microwave right what's the
one that's in the microwave microwaves oh right that's right
micro okay you're right this one's safe then he's trying to kill us it's too
loud gamma rays is what turned the Hulk into the Hulk well then you should be
happy and planet you know how much stronger all you guys will be don't get
me suspended you're fine just take like one a Tylenol no no no no no
don't you're fine everyone's fine just take Tylenol don't I don't abuse
Tylenol no no no don't just just relax just drink like some water and have like
a fucking I look some celery all right let's see one five this is one two
three four five that's done block it up one two three four five six seven
block it up is the one let's get shitfaced and abused Tylenol I never
said that do not put that word in my mouth I never I did not say that
absolutely not I have my analytics here on my dashboard it's a
transcript of every word I've said on stream don't four five six seven eight
nine ten so this is one this is free those of you don't see what's going on
here there has to be a space see what I'm talking about there in
between each number this is just barely free all right we got sick one
two three four five six look at that it easy one two three four five there's
the one there's the two and block those off easily let's see here one two
three four five six seven one one one three no no no no no no no hold on a
minute here Jeremy you've got something wrong one one three you got
something wrong here something's wrong no it's correct no it's good it's fun
one two three maybe yeah okay I had it by freaked out for a second there two
one two three no that the two is correct and that's done one two one
we get seven here one two three four five it has to be at least these this
one's done one two three four five six seven done done two three three three
two one two three nothing three here that's done three here one two three
oops oops oops oops oops oops oh check the link what do you mean you
guys want to do one dump truck this one's kind of hard I don't know if
you guys can do this one inspire but what the hell would I click that for
yeah that's not I don't want this song anymore what about like the happy
frequency is there like a happy frequency happiness frequency serotonin
dopamine endorphin release music I feel like we're going to we're doing
like too many drugs at the same time is it bad that we went we did like
the calm one now we're doing the we're doing the upper now this is not
good don't forget your healing oils in your crystals play ten hours of laugh
tracks now let's see how this one is I'm doing you guys want to do one I'll
help you and we'll do it together here what does enable continue what does
that mean enable continue I think if it's you can skip the level now all
right go for it ah shit no no no no no no no that's the first thing I
asked did anybody shit oh he shut up Jeremy get a grip he's doing all right
by the way that I'm just testing your resolve here that was not the brown
nose and I'm seeing everybody being real funny that was test your speakers
low pitch and that had nothing to do with any other like brown noise
frequency then why did I shit my pants that's probably something that you
did you have like a really did you okay here's nothing give you some
possibilities here did you do you did you get like a reheated in the in the
gamma ray microwave burrito from like four days ago that's the only pretty
much possible way did you eat a burrito that you reheated in the
microwave if the answer is yes then that's probably what happened I've
never had a burrito in my life how is that possible you've never had a
burrito in your life I'm not American Wow I'm you're missing out they're
actually really great do you ever get a chance to have one by all means
definitely eat one just don't reheat it eat it fresh gonna still play my show
yes we just had to take a relaxing day today tomorrow we're doing sims 4
mods first person is the main one because I wanted to do that a while
ago and I never did what is stream legends the bottom of the screen
it's just like a little game to play while you're waiting for a stream to
start or just like a little thing to put in there mail that guy a burrito and I
wouldn't be fresh by the time it got there
German please turn this off it's making my dog go crazy I don't know
what's going on really that's kind of scary I'm okay I'm turning it off
I don't want to I'm not playing brown noise I'm gonna play brown
noise for myself to make sure it's safe I'm muted let's find out I don't I
don't like this I don't know it's silent I don't want to do that no that
just freaks me out I just placebo effect I like almost hurt myself no
I'm sorry guys I'm not doing that that was a silent video and I could
feel brain pain nope you could just look it up type in brown noise do
you know the feeling when you first go underwater and your ears you have
that that's what I just felt I was blacked out in five seconds I'm not
putting that on string you guys doing pretty good my favorite part is but
look at okay is this 37 people that are playing out of 3,500 people
watching but I'm glad that though you guys are having fun those 37 people
right now this is like they're fucking filling this in and having a
good time I wasn't explained I wasn't paying attention when you explain
the controls now German stocks are way down too I saw that by low they're
playing against their will their own free will nothing not I could right
now I could just fuck this whole thing up I could click on every button I
could delete everything they did no they're just playing they're having
fun this game is really cool thanks for showing now Picross is a really
really fun relaxing just chill thing to do we've been doing this for two
hours don't you guys feel like we've been here for like ten minutes
we've been here for two hours come on it feels way longer feels like less
than two it feels like way less than two yeah what's the difference between
p-cross in Sudoku Sudoku is nine grids this is a much larger scale and this
is more about making a picture than solving a math problem I don't really
play Sudoku but I think they're yeah they're very different it feels odd
without the music I'll put something else on hold on how about the royalty
free old music like what's what's some old music we can put on it's free old
fashioned free film music no copyright this is the whole line isn't this
just like a popular song what song is this something made this in
garage band I know exactly the file name that they used they used high
trumpet zero zero eight and tuba zero one two it's the brown noise and it's
all loops this is adding more the old-fashioned free film music no turn it
up okay hey well done it was a tire let's play together let's do it
together here we go hey hey wrong one two one two crazy I'm gonna lose my
mind the game's crashing don't report me for getting ahead of you he's how
fast I can just clear what you did something's autoplay we're not having
autoplay bullshit happen right now again this 50 of these how many of these are
there this is like old Paris this isn't like the fiat commercials is this
correct this is not correct I need to one two two that's two four one two
three four five six one two three four five six one two three six four yeah
yeah that's all you guys can do a good luck one two three four one two three
four five six one two three four five six two two and two here two I don't
know if that which this could be the first two of the second two this is
five five in here five how this is wrong I didn't I didn't do that you
okay that's good no fuck I don't even know what that was I'm never gonna be
able to do this shit with you guys doing this here comes the next one
what's this one did an anchor to two right there probably sit get out fuck
out there no we're not doing that not relaxing you get I know it's
supposed to be relaxing what's it's a cold oh my gosh oh no that's not what
I'm looking for I'm not gonna put on minecraft music I want like old-timey
music royalty-free I ain't getting claimed this video has 985 views they
didn't they made me click on this no that's it this is every GTA 5 funny
compilations music you already made that joke I get to make that at least
more than once are you guys still playing no you're not um let's try
I'm gonna try an actual real one ADHD focused music okay I need that they
all do the same thing restart this fucking whole thing so how is this
supposed to work the your folk I'm focusing too much is what I can I
can like hear myself in my own head now that's supposed to be happening no I
have ADHD it's it's turning my ADHD off I can actually hear the things that
I'm saying interesting okay this definitely looks like one two three
four five six one two three four five six okay that's one and two how's
that wrong are you kidding me how's this wrong this one's wrong how's
that wrong this is two in the middle to that it can't be here how's that
wrong how's this wrong get out of here oh you idiot idiot idiot ADHD huh oh you're
really curing my ADHD you made it worse okay binaural face what is this
astral dreaming dude I'm gonna I'm telling you right now I'm about to go
lucid I'm going fucking lucid I'm about to see the elves that created
all the cosmos I can see him they're gonna come they're gonna come towards
me they're gonna say everything's alright they have ever-changing faces
they're the architects of the universe he's losing his mind yeah all it took
was for me to drink a Red Bull this morning play ADHD music get my brain
going with that's a dick on screen I have to make that I have to change
that you know I mean like five six I can't that was already correct that's
better Nintendo Labo VR just announced what the hell why would that ever be
true it was a good attempt okay that's one two okay so this is two
and then four it's probably over here that makes sense not a lie not a lie are
you fucking kidding me what hey wait wait wait get this on fucking screen
right now that was the worst troll joke I've ever heard but it's real
we're gonna watch this on stream yeah be kidding me but did you use it you
use your phone or do you use the switch that's gonna be so heavy why
was there a cat what was the cat for I've already done this one is this
the right one how is this different that's the wrong video hold on Nintendo
switch Labo Nintendo Labo VR kit concept but what is this like a
reaction video this is a reaction video isn't it no okay okay here it is
here's I thought this is a reaction video okay guys we have a new
Nintendo VR labo kit here I'm gonna break down the one-minute trailer in
a 22 minute full video with seven ad breaks and look what I'm gonna freeze
it right here for you I thought it was one of those sorry my mistake fucking
Grammarly god damn it how do I skip the Grammarly all right here we go
is it this it's the switch wow okay well that's kind of cool that's a
fake video oh how is it how is it possibly fake look at Nintendo's
Twitter Nintendo Twitter experience a new dimension with the latest Nintendo
labo kit with more games and creations than ever unique first VR experience
so what the fuck is that video so that video was somebody making that up
I know it wasn't there is no video am I falling for like the fucking
Facebook fake news bullshit did I just that just that just happened
holy shit did I actually just fall for like the Ronald Reagan used to wear
hats because he had devil horns and that's why he always wore hats to press
conferences so all right is it did I fall for that Jimmy Carter was four
feet tall what you don't understand is he was on stilts during press
conferences and they've like zoom it I fell for it okay the VR is real
well I can't wait to drink on stream again and everybody be concerned
it's the worst stream I've ever done and it'd be probably 2019 worst stream I'm
looking forward to it but you got this stream so you got some competition this
year I think the labo streams are my favorite streams I like them too all
right where were we show us the labo I here look from Nintendo of America
here it is here's the tweet here's a link to the tweet so you know
it's not bullshit there you go it's real okay where the hell was I that's Doug
Bowser spreading fake news first day in the job you give like a fake VR kit
press release all right so we got four two and then yeah so this is only it's
probably over here no because it's one no it's over here okay this is one
that's the only place where it makes sense one two three four five six
ooh ooh ooh no no no no no no no no no no no no Jeremy what have you done I
don't know that for sure yet but I do know that this is done so then two
goes over here very nice four also five one two three four five one two
three four five one two three four five one two three four five yeah yeah
yeah okay one two three four five six okay two one two three four six money guess
the dollar sign guess dollar sign oh you guys got it some of you guys got it
oh that's cool you can guess what it is like four or five of you guys got
it nice work only five of you guys out of thirty eight thousand let us
play you can do the next one because I'm gonna go get a coke a cola Nintendo
just announced a lab Oh pick Ross well that's wonderful one two three four five
six seven and go okay six seven eight nine not quite not quite I don't do
drugs we're talking about hmm interestingly enough I don't really
have much to go on to start it's gonna have to be down here
somewhere where's the music oh fuck you're right I miss the old German the
one that used to do drugs on stream well that German ever existed you're
making that up yeah go ahead and put like the top text there of like me
doing drugs and like bottom text of like can't believe it he's not been
banned yet and like spread it on you fucking Facebook because that's
essentially what you just did I can yeah I can do this because I forgot
about this side here yeah I know what's real and what isn't real okay so that
gives us that's one five five four two this is done completely that'll help
us probably somewhere here maybe not well mmm no that has to be there which
makes the no no no no no no no no no slow down here that's two okay any
more info I got an info here this is four in the middle one okay one
two three four five six seven one two three four five six seven I'm gonna
piss my pants you can't count worth shit I can piss my pants though I can
actually pee my fucking pants one two three four one two three four we got a
couple here one two three four one two three four so then I got that done
can close that out cuz not over here that's in the middle that's in the
middle one two three four five one two three four five block okay maybe over
here I've been talking about your pants all day they do what I mean my
pants what are you talking about oh this is wrong no it's not okay that free
anything else oh by the way I just want to make sure I make this really
clear I am issuing a gamer challenge to somebody ready to start some fucking
drama I am I hereby challenge Joel Vargo Skeletor to a gamer challenge
stream of pogo rage with your friends pogo over the mountain just want to make
that clear no practicing no getting prepared beforehand I want you to take
a screenshot of your steam library the day of the competition minutes
before we start with zero game time in pogo versus your friends otherwise
disqualified there you go challenge issue I'm gonna get decimated I don't think
so loser forfeits all subs to the winner well that would be pretty
catastrophic wait he's already beaten that game he already did that game
no he didn't that just came out did he already beat that game the pogo
stick game oh god damn it no he didn't do that yet did he somebody find out
for real he beat getting over it yeah it's not the same pogo stick rage
game is the other one what is this this is link here I can't wait for I
can't wait for all like the fucking jokey fake news posts on the reddit
in the next like fucking 12 minutes somebody asked him I drunk I'm no I'm
not I'm as sober as a bird because they need to be sober because they need to I
don't know why I'm just not no no I'm not drunk I'm so I am sober I'm a
sober as a bird okay four four three I am NOT I have not drank a sip of
alcohol it's gonna go here two one okay that's correct there I blocked
birds get drunk on fermented apples oh whoa do they really do they actually
that's actually kind of that's interesting that's actually true but
that's I did not know that that's really interesting okay so that's good
that's done two and then one it's not that one no it's got to be one
of these ones it's not this one either it's this one here that should
be good one and then three that's that and then we got two and three yes how
does this game work well what you do is and then on the title column that
felt good to do that felt good to do it did it's not what I mean it's
wrong no it's not it's not wrong ten one two three four five six seven eight
nine one two three four five six seven eight nine has to be here one
two three four five six seven eight one two three four five six seven eight
it's correct one two three four five six one two three four five six it is
correct now it is but how does the game actually work well I'll tell you
on the columns here so you got like three and then you move on to I'm
gonna piss a beer back oh right you guys yeah I'll just let you guys play
beer be there just so people know that I'm not here I'll activate it holy shit
this is awful yes you guys even try just gonna fill all the squares you did
it you fill them all in you win you did it nice no hey I was doing
something I was writing LOL all right you done all right that's it you done
I gotta redo the whole thing German is the upset teacher yeah I came in
after a rough day and somebody drew a picture of me on the blackboard it's very
unbecoming I got like a big nose big like eyebrow bones greasy hair boogers
coming out of my fucking nose and I had a rough day I was late to work I
spilled the coffee I got one of those Starbucks egg and cheese wraps and it
was too hot to eat I couldn't eat it I wanted to eat it but for some
reason I don't know why they do this the Starbucks hot fucking sandwiches are
ten thousand degrees and you cannot physically eat them until they get too
cold to throw in the trash I don't throw it in the trash god eight nine
ten one two three four five six seven eight there it is who buys a sandwich
from Starbucks working when you got done of time to get a sandwich that's
what I used to do I used to go I eat McDonald's man I used to get the
McDonald's drive-thru egg sandwich oh my god it was amazing people like dog
and McDonald's no why what's wrong with McDonald's the BRB screen is still there
it's our I'll get rid of it one two three you getting McDonald's right
now good I like that place the I wear to talk about the top two menu
items is the cheesy gordita crunch from Taco Bell and the Big Mac from
McDonald's that is written in like the fucking food Bible somewhere sell
out no that's that's just written in the food Bible of fast food the cheesy
gordita crunch is the best single food item you can possibly order from a
fast food restaurant that's just true I don't have to be sold out for that
but that's a good ghostbusters is the best movie ever made I don't need
to tell you that you already know that everybody does and gremlins 2 is
the second best movie ever made do I need to be paid by Paramount
pictures to tell you that is it just facts all right three it's one we can
block these two off for now back to the future three was the best movie
uh his thing about opinions though you know his thing about opinions
everybody's got one but only mine matters right and then how most people
think of opinions these days Paul Blart mall cup is the number one Paul
Blart ball cup is actually I didn't hate that movie I've never seen it
but I don't hate it all right you're derelaxing me let's see four four one
maybe here yeah you guys have to stop D laxing me okay I don't need I don't
need X lax right now you don't have to X lax me well let's see one two
three four five six one two three four five six six all right so it's
somewhere in here you'll hate it use the X's more often more that's the
200 IQ strat yeah I use them I only like to use the X's when I'm certain
though because I don't like it throws me off if I use them too much because
I didn't like I would use them here but I don't know it could be six and
then one just don't know okay that's completely done hmm one two three
four five six seven eight one two three four five six seven eight that
really helped middle click what the fuck is that for okay let's see for
maybes hmm that's too many things for me how do you play chat does a puzzle
every four or five sequences I have it currently turned off to to this way
would make sense let's say this six this way would make sense to this
is so easy you nerd you don't have to write all capitals okay let's see
four one it's probably here but I don't know no okay cuz then it would be one
you have to be there somewhere okay so that's that see here let's see one
three one yeah it has to be here because this is the one with the three
and it's not this way okay use the crosses I'm gonna hiss in just a
second one two three four five six seven eight nine four okay get in there
two hmm I started playing this when the stream started I'm already as good as
germo this is not a contest I at the beginning of the stream I wasn't like
all right everybody here we go queue up with me and race me six that's done
four and one two three four five one two three there's the one there's the one
there's the one and then you got two right here and there is what have I
done what have I done what have I done what have I done what have I done what
have I done no I know everything's fine it was this one oh it's a baby
stroller how's that a vehicle it's a pram the hell's a pram let's get
this one done quick four eight one two three four one two three four good to go
there's two pram is that like a the English terminology is that English
British or something probably a spider it looks like it's probably no maybe a
beetle ant some type of bug well that would make sense here's the eight
now that looked like a bug four and so it's there one of these two hmm four and
five but it could be this way could be this way three there's the one two
three a bug one five it's probably there one one two three four five six
seven one two three four five six seven is the one there's your buck one two
three four five there's the one oh I know what it is oh I know yeah I know
what it is I got two overzealous I know what it is it's not a pig it's a
black cat why would you say fuck you fuck you what why what did I do what
I have to do with that it's not my fault you got it wrong three four five
six seven four close these up three three oh that's be careful okay how would
you know it's a black cat five thousand of us said cat it was black
cat closed this game immediately can you do the sound of somebody get a
hit in the face by a dodgeball yeah four four five six seven eight nine ten
so this is just filled in that one's free so the only free one six seven
eight nine yesterday I asked you on Twitter if you're gonna do a
pit cross stream when you were and I opened your stream today to this yep
I did it I did this for you well it kind of has to be here doesn't it
four five good save good save good save all right let me relax for a second
because one two one two three four five six easy three and then two it's
probably down here because how is that that's not possible five it's gonna be
right there two okay easy now there's the nine there's your four and here's
you seven one two three four five six seven not quite it's the four that's
two there's five four which leads us to here I need four see one kind of has to
be here how would it be this way one maybe like that no no no no no no it's
one goose it's one who got it right nice nice work guys all right you guys
get a turn after this I'm doing one more although this streamer is so funny he
reacts in funny ways like youtuber gamers I watch with my two-year-old
daughter and she loves his wacky voices and silly jokes good like that's
supposed to offend me all ages that's well I mean everybody loves your
stream doesn't matter all ages everyone old young yeah doesn't matter
that's just that's a huge compliment thank you except for the yeah but
it's whatever okay this is tough this is tough because I don't have much to go on
six seven eight nine ten so we get three now I got funny two two three four
five six and eight three how did you bubble gum everybody gum click the links
everybody will stop spinning don't ignore I'm not a guy do what are you
talking about no I am playing that on stream you don't think I know what
that is you don't think I know what this is I don't play that whole
thing on stream yeah that's the German slot machine you don't think I'm
gonna play that no it's supposed to be let's just don't talk about it
something just don't talk about that for now just hold on three four five
six two three four five six I mean you guys you guys really spoiling my
birthday surprise there's the one so this could be two one one could be
that two two that would have to be correct right I think so which then has
one two three yeah that works so far it's my birthday yeah what's the
latest what's the least acceptable time to eat a bowl of cereal there is
no acceptable time doesn't matter Monday Tuesday Wednesday Thursday
Friday Saturday Sunday one two three four five six seven eight nine ten
eleven twelve one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve
one day eat whatever somebody can tell you not to eat cereal who cares it's
got vitamins in it what's wrong okay six this is probably yeah this is the
other one so one okay hold on don't freak out here six two I sound very
unhealthy what unhealthy what are you talking about how can you sound
unhealthy these are probably the ones right because then two would be here
I'm gonna just do an educated guesser that would make sense to it wouldn't be
this that's not even a guess that has to be that way whatever or could be no
well it definitely is not this way no it could be shit all right let me slow
down slow down slow down I can get this one here this is one one one
this two where the fuck would this be two going down which means two across
I don't have enough information I don't have the audio acts critical information
right that's tough well his three okay I see it I saw it I know somebody was
yelling at me now here's the real question where's the two you know
what I'm saying it could be three this way or three that way it could be
four this way or four this way hmm well it has to be here one of
these squares is this one I'm screaming into my monitor no I'm gonna accept no
I'm not doing this I don't want to do the maybe it's too much more
information I already know well this is three could this be two and then
one it's very possible but this is one could this could be one and then
this is one one two three whoa three one two one so therefore nope nope nope
don't need any of these so it's one of these two bring it down here this is
one one two one has to be here has to be one two three four five six one two
three one two three one two three four and then one two hold on we guys doing
stop get to asking for commands why is everybody laughing what is going on
over here why is everybody laughing so hard right now I don't understand what
the big deal is right here or was it was in their minds he actually doesn't
know I actually I don't know what you're doing what is going on in my
fucking chat room okay so what get it you guys guessed it right see we
congratulations someone call to remind dying help me no now you guys don't get
to do one you've been misbehaving this type of misbehavior you and you
want to turn no you're making me spam just stop just banning commands
stop doing that why would you do that right now stop I'm turning it
off yes there's no reason to be doing what you're doing I was
watching this stream and I dropped my phone in the toilet it's all your fault
you guys are gonna fuck up my channel all right let me start this six two
what's with all the laughter I got what am I playing right now that is
that what's happening this is the most LULs I've seen in this chat and
probably like six months somebody just got banned people are getting like
timed out people are getting like manually timed out what is going on
what is happening what was the emote only mode up its emotes only I didn't
know that I thought that everyone was just laughing how long is it okay I
dad didn't know I thought I didn't know that I thought it people were
just doing that I'm afraid to say anything because I don't want to get
in trouble yeah it comes a command I'm gonna have to like disable it
wait slow modes not working oh I told you you're gonna break my fucking
channel okay so we got two and then two two and then one one okay this was
this one's given to us now freedom I like how this is happening on this
stream 1800 second slow mo don't make me put on like three hours okay so
five this is one two one two one two three four five got it super cool
there's your one here's your two five there's your only option for two is
right there so we do this way that way this is a stinky home you guys were
telling me that I was on drugs are you sure that dick did something come
in here are you guys like breathing something in on this channel did like
the fucking laugh Factory open up like the fucking laughing gas on this
channel okay two this is probably down here yep yep yep let's see here so
that's two is done one and then four so that can't be there one two three
four possibly or one two three four we found your weed stash well I have got
really really really bad news for you marijuana is legal in Las Vegas
that just want to make sure you're aware of that okay somebody said are they
laughing cuz I'm auto playing the brown note you actually scared the shit out
of me for a second how much have you smoked and you guys I none okay this
is two one one so then two would be here doubt doubt yeah I don't I listen
I got nothing wrong with marijuana I don't partake in marijuana I don't have
anything does I don't have a problem with it at all have you smoke you do
like eddabees good I hope you fucking enjoy this be careful do it
responsibly he's a liar I'm not a liar I got nothing wrong with people
enjoying marijuana where you know I got nothing wrong with it it's got
some medical benefits you know like I know that I know it okay this is
pretty much done here is it a turkey it's a mailbox is everybody laughing I'm
so lost I don't know is this something okay I need a mod mod mod
what's happening right now what is what's happening right now why is this
happening did something happen I can't explain it it's like I don't tell
tell you're telling me I need to know I want a mod to tell me what's
going on Chad is just super bored there's nothing the game is boring your
stream is boring there's no way Lavoe could be worse than this I am trying
to enlighten your minds okay listen to me we would play a lot of wacky fucking
weird goofy drive the car into the wall games here I'm trying to get you
your intelligence your brain moving today I'm trying to get you to sit and
think and relax and maybe look wait a minute what is this game the cross
okay I'm seeing what he's doing here I'm following along I'm gonna try this
and then I'm the reason I'm the reason why you did better on your math
test in like two weeks and I want you to write at the top of that paper
you can write your name I would put my name in there too at the top let's
say your name is Greg Anderson I want you to dash Jeremy Albertson because I
did it too I helped you do that all right to pause the stream and you go
get a band-aid what happened what happened what do you mean to get a
band-aid that's not enough information what happened no you
probably like just cut his finger on like a toy now what kind of toy
would that be if you could cut your finger on a toy nothing would get
recalled is it a toy do we need to get a recall he stepped on a Lego on him
and threw his foot it's embedded into him all right four five six seven eight
nine that's not enough resident sleeper resident sleep
resident sleeper is seriously like so offensive to every stream any stream
think about how like I want you to think about this for a second but
like fail fish whatever like he sucks at the game like oh ha ha I made like a
dumb joke and I didn't think it was funny he's like yeah I was cringy
resident sleeper means this is so bad I'm falling asleep because this is
so boring to me that I can't stand it anymore at least you're paying
attention when you write some of the other ones resident sleeper is
like holy shit this sucks so bad that I'm going to bed good night I'm
not even watching anymore and it's in my title yeah all right it's fine all
right I got one four two two four five six seven eight nine I don't know I
know I don't know where to start with this one I don't have much to go on
here this is better than the Wow stream that the Wow stream was the
lowest point of my entire life that that single Wow stream was the lowest
single point in the history of my entire adult life but you guys know
when that stream turned off I smashed everything in my desk I broke every
monitor I broke all the controllers in here I broke all the glass I put holes
in all it was like a $16,000 repair job you guys don't know that that
happened I don't know where this next one goes so that's why I'm stalling
what will you do after this stream nothing because I'm have this is the
last dream was fine there was nothing wrong with the Wow stream it
was fun where does one of these go I've got only one piece of info here
one one I guess this could be one it has to be so this is one of the ones
also one of the ones two all I don't know if it's one of the ones four five
six seven eight nine it's not enough to fill one two three four one no I
guess it could be but I don't know that though because it could it might
not be there it's either like that or it's like this I don't have the
data I can do this though I started drinking in hopes of finding something
with humor in this string because this is to somewhere so I can go like this
because it has to be somewhere in here same thing with this one it has to be
one of these two so I can go like this okay go back to Floyd and
brothers I blended that disc up and stirred it up with my coffee and
drank it it was the most painful shit I've ever had in my life why
did I say that I don't know okay one two three one two three is gonna be
right here three it's gotta be one or one it's gotta be one and then one two
three one and one two three we got a two we got a four we got it yes okay
so then we got what what what two three two one four one two three four
one three one two four eight um four one two two one one thank you for the
you're welcome no no no no no no no no something's wrong no something's wrong
what's the what's wrong oh no what did I do wrong too ah one two four two I
would reset it no it's too close look at this it's just done I just need to
get it right what is wrong here shit I did something wrong one one one two
three four two then I got three two one one two yeah slow down whoa holy
shit I almost just it's okay that's off-center though that's what was
throwing me off all right I'm gonna do no bedside lamp hey you guys got
screwed sorry but we've been good 20 by 20 we're probably gonna move into
15 by 15 here I could I could imagine very soon I was promised Space Channel
5 and Resident Evil and did I promise Resident Evil? Space Channel 5 was
almost about to happen today Space Channel 5 and Seaman we're gonna be
today they were on the options list this was pre-streamed democracy voted
for this just to hang out and play pick-rocks Dusk was on here Toe Jam
and Earl remake was on here I just had a vote that's what happened there was
like three or four hundred responses you're shifting to blame what I mean
blame this is fun this is fun and yes I'm gonna keep saying that until it's
true it is true I'm having a fun time I'm in a good mood you understand I
had like all I had plenty of B vitamins today I had a I had some
what did I have for food what did I have what did I have what did I eat today
food what did I eat I had B vitamins what did I eat I had that it that I
just ate vitamins today that's it why do I what no what did I eat what the
fuck did I eat for food this was like three or four hours ago um vitamin
gummies no this is gonna I'm just gonna kill me hold on here you guys
can play this one well I think about this is gonna be fun like the 10
minutes to think about this good uh what did I eat I woke up I had some B
vitamins I took a fish oil pill last night and it gave me diarrhea so I
didn't take one today um what the fuck did I have for food it's really not that hard this is not
hard to determine it was like three hours ago oh you play it right do it
right oh I'm taking away the privilege get it right I'm clearing
everything play it right I need to narrow down the food groups all right
funny okay I'm gonna narrow the food meat did I have beef no chicken maybe
yeah there's a chicken it wasn't like pork I'm calling Kim right now I had
vitamins B I think it was really it was heated up in the microwave was
reheated did I eat any food I'm gonna text her hey random question what did I
eat today I'll see what she says 7 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 I wanted to play oh well
let me play give me a turn I want to try 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 what
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 3 this is the only way for us to what did I eat
for fucking food today no it wasn't a burrito it was chicken something chicken
oh I know what it was got it it was a it was a frozen dinner it was a
chicken curry frozen dinner that's what it was I win all right let's play no
wonder I'm so sad you guessed curry holy shit yeah good work was it still frozen
when you ate it yeah I just I took a fork and a hammer and I like chipped
off like a big chunk of the chicken and I just like put it in my mouth and
I let it sit in there cold frozen until the 98.6 degrees temperature at
Fahrenheit in my mouth warmed it up to a point where I could swallow it
and I could I kind of like mash it and mush it around in my mouth a
little bit dance game dance game what kind of curry was it it was a chicken
curry I don't know 98.6 degrees in mouth that's not natural Fahrenheit
yes it is 97.5 to like 99 is normal derma 98.6 okay okay okay five six
seven eight nine I don't have info I don't have any fucking info one have
this I don't have any info for this I just don't I could I could try to
determine this so that's the room two three one two three four five is one
off one two three four five mmm it's probably in here let's see one two
three or one two three one two three I think I got the three you know for
the longest time I thought that that emote was the Vinnie's Zelda emote I
thought it was somebody throwing up into their hand and then I was like oh
no that's from that cartoon that's from the Phillips CDI game right all
right come on no that's not Kim texting me back that's like it's like
my fucking I never mind somebody help me here you're so bored you're
looking for emotes for fun I am NOT bored I'm just stuck I'm just stuck one two
three four five one two three I guess it could be here in seven one two three
four five six seven one two three four five six seven three five two three
damn it three four five six seven one could be anywhere over here one two
three four five six seven it could be anywhere the one could be literally any
of these because this is three and this is also three so it could be either one
yeah the one can only be here the question is it's I can't I can't
determine which one it is so therefore one two three four five six seven one
two three four five six seven doesn't really help me though filling most of
the seven I'm doing it play English lessons no no no can I teach you how to
play the game yeah three five one three one three one three one one three two
five three three one three three one two three four five six seven eight nine
ten J I H G F E D C B A three five three ten one seven three one two
three one three one two two one one it's that simple I have to start
guessing the stream is just a looping back on itself oh hey how'd they go bye
you don't welcome to the stream all right so we got one two three or one
two three therefore goodbye no no no no no no no no no no no no no no because
it has to be either one two three or one two three therefore I think it's
impossible same on this side because there's no way this three can come up
this way it's either here here or here I don't have info for down here yet
brown car note is he finally using crosses I've been using crosses the
whole time what I've been using these the entire time almost four hours of
resident sleep or it doesn't even feel like it's been in doubt by the
way three and a half you're adding time you're adding a like a 40
minutes of time to make it seem like it's been more boring but it's
been three eight hours and 27 minutes three hours and ten minutes probably in
the game you added an extra 45 minutes how is that fair it's called rounding
up three hours and 27 minutes as you round that up to four no you round that
down to three three hours and 31 minutes round up the music is bad I'll
change the music well that make you guys happy he's there the music the
music is kind of round to the nearest hour okay how about I'm not
gonna play the brown note look this thing says warning the real brown note
brown frequency by the way it's by the YouTube channel apex legends clips
what I don't want to play this okay I did it I don't feel good I feel like
shit I don't feel very good all right warning warning here's a warning for
everybody okay I want to make sure I make this really clear I'm about to
play a low frequency sound that might cause you pain or a headache why the
fuck would I play this I'm okay here's the warning if you don't want to hear
this I'm gonna put it at a reasonable level here it comes okay I'm gonna tell
you right now if you don't I'm giving you a fair warning please it's gonna
be a low sounding frequency noise I would mute the stream for the next 30
seconds okay mute now want to make sure you have enough warning here
we go this is a THX sound yes that's wait that's the PlayStation one
startup sound no it's not don't tell me that no wait wait wait oh that
explains somebody said that explains why every time I turned on my ps1 I
had to use the bathroom okay you can you can unmute that's the regular show
intro they had an intro this is some this is something like deep fucking
conspiracy bullshit are they trying to control us with this noise how often
does that happen oh there you go I did I did the three
brown notes hopefully you guys aren't fucking thrown up or anything I feel
worse now I'm not kidding I'm serious I actually feel bad I feel not I don't
feel worse now I'm not doing the 17 Hertz saying anxiety tone it might have
something to do with the frozen dinner you ate no it was the frequency that's
making me have an upset stomach oh okay let's get back into this okay
okay okay okay how many times is he gonna say okay today three four five
six and eight one two three one I gotta put some music on or something
something anything how about something smooth smooth jazz royalty-free that's
good right smooth jazz royalty-free music did I just really get the pirate
thing preview I can't focus I can't focus anymore since the placebo effect
of the brown note it actually took over my brain ah all right five well
there's no way to tell where these are three five five three it could be one
two three one two three or one two three fuck two three four five six seven
I have to take a guess one two three one two three one two three four five
one two three four five hold on a second here though one two three one
four fuck someone one two three one two three it can't be here one two three
one two three can't be here okay okay hold on 1 2 3 1 2 3 can't be there
narrow it down 1 2 3 1 2 3 bingo three three one two three four five six
six seven one nice okay i swear to god i feel
fucking terrible it affected me i'm never doing that
again i'm never playing any fucked up song again
uh let's see i wish i had any information here
three one two three four five it could be
or it could be one two three really it can't be this one
because that's one two three one two three so this one has to be correct
which gets us to five one two three four five
and then not yet please listen to minecraft cat the fuck why would i put
this on minecraft cat minecraft 25 things you
didn't know about the cat minecraft music cat is this is this
a fucking hidden brown nose here they better not be that already made me
feel terrible i'm gonna get fucking i can already tell
it's gonna happen this is but this is good this is just
like weird clown music this is scary horror movie clown music
now it's a little bit better all right so we got five here
one two three could be there now i don't know if this is the this is
probably the one oh no hold on one this could be part of the three
yeah it has to be the three doesn't it one two three yeah it has to be
three and then that makes this complete
put an x there and one two maybe this is done three that's done
three in here somewhere three in here somewhere one two three one two three
one two three four five one two three there's the two yeah
there's the other three there's the other three
this song is fucking dog shit can i get something else please
just kidding i'm kidding i'm kidding i'm kidding it's a fun song
i'm sorry i will stab you it's whoa that's not something to be saying on
the relaxation stream excuse you pirate music one hour of epic
pirate pirate music and pirate accordion music
all right that's it there two there they go there they go
has to be here nice all right pretty much done
just need this one not there so one it's also one we need one more here
there's a two definitely right there definitely right
there definitely right there and it is did you get it
cherries who got it look at all those winners
you got 200 streamer points i'm still on the 10 by 10
let's see eight my guess from an hour ago didn't count
yeah this is this is also dog shit see what is sea shanties why is why is
everyone want me to do she see shanty 2 this is like
yoshi music all right can we get something else besides the mouse circus
no i'm just kidding it's fine yeah that was gonna go higher
oh this is from runescape runescape i didn't know that it's a classic
video game eight play the shepherd tone i'm not
gonna play any more weird tones it makes me feel sick
more guessing here one one two three four five six
one two three four five six it's gonna be rough i have to guess these
shepherd tone shepherd tone shepherd tone shepherd tone
is this shepherd tone is an audio illusion which seems to get
forever higher i don't want to okay it's an audio illusion which seems to
get forever higher but never really does should i do this
all right i'm gonna give you a warning if you're sensitive to uh like
audio visual noises and shit just be careful
i'm gonna give you a little warning here that that that is getting higher
what do you mean that's not getting higher this is so obviously getting
higher turn on turn it off turn it off
this is five minutes long we're having 30 seconds in oh
what it just reset it's going up it's going up
no no no it's back here it's back here it's back down
play sorting algorithms i've heard these before uh these are the ones that
are like
no i'm not doing these fuck that this is just i'm gonna give everybody a
headache this is space invaders on 400 times
speed that's what this is that was fun show us show us show us
show us what is what is there to show it's lines that go all over the place
and they scream at you there's not much else to show you there
i have ultra mustache hair today why do you only have one earbud in
because i i'm fucked no not the fucking
sorting thing got me messed up he's he has cooked his brain
click it i'm turning my headphones off when i click this
why on earth would why on earth would i play this right now
this is from jojo's bizarre adventure a lot what what
there's just no reason for that to be played not at this note is zero
it's i mean it's just that's a song that's part of the jojo's universe
you know steven's universe whatever it's called jojo and steven going a
bizarre adventure in their universe steven's bizarre adventure i've
actually never seen an episode of steven's universe
but i've never seen it i can't believe he's still on this level
because we had to take a break two three four five six
and one and then a space and a two and a three
and a one and two i'm extremely stressed now what why
dude dial-up noises why are you guys trying to like make me
like my brain exhausted i'm gonna guess that that's a
a one hey i got an idea you know the really really grating awful
like burn your head sound play that just play it
crazy frog i did crazy frog and beat saber and 100
expert of level fill in the middle two rows with six yeah but i
don't know which way they go i could do like let's say one two
three four for now one one two three four five six
let's just say there's a one here one two three four five six
you just assume you know you assume the dealer has a face card right
so one two three four five six one two three four five six do the same thing
over here there's the two don't have the three
though play english lessons no ram ranch is zoomer humor
don't know what that is one was the one three
interesting well here's the thing now i can't just delete because i
there'll be a one here well i can do this
because that much is certain nothing else is
nothing is certain nothing is nothing is
nothing is certain nothing is certain what is that happening nothing is
certain nothing is my syllabus is fucking crazy today
well two it's definitely not these two
one then maybe two down here has to be one of these
put on you say run i've already done that
this is the one that goes yeah i had it you just you'd hurt it
you can tell how bored everybody is because
hey dude maybe you should try uh three one
no maybe uh row five uh call column h check that
no it's just songs one two three people are playing this game
right now and it's just only songs how do you play this it's pretty easy
what you do is you uh i was about to do the you save run sound
effect again but i didn't have enough breath to start it
four one two three four oh can't be here
okay so then we got one two three four one two three four
one two three four one two three four pretty cool
dude trance 009 i'm off to bed germa the stream is making me feel sleepy
feel better hey that was no that's the point of the
stream chunky baloney 50 dollars from chunky baloney right now
coming in right now right now it just happened right now
50 bucks 5 000 bits from chunky thank you
thank you chunky they say i'm enjoying this stream it's nice and relaxing
forget chat music is overrated ps you're guessing on h6
remove that x you dingus oh all right well i thanks thank you
i do i have to put on ram ranch to make everybody silent
i don't know what this is is this like safe for work is ram ranch safe
for work it's not it's not safe for work
well sorry that's it i'm closing up it's not safe i'm not it's not safe
for work sorry it's not going on there play tacky on
uk i played tacky on like eight times on stream over the last like 12
months okay so we got three uh sm smother them
just gave 50 bucks 5 000 bits and smother them
says play undertale or i unsub for good
i already did i did a whole undertale playthrough i've already played it i
beat it on stream like four years ago oh they mean the
music oh well undertale music but i've
we've heard this a million times already haven't we
we've heard this a thousand times undertale
undertale ram ranch mashup let's see how it sounds
all right you get this for like two minutes we're gonna put it on
we're gonna put on just a random portion here i'm gonna go right in the
middle okay here it is you're gonna get this
for two minutes uh double d thanks for the
gifted subs five of them thank you thank you
no that's not true could be i can't even think
the song is laughing at me i can't think turn
it up i'm no yes it's going
i'll get it where is it starts here uh this is the wrong song how did i
skip that already i'm gonna try i'm gonna take a lot of
air for this okay here goes i gotta get a ton of
air in my chest and stomach and it's gonna come all that's gonna
come up
i almost turned off my stream i was so close to hitting end stream
no more songs i'm gonna beat the level and then you guys get a chance
i gotta i gotta get out of here i'll see you tomorrow sims 4
that was so awful that i have to leave i'm just kidding we're going
for like another hour two hours maybe who cares uh
uh ram ranch no stop with the fucking music who cares what the music
is just who cares relax everyone just calm
down just let's do a breathing exercise now
because i need to get this level done everybody do this
no this is like that's that's like a youtuber
we just want like a company video hey what's up guys chad here
no well that's just is there any company videos
hi i'm karen begins no no here we go here's like a company
like mass produced one this is horror movie hallway music this is not
breathing relaxing music all right everybody silence i'm gonna
beat the level now even you aren't playing the game time to
change no it's because i'm gonna play let's go
yeah i fucking guessed all right i had to
it worked you make me sick why wait isn't it with if if it
10 000 subs right all right let's get real here guys
this is gonna be let me be three one two three
one one okay can you select a bigger board i'm surprised we haven't seen any
15 or 20 by 20 i'll go back to the menu
and see if we can get like a big one and then we can all do a huge one
together here it comes here it comes no decided
against it today wait don't ever underestimate power of
the rumor so we got five goes in the middle here
somewhere one two three four five one two three four
five kind of has to be one of these maybe not all the way though one two
three four five one two three four five it can't be
certain can't be certain don't guess
one two three four five one two three four five
i think i did that it works re-e8 re-e8 re-e8 re
you don't have to re-e8 he didn't put it on e8 everybody calm down
i'm just trying i'm trying to relate to the younger crowd
i'm trying to relate to the younger audience and that's like a re is
cool right i don't know i just installed bttv
six days ago i don't know what that means
can't be there it's done nice relaxing stream
people to come here just chill and relax and you just fucking read in their
ears only one more apologize i'm sorry i know
i'm sorry i think that i think that works
one two three four five one two three four yeah it does
i don't know if this is the first one or the second one i don't know if
this is because this could be one let's see
could it be one one two three four five no this has
to be part of the five so this has to be one right here it
has to be right because there's no way that that can be
the one one two three four five that should be good one this is also
one there it is okay looking for a two
i fucking hate this stream why what i told you guys i was gonna have
a just a relaxed hangout stream don't hate me
i don't want i don't want you to hate don't hate me we're just having
a chill hangout stream i hate this stream well this could be
one is this this is probably it right here
you know i don't know that yet we're just hanging out
no pressure you know just there's no pressure here we're just having a good
time as a fucking community okay
there i could pay attention that's one one would be this would
make sense in either one of these two spaces so i don't know
five six seven eight
all right that's done so it was here where does that leave
this though one that's done too so is this
getting there three one so it has to be here
has to be there has to be there thank you thank you
not much left two there is the only two spots it could be
there's one there's the last one and then here's
eight eight there it is what is this lettuce
garden boots four people got that correct somehow
you garden boots oh you probably beat it you probably played this level
you're like yeah i got to this part before i know it you're too slow
yeah but okay the people that got past me garden boots they didn't sit
here for like 20 30 straight minutes
talking about like what i ate for dinner last night
and like put on fucking ram ranch all right let's go do a hard one let's go
to the menu suspend yeah yeah that's fine all right
let's go what do we got 10 out of 10 here but now we're
almost there we all right let's do 20 to 20
20 by 20 they're locked wait okay i don't want to know what these are
all right here's the 50 by 50 we can't do 20 by 20 we have to
fuck that guy i swear uh okay we'll do accessories 15 by 15
but this one's are what i don't know come on you don't give that to me this
is like 10 by 10 you took it away from me
that's the most exciting thing to happen in hours one two three four
five six seven one two three four five six seven
one two three four five six seven okay we're not going for excitement
we're going for ingenuity uh how the fuck am i going to do this one four
five six seven let us do one guy i said the re word
three one two three four five six one two three four five six
okay i've got two here now five one two
three four five get out of here look at that
oh that's good four could be right here
four two seven right in the middle there okay
is this minesweeper not quite six let's see one two three four five
no one two three four five it's probably one of these two
three let's see one two three one two three so this is all
bullshit same with this say one two three four
one two three one two three four so this is all bullshit up here one
two three four five one two three four five one two
three four five all bullshit no wait one two three four five
one two three four five what's wrong with my voice
okay three going up and down three going up and down again but i don't
know if it's connected to here it might be one two three four five
six seven no i can't tell six is though it's
possible one two three four one two three four therefore all
this is dog shit one two three four five six one two
three four five six all this is dog shit
derma sucks well everybody's got an opinion you know
four two can't tell i don't have any info yet
two and then two let's think about this for a second
five one two three four five one two three four five
that's right one two three four five one two three four five that's correct
then here's the real issue is this part of the four
or is this four and this two one two three four
one two three four okay is that part of the four or is this four too
i don't know you should try the quit puzzle game i'm not gonna do that one
two three four five six one two three four five six
that makes sense which means three four
one two three four one two three four
one two three four one two three four it's not there
damn it one two three one two three it's not here
one two three one okay nice two three seven there's the six
six again okay there's the four the two
oh it's just cascades like a domino that's what you say
chill out dude it's an accessory you guys are guessing animals
it's not it's not a this is not a whale
well it's got to be here or here therefore none of this works
one two three one two three four that's it for three
i don't like men under five feet sorry well that's great because i'm
five eight so no that's not true here no no no no no no no no i'm talking
about like this that's not real this is not going to work for none
of five feet
one two three one two three can't be here
two i'm gonna i know what this i'm gonna guess i think this is a
pipe a smoking pipe jerma only reads mean comments so we feel bad and give him
money one two three one two three can't be here
what is this two two three four five six one two three four five six perfect
nice okay one two three four
three excellent two two three two three
i told you it was a pipe oh my god a cheeto
okay remember this is 15 by 15 10 doesn't do anything for us anymore
so we can do 12 13 so it's like this because that's one
two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve
one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve
wait a second no that's fine because that's 12 13 14 15 i
guess it could be either way because it does he buffoon yeah still
not a real board yeah they're giving us
they're giving us like the slow drip here therefore 10 would be
how many how many down is this one two three four five six seven eight
nine ten eleven twelve thirteen okay so the middle
ten here so that would be like in here
let's see one two three four five six seven eight nine ten
one two three same deal here eight nine
ten can't really do much with that but we do know this is eight
and this why is it why wouldn't they fill this one in they filled all the
other ones in why not this one well that just made everything way
easier because now i can go one two three four five six seven eight
one two three four five six seven eight so that's can't be that can't be over
here actually none of these can be over here
wait yeah yeah this yeah yeah one could still be here
that one could be right here it probably is let's see
six one two three four five six two three four five six and that's
reaching i don't know if that's true or not
it's reaching two three four five six seven eight
two three four five six seven eight all right there's the ten there's the
ten close that looks pretty good now we
got twelve one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve
still don't know do something funny no i'm gonna do something funny let me
talk about one two three four one two three four
these two that's the two there here's the three
there's your six make do funny funny something funny
now it's not all about fun and games it's not all about funny
sometimes it's about just relaxing eight five six eight so there you go
i want a joke i want a joke there are no jokes
let me see what we got here four the ones are gonna be tricky
brown note sapped him of all is funny i thought sapped well i'm just having a
good time that's all that i had that you know
well it's very clear that one two three four
one two three four so this is nothing one two three four one two three four
so these are this middle here so it has to be one two three four five
four five excellent excellent i jumped into my favorite streamer stream after
a long day at work extremely tired to see him playing a boomer game
also why wasn't saturn on the t-shirt care to explain
because they're standing on saturn but how do i need to explain that
by the way if you don't know i have merchandise t-shirts
30 days old just about the night sky t-shirt and glue man had made a
return if you do hashtag shirts you're gonna
find the store and maybe you'll buy one if you want
there's no reason to unless you want the shirt and want to be involved in the
cool shirt club all right hold on what is this
can't be there one two three four can't be here and it can't be here
two three four five six seven eight one two three four five six seven eight
cool there's the one excellent narrow it down in here too one two
three four five six one two three four five six nice
did that give me anything else that gave me the three that means nothing
over there nothing over here there it is i still
don't know about that i do know that though okay so that's
close enough one two three four five six seven eight
i guess it could be either one of these one yeah could be all right
almost done with this one but we should have clicked on that white box
yep no no no no no there's still a one here
it's either this one or this one how the hell would i know
one two three four five six seven eight one
no that's not true i got the eight 12 eight possible um i don't like that
i mean it's got to be here right there's that has to be
look at how perfect that is i fucked up something what did i fuck up
row five is incorrect wait wait wait wait wait wait wait hold on what i
what do you mean i fucked it up one two three four all right
fuck six and then one two three four five six seven eight oh shit okay hold on
three four five six seven eight that cleaned that up but is it right
i think so yep okay i got it this this is
has to be there one two three four twelve is done
oh shit wait okay uh no no no no no no no no no
because this is shit six one two three four five six seven
eight one two three four five six seven eight
one that's that's correct though two three four five three four five
one two three four five no no no i've
this one fucked up block for two blocks that have screwed up hold on remove
these is this symmetrical here two three four five that's done
close that up that looks hard that looks correct that
we four and four two and two one and one one and one
again right and then one two three four five
six seven eight one and then one one
what this is correct though what what's going on here here
and here and here oh got it column g is completely wrong no it's not
that's correct uh that that was not auto
that's not even how moons work look at that here's the best part
this is like peeling off a bandaid after it's been on there for like
four days oh that's good this whole column is
gone there's one three going up five going up one two three five
four there that looks good four again five three i love when you get these
things for free you get the whole entire bottom row
for free it feels amazing so we got a lot to work with now
actually that took away like 40 of the whole board okay
so this is a lighting something to do with lighting
any other places i didn't fill in there's a two somewhere there's a five
there's a six there's a one three oh let's get the sixes
one two three four five six one two three four five six these are the same
right yep they are so that means we've got an eight
in the middle six in the middle this is done so is this one
now i'm going to assume the eight look at one two three four five six
seven eight perfect it's going to be the same thing one
two three four five six seven eight one two three four five six one two three
four five six you could fill these in that's the
five right there thank you very much five and three is filled in
same deal on this side what the hell is this a lantern or something
okay so we got six one three three's there three's there again
that's done six one two three four five six
six this one was done pretty quickly two one oh anybody get it
lantern right congratulations you guys did it
you guys want to do one you guys want to do one i think you guys deserve to
do them let me let me start let me help the
audience let's let's get the easy shit done first
like the one column you know i mean seven eight nine ten eleven you guys
got some something to work with here uh if if you guys do like two full
columns in a row like as like an lul laugh fucking out loud
um i'm not here's i'm gonna tell you something
we're not stopping this game until you complete this so
better work together go on welcome to hell
oh look at that by the way i want to make this really really clear until
you guys beat this level i am not going to stream another
game we're talking tomorrow we're talking the next day we're talking
you're gonna have to beat this level before i do another video game
how's that for a fucking little bit of encouragement you beat this level oh
this is all ice cream for the rest of my life
okay okay test it go ahead test test it let's test it have your fun
twitch plays picross every day until they get it right
wait you can do individual cells yes you can
yeah look at that democracy wins the never-ending stream
well i didn't say it was gonna be on 24 seven
i just said that when i turn it off if you guys don't complete this i'm gonna
turn it back on tomorrow and this is what we're starting with
it's actually kind of funny because the second i started talking about that
a absolute shit load of people in this chat was like
oh fuck okay no no no let's get this done i don't want to see this
shit again hey well you guys are doing like a
little joke filling in the squares all fill the whole thing in
hey this is all we're doing for the next week until you guys complete
this oh fuck okay time to do like time to
get this done we got to actually do this now
i don't want to see this shit again ever again all right oh i got you i got
you i got you i got you got you there you go
you just cleared it you just did that
you why what are you doing why there's no reason for that to
you cleared that already
look at that fight down here quick fill in she
doing it again and now you're about to fill in a again
change stream title yeah i will there you go
we got chat must complete a picross level or i stream this forever is the
name of the title of this stream there you go oh actually cleared the
top row you cleared the top row x is back on
the zeros yeah you good you got it oh uh look what's uh coming up here
next still good work coming up next is uh is
fill in all b take your hands off look i'm just trying to help i'm just
trying to help you guys you guys are never going to get away
from this you're going to fill in a and fill in b and then remove the
zeros and put the zeros back forever can i lower the countdown i
don't think i can i think it's just the way it is
guys okay if twitch chat could complete dark souls
i'm pretty sure you can do a 15 by 15 picross level they've twitch chat has
completed all the pokemon games they've beat
dark souls the difference is your chat is dumb
what the fuck filling in h7 what the fuck is h7
oh shit somebody's doing it you got it you did it somebody did it
somebody filled in h7 and somebody's about to
unfill in h7 you're going to take it away
why you haven't gone golfish to anything
some people are trying they really are uh i'm seeing a lot
less of fill the same row over and over again just leave the stream on
while i sleep and check it in the morning
just mute my microphone mute the mic
and just fucking have have at it am i allowed to do that
that's not correct i'm sorry it's incorrect
rename it to morons play picross oh good night guys
i'll be looking forward to uh i'll be looking forward to seeing what you
guys if you guys do it by tomorrow's stream i'll laugh my
fucking ass off if i keep this stream going all night into tomorrow
and i come wake up and check this and it's still
f7 gets filled in and removed i'm still here i ain't going anywhere yet i'm
curious how this plays out we got we got a lot of we got a lot of
people in complete anarchy we got we need some people to come in here
and really take control and work as a team and get this done
and to drown out all the people that are just
trying to make it hell read bits while chat kills your channel
i'm not i'm not leaving yet i'm not turning i'm not
leaving stream's on over oh oh oh play sad music well i heard an
entire row wildly enough look at that we got three in the
middle i don't think that's the right place
might be add a timer to the screen there yeah there is a timer isn't it
already on we actually can't the row and column
fills are too strong do a long slow mode check the
settings come on pause show time there you go
13 and a half minutes almost 14 minutes 14 minutes and then no progress
i think i actually probably put it on a slow mode a certain
right turn off the rows and columns i don't think i can do that
see i can't fill a1 fill i can't turn them off
click them no it doesn't do anything turn off twitch integration i think i
think you guys can do it play brain power what is brain power
brain power this this is too fast too fast too much too no no too fast and too
upbeat how's it going we got still in the same spot
here i'll help you this is the most non-exciting
fucking possible thing you could ever be watching
this is not exciting you're supposed to relax
come on you guys could do it i know you can so much people are just
trying to ruin it take control i can't am i
going to take control oh everyone's getting timed up for
spamming uh-oh wait what the fuck was that
here comes the Thanos step
you're never gonna get done why did i say that that was such a mistake
i know this is the bike channel is gonna die my entire screaming career is
gonna go down the toilet now you will never finish this level ever
stop dancing stop singing and get this done
no no all right you gotta get this done
look at everybody in this chat nobody's even working stop dancing
stop dancing and then you surround me
i start dancing too a little bit cut this out at once
i mean it's a little fun and even the fucking old disgruntled asshole has
a little bit of fun uh but for real you guys are not
doing anything you're not getting any progress
it's been 18 minutes and the only thing that you have here is
what i'm helping you with play the doom ost and we'll complete it
that's a that's not gonna happen how do i get you guys to work together
you don't we can we see a little bit of creativity here
the same row the same fucking row not like this row not this one right
here not like one two three random dots
this exact same row every time where's the ingenuity where's the
almost close it up you need to have a vote system
half of the chat is timed out right now
turn on sub only somebody just came in and said
low effort stream huh no no this is not what the stream has been the
whole time i promise i was playing pick ross
uh this is what you're saying is only the last 20 minutes that's a long fucking
time it's only been the last 20 minutes
this is not i'm not i'm trying to a reward will okay
okay turn this off for a second hold on
if you guys can work together and finish this within the next
20 minutes i will play minecraft vr the next time i do a vr stream
you want to get rewarded you got 20 you got until that says
40 let me give you 40 until that says 45 interesting
by the way oh hey let's make this a very very clear as well
i'll pause it we're not just well pause it here i'll give you till 50
i'll give you 30 minutes till that says 50 minutes if you guys can do it
i will play minecraft vr for at least one full hour
okay if you do not do this in 30 minutes i will never ever ever under any
fucking circumstance ever play minecraft or any minecraft
related content ever on stream ever again in fact
i'll never play it again off stream either ever how's that for stakes
is minecraft even a thing no i played it one time on stream
but people are always like hey you should like check out like minecraft and
you didn't make minecraft vr oh yeah you'll never see it ever
we'll see what chat really wants i'll give you at least an hour in
minecraft vr on the next vr spring reset the puzzle and go off the
in-game timer that's a good idea 30 minutes are you ready sub only i
can't do sub only you have to work together sub only
if i do sub only you guys will get it done in five minutes
sub only i think is cheating you get stakes like that and all the
sudden put it in sub only man oh we'll get it done we'll get it sub only and
everybody cool down grab some like coffee grab some cider
right remember that one oh he's gonna do that again
no you gotta work together no sub only
minecraft vr and i will recreate the first 12 minutes of that video in
vr i'll have this i'll have a fucking
cider there in front of me good luck
you're not gonna do it you're not gonna do it
take a look at what's already happening take a look at what's queuing
up down there oh that's that was
somebody's doing such a sad face oh well right here what are you
thinking what are you guys thinking right now
you don't how you don't know that this is here
bottom level like what do you why this is a mistake you can there's no way this
is impossible for you to win i'm gonna go get another drink
brb uh good luck because you're gonna need it
now i'll put your i'll put your like fucking pump it up song back on
maybe that'll work how's it going let's see
uh i see a little slow slowing down i think they are
chat is cheating wow how would you cheat
is there a math with a mathematician in chat right now
everybody still relaxed uh 24 minutes remain
i'm just like eating food right now what a stream i just get to sit here
and eat i'm eating a yogurt low effort
streaming that person was right i was like hey
wait a minute i'm just eating watching a tv screen
yeah this is pretty good show oh i didn't touch anything i did not touch
anything don't blame that on me you saw my
hands any more song requests no my mic got
turned down somehow play gas play this one gas gas gas
okay this is called gas gas gas who is it what is this who made this
i did i did it with you i did holy shit you guys are focused
that's the easiest like chat streamer bait ever
you guys are focused like fucking crazy right now
i've never seen you like this before you got almost 20 minutes
when he said minecraft vr get on it hurry step pump the gas louder
okay gained like 500 viewers by the way
since getting my hands off the fucking mouse
and eating food and watching the screen i invited my entire discord
well that's dedication oops i ruined it i'm sorry
19 minutes you still have quite a quite a few difficult things to fill in
here by the way everybody there was no rule
against me fucking with you guys with sound
you're getting a little too close here
okay let me think here
what's up there there are cats here everybody loves cats
good luck it's gonna be hard
sexy good girl early good girl don't go
don't stay focused
this one's too loud
it's not just
what this is an ad
wait what wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
what wait wait wait hold on did i what you guys weren't even getting
started wait a second wait a second wait a
second wait a second wait a second wait a second you guys
fucking serious you cheated you guys had a cheat
sheet how why where would you get a cheat
sheet for this that no that doesn't count that doesn't
count you cheated you actually got a cheat sheet no
take backs what do you mean no take backs you
don't cheat on an exam and the teacher says hey
uh little uh little timmy i know that you cheated on this math test you
got an f no i didn't you never said i couldn't
cheat uh timmy it's implied that you don't
cheat in school the teacher doesn't have to say don't
cheat ever before every test i can't believe it i can't believe you
guys actually cheated now um i'm taking away the uh apple
cider portion the teacher also doesn't play
annoying songs
the teacher is sitting there you're doing like a really important math test
that person would get fired immediately their parent they'd have a parent
teacher conference about the sicko that is trying to ruin the kids exams
all right all right yeah all right really you cheated you lied to my face
you cheated right in front of me so therefore uh you're not going to
get all those additional perks so i will play minecraft vr i'm not
going to recreate the first 12 minutes of germacraft
you cheated too well hey we both cheated you cheated first
i waited 15 14 15 minutes before i cheated
you cheated from the very beginning passing around your notes
all the whole classroom had the fucking cheat sheet
by the way that was really funny when i put on the you're welcome song
somebody actually wrote they were just like hey man like disney doesn't fuck
around with like copyright claims like take that off
all right all right all right all right i want to do one stop
hey well that was fun now it's my turn we gained
almost one and a half thousand viewers during that well oh shit i got
to change the title uh this is called uh pit cross bedtime
no you guys did it you did do it even though it was completely and totally
not for real you broke my trust well what the fuck do i care i ate a
full yogurt and sat there for like 45 minutes
i didn't have to do anything i had to play i played loud sounds
once in like 40 minutes oh yeah i should be thanking you guys that was
like the easiest 40 minutes of the stream i've ever done
all right andy streamer andy streamer what are we talking about
what what are you what it was an open book
all right one three four one two fraud fraud i'm not the fraud you're the
fraud you fraudulated me okay 14 so we got
how much across 15 by 15 it's an open book exam uh how long
we doing this for like five and a half hours jesus i don't think we'd
be doing it this long that's just how much you can just
tell how much fun we've been having it's been five and a half hours
we haven't done anything but this uh but tomorrow
i'm not done yet i'm gonna do like another couple levels uh tomorrow
we're gonna do the sims 4 in first person i'm gonna see how it is
i wonder if it'll be any fun no minecraft vr tomorrow all right
one that's one two three one two three four
one two that one's free mods yeah i'm gonna have some mods too
we are gonna do a new family by the way not the same family
we're gonna condense the family not like 10 people
that i already make them no it's more fun to make them when you guys are
hanging on are you kidding me mr andy this was the
funniest shit of my life you're welcome i'm glad you had fun
first person sims 4 can get you motion sick i think that's the least of my
problems considering like the murder serial killer mod is probably gonna
get turned on again i'm gonna try to find some other ones
that we didn't do all right let's see one six one two three four five six
no nice job bringing back the fun
all right what do we got five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve
thirteen fourteen not quite five let's see
if you don't complete this in 15 minutes you have to do a 24 hour
stream i can't do that i'm not gonna time
myself two three four five six seven nope
six six one six eleven twelve thirteen fourteen not
quite again this is what my grandpa plays
when he makes dad noises at the kitchen table drinking stale coffee
he's got some pretty good taste andy andy what like fucking toy story
toy story andy because you guys are the toys
i know what it is guys i have not like i opened up twitch for the first time
ever yesterday but for real though i gotta figure out one
five one two three two no i can't just guess i guess i could do one two
three four five no one two three four five one two three
four five okay so neither one of those but not like that
matters it's one well i can do that down here though
so one two three one two three okay getting somewhere five we've got
one two three four five no one two three four five one two three
four five okay play trollo for
ten hours no you sound like an optometrist
like an eye doctor an optometrist i don't get it when it comes to your
vision you can never be too careful that's why we're proud to be the top
local optometrist that sound like me comes to your
vision you can never be too careful
have you ever had an eye test yeah i have my perfect
614 vision yeah what's more than optometrist they make like six hundred
thousand dollars a year and they're like incredibly well respected they do
a lot for the medical field why would i be embarrassed about that who cares
we've lost 1500 viewers since chat stopped playing well i did also say
that that was it i said i was gonna do two more and
then people were like yeah i'm probably good i'm probably gonna get
out of here all right we'll see you stop stalling
oh yeah yeah yeah yeah you're right stop stalling
let's get that let's get the shitty i'm not gonna say shitty the game
this is great game all right one five six i could probably
eliminate something here and i already did
one two three four five six seven one two three four five six seven
does that give me anything no it doesn't shit oh you're about to head
out no that's not good you're gonna stop by
tomorrow we'll see you tomorrow this stream is pretty much getting
close to being over i just wanted to relax a little bit today
actually that that actually does help me no it doesn't
shit one two three four five six one two three four five six okay
does that do anything for me at all not really
we've been relaxing all day yeah we're just
chilling what is hanging out three one two three i just don't know
this is my first time in your stream and i stayed the whole stream well
welcome andrew thanks for staying we fuck around a lot here but it's all
in good fun welcome i don't know any of this
although two and in space let's just say it starts here one two three four five
six seven one two three one two i guess it
could it's got to be some of these in the middle here the five in the
middle that's a guess but it's i think it's
worth a shot what a shitty first stream to watch
what's wrong with this i like this stream i thought this is fun
that's that is five four is probably four
then that's six okay that's either that's probably two
two one two three i think that works i think that's good but what about the
middle here one five three two is this five or is this the space
in between where the three is one two three one two
because then that would be one two three four
five i'm liking it i'm liking it so far i'm liking it
two two again that was a perfect co-op really was
got that one all right two three four five
oh fuck shit this doesn't work no no no no no no no no it's already
screwed up one four this works though this is okay i
think skeleton fruit if you had the cheat
sheet this wouldn't be hard i'm not gonna use the cheat sheet
it has to be here if that's not correct then i've got more problems
that's all seven three okay it is the five in the middle so it's three again
one two three four five does that work though
one two three fuck one two three four five does
that's five one two one three is left you got the two then you got the
three i think it's currently working out
this three two three this looks really messed up but i think i got it
three three again then that's five no this is good okay it's sands
i don't know about that cv and then we need six one
two three four oh no it's fucking wrong that's correct that's correct
but i don't know three and then three now that's correct there's your two
i need a four in here somewhere what the
ah where's the four is this the four no one two
four one two three i think this is the four right here two
no this is the four right here okay hold on
it's 15 minutes are up i didn't have any stakes there were no stakes put on
here two what is the two three four five
two seven three there it is two but that's two two
and then one two three four five six one one two three four five one two
three four five six got it is that two
done yes what is it orange you guys got it i don't know we'll do one more one
more one more one more one more one more this is a big one
13 14 15 so that's one then fill the whole thing in
and craft same thing over here 13 and then one
there's a lot of these big ones okay so now
i got both edges here that's great one
one two three five some type of staircase it's a weapon
not exactly sure what kind of weapon looks like this it's the one
two three that's too many five six i love these ones what the
hell is this it's a weird looking weapon is it
the negative space here that i'm supposed to be looking at
okay so let's take a look what we got we got two
six and then two four two four five four one two three four one
not quite same deal here two two one two
one one two three four not quite one two three four five six seven eight
nine one two three four five six seven eight
nine two three four five six seven eight nine one two three four five six seven eight nine good
one two three block it two block it one one okay so that's probably the one one of the ones
can't be four can it one no okay have i played bob ross pickross i've not i played a lot of
these different kinds of pickross games not that one though well it has to be in here so
one two three four five one two three four five and we got three i'm relaxed right now
i feel fucking great really i can do this way too so it's one two three four one two three four
should be one two three four five one two three four five six seven eight nine two three four
five six seven eight nine we've got some things to fill in here there's three
fill it in play the brown note again i can't i can't that's too much all right now is that
there's one there one two three four somewhere in the middle here and then one there's another
one above here because that's not one two three four no that has to be one so there's a four
somewhere in the middle here one two three four one two three four bingo
okay this is part of the four so one two three four one two one two three four one two three
four three nothing else down there no this is part of the five two three four five one two
three four five i can't deduce it from here look over three one so if it's right here
space one two three one two three has to be right here at least one of them one and there's
your three right there completed thank you up guess streamer sucks what's that right so looking
for a one and then the three looking for five in the middle one two three four five one two three
four five one two three four five one two three all right getting a little weird here i gotta slow
down this is part of the four that's it for this what if there's four in here too one two three four
one two three four one two three four one two three four okay it's part of the six in here
deduce deduce deduce deduce deduce so that means three this is six two three four five
one two three four five six one two three four five six looking good this is the one
this is the three one two three one two three has to be here here's the two here's the one
there's another one and the five is back here two three four one two three four
two three okay two four oh it's wrong now it's wrong what does i fucking do two two two two
okay one two three four two two one has to be here don't tell me he's been playing this for
six hours yeah it's fun hold on let me go down here got six two one two three four five six one
two three four five six i need one more two four one one probably here i got too much shit going
on here blink twice if you're being held captive no never mind i'm not gonna do that
um this is part of the five so therefore well this is definitely not here one two three four
five okay that's two right there is this going is this going the right direction it might be
one two three four five six seven eight nine one two three four five six seven eight nine
all right close very close one four one two three four one two three four two three four
uh hold on hold on one one four one there it is which leads to this is done it's right here
right yeah so then we got this is uh oh no four and then four that's one two one two
yes bow and arrow who got it well it's actually just bow only bow nothing else all right this
last one this is that last one last one last one last one this final one it is a minecraft
sprite this is it final puzzle of the night it was fun this is a really relaxing interesting
game p cross i hope you learned it hope you figured out how to do it and hope you play it
because it's very fun interesting and really uh moves your brain all right here we go final
puzzle as you nine so then that gives us two okay not very much to go on one two three four
five six seven yep seven seven fourteen fifteen there you go this is nine a ten of course
so let's see from here one two three four five six seven eight nine ten one two three four five
six seven eight nineteen now this is this works because it already started up here
that's fine three four five six seven eight nine one two three four five six seven eight nine
it's two two two two they're all twos one two three four five six
and eight which brings us to this two of all this three in the middle here one two three
one one no eight and one maybe let's see one two three four this could be the one
let's see if this is the one one two three four five six seven eight yeah it could be the one
just don't know there's still enough room for it to be the one 12 is right here though so one
two three like this one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve one two
what does that do for us that's one they're all ones okay and we'll big numbers
i don't see any this does narrow this down though one two three two two one two two so
this could be here oh it has to be because of those two cool and this also is two two
so now i know and this has to be two oh yes oh yes thank goodness
is three oh this is great go go go go this is perfect ready one two three one two three
all this is done you know what that means get rid of this get rid of this get rid of this
and that is down here and there it is so this was the eight right here so that's good
let's put it up there let's see what that did two one that's another one same thing this one
this is just a completed row two one one three nice completed two one one three again
completed oh two three oh this is wrong two no it's not all right what we got here now
i got a lot of shit filled in one one one wait wait wait wait wait wait wait hold on
two one one one only one more this first one's a two there's a one one then there's another two
here well oh what am i doing one two three four five six seven eight nine ten nine got it
it's a one that can be blocked off this can also be blocked off and that leaves this one
huh well this is four one two three four one two three four that looks good so does that
so does that kind of has to be right here or right here yeah this whole right side is done
yeah what is this a book looks kind of like a book one two three four one two and that's it
no it's not no it's not what the fuck am i doing this is four done it's a book bro fist
yeah all right all right guys that caps us off at about the same exactly six hours so you know
what that means i'm gonna do one more i can't it's too it's fun i can't stop i will stop but
i'm going to just not yet very soon this is the end this is yeah this is the last one last one
last one last one final one no dicking around here two three four five six seven eight nine
ten eleven two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven okay same thing with this one
same thing with this one any more big numbers i don't see any this is one one eight this has
to be the eight here has to be right one two three four five six seven eight and that's got
to be here all these are the eights and the seven and the six what no this is a photography
what is this probably a camera pretty big and bulky all right so we got one two one two three
so that's it for that one six is in here somewhere two two don't know yet here's eight
one two three four five six seven eight one two three four five six seven eight one two three
four five six seven eight one two three four five six seven eight okay that's the one here's the
seven one two three four five six seven and then the one no doesn't need to be there could be here
it's killing him it's not killing me i'm doing just fine
six
two what nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen nines in the middle here somewhere one two three
four five six seven eight nine one two three four five six seven eight nine
one two three four five six seven eight nine one two three four five six seven eight now i got it
also two so it could be one wait hold on one two three four five six seven eight nine
wait there's a one here too wait wait one space one two three four five six seven eight nine
it's possible it's very possible well this is a two obviously this is two twos i think
this way and that way unless this is one two two no i had it right
i hope that's right
uh you guys are fucking funny one one and then one two three four five six seven
no i don't know there's no way i can tell he lost his dentures two three four five six seven
eight nine two oh okay okay i forgot this this one space up here is gone that's right
now i get the four one two three four one two three four one two three four
progress progress progress also we get the eight one two three four five six seven eight
not quite something here closing in we're closing on the six one two three four five
six seven eight two three four five six seven eight is the one six two three four five six one
two three okay so we got it eight eight eight eight these are all done interesting stuff
this is also done any more finished rows i don't have anything down here
although now one two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen
the whole row one two eight nice that can be done that can be done okay this is done
i'm still not i think this is like an old timey camera i can look at 1800s that's done you
know one of those with the guy i got went underneath the drape and the powder and the
flash comes out leaves not very much left teen and then two three four five six one and one
oh yeah oh shit that's a roll of film okay cool no all right that's it that's it that's
it okay all right we're good we're good we're good that's it we're done we're done we're
good that's it we'll call it tonight look all right one more that's it last one this is the
absolute well final one no more after this 10 11 12 13 it's going to be the middle five at least
nine 10 11 12 it's gonna be like the middle three we're gonna be here forever no no we
want eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen so i can do the whole thing
see i'm doing this one quick this is the same deal nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen
fifteen so that's nine and three see look it's going quick same deal with this one two eight
three look at how fast this is going already one and then seven one two three four five six
seven and then five five seven okay plane is an airplane a sport okay filled in some other
ones here two seven two have you got six one two three four five six no it's one two three four
five six then four this way nine here five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen
fifteen this can hold this whole thing can be filled in okay so that's three this is also
has to be three then no no no no shit this is five what was just here three what was just here
okay that's one two three five three six nine four with god this is done
joel thinks he challenged him to a pogo stick game i did don't worry we'll we'll we're gonna
we'll raid joe that when this is done and i want him to know i want you to clip this
okay i think you got a clip of it already but i'll give a real a real concise clip here
joel i challenge you to a pogo rage with your friends challenge nobody knows
what no start over joel it's me germo just want to make sure you're aware of this
i'm coming after you with a gamer challenge here pogo stick rage with your friends blind
don't play it i want a screenshot of your steam game time on the game it better be zero
minutes here we go do you accept the challenge yes or no okay there it will rate him after
this we'll get the response by the way this is nine by the way this is five two two two two
five up here as well getting close and then we'll end it we'll get out of here he's
watching the clip right now oh god two six don't don't tell any of them what we're playing
because they're gonna come over here and be like this guy's playing like fucking
old people newspaper games and he thinks it can be joel in a pogo stick challenge
so this is part of the six isn't it yeah that's seven that's done this is seven five
well hold on one two three four five six seven now now i can do it two three four five
one two three four five six seven got it and there's the two and three is in here somewhere
right here one two three four five six seven one two three four five six one two three four
perfect he's did he just we responded by challenge joel fargo skeletor i'm surprised
he didn't call me vag skeletor but keep going to a gamer challenge stream of pogo rage with
your friends pogo over the mountain is he saying okay there's three questions here
i sound like such a dickhead ever gonna play uh pogo rage over the mountain i sound like an
asshole oh my god all right that's nine right there ten is right here one two three four five
six seven one two three four five two three four five six seven nine you did use your asshole voice
yeah i did but if you don't know who that is then you hear that clip you're like what the
fuck is this guy talking about what's wrong with this dude it's 11 four and this one's
also four but it might be up here he's singing me an acceptance song so wait he's singing
okay i'm ready i'm ready to hear this let's see how can i make see how can i fit sit i can fit
seven right here right two three four five six seven no no no this is already done it's right
here bingo one two three there's the two oh here's the six let's see oh god what the
fuck hold on let me turn this off take your challenge play this shitty game with you
wait what's he wait what is he doing he's not supposed to be playing i told him did you clip
up the zero minutes what the fuck do you mean i'll go stick that i can't wake up my neighbors
with going i hope he doesn't get evicted but he's uh he's he's playing it on stream
ready he's showing like a collage of him playing the game oh that's the trailer oh okay
all right well clipped it clipped this clipped it why can't i just like talk to him
well hey click this and you go tell him we gotta get a day we get a day we can start at the same
time sending messages yeah hey can you guys go pick my messenger for me it's almost done
tennis not a tennis ball all right bunch you guys got it good job all right that's gonna be
it that's a final final final final final truly final one we're gonna do the bits i'll see you
guys tomorrow i'm gonna try to do the sims 4 with first person and mods if it works it
works if it doesn't then we'll do something else and i'm gonna do the bits thank you everybody
for sticking around i know a lot of you guys were uh a lot of you guys stuck it up there's
almost six and a half hours of pit cross and i had a blast i thought it was fucking wonderful
glad to have all you guys's company good shit joel thinks i'm crying we'll clip him this
i just don't know i don't have this like email or anything i'm sorry i don't have his email so
i can't fucking talk he blocked me on twitter too i don't know why why i didn't do anything
okay that's that's pretty good now you can prove that i was crying all right i'll see you guys
tomorrow we'll do some of the bits we'll go through some bits what do you say sims 4 tomorrow
and then we'll get the gamer challenge set up i don't know let's see what is he was in the
chat he wants to join his chat as well we're gonna come over there right now we're literally
gonna raid over there in about 30 seconds is he streaming right now how come but he didn't
just record those clips and send them to us he's watching the stream right now
hey man what's up hey
you ready for that you fucking ready to get challenged man i got me bringing it to you
that's all i gotta say my eyes are puffy because i was out in the wind
he's looking windy today i'm not fucking crying whatever you are shut up but i'm around you want
to do this and i feel like i'm just talking can i watch his stream watch so i need to get his
reaction in real time because we can't we have to talk to each other here through streams
so i'm gonna watch his stream and we can talk that way he just sneezed in my fucking face
hey thanks a lot i really appreciate that and now i got an ad she will never forget this
look i'm making sure that i can you hear this okay let's see what we got with taking that stake
and i'm flipping it baby you think you can challenge me at pogo this draw you all right
jerma you might be listening right now and the audio no i don't care because it's the
challenge i accept your challenge and i'm gonna make you cry no you have to mute your screen
because when the ww super pythons comes you have to mute your stream when you say things
no i'm not muting my stream i'm not muting my stream for nobody all right you're not gonna
okay here we go listen if you think you want to fuck with me have you seen how big my arms are
that's fine you can yell as loud as you want i'm gonna do an arm wrestling competition i'll
fucking destroy you there's too many things happening thinks he's gonna pogo stick challenge
yeah get dumped on motherfucker thinks he's gonna pogo stick challenge yeah i'm taking that
pogo stick challenge i'm taking that pogo and i'm slamming it somewhere else oh where where
doesn't want to break tos doesn't want to break terms of service it's all about the
terms and service i'm gonna die i'll just say i'm gonna shove it as far as i can get it
you're gonna tell me that you can challenge your chimney master so then when you have a fire next
it's gonna fucking burn your house down comes up brother oh you better believe this stream
is the worst thing i've ever done oh okay so uh i think he said i think he said yes
i think uh yes is what we got out of that yeah just a taste for us to go
i think you agree yeah i agree too all right we're good 30 i'm not 35 years old yet okay you can
see you can use that joke in two or three years who is the other guy that's joel that is
joel we're about to raid them he wants to shake monsters no screaming he promises not to
scream are you sure okay no screaming no screaming no screaming okay all right here's here's what
i propose if you're listening jerma in 10 seconds we're gonna count down together we're
gonna scream in 10 seconds we're gonna shake on it and then we're gonna say like gentlemen
all right here we go nine eight seven six three two one shake hands
i'm gonna win you looser because when the works killer comes out oh yeah you better believe
that the master of the bogo comes out and you better believe that i'm gonna win oh yeah
mama mia i'm making that making that pepperoni deep dish pizza pie oh i'm making you in
oh i'm gonna take a crunch angle munch munch munch because germa ain't shit for the war
skeletor oh yeah well i mean i'm i mean i'm gonna i'm gonna do this a little more civilized
because like you know just i'll do it just showing the just the extreme low intelligence
of screaming i mean then why why screaming just the extreme low intelligence first of all i want
to say i accept your challenge and i'm being screamed at but i mean just i can just smell
the your iq has to be like 20 i mean mine's like 180 it's way higher than anybody you've
ever met in your whole life and i know that that's what i have an advantage here
it's a pretty good one i don't resort to screaming i don't resort to fucking yelling
at people i don't yell at people okay like somebody i know that the initial challenge
now you got me yelling listen my intelligence it's like a game and i've got the cheat codes
baby you better believe i'm loading up that playstation oh you're watching you're watching
the cam how's this for a cheat card left right b a start oh baby listen you've seen that zooming
on that on your screen oh you think you got that checked well guess what guess what
my biceps are so big they don't fucking have 69 on stream anymore they have fucking ultra
vorg scales or dimensions all right listen listen i'm gonna listen here's what's gonna happen
all right no no we don't do that listen no no listen anytime any day we're gonna do it no
no no no you don't deflected deflected whoosh whoosh left right baby super punch out listen
my internet's dying no deflection armor on deflection armor comes off no left down
this is a frickin morty stream which one of us is which
we're both morty no no way i refuse to believe that
but did you hear that i hope you understand that we're both apparently fucking morty
all right whoever wins the competition doesn't get to be morty i'm playing to be rick you know
what i'm saying okay okay joey said playstation he's on it what all right he wants to he wants
to be rick no no okay now he's listening listen listen okay no screaming this time
listen germa no screaming this time i accept your challenge okay hit me up on discord twitter
we'll work this out i don't have any of those then we see who has the bigger brain
and you better believe i'm not gonna yell but i'm gonna tell you i'm gonna win
okay i have me being i have skype i have i have the 2006 client for skype so you're
gonna have to get me through there i have the 2006 client listen here's what we're gonna do
if you want to do it old school then we're gonna say screw discord screw skype we're gonna
do this on icq or uh something really old so it sounds like we're talking through microwaves
all right and and the looser has to communicate through that client for the rest of the year
all right they get stripped of the privilege to smart each other oh my god aol aol you're
gonna be streaming from from an aol disk buddy okay not not yelling i told you but no
okay that's what we do all right so here we go we we can we now we smoke signals
so here's what's gonna happen i'm gonna mute my stream so we can hear you
uh first of all challenge is accepted person that loses is morty the person that wins is rick
it's huge stakes nobody wants to be morty everyone wants to be rick and that's i'll accept those
uh those terms and by the way we're coming to raid you in about like two hours so you better
be ready for a uh turbo 985 raid rick and morty isn't cool anymore i know i still don't
want to be morty listen listen i still don't want to be morty all right all right i'm getting out
of here i'm getting my streams over don't you see this the screen just bottle up all your anger
and rage and unleash it on me in like three days okay you want to see what's gonna happen
you ready for this okay tell tell germa tell germa to check check my stream out okay oh i see
oh it says germ says germ oh yeah okay i'm looking at germa over over oh he's putting
he's putting germa over over no what he's putting uh germa over stream so this is germa over okay
he's putting uh germa over screen i get it that's interesting stuff
are you typing are you typing in my stream no you're typing on your stream very equals boo
boo boo booger germa is a booger
all right well i unsubscribe from him so hey if you win i'll resubscribe
uh look hold on a minute wait wait wait wait hold on hold on a second here
let's go back to his stream watch this watch oh i'm gonna drop this shit on him right now check
this out oh no i'm not subscribed i never was no it says resubscribe what no i was only subscribed
for like two months a year ago oh shit now i look like a bad guy uh forget everything i just
said no i'm not wait are you would you ever subscribe to me to losers ha ha would you ever
subscribe to me yes i was but but i unsubscribe through my brain this time because i knew this
was coming i felt it like a you know like a spider feels rain you know it like it knows
like retract like that okay all right i'm gonna get out of here i'm gonna do my bit reading have
a good stream you're playing kid icarus no you're not that's that's that's you both have mushrooms
you're doing trash squad no now i look even worse somebody gifted joel and stuff
look you both have mushrooms you both both of your names on my followers let's start with a v
so i i went to the first one i thought it was you you're playing trash squad have a good
stream hope it's good chat rules please read the rules you have your own rule website but
no i hope you have a good stream for real i'll hit you up on uh discord i had you on twitter
we'll dm we'll get it ready i'm gonna move back over here now have a uh have a fantastic
rest of your night and you'll be playing sonnet the hedgehog 3d recreation snes madison
more lots of stuff going on over on joel's stream you'll see it really soon we rate them
all right i'm gonna move back over here have a good stream take care guys all right where
were we after i was screamed at i was yelled at and i had a look i lashed out i had to
i was put back in a corner and i was getting like
well of course i'm not gonna lash out a little somebody gifted me a sub for joel yeah
all right well now like no i he's somebody kissy kissy
let's see this a lot of stuff here get away from me yeah he's like what twitch password
no no never mind never mind what happened to p cross i beat it all i did every puzzle
all right back earlier let's go back find ourselves just about seven hours ago here
and we had we had man boy thanks for the two dollars and 50 cents man boy
not sure if you've seen it but uh cad has released the germa slots trailer here it is
i'm gonna hold off on that because i'm gonna i'm gonna start with that i want to i don't want
everyone to be you don't know about it yet probably gonna start with that over the next day
or two whenever it's actually released joel wants to talk again no even we've talked
we have talked no no i'm ending the conversation there i'm gonna kick i'm gonna kick your ass
you know what i mean when you and me fight on the battlefield so for me to kick your ass
i'm so glad somebody got that one person did i'm so glad one person thought that was funny
he meant on discord oh yeah i didn't i didn't start it again i didn't start it again i'm just
gonna keep going uh yeah the the slots game we're gonna play in whenever it's ready spend
a little while on it it looks really well done looks really fun but thank you man boy for the
250 c42 thanks for the 250 hype they say hype pogchamp picross hype he's calling you a booger
again i'm not even gonna i'm i ignore i'm gonna ignore i said my piece he wants to continue to
to
and he can i'm not gonna address it he's mocking me it's okay we'll see who gets the last laugh
time's up it's gonna be me after i win the competition he just called you short that's okay
once the uh
never mind forget it sad vega thanks for three bucks what the fuck are you doing i
don't know i've lost my mind completely no it's okay don't just don't respond here's the number
one thing about a bully is just don't give them don't respond he's gonna try to get me to go
on discord and yell at him and uh no i've reported him to the principal i've talked to
the teacher i talked to my mother about it what is happening i don't want to have to open up
his stream again and then what the fuck what are you doing now he's playing mind games with me
listen listen if we did a wwe um wd promotion thing like oh listen what i just did and i have
this on tape now i would have been like listen i respect germa i think he's a really cool
streamer and all that and uh i'd love to stream with him and i and i said nothing mean i said
uh i'd love to challenge you my friend and here like cut cut vhs cut to germa and he's just going
you know that's the same thing that i just did we just both did the same mocking sound how
is that possible oh yeah okay all right i'm done i'm done i'm gonna get out of here
did he hear me do that when i turned on the webcam i looked like fucking like a deer in
headlights but sad vacant thanks with three bucks getting to watch you from work i own
four thousand shares of jrm stock and only see big performance from it in the future
you've already mended me a few thousand dollars dollar dollar dollar you just said that out loud
well i didn't i said it a little differently uh the twitch docs yeah the twitch docs that
weren't really doing uh so well were they not recently kind of went down joel just called you
a stripper whatever that's a problem what's wrong with that okay chat called you a stripper
okay whatever hey carly brady thanks for the 10 bucks hey germa seeing you as you like pick
rods you should have a look at hex cells i think you'd like it as well love your work as always
thank you carly brady thank you thank you thank you also we have 40 from gorenhole thank
you gorenhole for the 40 bucks it's a lot of money thank you local streamer drinks pac-man
energy drink i'm going to shit my pants he says go vote wouldn't you go vote who would
in a wrestling match this is not fair no he's got he's he's got his like he just turned his
stream on he's got a fully energized chat room i just turned my stream off and we're just relaxing
and i don't have a fully energized chat room right now right at the very beginning of his
stream go fuck that poll up yeah oh fucking go fuck that poll up go make sure that doesn't
happen yeah make make make me win that poll on his stream you know what i mean right now
he's going like what the fuck what no it's like what 50 this impossible right now he can't believe
it oh look at this right now he can't he can't even believe it i'm sorry i can't rightfully
vote for you joel is huge and young it's not about truth it's about manipulation
and getting into his head so then on game day he's not prepared he said wait a minute
people didn't think i was gonna win and then i come up from the underdog and
scoop under i'm a dishonest politician this is not politics this is a fight this is a gamer
fight i'm not gonna well as you see our politics no no no no no this is we're trying to win
you play to win but thank you so much for the 40 going home cdt thanks to 250 cdt hey germa i've
been watching your video since 2012 which doesn't even feel that long ago can i get a
happy birthday since i'm 21 happy birthday thank you cdt for the 250 glad to have you around for
that long thank you so much for the two dollars and 50 cents much love thank you we also had uh
divas gave 250 thank you divas flug boy gave 250 thank you flug boy thanks for the chill
stream i needed to apt it today here's a king crimson to erase the time of your day
to relax better king su crimson i don't know i don't know what that is thank you for the
chill uh response though and thank you flug boy for the 250 i need to address the fact that
earlier the stream fiti gave five tier three community subs that's a lot of money tier three
is insanely expensive especially giving five of them away so thanks a lot tod florid thank
you for the 280 minesweeper is better it's just a different game joel calmed down and
said i was cool he's he's cool too we were just messing around i mean he's a good
thank you though c4g thanks for the 250 cancel my last bits uh on the pickross hype right
i remember that one uh thank you jack for the 250 turn on six hour slow mode teach chat a
lesson you know i think i think the six and a half hour pick cross stream was enough hey
fiti thanks for the 15 dollars on top of your five tier three subs sorry can you explain the
game again that was a little quick for me hopefully six hours later you figured it out
it's pretty easy but kind of difficult you kind of just need to know what's going on
war void thanks for the five dollars war void i enjoyed that thanos with a stroke impression
that was so long ago i forgot i forgot even doing that derma lied about minecraft vr and
somebody's username i'm doing minecraft vr i told you that was still happening
i'm still doing that your username is is completely irrelevant i'm going to play
minecraft in vr i never said i wasn't doing that topac thanks for the three bucks topac
not sure if you spoke about this already but any word on why save was removed is unfortunate
to kill the off-stream chat uh i kind of wanted to clean up the off-stream chat a little
bit i think a lot of people were kind of just putting commands in and there's some i think
there was a couple people that had like scripts or something to like just run in the offline
chat i'd rather just people be able to talk and it was an old kind of meme old joke from
more than almost a year or two ago he saved them all there they were like there was you
saved 73 000 seagulls you saved every seagull on earth why not let it reach 100 000
because there's not 100 000 seagulls on earth there's only 73 428 you got them all the zoo
is packed yeah there was too many seagulls in that zoo but i cleaned up some commands
there's you know i'm just doing just doing a cleanup of kind of nightbot commands random
bot commands but that's pretty much the reason why talk about the game oh yeah i did act
not that's not necessarily to counteract the fact that i got rid of that but i turned on that
streamer legends game it's that like idling rpg game where you get loot and you fight together
i figured maybe something with like offline chat or before a stream starts might be
worth just playing around and being able to talk about and hang out i know some other
streamers have it on figured it would just something to just have you can pop it out
you can play it there's oh what the fuck i'm what i gotta give the loot i gotta give i'm
only gonna do this once i'm not i'm gonna okay by the way i still had jules stream up
uh i could give people loot right now hold on if you have it open right now uh i'm gonna give
you like a treasure chest i'm definitely not gonna do this all the time because i'll forget
every day all right you ready here it comes send gifts bingo well it's just something fun
to have this doesn't cost any money or anything it's just there if you want to play
with it you get gold for killing monsters and you can contribute together as a community
to upgrade the barracks and upgrade the base it's just like a little dinky rpg game
but it's just gonna be there what's it called they're called stream legends stream legends
it's all the way to the bottom of the page i sort of hit it so it was a little uh you
know off so it wasn't kind of taking up any real estate on the rules and anything so
can you move it further up so we can watch the stream here's the thing you can pop that window
out that window has a pop out you can put it anywhere you want on any monitor on any page
a little button but thank you topec sorry about the seagulls hey smelly boy thanks for the
three dollars germa pluto me sad me brain too small for smart streamer game me have no life
purpose thank you tavasi for the 15 dollars local streamer spends 40 minutes yelling at
children about how much smarter he is children what do you mean i didn't yell i yelled i told
joe that he had 20 iq i don't know if that was true or not i'm just remember manipulation
under the skin tactics on game day he's gonna fucking it's gonna get to him i'm just gonna
drink two red bulls and be ready the pac-man ones but thank you tavasi for the 15 dollars
hey man boy thanks for the 250 they say this stream in a nutshell
uh-huh jesus christ thank you thank you d jack for the 250 you're acting so
odd today i feel like the real germa died hours ago and this is just air escaping
watching who gave five community subs thank you watching who for the five community subs
no i was just like i was nutrient sized today i had a bunch of b vitamins i had some
caffeine i had a good frozen dinner but thank you watching who for the five community subs
appreciate it robot jones thanks for the 250 hello there my name is jones from whatever
happened to robot jones i challenged garfield to a cartoon challenge who has a better story
i don't know what robot jones is i'm sorry uh then we have uh bakers takers for the 250
they say uh germa isn't this the best star wars background isn't this star wars background
awesome star wars news dot stop what the fuck is this website star wars news net dot com
should i click this star wars news net is your source for news covering everything from the
films tv shows novels what is this that sounds pretty sketchy that star wars news net
dot com why is it not just star wars news dot com or star wars star wars info virus
oh it's a it's just a okay it's a background i hope you like it download ram it's like some
explosions the uh the tie fighters are flying by pretty cool bakers takers gave another
ten dollars here as well see what bakers takers has to say so germa will you ever play grand
theft auto four will you ever replay it i mean that update happened with the radio last year
wouldn't it make sense if you just replayed it i mean you forgot the swing set glitch what's
inside the statue of liberty gta3 artwork etc here's what's inside the statue of liberty
uh i know it's inside the statue of liberty i've been inside of it swing set glitch i've
did the swing set glitch me star did the swing split swing swing swing set glitch
like six years ago it's fun but thank you bakers and takers bakers takers thank you uh thank you
uh anonymous cheer for 750 here and five dollars and five dollars again so that's from anonymous
cheer thank you that's a lot of money appreciate it uh but uh answer the question
about going back to gta4 uh probably not gta4 i played so much of it star and i played that
game for so many hours that i don't think i could see anything in that game that i haven't
seen yet we modded the fuck out of that game we played the hundreds and hundreds and hundreds
of fucking hours probably just dicking around and doing stuff and i played through the story
at least two or three times so i had a lot of fun that's one of the best
multiplayer experiences i've probably ever had uh but thank you uh also what for the five bucks
jeremy you made me feel like such an asshole i don't actually have a dog i was making a dumb
joke i guess everyone must have their one guy moment somewhere the other well what what happened
the dog i mean i made a dog comment i don't remember what it was i don't actually have a
dog i was making a dumb joke what did i say something about the dog oh the dog going crazy
comment oh hey bro luck thanks for the 250 uh the other night your discord got rated my mate
recorded some of it yeah i'm aware i am aware of it thank you though there was some weird
weird shit going on it was pretty bad no not the savory dog smell thing but it's been it's
been taken care of it's all good don't worry about it everything's all good but thank you
bro luck appreciate it snoozing copter thanks for the 250 jerma what were you thinking when
you called your stream ultimate relaxation get fucked into bed what no i had a t
is this a dick what is this no all right what is this it's me as a teacher and this actually is
for real now i drew it a while back let's see uh in my free time i like to do a little
germa 95 related content oh that's the that's the survive that's the germa survival isn't
fucking awesome thank you snoozing copter i like the design on the uh survival gear it's good shit
hey zorro carlos thanks in three bucks you mentioned marijuana being legal in las vegas
i actually went on vacation in las vegas for the first time last week and it was really fun
however the one thing i hated was how every fifth pedestrian in the city spat out a cloud
of either cigar smoke or weed on my face and i got a little obnoxious very fun trip regardless
seems like a nice place to live too uh it is yeah i mean i think i mean those also might be
like vape pens you know those are fucking everywhere uh let me tell you about a stream
that i'm not going to do that i thought was potentially funny spoiler alert for like a
future stream that's not going to happen because i like axed it i was going to play fortnight
in a tank top and just have loud blasting music have kind of like a odd weird shitty
camera setup just ripping a fucking vape pen just like
and eventually what you don't see i don't really talk that much what you don't see
is over the course of about an hour or two i have like four fog machines that are slowly
going to be used and turned on until the whole room is filled with fog and there is
no joke that's that's the whole joke like i just i just turn my head like this i go like
this shit like this is a fucking shoot this thick fucking cloud over here right all the
while like smoke is just filling this room tons of it to a point you can't even fucking see
my face it takes like two hours for it to happen you know like all right wait wait
where we dropping for like fucking two straight hours and eventually the smoke alarm was going
to go off like and i was going to keep playing for like another 30 minutes and then
eventually the stream was just going to turn off without me saying bye now i'm sad that it
didn't happen well i was going to do it in the studio i wasn't going to do it like here
why was it cancelled you want to be honest because i was going to have to play fortnight
for two hours not even shitting you that's just why come on that hasn't been a full-on
dress-up joke stream in a while maybe i'll still do it just don't tell anybody hey
lightning rider thanks for the five bucks this has been the most uncomfortable stream so far this
year why what i've played pickross for like a few hours uncomfortable thanks for the five bucks
though thank you something or other for the 250 is it true that your middle name is sherbert
um no my middle name is not sherbert i don't know where you got that info from thank you
mostly lost for the 250 i just got a minor headache from that lawyer up chump mostly lost
again thanks for the 250 just kidding i was constipated and that cured me thanks you're
welcome you're very welcome smelly boy thanks for the three bucks you're playing minecraft tracks
oh how far the mighty have fallen did you hear did you not hear what i said after that
slow it down if you slow it down enough and you really listen i think you can faintly hear
something like this is dog shit right you got to listen really close and you have to it's
very very faint you have to play it backwards too hey 420 squid thanks for the four dollars
please play stall by c4 18 it'll make my night sorry i didn't see it i don't didn't really want
this to turn into a music stream unfortunately so sorry kind of turned into that halfway through
somehow somehow sometimes we just turn the stream into a i'm going to say a track out
loud and then jeremy is going to turn and just spam it into youtube and play it what's wrong
with minecraft music minecraft music is amazing it's fantastic it's very calming very
wonderful it's very relaxing stuff it was one of the grit that when when it rains in minecraft
for the first time and you get that rain song oh it was great you know you're sitting in your
first ever dirt house raining outside fire behind you i don't have a problem with it at
all so then play it then dumbass this is dog shit but that was just me i'm just kidding i
don't really think that i mean that song was i don't really like it that much it was okay
hey freudian weapon thanks for the 250 freudian pretty sure you've cursed my ears 10 times over
thanks but seriously though i'm super relaxed right now despite the headaches and gamma rays
fucking gamma rays man hey mostly lost thanks for the 250 i guess while we're on the topic
of meme songs this masterpiece by kiwo deserves more love people made a meme song
oh
it is backwards
so she sang the song backwards and then reversed the backwards to make it
cue up with the music this okay i've done shit like this before with one or two sentences
it took like 40 minutes this is a two minute song that you had to cue up this probably took
all day and matching it to the music
so
okay you know when you give a small child a microphone set like a three-year-old for
christmas and they play songs and they put the microphone right up to their mouth and
they start to sing whatever the song it is
pretty close
it was great it was really actually fucking great thank you most of us really appreciate it
uh anonymous cheer again came in three four five five dollars fifty cents thank you anonymous
cheer no messages or anything just money dumped into the stream thank you uh crustily bustily
thanks for the 10 bucks germa this has been one of your most thinking streams ever hopefully you
can beat all the puzzles this is more stressful than amber's murder case and hitman absolution
so did you talk with the guy who keeps ban evasioning streams um think about ban evasion
she's gonna be careful joel is still at it oh god it's been like an hour but no i'll tell
you if you break the rules and you keep trying to circumvent rules you're just gonna get banned
that's what's gonna happen i'm sorry that's the way it is it's joel
no he is he's definitely not still he just compared me to sonic sonic's really fast
one of the most popular video game characters has a cool voice i'm okay with that that's fine
also really small he's not that small sonic the hedgehog is tall enough
he's photoshopping movies he's are you declaring war right now fine i'll take a declared war
i got war he dropped the short bomb okay planet side 2 stream 4 000 versus 4 000 joel versus
gerbas chat we tried that before and it was a nightmare we did that with like a few hundred
people and we almost broke the game hey jess you got a thanks for the 250 i get my 50 badge after
this it's crazy how much it adds up here's to 50 more it's not a lot comparatively and
i know i don't have to give you any money but i'll give you as much as i can because
i know it's going to projects for our entertainment you're generally the best much love painting
should be done in a week or two thanks so much jess any amount of money that people give
this channel it means a lot and i'm gonna try to you know use it for streams use your video
stuff you guys are incredibly generous so thank you seriously and then we had a few from mostly
lost 250 some would say this is an experiment like twitch plays pokemon but it's really just
a game of chicken between you and chat well here's the thing chat cheated and i cheated
halfway through you guys cheating so is that i mean it is kind of chicken i guess
but i didn't i just played sound you could mute the stream that's not cheating
i was blasting fucked up sound effects all you had to do is press the little speaker
button and that was it you guys had the full entire textbook cheat sheet prove that
we cheated i had people was spamming a link that showed every dot i have the proof it's
already there yeah you would be in a dick bag whoa what i saw the i saw it i saw it oh my goodness
thank you creel for the five dollars we can fill lines as well pogchamp pogchamp pogchamp
pogchamp bunch of pogchamps don't challenge chat without explicit rules if you're going
to change the rules i'm sorry that don't cheat on the exam is not a given that's not a given
do not pull up the answer and cheat what do you mean that's not a given you get banned from every
online multiplayer game if you cheat if you cheat in your classroom you're going to get
detention you're going to get your parents called in cheating cheating we used our notes
that we brought no no no no no no no i don't think so i don't think so this is not a
class i should have named it classroom it's my mistake still gonna play minecraft vr it's
still happening hey hazy thanks for the five dollars hazy your latest youtube video is a
work of art phenomenal streamer you can thank the two very talented editors that put those
together so thank you hazy for the five dollars and thank you to mac and effectator
for their very very very high quality work for real hey syrock thanks for the 250 sore loser
i uh i didn't i'm still doing it i'm doing minecraft i'm doing minecraft if you guys are
acting like i said i know you cheated therefore i'm not doing it i'm still doing this yeah fine
i'll have a cider i will i'm not gonna i can't recreate the whole thing that takes i'm gonna
have to memorize everything but thank you lightning rider for the 250 while the first half
of the stream made me feel very uncomfortable the second half was amazing what happened to
the first half of the stream i'm making people uncomfortable the first half what did i do hey
future gamer thanks for the 250 recently decided to document all the major rooms by your arch
nemesis the vroomer decided to clip all the big rooms oh my god are you shitting me
that's so funny are we going to get a vroom compilation here
uh i look forward to your endeavor thank you future gamer for your contribution to the vroomer
that's like bird watching uh trotter thanks for the 250 greetings mr streamer man i found
the beginning of this stream to be rather amusing and decided to illustrate a short bit
you did don't ever break me what happened to my arm where's my arm where are my fingers
did i make a joke about like me getting my arms and hands like bit off or something
get it get this one that's a long one hey garfield the monday killer thanks for the
250 garfield thanks to you and mac for including me in the latest second germa video
it was such a shock to garf system i don't know what i did to deserve such a high
honor was it my sheer amount of garfographs i'm glad my dumb rick and morty message got
read if it means anything to you germ you'll always be rick to me if this gives you a
leg up on the competition tell them you have a garfield the cat consistently donating money
to you in hindsight that might be a disadvantage don't tell them germa lied about minecraft vr
thanks for the 10 bucks please don't play that game again thank you for the 10 dollars
germa lied about minecraft vr i never did i where are you guys getting this from
when did i ever say i wasn't going to do minecraft vr you guys you guys all in vegas
smoking weed did you forget ow hey be where i live thanks for three bucks by the way thank
you but uh germa lied about minecraft vr thank you 10 bucks thank you it's a lot of money
appreciate it be where i live thanks for three bucks germa i saw your ps2 stream and i saw
that you got the wrong shooter game with a real-time 12-hour timer the game you were
looking for was wind back damn it i knew it existed i can't cling thanks to the five bucks
watching your stream on my phone and i dropped my phone in the toilet and now it's completely
bricked worth it though stream was a lot of fun i'm so sorry to hear that you gotta be careful
that's why if you're sitting down on the toilet and you're watching something on the toilet
knees together come on knees together i'm sorry for that happening though thank you so much for
the five dollars hopefully you can get a replacement phone i was pissing oh oh oh that
sucks i'm sorry to hear that man and then finally jack thank you jack for the 250 was
that teespring merch link legit if it is you should plug it yeah you know it is i have a
teespring store like this look there it is now don't fall for any of the bullshit ones i know
that like sometimes when you have a link at least on reddit or on you know twitter and stuff
there's bots that come and say oh that one didn't work check out this one this is the
right link no no it's this one that's the only one i have internet's been holding up
pretty well holy shit there were a lot of subs uh internet's been like really good lately
i'm happy about it you're gonna play artifact no let me queue up let's get ready to go to uh
jules spring and talk a bunch of shit you know what i mean but be nice about it though
artifact has like 200 players well serves you right valve you've got like four or five ips
you could make games on that people are so desperately waiting for and you make a card
game five years late come on that might be that call me rude but seriously who wanted artifact
nobody wanted that game take any franchise that valve has any of them i don't care which one
ricochet 2 would be more well received you got so many great franchises i mean what is
he just is it just the dota 2 thing there's a shitload of dota 2 players and look what
happened the auto chess comes out they scooped that fucking whole thing up i'm not even talking
about uh their main main staple friend like it wasn't left for dead three in development for like
six years or seven years or something i thought there was like a left for dead three leak
like four and a half years ago what happened to that they just they cancel it uh that auto
chess game actually looks pretty fun i don't know a damn thing about it but it just looks
interesting looks like the old school warcraft 3 mods remember when you were playing metal gear
and you said you hated us i do i don't remember an apology no you're taking me out
context i never said that i love you guys i mean the thing is i could we can talk about valve
well why do you ever make no games valve what the heck what the hell they didn't have a lot
to do with the vibe i mean the vibe the hardware the vibe is just it's great i know
it's htc but they had a lot to do with it didn't they didn't didn't valve didn't have
anything to do with the with the vibe i thought that they were part of the so i mean
you could talk shit about where is tf3 they've been doing other stuff just video games are not
what they're even up in into anymore at all they got the steam they get the business
stuff on lockdown completely yeah valve is not the only company with issues no and i'm
just saying it as a salty fucking asshole i would say the same shit about blizzard i like
loved all their games all blizzard games all valve games oh my god this is amazing i can't
wait to see what they do next so i am just a salty e asshole you know what i mean stuck in
the past but uh that's gonna be it i'll see you guys tomorrow starting you know that same window
between three and four p.m pacific i had a lot of fun i thought it was a great stream
it was a bit relaxing very fun see you tomorrow we're gonna try the sims 4 first person
don't know how long we're gonna try it for but we're gonna try it and i'll see you
tomorrow let's queue up the raid to joel what are they even playing what is he playing
he's doing like sonic some weird sonic adventure game or something let's just see all right here
we go all right see you guys tomorrow thank you everybody for the subs and the resubs and all the
bits you guys are fucking awesome thank you again so let's go ahead and raid i gotta get
his name right varg varg skelethor rating varg skelethor cube if you'd like to go and say hello
see you tomorrow take care much love ta ta for now