Hello there. How's it going? How you been? I can finally finish laundry now. Ooh laundry day.
All right. Sunflower reveal. Oh yeah. Not right now. I'm gonna have to make you wait for it.
You're gonna have to wait around for it. That's we're doing that at the end of the stream.
I keep my engagements up the whole day. Now good to see you. I go over the plan this week.
We'll talk about it. Are you gonna play Pikmin 4? Since you loved 2 so much. Um,
I don't know. I'd like to play Pikmin 4 but I don't know. Maybe not on stream. I don't. Everyone
thinks I hate Pikmin in the whole franchise. I don't. You're referring to complaints I had
about the Wiimote and how I was annoyed at the Wiimote controls. That's what that was. I really
enjoy Pikmin. I think it's a great franchise. I think it's an amazing group of video games.
I just had an issue with the way the Wiimote was. Okay. He hates Pikmin. Yeah whatever. All
right so here's the plan. Today I'm gonna finish Trippang 2. Just gonna play it and hang out.
I'm at the last mission but there are at least three or four side missions. I'd like to do at
least a few of them. There's also wacky cheat codes that I would like to do. So we're not
quite done with Trippang yet. This Sunday, the plan this Sunday is, well I actually forgot to
tell you too, and we're gonna go over the sunflowers. It's not just sunflowers by the way. We went ham
this year. We got marigolds. We got wildflowers. We got sunflowers. There's a whole fucking ecosystem
over here. You raised pigs. All right so yeah we'll do that. I'm very proud of what we've done.
They look wonderful. You said you're gonna play viewfinder when it comes out. It's out right now.
I'm gonna give you the what's what's happening on Sunday. Let me talk. On Sunday
I'm gonna play Team Fortress 2. Gonna play TF2 on Sunday. I'm gonna just kind of see. I'm gonna gauge
kind of how I like it. I'm interested in checking it out. I did mention a month or two ago at least
that I've had the itch to play like man versus machine TF2. So why not? Why not do it on Sunday?
We're gonna play it for like an hour or two, get back into the swing of things,
see if I like it, and maybe I'll keep playing it. After that we're gonna play viewfinder. So we'll
give it a little we'll give it a little try this Sunday. Not on Sunday. That's the day I'm watching
Barbie. Oh sorry. That's the plan. That's gonna be the worst stream of the year.
Why? I don't think you like TF2 then. Of the whole year? Why? What the heck? Is
Gunu gonna make another debut? No. Gunu is in one game. You should ban him. Hey I'm that's just you
that's an opinion of the stream. That's an opinion of the stream. I cannot change that opinion.
I can just scream at you. Okay anyways you guys ready? Last mission. I don't think I'm
gonna do the last mission yet. I think it's probably a good idea too because I haven't
played in like a week or two. I think it's a good idea. Is this good? Let's see if it's too loud.
Is it too loud? Can we check? How is that? Is that bad? That's all right. Shotgun's a little louder.
Seems all right. All right let me remember the buttons. I got that's the slide. That's grenade.
That's obviously that. H is to do well. I got Q is I believe slow down time and F is cloak. Okay I'm
good. We want to hear your loudest scream. I don't think I can't scream loud. Anytime I scream try to
scream loud or anything if I ever try to it just kind of goes oh it just kind of turns into like
an air horn that you press too hard like or like a you know what I mean like my voice just breaks
when I try to yell. You turn into a toy chicken. Yeah that's what I mean. All right so I'm not
going to do the final mission. I have been told that prep hang two has some really really good
side content side missions. We're going to take a look. We haven't done any of them. We've done
none of them. So what is left for us to do? Wait didn't I do this? Didn't I do site 83? Did it not
save? Is one of these new? Yeah it did. Green is the side missions. Yeah but is this shouldn't there
be shouldn't this one be open? Oh wait no that's also a side mission. All right so where's the
campaign mission? Where's the next camp? This one here then. Okay that's the one that's blinking.
All right let's do let's do crash site. Destroy the crashed plane's cargo or unidentified structure
in the United States. Which one of these is good? People said there's a couple of really good ones.
This one here unidentified structure. Oh yeah let's go. Satellites tracked three armed individuals
running in separate directions from the structure this morning at 3 30 a.m. I know how to read it.
Identified as Horizon from their uniforms. By 8 20 a.m. all three had expired from exhaustion
or exposure to the elements. Investigate the structure. Satellite scans initially detected
four or five. All right so we just go investigate the structure. I got it. We're doing it on hard.
We plan on hard. I'm good to go. Don't call the sus guy at 3 30 a.m. You can read a clock pog.
It gets a little weird once you go over. Okay once you once you go over I think 1800 hours.
My brain has trouble because okay oh 600 hours. That's 6 a.m. 1200 that's noon. Okay 1300 is one.
1400 is two. 15 is all right 1500 is three. 1600 hours is four. You know what I mean? It's
already I'm already I got it already fucked up already. I already I already have it fucked up
already is literally just everything minus 12. Yeah but I don't want to do any math. I don't
want to do math. I am an a.m. p.m. Andy because like I just I don't know. It's just easier for
my brain to understand. American. I'm an a.m. p.m. Andy. I am. Are you scared that the sus guy
in quotes is going to be uttered at your funeral? No no I don't I don't think so. I don't think
that's happening. I think it's going to be more about like hey like let's that no one's going to
talk about the sus guy at my funeral. I'm not even going to give that one a response. Okay what
guns do I want to take? I actually like these two. I like shotgun and I like um but should I
take the sniper? Give me armor. Give me flash bangs. Bolt launcher was pretty sick especially
when you do this. All right I'm going to take this and then also this. I like the smg. I'm going to
do dual smgs. I take this with me right? I think so. Are you going to add derma dumpy butt naked
emote? Uh I thought about it but no. I'm just thinking like what how much um what it would do
for me. All right let's go. All right let's turn the audio up for me. Test one more time.
Jump button works. All right let's go. Why do you read the worst chat messages? Sometimes what you
think is the worst chat message to me is something that I think is funny to read out loud. So I mean
there's that. But there's also here's the problem. You also don't want to make it. You don't want to
make it a thing where it's like oh I'm going to read I'm going to read like the wacky comment
out loud because then you start getting copycats. Oh I he's got to read my message. I'm going to say
something fucking crazy. That's why I can't tell you the secret sauce because then you know you
got to have it naturally. All right so the goal is there's people in this building or they ran away
from this building. Is there something in here? Is there like a monster? Let's find out. That scared the
fuck out of me. I forgot how loud that was. You could even see my mouse move. Did it move? Did I
go like okay whatever. Turn that down. Okay I'm gonna I actually am because that was pretty bad.
This should be all right. What's this? To patrol team when you're back meet us at the vault entrance.
We haven't heard from the eggheads in two days. The vault is locked. We're gonna breach it and
check. Can I break into this? Yeah what's in here? Okay this is kind of this is like a safe room.
There's the burp. Oh do I want to take this? I'm happy with these. It's a gamer room.
Or kind of as a gamer room. It's all right. Go down. This is gonna be a monster that's in here
somewhere. This is gonna be the monster going into the fridge and like drinking out of the
fucking milk. I'm gonna catch him and it's gonna go. What was that? What the fuck was that?
I'm not even scared. All right what does this say? Feeling uncertain about any progress. The others
are mostly keeping me in the dark but had a good conversation with Dr Partridge yesterday. He seemed
unusually interested in my books especially the ones pertaining to my faith. I lent him an entire
bag of books to satiate his curiosity. It will be interesting to chat with him next time. I'm going
I'm taking this one out first. I okay I'm very aware of my nose right now and I hate it. You know
you know exactly what I'm talking about right? Right now in the game I'm very aware of my nose
and it's I'm looking down at it. I can see it. I can see my nose right there. Oh what the hell.
More intel. In game? Yeah in game but also that that's kind of what happens in real life. When
you become aware of your nose. Just wait it is just right there. I can see it. Big nose gang. I kind
of have a big nose. Yeah all right first sign of blood. What's going on here? Okay trial and error.
We've just decrypted the data encoded within the DNA of the biomass sample. The biomass exhibits
a remarkable ability to alter its own genomic sequence in response to the input data. Okay
limited internet access. The lack of availability training is okay. Mechanism underlying the
encryption scheme employed by the biomass is unusual. Okay I don't know why I don't know why
read this right to left down to up. Do you notice that is what I just did? That was kind of weird.
I don't know why I did it like that. All right well whatever this looks promising. Oh shit okay
is it gonna be like a weird person in here? Oh god what is oh that's the biomass.
This is kind of a maze. I'm gonna this something's gonna attack me. All right I gotta be ready.
Something growling like a coffin. System initializing training sequence with data set 41.
Unknown economic collapse poverty the end of civilization. Unknown the end is near. System
error unexpected output detected running diagnostics. The end is inevitable. Data corruption
identified data set 41. Contents replaced with unauthorized data by user A partridge. Unknown
apocalypse destruction the end of all things. Emergency such as everything's going absolutely.
This thing's moving. I put a fucking hole in its head. What do I do? Oh my god it's talking. All
right this thing over here is blinking. I'm gonna press this button. Shut it down. What the fuck is
happening? Did I win? This is gonna be some Slenderman bullshit. Look at there's like five
TVs to turn off. Oh my god I'm just gonna run. I think I'm just gonna run over there. This is
actually gonna be horrible isn't it? Just go go go go as fast as you can. Oh what's that? Is that a
pencil? What's this giant pencil? Why is there a giant goofy novelty pencil? Am I looking for that?
It's the spear from the spear gun. Oh okay all right all right all right all right.
The thing is huge. Fuck you game. All right I'm just running. Whatever.
Something's gonna be right here. Yeah nice spoiler auto save. Oh god I think this
goes for a grenade over here. There's one more TV right in the middle. This thing's gonna get up.
Oh okay okay okay okay okay. It's behind me. It's definitely right behind me. It's right behind me.
It's right behind me. What's going on? Why is everything so quiet? Why is everything so silent?
What's going on? That was scarier because it was so quiet. What do I do? This this no audio. Uh oh
I think I broke it. I don't know what I did. I think I'm dead. Where do I go? Let's go. Wait what
did that say? Shit. Okay I think I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I have to turn these off.
That's actually scarier than a loud sound. Just off-putting. All right is this it? There's only
one more. What the fuck was that sound? Turn it off. Got it. Do I fight that thing? Ah this sound.
I think I did it. Nothing else to do right? I don't have any ammo left. There's got to be
something else I have to do. Jump into it? I don't know. I don't know what to do. Leave now? I thought
the door is locked isn't it? Oh shit it's open. I this was locked. I have one bullet. Um oh god
they're behind me. Give me my audio back. There's nothing. There's no bullets in this gun either.
All right we're good. What the fuck is going on? What? Is this us? Is this us? Is this us? Is this
our team? Where are they? All right all right all right. You can't get in here. I got a lock on the
door. What are you doing? Turn it off. What the fuck? How many do you have? What does this do?
What? What? You? What the fuck just happened? Uh hey. Oh it's intel. Okay. PhD. Computer science. 62.
PhD. 46. PhD. Okay. Personnel list. All right. I gotta be ready. Okay this thing's dirty. Where's
he? Where's he? Where's he? Where the hell's this guy? Oh there he is. I just took out all your men.
I'm right here. I'm out here. This is that guy. That guy's a sniper. I'm literally standing still
and he can't even hit me. Who actually sucks at this game? Look at this. You can't even hit me.
All right. There we go. I'm going up top. This gotta be a sniper. What the fuck is happening?
Okay. Ow. What the fuck? They're at every angle. Single digit accuracy. Dude I'm being flanked at
all sides by guys in Omega armor. I'm going back. There's health in here. You can't even see me from
there. What is shooting? Well get in here then. Stop just firing. Get in here. What game are we
playing? I'm one person in here. Yeah. Shit. I need a sniper rifle. I can't shoot. They're all
surrounding me from every angle with laser pointers. I need a rifle. I have a weapon that
is effective at like 15 feet range and then this thing is empty. I gotta. I'm going up top.
Hurry. Go, go, go, go, go. Quick. I gotta get up there quick. All right. I want to go up, up, up,
up, up. But being outside is death. I need to go up. Who the fuck is this guy? I don't. This is
not even firing bullets, guys. What the? All right. Is there a rifle? There's gotta be a rifle
up here. It has to be. There's no way there's not a rifle up here. Is that a? Kind of? No. You.
What? Where's the rifle? You're holding a rifle? Ah, there we go. Now it's time for me to fuck up
everybody. Watch this. How do you aim? How do you zoom in? How do you, how do you zoom in with the
rifle? Anybody know how to zoom in? How do you zoom in? That's it? Oh, is it E? Where is this
guy? What's going on over here? What is going on over here? Why would they? I'm confused.
He's mad. No, I, that was really weird. Get this smoke out of my fucking eyes. This guy sucks.
I'm fighting an entire team of legendary warriors right now. Okay. Where are you? Where? What the
fuck are you doing though? Don't scare me. Dude, are you zonked right now? No, no. It's just this
every angle is people and this smoke every, I need a gun. I need a gun. I need a gun.
Give me a gun. This dude is so high right now. I, I know I'm not. Yeah. Got him. Anybody else?
What? All right. We're good. Who else? Okay. Okay. All right. All right. Here he comes.
Why is he so fast? Why is he so fast? Why is he so fast? What the fuck? There's so many people.
What the hell? So many people, dude. I got, oh my God. That guy was useless. I got him.
What was wrong with that guy? All right. We're good. All right. All right. All right. Oh my God.
When do I win? That's gotta be it. That's not it. There's more. This guy's got a grenade launcher.
Is that his head? You need to relax. Just a game. It's not just a game. It's an intense experience.
Can I have that grenade? Somebody said take the grenade launcher. Can I take it? That was intense.
He's literally on a secret mission. Well, it's a side mission. Did I do it? That was crazy.
Defend the fort. There's a gun mod in the house. I did see that. Where, was this thing armed?
It didn't go off. He was on top of a shelf. Yeah. That was a fun one. That was a good one.
What about the other side missions? Any other good ones?
Snipers bastard off the hbt board. Do the oil rig this way. What's going on in here? What the hell
was that? Well, actually, what was that? That was weird, wasn't it? Okay. Um, any more unlockables?
We keep the red shoes for sure. And fall rain. Let's just do fall rain. According to reviews,
there's more wave shootouts to come in the side missions. That's all right though. Site 32 is
caved in. All right. We just did this one. What's another good one for the side content? Oil rig is
locked, but it's really good. Okay. Do crash. Crash site is fun. Destroy the crashed plane's cargo.
That sounds cool. I'll do it. Our forces downed a Horizon airplane. It was carrying high tech
weapons to be sold to an African warlord. Find the cargo and make sure it's destroyed. Unfortunately,
it crashed into a former nuclear testing site in Algeria. The air is heavily irradiated. So watch
your Geiger counter. Oh, I didn't even mean to do that, but I did for weapons. I think I want,
I need long range and short range. That's been my problem. That's my issue. What is a good long
range? Let me just take the rifle. You don't need long range. Just run faster. I'll, I'll take the
rifle. I think this thing's pretty versatile. Do I want to do anything to it? No suppressor. Laser
sight, I feel like gives me away too much. All right. All right. Now for the short range. Can
you do aim down sights in this game? You can not unless it is, you have a scope on it or some type
of aim down sights thing on the weapon. Pistol. Okay. Somebody said, I fucking hate this dinosaur.
Why was this? What's this dinosaur? What's this? Dino dance was a dinosaur. You guys don't like the
Dino dance. I figured you guys would like the Dino dance. This is a dancing community. We have
six or seven different dancing emotes. All right. I'm going to, I'm going to do shotgun, shotgun
rifle. In fact, we're going to go, we're going to double shotgun. Even though I don't like this,
I'm going to do it because I'm trying to make the fans happy. Incendiary unfolded. How do I
switch to the other weapon? Can I do the other weapon? Oh, that was weird. There we go. All right.
Now we're good. This thing is going to be destructive. Full ammo. I've got flash bangs,
armor. Good to go. It has the other attachments on already if you do weld. Ah, okay. That's good to
know. It didn't look like it though. I had laser on one of the SMGs and it wasn't on the other one.
This is the hardest level in the game. Okay. This is the hardest level in the game. Hey,
I'm up for a challenge. Let's go. Somebody talking. What is all this? There is a sniper rifle here.
All right. I have an idea. I'm just going to, I'm going to come back and pick this weapon up.
Remind me that it's here because I'm definitely going to do some sniping here like this.
That was so bad. I have to restart the whole thing. I missed five shots in a row. I have to restart
the entire mission. Honestly, I should verify, I should verify integrity of game cache on steam.
Just, I feel like, I feel like I fucking corrupted the game being that bad. Okay. Let's go. I need
to put a suppressor on this. Suppressor. Okay. Here we go. I should be able to do this pretty
easily now. Easy. All right. Where else? Where's everybody else? There's a guy over here. Where is
this guy? The guy is just spinning around with his flashlight. What's this guy doing in here? Hey,
you tell me this is the hardest mission in the game. I'm going to listen. Okay. I'm doing this
the way I want to do it. I ain't, I ain't messing around. Ooh, nice. Weapon pot. Homing. Ooh. All
right. I don't think I need this anymore. I'm going to take this because this is pretty short
range. So I'm going to stick with this. I also have the double shotguns. I'm being here. I'm
going to see if I can. Oh my. What happened? Oh my God. What? Yeah. They did.
Oh, I'm the shotgun guy. I don't know how to. Where's my supplies? Wait, what? That's an enemy
right there. That's got to be, that would have to have been terrible. Oh, come on. Bring it on.
Oh, they told me it was hard. Like I exploded. Supplies. Um, I'm going with this thing. Is it
the same weapon? Is it the same gun? No, it's not. I want this one. This thing's kind of hard to use.
Two times scope. That's for this gun, isn't it? I'll put, all right, we'll do all this. We'll do.
Yeah. Yeah. That's fine. Two times scope. Nice. This is another two X scope. All right. Where are
they? Where is everybody? Ooh, give me that. There's one person just hiding somewhere. It's
still alive. You in the plane? Where even is this guy? Are you still alive? I don't see anybody.
Bro, please drink some water. I got, I got it right here. I'm good. I'm hydrating. Don't worry.
Nobody know where this guy is. He's down. Oh, you made that up. I'm trying to get to the highest
point. So I get shot at. There is nobody left. Is there, I don't even know which object. Oh, wait.
Okay. He's over here. What have you been doing?
Shooting it rocks. What the fuck was that? Get him. Get him. Ooh. Give me that. Look at this. All
right. I'm ready. I didn't know he was going to do that. And it's got on by a bird. Really?
I just got bird shit all over me. What the hell? Airstrike means airstrike, dude. I didn't know
if they were talking about right here. I guess. So what do I do? Dude. What the hell? That almost
hit me. What the fuck are you talking about? I thought that was a friendly plane because it
says supplies. Ready? Watch, watch, watch. Ready? Wait, wait, wait. Okay. Enemy activity firing.
Look that. Oh, that's it. I thought. Okay. Usually. Okay. Usually the ones that are indicated
with white means that I don't know. Maybe don't come down. I don't want that. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no. I want this. Oh, oh, this thing's out of bullets. See ya.
Hmm. Ah, shit. I helped. Where is he? There's only one left. Where is he? Yes.
Snipers. You got it. I need a sniper rifle. Oh, god damn it. Oh, god damn it. Hold on.
I need a sniper. Where's my sniper rifle? Where'd it go? I need a good spot. Right here. That guy
dead. Right here. Oh, where is he? The hell is he? Where is this guy? Oh, you're
right there. I see where you are. What's wrong with my sniper rifle? Why is my sniper
rifle a go-kart? Oh, that's why. Get out of here. See? It's a white indicator. The enemy
approaching is yellow. Yellow indicator. Um, good. I'll take the grenades. That doesn't work. I gotta
get over there quick. Come on. Come on. Hurry, hurry. Hurry. What? What is, what are you talking
about? You, I can't destroy the helicopter. I did not know that. It's okay. Oh, any more bullets?
No. You think I care? Oh, you gotta be fucking kidding me. Why would he do that? Why would you
do that? I didn't, I had no shots in that fucking gun. That was the last enemy too. God damn it.
What did you just drop? Uh, I just went like this. I just put my hands down on my chair. Okay. This
time I'm not going to blow it. Cause watch, I can't destroy the helicopter. So I'm going to wait.
This whole thing is going to be so much cleaner now. Watch this. Okay. Much. What? I died like
instantly. Oh, somebody sniped me. I got sniped. It's all good. Shoot the rockets out of the air.
That was pretty cool. Nice. All right. I got to get up high because that would have been great.
Get on this. What are you doing? That just messed up everything. All right. Much better. We're good.
I'm almost dead. I don't know what just hurt me, but it was a sniper probably.
Okay. I'm fine. Oh shit. Oh shit. I was, oh shit. Oh, he's still alive. Is he? That guy.
I, that, that was pretty good. That's pretty good. I knocked that guy into next week. Nice.
Get him. I need a weapon. Just run around and get everything.
Primary objective incoming. He's going to land and I'm going to throw a grenade right in his face.
There's no more weapons. I can't get anything. Pick up a different gun. Pick it up. Pick the,
I need a gun. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it.
This guy's fucking relentless. I, I don't even know who's firing at me.
He'll run out of bullets eventually. Dude. I can't, dude. There's too many fucking people.
There's too many people. Die. Die. Oh my. I got one of those. I got one of those guns. I got one
of those guns. I have one of those crazy guns. Oh, this guy's got so many grenades. Okay. Here
we go. Moment of truth. Moment of truth. I think I'm okay. I think I'm okay. Ah, yes. All right.
I'm good. I'm good. There's only like two more people. We're going to be very safe about this.
Where are you? You're over here. There you are. One more. Ah, thank God. It's not it. What do you
mean it's not it? Fuck what I just did. Nice. That was crazy. That was a wacky one. All right.
We're good. Very good. Very cool. I cannot imagine playing some of these on a harder difficulty.
I think hard is my limit. Very hard might actually be doable, but some of the two above very hard
it seems almost impossible. All right. I wonder if I've unlocked any cheats.
Uh, somebody I'm playing on hard. Let me see. Ah, okay. Unlock some squeaky voices. We're
turning that on. Uh, no, we're not. Spooky mode. No checkpoints. Well, I want to be able to unlock
stuff on hard. So when I'm done unlocking stuff, we'll turn a bunch of random shit on because if
I turn one of those on, regardless if it's just a goofy one, it means every difficulty is easy
or it's it. I can't get achievements for playing on hard and I still have to beat the game.
All right. What else we got? I'm going to let's all right. Let's beat the game.
I'm going to unlock everything so then I can just play the side stuff with cheats. Do you
really care about achievements? Well, I care about unlocking things and I think you have to play
missions on normal or hard to unlock things. All right, let's do it. Lead an assault on
Horizon HQ. Destroy Horizon once and for all. We've finally done it. We destroyed Horizon's
unethical research projects. We expose their dark secrets to the world. Their stocks are crumbling.
Employees are quitting en masse. The company lies in ruins. The CEO and executives are hiding
in Horizon's corporate headquarters. Eliminate them and destroy Horizon once and for all.
My accolades. All right, let me get different weapons because this is a normal mission. So I
want some different stuff. All right. Flashbangs are useful because you have five armor, obviously.
I'm going single SMG and it's going to be unfolded, unfolded stock. It's no suppressor.
And then I'm going to do honestly grenade launcher because it's just, I need some
destruction power. Should I even do homing? Lower velocity grenades with a longer fuse that home
onto enemies. Meh, I don't think so. What kind of games do you like? I like games where you have
upgrades. I love games that have interesting loot. I like casual games that you can play in bed.
Those are fun. I like upgrading. Oh, you know what I got to play? Uh, there's a new game.
Torment. What's it called? It's kind of like Vampire Survivors. It's new and it looks great.
Falls of Torment. Yeah, that's fun. I got to play that. That looks really, really,
that looks pretty damn good. Is it good? Can you please jump into the helicopter blades? I tried
already and it didn't work. So I'm sorry that I cannot do that. All right, here we go. Final
mission of the game. Let's do it. I think I'm good. I think I have a pretty good arsenal.
Was that poker game you played on iPad? That would be pine tar poker. It's very good.
Pine tar poker, pine tar poker. They keep cutting me off. Pine tar poker on the app store. It's a
fun game. It's a combination of Yahtzee and also poker. It's a very, very fun game to play. You've
got maybe an airplane trip you're going to go on. It's a good thing to kill some time.
If you want to just relax and, you know, take, you want to get like a little bit of a wind down
scenario in your, you know, in bed. All right, let's go. Let's go get them. It's time to use
everything I've learned. Do we swap or is it time to do a weld? How do I open the door? Am I missing
something? Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. Holy shit. You're all so dead. All right. The other door is going
to open now, right? I don't know. Open up everything. Take everything. Blow this up.
Other side for sure. I wasn't even looking in the right direction. I got 10 bullets for this. Oh,
yeah. This thing was a great pick. Good. Very good choice here. Yeah. I want the actual grenades.
He's patting himself on the back. Yep. It's a good call. I made a good call. I'm not allowed
to say that was a good call. All right. Somebody could be right here. No. All right. We're good.
We want to go to the bridge. You think I would wait till I got out of the elevator before pressing
the button? All right. Let's go. Yikes. What was that? All right. Oh, my God. We'll be still
alive back there. Whatever. All right. Do I have to get in the building? What's that? Remind me
that this is here because they definitely want me to do this for some reason. Smart gun. Bullets
home on two enemies. Yeah. Oh, OK. Dude, dude, these bullets. Smart. Not that smart. You have
to aim. Stand back. Stand back. Stand back. Stand back. Stand. How about these fucking smart
bullets? Who's left? You? I got him. All right. Let's I got to do some inventory. Where is this
guy? Oh, my God. Oh, my God. I need to. Give me that. Give me that. Give me that. Give me that.
Give me this. Give me this. Fucking ammo in this gun. I'm sorry. I can't fucking do anything.
I can't reload the gun. All right. Come on. No more fucking around. Give me my smart gun.
It's overstimulated. All right. These are smart. What the guy was aiming at the ground. Oh, shit.
Are you all right? I'm going in. I'm going in. I'm going in. Oh, I give me some help up here.
I don't know. Do you like it? What the fuck am I doing here? I need to go. Stop being an idiot.
No. Get off of there. Get out of my way. Dude, I got no guns left. I have no ammo left. You guys
have to help me. You guys have to do a lot of work here. I have no bullets. Oh, my God. Please.
Give me his gun. He had a gun. He had a gun. He has a gun. He has a gun. Give me that. No,
give me the gun. Give me. Give me. That guy didn't even exist. That guy didn't exist. Oh,
my God. Your fucking oxygen tank is just such a pain in the ass. Okay. Move up. Move up. Move up.
You guys getting? I got it. That was crazy. That's not it. Oh, my God. Wow. That was awesome.
That was hoggers. I'll keep the shotguns. Let me make sure I have ammo, though.
Horizon factory explosion, chain explosion. It's just kind of a new story.
Everybody all right? Pick up all the intel. I hereby tender by resignation from Horizon
effective immediately. I am deeply troubled by the recent revelation of the company's
immoral activities. Okay. You know what video games do a lot and movies do this too?
The trope of the CEO has a message that's just being played on giant speakers throughout the
entire building. There's like a CEO monologue that plays where is this an I don't think that's that
normal of an occurrence to have the CEO be just like talking through giant PA system all day at
work. You do this at work. Oh, I created you. Am I the bad guy? I'm sorry. I didn't really hear
much of what you said. I was thinking of a really cool way. I was going to kill you.
Oh, we need to all just got to chill for a sec.
Attention all personnel. Evacuate now. That's still got you, buddy.
I don't know. No, no, no, no, no, no. How is he dead? All right. This is going to get intense
right now. Or you take off. Just give me 30 minutes. I may be able to install something
to help with the upload process. They're uploading the virus to the cloud. Almost got me.
Oh, my arm. How is that? I want to know how it's possible that I just missed all those.
How is that possible? That is impossible. More Intel. There's a lot of Intel here.
Our employee satisfaction survey just leaked. It was all one star reviews. We need to find a way
to cover this up as soon as possible. Maybe a few incentives will change people's minds.
One star. Here we go. I got running. They'll never see us through the blinds.
That guy's head did a full 360. We're good. Oh, he's he has a lawnmower gun. All right.
He has a lawnmower gun. I want a smart gun, but I want all right. There we go.
And I only have one of these. I can only hold one. I can't do a well. The smart gun. That's too bad.
That would have been so funny. You're reading this. You are among the few who chose to remain
and make a stand. I applaud your bravery. I am moved by your passion and belief in the company's
values. Most of us will not live to see tomorrow, but the people of the future will thank us for
the stand we make today. They may not know your names or your actions, but what we do here today
will leave a mark in humanity's history. We cannot win today, but I still have one trick left up my
sleeve. My last request. Buy me some time. Your children will live in a better world for it.
I'm gonna smart gun this guy. All right. Should I not even give this guy a second to talk?
I'm thinking about just revving up the lawnmower, opening the door into slow motioning.
Hi. He's just dead. Oh, no. He did. He did the joke. He did the joke.
Oh, no. It was the Puzzler. It's your lucky quarter. This looks like a FPS map.
Okay. I didn't even know what we were doing. That was okay. That was like a first person shooter
map. I didn't know we were changing maps. This thing is too hot. It's too hot. It's too hot.
It's too hot. Get this thing ready. I don't know who's up there, but I'm gonna make a funny joke
and you'll know when it's about time for you to die. Here we go. Playing Mario Kart.
All right. Where the fuck are you? He's so silly. Oh, that was so silly. What I just did.
I need ammo. What's this? Oh, boy. Okay. Well, this is the final battle, I think, coming up.
How do I want to be in the final battle? I feel like this thing is gonna- I'm gonna get rid of
this very quickly. I'm not sure it's shotguns, honestly. I think I want a sniper rifle,
as weird as that sounds. This might be really stupid, but I'm gonna go sniper rifle and smart
gun. I'm gonna go in headshots only. Smart bullets work aim down sights. I don't think
there is an aim down sights unless I have to put it on. I'm gonna try it. Here's the last piece of
intel. Calling any personnel who meet or exceed the following requirements. Cranial capacity over
1,800. Master's degree or higher. You're needed for an emergency project immediately. I gotta
pee real bad. Give me one sec. For the final battle. I have returned. I'm ready for the final
battle. Okay. I'll try sniper. Yeah, you gotta get the pee out of your system before you do
something like this. You married into it. It is hot out. Sorry. It is hot out. It's on way more
Chad. It's hot and dry out here. All right. Give me some, give me a little bit of slack.
It's very dry and it's very hot out here. I'm ready. All right. How do I, where's the,
let's go. Dry or humid heat worse? Humid heat is the worst thing on earth. I will take dry heat
over humid heat every single day of the week. Every day of the week. In a dry heat, you do not
really sweat, which is actually kind of more dangerous in a way because you don't, you don't
realize like, oh, I'm not sweating. It's so dry. Everything's fine. But it's like 110 degrees out
and dry. You gotta be sure you're hydrating. Oh, we gotta go this way. All right. I got full
grenades. I got full smart gun. I'm ready. This is it. Let's kick the door in and I'm ready.
Cutscene. Ooh. Wait, what? Wait, what? He's just lying down naked in a chamber.
That was never, that was never going to work. Brain upload in progress. Wait,
that guy just sprayed me in the face like a bottle. Well, water bottle. What? Oh, I don't know.
Where's the brain? Where's the brain upload? Oh, can you do crazy frog? What's going on?
Yeah. God damn it. You've leaned. You've leaned. Like I leaned.
I just picked up every single fucking health pack. I'm in so much trouble. I'm in so much trouble.
Smart gun out. Did you hear that? I slid by that wall. It was just I picked up every health pack.
I forgot. I forgot. I forgot. I forgot. I forgot. I forgot. I forgot what was going on.
I forgot. All right. This is the one right here. Let's go. That took a lot from the smart gun.
Damn it, man. Okay. All right. All right. All right. I got to take the smart gun out there
and just spray. Where are they? Where are they? Get it. Oh, pick it up. Why would I have two sniper
rifles? This is not good at all. Where's the brain? Where's the brain? Holy shit. This is hard.
This is hard. Did I get it? I didn't even. Dude, I die in three fucking hits. Okay.
Dude, I just threw two grenades at it. Do I have to shoot it through the window?
I have to shoot the glass. I can't load up with that. It didn't hit the glass.
How does a grenade not hit the glass? Okay. Go back over there. All right. Go, go, go. It's
on the other side. Other side. I'm not dead. Oh, where is it? Where are you? What the fuck are
you doing over there? Oh my goodness, dude. You got to be fucking kidding me.
God, what is happening? Wait, I didn't even reload this gun yet. Who's talking? Who is it? The
dentist. No. No. Yeah. I need a gun right now. Dude, what do I do? No. I'm so glad I'm bad. I'm
so glad I'm bad. I'm so glad I'm bad at this game. I'm so glad I'm bad at this. Oh, fuck. It's just
so much going on. There's just too many things happening at the same time. Do I have to do it
all over again? Oh, this sucks. Dude, I don't know. Just take it. Take it. Go, go, go, go. I don't
know. That's it. That's it. Shoot, shoot, shoot, shoot. Go, go, go. That's it. That's it. Where is
this? There's still an upload going on. Where's this last upload? What the fuck are you talking
about? What? Dude, where is this last part? I need a different gun. Like, give me ammo for the ships.
Give me ammo for a different weapon. This is too much stimulation. This is like overload. This is
just like, I feel like I'm playing the game at times 10 speed. Am I hitting anybody over here?
I don't know where anybody is. There's no way to tell. I don't know, dude. They just keep respawning.
You have to aim a dude. Okay, here's what's going on right now.
That's the only sound effect. I can't.
Fuck you. Dude, I keep here. I keep getting put back to the dentist. Oh, and everybody has grenades.
Oh my. I can't like brain upload. All right, now what the fuck do I do?
You idiot. Why would you walk over to me? Why would you walk over here? You idiot. You dumb guy.
What's wrong with you? Okay. I get rid of this thing. This thing does like too damage. This weapon
is awful. I don't even, I don't want to snipe a rifle either. I picked the two worst possible
weapons for this fucking mission. This grenades everywhere. They just crashed the helicopter.
Crash the helicopter. They just crashed the helicopter. There's too much going on.
I have to restart the level and pick different weapons. I have no ammo all of a sudden. Give
me that. All right. Now fuck you. Perfect. How are you guys still alive? Shut up.
Let's go. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
All right. Now what? Smart gun, actual smart gun. I can't get in there.
Okay. Oh, you've got to be fucking kidding me. There's no way. There's no way.
Shoot him. There's too many people. There's too many people there. I needed that. I needed it.
Get me out. Get me out. Get me out. Get me out. You better not kill me. Oh no. Oh my God. Oh my God.
There was like a hundred people there. There was a hundred. Why were there so many people there?
Why were there so many people? Oh my God. Oh, thank God. There's a checkpoint.
Give me that. Get out of here. Let me in. Let's do it. Yes.
All right. I need some. All right. Give me your gun. Where is it? Okay. Fuck it. Let's go.
I'm ready. No, I'm not. I want help. This game doesn't look very Christian.
Oh yeah. Probably not. I don't know. All right. I have, I want a different weapon than this.
We'll go with this because I think I'm going to get spawned on. I'm going full firepower
and I have to take cover. Where am I going to take cover? It's probably a good idea to
go in the building and hide here. Let's do it. Get the fuck out of here. Get out of here.
Is it me? That's me. That's me. Wait, what? What did I do? I like teleported. Was I him?
Did I like, my consciousness jumped? How did I get through the wall? Break the cycle. How did I
get in the, how did I get in? There was some weird stuff going on early in the game. You know,
those drones, they're like, Hey, don't trust people. And you're, it's not, everything's not
what it seems. And now the room filled with gas. Liquidation process initiative. I'm getting
liquidated. It's been cool to have one of those. That seemed like an awesome weapon. I'm everybody.
It's a different 106 every time. I'm everybody. No, it isn't. Not if I have anything to say about
it. Why would you pick a gun out? Why would you take a gun out? That's up and point it close
to my face. I was about to be burned. Oh, that guy. Hey, they're going to write a whole
entire history book about how you fucked up right there. There's going to be
textbooks written about what you did. What's the Intel terminate rogue assets. This is what I am
armor and speed improvements recommended for next cycle. Give me that. Oh, okay. Yep. I'll stand
out. What would you want me to go back and lie on the, on the burn table thing? I can do that.
Yeah. Where was it? It was back here, right? Stand. Yeah. Here we go. Okay. I'm ready. I'm really
sorry. You can press, you can press the button. I won't do anything else. Ooh. Oh, watch out for
enemies. We were friends quarter master. Really is not. It sucks to be that guy. The guy that opened
the door. Yeah. I mean, come on. Oh my God. I'm so bad. Any health. There we go. There's a nice spam.
Hey, you do what you got to do. All right. Nobody else. Okay. Uh, I don't, there's nothing really on
the ground. Have I not picked up any shotgun ammo? It seems impossible. Okay. Where's the
off switch for this? What do you mean? Dude, dude, what, what? Shoot the red. I have to pull one of
those fuse boxes. What do you mean? Shoot the red. Dude, I'm sorry. I've never had to do that the
whole game. I have not had to do that the whole game. I've been looking for a fuse box, dude.
Let's go. I didn't kill either one of them. You know what? I got a better idea. Oh, it didn't
kill you. All right. It's all right. Okay. Good. Oh my God. Oh, are we okay? Am I alive?
I have one shot. All right. I, I got to get ready. Shut down. I think I'm good with this for now.
Send here. And, uh, yeah, here we go. Super soldiers or something. Oh, that's literally me.
We're all. Oh, all right. What the, that's actually scared the shit out of me. That was right.
That's behind my head. Oh my God. I hate that. What am I doing? I didn't mean to press that
button. My fat fingered it. Okay. I'm thinking shotgun. Okay. I can see you cause you're on fire.
This is perfect. Damn it. All right. All right. Spy checking. Yeah. How did I miss?
What are you doing? Where'd he go? Don't walk over here with that on your body.
This place is like gonna blow. Oh, it's so dead. Anybody else? Where is he?
I'm so sorry guys. I've just fucking, it's terrifying. Where's he going? What? What? Turn
it off. Oh shit. Yup. Wow. Um, okay. I have one arm. Go, go, go, go, go. What is that sound?
Oh my God. Oh my God. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Uh, oh, a drone. Location. Syndicate
cloning facility. Accessing user memories. Successful. Package. Syndicate cloning activity.
Upload complete. Accessing attempt. Accessing network. Subject 105 termination. Verified.
Pandora Institute. Evidence of anomalous research. Incomplete. Mission to terminate subject 91.
Incomplete. Syndicate thermonuclear warhead. Cyperia. Tower massacre. Incomplete. Syndicate
cloning activity. Mission critical data. Incomplete. You'll be remembered. There's
no extraction. Destroy the facility. You'll be remembered. These are the drones that you missed.
Bad ending. Okay. Exiting program. Well, how does it end? I feel like this is not a lot of bullets
for what is about to happen here. I could be wrong, but let's just go. Uh, this is the way
I came in. Okay. Let's go. Oh, that's the nuke. I remember. I tried to blow this thing up. All
right. Don't let them get near the nuke. You think you can block that? What if I go invisible?
I need a gun. Shotgun. I need a shotgun. There's the shotgun right there. Give me that. Give me
your gun. Give me that. Give me that. Oh, fuck you. Oh, I have nothing. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. I...
Where did they all come from? Dude, I... Oh my... Why do I have a pistol? This pistol... Can I just
throw this in the trash? All right. Let's go. Why did I pick up a pistol for any reason?
Where is he? I'm just trying to... Oh, I'm going to get hurt too. I'm getting too hurt.
Way too hurt. What's going on? What's happening? What's going on? Did you hear that? That's way
too many people. Stop throwing grenades. All right. I think I'm good. Only one more. Let's go. Let's
go. Let's go. This is it. This is it. This is it. This is it. Where is he? I'm getting too greedy.
Too greedy. Don't be stupid. Don't be greedy. Goodbye. Yes. Those of you playing harder than
hard, you're a god. You are a god. I think we just blow it up, right? I played this on very hard.
I have no idea how I'd go harder than that. Oh, we just nuked the base. Oh, that's the intro.
I was wondering why they kept showing that. That's you nuking the base. I get it. Hey,
Gianni, do you not have to nuke yourself for the good ending? That's a good question. I'm not sure.
Filing data. Publishing 3968 sources done. Reconstruction unavailable. Memories incomplete.
Signing off. We uploaded it. Okay. Mission accomplished 106. Hope you enjoyed playing
the Trepang 2 campaign. You've just unlocked a ton of cool new camos, cheats, and combat simulator
missions. Go check them out sometime. Come join the community and hang out with us sometime. We
love to talk with our fans. That was great. That was genuinely really, really, really wonderful.
Okay. There's a lot of stuff here now. What do we want to do? Enemies activate physics thrusters
on death? Insane gore. Let's do a couple at a time here. We're going to do squeaky voices.
Wait, hold on. Let me just see what is actually unlocked here. Show the sunflowers. I will do
that when I am done with Trepang 2. So soon. Not immediately, but soon. Anything else unlock?
I only have one other mission here. The Gunnarsson complex is fun. Look at it just in the outskirts
of Stockholm. The Gunnarsson complex is the center of Horizon's intelligence gathering in Europe.
Solve the facility and retrieve the encrypted data. That's right. I don't really care about
the achievements now. Let's do squeaky voices. NPCs throw a lot of grenades.
NPCs respond as jiggly boys when killed. Okay. Scale enemy accuracy. What does that mean? Scale
NPC reaction speed. Move speed multiplier. Cloak removed. Focus removed. Slide does not do anything.
Your health constantly drains until 1%. Spooky mode. Infinite ammo. For a second I thought
they said can't read. I was like does that mean you can't look at intelligence? Everything is
a knife. All weapons become inaccurate. Okay. There's a lot on right now. So we're going to
do these. NPC thrusters. Okay. Why is it all so dark? Oh because it's spooky mode. That just
means the game is dark. What do I want to bring? Blue double SMG. That sounds fun to me. And
grenade launcher. Sounds good. Don't need homing on it. These are just default. He's fine. All
right. Let's go check it out. All right. Spooky mode. Spooky mode just makes this really hard
to navigate. Where's the stairs? Okay. Let's go. How come the voices aren't squeaky? There's no
squeaky voices. What have we been waiting for? Probably just the enemies here. This was in the
demo. This was in the demo. Spooky mode have turned it off. Oh shit. That's not going to help us.
Okay. Yeah. So I, this is cool. I just can't really see very well. Let's go for it. Who has
the squeaky voice? Oh, oh my, that hurts my ears. That hurts my ears. I can't see anybody. What is
that? He's still alive. It's the minions. What? Jesus. All right. I'll take a more proximity
mines. Oh my God. What is wrong with this guy? Okay. Can I have the light back now? There we go.
Okay. Okay. Here we go. Okay. Hey, hey, holy shit. Everything. Get out of the way, dude. Get out
of the way. It's too much. It's too much going on. I'll try it one more time. I'm going to try to
win. I don't have any ammo. Almost done. I mean, it's kind of funny. It's kind of funny. It's kind
of funny. All right. Where's the next one? Okay. Pack it. This one's done. Pack it.
What just happened over here? Who's smoking? All right. More and more of those. All right.
Hack. Oh, we good. Oh, holy shit. All right. I got to turn this on. I turn this on. Turn this
on. It's funny. It's fun, but I got to, I don't know what I just did. Is this like one of those
flash games? What do you mean flash game? What do you mean it's a flash game? I'm going to try
this one for real, and then we're going to move on to the sunflowers. Restart level. I'm going to
try this one for real. All right. Let's try it for real. Oh, wait. Somebody's hacking it. Hack it
again. Hacking. Need to fill the dead air. Um, got him. Somebody up top two. Watch out. Yep. Right
here. Got one. Specialists. It's another one of those words. Specialists. Specialists.
Specialists. I did not even get hurt by that. All right. Whoa. Where are you? Woo. Where are you?
One more. One more guy. Get off of me. All right. Load it up. Good shot. Good shot. Huh?
Cool. No, you did not get me. Dead air. Um, uh, dead air. It don't matter. I'm just playing.
I, it's all good. That was so not cool. What I just did. All right. Where's the last one?
I need supplies actually. Where's the box? Here it is. Okay. Give me. What do I want?
All right. What do I want? Should I get another grenade launcher? Give me the bolt launcher.
I'm okay for now. Okay. I think this is all right now. This thing is destructive.
Mm-hmm. Okay. Oh, ouch. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh. Oh, oh, oh, oh. I'm out of ammo. Oh, this is not good.
Get in there. Don't you dare kill me. I don't know for health kit. I can, I can do armor. Okay. Okay.
Who's left? All right. Through the window. Oh shit. I didn't even start them. Oh,
that's embarrassing, but whatever. I'm going to get flash bangs. Okay, boys. All right, boys.
Oh, oh, fuck you. All of you. I'm in big shit. Oh, no way, dude. No way. No way. Oh, that's rough.
That was the end right there. It's all right. Oh, dude. No way, dude. Open the door. Why would,
what were you thinking? All right. All right. He's hitting gamer fatigue.
Ah, maybe a little. Oh, the guy's head just went in so many different directions.
That was fucking crazy. Oh shit. I got nothing left. I got nothing left. I got nothing left.
Oh, fuck this guy. Oh, that guy sucks. I need a different weapon. Oh shit.
I can't. I'm too stimulated. Get over here. Don't. Oh my God. Damn it. I need, I need two
seconds to fucking reload. Give me more ammo for this thing. You can't be still alive. It's
impossible. You exploded. I don't have any. Who's left? Oh, fuck that guy. Seriously. Oh,
fuck off. There's too many of you idiots with these fucking power armor. Oh, eat shit. Oh my
God. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I need more weapons. I can't
just go down there right now. I need to go to the supply thing. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait.
Where's the supply thing? Hey. Hey. No. Oh, pick it up with H. You idiot. H. H. I can't even.
There's too much shit on the ground. Oh, you piece of shit. Oh, I did it. I actually did it.
Yeah. Okay. I'm ready. How do I get on the roof? How do I get on the roof? How do I get on the
fucking roof? How do I get on the roof? Damn. All right. I did that on hard. There it is.
Did I unlock? I unlocked a new cheat. Well, we have to do that. I need to see big head.
I just want to see the big head and then we'll take a quick break and then we'll look at the
sunflowers. Yeah. I don't need to do any outfitting or anything. Here's the oil rig. Everyone said,
hey, do the oil rig when it's available. This is the last side mission. I don't think I'm going to
beat this one. I think I'll just check it out. I mean, I'm already in here, but as well. Actually,
no, let's do actual grenade grenades. I am all right with this. Tell us that there was some
freaky shit at that oil rig, but they ain't said nothing else. All right. Let him game. Yeah,
I'm just gaming. Oh, his head shrinks. Okay. Now it just feels like this is the mobile game they
came out with at the same time as a marketing tool. This is the mobile game. Okay. I'm dead.
All right. All right. All right. Let's do the sunflowers. It's time. I'm going to take a quick
break. I'm going to get them over here so I can put them on the screen. We will showcase the
sunflowers. You have no idea what's going on pretty much every year. The last two or three years,
although didn't do very much last year, but it's been very, very, very hot. Sunflowers got a ton
of sun this year, but yeah, I, Holly and I planted a bunch of stuff. We've been very good plant
parents. At least I hope so. Are they taller than you? Yeah. Here's the thing. The last time we did
this, we got ones that could go up to eight to 12 feet. I think is what it was. These ones were
only supposed to go because it's like, Oh, but let's maybe we'll do some smaller ones this year.
These were supposed to only go four feet and they're still 10 feet tall. These were not the big
ones. It's just out here in Vegas. The sun just rains down all fucking day. They love it out here.
They just absorb so many of these sun's rays and we fertilize, you know, fertilize them. All right.
Give me a minute. I'm going to get it set. I'll come back. We'll hang out for a little bit longer
and let's do some sunflowers. See you in like four or five minutes. I'm going to pee. I'm going to
refill my drink. I'll be back. Okay. I am back. I'm going to put some nice music on while we sit here
for like 15 minutes or so. Let me get some nice music. What should we do for nice music? What do
you think? How about Stardew? Oh, that's not a bad one. That's right. All right. Stardew.
We're going to go right in the middle somewhere. Stardew Valley OST. And there it is. Hey, there it
is. I think that's a good start. Okay. So for those of you that are about to join me on the journey
for this year's harvest. Okay. Let me figure out how I'm going to do this. How should I do this?
I think I can just drag them over here. Yeah, this will work. All right. So here
is the, here are the babies, as you can see. The thing about sunflowers and growing anything,
it's actually kind of sad what you need to do. So when you plant sunflower seeds, oh wait,
it doesn't, whatever. You have like a, you know, I'm going to do this. I'm going to do that this
year. You have to thin out the ones that don't really make it. If you're going to do them in a
pot. Like if, let's just say for instance, you don't have a bunch of land to do like 50 sunflowers in
a row, you plant, they have to be at least eight inches apart, 12 inches apart. But sometimes,
as you see here, see the one on the left, that, that guy was ready and he was obviously the
stronger one. So that was the one that was going to stick around. The other ones, unfortunately,
they have to go purged. Yeah. And it's always like, no, but if you, I'm going to put you in a
different pot. And what ends up happening is you end up having, you end up, you end up kind of
transferring all the ones that weren't going to make it to a different pot. So you just end up
having a bunch of pots of these ones that kind of don't make it in quotes. You kind of just try to
spread them around. These ones all lived by the way, these were dwarf sunflowers. So I'll give
you another picture here. It's the same group. As you can see the one in the back, a little bit,
a little slow to rise, but all three of these made it. I think that's a pretty good one of them
down here. There is. Yeah. So the big ones, the ones that we have in a big pot are here.
Take a look at these ones. So that's how they start. Oh, hold on. What is this doing? There we go.
They end up getting a little bigger. These ones are different though. These were not,
these ones are not the little ones. Yeah. Again, we went with three this year. They're very,
very strong, very healthy. They got to this stage pretty quickly. It was, it was,
it was like, wow, they're growing really, really, really fast. We didn't just do sunflowers though.
God, gardening is so nice. Let me show you this. What do you think about this one? So those are
sunflowers. Take a look, take a look at this one. Ooh, I don't even know. We don't even know what
this flower is. We just know that it looks really nice and we want to make it look like a national
geographic photo. This is a wildflower. Don't even know what it is. Is it a tulip? I don't know.
This opened, this opened wide. You'll see a couple of pictures of it. This thing was open. Here's
another one from side by side here. So I believe this is the same area. There's a little moth on
this too. There was a couple of orange ones. There was a few pink ones. There was some blue ones.
They were all over the place. Oh no, there's a bug. Just getting some shade. There's a couple of
really, really cute photos. Any more of the tall wildflowers? Yep, I got one here. So this is the
one that you see on the right. Oh, sorry, on the left. Looking through the, looking through the
jungle. Ooh, that's what it opened up into. So what is that? We don't really know what it is.
We just don't, because the wildflower packets, you just shake it out. It's just a ton of different
random things. It's a Cosmo? Cosmo. That's cool. It's opium. It's not, it's not opium. This dude's
growing fucking opium. But I know what you're really here for. You're here to see the fucking
blue wildflower. Same pot? Yeah, same pot. And these just popped up kind of randomly. It's kind
of cool to walk out here sometimes and be like, wait, there's a purple one now. That's kind of
cool. Is there any? Let me see. Oh, here's a good one. So this is, this is right before one of the
sunflowers opened. Take a look at that. So as you can probably see the color this year, we had,
they were kind of yellow with brown in the middle and they opened like this,
but then they got to be pretty much yellow. Let's even get that one open. Yeah. Hey, you ready? So
this is kind of, I don't want to show that one yet. We'll just show this one. We'll show it's
starting to open. So there's that one. Take a look at this. Ah, it is opening. So really wild color.
It was like electric in a way. It's so weird because like I said, over time, these actually
get paler. All that orange in the middle goes away almost completely. Just that's how they start for
the first week. Do you grow them inside? No, no, these are all outside. They kind of have to be.
They have to be in direct sun all day. I Googled sunflower and found this on the second page, bro.
We stopped, we stopped fucking with me. Come on. Like we didn't do sunflowers this year. Okay.
Fine. What would you, what do you want me to say? Don't, don't, don't get up in here and fuck it up
for me. So yeah, I want to show you, can I show you my favorite one? And this is a big deal by the
way. This is a big deal. A lot of times when you grow some flowers, you get yellow, yellow, yellow,
yellow, yellow, yellow. This year we got a massive orange one and it stayed orange the entire time it
was here. Bright orange. Let me make it a little smaller. I love the depth of field too. It looks
so nice. And who's that? It's Otto. Yeah. This thing is the size, the middle there is as big as
a fucking softball. This was almost two fists together. How big that middle is, is gigantic.
It's my favorite. I don't want to play favorites, but that's my favorite one this year. Just,
just saying. It looks stunning. Here is one of the dwarf sunflowers open. Very pretty. And these
only get to be, and a lot of people say, Hey, this sounds like really fun. This sounds like really
cool. I can't do that. These are like not even a foot tall. They're tiny. Actually, man, this might
not be the dwarf one. No, this is just one of the regular ones. See the other head forming on the
left side there? Yeah. These were vibrant. Sunflowers are so easy. Oh yeah. Absolutely.
But as long as you, if you, let me learn to talk again. As long as you're in an area that gets a
ton of sunshine throughout the entire summer season, you'll, it'll work. Sunflowers are pretty
easy. And they just, they blow up sometimes. Remember I told you that one of them was a Hydra.
We tried to get some decent pictures of just how many heads appeared on this thing. So let's see.
Yeah. Take a look at this. Are you ready? Check this shit out. So this is at full growth for
the one that I was just showing you. It's like a fucking Elden Ring boss. There are one, two, three,
four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, 10. I believe there are 11 heads. It's just trying that they were
facing the other way. And it's just like, ah, shit. It's all right. It's okay. There's a pretty
cool one here looking up here. This one too. This is taken from like the bottom looking up.
This thing was huge. It was probably 10 feet tall and there are heads that are still going to open.
The photos are awesome. Yeah. This is Holly taking all of these pictures. I took one. Yeah. These are,
these are all Holly. They are very, very, very good. All right. I'm going to show you something
now that's going to make you cry. You're going to cry. Hope you're ready. You ready? I don't
know if you're ready. It's a hummingbird drinking out of the big orange one. Not a, no big deal.
Yes. We sat staring at these until one showed up. That was an entire afternoon at one point.
But yeah, we did get a couple of visitors. Speaking of visitors, it was really nice to see.
I don't know. It makes you feel kind of good. So this is a wasp and they would just kind of pop
in from time to time. If you don't like wasps, then you know, you're about to see one. But what
I told you guys last week, I was like, man, when you really kind of just sit here and watch,
you kind of go, they're just kind of hanging out. So this was a wasp and this wasp found this
piece of shade here because I told you, it's been insanely hot. It has been a hundred plus 110
degrees every single day. And this little, this little guy found the shade and slept.
He literally is sleeping here. He's lying down in the shade. He found a little spot
and it's just like, it is too hot, man. Yeah. He's actually like lying down,
just staying out of the, out of the heat. Did he get up? Yeah. No, he's not dead.
Nobody tell him. Nobody tell him he's dead. No, he got up and flew away like 20 minutes later.
He's not dead. Nobody tell him. Nobody tell him. Nobody tell him. He got up and flew away
literally 10 minutes later. It was like, oh, there he goes. Wow. He's, he's still alive.
All right. He's not dead. Stop saying that. He's not dead. Oh yeah. What do you think about that?
We got visited by all kinds of creatures, ladybugs, lacewings, bumblebees, honeybees.
And these are awesome because these eat all the aphids. Something I never knew before doing
plants and gardening, whatever. There is an entire group of animal that just spawns a hundred million
times out of fucking nowhere and eats everything that is green. It doesn't even make any sense
where they come from. Lacewings eat them. Ladybugs eat them. And it was actually pretty under
control this year. I'm glad that the ecosystem kind of could do it. You should go outside and
paint yourself green. Why? What are you? Time that, time that person out for like at least five
minutes. Hey dude, can you go outside and paint yourself green? Like what? And pretend to be a
flower? Ants farm them. Yeah. Ants want the, the delicious juice that they secrete. So ants will
farm them. Ants will literally turn them into like these, they just produce this liquid that
the ants want. So the ants bring them there on purpose and just turn them into bug fucking
like workers. They essentially have like, it's like, it's like slavery. It's crazy. It's fucked up.
They literally take these aphids and like make them, it's fucking crazy. It's actually insane.
If you look into it, go watch or read like anything about how, what ants do to aphids.
It's like, huh? What are you talking about? They'd, no, they don't do that. Yeah, they do.
It's fucked up. Farmer ants, bug, the aphids get protection from the ants. I was under the impression
that they kind of would just like, you go up there and do this and we're going to take your like food
from you. It's like, it's kind of, it's kind of, is it mutually beneficial? It's kind of like cattle.
It's like livestock. Yeah. Ants farm them. It's fucked up. Well, we're looking at a cute wasp
sleeping on a leaf and a ladybug. Okay. Speaking of the other plants, these are, I showed you the,
why didn't you, actually didn't even see them. This is a good one of the other marigolds. The
marigold, everything was orange this year. These are marigolds. And the reason why these are here
is because they help actually deter, which I know the book is kind of out on this, but according to
some people, marigolds actually repel a lot of insects. They hate them. They don't like the way
they smell. So this is a little popcorn marigold. Is that a good ground cover? Yeah. Do bugs use
neti pots? Uh, I don't think so. But over here, look, look at that. Out of focus, but there's one
of the, see how small they are? That's one of the dwarf sunflowers that you saw before. And you see
one, two, three, remember in the very beginning? That's them. So we did end up pulling them out
and putting them in individual pots and they were very happy. They did very well. There's also,
there's like a couple more I want to show. Let me see. Oh, this one's cool. This is another one
kind of like looking up at the, the big Hydra. The sense of scale is hard to show, but this thing is
about 10 feet tall and no, I'm not going to stand next to it because I know a lot of people would
just like shrink me and make me like four and a half feet tall. Let's show. Ooh, this one. Oh yeah.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Take a look at this one. Remember that hummingbird you saw earlier? Yep.
Look at how, look at how majestic she is. Yeah. They, they were all, they were all about this.
They're all over these and we'll show how many more do we have? I think I could show this one
too. It's actually kind of cool just to see them closed. But for instance, this one here,
now let me put this one back. Where did it go? Yeah. It's I'll put this one back up. It's so weird
because before these open, it's almost like there's like magic going on in here because the,
the head is closed. It just, it stays closed pretty tightly. And then just one day you can start to
see color in there. And then a day or two later, the whole thing is open. It's so weird that it
does that. And then a few weeks after this, it generates hundreds of seeds that you then can eat
or just plant in the ground again. Plants are ridiculous. Nature is insane. How long from start
to finish? Uh, the first picture is here. Like for instance, these ones here. This was, I want to say,
because you're supposed to plant them a week or so after there is no chance of a frost because it
it'll, it destroys them. So once you're past the last frost of the year, so sometimes that's like
May, sometimes it's mid-May, early May, sometimes it's late May. It really depends on where you are.
But for us, uh, it was pretty early in May. So this is probably, I want to say like a month
and a half of growth. Maybe as of these photos, probably like a month, like four to six weeks,
I want to say. Yeah. So May 6th is when we put them in the ground or May 9th, maybe. And then
you're seeing these photos as of like a month or so later. Where are their faces? Well, yeah,
that's what I mean. Like it's, it's so crazy that this thing, right? This like piece of fucking lettuce
right here develops this on its head. That's just, it does like, that's so wild that this actually
does this. Hey, well, I'm just, I mean, look at it. It kind of looks like a piece of romaine lettuce.
And then just one day after getting a lot of nutrients and sun and water, it turns into this.
Let me get that orange one back up. This thing was rocking for like a week or two straight.
I think somebody said, would you, would you ever do vegetables? Vegetables kind of scare me
because, well, I mean, sunflowers are technically food, technically. But the thing about vegetables
that freaks me out is I almost feel like I would, I don't know. I feel like it's, am I watering them
enough? Are they going to taste okay? What about the water? Is the water, am I using like, should I
use like purified water? What if it's going to be like gross water in there? What's the pH of this
water? I don't know. I feel like I'd freak out about it. You should grow tomatoes. What actually does
well in Vegas? I always felt like that anything that wasn't something that needs to get scorched
by the sun just can't really work out here. Sunflowers work out here. Would tomatoes work?
I feel like tomatoes would just get burnt. Money trees? Well, money tree, can you eat a money tree?
I feel like that's kind of weird. I don't think I'd want to eat a money tree. Isn't it supposed to,
you're supposed to have it for like good luck. I feel like, I feel like eating it is getting,
is bad luck. Dragon fruit, peppers, and, so, wait, dragon fruit would do well out here? Like, that
sounds actually kind of fun. Holy shit, you can actually grow pumpkins. Really? It was just a
joke. I didn't even know money trees were real. What? Succulents? I actually think, I think that
would be, yeah, that'd be really, because, I mean, there's a lot of cactus out here, just naturally.
It's kind of everywhere. Did you use fertilizer? Yeah, just the generic stuff. Just that, you know,
the bag you get at Home Depot that has, you know, you can just sprinkle it in and rinse it in there.
It's pretty, pretty basic stuff. Every two or three weeks, drop it in there. We only did it,
I want to say, maybe three or four times total. So, every two weeks. Prickly pear? Oh, yeah.
What the fuck is this stream? It's in the title. It literally says,
Trey Pang 2 and Sunflower Podcast.
Grow some peppermint. You should grow aloe for the skin care. That's true. Ban that guy. Nah,
it's all right. Would you get some creatures for the garden? We get a lot of, they just kind of
show up. Last time there was praying mantis, there were honey bees. If you have this stuff,
they kind of just show up on their own. You don't really have to do very much. Just like,
jump scared you, I'm sorry. Yeah, like sometimes, oh, you know, I need shade. I'm going to hang out
here. Hummingbirds are so cool. Can I tell you, hummingbirds are my new favorite animal. They're
just so interesting. I can't even describe how, let me just tell you, they're great. Hummingbird
feeders. Do you have hummingbird feeders? I sure do. We sure do. They're, that's essentially what
these are. They are hummingbird feeders. That's kind of one of the points to do it in the first
place. But yeah, that's probably it. That's pretty much it. Got to go over a bunch of them.
I think we, there's a, there's a few more that we have that are really big close-ups, especially
after we harvested some of them. So we can show, if you want to see, hold on, did I show,
I'll show this one too. So this one, oh no, we already saw that one. We already saw that one.
Okay. This one looks, oh, this, this is a good one. Take a look at this one. So this is sort of how
they were set near each other. You're wondering, just kind of in placement, like, wait, where's
that orange one? So there's the Hydra and there's the orange one. And as you see, see the one in the
middle on the right? That one is ready for harvest. You essentially, once they're ready,
you snip off the head and there it is. And there's your seeds in there. You just kind of fish them
out. Yeah, you can see the color difference now too, much better. That sort of sprinkled in orange
brown on the right one, the one on the left is like fire orange. Do you cook them? No. For the
most part, it's more of, I want to keep these because I want it. I want to plant these ones
next year. So you kind of keep the family. Now there's hundreds of them. So yeah, you can,
you could cook, you can toast them up and eat them if you really wanted to take them out of
the shells, toast them up. Yeah. There you go. There's this, there are the sunflowers. There's
your big fiery orange sunflower. And then the, the family of 11 heads, very, it was wild this year.
You need to name them. The one on the left is Blaze and the one on the right is Cerberus.
You don't think we've already gone over this? Many, many times. Where's Otto? He's right here.
You didn't see? It's Otto. All right, that's going to wrap it up. Short stream today, but
you know, there'll be a lot more of these. I had fun. It's a good day. The next time I see you,
here is the plan. Sunday we are going to do Team Fortress 2. I got to say it again. Make sure you,
you know, clear your ears out a little and go, wait, what did he just say? Team Fortress
2 on Sunday. I'm going to play it for an hour or two. See how I like it. See if I'm getting into
it again. And then after that, probably start viewfinder. Play that for a couple of hours.
That's the plan for Sunday. Hey, botanist here. Ooh, hold on. Some fun info about sunflowers is
each place that bears a seed is a singular flower. Each head houses hundreds of singular flowers,
two different kinds too. Disk flowers and ray flowers. The middle flowers are the disk once,
and the ones along the rim are ray flowers. Each ray flower has a huge petal. Yeah, they're all
into that. That's wild. We've got botanists here. We have scientists here. We have doctors here. We
have lawyers. Most educated community on earth, by the way, on earth, I said. All right. I'll see you
guys later. Thanks for watching. See you Sunday. Probably starting around the same time, around
three o'clock. Hope you enjoyed the sunflowers. It was about a month and a half to get them there.
Marigolds, the wildflowers. They're still around too. I'll probably show a couple more pictures
later because the wildflowers are still going strong. There's a few more heads that are going
to open on the orange one. So maybe we'll do an update in another week or so. Yeah. See you guys
on Sunday around three o'clock. Take care of yourselves. Thanks for hanging out. Trippang
too is, I would think that's probably one of the most fun games I've played this year. You want a
real assessment of that. That's probably up there in the top five games I've played this year. It
was just very fun. You can challenge yourself like crazy in that game and it's really interesting.
You can go as hard or as easy as you want. I thought it was great. I would say that it was
very good. Dude, you've only played like six games. That's in the top five. What's the one
game that came out this year that I played that I've really despised apparently? I don't know.
What have I not mentioned? Gollum? Yeah, yeah, that's true. Diablo IV. Yeah, I didn't really
talk about it, did I? No. Yeah, we don't need to get into it. We don't need to get, we don't
need to get into it. You know what I'm saying? We don't need to get into it. I'll be here for
another six hours. We're not going to get into it. I'll be here for six more hours.
Get into it. I'll see you Sunday. Maybe one day I'll get into it. When are you going to
do the browser game and quiz stream? That's true. We do need to do that. We'll do it soon.
Sorcery part four also as well. Dude, start ranting now. No, we just showed off all the
sunflowers. I'm in a really good mood. I don't want to get into it because then I'll get all
hot. The room will heat up. I'll have to go get a bunch of water and I'll be pacing back and forth
for the next hour off stream thinking about it. I got it. Yeah, I got to log off. Let's log off
for a little while. Hey, say happy birthday to my cat Goober. He turned one today. Happy birthday,
Goober the cat. All right. I'll see you guys Sunday. Take care of yourselves. Call your mother,
call your father. Hey, do something nice for yourself today. Do something nice for yourself
today. You understand? Hey, do something nice for yourself today. See you guys later. Take care.
See you Sunday. Have a great one. I'm also going to wait till four hours so it looks much better on
paper. You know how it is. It just like, you know, four hours looks just on paper looks a lot better.
I got just enough time to talk about D4 and I get it out in two minutes.
All right, let's get into it. I'm gonna get into it. I got two minutes.
I can't get it. I can't get into it. I can't get into it. It's like a whole, I have like a whole,
I'm like just a whole thing about like modern video games and how it's almost like things are
being they're not being made. No, I can't get into it. We have two minutes. I actually can't
get into it. I just picking up Saigon's boots fucking eight times and that's the only item that
you that drops something going on there. That's true. You know what I mean? Or like, you know,
distant enemies are stunned for four seconds for the 15th time as an aspect. I just don't like this.
That doesn't do it for me at all. That just doesn't do it for me at all. This doesn't do it
for me at all. Go off. Go off. Log off. I'm going off. I'm going off. All right.
Holy shit, dude. Wow. Super hot take. Oh, wow, dude. Did you hear that?
No way. Nobody else has that take. Only German says that. Whoa, dude. He's so brave for giving
his take on D4. Dude, no one else has said this. Not like six or seven million people that have all
said that exact same thing. Dude, you are. You are. Whoa. You are a visionary, by the way.
We're almost at four hours. We're good. These are CCO takes. I like how Diablo one just had a sword.
It just it just I don't know. I just feel like I was like working.
Does that make sense? I feel like I was like working when I was playing. It's like I was at
I was like working. I was at work. I would go to work and then I would just salvage my entire
inventory. He missed it. Oh, because the foot. No, it's fine. We're at overtime. Yeah, we're good.
I can hit 420. No, I can't. I can hit. Let's try for four, one, four, one, two, three. OK,
we're going to do four, one, two, three. No, not four, one, two, three, four. Yeah. See you Sunday.
All right, here comes four, one, two, three. See if I can get it. Take care.