How's it going? Yeah, I was gonna do it tomorrow. It's gonna be live tomorrow, but eh. It was on the
brain. Just figured I'd finish it tonight. Probably not going to be a very long stream, but I'm into
this. I want to play it and I want to finish it. Reverse delay. Sometimes it happens. Well, it's
actually been happening a lot more frequently. Yeah, it's supposed to be tomorrow, but yeah,
whatever. Let's go. I imagine there's probably only another hour or two left in the game, so why not?
You got a Tom Hanks voice today? What? No, I don't. I do not. And whatever. I don't care.
Well, I feel like I've lectured pre-stream chat about a bunch of random subjects.
I feel like I get in there sometimes and I just kind of write. I honestly, sometimes, I know. Okay,
here we go. Here comes the beast. Gonna break the magic. Sometimes when I'm in pre-stream chat,
I feel like I have the bugleberry mask on. You know what I mean? Like I just kind of, I can,
it's just, I can just say anything. I don't know. Something about it. It's only like in pre-stream,
but I just, oh, the grilled cheese hit the floor kind of stuff. Like I don't even like,
it's just whatever. Mask, mask, mask. I mean, sometimes I put the bugleberry mask on
because, well, I, you know, I've, whatever. Santa isn't real. Okay. Sorry. It's been your
parents the whole time. Bro, what the fuck? Bugleberry is my parents? Take that back.
How can, how could I possibly say Santa isn't real when Santa was on my stream a couple months
ago? You guys can't be serious. Who was that then? Yeah. All right. Let's, let's get started.
500,000 bugs watching today. That's a lot. That's a huge viewership. Damn. Why are you like this?
I don't know. Cause I like having fun. It's really all I care about. Like the only thing I care about.
Sometimes I make my own fun. You know what I mean? You ever played brutal legends? No, but it looks
fun. I always saw, I saw it kind of always on the shelf. Like, oh cool. I never really played it.
Seemed like a cool concept. Yeah. Let's, let's finish this. Like, I don't know. I'm not, there's
no time limit on this stream, but there's no time frame. It's just, I'm going to go until I beat it
and then we'll see. Finish Hollow Knight. Yeah, probably. Are you going to stream more than three
times this week? Um, well, technically this is the end of a week. It is currently Saturday evening.
So I, the answer to that question I believe is no. So not this week. Sunday is the only,
I'm not streaming tomorrow. Instead of streaming this tomorrow, I'm streaming this today.
Just do four streams in a row. I mean, maybe I will at some point. It's in the middle of the
night on Sunday. Well, yeah, it could be anywhere for anybody. How am I supposed to do any work
if you keep streaming you shithead? I don't know. Maybe just, maybe do the things you need to do.
Hey, I'm, I'm going to, I'm going to be here. Go do the things you need to do and then come
back when you're ready. Hey, that's not on me. It's not on me. All right, let's go. And the
good thing about this time rather than last night is I know exactly where I am because we beat a
boss and I immediately stopped the stream. You don't get it. It's not that simple. You know,
you kids, you kids don't understand. Back a long time ago, if there was a television show on TV
and you missed it, you didn't get to go back. You had to catch it when it was on or wait till
they released the fucking DVD like seven months later. You don't understand how easy you have it.
All content is available. You have no idea. It's called a VCR. You could tape it, but what if you
don't have a tape? What if you have like a box full of tapes and what if you ran out? What if
you're just like, I don't like, what if you don't feel like putting a tape in and hitting record?
What if you missed it? What if you, I know like, oh, what? I'm just going to record
because I know it's going to be on at the tape could only record 60 to 90 minutes.
You couldn't go to work and record something. The tape was only like 60 minutes. Nice villain
monologue. You have no idea. The point of this initial monologue tell you, you can just watch
the VOD. Although it's not ideal because you can't say, okay, yes. When I do something,
I get it. I do. Uh, TLDR time that person out for five seconds. Let's go. All right. This is like
fucked. It is like a fucked up comment, but I have to read it because it's actually, it's just,
I have to read it. They say, what do they say? It was, where is it? I want to get it right.
No, I need to be in sync with your breathing. All right, you know, time that person out for five
seconds too. That is a weird comment. All right. How come my controller doesn't work? Um, hello.
How come I can't? There we go. All right. So the last thing we did. Yep. I beat that boss.
We got to the new area and I am precisely where I want to be lined up lined up perfectly with where
I want to go. Nice armor. Thanks. Oh my God. Okay. I didn't wait. Start over. There we go.
The audio was low for me. I, yeah, this, this, this is bloodborne. This is supposed to be bloodborne.
This is great. Where's the beetle cam? Uh, I don't have the Beatles yet. Notice how I said yet.
That decision has been locked in. Yeah. So for those that don't know, I, all right, I got, I,
it's so funny how your opinions and your life kind of changes and the way you see the world
changes as you get a little older. I never thought I was going to care about bugs. Bugs, oh bugs,
who care? Like when I was younger, no, not even close. They kind of like fascinate me now. It's
interesting. It's weird how it was like, oh yeah, I didn't care at all until like literally
this last year, Jesus die. Okay. But anyways, the, I, I've talked about it a couple of weeks
ago or so, whatever it was, but, uh, blue death feigning Beatles, they just look, they're so cool
looking and they're just so, it's just like silly. They're just silly little friends and they can
live a very, very, very long time. They don't take a whole lot of maintenance and it seemed
like kind of cool. Just like a thing to do. There's a, it's a fascinating world and sometimes I kind
of want to, I'd like to experience it, right? That's pretty much all there is to it. The Dead
Space remake is Jesus Christ. Hold on. I'm dead. I'm dead. All right. These things are no joke.
Jesus Christ is in Dead Space. Do you know what I keep laughing at? I, I need some opinions.
I need some chat opinions. So, uh, Wild Hearts last night. Um, the pig talking clip is just living
in my head rent free. I just keep thinking about it. Something, I don't know why I thought it was
so funny, but, um, so part of that sponsor is, um, I'm going to be tweeting out a clip from the stream
and they were just like, yeah, pick any, like any, like fun clip, doesn't matter. Like whatever it is,
as long as it's like fun or interesting. And I kind of want to use that. I think that that's,
I think that's fucking hilarious. Do you think that would, do you think that goes hard? I think
it does. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Cause I was thinking about it. I was like, maybe it should be that
cause I don't know. Whatever. Oh my, okay. This is, these are the hardest enemies in the game.
I can't, I gotta, Jesus, I'm dead again. I lost 10,000 souls. Yeah. Or that, that falling. Yeah.
So there's the other one when I have the hammer and I'm going down the zip line and I perfectly
time it. So I'm about to land just one, two, three, four, five, spinning with the hammer.
And I just land and die. And then Vinny dies right next to me. You can see, maybe people didn't pick
up on that. Or if you did, then you did. But Vinny literally at the end of that part falls right next
to me in the same spot and dies. Holy shit. Hold on. Oh my God. Uh, run a poll. I mean, there also
was a kind of a cool gameplay moment where I did the bulwark boom timed it perfectly and then did
a huge jumping slash. All right, let's get a poll. I'm curious. Uh, cool bulwark into jumping slash,
the pig talks or falling with the hammer. I mean, there's no way the gameplay one's going to win,
which, but I mean, we have to put it there. The pig is going to be 80%.
I don't know. The other one was, was pretty good too. You know what it is? These guys don't get
staggered when you hit them. Oh, these are unbearable. Could you do all three? Um,
pro probably. Can you show the clips? Um, I think it's, I think it's pretty much not even close.
I don't think we need to do that. Judging by what this looks like so far. Looks like, uh, yeah,
appreciate it. 83% damn pig sweep. All right. Don't lose here. Cause one comes from one runs behind
you. Oh jeez. Oh my goodness. Please do not. No, no, no, no. Oh, this area fucking hard.
Okay. Both headphones are going in now. Both headphones going in. I wonder if I could,
maybe it's better to parry this you think probably right with relentless enemies like this.
I think the play is always to try to parry like the first attack. This is a parry shield. Okay.
This is a parry shield in the wrong hand, but it's better than all right. Here we go. Let's
try it again. Let's see if it works. Christ. I'm dead. Well, it definitely got harder. Let me try
this again. Fuck. All right. You, I got it. I got it. I got it. It's hard to do that. It's actually
very difficult. What about blocking? Ooh, that person's got the right idea. I'm going to be fat
rolling, but it doesn't matter. That person's got it. Oh, oh my God. I hate these guys. Hey,
VOD watchers skip 15 minutes. No, uh, uh, don't you don't know anything. What if that, what if
it ends up being five minutes and that person listened to you and you were wrong? They're going
to be very upset with you because they're about to, you know, 551 51 601 64. Okay. Six 14. If I
hope they did skip 15 minutes because it's six 14, there's going to be something really cool
that happens. I'm going to make sure of it exactly when it hits six 14 reusing this bit.
I loved this bit. I was just going to bring it up. You guys remember the Spongebob VOD treasure
hunt. A lot of time went into that one. Jesus. I'm, I can't do it. I can't do it. I have a better
idea. Eight endurance Andy. I got a better idea. Give me the shit I had already. Where is it?
I have a new strategy. Oh my God. I tried to pick up the item that was probably going to be on the
ground and I just reset that. I think we're just going to get lucky with the crits. Just go all in,
go for it. Just go all in and hope that like my 30% crit rate works one at a time. I see you up
there. I'm going to play that game. That's fine. Come on. Yeah. Yeah. What, what happened? What's
going on? I just don't want two. What the, oh my God. Shit. All right. I'm going to go in. It's
three. Oh God. Okay. The other one disappeared. We lucked out. Nope. You're right there. Locked
out. Bucked out on that one. Good. All right. Now you just got to tank it. Your character looks like
you got dressed out of a dumpster behind a Halloween store the day after Halloween.
That was a good one. That was a leather jacket. Okay. Everything's going good. Explore down here
first. Should I go up? Maybe I think I can go backwards. Stop attacking for a second. So I'm
going to attack you. Oh, it's just unfair. The devs knew what they were doing here too. It's just
one of them runs up from behind you and hits you like three times. The devs knew what they
were doing here. I kind of want to go back though. Specifically for that, that reason right there.
First of all, that's a problem. And that person's already being annoying. It doesn't just annoy you.
It annoys me. I'm going to jump down in a second. I want to go up this way. Can I go up this way?
What? Are you going to do this? Oh, I can break it. Unburdened shield. What is that shield? Unburdened.
Seventy five point six thousand sixty thousand and one. A weird number. A big number. Blood of a
forgotten NPC. I haven't used any of these. I really should. I feel like the game's like going
to end in an hour. I'd do this with everything though. It's all to drink and eat at the same
time at the last boss. This is Resident Evil ruined an entire generation of gamers. It really
did. You know how many fucking red herbs I didn't eat? Yeah. You know how many magnum ammo I carried?
40 hours of gameplay to shoot and miss 12 times at the last boss and maybe hit once. One of them.
We've got to stop doing that. And you know what? I'm going to be the thing that I'm. You know what?
Let's start now. I'm going to start now. You know what? Let's start now. Right? Increases item
discovery. I'm using it. Let's go find something. Item hurry up. This thing's going to. I think it
died. Item actually worked. Do I have coins? I used 40 coins last night and I didn't keep them for the
one part of the game that I needed to keep them for. You know don't ever use any of these. Don't
ever consume them. Don't ever. Always hold it to the very end. I just proved it because now there's
a maze. Plus weapon degradation damage. That's pretty cool. Maybe I should do it. It's right handed
though. I'm a uh you know it's kind of weird. I'm a lefty in this game. I've never played an RPG or
any like from software yet and I've never been a lefty. I'm actually a lefty this whole time.
It's kind of cool. What about Zelda? Is Link? Link is left-handed in Breath of the Wild?
No right? Is he? Link is left-handed in most Zelda games. Oh in the Wii games he's uh
ambidextrous but traditionally left-handed. Oh. Henceforth I shall not interfere. That was I
don't know why that scared me. I actually have to apologize for that. There was like
no reason to get scared by that. I'm gonna open my phone here bro.
Bro I think I have the wrong address for the Halloween party. I'm fucking kind of freaking
out right now. Good thing I'm left-handed.
Shut up. All right here in Anvil. No I was gonna just say something. I want to just.
No I want to put my face into that and push the pins out. It's one of those toy things where you
push like your all the little pins they're like individual pins. You put your hand in it and it
makes a mold of your hand. How many of you guys did that? How many people did the like put your
hand like you know that you put your face into it? This place was once a facade. We crafted
decorative theatrical torture devices for the great ritual. We didn't want to hurt each other
That's a millennial thing. I'm sorry there's three of us talking right now. It's probably
hard to pay attention. Yeah it was a little it was like a weird what was it like a what was
that thing even called? It was a thing that it was a hundreds and hundreds of little little nails
right? What was it called? It had a name. Pin thingy yeah. It wasn't nails. No it was like
it was little pins. They weren't sharp or anything. It might not have even had a name.
Look at this. I need four fragment of tradition. Everything has a name. Pin art toy apparently
or it's a pin screen. Oh okay cool. Should I do damage or I keep complaining about stamina.
I don't think is that like a boomer thing? I feel like that's one of those toys that just
never ends. It's a toy that is always available forever. All right let's go. Actually I have
enough. I feel like I'm talking during the movie but hold on. I can't attack. Oh you thought you
were gonna get me? Nope. Actually wait a minute don't I oh no okay I thought I had one of those
uh let's uh to get another charge of my flask thing. Fable of glitch? What is that?
Oh it's for the it's for the smith source damage. Damn it. Oh fuck it's one of you. Nice.
She talks more than you do. I'm I'm supposed to be talking. Complaining well not complaining
but like addressing a streamer talking too much is like addressing the fact that your hamburger
has a meat patty on it. I just wanted the bun. Less talking. What about a vegan burger?
The patty. The patty in the middle. It's a chicken costume. What is this a reference to?
What is this? Hotline Miami? That is what it is isn't it? Yeah that's cool. How can it be
locked from both sides? I'm not going this way yet. It's called just unlock the door.
This should just lock from both sides. Okay I'm gonna put a thing down here. No and this one
that says not this one and then down right here I'm gonna write this one.
I gotta play it like Hotline Miami and why is this thing stuck and die a dozen times?
Okay I remember Hotline Miami 2. That was when I think about the most angry I've been on stream
on camera because let's be real like everybody knows right getting angry on stream I'm usually
not I'm usually it's like oh whatever I'm like annoyed for a second or it's like oh frustrating
for a second but I very rarely get actually upset truly upset on uh whoa holy shit oh my god
that was unbelievably ridiculous that last five to ten minutes my heart is racing right now
of how ridiculous that was guys wasn't that the most craziest fucking thing you've ever seen on
stream and you're into ever that I've ever done holy shit whoa I'm speechless I mean I'm talking
a lot but I'm speechless I really hope that nobody potentially skipped the last 15-ish minutes of the
stream that would be so oh my you would have missed something I can't I don't even describe it
I'm speechless right now I just got here oh oh oh but those who just got here uh 15 minutes
ago somebody told somebody to skip 15 minutes so I wanted to make everybody that did that um and
listen to that person um question it you missed it what it was 25 minutes ago no it hasn't you
calculated it wrong but lul I appreciate it thank you I like the sympathy lul I appreciate it
go don't fall down that all right I'm up here now oh
oh you suck say something else say something funny he's being toxic
okay that's all I can do here let's drop down locked I think there was another thing to do
this way blah blah blah blah yackety yackety yackety yackety blah blah blah blah
okay so the only way to go is up that way just was checking to see if there's anything else to do
and it does not so let's go she's done locked okay I gotta go up and around today I went here right
yeah okay this is the only way to go I could go down that hole that's the only way to go so
we're gonna drop down it's up one hit I must just turn the stream off after that that just
fucked me up so bad like I was so pissed that I said that and it just that actually
fucked with my head fuck it's how I know where to go if I held it for a little longer
I had a choice let me tell you what the choice was I don't want to lose 17 000 souls so hold on
you have I made a choice the choice was hold it for a long time to make it actually make sense
or stop it immediately and pretend hopefully nobody notices I chose probably not wisely
get out of the way get out of the way
I'm all right yeah imagine if it was like one hit why am I doing it again Jesus Christ
that guy swung so many times in a row one two three four five like I had that too
oh my god I'm not talking anymore for at least 10 minutes get off me what is going on with this
guy in the doorway what was going on with the guy in the doorway
do you like revenge of the sith yeah all right we're good
what oh green herb everything's good now let's go wrongness extra item where is it
stop all right made it finally yikes dungeon gate key up I'm not running through all this
shit again there's another one where is it where is it is it down yeah okay that's much better
there's three of them I think I'll be all right do you like dumb and dumber yeah yeah I am not
you're not making me do that you know any of these games I've played only the popular ones
that are very agreeable to play Dark Souls 3 Bloodborne and Elden Ring and Dark Souls 1 I
haven't done I haven't played any of the other ones I never played Dark Souls 2 Sekiro I played
them all hey do you like things depends on what that thing is okay I got to play this right
Dark Souls 2 is great but different yeah I mean I'm I played through the whole thing
just didn't stream it yeah probably I'll be really honest with you guys you would not have
wanted to watch that it's definitely at least three or four times at least no what am I talking
about they're probably three or four hundred times during my just solo just sitting around
playing Dark Souls 2 where I was insufferable I probably would have lost like 50,000 followers
if you had actually watched me play Dark Souls 2 people would be like holy shit I don't I don't
like this stream why what he's like he's he's being like he's saying awful things why why does
he keep screaming fuck as loud as he can he needs to stop doing that can you imagine somebody just
like fuck fuck I I did not do that I'm kidding that just hurts your voice I nobody would have
wanted to watch that something amazing has spawned no new silly though you sure are swell when your
cycle started an innocent uncorrupted NPC also appeared that hasn't happened for ages hey I
have a fun idea how about you find them and bring them a little gift from me an innocent wouldn't
be able to stay innocent long in this messed up world this guy's evil
oh stop I see a lot of people saying to do that and I mean it's like I'm stop telling me to hit
the pink guy it's like it was funny at first but like mods actually start timing people up for it
holy fuck oh that was the original title of the stream by the way I changed it last second
I think that's an instant kill move whoa oh my goodness all right I'm gonna be honest I don't
think you are real it's not personal but what is what is what is going on with that lately
have you noticed that what is without what is with that what is what is up with that
it's bad stand up where is this person can you do the touring test yep one two three four five six
seven eight nine ten um my fair color is blue and I like the alignment of the planets and shit
like Galileo figured it out uh over this is the train tracks with the five people in the one
person and I have to decide um no I only say hold on hold on hold on this is actually a
fucking huge problem if I don't beat him thank god okay I feel like I've been seeing a lot of
that lately like is he real thing it's like yeah bro I'm fucking real relax this is embarrassing
oh shit I think I am to be civilized or some grim echo of that process whatever it involves
I don't really care to find out and I don't suspect it'll work we've not spawned looking
the way they want us to be rendered but for better or worse this is who I am no torture
can change that it can only be torture please if you can find a way to mask what they hate to see
of me before they tear me apart can I open the door why don't I just open the door can I open
the door oh wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait very important you know usually when
you pick decks decks is like the there's only like probably two or three just straight up
dex weapons in this game I actually really like that I went into this dumping all my points into
decks and luck but you could there's a lot of you could do like hybrid stuff that's like the whole
point that's cool I like it what is this a reference to bloodborne vampire boss that's
not bloodborne Castlevania that's probably more likely yeah Castlevania all right so nearly
heroes were we and now a world needs us please find a way to cover what they hate of me
convince them I'm the civilized adherent they seek nearly we can okay your kind once upheld
all worth saving they ushered change to that worth changing it was not always their own wills
they served oh heap of the stolen crown five of your relics come on nothing here
oh this place is cool Dark Souls 2 scholar the first sin is the best from software game bar none
it's hard to do that after Elden Ring comes out because you know I think Elden Ring it's hard
to put that on the from software tier list because it's kind of every single from software
game in the same game it's every single one of them together so it's kind of like a hard
to put it somewhere friend have you found him have you found the king not yet oh wait I find
okay my heart is pounding my heart is pounding my heart is pounding my heart is pounding I did that
because that would be fucking crazy to see somebody do that you'd be like holy shit this
person is the real deal nobody moves like that I'd be like whoa all right I'm taking this person
way more seriously now shortcut to where unlocked elsewhere come on really yes I'm gonna keep going
oh no I'm gonna cheese this fight I don't want to die here help get me out here wait this is
perfect this is actually perfect there's no way his AI pathing is gonna get this right considering
where he currently is stuck what are you doing can he not come in this room oh my god I thought
he died I thought he was dead I thought I heard the explosion anti-hero uptight ass kick what
cobbled leggings that defy the establishment is right one valiant hero they're not all blocked
are they it's just a mess rooting voice potion Elden Ring is better than Bloodborne yeah but
it's kind of it's in Elden Ring Bloodborne is in Elden Ring they are they are one that's a bad take
I mean I don't think it is also this whole catalog spans like 15 years at this point
and it's they're very similar games that's why I mean it's hard to do it because think about it
think of like Super Mario Brothers and then they could look at Mario Odyssey it's like those are
both really great for their own reasons but Mario Odyssey kind of is it's great but I mean but Super
Mario Brothers is it's so good it's so classic it's hard to do that is Mario Odyssey objectively a
better video game than Super Mario Brothers like what do you think the answer is like probably yes
right but is it you it's hard to say that Super Mario oh what's the best Super Mario game well
Super Mario Brothers of course the original it started at all the classic is it a better video
game than Mario Odyssey that's that's you can't it's hard to do that you can't do that they're in the
same the same franchise same developers well for the most part right or at least um somewhat
Mario's been around for a little bit longer I just play games and like them that's a good take you
know what that's a great take all right let's not mess this up not this gigachad I'm a gamer
it's kind of cool that there's there's so many different genres of game they fill up so many
different uh niches a lot Super Mario World is probably the best I would probably agree with that
it's kind of sits right at that spot philosophy Andy yeah but whatever oh hold on a second I
want to see this that's Street Fighter Metroid Zelda um I don't know who that is that's Peg
Ganon Dr. Robotnik Diablo who's that up there Carmen Sandiego okay Carmen Sandiego the the
Madman from Mega Man uh who's up top who is that Freddy no that's not that's not
Freddy Krueger it's supposed to be Wario all right what about over here I think that's it
this river of blood is interesting I don't know what that was hero Stumper chainsaw it's a dex
weapon it's a pure dex weapon what this is not what I thought this was I thought it was just
I thought it was a chainsaw it's a chainsaw on a stick I wasn't imagining it was going to be
just a chainsaw it's a thrust weapon but I mean I don't have anything much better I'm going to
upgrade this how is it with it in my offhand I actually kind of like it I don't know what that
is but weird these things are not explode right whoa it's a comedy weapon it's one of the few
pure dex scaling weapons I've found in the game so far so it's a it's a weapon for me who is that
Bowser maybe it's supposed to be Bowser oh cool wait did I did I see in chat on the right straight
ahead who is that I couldn't I didn't figure out who that was Eman Sephiroth Nostalgaia once loved
you loved heroes I mean but you betrayed us the betrayal of heroes I mean yeah what does it do oh
source no how have I I've got a billion souls right now I have a billion I don't want to die
oh oh do you throw stuff oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh come on this is backed off where is that one
down here get away from me hardcore pill we're gonna cheese this too no yeah we are do it again
keep it hardcore keep it hardcore come on do it come on do it I might be able to get him from here
I'm so paranoid about this thank God I need a bon fire now who that helps
that's also good drop down here
fuck I don't give a shit I don't give a shit I don't give a shit I don't care I don't care
I don't care I don't care I don't care I don't care I don't care I don't care
i don't care i don't care just don't care and and i go i just don't care and that's how i'm gonna
get through it i literally don't care see i don't care literally figuratively i just don't care
see i don't even care
i didn't want to come in here but i have to stay in here now we have to stay in here
i'm not doing it on purpose there's nowhere for me to go dude why is this so far away
whoa nice nice all right that's even quicker
we're good this we're good we're good we're good i remember this hello
i'll be back later i'm back now where is there a bonfire it has to be one right did i just miss
it completely go get your souls dude i don't i don't know where i am i i don't i don't know
where i am i don't know where i don't know where to go i don't know where i am i don't remember
this i don't know i don't know where i am i don't remember this i actually need to slow down though
because yeah i am not gonna lose here oh no just jumped a hundred feet in the air give me a crit
please but you never know who's gonna run up the stairs i have to be ready
all right so now where i know where the my souls are power star oh because it's super mario
oh i don't want to aggro that thing that's dumb that's what i was waiting to have happen but no
wait i need hold on no no i want that item something up there right like up into the left
i have to get the my souls are over there in front of that door i think i have to go this way or
else i won't be able to get my souls back yeah come back now yeah fuck this i'm out of here
where does this go oh my okay um sure i guess i'll do that be careful here loot heroes loot uh all
right hold on a minute let's not get too weird about this follow me all the way down here please
don't shoot it nice aim that's ridiculous what does this do get this shit away from me this gas
what the hell oh my goodness get off the screen get off the screen get off my screen get off my
screen get off my screen get off my screen get off my screen all right i need to figure out how to
oh um don't what's running that was a weird sound it sounds like you just got tased god damn it
there's not that much left just be be careful i got it
fuck no it's so difficult i didn't know where to go i fell down and lost my fucking souls i fell
accidentally two deaths ago and i thought i had enough health and then i ah god damn it i don't
even know where to go what's with your laughs today they're very goofy fuck this place sucks
i don't even care i'm just running i don't care just hit me again don't care i am i'm just running
to the exit get down here i'm killing everything hey no more mr nice streamer all right i just
i'm fucking pissed it's so far away you're missing the bonfire where is it you mean to tell me there
was a bonfire there the whole time and i just didn't find it what the hell is it it's outside
the castle didn't i go out there what do you mean it's outside so it's the room with the blood it's
to the left let me check outside though if there's one sitting right here i am going to be very very
mad yeah but that this one i mean there's technically a bonfire here but it's not
connected to anything god damn it oh that stinks oh man i just saw a big circle i thought you were
just standing here and i think that i didn't i didn't oh that's i'm sad it was right in front
of me too it's right there running around going how do i get out of here where do i go i help i
have 30 000 souls it was right there the whole time shucks i need new i need new gear you know
what i mean is dark souls um i'm thinking skull head i'm thinking yep that's cool i'll admit
neither boxers or the bone legs actually i like that too how am i fat rolling really this stuff
doesn't weigh anything all right i guess i i think that's better i don't know take my time again
sans sees a skeleton sans now don't waste these now incomprehensible drip all right what kind
of weapon is this it follows you up and down stairs i mean i've heard of homing missiles before
but that's another i'm just i don't even i'm running what's up dude i finally i was locked on
and i wasn't for some reason i'm gonna puke anything glowing here wait oh it's a source
weapon i don't have enough memory anything else uh i can definitely get there 6 000 right that's
not gonna be enough all right let's see what it is what about the lore an out of place blade that
harnesses glitch what's this from see how to go haunted thoughts new helmet not fat rolling all
right that's where i'm not gonna die going down here but that's not where i need to go i need to
move this over this has to move where's the room i'm killing you because you're just gonna be a
pain in the ass okay you have a two swing pattern that was weird and you know it all right that was
weird where did this guy come from i have to get this little shit out of here god damn it no don't
deep ice yeah do you cast your magical bullshit god cast your magical bullshit no one cares
you make the weirdest sounds a lot of air a lot of air comes out of my esophagus a lot of air
just kind of shoots out it has nowhere to go okay how do i get over there i don't know how do i get
over there shit i have to go down so if i pull that one will that do it i don't think i have very
many souls anyways no i have to it's so stressful when you've got these lizard people casting these
weird spells all right so go over here and then i think i did it wrong i know it's too many things
to look at i don't know i feel like it's the other one does the i have to get up there and then
oh they don't know what to do okay i haven't been here yet oh i don't want to fall off the
fucking edge give me a safe spot don't love it i have to commit i have to commit i have to commit i
have to commit that's why you commit i don't have any heals left uh my heart my heart hurts
i'm not even up there either there's probably a dozen more enemies before i can get where i need
to go this is not even correct i gotta get up there and then around the corner um that sucks
i don't remember how to get up there oh i don't i don't is it all in the right spot still i'm so
sad what am i having to the reduced agro range that other guy didn't even see me oh god oh that
stinks i think i know where i'm going i see i have this issue when i'm under stress i'm not committing
anything to memory so in my brain this is all just a blank canvas with enemies attacking me right my
number one priority is not to remember what route to go it's don't die to the thing trying to kill
you so it may as well just be a blank canvas i think it's lined up already though yeah i think
so i think i'm all right and then through here and then this way get away from me okay thank god if
it reset i'd be very sad okay we're good things are going fine i thought someone was behind me
all right you two pieces of shit come on that thing is always like another second later a lot
of a blood of a blood of blood all right pull it and then how do i do i have anything that connects
to that one will this one move and go over there what happens if i pull it twice just go back to
the original bro it's right there i don't want to make oh i didn't want to make any decisions till i
got a good view don't rush my decision making there we go was there a lever did i just not see
it this one there but i need to move this that way but i could only move this that way if i go
that way over there to the left pull this one to turn it but i can't go that way unless i turn that
one to go this way so just jump there's no jump in the game there's no jump i drop down i need to
move that one can i get no i can't unless i drop down that's the one i need to pull so how do i
get over there all right very clearly it wants to move this one to here but the only way i can
physically do that is if hold on and turn it back he's so smart i always fucked that move up all
right let's go finally here's the door line it up spin this shit around again so now i can just run
up the stairs we're good this keep is rank with conviction and pride perhaps your patheticness
preserves you from such folly but that was a compliment your deal why are you always here
i told you to give my present to the innocent now he's been ruined by experiences thanks to you
how can i trust you again after breaking my heart suck it up reservoir it's not my heart that
matters evil the great one in this keep had swell intentions she wanted to remake the world like it
used to be but reversion is still transformation it doesn't really matter that suffering can bring
about change the problem is that change brings about suffering she made a boo-boo sound familiar
if you want to heal the heart that actually matters unburden her i'd like a checkpoint
can i jump out the window game stinks now we're in vampire land sure would be nice to have
50 000 souls right now that'd be great i feel like we're getting into the end game i'm wondering
30 dexterity what's the new ability refill access on use refill access on use what what
stuff even do refills access what is access i didn't even looked at that in the menu what is
its ammo it read uh that would be great and have wouldn't it wait are you sure refills your ammo i
can't put it on the hotbar okay um there's this way there's that way this is shortcut at the bottom
of the level i mean it has to be although this doesn't really make anything faster it's good to
have it unlocked in case there's another one it's good to know i mean there's a bonfire right here
anything to remember yep health boost on parry i that's a really neat feature i just want enough
to go level up one more time that should do it yes because i don't want to lose 10 000 souls
enemy is relentless what are my thoughts on the game so far i would classify this as a game that
i'm gonna give it the term hidden gem very truthfully when he said it's like dark souls
meets paper mario it's got a bunch of references and you know what else too it's a game that's
baked around a kind of comedy but all the comedy and all the humor and all the joke stuff
has been it hasn't been really heavy-handed or anything it's been very enjoyable so very charming
bundle of sticks had the king ever closer with each pixelated step was it truly happening
if they'd listen to this lady again
jesus
rocked by your desire this is peach run home
strength
okay
oh this place is
humility can't open this show your airy knuckles
all right that's a that's another time that person up 10 minutes you guys are so wacky i'm
getting too cocky trying to take two of these on the same time caught on a plant you never
used the chainsaw oh my god i forgot it was in my hand that's true i'll i'll upgrade it when
is this this is a friend no it's not now he's angry i gotta go upgrade this thing i definitely
do no don't whatever i'm running i can do that too you know i just think of uh fenrir from smite
see the whole world can't you not really all right here's i'm gonna do this good conviction
oh she said it bro what is going on right now it's
meat finish it the awesome stick figure crashed upon them like almighty thunder
rip them to ribbons my good fellow this is gonna drive me crazy
oh no get it turn it off turn it off foreign queens chill that one had a lot more health
shit i was lucky ah it can't be serious okay that wow uh-huh what the hell was that
i need to upgrade my weapon bro your cd is broken no did i put toothpaste all over it and cleaned it
off was that did that actually work i feel like that was a weird myth that was completely made up
that everybody kind of believed did it actually do anything something about the the crystals
in the toothpaste right something weird bro i'm just telling you like it was i'm just telling you
that's what i that's what people thought why did people think that anybody have like an actual
answer it was just wild speculation it worked on minor scratches it was a light abrasive
that could smooth out the surface so it wasn't total bullshit then
gosh tell gaya why is this weird right hold on humility
purify or release
faith are we releasing or we're purifying
you give me a poll release or purify
now uh i'll reach out to you for a second here give you a little bit time to decide
what are we doing release purify it's an important hint what she's saying wait say it again i want
to hear the whole thing i'm in faith right
release she said right she said right but i have to listen to chat here
she said you do not think that right exceeds your instincts fidelity is next to the all
sorry chat you picked the wrong one oops yeah there are a lot of spells in the game
that's a cool little easter egg oh shit wait isn't isn't humility down here okay
wait wait wait say it again what do i need to do okay lose the ego humble myself
okay step on the button all right i have to step on the button humble yourself
oh
i don't know is it a certain outfit where did this person come from
come fight me over on come fight me over on the button and see what happens
i've never dodged that move i mean this is kind of the opposite of humility i took all of my gear
off and bm'd that person i don't think i'll be able to do this i was so prideful that i was
proving that i could kill that person with no gear i think i blew it wait a minute whoa seven
thousand bucks i can put the whole set on now that's cool how it actually turns it into like a 3d
model i don't get it sit there for more than 10 seconds just wait there it is let's go there's
a huge ass tower perfect fit it's a big heavy thing it's like a roof minecraft tetris
okay
i think i've done all the towers still the ones that i know i can do
you know what games would you say the best at oh if i'm being honest it's probably games where
you have to press a button very fast clicker games name one game where that's important
name one game okay i'll tell you i'll tell you you little bastards
in metal gear solid there is a part where you have to press circle as fast as you can
to withstand torture i was always the guy in the room when friends of mine would play this
just hand the controller to jeremy it gets so hard it gets almost impossible but if you do it
and you do it the whole time and you actually don't you actually withstand it it unlocks
an omega item at the end of the game they used to hand the controller to me
you little bastards i'm sorry i thought it would be funny am i sorry let's go
now you know what yeah not not sorry
oh it's bold coming from somebody that's five eight you've seen me sprint i'm fast i bet i'm
faster than you now i can only do this for about one and a half full seconds before i have to sit
down for an hour but you better believe i've i've been running faster than you faster than a speeding
bullet yeah i would actually be a really bad superhero now that i sit here and think about
this even if i had powers i would run out of gas in in fucking 10 minutes i would be like
punch punch kick kick kick slide kick and i would take out one person and just sit down
and on the on a bench and just breathe heavy for like two hours just save me for the final boss
you know what i mean like you all right you can just relax for the entire time that like thanos
is attacking us but at the very end we're just gonna give you like an espresso and a bag of
Doritos and just all right he thanos is in that room we've got him cornered jerma get in there
and that would fuck him up so we have no idea and that's it that's all i would be able to do
and i would have to tell it be like hey hey hey wait before i get in there can you wear him down
so in 10 minutes i'll be able to kill him and they'll do their whole thing you know everyone
will fight of and it'll be epic and then everyone will be like defeated and it'll just be me in my
fucking underwear with like with like a fucking club and then he just like obliterates me in one
second oh this is a shortcut 30 000 souls you're 40 not 90 you could definitely do a roundhouse kick
yeah i would just queue up a huge roundhouse kick and just it would be really really shitty
my leg would only come up about a foot and a half but i would i would kick him with such force in
the stomach just make some insta puke and and then i pull like my i would tear some like two
or three muscles in my leg like superman kind of comes in and just laser eyes him why is superman
in marvel well we're talking about a multi-franchise level threat which who knows
you know like let's be honest for a minute here i feel like marvel's going so far into this like
phase five phase six phase seven at some point i'm expecting a like gordon ramsay style fucking
cooking show in phase seven like wolverine is one of the judges ad i don't know like captain marvel
and like fucking cyclops are competing and shit i feel like we're going there i like phase eight
i don't know what to do germa you seem like the type of guy to bring a lunchbox to a superhero
fight you know okay what about the magic rock that's in that lunchbox that has the power of
50 grenades i can say about that that's not powerful against like thanos but then i would
just distract him i would do the super funny comic relief thing where i would just be behind
Thanos and be like oh Thanos look over here and he'd be like oh what's that little worm
insect and i distract him long enough for somebody to hurt him he's the character everybody hates one
all right somebody said this one day and it was it was pretty funny you know sometimes you have
to have a little bit of humility right somebody said one day i don't know i by the way i don't
agree with this person but it was funny and sometimes you know whatever it's like if you're
making a joke whatever somebody said that this stream was a marvel movie with all the quips and
none of the fighting it was just like germa your stream is the worst kind of marvel movie it's just
only jokes and there's no action or anything it's just like quips i disagree i disagree with it
wait which one goes up this one it's wrong but it's funny oops oh no no that was you that got
hurt not me i would just freak Thanos out to a point you know what i mean like everyone always
expects like we're gonna fight maybe it just wouldn't even fight him we're just like one
i would be like i want to join you Thanos i will join you it doesn't he like when people do that
yeah and then and then like i don't know during one of the biggest battles there's like 10 people
and i'm there and i have access to like the pa system i was gonna fart into the pa microphone
and just fuck the whole thing up it's gonna be what the fuck was that what the hell's going on
and then the confusion they'll be able to get him oh my god that is so unfunny is that what he said
okay i need to cleared pretty much everything Loki tried that germa and look at him now i didn't
see and watch Loki wait Loki in the Loki series farts over the pa what no i go from here literally
yes he does liars liars liars liars all right there's everyone's line the word i'm getting
called out by my girlfriend here she said you would never publicly fart and you know what that's true
i would have the opportunity to do that to distract Thanos and i would be like i can't
it's gross no it's gross and that was what yeah i wouldn't be able to do it no don't open all the
doors at once wowie what a bad room to fight two of these things and god what is i don't know what
it does when it fills but i don't want to know what's this okay wait there might be actually
something here anything uh oh strength and source but i mean you get the bonuses for doing it anyways
holly not even you are safe from making random messages mean that's funny okay so now where do
i go you said i'm laughing here where do i go i have to like do something here hey apologize
for making me sound mean earlier too but what if you were being mean and i just don't know it
wait i know what to do what's gonna happen oh my goodness threshold of the fanatic sacristy
last of the great one lieutenant almighty guide you in us your reign of terror ends
oh it's this is fucking
i'm dead oh shit wait i wasn't paying attention i was doing the stupid thing where i'm like oh you
i got 10 minutes whatever blood-borne it's bad it's real that's kind of a long walk i guess
there's the shortcuts but still but no no no no i want to upgrade where's the smith where's the
smith where's the smith other bonfire don't know how much longer the game will be i think we're at
the last boss i imagine this is the last great one right so they said find out i have to beat it what
are your thoughts on the modernizing of mcdonald's restaurants i know that that
question is bait because they know it's going to get me to talk for like an hour and a half about
it but um everybody already knows is there another did i miss a shortcut i feel like i missed a
shortcut i was reading chat sorry all right let's go i'm messing around perfect dodges i'm dead
great yo no great great great great great great great great great great great oh that music that's
got really cool too i want to upgrade this physical that's all right then upgrade it i know but i
need to go to a where where is he get this stuff out of the way wasn't there i swear to god there
was another one right down here i don't want to tether to it i just want to upgrade i'm finding
all kinds of new shit right now wait this probably this is like a graveyard hold on there's probably
something here right this is kind of an interesting graveyard shit i don't know i thought there was a
smith right back there somewhere in the uh behind the maze i guess i could go this way and then run
back i'm gonna this is like one of the final fights of course i'm gonna be prepared of course
i'm gonna be prepared all right so then the way to get out of here to go back to where that
i actually don't remember where is the way to get back to the bonfire i don't know i'll just beat
it without it gives a shit i got this you only got 10 days left to play frog detective i know
i got it don't worry can you do this fight and use your trump voice um let's see how i feel
i'm gonna be such a greedy asshole too hold on there's an item uh there's two uh um wait wait
wait wait nobody fight me time out time out time out time out time out the sword is messed up again
what's going on i want to get up there uh new plan forget about the boss i'm going to clear this room
and go do the other little things in this area i feel like there's something else i'm missing
we have permission to swag out no not yet no when i beat the last boss you have complete
permission to swag out i'm gonna need you to contain it for a little bit now let's be honest
what's what are we swaging out for right you don't want to preemptively swag out because
i mean you got to make sure it's worth it you look like bender from futureama oh yeah it's me
bender oh hey fry wait oh hey it's me bender that's a big one that started out really rough
whatever i don't i told you yesterday i i don't give a shit anymore oh my goodness i think he
actually does give a shit and his feelings were hurt uh-oh evil arc no i'm fucking kidding i do
want to clear this though i don't want you to do that thing you first of all you die now
i was running okay that's that part done i don't need to worry about that that's fine i wasn't
prepared for the crit and it's going to be the downfall grandma you have a right-handed weapon
uh this being in my left hand i get extra crit damage only if i swing with my left hand god
damn it that thousand people up here yeah it's uh swinging with the left hand just does more damage
for this exact character it was built it's precision to be able to do the things i'm doing
right now it's just it's just so goddamn annoying that tracking on face it the it
the tracking on that trident it's just like heart is pounding well get up there and help me fight
i don't want to do this wait till the last 10 minutes bullshit that's my gig i think i'm just
gonna run hey bro my summon sign is at the door yeah but your name is is piss drinker 5000 i'm not
i'm not gonna i'm not i'm gonna have you on stream okay i'm not doing this again i need to be very
good about this and here's how we're gonna play it who cares run figure out i cared this isn't
there a blacksmith right here i don't care i actually do have to get a couple of kills
because i'm gonna open the chest i need what 10 11 000 to open the uh chest and the door bring it
on yeah all right the the wolves in the bathrobe you just have to spam and just hope i get a crit
because it'll kill them okay going up don't you kill me i you're gonna you're gonna throw
in a homing missile at me that move sucks asshole it's it's so fast and it just like
it just homes to you and they can throw it from wherever they are on the map and it just like
teleports to your character how can we get so mad at the end i'm not mad at all i'm having a great
time do not confuse um do not confuse jokey frustration with anger i'm fine i am not mad
at all right now i'm just coming out here i'm just relaxing don't you hate it when you're really like
annoyed or mad about something and you just and you and you and you need to talk and it's just
like i i i'm just trying so hard to form normal fucking sentences because the whole time you just
want to check this out i've had my eyes closed this whole time just opened up i've been really
mad at a game before and i'm just like i i i don't know do you see that all right this is
gonna be risky almost didn't get it we're good let's chill out there's so much shit up here very
good i have enough to open both of those things let's just not screw it up i'm gonna do this
because i don't this person's really annoying dude unplug the steering wheel and use a normal
controller that'd be so hard all right only one enemy left we did it all right what's in here
ruined lifting barbell probably strength equipment load hmm i think i'm gonna put that on at 58 what
is it normally 67 it's really not that much shit this is 13 sounds good expensive but hopefully
there's something in here security code i think shaking no security code keep memory on death
pretty nifty mario mario mario i don't think that was worth 10 000 souls but i only have two heels
left um just do this again wait is there anything else here that i didn't do before i leave to
refresh so that's to go down i think i'm all right but i'll level up a couple more times and then
it's gonna be a lot i think all right how we doing cool let's try it again please listen to us the
bonfire at the top of the lift here but we only you're gonna have to only listen to the music one
more time because i'm gonna kill the boss right now can can we bet um yeah i mean if the mod wants
to do it i'm not fucking around this time as you'll see in a second i'm so curious where this goes
definitely goes up where the hell is that uh good luck everybody i'm gonna pop every cooldown
and run in there oh shit i thought i didn't have the heal on well that's unfortunate i thought i
had i didn't switch whatever she's she's killing me in two hits i'm kind of concerned about this
she's hitting me two times and i die how could you do this to me oh no that person's sad i know
that this is gonna give me crits crit damage up and off hand but i wonder if it's worth just
two-handing it i don't know i tried to do the thing in these games where you press the button
and leave but you can't you cannot do that maybe parry's would not vote yes on this i don't know
who's up to you do what you want with your points who knows she does that move when she
cues up and then dives forward slash i might be able to get it pretty perfectly
somebody said get this elevator i don't know where to go for it i feel like i've explored
everything here maybe not maybe i should go look all right i'm going for it i'm gonna try
i'm going parry strategy see if it works she's broken she's broken she's broken she's broken
she's broken what do i do where do i go should i wrap around and try to stab her oh my god i win
what that was a perfect parry slow it down oh my god she's broken
oh my god just stay alive the parry breaks her animations don't holy shit what the what
i know the strat i know the strat dude this is like hi what the hell do you like my song
i'm gonna i'm gonna break this and just win who cares how are you still losing because this boss
has a move that just goes and you're dead get more physical resistance i put all my points
into a good thing i could go buy a lottery ticket i uh i'm gonna really lucky today i have eight
equipment load i can't even wear anything this shit's made out of plastic there's a closer beacon
all right if there is actually a closer beacon i want can i get directions okay from where i'm
standing right now where do i go please give me directions in the door okay now we're left
thanks dude isn't this i want to i want where's the smith i'm going to the smith it's down here
right like i'm no where's the smith tether warp yeah teleport uh you cannot teleport this game is
sort of like uh dark souls one there is no teleporting between bonfires there are a shit
load of shortcuts the game is full of them it's you're supposed to do that but i have i have no
memory so it's hard to do that i want to make a milkshake after the stream but don't have any
ice cream make banana got any ice you got ice jesus that scared me ice oat milk banana freeze
the bananas i'll save you some time oat milk frozen bananas a little bit of peanut butter
you're done that's all it takes peanut butter banana smoothies are phenomenal what do you guys
eat it has to be a way where i do not take her out of this right this is cheap and you all know
it well i'm running out of these shurikens so it's not over yet no now i haven't okay now here's the
plan ready check this out okay now i'm gonna put this sword in my off hand and quit the absolute
hell out of her ready shit takes too long oh it's punched her in the face i tried to do it but it
didn't work got it what oh what's with this dropkick shit stop doing that all right wait
got it yes i don't even need the exploit finished her all right i can go turn that thing on now phase
two right do i become elden lord hmm how much should i use i like it matters if i could upgrade
this i would use it so i have to go all the way back to that place underneath what looked like
firelink shrine i didn't do anything evil sticks nation of tradition breaker of meaning
your story is over roll credits what did i just get a wicked shit ending i just got a shit ending
oh wait minstrel this hero's story endures thanks dad appreciate it has lost his meaning
his purpose so he prevents the next chapter of your story from unfolding you must confront him
final boss grief as before has whisked him away to the start of sequence a place where meaning was
once conveyed it long ago became inaccessible to heroes we must find you a way inside perhaps
a way which your kind was never meant to see meet me below this husk of a keeper memory of a monarch
it's a little one that's tiny return to the edge of the wild you shall pry open the narrator's mouth
and extract the information return you okay uh this is where it is uh i'm gonna go up though
i was wondering i was like where the hell is even is this thing are you the sus guy that's my little
brother we share this account anything you've ever heard of this channel like outside of being on
this channel is my little brother did it your hero will come your hero will come weird i do anything
in this room there are no heroes huh except for me i'll be a hero you are the little brother
no no i'm not if you've seen every time you see mario kart we played on this channel that's my
little brother how do i get back to the beginning of the game hey dude i think i saw you at the
at warp tour moshing in the mosh pit uh well i'm sorry to say that was not me it must have been my
little brother your little brother's got quite the life yeah it's pretty cool okay this is the fun
this is the fun time right return icon oh cool this is the fun part where i get to have no idea
where the hell i'm going and a thousand of you are gonna make fun of me the other 60 million
people that are here will be very nice to me and tell me exactly where i need to go and help me
and do the best they can to make sure that i can get there in a timely manner i'm just gonna walk
such as your nature yet you never succeed my success was never measured by the outskirts
seemed to want perhaps yours is not measured by your class and the kings such as i thought
the success of a father is measured by that of their progeny um yeah it's the bug viewers and
i got a huge huge bug audience they're super cool too they're always like super supportive and
awesome it's really cool i was thinking about uh changing the stream to be like bugs only like
no humans anymore how's it gonna be like a bug streamer it is done then the fanatics reign of
order has finally passed but the crown long repressed is now only ash forgive me but what
is a kingdom with no king what should be saved if there's no station to keep it safe when its
saviors inevitably pass here take this the heirloom too has been forgotten
nostalgaia has no need of it now good tradition died with the good king good tradition died
what is it strength wonderful point maker i have a final decision to make of what i'm gonna upgrade
but this is kind of cool what's the scaling everything wait i can remember this throughout
places never meant for of these corals leads to the npc city respite those facilitating the great
ritual cast off their costumes and simply be but it has changed to reach the narrator
venture through the npc city and into nostalgaia's forsaken tutorial find a staging room entrance
beneath the wiles and meet me within okay i was in a lot of those earlier meet me within okay so
i feel like i have no idea what that is i have absolutely no clue i remember walking around in
it i think there's one here somewhere to get there i'm just gonna run isn't there one of those here
somewhere i hear you're on good terms with the roaches yeah the beetles the ants the roaches
bees mantis that's dangerous staging area shit um my eye is so itchy do you like jumping spiders
jumping spiders are cute they have um they have a they have like a face uh staging area right here
all right here it is okay so this is where i need to be npc city npc city i explored down
here a lot so i'm actually kind of glad i knew where this was hello ah this is where i couldn't
go before but you were drawn from some forgotten time and space the memory of you does not fit
and that too gives you power fear not the shallowness from whence you came for its
meaning is multi-dimensional embrace the depth of what you are some areas have collapsed into
a one-dimensional surface you can traverse these areas by harnessing your inner flatness
approach this wall and think flat thoughts new ability flat counter when you see this
above an enemy stand still and press b i've seen that before in pc city so can i do it
from the strings with which he finds you you seek to confront the power of story
leave me to my misery oh okay is that you whoa this is weird what's this
hall of heroes wait this is this is the yeah this is the tutorial okay so this is back in the very
beginning of the game set it here can't really level up or anything but i keep going dude isn't
that so crazy in the tutorial this door was the end game imagine being able to walk through there
this is the last part this is the end game final boss through here it's so insane i actually do
think that's i like it's i like that actually interesting to me like you're so close but so far
i like it if you don't like it get out of here all right what are you doing here
here nice the memory saber strength god damn it yeah you unlock it here tail of luck why did you
have to do decks because in the first three or four hours of the game i found a cool weapon that
scaled off of decks and off of luck i know you're probably saying that's not true but it is because
luck gets me more crit more crit damage in my offhand the scales with dexterity therefore it's
perfect for the class that i'm playing right now i mean this is kind of rude modified cane of what
was it modified cane of helpfulness there's so many cool strength weapons it's just an axe
i feel like this thing is pretty good for being in the other hand and i committed to dual welding
as well that's why bloodborne oh right wait i just hit let me try that jesus dude wait what
what just happened i am so confused right now did that like stun him all right you gotta dodge
through that not to the left or to the right oh there it is of course you're gonna let me
have that item too but um it's gonna be strength strength decks can't put it on and remember it
though it's a lot but whatever freeze damage to abominations yeah cool it looks like a most
all right so it seems like a huge amount of items scale with strength decks deck source nothing
really scales with luck so i mean the crit thing is luck but there's no weapon that it does this
luck is not a stat that and you know what i don't want to talk to you but i will if you want to
heal the heart that actually matters unburden her maybe i should do this to something or is
this a bad end or something i i unburden something and i get the bad end i'm not doing it nobody
likes you that was mean i only said that because i look over a chat and i see everybody say leave
don't talk to him don't leave don't even look at that guy i just heard a uh huh where is it
what is the i thought it was a shadow i thought it was a shadow on the ground i didn't think it
was a bunch of holes i thought it was a shadow the hall of junior hero jeez not this again i
didn't read all right we're good left-handed all right cool good show what happened there
can you please do your chickadee d d noise no no all right no i don't want him this upset all
right let's do it again away away are you great killing right it's all your fault comes for me so
i thought it was you grave stealing rat you grave stealing rat and that's what i actually thought
it was can we just do the other part of the combo you're really making all of us mad you're just
making everybody mad now let's try this again this time i will be aware of that and you have not
aggroed yet so let me just cheese this i think that's cheese enough you too you still hit me
okay that's the i have a lot of points in decks that thing is actually saving me a lot of time
that's the one great reason to use decks that item and i feel like i still don't understand
how that thing works easy maker key drake saber oh remember i asked how to get up here wait a
minute oh my god this is very girl scout cookie um i like the mint ones ladder here too i'm not
supposed to even be here all right what was this for silver of tradition oh no hold on that is that
all that's here i think i've i've i've been here now yeah i've been here before yeah i've done this
already well that's cool that it wraps all the way around but how do i like this please play a link
between worlds right now you're gonna have to wait at least a week so you're gonna have to wait at
least a week and up to um a couple of years at least there's a range in there somewhere
and halfway through that range i might just not feel like playing it so i probably won't play it
oh i said come on this thing seems so cool reminds me of banjo kazooie talking holy
you should play kerbal space program dude is this a fake memory or did i play kerbal space program
one for like 30 40 minutes and i just couldn't comprehend it couldn't do it i couldn't stand it
and i was like guys i'm sorry i can't play this game that happened didn't it i remember yeah no
it really did i think i did not on stream is this is this has to be a real memory maybe i like
was gonna make a video on it and i was just like 30 minutes in i was like no fucking away
i never streamed it maybe i was gonna make a video on it that's probably what it is maybe when it was
it was really really kind of popular back in the old youtube days that sounds more accurate yeah
well that's what happened well jerma will please play animal crossing again i want to see your
island dude i'm gonna go back to that island it's gonna be a bunch of fucking skeletons
i i haven't played animal crossing in like a year and a half that would be depressing i don't want
to do that i have to start a new land or something this is such a cool feature udder annihilator
it's gonna be a strength weapon you don't come on damn it all right i probably don't have enough
to remember it whoa this thing is kind of amazing 100 of almost everything i can't remember it um
but hold on increased damage for remembered weapons very stamina regen speed is at 20
i need one i need to remember one more thing i think i can get there yeah i can definitely
get there yeah let's do it secret cow level oh my god diablo 2 so now increased stamina regen
speed that's huge you'd like actually go down that way but no diablo didn't diablo going into
like a beta or something in a month i've not paid very much attention to that game i've been
i've just been so i don't even want to know is anybody is it good has anybody tried it at
any of the times they've a lot of people to play it yeah i have not paid attention to pretty much
anything blizzard in god it's been since probably overwatch one maybe hearthstone a little bit but
not really not really i go from here flat there but yeah i go down there most of like wow wow
classic um i gave it a look i'll be honest but i mean just not into it anymore like at all these
are red i'm drinking this holy shit that's bad overwatch 2 is decent i've heard that it's i've
heard it's pretty good i just have no interest the only thing that would really want me to play a
blizzard game is if the uh like if diablo 4 is holy shit bro bro you have no idea diablo 4 is
you have no idea and then i'd be like holy shit i don't have i have no idea apparently and i'm
maybe that's right that's probably what it would take no bro you have no idea that's so bad that's
a run ruiner right there where you going we're going run ruiner i'm not gonna let you do that
i think that's the other side of the sewer thing that i was looking at in the very beginning of
the game who even is hitting who here any memories satisfying noise finally the smith where are you
finally the smith where are you oh thank goodness last time i'll probably see your face this anvil
must have been brought here from one of the npc's workshops we used to retreat to our staging rooms
to recuperate and to repair our battered costumes but these ain't costumes being forged here
this anvil has been pounded with hatred we use it out of love tradition is more than any instance
of its work the full power of the smith's hammer is restored we serve you always hero cool well it
this thing i'm gonna i'm gonna max this out because it's obviously for the build
i need one more of these to get it maxed but also do i want to upgrade something
the hammer serves that i feel like i need to do something i could just put the default dagger up
actually no it's this one although it's not remembered i feel like it's not worth it
i could put a point i could put one point two points in strength and one point in
source and be able to put this on but it's not remembered probably this the key is kind of cool
i have it memory unlocked dex 1.1 i probably would have done this one two point wait a minute
excuse me this thing is a dex weapon loot heroes loot i need to get this remembered where do i go
festivity row maybe that might maybe that's the other hand this one's 2.3 i had options here
gilded axe or loot heroes loot two point uh i mean this is 2.2 scaling i have it remembered
i feel like i could just beef this up like crazy this also uh this is kind of ugly this is a
two-hander this is unburdened but kind of cool i think it's i'm gonna go loot oh it's an axe
that's funny i mean if it scales this well off of decks then why not it's a guitar hero controller
let's level it up why not i definitely want this to be maxed out because that's the best
weapon i have for my character all right so where is it let's do it tradition right wait what do i
need piece of tradition so this is fragment of tradition fragment of tradition piece of
tradition 120 193 now what is it now 112 183 121 272 pretty good it's not even remembered yet
hammer serves the hero always so i have to go back to that kind of loot dungeon i really i'm not sure
where that is maybe it's right here that would be so cool if it was but hold on where does this go
repurposed cane of support the combo with these two together is way way better strengthen decks
i like this thing a lot it's great it's a great follow-up from the other side
good stuff finally got my build it only took to the last like 30 minutes of the game
every hero who spawned upon nostalgaia i told their tale defined their tellings this is the end of
your story start of sequence oh this is the i made it to the end zone we're not doing this
you're ignoring the peppermint guy what peppermint guy all of heroes wait there's a door back here
that i can open now all right hold on let me hang out here for a minute there's shit i can do here
where is some of it there's some of those glitch doors here somebody ate 30 peppermints and is it
gonna shit their pants um why are you eating that many what are you what are you doing have eat eat
three okay looking for a glitch door i heard it blinking where is it further away now what the
hell is making that sound is it just the torches and it's just messing with me it's in the wall
or is it down it might be all the way down oh look what i found what was the point of this
no point no point is it a memory maybe oh it's definitely that yes it is it's going to be the
target chess piece there it is i think that might be better it's 18 13 20 my fat rolling
shit i am well it's cool to know all right let me go back to where i was the shortcut here really
really really freaking cool my addiction to peppermint started around christmas i needed
him for a gingerbread house but there was some left and i ate the whole bag in a week and i ate
two bags in a week and now i would say that i eat 20 a day i'm gonna tell you that's probably not a
great idea i don't know how harsh that is on you but yeah and i'm not i'm not a i'm not a doctor i'm
not a scientist uh but i don't that does not sound healthy sounds like a lot but yeah um i'm
sorry that happened or thank you for the feedback i don't know what do you want me to say what uh
how am i supposed to respond to that hey dude i eat uh like i eat 20 fucking peppermints a day
what do you think it's a little abnormal apparently hey hey hey hey hey so grotto beasts
grotto beast account twitter is moments away from showing my artwork the artwork that i did
i'm curious i would go check it out all right so this is the way to get here that's great it's
let me hold on let me make sure this is my teleporter do you see it stop doing that i just
want to leave yeah i i did one guy the big sword shows how powerful one guy can really be all right
so there's two options i can either go back to the npc city and get to the end of that and see what
the hell's there or i can just go to the end of the game um it's only been like four and a half
hours i'm good i'm definitely good just to i mean why not i'll see what was at the end of it my
sword girl uh i wanted to go do the loot thing i don't know what the fastest route to get there
is from here but this thing is really good i really need to unlock it i think it's better
than the sword it's kind of a long way to go i gotta somebody please keep in mind how they
get here i'm not gonna remember this bet your ass i'm not okay so remember i need to go here
eventually and they give you a pan that's what's there that's it's right next to the smith somebody
remember that oh my god it scales with the yeah this is how you do it this is how you do it that's
how you scale it with luck this is how you scale it with luck that was in damage for a crit what
about the other one i can't do it to anything else oh no no no i can take this off all right
but should i just do them both luck because this right now is just do both luck 1081 with a 13
percent crit rating what uh-huh um it's over it paid off finally i just have to figure out what
that you know on a second and third playthrough that's when you you know you know what you're
doing all right so now i am going to go this way it's still a little bit more of an npc city
to explore and that is precisely what i'm going to do now almost 1100 1200 damage oh all right we
didn't we didn't get a crit but it was pretty cool i hear a uh glitch where is it where is it
okay i got destroyed i think it's probably i don't know on the other side i don't know maybe somebody
else will figure it out one day i don't think there are fake walls it's probably on the outside
somewhere that way can i not walk up um i can't really go that way all right all right anybody
have any idea how fast i can get to the loot place i don't think i even need it i am beefed
up like crazy these crits are going to be so filthy it's it's not even going to matter yeah
these crits are going to be filthy tutorial one attacking well hello not even a crit and it was
insane i want to see i want to one hit kill 271 normal that's pretty damn good jeez tutorial two
ladders rancid crits just downright abhorrent crits disease-ridden crits it's a good chat
message i try i thought it was gonna whatever yeah jesus why is that there that it's gonna be
to remember something guaranteed right there's no way there's no way that there's not a remembrance
right here right it's guaranteed friendly npcs oh that's creepy weird that's some game design
right there 15 access this is a really awful place to do this this i can't believe i didn't
fall off it was a lot of damage i have to commit i have to commit i fucking thought i'm just gonna
be behind me i thought he did i don't know dude it's what a bad place to fight he disappeared
and they appear behind you and grab whatever panics bad karma it's all right spawn you see
rhythm allows the bard to play magical tunes rhythm allows the bard to play magical tunes
that's what i was freaking out about high five that's what you look like that was 2000 damage
in one second let's not blow it again please what happened doesn't make any sense why did i just
what the fuck uh i'm not it's so it's such a free kill too that's the worst part that's the worst
part if you got stuck under the ramp i don't know what happened that was weird let's take it slow
um i'm gonna take it very slow i think that is frost damage i know what i'm best in slot it's
gonna be increases your luck by like 10 all of heroes i gotta get some better end game
drip you know what i mean i know i know dude you're almost 40 i know you don't have to write it
skeleton kind of like the skeleton what are the stats 16 15 no this thing's fine the oven mitts
have been really good too 57 i kind of like it i'm what just what happened to me that was bizarre
welcome uniform i feel like that might be shaking here 19.5 19.5 7.5 i like it what's the character's
name i actually don't know i don't think there is a name that you just play oh my god oh thank
goodness these enemies are so so bad really oh no i lost like 30 40 000 souls but wow it doesn't
i'm at the end game anyways beater does it really matter i think i'm gonna parry these guys well it
wouldn't be the last area if it wasn't difficult how long are you streaming for tonight until i
complete this game so whether that's 30 minutes from now an hour from now 10 minutes from now
this is the last area i just have to get to the end of it but you've seen how how that's working
i just had an intense craving for tabasco sauce it hit me like a ton of bricks just that like
oh i like tabasco sauce make a grilled cheese with tabasco sauce oh that sounds pretty damn
good actually i didn't even have to fucking look at you that's how good i am good go on that hurts
so much where to go back to where i was progress great i want this item i'm going to do this i'm
not just gonna leave i want to kill this thing that's what i should have done from the very
beginning just checking what the fuck is going on what's happening that was not fair where am i
what where to go what the fuck was that that was horse shit he's like huh okay okay he literally
bugged out the character bugged the fuck out where did i even go they do that thing and they
teleport once behind you they don't spam it for five seconds go go go go go go and then i fall
in a hole why you please win this time it's not funny if you pretend i am about to time you out
and i'm reach over there so much effort for me to reach over click once scroll permanently ban
click it's two buttons i feel like it's hard to get the actual like front stab whatever the
hell it is it's thrust thrust is the thrust is dumb i hate thrust weapons i hate thrusting
there's nothing fun about it it just now you just make me snot i'm so angry that i just want to kick
i want to drop kick you off a cliff that hurts all right let's go that's what's going on fool me once
shame on shame on you fool a fool cannot be fooled again my dad references that all the time
all right it's only one remains if i went down that hole i would have shit my pants
i'm dead oh my god i'm fucking dead i thought i went down the hole and it fucked everything up
these claw enemies i hate these things these things suck they kill you in two hits
they're super fast they can teleport and they don't even have a body they're just dust flying
around and a pair of hands i know i want that item i'm just gonna run to it i ain't fighting
anymore you can see my butt through the wait is that yeah you can i'm just running i'm just
gonna i'm sprinting over there i'm not playing the game anymore i'm not i'm just gonna run there
they can bug out all they want yeah goodbye i just have to fight one dude where does this guy come
from where am i let's go memory of a valiant is all that was here come on no way this definitely
remember zone right at least they're dead do your best evil laugh all right i'll try
don't fall through that all come on dude i don't want to do that again i don't want to run back
there that's come on man oh you pain in the ass or whatever at least i can just run by
he fell for the train there was no choo-choo before that blew down just happened it wasn't
really anything for me to do maybe i guess maybe just block it or just stay i could i could just
step out of the way i think that's what you're supposed to do and not freak out in my brain i
thought if the in that split second of time that i had if the train hit me i was going off the map
i was like i've been hit by this train before it's gonna knock me off the map but let's um
will it hit them i fucking hope so oh my god i thought they despawned i was with why was the
train i was waiting for the train i was waiting for the train the train did not i have to go try
to okay i have to touch the lantern for the train to spawn i thought i had to just cross a certain
plane and the train would spawn if i walked past it so i'm gonna take it very slow and i'm gonna
kill everything there uh i have never really played f-zero somebody asked i've not played
f-zero maybe a little bit when i was younger back in the day i remember it being too fast is that
wrong no i'm thinking of a different game no maybe not i remember it being just everything was so
fast okay i kind of like hurt my head to play at least the old one for the super nintendo how are
you still alive what maybe it's not midnight it's only 10 30 so everyone that's trying to sleep
all right wait wait wait wait wait wait does it not happen again i think it's just a one and done
yeah i think just happens once consumables i believed in you we believe in you i hate this game
i can't they have to do the big burst oh my god there's no way that i get launched that far
i went soaring oh i get parry all right one and i fly back a thousand feet these enemies are really
tricky i'm not gonna let it beat me though i will win we're gonna do that by simply just ignoring
everything and just run to the end of the level check this out i want you all to pay close attention
class is in session fuck you oh yes i'm out of it finally i saved that whole thing so i probably
have enough what does this give you okay let's use everything that's probably the last buyer
i'm gonna save this yeah use all the crunchies um wait i gotta make sure i tether myself to here
it would be a disaster if i didn't let's see what is down here it's you again what do you got
if you want to heal the heart that actually matters burden her oh hold on right here is
this the dead space one no what is it part of a hero maybe i'll put it on 24 physical
it doesn't really match i he got like trapped he got like he's like i heard like a crash i know
i'm making a lot of noises right now but this is what happens when you're at the end of a game
like this you just revert back to caveman talk what am i looking at oh shit no shit i feel like
i'm 200 levels under leveled for this area for you fucking asshole he usually goes behind it
wasn't behind me god damn it this place sucks these things are so hard you're so fucked up
they they kill you in two swings they're super i don't i'm not even gonna describe it it's very
difficult their swing pattern is weird there's two or three different kinds of these enemies
there's the one with the claws that have horizontal swings there's one with like a
axe or some shit who cares all this area if you dodge you fall off the cliff
it's a rainbow road of dark souls parody games you you would milk every last ounce of decency
from our world this is not a place to fight anybody you can't even fight in this area you
can't fight here and we're fighting on swish cheese coward run actually coward runtime fuck
go ahead do it oh where'd he go god damn it no my god these things are fucked up
this is the most trouble i've had in this whole 20 hours i've been playing this game
these things are relentless want me to get my brother he usually plays a little better than me
dave dave come in here oh yeah what is it what is it jerry dave can you help me i'm at this area
and i can't really do it could you just like kind of sit down and help me do this
shadow's making fun of me and shit yeah of course of course let me sit down for you
oh let me get that controller there take it man thank you no problem at all what were you having
trouble with oh these enemies yeah well i yep of course oh you didn't do is you didn't jump
over that ledge you actually avoid these enemies completely walk through the door
and just keep on going jeremy there's no reason to stop in these areas too hard
i wouldn't drop there though are you just head down here and make sure you never give up
that's how i do things well a little bit of a glitch there that's nothing i can't handle
i am dave of course hey would you like the controller back yeah okay well here you go don't
give up okay thanks thank you i appreciate it oh by the way we're having lasagna for dinner oh cool
actually i like that that sounds good appreciate it thanks man i guess it really was that easy
but whatever no no dave get back in here i need you oh dave help dave oh my god he teleported
across the thing no somebody help explain that to me he teleported how did he do that he was
oh no he was he wasn't even i whatever why am i fat rolling why am i fat rolling right now
what the freaking heck i'm gonna listen i'm gonna do dave's stuff hold on dave can you get back in
here no you only have to use me once and that's it and then i want you to make sure to say hello
to sorah for me i fucking lost my mind i'm done i'm out of here god damn it i should have just i
saw the item i just like got a guy i saw dollar signs were in my fucking eyeballs what stop shoot
they have incredible attack range where are they even shooting what i do i some
all that guy back there that guy oh that motherfucker all the way back there the
microscopic person over there the person that is a tenth of an inch on the screen
is shooting me with a homing missile across the whole game that little microscope guy is the one
that's shooting me let me see let me line that up yeah right there that sounds good okay let me shoot
somebody through the fucking door what huh this is brutal this area okay they turned the difficulty
from like a seven to like 50 in this last zone we need dave again no dave dave is not coming back
i am i'm gonna be as slow as shit here watch this i'm gonna be incredibly slow arrows don't do that
arrows don't do that arrows don't do this all right motherfucker let's go no crits you're gonna
be shitting me you've got to be fucking kidding me why'd i even make this character if i have like
a i have like a 70% crit rate what the fuck are you doing jesus christ i played that perfectly
until that last bit dead cool thanks thanks for giving me extra help get you dad dad dad come in
here oh son something happened what happened can you come and help me dad of course i'll help you
okay let me i got the controller in my head all right let's see what i can do here
i didn't dave i already helped you do this oh no oh that was really looks like it hurt oh gosh
i don't know how to play this fucking game jeremy here you take it back i don't i'm your father i
don't play video games that often unless it's something on my telephone or something thanks
dad appreciate it your family's fucked up yeah why all right i have a question why is
everybody in my family i talk like this um why do i not have an accent like that why do i not have a
like a southern accent why do i not talk like that all right what even accent is that it's
because you're adopted god damn it all right i'm killing this thing right now what i told you so
all right let's not blow this again no more rolling what the hell do i have three stamina
stop freaking out i didn't i dude crit somebody i've i have like a two percent crit rating
remember hold on a minute it's because i'm not swinging with this thing i feel like i'm not
hitting anybody with any crits it's because i'm not using the offhand dude i really hope the last
boss is a slug where is he fuck you i'm just running i do want that though yes oh it's you
we've come a long way my seems cycles ago that i doubted my destiny you gave me focus
not once but twice nero does not forget those who embrace him before us lies a quest
akin to the one we began together so long ago i hid behind your shield back then i concealed
my self-doubt with bravado will you fight beside me as allies and equals i'm gonna be really honest
with you i'm going to just you're gonna take aggro and i'm not gonna even fight because these
things are hard and i don't even care if you die i thought so prove our destinies pull it back here
pull it back here pull it back here did i just aggro that accidentally no you've got to be
shitting me i didn't i was trying to i was targeted on this is not good just spam spam it'll work
okay okay okay okay all right we're good that's what we do teamwork we're good i
try i believed in you all along heroes don't look for acceptance heroes change their world
to accept them that was very helpful i'm so can you imagine let's put this out there right now
can you imagine if this guy i did not do the quest he would not be standing there right now
and i would be in a lot of trouble i definitely would not have done that i only did that because
this character is here so if you're going to play this game let me give you a very big piece of
advice do this quest this guy's very helpful something new though oh it's a dex weapon
what and it's got a ton of damage and it looks super cool what's the damage on let's see 80 plus
141 damn this is just better all right let's go i don't know what's next but it's time to move
forward where is ford go back down here how do i get out of here all right all right it is a
tutorial tactics time for your training look at all these holes fuck you i am trained oh my god
uh this is this is bullshit and this these things too um just fuck this i'm out of here
just open the door get me out get me out please get me out get me out get me out get me out get
me out get me out get me out stop saying that get me out of here give me open the door this is locked
help get me out of this area okay all right fine fine oh go go go go go go this way this
way this way open this one all right cool sweet me to action oh has it moved me huh
what the fuck are you doing um this i can't get in this door i can't get in that okay calm down
everything's fine climb this no i was just there that was horrible i cannot die here
you know what i mean like this would be a disaster if i died oh that's pretty funny
cool somebody can read that later the image in lasagna again was did you actually want lasagna
for dinner oh yeah sounds awesome perfectly delicious um which way do i go you oh fuck you
oh yeah good that was actually smart game development to make somebody lose good thing
i'm even awful at rolling into inanimate objects treasure or yeah come on this way this is the
troll zone i am not messing around here not anymore this is legit though like we're just messing
with you now i hope this is real thank god it's real thank goodness that part where the train
and dropping the ground out with the cows and the troll drops oh man that's uh that's rough
i'm so shocked i actually got through that that was a mess hey whatever right no the live zone
oh i'm live over here like if i didn't turn into the um thingy i don't know why i'm parrying dude
i can't get that light out of my face see you later see you goodbye okay isn't i already out
here no you should have waited my signal is so curious about how that actually works
there's a there's a lot of blocked doors maybe some kind of key or something i don't know
i'm not moving through that there we go look go flat on the castle oh that's not that's actually
a pretty good idea bro what do you how does it miss fuck off with this shit what is the crit
damage on that it was nothing whoa i'm not gonna let you blow this for me no way whoa crit him
jesus crit the bastard oh mr knight you're so loud i dude what do you want to do i can't just
sit here and just not be loud my whole life flashes before my eyes every time one of those
enemies swings shut up buddy flee flee from your doom i always see you train here it comes
ah damn that's a pretty big shortcut keep of the stolen crown locked of the castle um let me
unlock this first because i don't want to die but you know we'll see wait where are we this is a
shortcut back here uh let me level up okay so gotta go back should i make this should i tether
here because if i have the shortcut there i feel like i'm not able to run through a bunch of
bullshit right probably a good idea yeah i'm doing it we are painfully close we are almost there
then where do i go from here this game is a lot longer than i thought it was going to be
second or third stream of this game five six hours each 15 to 20 hour game i'm surprised i
thought it was going to be like 10 okay so this is where i ended up in there part of the sequence
um oh maybe okay yep no
narrator's pocket watch this is a weapon nine source get up there okay i'll be hiding right
there that's how i go back so right i don't think it's in here is it out there you how do
you like that eat shit eat shit you can't teleport up here and you don't even know how to use the
ladder over there straight ahead not a single crit to be had what i was out of the way complain
complain complain complain complain complain complain complain wham wham wham god damn it
another one come on they really do not want me to go all the way over here they just they so badly
don't want me to go through this door is this thing teleport i think it does i am not we are
going back to where i can actually hit you would you know the truth of your get me up here would
you see the substance of what you are then come to me it's gonna be fake that's gonna be fake
it's not fake one more point what should i put it into has there ever been a fake one
there has been one or two fake ones just luck again we might as well go all in i wonder what
the caps are in this game they might not even be any caps i know new luck ability well that was a
good idea recover health on critical hit take no damage well too bad we didn't get that that's
actually really good all right game it's time for you to show us what the deal is big reveal
gonna be slug one hit i hate you and i do let me spin a tale to show you your journey here was
easy what see nostalgaia holds her hero's hands but what if the story had held nothing back
uh okay i tried to turn into the thing it's just b without pressing any other buttons right
ouch and i just got triple tapped i got triple tapped because of this
fucking sausage behind me this cigar behind me blocked me from going backwards your journey
here was easy all right bring it on string it together give me like three more of those
there it is that's why you build luck some skillet arms does not a true hero make
heroism is in the heart and yours is cruel okay why am i this doesn't seem right all that was good
lies dead at your feet this is your legacy you wish to rid nostalgaia of evil
then face it well that hurts a lot that's annoying why can't i get the front stab
three hits is good but you give me a couple crits there it is that was weird
i didn't hurt my intimate now gg were it only so easy everything i love destroyed
there's nothing left to tell oh shit you just got fucking destroyed still live you obliterated him
so hard he can't even move i fucked him up so bad oh no i can't feel bad i smushed him in the head
so hard i have hated what i feared you were a hero is no longer mine to tell if you truly be
different than the rest of your kind my study find the threads they're in and sever them
plot thread scissors wait that's a dex weapon isn't it kind of not really
damn okay level up i need to kill like one thing um no it's whatever wait watch this video
good video it was me barry i killed your favorite wait what is this roll up it was me germa i made
the final level of this game harder so you wouldn't be able to beat it making your sleep schedule a
little bit more difficult difficult enough for me to kill vinnie what is what is that
what character is that what characters are these who's this mustard guy i don't know what this is
all right let's end this it's reverse flash is reverse flash just really slow and lazy
it better be to me reverse flash is an insult like all right reverse flash it's like fuck off man
it's my day off today oh really you got up at uh got up at 1 pm huh reverse flash shut up all
right go to my study where is that is that the big thing that we've been seeing underneath um
you know i'm talking about right where is that go to my study remember heroism with train oh the
train hole that's right now i'm gonna need a little bit of help because it's been a very long time
time that's like down in one of the first area like the second or third area staging room
anybody know actually let me level up one more time i'm gonna have enough in a second
obliterated the left room go behind the elevator back wait wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong wrong
wrong i just don't remember all right i'm standing here i would like the precise directions
find the elevator very cool and then down the hell did you know that now isn't it down here
wrong the guy said he would unsub if you don't play sky room all right wrong wrong wrong wrong
wrong no help yes help staging room in the tutorial area okay so where is that it's been
a lot of twists and a lot of turns a lot of twists and turns a lot of doors a lot of things to
remember a lot of openings a lot of places to go a lot of things to see a lot of things to do
a lot of places to look at a lot of enemies to attack a lot of things to do a lot of things
to be a lot of places to see found it correct oh yes no what's going on in here definitely
remember something what is this strength the memory saber the almighty inspiration had always
been treated as set dressing a thematic arch type merely used for props but purposelessness
led many npcs and heroes to try and grasp the ungraspable they formed cults creeds and
superstitions trying to make meaning out of their now meaningless existence the institutions they
formed were abominations uh and there was a problem anything else it's a cold room all right
the time has come me to go level up lightsaber bro use it i don't have enough strength you know
what you can do this and you can do that in your playthrough i might maybe not on stream but i
might play through this again uh with um oh my god i need like a hundred i kind of want to do the
spell casting come on give me another play with a friend uh i don't think this multiplayer in this
game i think it's a lot i think it's just the signs the game is full co-op you serious it's
two player co-op i did not know that that's enough one more point luck just for good luck finish it
this game seriously is one of the better souls likes i've seen it yeah it is i am pleasantly
surprised by how fun this game actually is i want this to be really cinematic so please leave me
alone in here all right let's get it cinematic is this what i'm rocking with is this the final
clothing reminds me of the sakiro noise uh actually might be the sakiro noise okay who's next
gauntlet let's go what do you got what's up whoa what are you doing man one final shortcut i know
there's a bonfire here closer all right so where is the closest bonfire to here all right back here
no back here where am i going other way upstairs i would like to go to the smith one more time
i could oh you guys are so helpful thank you so much my god all right let's move thank you for
the help i wonder if i can just run by i don't aggro all the way down here whatever okay you
geez man that guy has so much health i fucking hate those enemies i hate them they're just so
annoying just fight them normally i was fighting that guy normally i thought that guy normally
i did the dodge i did the i was not doing bad it's the other enemies that just
and stand up and then i get stuck let's do it already that guy is cycled the other way which
is fine let's go here we go britney clarkson britney clarkson down him j young come on what
are you not entertained fuck you caesar oh uh-oh who's next robert davis i know to do oh
oh almost got me robert oh that thing is so fucking slow fuck all of you fuck all of you
my last breath hey i think it's so goddamn slow all right i get it now all right let's go
it's all about parry's parry but i feel like i can't get i can't get the crit even if i go
in the right spot it's kind of buggy kind of finicky it's like weird i'll parry and then it's
like i go right up the front but yeah i don't get it you're moving to the side i started moving to
the side because it wouldn't work in the front you're a caster holy shit she has spells come on
what the fuck what the hell is going on see that didn't work that time oh my god that like half
animation swing what the fuck are you talking about man it's not an account it's just playing
rock paper scissors are you gonna dodge or swing it's it's just rock paper scissors i chose rock
sorry why is it not working i'm doing it look at you see you're watching me run up and hit r1
r1 what the fuck the crit don't work it's like it's like it's such a tiny little window in some
random spot that i just don't understand that's as close as i can get i got it once and weirdly
like the character went like to the left a little i don't i have no idea all right come on that's
that's and that's how i'm supposed to start this see where were those i've been looking for those
for fucking years it's been years that's what i'm talking about that's what i mean aggression
aggressive only sekiro taught me that what do you say overconfidence could be a slow and insidious
make sure you kill fast that's weird i'm telling you i wanted to oh oops get out of my domain
who's next what are they all gonna attack me at the same time i thought they're all gonna run in
just check right not a bad idea that was intense whoa whoa why is it counting 24 25
six what's going on 27 28 that was weird did all those people die weird let me just check
i don't sometimes they put weird stuff over here ah my body that my whole my back hurts my head
hurts um my my thighs hurt somehow my fucking whole body hurts right now new order new order
what was all that new orders rule i think it's heavy as hell okay those are the strings right
loud loud this game is i turned it down to where is that where the hell is that that was a demon
face does everybody remember what that is it's in the demon room by the shop yeah in hell with the
pink guy the shop at the market square market square yeah second area of the game can somebody
give me uh directions what was that all right uh where am i going i don't i got i don't know man
i i don't know i don't know where i'm i don't know where i'm going i know what to do these guys don't
hurt that much it's all right homeward bone it's what exactly what i was thinking carry on down
the path by the shop there's a trek down a snowy mountain with some tough monsters for this early
in the game make it at the bottom though and there's a cave this can be remembered here let
me use my points there we go what's the one of the last luck abilities with something crazy right
okay take no damage so there's a one percent chance that i don't take damage whenever i get hit
or what do these percentages mean okay so it's guys i'm standing here which way i'm seeing behind
you behind you there's only one shop in the game yeah but this was three days ago it may as well
has never happened well he's wait what about this thing down here i'm curious about this
where are my friends i'm not too proud to admit you've taught me much old friend rules cannot
prevent a hero from fulfilling their destiny we were not spawned accepted so we surpassed
expectation look upon me now great ones look and tremble
oh i will face the pipe layer i make my own destiny i make all right what about you i have
literally only two people made it no three gone off script have you most noble heroes follow the
path prescribed between you and i i do not know how a single great one yet remains between you
and an open heart the pipe layer pipe layer stood within the layer of the adversary when you have
done all else you require seek the unbreachable more beneath or shaft there's a well-traveled
path along the now sunken crater when you have done all else there when you have done there is
okay leave me leave me all right all right i'm standing here where from here actually let me
look down i want to see this thing okay all right standing here where do i go from here my cat just
got sprayed by a skunk oh that sucks i'm sorry that's horrible oh no that's not good oh no oh
hope they're all right that's probably pretty scary oh i think i remember now that guy that guy
that's chained up right he's like oh i have to chain myself to the wall right i'm gonna actually
put it here he's like where are you he's over here in that weird spot where where is this guy
place where the big statue sits in the middle where am i going i'm gonna level up one more time
just 12 something i hope that's enough oh come on i wish there was a counter that just counted down
to your next level it's like oh hey ding you can do it now all right let's go hooray never opened
that i'm look i heard the blacksmith kind of wanted maybe look for him but okay i gotta go
wait leave me alone i gotta go down why even attack me i can kill you all in one hit okay i
want to get down there i'm gonna go this way wait no what okay bro oh okay come on this better not
kill me or i will scream i can't even do it anyways so what was going on in here past here
through here kill this guy now that's the end of the game can't talk to the shopkeeper anymore
i cannot talk do it need to go to sleep i am perfectly fine for some reason i thought i was
out of the hitbox disgraced glare this looks awful cheeseball it see i'm surprised this game is
really big it's very it's huge god here it is okay all right all right yeah yeah sure oh get out of
come on i got a weapon though remember it demon tearjoker gigachad gigachad gigachad
wait that's far away am i crazy that's very that's really far away isn't it no way i don't
no no okay it's not that bad it's kind of stat is that sucks though for some reason i thought i
had a close bonfire oh man that would have been awesome if i'd made it though um
um shit it's all right it's all right everything's fine um why does everyone
need to sleep if he's not real didn't we just talk about how painfully unfunny that is now
don't hurt me please it's 500 bucks i can't open it oh there's this many people in here
there's not even this many people in the whole game there's not this many people in the entire
game my sword's broken my sword's facing the wrong way it swings down now god damn it why does this
have to happen to me okay please put the sword in your hand correctly that would be fantastic
what's behind there holy shit this is actually kind of sad you must gather your party before
vent that's like really sad they all died in here what's this a suspicious spoon um that's kind of
incredible wait what is he doing there he's just hanging out down there what okay can you i'm done
with that enemy was there a place i can just drop down i wish i could just jump off the
fucking edge here why do i have to run around a goddamn circle it's gonna lead me out okay um
let me find the one door to go through to get down here just let me jump where the hell you ran past
the drop down point screw you actually yeah i should talk to the ball if you want to heal the
heart that actually matters unburden her i wonder what actually happens if you there's probably
like a few different endings i'm imagining is that little dude just keep showing up and telling me
to do that maybe if you unburden a certain amount of items that makes sense okay i really have to be
very careful here i'm gonna try as hard as i can i'm not gonna make a gigachad fall joke i wasn't
even trying to there's no bonfire down here i'm gonna do i'm gonna go as slow as possible all right
i'm taking all my gear off so i can dodge roll super fast if i need to is it under 25 maybe i
wonder if this is like a really crazy one okay no gear super quick i got a very very good
start let's go please pray for me the ball don't be deceived by that ball
dude this thing i don't know when to go um now uh now holy shit i made it
okay all right all right all right all right sweet very sweet very cool let me put my gear back on
that would be helpful what is this thing 75 damn it right at 75 damn it all right that's good um
play it safe don't be dumb i need a bonfire oh yeah so is this a whole nother area oh my god i
thought i i didn't think the game was gonna be that much longer this is like a whole nother zone
damn i'm still into it no i'm i'm good i'm having this game i love this game oh they're so thin too
it's hard to even see where they're going
i'm sorry all right i'm fucked here uh give me that item please yes this is got gas everywhere
dude oh this is how this is fucking terrifying yikes kick a chat kick a chat oh my goodness
holy shit oh dear um uh what what if i go and that's a dead that you just die how come that why
do you think that was a good idea um i think mainly it was because there was nowhere else for
me to go and i'm like where should i go i was like maybe i'll go there maybe there was a secret
who knows maybe there could have been like a treasure or something you fall through it's a
dark souls like parody secrets game of course there's gonna be interesting things to do holy
that's not over there dude why i i just watched the same movie i just saw the same movie
and this movie stinks that's just you just mean at that point you just did that you're making
like a funny joke that i just got hit by that well i guess who doesn't think it's funny me
where's the ball all right maybe i'm gonna go this way jesus what was that where am i
what what's happening what is this this is supposed to be doom i just got the i
am i making progress i i think so oh no what's that mean dude can what the fuck is happening
uh not a chance in hell by the way i holy shit why does this guy have a weight on him
dude this place is fucking ridiculous i don't even know how i got oh i there was so much
happening i don't even know how i got over there i have no idea i i i picked up a red shirt
hey you should slow down are you are we see are we on the same channel here do you see what just
happened look at they look at these balls they throw these balls at every fucking angle okay
i still this is just a joke level this is a joke level they made this to specifically
a dev is watching this right now going like oh wait he's not supposed to be here this level
sucks i made this just i just was fucking around on a saturday afternoon why can't he get hit by
the ball oh but stop what happened which what is it is somebody just pushing me and and hitting
me with a hammer in the head it's too many sound effects um bad dream i got some new shit here i
damn it it's decked uh strength 10 000 no thanks all right now what uh is it up i feel like it's up
didn't i just go up i did but i think i fell i think someone hit me down fuck um i don't know
okay was i right i don't know i feel like i've been pretty much everywhere just keep going down um
i'm gonna die found it serious is it a minecraft portal take the lift now afraid of that ball
waffles versus pancakes i don't like either one of them if i had to choose it would be pancakes
no that's not true it would be waffles i'm not like i'm not a big fan of either one of them
okay so this way to the left or to the right i gotta go that's the only place i have really
haven't been all right so now what oh my god okay don't move okay up again i don't want to get hit
by a ball no man look at all this look at all this this is a hard mode i'm getting lucky though
good thing i'm lucky dude what the hell this sucks oh super sense fortress okay i got a key
oh don't don't don't wowie so i haven't looked at chat in at least 10 minutes
where are the balls don't do this now they stopped spawning what the fuck are you talking about man
oh my god oh my god luck is really paying off right now he's getting closer oh shit
no oh my god this is so hard this is so unbearable what the fuck everything here is from the original
quake dude what the hell this place sucks lift me up that's the way to that's the way to do it right
all right i'm gonna give this to i thought this game was like 10 hours long huh who beat this game
in 10 hours who are you i'd like to meet you i'd like to i'd like to say hello i would allow one
chat message from that person i would allow one dm it's gonna be like new germ is typing hey bro
you beat this in 11 hours on your first try bullshit tell me what you did what you download
what you download what did you download what you download hey man hey hey what you download
fuck don't okay at least i know where i'm going where's where's the money where's the money yes
you froze me right at the end these guys hit like a truck two hits and you're dead what is
going on in this room you know what i'm just go i'm just running to the boss i'm running the boss
on your playthrough you can check it out on your playthrough oh my god don't blow it here
i really could have used i just got saved by the one percent i just cheated death i didn't take any
damage oh thank goodness oh it's so nice to see a bonfire okay wait tethered to this it's going
all the way back gonna be a staff room right i bet you it's a staff room looks like it hello goodbye
this level is fucking wacky that was actually freaking wacky all right so what's down here
player of the adversary you carry one relic that can be remembered this is it boys and girls
this is it interesting interesting very pretty i don't know what you did but it was almost one
hit i just got saved again by the one percent dude oh my god these these guys hit so hard
hey what did you download jesus jesus jesus get stuck there and don't come down starlight star
bright first rsc tonight man i wish the scorn we're not sleeping tonight are we well i mean
oh it is one oh my god i forgot about my lasagna oh shit bro the lasagna lasagna what is in there
what are they dipping in there what are they dunking in there dude they're dunking somebody
in there america runs i'm dunking dunking fucking donuts oh hey what's going on you want to you like
dunking yeah of course i do i think i want the shield for this what do you think you're doing
oh my goodness dude i what is happening with this level i'm so glad i have luigi mode on
40 luck means i don't die half the time it's definitely that's more than one percent without
a doubt that's like 30 or 40 i die without that look at how much should i keep refilling these
because of the luck luck after 40 luck really does work very well look at that i didn't get hurt
it's awesome come on refill it refill it refill it bullshit right oh my god it's a spear not just a
oh i'm gonna die die i'm gonna die and that one was longer that one was longer
they it's varied i have to run you well here's the thing i'm running into that it's my friend
dude i'm so glad to see you you have no idea how happy i am to see you thank you for you
what wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait no no no no no no no no no no no what
happened we're supposed to be friends oh shit i should have killed you months ago i should have
killed you months ago dude i should have killed you months ago when i had a chance oh shit okay
hold on are they still following me that's how you clutch it up oh yeah thank goodness all right
dude i really don't want to hurt you but it's kind of messed up and i'm right behind you and i have
to give you a quick little uh smack i want that shield and i'm gonna get it nice that's not nice
i would let you live but that's not gonna happen eight decks ten it's a it's a spell weapon yeah i
gave this to you don't ever forget who gave that to you what about this thing forgotten simple of
qco's favor ravaged by pixelization some relics are too far gone to be restored temptation quest
ends interesting okay that's unfortunate i really like that guy there's one something
meaningful about this item a legacy that can live on in you returning this to nostalgaia through
her beacons will increase the use of your heroic icon well i probably missed what too cool 45 is
keep memory on death i wonder if i got i might i probably won't probably won't get there all right
what is through here where this is the this has got to be the final arc of the game hold up okay
the whole thing's coming down you said that three ox ago why are you questioning me if i had 40 or
50 decks these would hit for a lot more i got them all back too i didn't want to lose the lock
on so the final boss is absolutely super mario right in quotes there's no way this is not mario
behind one of the behind the big door there's no way shield uh the the area what happened
or bowser yeah refill it shit shit okay dude staff room yeah i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna
finish it tonight right i mean i don't i don't i'm not streaming tomorrow i do momentum increase
of course you're making it easier to stagger enemies i wonder if that's probably something i
should do hmm what is that for i don't know oh i'm very confused what about your lasagna
there's definitely 15 minutes left in this game i'm at the very core of the earth see it doesn't
shake like that unless you're in the deep end of the crust this shit was already open weird
umbrella i climb that i can't climb this what's the purpose of this it's gotta be worth like at
least a couple gold can i go flat out here no i don't think so it doesn't look like it
hmm i'm not jumping down that's a big mistake or bugged out okay listen to music all right
what's up chainmail thong chainmail bikini this thing is heavy meat pong on and go up
come on nope that is a gigantic bed this bet is ridiculous this thing is huge
a hot tub this is a pipe yeah this is bowser shit this is mario shit all right where are you
where are you well that's definitely the way to go but not yet this might be a shortcut yep hell
yeah okay very very nice i'm gonna have an opportunity i have seven of these 14 000 jesus
jeez i'm also gonna put all the healing on my bar and i think speaking of healing i think i'm
gonna put no let's just commit to it 43 gather here put all the heels in the bar these meat i've
got what is this yeah i mean why not fully restore stamina i mean who cares what just put it all on
all right this is the final mission the final encounter i hope everybody is prepared did i
tether it yep i did i think i did right i did didn't i wait hold on let me let me stretch
have i not no i took a break didn't i have i not left this chair no way all right now it's it's
it's time for a stretch break i'll be right back give me two seconds okay stretched a bit
went to the bathroom did some did some squats got a drink let's finish this up and i really got to
beat this in the next 30 minutes because that's when the edible is going to kick in so i better
hurry the freak up kidding it's 1 30 in the morning okay let's go and who might you be it is i jock
geek of the thong kingdom no you know what you can just call me jock you can call me
fucking jockstrap what is this little shimmy oh my goodness dude well this is going to be um
barely difficult jockstrap didn't quite make it do i have to shimmy every single time here i can't
just open the door all right strategy is just dodge one two and it's a spin what the dude this
guy wait you're holy shit man you're annoying just turn around turn around turn around come on
but he's small he's small get him when he's small get him when he's small where what what
just excuse me full health again dude what he jumped on the throne do i have a very important
question we're gonna see my what is it called fragment of tradition i think i can get something
to max level now right piece of tradition there it is uh if i have a if i keep having trouble here
i'm probably gonna have to upgrade the weapons something tells me when you get them down to
really small maybe i can do something the loot too yeah we'll see i wonder if there's any strategy
i don't know maybe parries i feel like let me let's you know what i'm gonna try let's try parries
get that shit out of here it's an annoying move he's so slow it's gonna be so hard to parry
can't even i can't even get up i couldn't even move he switches back and forth from unbelievably
slow to unbelievably fast he's one of those dumb bosses you can't just you can't oh why can't i
not open this why why can't i open that no parry's not gonna work parry's not gonna cut it
there's got to be a catch to when you get them small turtle with the shield i'll try it one more
time where is the attack where is the attack opportunity on this asshole like the guy just
like what even if i got in there i wouldn't have time to swing one time even if i got in there he's
already doing another move and you just get hit for me to go like this i'm in he's already swinging
again uh all right i gotta i'm gonna go upgrade like here's the great question i am so far i don't
think i can maybe through the staff room i could probably do the staff room but i honestly i was
running through this so fast because this last area has been just chaos which is apps just just
carnage at every corner that whole last 40 minutes was a blur i don't remember how i got
in here i remember just sprinting through because it was just a fucking mess on i can't even see
myself on the screen all right let's go mario jesus dude what the fuck what are you doing
oh my god stop swinging the fucking weapon for one second get him small then it's free
this asshole was jumping around everywhere just be patient this the the attack opportunities seem
like zero for the for as long as me to go like this he's already doing something else the fuck
under leveled no way 63 what what should i be 80 103 okay no one two one two two three
three flip flip flip yep get me out of that come on man that's not cool that's not cool it takes
so long to get up it takes so long to get up no i didn't want to press that god damn it happened
to fucking go i pressed x accidentally little shit no it's get over here no mushroom there for
you now is there dickhead god damn it i'm just trying to get the fuck away from them
come here you little shit i die where am i oh shit in my fucking pants he's going up again
that don't work what uh oh what does that mean what does that mean what does that mean what does
that mean where did you just go dude i didn't mean to do that i'm an idiot die
get out of my life mario oh yes i like the bat chest bat chest get out of my life mario oh he
said it let me see what that is it wants me to do this so bad i might as well that was hard all
right so that that was that was pretty cool that was that was very difficult that was tricky
here's the pipe 30 strength oh take that mario i was trying to think of something really cool
to say at the last hit like two in the morning van give me a little bit of slack and just lance
cool all right let's uh let's see the end what do take the throne okay the adversary's empty
throne sits before you the epicenter of nostalgaia's conflict you have liberated
and restored so much perhaps if you claim this authority for yourself you could be the one to
fix all of nostalgaia's problems here's the thing not quite the thing beneath here it lies open for
you enter it ready for all of this to end uh might as well just keep it going good luck helps so much
all right so that that was probably bad end or maybe one of the i imagine there's probably two
three endings but here we go this is this good end you think find out memory flows freely into
nostalgaia's open heart she's ready to receive you when you are ready to complete your heroic
journey give your memory back to the world all right so i have to give all my memories back
or i just take the throne but i'm curious let's see what happens warning this will end the game
i cut the cord yeah you want to pull what do you guys think should we pull it up i mean you
guys stuck around for this long i feel like you should have a say let's go for it take the throne
or restore the memory and by the way i can veto either one so nah i want to do this never mind
i'm doing this never mind game over sorry everybody okay oh well it was 82 percent anyways
jesus oh my god is this it's gonna be another thing at the end right
oh my god i'm so sorry most credits let's find out i didn't i i have my game volume turned pretty
far down too all right are you ready for the review are you ready for the review that last
area was a mess but there's a lot of really cool shit in this game i feel like you could play
through it a couple times with different types of classes i love the memory thing that's a really
nice twist on upgrading weapons super cool game was actually pretty phenomenal i would say
i'm gonna be i'm gonna be weird here i'm gonna be weird here i think i don't think a lot of
people are expecting this this is a um this is a this is an 8.7 there it is 8.7 this is yeah that
was great that was like very very very fun i would say that was great i i i think this is not a seven
if you take away the memory aspect of this game i think that's bumping it up a whole letter grade
for me that system is really unique and deserves praise the 8.7 that was great was it better than
eternal cylinder i mean i give what i give eternal cylinder like a 6.7 or like a seven or something
like that 7.5 yeah i think this the this game was way more than i ever expected i've really really
enjoyed it somebody said this earlier i've played i've how many times have you seen me attempt to
play as souls like in quotes and i kind of just like yeah that was like kind of fun for three four
hours but i'll move on that happens a lot i've i know i have loaded up on this stream and off stream
too at least a half dozen souls likes and i just kind of give up in the first like four or five
hours i did not do that with this this this kept my attention the whole time it's got that crazy
every single thing is connected dark souls one for all of you dark souls one brains out there
um i'd say you probably would like that i thought it was very very good i thought it was great
and to me somewhere in the eights is great not quite a nine i think nine implies it's like
incredible i think that was great and there's a lot of i didn't see there's probably a couple
areas i probably kind of ran through skipped over that last area was a little messy but
all in all can't complain all in all the games in eight point uh seven not like me reviewing
anything matters be giving a score is is it doesn't really mean very much but it's great
all right everybody what about the blunt rotation oh shit okay uh pink eye's not coming anywhere
near like where i live i just want to make that really clear um probably the lasagna that i
didn't eat the guy that betrayed us in the end and the uh the old the old guy also the game's
like an eight high kind of mid to high eight for me just because i actually might play it again
off stream just like in my own time and play like a sorcery that's how i can tell that like all right
all right so that should be a couple of notches higher it's got multiplayer too isn't that
actually though well done collapse in the chat for the developers i don't know how much is this game
seems like it's got a lot of secrets how much does this cost it's 25 bucks 25 bucks it's got
a demo too that's that's fair as hell fair as hell uh nice job that game was great i will see
you guys in a few days probably be live on wednesday i think did three days in a row here
probably take two days here i don't know if i'm i i i really like doing these i say this every
single stream i feel like at the end of the the late night streams but they they hit so different
that i just it's probably staying have a great night get some sleep see you later take care
of yourselves it's kind of a clean slate as of this coming week don't really have anything planned
so we can maybe fill in some stuff it's been a wonderful night yeah it's been great hope you
had a good time what about sorcery please please i'll probably pick what's gonna have to happen is
i'm gonna have to catch myself back up with what happened in sorcery we might we might have to do
a little recap stream where we said we have to kind of remember what happened and go from there
because i was sort of a third of the way through the third episode i enjoyed my stay and then you
drew a dick all right i'll let it slide it got removed hey as as the mods have famously said
i would be banned from my own stream and i would be banned from my own discord and we gotta have
we have to have order though you know what i mean there has to be order right otherwise it just
develops devolves into just chaos you gotta have we have to have an order all right good morning
good night whichever one uh everyone will do it for you now have a beautiful night see you soon
and call your mother for god's sakes gone yet i just wanted to address something in chat it was
pretty funny somebody said i keep calling my mother and she keeps asking about sorcery and
i don't know what to tell her uh still would have waited a little bit longer all right see you wednesday