Yo, what's happening guys? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary!
Playing as the sniper tonight with the Machina.
Never done a Machina gameplay, a lot of you guys asked me for this, and I finally have done it.
So it's the Machina, the Darwin's Danger Shield, and the Tribalman's Shiv, I believe.
I die once or twice in the beginning here, and after that, I just start mowing people down like crazy, headshot after headshot, it's pretty awesome.
So why I never use the Machina and why I've never done a Machina gameplay?
Everybody always tells me, Jerma, the Machina is the best sniper rifle in the game.
Hands down, why wouldn't you use it? Just equip it for crying out loud.
And the reason why I never use it, guys, is because I can't handle the line that comes out of the gun.
That might sound weird, but it has nothing to do with giving away my position.
What bothers me about it is the fact that I can't really see that well.
It sort of messes with my aim, because I'll shoot somebody, and if I miss, this big bright line comes right in my face, and my ADHD kicks in, and I just focus on that, and then I get shot, I just can't recuperate.
So I can't use this gun mainly because of that line.
The second reason why I can't use this weapon is the no hip fire.
I can't take it, because I'm one of those people that if a spy is around, I'm much more satisfied and much safer shooting him from the hip rather than going in and getting face stabbed.
So not being able to hip fire really, really sucks.
And I know a lot of you guys are going to tell me, well, Jerma, equip the machine gun, the SMG, that's the perfect combination.
It's just the SMG has such weird hit detection.
It seems like when you use the SMG and you shoot somebody, half the time the bullets don't even register landing on the person.
It's just really odd. I don't like the hit detection on that weapon, so I don't like to use it.
But all in all, this gun is very, very good for killing people who are over-healed.
This is the over-healer killer. Kind of a mouthful, I know.
You can kill people that are over-healed with a body shot with this gun.
Any of the smaller classes, a scout, a sniper, spy, even a medic, you can still body shot them and potentially kill them with a fully charged body shot, which that was not the case with the older sniper rifle.
So one of the only tips I can really give you with this gun, because honestly I don't really use it that often, is you have to be patient.
This is the patient man's sniper rifle. You can't just go shooting like a Texas Longhorn.
I don't even know what that is. But you can't just shoot all over the place.
You need to really time your shots, because guys, you're giving away your position every time you shoot the gun.
And to touch upon that for a second, if you stay in the same position for long enough, you are going to get found out.
People are going to start to shoot at you. People are going to start coming after you.
So move around a lot, guys. Don't stand in the same position for more than 20 or 30 seconds.
And I know I don't do that at all in this gameplay. I'm standing in the same spot, but that's because this is on Gold Rush.
And Gold Rush really only has like two or three places a sniper can even stand in the first place.
But on a big map like Upward or Badwater or something like that, you really need to move around.
So there you go. There's my rant on the Makina.
I'm going to talk about the gameplay, what's going on on the screen now, while there's still time.
So I just walk out the back door here, go pick up this health. I love this health pack.
This is the best health pack in the game. Just because it's a full health pack, it's right there, right around that choke point.
I love it so much. Coming back to this window here, bad idea.
Almost get myself killed for a second time. And you would think I learned my lesson right here, but I do not.
Get some health, come back over to that same window. I want to get that Demoman, whether it kills me or not.
I don't care. I want to get him. There he is right there. I don't get the shot on him.
He's too well protected by that wall. Sniper just dies. I don't know whether he had a heart attack, I think.
So look at this. Nobody's coming out. The heavy medic pair is up there doing work.
There they are. I figured time to get out of this window.
Jumping down, I get right next to the car because nobody's on it right now.
This is a great opportunity to push the cart and nobody's on it.
The plan is to stand next to the cart while you're zoomed in so you still get the cap points.
Gets a little too dangerous to continue to do that, so I sit back here, try to get some spawn trap headshots.
I think I get maybe one or two and I end up going around the left side because action kind of dies down right here.
Don't see anybody really coming out. I'm missing a lot of shots.
So I take a left-handed turn over here, go around the left side, try to flank him a little bit.
Ends up working out much, much better than this is right now.
I take the turn in about five seconds here, go around the left side. I get a bunch of headshots after this.
I get one shot in particular that I just couldn't believe I got it.
I was like, wow, how the hell did I get that?
It's an engineer coming up right here. Get this soldier. I believe I get this pyro as well. There he is.
So it's an engineer that I end up getting. I missed this scout right here, but watch this.
When I get this engineer, I like perfectly track his head, almost like I'm hacking or something,
but I promise you I'm not hacking. I end up just getting it somehow.
There it is right there, perfectly tracked headshot on an engineer jumping around a corner.
Germa hack version 1.6. That is going to be the end of the gameplay.
I get this last heavy. He's kind of just standing here.
I missed the headshot right there, but I get him twice, one and two right there.
Thank you all so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
I top frag in this gameplay, which is always fun, always cool.
So if you like this video, go ahead and throw me a like, and I will see you guys all next time.
Take care, everybody.