I'll tell you, all of you that tell me that that taking the going to the bathroom the second way
takes less than 10 minutes. Nope. No, it does not. I don't know how the how you do that. How's it
possible? How do you take five? No, it does not. No way. I don't believe that person at all. It is
such it takes so much. You have to get in there. You have to get comfortable. That takes about 60
seconds. Then you have to be ready. If sometimes it's not all the way ready. That takes a good
solid minute or two for that to happen. Simply simply wiping your eye takes like at least a few
minutes. You can't say I can't say that. That's a bad word. And then after you're done, you have to
you sit there and contemplate the world for five minutes. That is the best place to decompress
all knowledge in your brain. You sit there and you die. You just you just take the world in for like
five to 10 minutes. If I don't get my decompress the world time, I did not go number two. If I
don't get that five minutes of like opening up a Twitter thread and judging every single person
in it. If I don't get that five minutes on the toilet, I'm sorry. I did not go number two.
Are you even potty trained? Imagine like I don't I have one of those like little toilets with little
kids. Remember why is there no plumbing installed in your house? I don't I don't know what I don't
know why. I don't know what that is. Not potty trained. You're gonna love them. A tweet? Oh shit
you're right tweet. Anyways the the reason people saying why you're talking about this. This is why
the stream is 20 minutes late. What's that um Newton's third law of aerodynamics? Anything that
can go wrong will go wrong. Somebody somebody made that up. That's somebody's law. Murphy's law. Okay
yeah right. Like Otto had to go to the bathroom. I had to go to the bathroom. I was hearing a weird
noise. I had to like investigate the noise. I need to water my I have plant. I need to water my plant.
When is the McDickie game night? Soon but not next week or the week after. All right so let's
uh here's his plan. Let me tell you what's going on here. Hello welcome back by the way. What kind
of plant? It's a money tree because it's like I think it's a cool looking it's a it's a little
money tree. It's a braided money tree and um if you have one of those in your house then you get
you you get to be you're a millionaire. You get to be a millionaire right? I water it every day and
I fucking make sure it's completely healthy and I put it in the exact spot it wants to be in in the
sun. Except here's the funny thing about a money tree. I believe you're supposed to be gifted a
money tree. I don't think you're supposed to just buy one and hope to be a millionaire. Like it's
not a scratch ticket. I like I don't know that's not accurate. I believe you suppose you're supposed
to be gifted one. You don't just buy one like a fucking lottery ticket. No I like plants now. I'm
a plant person now okay. I've got like three plants in my place and I take very good care of them
and they have names too Huey, Dewey, and Louie. Let me tell you Louie is quite the troublemaker.
He's quite a troublemaker. All right let me I'll be right back. Let me tweet. I didn't even tweet.
I'll tweet right now. Oh by the way the people asking about the title. Okay the reason why the
title is the way it is is because think of every pawn tv show or media. It's always about like porn.
Hardcore pawn. Okay pawn stars. Pawn. Porn. So I figured that you know the generation the zoomers
and the millennials will understand this one. And coming up next on enough pawn tabs to crash my
computer. They're gonna buy a helicopter. Will they? Oh you guys are pretty torn on this title.
I'm not sure. I don't know how to how to gauge it. Stop with the plus twos chat. It was clearly a
minus two. Oh you guys can debate that for a little while. Okay all right it's a pawn game.
It looks really fun. It looks really engaging. It looks really interesting. So we're gonna play it.
What am I talking about? Have you not seen any pawn tv show? They're all porn references.
Hardcore pawn and pawn stars. What are you talking about? How dare you? Okay pawn shop game.
Here's the twitter. Here's the twitter. Okay I know I can set this to be auto tweet but I don't
want to connect my twitch to anything. It always freaks me out. All right tweet is out. We can get
started here in a sec. The creative technology. I don't know. I just don't like connecting everything.
You're making this up. What am I? All right now I'm just being.
Hold on a second. My laundry is almost done. I just went into spin cycle. I'm just trying to
play a game here man. What's that? Popcorn? Yeah I got a popcorn machine right here. Are you angry?
I'm not angry. I got like a frog in my throat today though so you can hear a lot of like
mutes like that. I got this like annoying frog. It won't go away. All right let's go. I think
we're ready. Aren't we? I think so. This is called no umbrellas allowed and I'm very excited. Do a
ribbit. Oh speaking of ribbits. I got a quick story for you. It's really really small. You know
when you do one of those burps that's an internal burp. It's almost like a frog burp where your
stomach goes like and it comes back down really fast. So I had my iPad on my. I have like a
little thing that holds my iPad and it just sits in this little tray and I put that on my stomach
and it's like it has like a keyboard too. So it's like a little like half fake laptop little thing
and I did one of those. I was just sitting there with my arms behind my head watching like a YouTube
video and I went like and the thing bounced up like I like somebody was on a trampoline
and it almost hit me right in the face. It was it was scary. It bounced like and hit like almost
hit me right in the like bottom lip. It was terrifying. All right we're gonna play a new game.
2080 Ajik City. My throat is annoying. It was a cool story. I told you it wasn't even a story.
Last night there was a massive explosion at the Citizens Alliance Research Institute,
a central bunker district. Due to the explosion most of the artificial rain tech files and the
fixer manufacturing facilities are all gone. Get some water. I've been drinking water all morning.
I had a big salad too. I had a whole. I almost ate an entire avocado today. Hopefully I don't
shit my pants. The government and the Association of Victims of Avarice Crimes have announced that
they need at least eight more weeks to resume the fixerian project. Now Ajik City, the last city
waiting for the fix rain, is to stay dry for a few more weeks. Hey are you dead? Please help me.
Shush. An AVAC guy is coming. Hey Cheb thanks for the 25 community subs. Listen to me. What the
fuck? This is dalping joe from whatever it was. Oh look at the night sky. More beautiful than ever
isn't it? Thanks for the subs though. That's a lot of subs. 25. What's wrong with him? Is he injured?
Is he from the institute? No this is my son. He's got weak legs since he was a child. It's typical.
Don't worry. Do you need any help? No everything's fine. As long as every character is over the age
of 70 today I'll be able to be fine. Lucky me you fit the profile.
Pudding throat. I know I'm trying to work on it. Hey you're here. The doctor said your face got the
most injuries so he covered your whole face with bandages. You can take them off after a week but
he's not sure your face will be the same as it was before. Ah I'm Darcy just an old-timer who owns a
second-hand shop nearby. Oh here it comes. And from this moment you'll be my son Bob. I know
you're not just an ordinary fugitive and AVAC will keep track of you as you show up right after
the accident. So after you get back on your feet you should manage my store pretending you're my
son. Store is on the b1 level of the batopolis and sing sing side. It's just across the bridge.
And you um do you have a phone can I call my like parents like why is the guy's making this like
whole thing up about me it's like dude I like live like an hour away so I got I got a thousand
v bucks and I have to help manage his store all right those b1 is this hey you're new here aren't
you you gotta pay a fee to pass through here what are you staring at looks like you really are new
here falling for this crap what what beat it before I make you pay what why what is what
everyone's minus twoing me I didn't even do anything oh because it looks like Rick and if
I had said that I would have been in big trouble okay what was the v bucks joke no you okay so
what's worse me all right whatever fine okay I'll take that loss that's fine okay so I don't who is
this person their mind is doing the v okay all right we're gonna go b1 b1b up or b1b what is this
bus stop why can't I tell what floor I'm on Darcy's son is back in town or a b1 to me is
like basement one isn't it what this cat it is yeah Simaruk Lofts okay move to wait what do
you mean move by the way why aren't you looking for a job what for we'll soon all get fixed
anyway this is the store no junk side all right that's my that's the store agic city for runaways
what if they poured out fixed rain tomorrow so what there's like a rain that they drop on us
I wish junk side could be developed even by half of I don't know I can't read don't rush it's
dangerous what's your purpose in sing sing side today this is low I gotta turn this up buy some
flowers and clothes to do hair too I'm going to the secondhand shop coming with me now I like
to buy new ones okay minus two I feel it I you can't just predict a minus two that's not how
it works like you have some type of telepathic ability to tell when I'm going to tell a joke
this does look like pickle rick though it does looks like double pickle rick I'm surprised I
didn't met all right that person was right I don't know how you did that but like fuck off
how did you do that like an asshole whatever uh he's out here today again I admire we want change
okay he's in office AVAC must stop rebuilding the institute we must keep agic city safe from
fixer AVAC must stop oppressing citizens throw away your greed to me EMT center is like a hospital
your donation perfect fixer support the AVAC for the well I don't want to do that emotion
mitigation treatment center go to lower floor where am I supposed to go a depth hold on
come to Darcy's it's on level b1 podopolis sing sing side oh I gotta go down there it is okay
this Darcy's never seen the floaty around we've had a comedy recession and we didn't take a look
at the log all right so we have to go to work this is Darcy's here so here's like the different
let's go I'm Hugh people call me the sphinx of Darcy's and you are you look much better now
welcome to Darcy's the secondhand shop I've been running this place for more than 30 years
as I told you you are now my son Bob who will inherit this store from me that is why I picked
you up from the beach AVAC's been pestering me about what it is whereabouts and I needed to
stand in for Bob yeah after all that time now they're looking for Bob oh but Darcy what if
Bob comes back out of the blue that is not gonna happen it's almost a decade since he left by the
way this one here is Hugh it's got a mouth on it but it will be of help anyways now let's start
discussing what you're gonna do here at here you're going to both buy and sell things and you must
stay alert at all times every customer wants to get paid more money that's because this place
is off the grid from the citizen discourse data radar can I go home what the fuck is this I did
that so I don't have to care about what the AVAC is doing in here there are side effects just like
Hugh said customers all get so cocky as soon as they get in here anyway for today I'll teach you
how to negotiate price when buying things that's where to start when buying things it's really
important to find a balance it has to be a price that the customer can accept and that can still
make you a profit when resold they can't just start yelling out prices why not you must praise
the item first when it comes to appraising things I use cards do the voice fuck customers
introduce their items with cards gray card is base information base price it's a cup if without a
lack of fins or a long tongue okay it's a cup a green card is detailed information and changes
in price so I get detailed info from like so there's different rarities so if it's a green
card it's like okay this is could be the prices could be changed a lot here oh I forgot the blue
cards green cards include object objective information on the other hand blue cards are
close to opinions just like how damaged how popular or rare an item is so this is people
come in they go hey you die this is this is worth like fucking 50 bucks and it's worth like 30
sharing blue cards are like sharing your opinion at which customers may protest or get mad okay
card slot what the fuck is this to share a card with a customer you must insert the card in the
card slot combination of cards yields a price you can use it as a guideline while bargaining
all right so I have like the combination is the price of the of the actual item is it a card it's
not a card game don't worry about too much about colors for now focus on bargaining the price based
on the cards here the gray card for this bag says bag bags are usually sold for 100 vannas let's
say brand a is pretty high end which means the price goes up by 200 v bucks whatever I don't
care minus two me cowhide means adding an extra 50 v bucks to them and finally the price went down
by 20 percent is just slightly damaged now you can start bargaining based on the price these
cards have set and you see 280 v below the card slots that's the guideline you can suggest 280
from the start if you want to go easy you want to make a profit you better cut it at least one third
jesus decide how much to offer at first offer less than 70 percent of the guideline make an offer use
the calculator to set its buying price and press offer say yes or no to a customer's offer to say
yes press accept if no insert a new number and press offer fuck we have to do math so since this
is your first offer you can be a little bolder use the calculator on your own and try okay so
this is a bag just a regular bag it's damaged but it's from a decent brand and it's made of a cowhide
I'll give you let me do the thing that they do in pawn stars first of all he goes
okay
ah the best i can do is 40 bucks and the guy comes in wanting like 500 he laughs again really loud
okay so let's just should we do 40 dollars all right so let's just i'll give you i'll give you
150 bucks for it about 150 no this time we do as i said 190 what what no you tell me whatever
the best i can all right man the best i can do is 190 good but mostly customers won't accept
your first offer instead they will make a counter offer like this about 240
now man i'm telling you i i gotta put this on the shelf i don't know who's gonna buy this
i don't know who's gonna come in here looking for one of these am i just on the shelf for a year
i don't know that's 210 some well all right i yeah let me call my buddy he knows more about
ancient artifacts than i do i came to realize that i that's that's rick wait are you want me
1500 bucks wait a minute i just missed a huge huge huge fucking part of this i'll take 115
v what's going on not a good strategy leave your debt unpaid for long he just turned into like an
evil character what happened and it's not just the debt that you should make money for if you
don't save money you won't be treated as a human being after you become a fixie strictly speaking
they are not human beings anyway to be treated in a fair way even after you get fixed you have
to join the fixie pension plan to join it uh i forgot again the silly requirements just so we're
clear it's not because he's old it's because there was more than one as far as i remember you join
it by paying 10 000 v or was it 30 000 v let you know the details next time making some money is
the first thing to do anyways don't say anything you shouldn't when avac avac shows up just don't
try to get involved with them have a great day my dearest darcy i understand a little bit we'll
figure it out i was gonna say uh that's what's that guy's name rick dear citizens of a jick city
good morning from the association of victims of avarice crimes they broadcast in that manner
every day the association will stay closer to you than ever until fixer comes down again
let's win victory in the war against greed together thank you you're new here aren't you
i'm gonna get scammed does darcy have a problem in the in managing his part-time workers the
last guy was a nightmare how good are you do you know how to name prices hold on hold on this is
bob he's not just some part-time kid he's darcy's second son your darcy's son then is nari your
daughter no you're talking about bookgu this here is book who's younger brother bob and bob never
get intimidated by cut at what point do i literally just leave i could just walk out right now his
hands are shaking already what do you got anyway take a look at this my daughter gave this to my
ex-husband who used to be her father okay used to be would you please figure it out by yourself
all right people expect too much for me i'm divorced living with that man meant nothing
but a threat to my daughter and me we always had to keep our heads down when avac is near
i heard he's doing some kind of one-man protest these days he has some kind of hero complex to
stand against avac anyway what's written on there is removable so don't worry about it
bob why don't you start at 35 dollars you just i would just go immediately hold on this is a
trophy it's made out of plastic do i do do i do the pawn stars laugh and say man it's made out
of plastic this is not made out of gold man uh you're gonna i would take this down i would
recycle it that's what i would do okay it's in perfect condition though but here's what i was
gonna say before i like connect with rick on a very spiritual level because i feel like that's
half of these streams like a situation will happen and i'll just go even if it's not even
that fun i get interesting i just do it i feel like i connect with him okay so it well it's a
right a crazy price by 10 so that you want 60 but i mean it's made out of plastic so i'll give you
well this is a tutorial house 35 something yeah all right okay that was easy right but hey you
should get your hue repaired or something yours is so rude he was supposed to talk back to its owner
aren't supposed to talk like that they're supposed to talk back like that one leave now dear nosy
customer all right here's a tip for stock management i have an inventory all items you
purchase go directly to the inventory items are listed here click each item to see its details
cool wait so i can i sell that now why are you still here center right with a small triangle
in it okay let's open the inventory it's a button on the center right with a small triangle on it
center right oh okay customers can't see what's inside here so you have to place items on the
showcase to sell them really oh i'm gonna like this game oh cool this is cool display items to
start selling display an item drag out an item from the inventory set a selling price click the
item use the calculator set a selling price and offer so you put stuff off on the shelf
okay clear sold out sold items are marked as sold click x to empty the space okay nice let's put
the track place in what you just bought on the showcase to let customers see it okay praised at
60 bought it for 35 and then where does it drag it out somewhere should i put it go to the showcase
but clicking the button on the top left oh okay now on sale special price 60 did i put it i mean
that's all i have i don't have anything else is she gonna see that she's gonna see that though
right good job are you having fun she's so twisted whatever there's one more thing to tell you bob
whoa reputational card witness of darcy's this card will give you more advantages if you keep
recommending valuable items it will make customers trust your recommendation and encourage them to
make a purchase it will be automatically created and generate special price when an item is put in
this spot like right in the middle it's an exceptional selling price for recommended items
shit all right so i put that in the recommended and i can just say it's special price hard with
witnesses witness witness of darcy's is one of the reputational cards and darcy will soon explain
more about them i think this is gonna be really fun i'm getting ready what do you got all right
hi i found this at home how much can i get for it politics of corporate republic pretty sure you
need more items now your showcase is close to empty i just i just started all right this shit
is post it's a 50 it's 56 bucks for this poster made it a recyclable paper it's worth something
a little bit although it's damaged as hell i mean this thing's damaged man i'm gonna have to offer
you how's um okay i get but most i can do is 20 bucks whew so it turned out i got scared for
nothing 20 what a great deal all right i got a guy that can restore this shit is this yeah the
secondhand shop sorry i don't know anything about this town are you from another city have you
escaped the fixed rain no i was studying abroad and just came back to find my friend
and why are you here and not at your friend's house there's an issue and i'm here to ask you
to keep this for me i have to look around for a place to stay but it's so heavy i'm afraid of
avac is that a fucking moon rock what is this would you get it is a moon rock have you been
carrying this around the whole time yeah i'd almost pulled out my arms oh can i buy your arms
anyway i'll be here by this evening so please wait for me and don't sell it
lotis from other cities are so naive you don't bring them hey excuse me i'm looking for a moon
rock you have moon rocks alone welcome to agic agic we have two new stories coming up oh good
my tv at home is broken first up avac has launched their investigation into the fire at the citizens
alliance research institute the investigation is focused on finding if the fire was a mere
unfortunate accident or an act of arson it's clearly arson everyone was just waiting for
someone to act whoever set that place on fire i'm fully behind them next up professor yang ji
choy is staging a one-man protest against avac he argues that the lack of clear standards for
what are and are not avarice crimes will cause huge confusion he also claims avac is interpreting
the law however they please leading to the incarceration of innocent citizens i respect
his courage but don't think you don't think he's all talk why can't he do something real like that
arsonist oh do you want something can i help you what are you doing in here the rules must
be ambiguous and penalties must be harsh to make the citizens behave sounds not working i told
darcy to at least get a somewhat decent tv television citizens of ajax city the bunker
of freedom is opening its doors once again bunkers opening again it's gonna get loud around here
so let as many citizens as possible avoid fixed rain we have lowered the entrance fee
the last time they said that they charged a hundred thousand dollars
the new entrance fee is twenty five thousand dollars per citizen
twenty five thousand this is fantastic i can hide from the fixer with 25 000 of course only
pure floaties can enter the bunker that goes without saying and ticket sales are scheduled
to begin in five weeks until the day we meet the bunker of freedom will be waiting for all of you
that is in discourse data is still pretty quiet folks must be watching out on what they say
because of avac but the data record is blocked in here right this is a once in a lifetime chance
i won't need to stick to the silly fixie pension anymore i'm not gonna miss this got any moon rocks
he's all excited avc is gonna catch up to him before that they didn't mention one thing i'm
curious if they'll charge you extra for bringing hue can you ask around for me bob i want to go
to the bunker too i don't want to be left with fixies all right hold on uh what's this raise it
425 this is moon shit it's in perfect condition i could sell this like five 600 bucks praise the
24 all right let's put this on the shelf i'm selling for 50 40 uh i sure i can't i'm not
gonna sell this i'm a pawn shop how would i if you pawn something in a pawn shop you they don't
just sell it immediately within an hour of you giving it to them everything going all right
of course darcy i'm here hang on what's that rocking storage guess what darcy that's a moon
rock and maybe you could make some money by selling it where'd you get that lady just came in and
asked us to keep it for a few hours oh you got it for free yeah but she'll come back in a few hours
she's that stupid i if she's in a situation to ask you that pretty sure that she's being
chased by avac she won't make it why don't you just give it to me i was actually in need of money
come on oh fuck i can't i can't do that if i'm gonna have a reputable business
i need to be able to prove that i'm a reputable you know barterer no you can't take it i'm sorry
that's not how it works oh my god he's like about to kill me looks like i bought a stubborn one fine
fine you can't hurt his feelings like that bob i did it's company policy what do you want to say
yeah hi uh this is darcy's right i thought i came into the wrong place
uh can i sell this you like movies i'm just wondering what the fuck is this pretty sure
you need more items now or your showcase is close to empty uh eight bucks will do right eight bucks
get i'll just i'll give you two bucks spinning top it's just a top made of made of metal
okay damaged eight bucks okay okay i'll you know what i'll give you two dollars for it
well i think it deserves more uh can you tell me what made you say that it's fucking damaged man
how do i tell them when i say this shit's damaged dude no two two dollars two dollars is the best i
can do you're not getting one nut you not want to compromise you're not negotiating at all i want
to stop here you brought in a top that's worth like two dollars that why oh it's you look who's
little brother welcome back to agic city um could you buy this off of me this used to be my grandpa's
favorite all right what have we got old fucking spider-man volume thought you thought you're not
accepting items anymore i didn't see much stuff on the showcase we got i was expecting 29 bucks
will it be okay with you oh shit that's actually very very very fair that's incredibly fair
this shit's worth like 40 okay just really damaged though all right the world of fantastic
adventures by count one i all right i'll give you um that's 25 i think 27 is fair for both of us
27 i get best i can do and i have to shake my head left and right best i can do is 26
that's the best i can do for 26 i can't do any more than that all right thank you and both of
my hands are on the glass flat leaning in and it's like they're fucking glued they don't come off
wait is this the person for the moon rock i give the okay yeah here i got the moon rock for you
of course here you go thanks for using enough thanks so much i could tell by this side but
you're really nice person i don't want to miss dialogue here wish you have a great evening then
thank you have a nice day and of course you didn't even mention anything about a storage fee
we supposed to get a storage fee now hi uh i'd like to sell this on the back burner now but this
was once my daughter's favorite cute okay i expected more stuff to be on the showcase by
the way i look i just i've got three things it roughly deserves about 41 doesn't it it's
baby goods it's made out of wood it's but it's damaged a little bit damaged hold on i'll be
right back hey hey old man old man you're gonna take this one well let me see what you have here
it looks like you have a baby good and the thing about baby goods is babies use them
and babies are very cute and very very very nice but unfortunately for me it's made out of wood
and was not very good at a sale again i don't think i'll be able to sell it chum chum chum
why don't you come over and take care of this yeah okay uh i don't know what's your baby what's
your baby and everybody everybody looks at the camera and everybody looks around at each other
like this a bunch of zoom ins uh i don't know man i'm just gonna go in my car hey hey big
horse come on out here uh hey what can i what's wrong what's happening uh my dad just told me
was uh it was gonna be 45 i don't know maybe 50 uh best the best i can do man is 50 is 42
best i can do is 42 works for me all right she wanted 41 well this is what happens this is what
happens when there's no communication the four of them just run around the store and they just
don't talk to each other my ass why is she being so weird bob this is nary joe she's your fake niece
all right wait a minute everybody hold on i back up i gotta go to the back room okay i've got this
baby toy praise it let's let's put it up there for 50 i got this book of smells raise it forward
this is worth a lot let's go i'm this one's 60 in fact get the shit out of here i'm putting this in
here this is recommended 60 bucks holy markup it's not a markup i had to restore it okay filling
out the book here you mean he's my fake uncle why would bob leave bluebird for a shithole like this
in the first place hey you if you're dreaming about inheriting the store you'd better shut it
off right now because there's no seat for a bogus son like you this place is supposed to be mine
once grandpa passes away the crap and buy off this cup how do you keep bringing garbage like this
do i have to explain why don't you sell your paintings you have tons of them stop that joke
do you think i'd sell my works to a place like this please think before you open your mouth
quit whining and take this cup for 90 bucks you know that's a special deal first of all first of
all that's way too high second of all a cup like that i mean did did george washington drink out of
it because if i get a guy in here and we figure out we do like a dna test on it and then i can
sell for like 20 000 but no 90 bucks no way 90 dollars for a cup no looks like someone needs
a lesson and let me make this one thing clear george washington did drink out of this if you
ever ruin this soon to be inherited i'll make you into a hue just like that thing crossing the line
nari i mean once grandpa finds out what a deadbeat you are he'll handle it himself stay strong i'm
fine even makes me want to run away sometimes i'm i'm doing just fine breaking news from
ajik ajik the association of victims of avarice crimes is still looking for four missing persons
after the fire broke in the citizens alliance research institute all missing are men in their
30s including an accounting staff sang su an ok bae and jisoo cha who've been working as
researchers at the institute an experimenting participant young doe are missing as well
this is reporter saw a oh or ajik ajik news you don't need to avoid my eyes i don't care if you're
one of the four missing just don't cause any harm to my darcy i like to buy the fantasia rulebook
over there how much is it oh shit 60 bucks i think must be wrong who buys this for 60 bucks
i'll buy it right away if it's 46 46 55 okay i wasn't sure you'd accept my offer thanks
wait what i said 55 wait what i said i said 55 i said 55 except 55 what the fuck how was your
first day i didn't want i wanted to oh i didn't hit offer but what the fuck okay i was thinking
55 it said yes take next monday avac will come by to check your identification
you have to make a fake id by this friday fortunately there's a man who could make
fake ids he lives in the same building as you right above your room visit him after work since
he sleeps during the daytime and works at night he will ask for 800 what if you can afford it
visit him right after this what if i fail to get a fake id well then the avac will come to take
my fake son away oh is it closed yeah we're closed huh then what about this gentleman here
he's the owner oh is he by the way is this the theme here theme what theme wrap up an employee's
face to make him look like a mummy or is he just caught in a terrible turmoil nah just kidding
have a good evening then did he hear us i don't think so but no let's not forget about him
anyway just make sure to get your fake id by this friday it's for yourself
i wrote it on the calendar small one behind me here citizens the association of victims
of civil rights crimes is announcing the day is at an end the forecast for tomorrow is sunny in
the morning but rainy in the afternoon as you know no umbrellas are allowed thank you oh that's why
it's called that because the rain like fucks us all up and controls us or something you get to
miss me deadly have a dream of me tonight okay i have a calendar i get skills i'm gonna get like
skill points more visitors will come to buy goods recommended items will gain more interest no okay
so i'm like rank one likeability holy shit there's a lot of stuff here okay so i gotta should i buy
friday right what's today's date do i have a calendar just get it now oh now do it now
donate donate to the avac wait please donate 100 bucks i don't want to donate that no deny
is it like multiple endings or something here we want change we must keep agic city safe from
fixer safe with avac all right well i'm not doing that what's this interact office of jung ho gong
the stabilizer of the fair tread commission okay uh i gotta go across the city again right yeah
look at the fake id i i'm gonna how do i go where's that thing oh there it is scavenge
13v let's take money from this guy what's this on vacation undergoing remodeling under maintenance
maybe i'll eventually be able to do all these uh i have to go up again all right so the sing sing
side is where i go to work so i have to go he looked so seriously injured can i buy oh wait
the little lofts can i um buy anything guy's apartment is above mine this is the association
of victims of avarice crimes you must pay your fine right now to prove your non-possession bunker
of freedom is a savior sent to us or else i'll arrest you for crimes no i i all right where's
my apartment he's in the apartment above mine so this is my apartment right here somewhere right
where's mine no we're gonna go so wait where is he where's my apartment this is my apartment
who's there ah oh it's over here here money first 800 v that's a lot i don't have not gonna have
enough money to buy product you name bob joe i'll send it to you monday morning check your inventory
then we'll have it it'll be a purple booklet that's your id i'll go away i think we gotta
go down one more floor don't you need it by friday i think i just need it before they come you know
what the guy next door is like disposed moon rock sold a 76 return pretty good day one a woman asked
me to keep her moon rock for some hours with 25 000 i can enter the bunker of freedom to avoid
fixer ticket sales will start in five weeks darcy wanted to get the moon rock but i didn't give it
to him i returned the moon rock to the owner i met darcy's granddaughter nari there are four
people missing one of them's probably me i have to make a fake id by this friday i bought the fake
id it'll be my inventory monday and i paid 15 dollars in interest to darcy i'm just sleeping
dream look i talk too fast okay here we go new day i have 121 bucks here comes another jobless
wimp i'll walk around doing nothing just stand somewhere like me what you looking at get lost
that does look like rick i'm not going to be the one to say it that's going to be you that says it
because i will get raked wait what's going on this is mine no it's mine i'll get raked over the
coals if i say it ow i'm sorry but an avac man was right there he freaked me out so that was an
avc guy ricked i know i didn't i well i feel bad for anybody with the name rick in 2021 you know
what i mean like because when people hear the word rick there's an immediate just visceral
reaction to it like imagine if my name was richard and people were like oh hey rick you guys would
be like yeah tell him to stop saying that don't say that word rick imagine if your name was peter
that would be fine rage all right let's go keep up the hard work bob thank you jeez did you get
to wash your face you got sleep in your eyes bob it would take one pound of pressure to just punch
you in the head and blow up your brain just i want to make sure you understand that are you mr bob
joe are you here to take him away this must be a record you've received a report about you from
your niece nary joe harry not again she said you're so obsessed with money and never looked
after her she also said she could prove it so you have to pay the fine right now to prove your
non-possession spirit or get arrested for avarice crime on the spot what what's going on it's an
emergency darcy bob's in danger mr joe your granddaughter reported your son for crimes
jesus let me take care of this we talk outside is john gong yes miss gong this is where i go
stick my tongue out and then i look look over at the robot and i go yeah anyway morning bob i made
a song about you yesterday it's called new bob bebop bob bara beep new bob bop it's the new bob
in town hue bob up ah that was great citizens of agic city good morning from the association of
victims of crimes they cut me off have a restrained and greed free day thank you
you haven't run away yet now it's time for me to teach you how to check materials and damage
levels let's look at that bag from yesterday i said that this bag is in perfect condition but
before moving on to the next step you should check for yourself by using a tool praising an item oh
here we go customers sometimes lie means you have to check each card carefully they show you
scrutinize an item use the tools in the manual oh boy insert cards from the manual pull out
cards and insert them into the card slot if you're wrong customers mostly turn it down
what a slurp i'm fine here's the toolbox click the damage assessor and move it onto the bag
it's in the second slot holy shit this is gonna get well isn't gonna get wacky here are the two
essential tools damage assessor and material magnifier this measures damage level and this
shows what texture it actually is okay so you're saying that this is it's not really
perfect right and let's move on to its material click the material magnifier and move it onto
the bag wait so the happy face means perfect this is what a stupid meter this is a baby toy
i'm gonna look like an idiot you see its material up close but you can't tell what exactly it is
for now that's what you need this manual for oh my god the manual complements your knowledge
and expertise you use keyboard shortcuts to navigate efficiently lets you move to each page
right this is where you pull out cards from in the manual okay in the text page what are the
manual list in the manual okay the material list find out which material looks closest to what
you just saw drag the one you found from the list of the slot you'll be pulling out a card
and putting it in the slot it's this one yeah it's this one cowhide oh leather cowhide but
now that's what's worth more money it's cowhide that's it did you see the card and the price change
next let's head to the condition page from the manual list use the damage assessor again and
decide which damage level it falls into this would be i would say this would be slightly damaged
this is slightly damaged it's not perfect condition ooh cards in the slot are tagged to items and
shared with customers as you put things on the showcase oh to let customers know this item is
worth this much cards have to be accurate and concrete to earn trust of customers and with
trust you will be able to sell more so keep in mind to use the tools in the manual there's one
more once a customer accepts a card you can't undo it which means you cannot remove or replace
cards once the deal is closed so don't lose focus during an appraisal it's the only chance you can
decide which card to tag onto an item this is one last thing you have to keep in mind during
appraisal okay reputational card too this card gives you more advantages as your appraising skill
improves customers will begin to buy items appraised by us without any doubt or even paying
more it's a reputation scam everyone will only scam some people i can't say we're gonna scam
everybody but we'll scam whoever we need to it doesn't show up from the beginning but
right after appraising and purchasing so it's automatically attached to items after you appraise
so i have to get that skill up you already mentioned the card wittiness of darcy's right
oops these three cards indicate our store's reputation from three different views these
are special because they improve themselves along with you better you get the more effective each
card will be by driving the bargain to your advantage or encouraging customers to buy each
card shows its detailed effects sick you can check the effects and the progressions of each
card here all right i'm ready for day two it's one oh just one last thing i feel like i'm this is e3
it'll be beyond your capacity for now so i'll let you know about it later it's a 10 second trailer
for elden ring for now focus on improving your recommending skills okay the abc must have scared
you back then don't worry i took care of it they wanted you to either pay the fine or get fixed
might sound like they've given you a chance to make a choice but they're not the amount of
fines is ridiculous and most people can't afford to pay it avac wants nothing but to make more
fixies so try not to give them an excuse to get you and please forgive my granddaughter she may
look a bit selfish but she's just a poor kid both her father and her uncle left town when she was
so young moreover her father's now a fixie you can't imagine what she's going through
they always blame the parents if things go bad anyway i should leave now wish you good luck
well you may turn the closed sign over because you've been talking to me for six hours
store's not closed it's eight o'clock all right hey how's it going are you a new owner of this
place can you take a look at this already in the past but still sad isn't it it's not good to have
a large population okay what do we got made out of paper let's fucking make sure it's made out
of paper yeah that's right here what is that surgical steel oh shit should i lie wait this
is made out of surgical steel am i scamming myself no i'm not am i scamming that's stainless
steel what the fuck is this okay this is fairly damaged this is very damaged it's made out of
paper oh i'm sorry hello you dummy one okay it's paper it is in fact made out of paper but it was
way more damaged than you said it was liar what's this uh best i can do i'll give you i'll give you
10 bucks for it what do you think i did miss some details but still you can't cut the price like
that yes i can i see it's you literally came in here and you told me it was slightly damaged it
was incredibly damaged give you i'll give you 11 okay yeah there you go that's how you make
that's how you make a fucking deal i'd like to buy the trophy over there how much is it
uh it is good i expected as much i'll take it yeah all right yeah 60 bucks thank you just an
ordinary bracelet made it a silver okay wait what's this what's that made out of uh bullshit
it's made out of paper liar i'll give you a dollar all right what is this hard to tell silicone
is this silicone what does this matter is this i think this is silicone silver is it actually
silver this thing's fucking damaged it's really damaged yeah it's damaged fairly can we let it
pass a slightly damaged oh wait a minute we'll look up blind what do you mean look up look up
what do you mean look up look up uh slightly damaged and no no no i'm sorry you're making
me nervous bob it's a relief you know you shouldn't compromise on condition no i'm not
gonna pay two times the price of it all right what about material because i don't think this is real
maybe it is look up what am i looking up at why is everybody saying look up use eyes look up what
do you mean look up like what do you mean like scan his face i don't know what you what do you
mean second row look up yeah but i don't okay it's silver it's silver all right no it's silver all
right fine it's made of silver right but i thought it was like could be this one or this one i don't
know you guys freaking me out i'll give you 35 dollars for it i know you're generous come on
i'll give you 40 thank you i didn't really think you'd give me more get out of here don't
fucking come back i like to buy the baby mobile over there how much is it uh that'll be uh what i
expect this much oh i put it up to 46 i put it up to 50 hell yeah you again how could you report new
bob to the avac new bob was so close to getting dragged away i'd call it a welcome party what
brought you here today what kind of garbage did you carry here knock it off or i'll throw you away
to the stupid junk junk huh uh now look at this never seen such an amazing painting have you
uh i don't know about this uh don't you know what amazing means um i don't have any i can't buy this
uh yeah this is cool i wouldn't say that's cool right okay then you can take this for free oh
what's what's what i want to examine this at least you got an eye for painting this is a stolen
property yeah this is stolen property she's trying to get me arrested yeah i gotta check this thing
for like fucking wires or something poster picked up in bluebird on the showcase how much is it
uh that'll be that's too much for a used one but okay it's hard to get a new thing these days
40 bucks i put it before oh shit you paid way too much for that all right thanks
i kind of want to like get rid of this thing show me a silver bracelet bracelet without any
decoration he's asking for a recommendation in this case find if the item that meets her
requirements is in the inventory idea i got it on the table customer will ask you the price that's
when you can speak out how much you want if the customer is looking a lot for an item that you
don't have or don't want to sell just press the button decline on the calculator yeah i got a
bracelet i got one right here i have yes i'm doing the tutorial you hear that this is what i wanted
how much is it it is 120 dollars 80 bucks 80 it's 75 75 dollars how about 57 60 60 like why
can i offer 60 six can't offer it why can't i offer another one except 65 i have to decline
oh decline sorry let's stop here no no what no i wanted to haggle no what the fuck what why
couldn't i say another price you have paintings what i wanted to i wanted to say another price
you only get one offer here this is 450 dollars i stop i what is happening this is how you do
business this is uh not really good let me show you my painting tomorrow you may even cry seeing
it fine then come back with your painting tomorrow what the fuck i hold on i need to put this on
display 75 dollars for that is this locked raised it i don't even know what this is fucking worth
what is this worth i don't know i don't want to sell this this is praised at 13
wopper 11 i'm not gonna put this on no because this is definitely like stolen property she's
trying to get me arrested she made that really clear she made that incredibly clear it was my
birthday present can you please tell me how much this is worth valueless let's find out
this shit is made out of paper okay and it's uh slightly damaged
slightly damaged what i just made it worth more money what
no no what i know he just wanted me to i thought i was appraising for him i just
boosted the price no i he said how much is this worth it's garbage get rid of it are you serious
i should never have told him that okay i get it now i want to sell i know but he just said hey
i got this for my birthday what is this worth he didn't say hey i got this for my birthday
and i'm gonna be a dick and sell it immediately to you right now somebody gives us a birthday
present fuck i don't want it let's just get out of here just go just go get out of here take
your fucking thing and go sell it somewhere oh hang it up i don't know hi can i sell this
the showcase is nearly empty now it's just a blip right all right how much is this thing
actually fucking worth what is this thing's made out of goddamn diamonds i think what is that
okay i've made it a glass and this is he says it's slightly damaged if this is in perfect
condition so i am not going to tell you that i'm not going to fuck that up again so this is worth
probably a lot because it's a it's a who chew game studios plaque so um you know this by the way the
thing is fucking pretty damaged i don't know if you knew that you're dishonest you can't lie
all right here i because it's this is worth like 100 bucks he thinks it's slightly damaged i'm going
to say i'll give you 50 bucks for it guess you're very careful while appraising i am 50 bucks
but i don't like to argue for a few more bonus i'll take it thank you nice dick hi how's your day
your darcy son the one came back from bluebird i didn't scam anybody take a look at this
it's soft it's good to sleep on fruit i expected more stuff to be on the showcase by the way
okay people keep buying things all right what is this thing it's made out of like pebbles what is
that this is made out of velvet oh wait a minute here velvet don't say that put stuff on the
showcase hold on well you can't reappraise things afterwards i can't reappraise this i it's this is
just what it is oh shit i have to be honest okay well this is velvet be honest appraise it i mean
it is slightly damn i mean it's i think it's fairly damaged by the way uh no you got that right you
just didn't know it was velvet all right what do you want for it 93 bucks uh i'll give you 40
are you trying to play mind games with me on a 30 margin then let's stop wasting our time and
settle on 60 64 that's actually that's not bad i'll take it i'm gonna sell this for 150
insultingly low dear citizens we are announcing the day is at an end as we informed you yesterday
it will be raining this evening we'd also like to inform you that the rain today is not fixer rain
but just rain as you know no umbrellas are allowed thanks for your cooperation we put
some shit on ourselves this shit was appraised for 72 we're gonna a hundred bucks for this one
uh that's up there this thing i'm gonna this i'm gonna get 125 but i don't want to sell this it's
probably illegal all right let's make some money this is a scam shop um if you think this is a scam
shop i would like for all of you to watch one episode of shark tank and listen to when kevin
o'leary leans in and goes what are your margins what are your margins how much do you sell these
for and they say we sell them for 29.99 and how much does it take to make them three dollars and
45 cents just watch one episode of shark tank of royalty what i'm gonna offer you is a 20
royalty on every single sale until my loan is paid back and then in perpetuity i'd like a fixed rate
of 10 yeah he always just he always has the convoluted deals don't you feel like that kevin
o'leary does not want to give anybody money he just wants to like make people confused to a point
where they pick mark cuban and like mark cuban just has to buy all this shit like it's up it's
always like barbara you know what i mean like barbara and it's always barbara steps in and
just like you know what this is what i'm gonna do for you i'm gonna offer you five percent more
than what you're asking it's a barbara's always the one that buys the stuff based barbara you know
can i say that it's an old joke i've been going for 10 years all right we can do old stuff
all right that's fine we're good you may get soaked up to the bone be careful bob
all right so i can't it's raining out what the why is it raining is it fixed rain
no relax it's just ordinary rain how would we tell the difference any money in the trash lucky me
what i get gotcha lucky me what i get i didn't get anything run home no you don't run home in
this scenario those of you that had a bus stop and you went you walked to the bus stop
or if you were walking to work or whether if you get off of like the subway or whatever
this kind of rain you see people sprinting around and panicking but it's already over
if you stand in this for more than five seconds it's over already you might as well just walk
normally you're not oh no i gotta rush really fast to get out of this rain you're already
somebody dumped a bucket of water on your head already it's over let's get running and all running
does is just makes it hit you in the eyes because if you run really fast you're giving yourself
like this perpetual forward motion so the rain droplets actually hit inside your eyeballs
you know i don't know what that fucking rain's been i don't want rain in my mouth i don't want
rain in my eyes it gets like sucked up from the ground evaporation style and comes up i don't
know what the fucking clouds are i don't know what kind of dirt is up there where did that water
come from i don't want that fucking water in my mouth what is this whether it's true or not i
want to stop even the rain noise sounds creepy this bro is fucked that's not how rainwater works
um yes what do you mean freddy dread 25 community subs what's up freddy the freddy dread everybody
ladies and gentlemen i'm gonna sneeze i just want to make sure everyone's aware and i'm gonna make
sure i get it at the perfect you know i i always think that that's really funny but that's probably
getting old how okay is it more than five times is it old what do you think i think if we do that
10 times i have to stop doing it 10 times is too much all right i got 19 return on this 100 return
on this cool i picked up oh i picked up a book what that was in the trash nice cool all right
all right this painting i don't like it i don't want it looks good residence sleeper
it's a crime book okay i only have 90 dollars this is bad should i do that kind of look around
and look at more trash and stuff i feel like i need more items should i go like take things
oh hey those kids again caught a cold yeah you know it rained yesterday yeah and i couldn't use
an umbrella and where's that fucking rain been thank you our kids are getting made much smarter
let's not go outside when it rains then rain doesn't give you a cold rain doesn't cost i know
guys you learn that in like fifth grade science maybe i can catch him by myself umbrellas yes
umbrellas are not allowed because there's something in this world called fixed rain uh and if it
touches you apparently it fixes you and makes you like a i don't know like a government conspiracy
or something i don't know we need more information from the story erin you're buying a darcy's well
i won't stop you what's wrong with darcy's here are citizens of agic city good morning have a
restrained and greed free day thank you i'd like to ask you for a favor the man's going to show
up with a statue sometime today and he's going to insist about checking its material please tell
him it's 24 karat gold 24 karat my life depends on it please help me uh the daily on the showcase
how much is that only 25 dollars what this is crazy who pays 25 bucks for this i'll buy it right
away if it's 12 it's been appraised at 13 now you pissed me off no no what do you mean fuck off i
can't that's your final you just gonna leave no i i bought it for how much should i buy this for
11 i'm gonna get one dollar return no someone will buy it no get out of here well it was not
a bad offer yes it was the things were 13 dollars i had it appraised by me i'm the smartest person
in this room i i brought my painting look at this kraken doesn't it scare you let me be honest what
really scares me is your confidence sorry oh nothing what do you say if i can give it to you
as a gift i think we may be friends someday we refuse the gift you're being funny trust me
people will soon line up to buy my paintings they'll get crazy about the greatest artist
boko park until the day comes i'll be staying in the bunker of freedom and in the bunker i'll
practice and practice you know once i get into the bunker nothing can take away my artistic
spirit and talent i need 25 000 to get in there got rich parents come on look at the bright side
we still have enough time to make 25 000 speaking of which i gotta go and find some more part-time
jobs see you around i praise this painting you don't have to be his friend bob he doesn't have
rich parents i want to can i not praise this thing holy shit hey let me see what this is made of
oh here we go so this is okay the guy told me that his life depends on me telling him
okay this is perfect condition do i say perfect condition what if okay so i but i can't perfect
condition just check the material oh okay fine it's made out of fucking stone but it is made out
of gold it is made out of gold why do i have to this is not a lie didn't he say tell him he said
tell him it's made out of gold it is made out of gold you don't have to buy it well then tell him
that okay it's made out of gold don't lie yeah the guy it's gold the guy told me to say that
24 karat that man got you too didn't he stop lying to me is this really 24 karat gold um yeah it is
are you two scamming me i know the truth tell me the truth before i report you along with him
um i'm gonna lean in real close let's say 24 karat gold and i'm gonna stare it's 24 karat gold
you told me twice so it's on you if you're wrong somebody wants to judge my appraisal how fucking
dare you how much is that here we go it's 25 bucks i don't think must be wrong who buys this
for 25 i'll buy it right away if it's 14 all right we get that's a that's a better return
check the next page um i don't think there is a next page on the materials it was my birthday
present can you please tell me how much this is worth bluebird ocarina all right well judging by
the cracks on it i could tell you that this is absolutely made out of clay no it's made of clay
and then i could tell you it was all right i was already aware of that but i don't blame you okay
uh and this it's not i don't know it's fairly damaged i don't it's fairly damaged not worthless
oh it was never on my mind thanks for telling me the shit's worth 129 bucks base
and these refer to brands for more these arrows don't yeah there's no page two all right so so
what do you want for it you want to pawn it you want to pawn it you want to sell it i'll buy it
for 40 good and it was so great to know every detail about this yep you're welcome i have no
money left by the way i have to start selling shit uh get this fucking out here nobody wants it um 75
this painting though let me see a detailed about this thing is 2d artwork failed price
created created by feet not hands but wait he made this with his feet failed piece
slightly damaged and the signature is unidentified all right well i'll sell it for 50 i've got this
book too book velvet valueless i can't appraise it in here i just have to sell it i'll sell it for 20
and this little bird thing all right praises it says 65 bucks accept one hold hold hold don't
sell the painting hold it hold the feet work hold it why what don't sell the paintings they're
fucking worthless they even say they even told me this this stuff was worthless hold it hold it
hold the door what it's 2017 hold on bob did you eat up our money little by little i think it's
time to get a loan oh we can't buy more stuff you remember the button on the upper right corner
if you're too proud to get a loan night dumpster diving is another option how much is the picked
up book what this is crazy who pays 20 bucks for this i'll buy it right away if it's 11
dollars fuck you 15 no fine take it i need money i got it for free this doesn't matter if i went
some if i found like in a dumpster an old like little figurine i'm not gonna just give it away
for free i'm gonna try to sell it but what if it was worth like 500 dollars thanks for not
turning it down this is never our decision darcy she's just like her father she's dreaming of
becoming an artist even in a situation like this without adac both nari and her father would have
been following their dream by now i could do anything for nari to let her enter the bunker
so she won't get fixed as her father did harry's dad took off to haga city a few years ago saying
he'd become a great painter haga city is where artists used to live in groups but you know fixed
rain came down over all the country now he's trying to hide it but she's going through a lock
haven't you felt that she's not hiding it at all darcy anyway i'll take the painting for five
foot why no you don't think you don't give me 500 bucks what the fuck bugleberry voice
oh yeah this is how you know it's bugleberry's voice 100 bucks well i like the price but let
me think for one more second in my opinion 93 dollars is just about right oh you know what fine
i'll take it quite good at hitting a happy medium breaking news more than 60 citizens are
complaining of severe cold symptoms after yesterday's rain one male citizen said not
allowed to use an umbrella i was fully exposed to the rain that's why i caught a cold he also
said i asked the association of victims of adverse crimes if they could let the elderly in the week
use umbrellas the association however is not responding yet to his request this is reporter
oh for agic agic news can you take a good look at this oh boy i don't really want to let it go
but my mom has been pushing me so hard to sell it but we can't take this item at the moment sorry
why any hard feelings on the arcade xo no but let's say bob is just not ready for this
what yes i am fine no worries even because my mom pushed me so you're my excuse now what are you
talking about i mean i'm not ready for this unplug this guy what was that all about common silver
bracelet on the showcase how much is that 75 i think must be wrong who buys this for 75
i'll buy it right away if it's 42 it was a bad offer because it's not even you didn't that's
not even worth the base price get out of here what do you want is my painting sold out you got a
bigger problem now re your nemesis has arrived my nemesis yesterday we showed your painting to a
guy and he said the painting is hideous and he showed us this his painting uh why am i not haggling
because it's not an option if they come in and demand a price i cannot haggle it's only an option
i think when you appraise there's a shitty name on this is his name boko park bye during the whole
time i knew a nemesis was coming for her how much is the hue doll oh i was like dude take it for free
it's quite much for this i buy it right away if it's 107 holy smokes
i get a oh i'll take it my pool of money is going back up how's it going cdd recorder is being
blocked right stop talking just take a look at this who's setting the reselling prices by the
way they're higher than i expect me all right this thing is uh first of all let me tell you
what you got here you got a slightly damaged crown but it's a 400 bucks okay thanks for being honest
yeah uh it's also because i'm made out of this thing is made out of what you got here is you
got it holy fuck it's made out of platinum all right everyone's saying i'm stupid why did you
tell them so okay listen if i don't appraise this is platinum i can't appraise it again
so i can't sell it for what it's actually worth because i cannot appraise it if i lie
i can't repraise can't appraise it again so i either sell it for like 400 i'm talking back here
it's made of platinum all right what do you want for it how about uh i'll give you 250 as a thank
you for your hard work i'll take your offer right away hey here's something urgent seems like the
stabilizer is going to be here soon he thinks actual bob came back from bluebird so he'll get
you to take emotion mitigation treatment emotion mitigation treatment basically suppresses your
emotions it's so expensive that you may feel you might as well become a fixie the reasons why some
people desperately wait for fixed rain anyhow taking that treatment won't do any good for you
to tell the truth it's pretty easy to avoid it you have to tell yourself you're a fixie and
suppress all your emotions simply put just act like a fixie as best you can oh you know what
i'm gonna say here it comes oh you can always tell because i go oh what about fixer his brain
must have been so messed up fixer is a drug to erase human emotions and desires people who got
fixed are fixies people who haven't are called floaties fixies are nothing but the dead who still
breathe they're unresponsive to whatever happens around them even when their house gets robbed
or when the avc takes away their family right before their very eyes they just stand there
and watch no anger no sadness no desire nothing almost every citizen living in this country
mindlessia is already a fixie except for those in this city it's because a year ago the association
of victims of avers rained fixer all over the country except agic city we were lucky because
the citizens of alliance and research institute exploded a few weeks ago that's how we became the
last floaties in the whole country anyhow the stabilizer comes pretend you're an emotionless
zombie and please don't say you don't know what zombie is even if he offends you or acts nice to
you don't move a muscle there'll be only two choices left floaties who can't hide their emotions
in front of stabilizers either get emotion mitigation treatment be labeled an avarice
criminal i've seen countless people going bankrupt trying to afford emotion mitigation treatment
once you're labeled as one of these criminals otherwise the avc will arrest you and fix you
so never let the stabilizer get to you how will i know who the stabilizer is did he say i'm the
stabilizer i got more shit to put on the shelves hold on common silver bracelet oh yeah how much
is it 75 bucks buy it right away it's 43 look off fine just i'm getting rid of this dumb thing
i've overpaid for it since i'm not an expert i don't know its details but you're an expert
you can find something right super soft cat bed hold on i gotta get this take this stuff out of
the window it's just going right here and it's i'm selling this for 750 dollars right no 600 how
much do they sell this for the basket the smart master 600 i think 600 is fair yeah that's fair
all right it's pet goods made out of cotton it's value let's find out what you got first of all
by the way buddy this is velvet so not valueless got so you got here you got a velvet pillow
yeah and um let's take a look at the condition it's it's slightly damaged i don't think it's
valueless i think it's got some uh got some value to it yeah so uh i'll give you a
35 40 i'll give you 55 i'll give you 50 bucks thanks for finding me every detail so kindly
see 600 is less than a 25 markup you could have gone higher whatever hey it's you the moon rock
lady after i saw you last time i couldn't stop thinking about jisu so i just dropped by my
friend jisu was such a good person and really smart too he even got a job in the citizens
alliance research institute but i heard he had a hard time there while doing all sorts of
experiments on floaties and fixies must have been really painful for him to watch the experiments
killing people and driving them crazy by the way here's a mars rock this one's worth five
grand anyways it was jisu that i was looking for but after the fire in the institute he's
gone missing however i will do anything to find him i'm sure he's still alive anyway it was great
to see you again take care then and stopping by i thought she was hitting on you um well thanks
for coming by are you darcy's son who came back in town oh this is the stabilizer he's from the
fair treaded commission and his roles to prevent and settle down the chaos of the city according
to the citizen discourse data stabilizers usually create even more chaos knock it off i'm not like
those idiots nothing none of them can pick on floaties as skillfully as i do oh so you're proud
of it by the way why do you have your face wrapped up like that is that a problem of course i just
see the face to decide whether he needs emotion mitigation treatment or not maybe i can put him
under intensive care he's been in bluebird for a decade huh and the bell is on you shut up time
to see how good your master is at restraining his emotions you better be completely honest question
number one if i say i need tons of money right now are you going to ask me why no don't be serious
it's just a test now if i say i need a hundred dollars from you are you going to give me that
no don't need to be so serious i don't need your pocket money let's just stop this shit i can take
you straight to abac and give you a dose of fixer sure is that an easy decision for you
wacko are you upset now no but your voice is telling me different here take this money and
calm yourself down uh yes now i'm kidding of course 10 bucks isn't enough why don't you work
for me forget about your father and just follow my orders uh what's what's emotionless yes
right that's what that is no would be like no yes you're just a yes man you just want me to leave
no yes i don't know should i say yes i do want him to leave but but isn't saying no like no don't go
yes i want you to leave but is yes more emotional like i want you to get out of here because you're
annoying or no i want to keep you here because i'm like i like this conversation too much which
one is correct yes implies want yes is more emotional no no here's your result there were
some points your emotion level exceeded the limit but i'll cut you some slack for now they don't
want to give up this fun too soon how evil but i will keep watching you remember i'm always ready
to put you in the treatment process fast you're not a good actor by the way to look like a fixer
you have to loosen up and act like a zombie that dull face of yours right now is what you really
needed earlier uh hi uh could you buy this off me you look very kind by the way not like darcy
um didn't i didn't i sell this to you who did it wait what did i get who did i don't want this
just made it a paper yeah pretty damaged that's just fair this is fairly damaged i'm sorry fine
but you could have just looked over it no like yeah i don't fucking want this shit i give you
five dollars for it i'm gonna leave a margin like 30 percent that i'm pretty sure nine will do
that'll be eight it's seven dollars i'm not going to be able to even sell this for more than like
12 anyway i made it what do you mean i made it that wasn't even a real newspaper article
i heard you were back bob it's me hondja remember me i must have run into you in the streets but i
didn't recognize you with that bandage i never thought you'd come back i think serene is going
to start soon in the city actually let's save the gloomy talk for later it's been so long
i have something to return too i borrowed darcy's year estimator last time
tell darcy i'm sorry for taking so long and if you have anything that doesn't sell for over a week
feel free to give it to me i still run my junkyard right downstairs remember all right anyway i got
one more thing to tell you now you're operating this place instead of your father so you're a new
member of the batopolis merchant union now i'm the president of the union but we usually don't
have a lot to do together it's for a day we got to make one voice anyway that's all for today
and you can come to my junk shop every morning if you have anything that's not sold for more than
five days it's right downstairs not at high prices but i will be uh without i'll buy it without
arguing hey unionize your workplace thanks for the 25 community subs picked the right time to
do that drink water i don't need to drink water he needs to drink water the association is
announcing the day is at an end the forecast for tomorrow is clear skies thanks to the 25 subs
i'm so tired head home now bob tootaloo oh monka monka dabadee monka dabadee okay uh
we gotta look for stuff in the trash i gotta do more trash searching got it lucky me what did i
get oh he threw it away wait who threw that away what is this it's a hoverboard why is it
valueless this is the way to do it just find trash 20 bucks nice i didn't have to do anything cash
55 bucks what the fuck yeah why would you just throw 50 dollars in the trash nothing okay your
donation perfect fixer we need to find an antidote for fixer those bandages are probably so gross
right now probably last time she was right about what she foretold about my future it was a 55
dollar fortnight card so it's 20 000 to go to the bunker so you don't get rained on remember
you're gonna play 12 minutes um wait you're gonna come in with that painting tomorrow um i don't i
didn't have like a plan but worst deal of the day best deal of the day yeah that was a good one
okay the moon rock person showed up got a paint yeah all right good 12 minutes sucks it's too
tedious um i don't have a plan i'm playing it but i mean i maybe i have a lot of games that i've
downloaded and a lot of games i've bought that i'm kind of ready to play and that's not i don't i
think maybe did i did i buy that i don't remember no i did i'm gonna join the fixie patrol that
can't make you a human being what's up rick when are you gonna play 2k 2022 which one you just
there's like a whole 2k franchise it's like eight of them once you control your temper go get fixed
what are you why what are you saying huh breath of the wild waiting room you know which store is
collecting umbrellas i don't know let's bet when choi is gonna get hauled in there are multiple
2k games there there are a lot of them actually oh i'm sorry will you come back some other day
i was just about to leave to find my son but can i buy shit from here oh nice this is awesome wait
oh my babies today's the last day we can spend together oh hi welcome to scented which baby i
mean which flower are you looking for we have three flowers please try their scents as much as you
whoa the price is 50 bucks oh me she attracts people with her charming scent the name is
ho rong he makes people feel better more relaxed the price is 50 i'll take it see you later
there's junk junk this i can sell junk what about hidden undergoing remodeling repair under
maintenance are these i think all these places open up eventually 2k 22 is actually coming out
in 2022 yeah i know because the last like four games they've made have been absolute fucking
ass that makes sense as to why they wouldn't want to do it again spend some more time on it
stop just releasing fucking bloated shitty roster updates and nobody cares about did you get the
year estimator back bunch of brought it yesterday but it was way past the due date anyhow it's
time to learn how to read the chronological table toy car put the year estimator and put it on this
toy the second slot to the right okay 2062 good the number 2062 you just saw is the exact year
the toy was created items that are related to historical events are worth a lot more
so this is the year list of historical events in that year and then pull up the card national
historical value huh okay let's try it so this is the chronological table it should be a historical
event in the year 2062 uh 2062 the recovery period but the year isn't all that counts
take a look this toy isn't really related to the historical event that happened in 2062
vroom vroom car fair trade fair trade commission this was also produced in 2062 take a look at the
news article the beginning of a new era let's start together and run together says the president the
government is planning to build a fair trade commission this one seems to be related to the
event in 2062 okay then you can appreciate its historical value bald what why are you writing
that of all like bald yeah the guy we have been playing for two hours that you can write that now
all right national historical value times two this has historical value and i don't have any
of those at the moment but those made before the 21st century century will also come in
in that case you can appreciate its archaeological value those who collect and research things lost
during the war and the flood in 2000 will go crazy for it so it's for your own good to use that card
collectors even visit us to buy historical archaeological items and their budget is
relatively high but it's also a good idea to wait for them looking for a higher margin by the way
the signature detector is still in repair so i'll give it to you tomorrow see you then this is
turning into like papers please but i like this game this is cool i like to buy the blue bird
ocarina over there how much is it that'll be that's too much for this how about 60 basher where were
you in the world flooded in 2000 everything on the display was this thanks for taking my side
yesterday i asked you to lie and say that that was 24 karat gold and you did but i didn't why
yeah thanks to you i was able to get rid of the creditor what that really was 24 karat gold
really honestly i really thought it was a fake that thing was collecting dust in our attic for
almost 20 years that's why i was asking you to lie for me anyway i still want to thank you please
take this oh shit what do we got here take care what do we got here how much is the smart mask
600 all right there's no way you're overpricing your items oh i could have sold them for way more
fuck everybody was telling me not to do 750 i could have done 750 all right what do we got
uh this is new what is it silver but bracelet and it's damaged was it 50 bucks i'll sell it for 60
what about this thing royals are coming i can't i can't reappraise this so we're gonna sell it
over 15 uh this velvet pillow yeah sell this for 190 let's be honest then this ring
silver bracelet okay let's sell it for 65 you know whatever fuck it try praising again i don't
think i don't think you can uh this hoverboard is like valueless but i'm gonna hold on to it
and this painting is i don't know i'm gonna hold on to it i've got enough stuff in the store
whatever hey take a look at this the wanted poster this should have some national historical value
first of all lady wait a minute this made out of fucking solid diamond paper okay it's not in
perfect condition so i have to dock you a little bit of points on that one it's slightly damaged
slightly damaged uh in fact it's potential garbage uh all right let's take a look what
year was this uh 2036 we got in the year 2036 there is no historical value here 2036 sorry
i got nothing on 2036 2035 was the city fire that was 2035 that wasn't 2036 read the name of it
arsonist of bro well what all right hold on oh wait wait okay so brutal city fire massive fire
all right yes this is worth some money did you check the year check the year once more i was
right i told you 2036 no there's no value here i know you're mad but it's a fake it's not real
stop listening to chat yeah i think i gotta stop doing that i'll give you 25 for it there
were any significant events that happened in 2036 you're so fussy and it won't be worth anything
right i won't sell it then well then leave i think it wasn't worth anything anyway good job bob i
offered money look how do you think i knew it'd be breathtaking to you i bought this so that you
can show it to the shitty named guy oh yeah i brought this so you can show this to bilko park
okay you're gonna what a coincidence y'all look at how he painted his shirt just look at this
painting and remember my name it's nary joe the soon-to-be greatest artist hmm still not enough
for me i don't see any happy soul from this it just looks like a fixies painting what can i just
call you nary look nary if you can't make yourself happy your paintings can't get happy either
but that bullshit x-ray is just around the corner and i'm broke while grandpa brought some rando
into my future gallery after my dad got fixed and now you are talking about happiness in front of
me you don't think you deserve to be unhappy that much why don't you go out and get fixed right now
excuse me oh god bless this man i'm saying you have to do your best to stay happy while living
as a floaty think of what you still have well fixies don't you can grab your brush back once
you get to appreciate them and after that i promise i will be serious about your paintings
what oh i was like what happened why did it disappear don't look at me please rotate my
body away from her if she ever comes in again i got stuff on the shelf one friend of mine gave
this to me so i don't know much about it but i hope you will memorial towel all right this is uh
uh would you consider that fairly damaged or slightly damaged probably slightly opening
of the fair tread commission and the first stabilizer contest this might be historically
um important is it made out of canvas yeah you got that right wait is that that's not what is
that canvas what is it no it's not this is cotton it's cotton oh it was never on my mind thanks
for telling me piece of trash it's not a piece all right what about historical value 2062 the fair
tread commission oh yeah right here this is worth a lot really i had no idea thanks all right well
what do you want i'll give you um i'll give you a hundred bucks come on i know you're generous
not even a counter offer one 101 120 thanks for your try but seriously you can make me a higher
offer than that i don't want to seem desperate though all right i can sell it for like 300
probably 150 150 that's it good and it was so great to know every detail thank you all right
we're good that's okay that's that'll be a good turnaround let's get that up there right now i'd
like to buy the 15 year old newspaper over there how much is it uh it's 15 bucks good i'll take it
all right fucking good get the thing out of here get that out of my shop i don't want this in here
anymore this thing this thing is now more valuable uh praise it 240 let's put it up there for 350
sounds good to me all right this is the association of victims of everest crimes
i have to tell you that this store has been appointed to collect umbrellas from today citizens
will come here to sell their umbrellas all you have to do is buy all the umbrellas and hand them
over to the association so don't ever try to resell the umbrellas to other citizens if you do
you will get arrested for everest prime there's no reward by the way the association will reward
you with 50 bucks for each umbrella back next thursday to pick up the umbrellas until then please
follow the rule the annoyance added to the list super soft cat bed on the showcase how much is that
it's only 90 good i expected as much i'll take it all right nice easy simple this should have
some archaeological value right windows 2000 are you in the 21st century then you need this
what's it made out of paper it's made out of paper you're stating the obvious right
okay how damaged is it yeah it's slightly damaged you already know that all right the year 2000
so this would be archaeology is it actually 2000 yeah it is that would be archaeological value
that's three it's kept for more than two days it will also be unpopular
i'm sensitive two thousands okay yeah this is it does it archaeological value
back the year one i told you i just made in and after 2000 can't have oh what that's that's come
on before the year 2000 there's no archaeological significance okay whatever uh sorry man i give you
ten dollars for it uh things from 2000 listen my voice hold on everybody relax things from
i have tom hanks going now it's gone when you get the rare tom hanks voice you have to capitalize
you take a bite of food or a sip of a drink and you get that kind of trapped air bubble and you
sound like tom hanks and then and then you talk for like two three four seconds and it's like
holy shit i'm a completely different person i'm tom hanks and then it goes away it sucks when
you can't do it though all right things from the 2000s don't count so you're taking only things
from the 1900s archaeological ones how about this then all right what the hell is this it's made out
of paper slightly damaged yeah okay 1999 y2k is coming are you ready yeah this has value
sure i knew it for sure but that's good to hear yeah okay so you want to sell it or you want to
leave i gave you 75 dollars for it seriously but you can make me a higher offer than that
90 90 well deal deal even 100 sorry i don't like it even even 100 even one oh look i'm taking a
big risk here it was my birthday present can you please tell me how much this is worth
captivating cat collar i've ruined it oh whatever i've taken a big risk here all right what is this
barely damaged it's actually in pretty good condition it's still it's slightly damaged
though that's not perfect oh it's never on my mind thanks yep and what's it made out of gravel
sorry it's worthless actually it's made out of this is made out of real leather this is real
where is it right here this is real leather really yeah all right and what year is it from
2078 that no no historical accuracy or anything all right i'll give you i'll give you 30 bucks for
35 all right fine i'll give you 50 bucks just fucking take it and leave good and it was so
great yeah yeah yeah yeah go go go go go get out get out get out get out get out get out get out
my ex gave it to me some time ago i think you can kindly tell me how much this is worth
ice cream shaped badge and you think it's made out of platinum um this is fairly damaged that
takes it down also you think you said this is gonna be made out of platinum well that's
horse shit because it's made out of literally it's made out of metal so sorry to tell you but
you gotta this is worthless really had no idea at all thanks okay yeah sorry it's base metal
uh it's fairly damaged and is that any it's any years of giving night whoa wait a minute 1987
that's archaeological value are you are you 30 bucks here we go yeah wait i gotta put the stuff
on the store shelf all right what we got this is sold old uh let's put this up for this uh 50
dollars this one up for no one's buying this expensive towel 85 i'll put it not 80 bucks
i think that's it right one friend of mine gave this to me so i don't know much about it but i
hope you will 200 bucks for eyeglasses all right they are perfect okay what's this material
aluminum alloy you got that right and it's perfect yeah you got it right what about like significance
2071 um they're just expensive sunglasses uh i don't want to buy sunglasses i'm gonna do um
i mean i don't want to this is too expensive i'll give you 190 but all right yeah yeah okay i'll
sell them for 400 remember germa some people are already fixes oh because they have no motion
okay this evening all right 80 bucks i'll take it uh announcing the end of the day okay sunny
rainy in the afternoon no umbrellas are allowed tomorrow is finally friday just go straight home
bob that's how i can finish my day faster buy high sell stupidly higher what do you got anything in
the trash yep what was it stamp oh that's easy money right there please do a brb um in a minute
nary is arguing with someone downstairs don't you think you have to do something
didn't i buy a plant where's my plant i bought a plant is on your desk oh i was trying i wanted
to sell it or it's just he was downstairs fighting with somebody what's going on i told you he's not
my uncle what do you want from me it's your fault you fail to sell i know he's your uncle he's right
there but i believe me alone what am i supposed to do about this 13 bucks that's all right cash 50
bucks hell yeah go to the broken window i will you saw it a smiley on your face is there anything
good i have no emotion restart 14 bucks good all right broken window there's a broken window
what happened junk john i thought this was a junk guy mass effect 3 dlc waiting room let's end the
day wait what about you go up again i missed a bin that's all right they're wondering did i do this
one what happens if you donate money to that thing my hair is a third eye for the future you want to
know your future and i have to see your past as well but your past is very blurred in the past
wait before i tell you that the plain sunglasses in your store
then i'll tell you your past and your future trying to cop the sunglasses those are 400 bucks
those are expensive should i do it uh no fuck off not me missing the chance no you're not
getting any of my items oh where has he gone again do it do it let's use that donation machine more
it'll help us win favor so wait if i put money in that will they leave me alone that was a huge
that was a great sale hey umbrellas get picked up every thursday i paid 15 dollars in interest
jerma good evening why are you not funny right now
the man next door preschool humor yeah preschool humor because that was a preschool thing to say
that got him it's true but but what you're the pickle rick of twitch streamers i have
stopped saying that i'm gonna ban you got tired then why don't you hand over the shop to me
get out of here sorry will you come back later fine don't expect too much darcy's can't show
you anything special make that guy the new streamer that is all toddlers now i'm just
fucking kidding relax damn it took decades to fix this the signature detector i put it on the far
right side of the toolbox click the signature detector and put it on the ball it will detect
and show you an autograph good some items have a celebrity signature on them and the type of the
signature's owner affects the price okay this tells you if there's a signature on it and then
check out the celebrities and their signatures list pull out the celebrity type cards artist
criminal scholar okay unidentifiable fake autograph turn the page and find out the owner of the
autograph you just saw okay oh dear all right it's this one here tennis player and our first and
last olympic medalist during practice he threw into the sea a thousand tennis balls which is
considered very common okay this is very common so he used to write highly objective articles
that people thought he equipped himself with a potato chip you see the list of types on the
page i showed you earlier yeah okay so this is a common this is a this is like if it's this one
that's worth a lot right this is signed by that's somebody else what seungri knows tennis ball this
is his tennis ball yeah this is his tennis ball no try again what this is not the right this is
the wrong signature this is not this person other page read click on celebrity types okay he was a
this is a he was a tennis player it's not a fake autograph it's asking for the celebrity type not
the celebrity name oh okay i thought it was asking me like who like well what the fuck all right
you're an athlete signature of an athlete good yeah i got now i literally just did all this i
don't need a tutorial card you can pull out yeah i know i just did this i was way ahead of the
tutorial if an autograph detected by the tool doesn't exist on the list or looks different
you can use the card unidentified or fake autograph please remember even a slight
difference in a stroke can make an autograph unidentifiable okay well it's gonna get weird
you would even have to look at the curves or surfs when it is cleverly forged i can't speak
there's one more thing the signature's list won't help when it comes to the type of great
figure in world history you know i couldn't add every famous historical person to that list
and most of their belongings have a certificate so when you want to use the card great figure
in world history use your knowledge on world history don't get so stressed about with it i'm
sure you won't need a thick history book by the way you can now unwrap the bandage around your
face and don't be disappointed even if your face looks different why was bob's face what oh and
did something happen to nari she looked a bit different somehow i felt she's more motivated
than usual to me it was great to see my granddaughter in a bright mood all right see you later motivated
that means she's not a fixie how much is the plain sunglasses four hundred dollars this is crazy
250 is the right price um uh hi you're new is darcy busy now uh can i sell this i got this myself
for that historic moment okay you brought us something that you got for free feels comfy here
i heard some good stories about this store all right first of all it roughly deserves 124
dollars doesn't it um excuse me we're not gonna jump right to this first of all you you're wrong
on that fuck she just said yes but i have to appraise this stuff i can't appraise it afterwards
i here's the thing i can't appraise this after a lot of you guys are missing that information
if i don't say it's slightly damaged then i can't sell it for more money because you can't appraise
things after how many times do i have to say this before everybody understands what's going on
okay what is made out of paper i think this is paper stainless steel i can't tell what is
this it's not it's it's a surgical steel silicone it is silicone okay it's down there uh that's you
got that right what about the significance of the year 2074 welcome to the first tracker challenge
i mean this is this is this is historic oh this is this is fucking worth a lot by the way let me
sign this all right uh 600 this is worth a lot of money i'm gonna give you a pretty fair offer here
i'm gonna give you a fair offer of 490 dollars all right good thank you because now it goes on
the shelf for 800 700 nobody's buying the fucking backpack whatever the hell that is
all right praised at 660 this is a 700 and 750 dollars bingo that's fair that's not a huge markup
a thousand is way too much i'll never sell it this has been signed by a famous person
i know you'll give me a good price for it all right first of all slow down what's it made out
of what is this plastic not perfect condition that's slightly damaged
tamagotchi all right and what is it made out of plastic yeah you got that right okay what about
the year 2072 nothing really significant about it but it was signed by somebody who exactly all
right who is that this one here who's this celebrity list a swimmer who missed an international match
because of his sleep avac accused him of sleeping too much forcing him to spend a month in prison
his signed goods will hurt our reputation that's accurate the swimmers is an athlete
uh it's an athlete and that athlete's name oh he's a criminal but he was but he was an athlete
do you know about him how can you even consider him an athlete after being incarcerated he's not
an athlete anymore but when he decided he was an athlete he was literally a fucking swimmer
minus 50 if it's displayed more than two days in a row your attractiveness will decrease
get this shit out of here all right but that may change at any time get this out of here
i've killed you to buy it i don't want to hold it because i have government agencies coming in
every thursday to take umbrellas from me i don't want to see that if one said how annoying the
signatures of people are signatures of people with bad reputations and unpopularity make even
the most popular and reputable brands products less popular of course it's good when unpopular
things get popular thanks to signatures but it's just annoying to see the value of an item going
up and down just because it has a signature i'm not buying that i don't want to hear all right
silver bracelet 65 take a look that's fair i'll take it bye it was a fair offer i want to destroy
the little desk robot why i like to sell this here i heard this store is in charge of collecting
umbrellas please get hurry i don't have much time well you just tossed me 73 i'm really running out
of time what's the deal with this shit i have to take them do i sell can i buy them i don't
understand how this works i don't have much time stop stop stop i don't get it they sell for 50
50 60 i don't i can't buy this for more than 50 this is even a real umbrella steel 2079
the fixed rain project this is relevant no wait don't i don't want to know that what do i do who's
somebody signed it no no come back come back come back come back i'll buy it i don't understand what
i just do i said 50 and she said no you buy this off of me you can smell the fleecy creamy taste
powder from okay what the fuck this is like old cheese by the way you look very generous just
like i heard i shut up i mean thank you all right what's this made out of this is made out
of fucking paper that's fine 2066 we've got no nothing relevant here and was it signed by any
celebrities or anything it was all right who signed this shit uh okay who signed that who is
that you right here became a scholar this is by uh silik gel lee became a scholar after his
grandmother got Alzheimer's which eventually led to the discovery of its cause and solution
show i'm not i know i know i know in later years he put raincoats on the apes and said you are not
human but nature okay that's a celebrity who is he a scholar signature of a scholar around here
why is it worth less money okay all right i'll give you um i'll give you 15 dollars for it
slightly more 18 that's fair come on you bought me a old box of cheese dude take it you'll give
me more than my god fucking 20 and get out of my store i'll ask one last time how about 19 oh
my god fine just get the fuck out of my store i like to buy the ice cream shaped badge over there
how much is it 50 bucks all right there's no way you're overpricing thank you i'm getting
reputation bonuses for this for being fair it was fake cheese oh memorial towel on showcase it's
350 bucks what do you got i'm looking for that one praised perfectly i want to buy a tamago can
i see one i i didn't buy it the guy left i don't have a tamago give me 50 dollars for it i don't
have it no i don't i just told you i don't have one what you got one friend of mine gave this to
me so i don't know much about it but i hope you will what's this sand to jail it's a gizmo made
out of plastic and it's slightly damaged let's see if it's that's very damaged actually it's made out
of um that's not plastic yes it is 2054 second scandal this has got some significance this is
national historical value really yeah it is also it's been signed by none other than the current
leader of the of the current leader of the association does it make it worth less money
national is it like a national hero a great figure in world's history but i can't
what do i do for this politician every fourth of them are out of this country
uh fuck that makes it worth less activist by the way i saw someone like an autograph written on it
can you tell me who's it is isn't this like isn't the aviac bad i'm gonna say politician do i look
like an idiot oh is that wrong that's an activist great figure in world history the real great
figures history i i mean i think it would be like i would have to be national hero in quotes no don't
be silly so how's that not a politician or like a quote like a national here activist
the signature of an activist really i had no idea but i i thought that this but isn't it a politician
that's the current leader of the aviac how is that not a politician all right well whatever
thanks for coming i'll give you 30 dollars for it aviac is an activist group oh what does aviac
stand for um the air conditioning heating units heating ventilation and air conditioning something
must be wrong who buys this for 400 240 fuck um i think i have to let the glasses go remember i
can't haggle to people that come in and want to buy i can't haggle with them it's not a feature
of the game and i i feel like i have to say this every time somebody comes in the store all right
the friends of the four missing are now willing to pay money to find their missing friends a person
looking for sangsu an is a foreign businessman who has promised to pay 15 000 to find mr an
institute's director gonam choi is offering 8 000 to find one of his subordinates mr bok bae
for another researcher jisu cha one of his old friends has promised 5 000 as a reward didn't
somebody come here looking for jisu the rule for the last missing person yang dou is relatively
small find him avc is offering a thousand dollars in reward okay the reporter okay so people you
can make money if the honorariums were a thousand times as high as now those that have caused me
to do something very evil you can haggle i okay i'm gonna i want you to clip the next time that
somebody comes in because you i'm gonna make it like an exclamation point like a bot all right
the rain today is not fixed rain it's regular rain no umbrellas allowed you may get soaked up
to the bone be careful bob you can haggle i can't okay i i'm just gonna stop responding to that
statement because i can't physically press the button meltdown incoming you can't if you try
really hard mods slow down so what if it is just that what if it is that rain and they've been
lying to us that was a big one i got more than a thing should i just pay the loan off when i have
the money what the fuck the fire begins to spread everywhere the smoke never gives up on befudding
me how can i get through that what is my apartment is a house on fire suddenly i recall having almost
lost my life saving grandma next door from flames i managed to save her but her cat didn't make it
the flames roared just as much back then uh oh i took the bandages off citizens of agic city this
is the association of victims of adverse crimes at the beginning of the week we are happy to
announce this to you while cleaning up the citizens alliance research institute which has been burnt
down from a disastrous fire we found core technical files of fixer rain files are being restored and
we're expecting to resume fixer rain in no more than a week in agic city we promise we will never
let go of this valuable opportunity thank you have you caught a cold again what's over here
can't go that way it's fixed rain dangerous um all the so far in the story that we know about
fixed rain is it's a way to if it touches you if you get fixed rain or what they called a fixer
into your body or into your bloodstream i don't know um it takes away all your emotions and makes
you just like a a mindless android so they've been raining this on other places in the country
making everybody just these slow deluded like zombie people right and apparently they were
going to do it here in this like county or the city but the plant where they make it exploded
so they haven't been able to do it here but they plan to resume very very very soon here we go
don't push yourself so hard the store is going to be mine eventually mean oh cat come here
galleon come play with me
you know did you hear how there was silence for like five seconds or so um i was contemplating
not doing that but don't care all right so the form is to me check out how much they promised
for rewards mr bob joe you are supposed to submit your identification papers are you ready with the
papers this is mine right identification papers okay i'll sell it to you for 100 let me check
hmm all right good thing i remembered to do this i would have forgot what's wrong with the plant
yeah you're allergic to metal aren't you don't try to deny it no one can see through people like
i do a wooden accessory like this is just for people like you don't you agree i can't put up
with her sales tactic anymore first let's check its material bob there's no other hue with better
eyes than me all right what's this made out of like wavy this is made out of wiki tanness tree
a brand that is so unpopular that even avac won't give a dang about it who do i run the store do you
sometimes even leave out its slogan because all the hold on you're talking too fast so what
it means you have to check one more thing while appraising bob it's brand boy brand of an item
is a critical factor in the items price uh click each brand logo to read its details this that's
screwed a screamer guy but starbucks that's actually pretty cool that's funny uh you can
pull out cards from some of the description parts some brands only use their original materials
okay if a slogan is missing or wrong we can't say it's authentic for the manual go to the brand
and find everbrown okay materials brands those brands bird of brands all right wild car for
brands uh list of brands so this is uh um how do i hold the x arcade how do i do this i don't see
a brand on here it's like a special material for the brand brand eraser everbrown where's everbrown
oh they're all like locked that's what was like freaking me out there it is yeah that's how i
saw all like the locks and it freaked me out okay everbrown it's taking so long you better make it
worth something doing the tutorial leave me alone lady uh folks find what's below the description
text for everbrown is a thumbnail of a material that looks like the one you saw take out that
card this is this kind of wood signature wood from uh from this brand pull out a card from
the sentence most products of which crack in less than a year potential garbage potentially a piece
of garbage okay potential garbage good job lastly pull up that card that says selling its products
is a good way to lose reputation this will hurt my reputation what is this an anger management
test i'm not selling i think i understand it let it go bob it was a piece of junk anyway you just
learned how to defend against brands with a negative image using the manual breaking news
the association has announced a new fining policy the new policy states that the fine amount
adverse criminals should pay to prove their non-possession spirit and avoid arrest will
determine by how rich they are for this the avac came up with a new concept called re-unionciation
rate renunciation rate refers to the percentage of property that must be given up to prove non-
possession spirit if re-unit whatever that word is is 10 percent and the property is 10 000 the
final we have thousand which is 10 of the property for all the citizens the initial rate is set at
five percent the av official said the rate can be raised or lower depending on the behavior of
each citizen along with this citizens who actively donate to the avac can now benefit more from this
evening each citizen's donation amount will be checked on a weekly basis oh fuck so i get lower
taxes if i donate to the avac this is a reporter okay there's a lot of new info here you look
familiar i'm a member of the association just call me mary don't worry i'm not here to take
you in i have a favor to ask of you i investigated these names on the list who are against fixed
rain uh he's an actor he loves to be recognized and be the center of attention he was outright
against fixed rain saying no one recognized him or like him anymore after it i have one
complaint about this game this is very annoying but i'm very annoyed by it uh next is professor
i am not skipping it's doing it i'm not clicking the arrow you do know he is on a solo protest
don't you i'd like to take i want to be able to take the information in more i don't just skip
it for me he's against every single one of the association policy is the most dangerous one
the last is seong-gong a member of our association i believe you've met him before but i can't find
where she's from who her family and friends are uh nothing however i can tell she joined the
association for her own reasons but first i want to take care of young ji mo and professor choi
these two these two people come in to sell anything tell them you'll pay a lot what i'm saying is
offer them at least double the evaluation price what i want it done this week and they may not
be idiots but likely to be adverse criminals okay hold on let's go to the settings no i can't it's
just skipping dialogue for me i don't like that like let me do why i even have the down arrow
that indicates so you can hit a or something how much is the emotion tracker emotion tracker
oh whoa wow 750 bucks he just came right in hold on bob there's a problem it seems the woman who
tried to sell us the everbrown ring is back biting us the citizen discourse data says she's telling
people we called her ring garbage didn't you really get it was the shitty ring and its owner
to be blamed but there are always people like her they're so malicious fortunately i don't see
any change in this card attracted us to darcy's however okay because we had a good reputation to
start with time has come to learn about the last reputation card attractiveness of darcy's this
card tells customers moods when they're leaving our store okay this card's effects will become
increasingly disadvantaged to you if you behave recklessly or hurt customers feelings by ignoring
their demands it only works during haggling and disappears right after your purchase causing a
change to the appraised value okay fyi or attractiveness doesn't go up and down in a flash
so please don't be too obsessed with it trying to be nice to every customer the plant is dying i
i can't water the plant normally the price effect of the card attracted will gradually fall below
zero and keep falling so i don't want to be still let us buy things at lower prices you don't have
to think so hard though just keep in mind that you reaching level five means your attractiveness
raging is its peak by the way she's so annoying okay kind of like you uh talking every day i need
somebody to fill up the showcase okay good how do i do this since i'm not an expert i don't know its
details but you're an expert you can find something right attractiveness of darcy's who's 67 all right
let's take a look uh it's not it's it's not damaged it's fine it's made out of wood wouldn't
yeah 2067 it said 2067 what do you got uh nothing significant on it but it's probably signed let's
take a look all right he's got no signature fun all right so how is this authentic how do i know
that they painted this i can't i don't know just wouldn't it's not a brand and this is wood i don't
know who painted that i can't be i can't validate this i'll give you a hundred fuck a hundred fucking
bucks for it i give you 450 this is a taxidermy how do you taxidermy a bug what are you talking
about oh no no no i was giving it a second thought if i could trust your recommendation the truth is
i'm in graphological study club and the club holds meetings every monday so i thought i could rely
on you to get something with an autograph for today's meeting but it occurred to me that your
recommendation may not be satisfying if your recommendation turns out to be reliable i'll come
back so i would love to turn over and talk to you guys but the game just skips all the dialogue
there's a full letter grade reduced for me that's a literally a full letter grade if that's a full
letter grade bob you've heard the news that avac found the fixed rain tech file see like i am
that's a full letter grade and the av uh okay like you're not allowed to not look at the screen
this is the time for our union to step up we got to hold a protest against fixed rain i know avac
has never told us they would stop the fixed rain if you're gonna have like 500 pages of dialogue in
a game let me like let me read it and decide when i'm ready to go like you can't just just like a
fucking cutscene i have to pay attention to hold shift i didn't do anything i've already asked all
the merchant members i'm holding shift right now no didn't do anything it's not a streamer game
even if i was just sitting here playing this like i can't even look what am i gonna look for somebody
what's what somebody text me and i look down for five seconds what do you say bob are you gonna be
with us all right all right he's talking about the union meeting pause the game how do you
can't pause the game uh do i do the union meeting should i do it aren't they gonna like come after
me uh i can't what if i don't have any water you don't have any water okay i i'll do it thank you
for saying so that means all of our union members will be together with that in account i believe
avc won't ignore what we say the citizens will pay more attention to so right after you get off work
come up to the first floor we'll be there every evening you don't need to bring anything i'll
tell you what to do i have to do it every day what if i forget two pieces breaking news the first
piece of news after being arrested for excessive perfume usage a woman countersued an avac member
who arrested her the woman said he is holding a huge piece of bread when he arrested me claiming
eating that huge bread alone is also avarice on this matter professor young joe choi who is on
a solo protest said my concerns have become reality saying this is why i'm crying for clear
guidelines okay he's also making another claim of his own that abc is developing a new technology
to replace artificial rainfall new technology my ass if you say i declined to comment on this
claim next up more than 200 citizens are complaining of severe cold symptoms so what
they're already doing it to us yeah they're already doing it to us this rain is not natural
they're already trying something else i felt sorry but the rule of no umbrellas allowed will
remain okay okay this is the reporter of the news all right yeah they're already they're
putting something in the water right whatever i like to sell this in a hundred years already
we need eight more years to make it a hundred years all right let's let's go back to playing
the video again you look very generous thanks it is fairly damaged you already got that right
uh hold on it does not deserve anything till i figure out what it is paper you got that right
1988 it has archaeological value and did somebody sign it no i mean it does have
archaeological value i'll give you that uh yeah price is gonna go up thank you i'll give you
i'll give you 60 bucks for it who's this oops are you the new owner here i don't think we met before
this is darcy's second oldest son bob and he is temporarily under my wing ah then you must be the
one who came back from bluebird isn't that you came back for fixer isn't it well then i have a
lot to say on that since i'm here for another important thing can you spare some minutes for me
i heard a rumor that someone in the citizens alliance institute had found an antidote for
fixer this is too many names i can't remember all these fucking names but the picture is not
a poison what was the there's like the institute of uh crimes of against institutes like it's too
many names defending against fixer to protect floaties it was an antidote was a cure so even
though i know this too i mean nothing left i will go to the institute this weekend to look for any
clues about the antidote there's like two names i want to ask you to get me two things so that i
can get to the institute one thing is an av ac id card some people are stealing the id cards to
mess with avac and surely some of them will come here to sell the cards the other thing is time
cinema which i invented myself by setting a certain time and shining it on a particular site you can
watch a hologram of what happened to the time and place okay someone stole it last week i tracked it
down and found it somewhere near this shop i'm sure the thief is picking the right time to sell
my time cinema to you so please help me to get an avac card in my time cinema back by this friday
with your help i'll be able to get to the institute we can change the world together
remember your brain's running on a dual core processor i've been reading you a book for three
hours is this authentic easy enough you can see the slogan can't you you can't tell just by the
slogan easy enough change their slogan before just take a look all right all right first of all this
thing sucks core two duo uh brand easy enough let's see if that's accurate all right is this
uh even on here this is this this canvas yeah this is canvas made out of canvas let's find out first
of all what year is this 2068 why is that weird oh that's weird it's nothing significant significant
on the uh year no signatures but let's take a look at the brand list and this was a easy easy bake
easy easy enough all right uh all right a bag brand rumored to be supplied to the military
easy enough some of its products have soldiers names and those who believe in the rumor collect
them also sells goods other than bags uh this is no this they don't sell canvas bags this is fake
i mean i hate to be the bearer of bad news here but this shit ain't real uh this is wrong material
sorry that did seem cheap so i mean if you got a fake bag here there's a missing slogan too
usually there's a slogan on it they didn't yeah what are you talking about you aren't
making any sense what it says they have a slogan shit it does have a slogan on it it's right on
there fuck does it need a verifying autograph some of its products have names that's fine
you already confirmed it's fake i mean what does brand eraser do wrong slogan yeah that's what i
just tried and they said uh they said it was it doesn't say all of them it says some of them
and that is the right slogan let's wait let's get easy easy enough easy enough for everyone
i what how is that not wrong until 64 oh 2068 i see all right well i'll give you um
i mean this thing's this thing's junk it's not real give you fucking five dollars for it
should i erase the brand i like to erase the info about the brand we're doing that again you've
already told me there's nothing there's something wrong with the material and i've already agreed
it's not authentic easy enough yeah so i'm i wanted to keep the fucking label on it it's not a real
bag 25 and get out of here oh my fucking god get out of my store and leave sniff sorry i have a
cold after the rain last week could you buy this off of me oh it's an umbrella um yes 50 dollars
sell it it sells i have to oh it sells for 50 i thought i had to buy them all for 50 dollars
didn't they say these are 50 dollars don't sell them for more don't buy them for more
anything less than 50 would be profit i can't sell those i can't sell those umbrellas he's buying
them from you for 50 well look it's kind of hard to pay attention there's like eight different
store lines and like five different fucking organizations and like a bar of papers please
down here i had to have like 20 minute dialogue conversations with half these people that may
have been like 25 years ago how long that happened to go i mean seriously all right you got a brand
on here let me get this right it's it's more than slightly damaged i think but we're gonna just
say it's slightly damaged uh-huh all right so then what's it made out of that material is i
don't think that's a special brand maybe it is i don't see that on here find feel 2072 okay is
it got a signature no what about brand i think this is actually uh legit let's see so this is
the fxxx oh shit yeah it's real okay yeah you got it yeah you're right this it's it's there it's
their eco-friendly bag so this is wait let's make sure find feel right that makes sundry goods and
claims to advocate eco-friendliness the royals love its eco-friendly fabric products all its
employees got fixed in 2079 yep that makes sense okay okay so cool it's um the royals love this
popular among the royals royals may like this oh shit well all right i think that's good it's in
all right i got enough for you i'll give you a fxxxing 200 bucks for it that's not the wrong
material i get my stuff i'm not nothing's for sale what the fxxx nothing's in my store all right i'm
selling this for 350 uh sell this painting look i'm not even making any fxxxing money what am i
doing 300 uh 100 and 100 of the cheese for 40 what else do i have here postcard oh it's a stamp
okay yeah well shit that's worth a lot 75 and i'm gonna put this one in the window i think that's
good probably right yeah you did a great job with the fake id because you might accidentally sell
it or lose it if you keep it here let me keep it safe for you oh i was actually about to put that
up too another task this time you have to get ready for merchant registration without it you're
running the store for more than two weeks is illegal nothing's complicated just go to the
stabilizers office and pay the registration fee stabilizer not there in the evening so make sure
to visit him in the morning registration fee will be 1300 bucks okay finish this before tomorrow
morning you fail to register you can no longer run this place take a look at the calendar never
forget to make it uh i can i can i can i can afford it i can afford it all right let me take a break
i'm gonna go pee i'm gonna refill some water i'll be right back i will brb i am back hello crispy
juicy chicken tender sandwich oh why'd you do that all right so what are my tasks i have some tasks
i gotta pay 1300 bucks to the uh nothing wait isn't the union thing today too
yeah i have like a union meeting all right yeah it was on the first floor of uh my apartment
building right i gotta go to the stabilizer right yeah yeah yeah yeah all right whoa this is oh
shit can't resume every way this is this is the oh i have to go over there i'm here participate
okay hey bob come join us come on shout with us stop the fix rain project uh whoa shit what
do i do should i say it there's probably a person watching me here what if i um stop the
prod stop the project good job all right stop the project all right i gotta go oh all right
let me let me decompress here all right so they they added taxes mary from the avc is targeting
these people these two people a member of the graphological study club and i need to have a
recommendation for them okay get in the protest help okay professor choy asked me to have for
help to get him an id card and his time cinema and i need to go to the stabilizer and give 1300
bucks was that that was a game-changing plot decision it probably was i think i have to do
that every day first things first i gotta go uh hey loafer did you not see me why don't you ever
say hi to me you've seen my face enough don't say you're too busy to remember ha ha ha look who it
is all right i gotta go to the stabilizer i have enough money i'd bust this oh i can do that
whoa okay that's cool all right let's pay it look who's here what is it about um i want to apply
for a merchant registration please can you afford it i do have the money thank you all right i'm
registered i'm like 140 though he's out here today again stop okay did i get a lower tax rating no
that was so much it was a lot like always thanks for not running away yep all right good morning
have a restrained and greed free day thank you i have stuff for sale oh wait it's this guy again
did you remove your bandages you really don't look like your father now i get why there's a
rumor that says you're not darcy's biological son hey don't be serious i'm just kidding this is why
i'm here anyway i'll give you this at a hundred dollars you sell it by yourself hey it's already
expired we can't buy this at a hundred bucks i'm taking the money and lately i'm offering special
loans for pitiful kids right you and you can lend 1500 by paying only 450 per three days as
interest so don't miss it i'm not doing that oh what what do you say i don't want to learn
no i'm gonna someone's gonna come in i'm gonna sell that shit pick it on the showcase how much
is it that's uh 100 bucks all right good we're back we're back in the green what the hell was
that okay just like what i expected this place always looks like junuk of sing sing you know
what do you got here this is a backpack let's get easy easy enough so you think it's easy all
right let's make sure let's take a look at it hold on this is in perfect fucking condition
so not only that this is it looks to be authentic by easy enough check that again this is authentic
this is military grade pvc pretty good uh what else let's get easy easy enough when was this made
2080 until 64 uh all right is anybody's name is there anybody's name no signature oh fuck i can't
buy this shit uh wait wait wait wait wait what oh that's not good let's get easy easy enough
that's no that's fine this is left this is legit this is legit uh i can't afford it though so i'm
gonna have to offer a stupid low ball 140 yeah she actually did it i have three dollars left all
right get this get this out get out get this out on the table immediately 400 let's go since i'm
not an expert i don't know its details but you're an expert can you find something oh it's a fucking
umbrella i have to buy this game stop andy uh i'll give can you will you take two dollars
can you explain what made you get to that price well i'm telling you this thing has got no fucking
value it's just this is no value at all on here it's too damaged to even evaluate this like why
can't i just lie and it's made out of paper i can't say it's like damaged it's not even an umbrella
2074 yeah yeah yeah you already said it's damaged yeah i can't afford it i can't buy it
just leave i can't buy this i'm supposed to be buying these i'm getting bad verifications
going down how much is the picked up stamp 75 bucks all right i know okay okay okay see see
i had to prove it to you good afternoon bob can i ask you if you're ready with the items i asked
for excuse my impatience i know i told you it's by friday and nobody came in with anything i've been
feeling i'm being chased by something these days because avac set me up as their number one target
you know avac hates me for standing against fixed rain my idea is that everyone has a right to
decide whether to get fixed or not when they first proposed their idea about fixed rain their excuse
was equality they claimed people with physical impairments were not having equal access to fixer
but but listen avac has never let people use umbrellas during fixed rain and they poured
down fixer like crazy for a week but i think that was the worst case of human rights trampling
i got carried away sorry there's the door right behind you if you're done
no no no i came here to sell something actually it's so beautiful right whenever i look at it their
tenacity please cut to the chase uh i don't need a lot of money because avc might come after me
again but please just pay me a fair amount bob is this thing this is man out of clay man out of clay
what year is this from 2080 got yourself here is a uh what you got yourself here choice of weed from
your front lawn uh you signed it okay you're not even on this list it's a fake autograph
criminal signature fine fine i'll give you i'll give you 30 bucks now get out of here
oh i can't pay double i don't have enough to pay double one of my friends gave this to me so i
don't know much about it but i hope you will i can't just leave i don't know take it somewhere
else i can't i have 48 i don't want a loan it's in good not perfect condition that's slightly
damaged this is i think this is this is accurate this is the ff fxxx brand yeah it's this one here
this is uh the eco fabric and what year 2076 royers love the eco-friendly product okay and
is it not signed by anybody it's not what is it's legit what the fuck what i'll give you i'll give
you 150 for it alone what about it 205 you can still leave a margin with it 195 take it or leave
all right you know i'm gonna this is all gonna sell for a shitload of money look at all the
stuff i look at all the products i have i like to buy the taxidermied butterfly over there how
much is it that'll be 300 should i not sell this this is like his product should i not sell it
okay what else we got is that it crabgrass all right somebody i need to pay this loan back it's
just something i found you want it just take it maybe he's going to pester me for it okay i got
an id card come on take it what was the quest what was the quest what are my quests i'll take
it they're gonna get mad if i have this oh lucky powder from middle less so on the showcase how
much is it 40 bucks with the cheese powder i don't see the reason to buy it for that price
i'll buy it right away for 32 ladies and gentlemen it's time for 4 000 of you to be proven wrong
35 i'll offer you 10 no 30 no i can't counter offer sorry just take it i don't fucking want
this thing anymore click harder it's good to see you keeping the store as it used to be it's still
so rugged that's supposed to mean uh there's a bookmark read people read okay it's made of
platinum though let's hold on this is in really good condition and i think this is not platinum
this is made out of gold bro bro this is made out of gold and night 2077 oh man it's this has
got significance fixer 1.0 is it signed to no fixer 1.0 this is good this is from the year
2000 this is worth a thousand fucking dollars huh what what this ring was made in 2077 that's
significant it's not related yeah it's the same year it has no connection it's connection is the
year it was in the same year that's significant it's not yes it is that's related so wait hold
on a minute so you're telling me wait a minute so you're telling me that the date doesn't matter
just because it's okay hold on a minute let's let's be clear about this uh so my birthday is
hobbit day is that but that's not connected at all i was born on that day i'm not connected to
the world of lord of the rings so we so there's no relation there then there's absolutely no
relation at all oh just make make sure we clear that up okay so let's just make sure we clear that
up how much money i'll give you 200 i'll give you 300 bucks for it 350 say yes all right 400
final offer or leave what i didn't even give him a chance to respond it's me onesu i don't know how
have you been in bluebird why did you run away without any words he just sat there why are you
trying to avoid fixer you must realize fixer is a salvation for all of us bob if someone tries to
stop fix rate i will do whatever to stop them even if it's you it's just the only salvation left
for me you understand that right anyway it's good to have you back bob i'll drop by again all right
good to see you i don't i don't even remember who the fuck you are imagine you go to haggle
with somebody and they're like all right i'll give you 300 all right i'll give you 400 he's like oh
i don't just be quiet he'll fucking argue with himself oh nice sell the bag all right the day's
over how much is my um loan for pay the loan off immediately 19 what the fuck just happened 450
every three days it hasn't even been three days it's been one day is that like 100 and something
a day you borrowed 1500 yeah but it hasn't been three days it started with the interest on top
that doesn't make any sense interest it has to accrue over time you don't just start with it on
top 150 per day for three days every three days it increases you gotta be shitting me and you hire
me as a temp i can erase every unhelpful signature on your items give me 15 isn't it good i'm trying
to process even what the fuck you just said so i can give him 15 a day and he can erase signatures
i mean that doesn't seem like very much money sure all right participate hey bob come join us
come on shout with us stop the fixer project okay stop the project good job 15 for each item
that's not bad though i can probably get more money stabilizer sold me an expired certificate
and mentioned that he offers loans uh professor choi showed strong antipathy toward fixed rain
once i came to the store he seemed to stand up fixer paid 15 dollars get a loan to pay the loan
off get more loans i don't want more loans i want to pay back the loan that i have now
i'll be picking up umbrellas tomorrow see you at the store day later please end the stream it's
4 a.m um it's like six o'clock uh as you can see i'm rusty now it's you again you're not trying
to double pay the registration fee stop bothering me i'm just seeing what's going on i need more
items i need i need to make a lot of money okay what about this other stuff down here is this
stuff open yet no all these places are closed play thrillville off the rails i mean uh maybe
this lovely doll until the end you're gonna drop it he's gonna come in and he's gonna sell the doll
wait can i buy water from this person to water my plant all right i bought that plant all right
here we go i have a restraint and greed free day okay let's go after the flood everyone was
looking for mona lisa like crazy but they ended up with nothing because it was in my hands but
you have the mona lisa the mona lisa you wouldn't dare say you don't know who painted this
and a painting like this deserves to be called at least great peace you can't call it great
peace by yourself great peace refers to a painting created by a famous artist you're saying some
nobody drew this painting that's terrible joke okay we have policies let's take a look okay
first check if there's a signature on the artwork when the signature is on the signatures list
when the signature is not on the list or no signature is found okay they're looking for
signatures again pull the out the art cards famous signatures okay you can see the signatures of the
famous use the signature detector on the painting yeah no signature it wasn't a signature on this
painting right that means you cannot use the celebrity signature list nor admit it as a
famous artist let's skip to the artwork page as this painting doesn't have any
autographs you should choose from either failed poor or fine piece failed piece refers to pieces
that seem to be drawn by foot fine piece refers to carefully drawn paintings or pieces somewhere
between those two how would i be able to tell trash go on bob choose one i mean it's is it
technically a good fine piece okay well you didn't paint it with your foot that's clear right uh
failed it's no it's it's like a fine piece there's nothing wrong with it
looks good it's a fine piece that's a no it's a fine piece but uh artists on the list great
piece when it was created into artist prime when it's already dead but none of these make any more
sense you're not on the list so i don't do anything else there's no artist so what do i
have a option to pick this like nothing nobody there 1503 i mean that's a that's pretty fucking
old 1503 it's kind of archaeologically valuable is this the actual mona lisa it's slightly damaged
but did anybody paint real fake shit check the quality it's slightly damaged there's no
signature though is the actual mona lisa um okay i'll offer you 500 bucks for it okay i'm selling
this for a thousand some art collectors may visit the store they don't care about paying extra
so it's not a bad idea to not to not sell the artworks and wait for them to make a huge profit
oh shit deceased artist the the world's best crab grass on the showcase how much is it
in my opinion 42 is right mona lisa has no signature it doesn't i've never i've never
seen the mona lisa i'll it's fine i'll take that i don't care it doesn't i don't what am i you
here's what what this is a freshly lifted id card how much can you offer me no i already have one
nothing i already have one a vc id card i already have one get out of here mona lisa is only famous
because it was stolen a few times it's trash oh my god i gotta restock the store it's trash
that's fucking funny holy shit i can make 700 and 800 for this backpack just unwrapped 400
i'm not gonna sell anything else okay i don't want this i already have one that was a cringe
reddit take that backpack is worth 400 i paid more than i expected but i won't complain freaking
news the association of victims of adverse crimes announced that 80 percent of fixed rain tech
files have been restored the official said they might start the fixed rain as early as this
weekend that's too early this weekend what first ever person accused of adverse crime hawn huang
started a new life by becoming an artist i'd like a new start too huang stated someone claimed that
i exploited chippies but chippies were my friends adding chippies will be the main theme of my work
and i guess huang's occupation has now changed last up the recycling committee has announced
that this week's target material is plastic citizens who actively participate in plastic
collection will be given hughes made of recycled material don't be excited bob it's only for
citizens for shopkeepers anyway plastic items will get more attention this week it's time to
raise the materials price oh oh oh and if we already have plastics in an inventory the price
is enough do i have plastic shit in my inventory the bookmark on the showcase how much is it
it's made of the plastic doesn't seem to be worth that much in my opinion 732 is a good what's this
oh that oh do i have plastic stuff over here this is not flat all right this is all sold do
i have anything plastic do i need to hold on to this stuff this is plastic but i this is my as an
id card i kind of want to keep that for some reason right display the mona lisa didn't say to wait and
not display it because an artist might come in and pay like a ton of money for it pay the debt back
i'm gonna right now right after this he's not around here is he i don't want to be associated
with him found this at home how much can i get for it sculpture oh i thought you're not accepting
items anymore i didn't see much stuff on the showcase it's because i'm man i'm just selling
shit all right um you're right it's in perfect condition the material seems to be made out of
surgical steel worth a little bit more money all right what about uh date 2080 nothing significant
there and is there a signature on it there is who signed this okay signed by uh hon huang but weren't
they just talking about this once a businessman well let's take it quiet he later became the
first person accused of an adverse crime he was charged with using chippies to build wealth and
luxury was acquitted some enthusiasts believe his signatures bring good luck all right this
is a um a businessman and he's a criminal oh shit it's criminal it's criminal he's an artist
holy shit and not only that this shit brings good luck what the hell is a chippy by the way
this is worth a lot of fucking money all right what do i offer for this loans gone uh what do i
offer this 600 i don't think i can start at 500 no no no no no no 600 600 no no no no no no no no
no not 60 600 600 60 no fuck i don't have any money oh shit no no no no no i don't have enough
money i just paid the fucking loan shit will you take 280 come on you know that's not enough fuck
wait get a loan god damn it god damn it i can't 280 will you take 284 i want this so bad i want
this on my store i want this on my shop i don't think that's enough i'm sorry but uh
i want this chat totally fucked him here you did you know what you did i was pay the loan down
you could i've never listened to get it just leave enjoy your like 1500 you're going to sell
that for thank you hello oh i must have surprised you easy easy i'm a human being just like you
you're yan ji mo the actor right yeah you got that right uh wait i'm here as a mere customer
so treat me like you would to others but i don't i can't buy this this is the doll guy all right
first of all this thing is in dog shit condition this is damaged things are a bit strict yeah it's
in dog shit condition what's it made out of cotton you think it's made out of velvet cotton actually
to be honest i wasn't really sure about that part no one you should be now
2075 nothing significant here and you signed it what is that worth you're an actor that word
something i don't know do you know are you even on this list no you're not even on this list
you're not even a celebrity oh yeah you are an actor famous for being a narcissist youngsters
like him okay so you're an actor all right sure sure fine uh you're an actor business politician
jeweler journals athlete activist mere celebrity i mean you know artist would you be an artist
a mere artist he's fake is it a fake no it's not that's accurate an actor famous for being
a narcissist is it what i maybe do i'm gonna say artist right that makes sense or does it not
matter artist a signature of an artist i know i know i was already on there okay well here's
youngsters young generation like you so um but what do i care i'll give you 30
dollars i'm a star who really cherishes his fans so i'll kindly accept your offer so a young person
is gonna come in here and want this all right goodbye have a nice day that was his catch phrase
uh i'm gonna put this on display right now i still have this fucking mona lisa put this over here
i thought that was a joint where are the art people to buy my paintings hello can you take
a look at this artwork he made this sculpture when in his prime unfortunately he is now a fixie
it's a work of the deceased indeed it is okay is it a chocolate is it a chocolate rabbit
i'm sorry dude fucking like reese's comes out with these every year this is worth like four
dollars um that's slightly damaged it's fine it's wood this is made out of wood yeah you already
have that okay 2064 no all right but you somebody signed it you did okay dongjun lee a sculptor an
animal lover he spent his artistic heyday during 2058 to 2067 recently became a fixie he's being
considered as dead so he's deceased uh so he is uh where's how do i do that celebrity types
celebrity list where is it is there a way how do i drag that artist is already over there
oh it's an artwork tab right all right so he's dead whoa what i can't afford this okay i'm just
gonna make an offer i'm gonna make him i'm not gonna put this on here what about the appraisal
shouldn't you finish it don't forget to check the artwork section oh fuck off i can't i i can't
buy this well i'll appraise it for you so maybe you'll make some money god damn it whatever
there you go it's by deceased artist it's worth 2800 dollars you can take it you know yeah you
don't know it could be worth whatever it's too it's worth 250 man usually this stubborn yeah
why don't we just stop here i want to stop talking to a wall oh whatever i don't have
enough money why did i even pay the loan back i would have been able to have so much more
inventory never listening to chat ever again this is nightingale socks certificate of legacy of
nightingale second degree we hereby guarantee that this item was used by nightingale um they're
damaged what are they made out of cotton that's not velvet oh he's never in my why why would i
want to like 1905 i mean that's but it's it's historic okay historic socks and they're signed
too which is kind of weird but this is gonna be worth like a thousand dollars who signed it
uh i can't see this i don't see this on here this is not real okay so it's fake or there's
no signature for it unidentifiable autograph it's a great figure in world history great fig but i
don't know it's fake it's a great figure in world history it has a certificate though yeah that
makes sense fuck but i can't buy it smile i i how why did i pay the loan back everybody's freaking
out for me to pay the goddamn loan you idiot you're gonna pay the loan it's never gonna go
and now i can't even buy a new inventory i can't get another one just leave just fucking leave
i like to buy the eco-friendly shoulder bag please that's 380 dollars it's not quite much
304 you know what i'm desperate for money just take it to sell some stuff i can't sell anything
until somebody comes in to buy something it's not like a sell button the painting on display no
because an artist is going to come in and want one this is my mom i painted it myself okay my mom's
a little sick lately and she stays in bed all day but she used to smile like this so pretty
if you buy this off me i'll buy some flowers and gift them to my mom this would be uh yeah i mean
this is just what do you want to do with this it is in slight it's in pretty good condition
it's in pretty good condition but it's damaged and it's made out of canvas it's made out of canvas
uh-huh it was painted in 2080 no significance did you sign it you did um but your signature's
not on here sorry you're not a celebrity or anything this looks like it was love you mommy
this is a foot painting this yeah this looks like a foot painting this is a failed piece oh i got
it wrong then yeah uh you did paint this during prime okay so i don't really want this i'm just
gonna offer you like i'll offer you five dollars for it 15 but that's not what i expected can you
offer me a bit more you bring in a painting that you did with your feet of your mom and you want
more than 15 for it 20 for it i what do you want me to do all right just get no what this is as high
as i'm gonna go for this how many more times should we repeat this why don't we just stop here
i don't want this painting lower it back to 15 can you take a good look at this yeah i don't really
want to let it go but my wife has been pushing me so hard to sell this okay it's a fantastic
hoverboard by brand all right let's take a look damaged so that's not worth it you think it is
what's it made out of it's made out of some some weird material here as i think an authentic brand
okay the brand is uh vertivo let's see vertivo that's authentic vertivo material it is and this
is their uh this is their vtv steel oh you know you're right it's authentic yeah okay popular
item too all right anybody sign this so this does have a signature on it from that actor guy wait
hold on what's the date 2073 nothing significant 2073 but this actor wait is it actually the
signature or did you fake it it's got an artist signature on it or out of reach sore out of reach
vertivo dt 2073 2046 an automobile company that lost its fortune developing spaceships and now
makes only hoverboards okay products are popular right it's already listed there for dolphin-like
shapes however the royals say these those produced before 2068 are ugly okay well this is produced
after 2068 dt 2076 is the newest model all right so this is the new model no it's not look at jet
please but please put up the painting artist won't come until you do okay all right so this
is the this is legit um it has this guy's signature on it so we're gonna put artist
signature on it again i don't want to make it too expensive though uh where is it signatures
celebrity list celebrity types artist as a signature of an artist fuck no i mean i have
bring it down okay i have 500 bucks you don't have to fully appraise it the last time i didn't
fully this is why okay i'm gonna give you another criticism this game so if i don't have to fully
appraise things the last time i tried to not fully appraise something the lady said you didn't fully
appraise it why not and i had to fully appraise it anyways like can i actually do that some
customers just are just dicks you have to fully appraise for your reputation you can't buy
sometimes they don't notice all right i'm gonna let's start i have 550 bucks it's a mere celebrity
well i don't want to make the price more expensive i'm gonna do 500 would you please make me this
thing deserves more of your attention well i don't want to fully appraise it because i won't be able
to afford it why did i pay the loan back that was the worst decision i've made the entire game
uh make sure that i can get at least one of the two items what does he want he wanted um what
does he want what does this guy want he wanted like the id card what did he want exactly how
much is it um see 100 bucks that's not what i can afford can you please cut it to 68 all right well
this is a quest item so just take it and leave i need my time cinema no i mean no 1500 what should
i put it up there for too low more this is the mona lisa 2000 i'll do 2000 2000 and then 200
for this one it was my birthday present can you please tell me how much it's worth sweet pocket
mommy pocket mommy put pocket mommy in your pocket she will nag you for 24 hours a day
oh it's made out of plastic this week's target material the price has gone up hey yeah by the
way this is made out of plastic i just made it more expensive for myself but i have to tell them
uh this game i'm confused about how this game works sometimes because like you don't fully
appraise something they say but fully appraise it but like i have to do some appraisals like
i have to do some of the stuff i understand all right 2074 uh what is this the first is
a significant tracker i wonder if this is a tracker don't worry about me i can wait as long
is it right is it wrong not a tracker i mean it's a pocket mommy that sounds like a tracking
device all right well don't be mad 2074 whatever no signature on it it's just made it's just
whatever slightly damaged piece plastic okay i'll give you i'll give you 250 bucks for it
thank you all right now put this up immediately and sell it put it up for 365 hell yeah for i'm
gonna be easy with this one 400 my pocket mommy is not a historical item you're an expert can you
painting happy tears of a crocodile all right who did this i'm not sure i'm not going to correct
you because i want to buy it this is not even canvas what is this paper yeah that's fine 2069
oh all right who signed it who's who did this rocko is happy today like always okay yin jong
lee a painter all right in protest against the fixer and project in 2079 she donated umbrellas
with her signature on them to citizens she became a fixie recently all right so let's get an artist
on it i'm looking at i'm looking at it i'm looking at it i'm looking at it right now
we give me a minute okay so uh deceased became a fixie recently does that mean she's dead well
it's an artist so let's put that on here okay good i'll buy it i'll make you an offer uh i'll
give you a hundred and seventy five dollars for it because these are dead yeah but if i say that
i won't be able to buy it okay good good good good good good good good good good good good
i don't make it worth like two thousand dollars i can't afford it all right uh the end of the day
all right i only have 200 bucks they're planning to test run the artificial rain tomorrow afternoon
the forecast for tomorrow is sunny but rainy in the afternoon i feel like i'm gonna be so lonely
tonight but i'll let you go bob tootaloo repair shop downstairs will open tomorrow useful place
oh so yeah i can repair my hoverboard oh oh and then i can sell it for like 5000 or 2000 whatever
it is 45 bucks all right i'm just gonna check every toilet whatever the recycling bin honest
to god it's more efficient than selling items what was it holy shit i can sell this with like
300 bucks what on earth do you know about my father i didn't show you anything wrong
yeah my dad is a fixie now so what you're gonna fix him back this is just drama i don't want to
pay attention to nothing in there all right i want to go down lucky me from a different brand
adds 20 dude i i can sell that for like 50 bucks can i start now are you hiding yet mild gamer neck
spotted yeah i mean that that's that's uh i would consider that a little more substantial
mild gamer neck i don't know if i'd call that mild gamer neck as much as i would say that's mild
shaggy you'll come here to get the treatment tomorrow okay sweetie all right the union against
fixation okay uh come join us out with us um sure let's go stop this fixed rain it's fucking us all
up what happened oh what did i fall asleep all right uh i met yanji mu in person who mary put
on the black list chloe came back wishing i'd give him an id card and i did and i paid some
interest what levels of gamer neck are there there's uh shaggy is considered pretty pretty
mild and it goes all the way to dark crystal skexy so there's a spectrum there somewhere in
the middle you know what there's four types of loafers in this world good loafer bad loafer rich
loafer mindless loafer which type are you all right where am i on the gamer neck spectrum um
i don't know i mean i feel like if you have a gamer neck and you have a big adam's apple
like it's like a you could double whammy i have a pretty big adam's apple so like it looks like i
kind of look like a turkey sometimes show yourself well hold on am i decent i'm decent uh so if you
see what i'm talking about here this so i feel like my adam's apple like is pretty big up here
so if the adam's apple is large then you end up like a scenario like this right with this juts
out far and if you have your neck kind of cocked like this it looks kind of like you have like a
gobbler here you know big my adam's apple areas that's how i'm able to go like this
yeah i got a big adam's apple and big vocal uh whatever they are that's how i'm able to do that
car noise it's like green green green
oh
stop what i'm doing things oh the repair shop there's nothing in this trash repair shop is open
all right let me repair some of the stuff welcome to first repair we take care of every stuff as
warmly as child care that's a kind of an odd sentence i can repair items that are fairly
damaged or worse slight damages may remain though okay i repair services mostly done in no time but
it takes another day if the damage is really serious uh 50 bucks some of the items that need
repair um well first of all this this is like really damaged so that how damaged is this this
is damaged too what about that one and this one too i can only do two items at once all right how
about that show i can fix your picked up emotion tracker right away and i need one more night to
fix your picked up hoverboard 120 bucks sounds good do an impression of bowser okay
i'm gonna come back tomorrow okay and now what's that worth nice that's worth it all right let's
go there's a worst impression no it was not good morning wait before you say anything or hundred
what else needs to go up here that's just a stupid lamp whatever it sounded like a bathroom sink
that had sorry for your trouble what what just happened what just happened how much is it picked
up emotion tracker prepared you're not really selling this before 100 i've picked up from the
trash i'll buy it right away okay that's still a lot of money that sounds good thanks he gave me
the umbrella okay hey how's it going how are you can you give me a second to catch my breath from
home i kept running can you take a look at this well it's quite obvious what's told in this article
who's setting the reselling prices by the way they're higher than i expected
eleven dollars will do um well hold on this thing is in really shitty condition it's made out of
um paper you've got that correct in 2061 on for good nothing in 2061 and it was signed though
who was it signed by it's assigned by gong gong in oh he used to write highly objective articles
that people thought he equipped himself with a potato chip was the journalist oh this is fake
yeah this is fake dude uh this is a fake piece how do i where's a is it celebrity list this is
a fake it's a fake autograph okay so this is worthless um get this get out get out of my store
smart guy good gamer thanks where's my birthday present people keep bringing their birthday
presents here einstein's chalk certificate of legacy of einstein we hereby guarantee that
this item was used by einstein that's fair that's i'm gonna say that's fairly damaged
no i mean well it's not perfect seems to be made out of uh it's wood you've got that correct at
least it's from the 1911 interesting this has some archaeological value never on my mind all
right but is that albert einstein's signature it's not on here but it's got a certificate
i mean it has a certificate right great i can't afford if it's a great figure though if i say
this is a great historical figure then i'm going to literally it's going to be like times it's going
to be 800 dollars yeah there's an autograph on it i know unidentifiable a fake it's unidentifiable
but um scholar no no this is a this is a this is a fucking this is albert einstein this is
literally albert einstein now i can get this for 450 bucks although it's unidentifiable though
it's wait what um it has a certificate okay i'm gonna i'll give you 50 bucks how does that sound
i'll give you 50 dollars will you take 50 bucks i'll give you 50 bucks all right fuck yeah let's
go picked up glass on the showcase how much is that worth uh that'd be 30 bucks i'm not an idiot
to buy something picked up from trash for 30 dollars all right fine streamer's foaming at
the mouth over his pawn shop erase the signature on it excuse me can i have an umbrella it's urgent
we can't sell umbrellas but i need it before i take my mom home she already suffered from pneumonia
if she gets rained again she'll be in real danger she's going to work not to lose her job the company
didn't allow her to take a day off please let me buy an umbrella just one i don't have it i can't
do it i can't do it i can't do it i like to buy the doll of me over there how much is a doll of me
oh that one doesn't seem to be worth that much in my opinion 46 is fine i want this thing out
of my store anyways if that gets tracked back to me then i'm gonna i get arrested how's this guy
thank you for being at the protest yesterday bob i heard avac is finally noticing our work since we
all made one voice avac will definitely let out any reaction this evening will be especially
crucial i heard there will be a test running for an artificial rainfall this evening we must protest
with one voice so please make sure to come out this evening too let's make a change what if they
rain it's gonna rain on us are you the manager who's in charge of collecting umbrellas about
that job i wanted to ask if you'd like to sell umbrellas to me not avac i just don't like to see
people blindly obey orders i want to show avac that we're not just their puppets if i don't avac
will never give up on stepping on us don't worry about getting caught by the way i won't use the
umbrellas nor talk about anything that happened between us and i can pay you 150 bucks for each
it's even more than you get paid by them this could be this could be a lie it's gonna i'm gonna
get arrested no okay i don't know what if this guy's works for them that's a huge offer i don't
think it's worth it this could be an avac user this is a fixer yeah i don't know not gonna happen
you can't trust anybody are you afraid to disobey now i'm afraid to like give what is absolutely
you are avac i don't want to like you're gonna turn me in that was way too much money for that
not to be fake i'd like to buy the master fees la geoconda over there 2 000 this is crazy who pays
2 000 oh fuck off this is appraised at 900 i'm not gonna get out of here it was not a bad offer
yes it was it was appraised for a thousand dollars leap you know professor choy you know that idiot
that guy doing a one-man protest and causing a ruckus i wanted to see what his living conditions
were like so i went to his house and the security was so bad i found this was just lying on the
ground oh wait is that thing a long time ago choy was talking about a time machine or time
capsule or something he boasted about how he made a machine that looked good let me read it i wanted
to use it so i stole it but i can't figure out how to use it for the life of me so i'm just going
to sell it for a low price okay oh let's see it's in uh so i just like who cares and just buy it
because he just wants it he sure is real the world's fastest travel with professor choy
yeah that's that's correct yeah i'm just gonna buy it i don't want to i'm not gonna tell you
what it's worth this is he just wants it i'll give you 120 bucks for it yeah i don't want to
i don't want to appraise it but like i have to appraise sometimes it's kind of confusing
how much is the masterpiece 2 000 i think must be wrong i'll buy it right away if it's 942
fuck i need that money can't do counter offers i'm waiting for at least a thousand it's the
mona lisa i know that's why i'm holding out in a week last time i didn't know you just came back
from bluebird i did think you were really getting what's i did think you were not really getting
what was happening by the way why did you come back from bluebird you must have been aware that
fixed rain would come down soon am i wrong you don't like to answer please don't bother you got
any umbrellas this week anyway i do got two of them sent you 50 each there's one more thing i
really want you to know by the way how did you make it to bluebird 10 years ago i didn't have
the lucky passport event back then did they and what did you do over there for 10 years
lady i have amnesia i woke up in an old guy's bed and he told me i was his fake son i don't
know anything you really get on my nerves i woke up in like an old guy's apartment
well maybe that was my apartment movie script this is bad condition this is very bad um i would say
it's probably fairly damaged though though i don't think it's that brutal although let's see if it's
made out of what is it made out of paper yeah here's the kicker though when was this made
oh no this is not like all right 2076 significance and oh it's the sky it's like actor actor famous
for being a narcissist he is his script he just drew all over it okay well it's an artist where
is the celebrity type service uh it's signature of an artist and i know exactly who it is and
young people are gonna love it but at the end of the day it's still kind of rough around the edges
i'll give you 20 bucks for it 35 30 30 32 why do you keep calling the guy an artist it's triggering
because i've i don't make the rules of the game sniff sorry i have a cold after the rain last
week i found this at home how much can i get for it picked it up on the beach all right this is a
bob here too oh it's nothing all right this is good this is definitely have a signature on it all
right let's see what's it uh it's in shitty shitty condition uh this is in bad condition make sure
it's accurately made out of this what is it made out of cotton not made out of velvet sorry 2035
brutal city fire although like it has no uh whatever all right who's this all right this
is actually his signature tennis player so it's an athlete this is a this is a very common signature
that is an athlete you have to be you know we got to give an athlete signature of an athlete
and uh i'll tell you something you should know these are really common this is obviously
pre-recorded they all are every single one of them i'll give you five dollars for it price is
already low can you just give me 12 yeah sure that's fine yeah that's fine it's 12 bucks why
are you wasting time on stuff that's worth 20 dollars because of its reputation hilarious cracking
how much is it i must be wrong 38 bucks no but you guys told me to you guys told me that they were
going to come in and buy this for a lot of money is that accurate or is this bullshit okay this is
the pocket mommy albert einstein's thingy okay i'm going to sell this 500 bucks is that too much
tennis ball will sell 20 too much uh oh this thing too sell this 60 looks good all right don't sell
any other stuff erase the signature from einstein hey bob i was wondering how you're doing i'm doing
all right once what are you doing here you're supposed to get treatment by now gosh are you
are you bob did i hear that you came back but what was that who do you what do you have been
who had bandages all over their face i'm sorry i didn't recognize you anyway i'm here to take
once so let's talk i'll come back next week take care till then come on sweetheart it's time to go
i okay see you bob see ya jane wants to both unlikable i'd like to buy the masterpiece
2000 all right this is the that's over a thousand dollars is that not good enough wait for a
collector i need money now not like in two weeks hold the line uh the day is at an end all right
so they're gonna like rain on us today right overcharge why is that making me laugh overcharge
hey bob come on let's go good job okay bye didn't sell umbrellas i know i'm not selling umbrellas
thank you for taking part in the protest you wanted me to be there today i was uh she's gonna
revisit me the lady and her son and i paid some interest and then i gave the umbrellas to the uh
people judge uh pretty good judge if you put the painting back in your bag a collector will buy it
for huge money but i shouldn't have it on the display i don't know what to believe sell some
umbrellas you coward he's in the car we've never played this game we have no idea well neither do i
so we can't all act like we know what's going on i agree we need to fix her you know one of my
friends died from depression she had been fixed she wouldn't have suffered from depression and of
course she could be with us now she's a fixie then anyway she's alive what's the better we why
don't we just arrest them because we don't have to they will come to an end all at once this evening
what uh um what does that mean what's wrong with used ones if it's darcy's it's not bad
i give my hover hoverboard by the way does bob have a fiance i don't know pick up here you go
you have anything to request how's this oh dude nice sell it like 200 uh anything else damaged
not really tsa skipper yeah sorry i i skipped travis strikes again so i don't understand what's
going on in this game right now i'm sorry does young g come around here i don't want to be
associated with him can you take a look at this uh you're collecting umbrellas right it's not his
only job but you're right by the way are you in charge of reselling too the prices here look
pretty high you know you're not the first person to say that uh i'll take it for 38 dollars exactly
no i'll get i'll take it 30 plant is dying i can't water them how much is that painting
none of these people want to buy this no i'm not selling for 30 bucks i think i have to put it back
in my inventory i have to put this shit back in my inventory get them off display and put the
fucking ds up here this wow it has been a while yeah we used to meet each other like every day
i will never try to be polite to you anymore did you see what is this i finished it last night
bako the guy who had paint stains all over his shirt um yeah i i know who that is and you know
how much i want him to see this right if so i need you to put this on your showcase so that bako can
see it on on the way free yep you don't want to have it oh stop and put it on the showcase right
now you know what fine i'll do it praised at 385 so i put up with like 10 bucks how much is the
movie script 60 bucks 60 bucks 14 i was gonna say if you got an authentic signed movie script
by one of the actors of the writers in the movie that would be probably worth people
hundreds of dollars right hundreds put it in the showcase all right fuck excuse me excuse me
that painting of the centaur who's the artist behind that piece why are you gonna report it
to the avac no i'm not i just find it fascinating it's been a while since i've seen such a vibrant
painting it almost sounds like it's saying i don't care about what avac thinks so it deserves my
respect anyhow who's painting is that the owner's granddaughter he has quite a temper though oh
harry joe all right i finally had the money right now i'd buy it right away how unfortunate
uh bob i want some arm upgrades i'm gonna be a painter too just like what i expected this
place always looks like junuk of sing sing you know another umbrella uh it's an umbrella i'll
give you 40 bucks for it i get 50 bucks anyways who cares i'm drunk be careful slow down don't
drink too much drink some water have a few have a glass of water slow down a little and relax
i'm gonna go too far i hope you having fun oh shit how much is the einstein chalk 200 bucks
exactly what the fuck do you know uh-oh the music i'd like to buy the tennis ball how much
it's 20 bucks fine whatever it's gonna be 10 three dollars oh i uh whatever it's a waste of money i
should i'm not gonna buy any more of these they're actually worthless i'm not buying anymore i found
this at home how much can i get for it okay here we go here we go it's really actually really good
condition very good condition this is leather that is authentic leather it is you got that right
seem like an honest man 2079 doesn't really have any it does have significance but not it's a bag
what have we got here no signature it's just a bag it's just a bag okay it's just a bag um
i'll give you 280 all right all right 300 that's the best i can do there was there was no brand
there's no brand on it brandless all right movie script 60 why does nobody want to buy
this for what it's appraised for it's worth should i just get rid of this whatever i mean
no one's gonna buy it reputation declining i'm doing all right hey bob thank goodness it's friday
have you found my time cinema i did i did get you your time cinema here it is for you bob i'll give
it to you for 150 so you eventually helped me get all the two items thank you thank you so much bob
and believe me i'll never forget this i gotta head to the institute please wish me luck is it
gonna like time travel back in time or something what's it gonna do with that finally i get to
meet you i've heard some good stories related to you in this store i wanted to give you a present
can i give you a present i picked it up somewhere it looks really old but there's no space for this
painting in my apartment i'll take like 50 million dollars i've got no i do appreciate it so i thought
i'd be able to give it to you it's been a while since i've felt gratitude thank you all right see
you later wait hold on a minute um i mean this is like i this is worth a lot of money my ex gave
it to me some time ago silver glasses okay well how could silver glasses be made out of platinum
that's what i don't understand what they are that's weird okay that's strange 2065 nothing
significant signed by anybody they are who's this a jeweler in charge of the inspection of the jewels
of queen of hearts so that's a jeweler look at that signed by a jeweler isn't that interesting
very cool and i think that's uh let's make sure we get that right nothing i can drag over and
that's it i'll give you i'll give you two uh yeah 240 will you take 240 all right nice all right
get cool cool cool cool cool cool cool cool cool cool cool cool all right let's put that immediately
up for like 400 look at this shit 400 bucks i'm gonna four four ten how much is the sweet pocket
mommy 400 good oh yeah nice okay we're back in the green missing anything oh the bag yet
raised it 400 we're gonna put this up here 500 oh shit i found you didn't heed my words you helped
professor choy you let him get a weird machine of his strictly speaking you are an avarice
criminal too you helped a dangerous figure so you must pay your fine right now to prove your
non-possessive spirit or else i'll arrest you for crime fine is wait i changed my mind don't mind
the fine but there's one thing you should follow what from this point on everything i say to you
is confidential uh okay you know about yujin oh you know you mean the former leader of the avac
if items related to yujin oh come in don't resell them just throw them out in junkyard
there's too many people just do what the fuck if the association finds you sell items related to
yujin oh you'll never see the light of day again dude there's too many things that i how much is
it it's an artwork right i'm just asking because you haven't made an art appraisal on this i'll
buy it right away if it's 100 but i can't appraise it i can't appraise this go home oh it's you bob
thank you for being at the protest yesterday now let's wait see what will happen i think avac will
give us a kind of reaction by this evening because we including you all protest with one voice all
right then enjoy the rest of your day there's some shit's about to go down in about five minutes here
i want to buy the crocodile painting are you just in here oh yeah okay i got it i'm like i'm good
there's something going out something going down tonight all right i gotta be careful
it's about to go down they're gonna rain are they raining on us even if i sell all i have i can't
live in pedopolis huh everyone please go back to your home oh god the association is preparing a
new policy so stop causing more disturbance and go back to your house a new policy tell us what it
is i'm not in a position to announce it please go home for now uh we should press h mister do you
like cats i do yeah i pressed h i'm so sure avac will ask us something preposterous
are you saying you're pro fix rain i really want to get in there the bunker of freedom
you have anything to say i'd rather tie once who up to the wall okay i'm gonna make a lot
if an art collector comes in i'm gonna make a shitload of money okay don't sell anything of
yujin oh throw it away in a room so dark that i can barely see i feel hopeless what do i do now
what about i just bribe him no i cannot waste even a vana just bribe him who me who are they
talking about you should play the outer wilds dlc coming up are they doing that at the beginning of
the week we announce our new plan last weekend the association stopped the resumption of fixed
rain however we are still deeply concerned that it will lead to more crimes therefore we'd like
to ask for your active cooperation in tracking down avarice criminals from this week from today
all citizens must cooperate to hunt down 90 avarice criminals each week by abiding by this
one rule agic city will be free from fixed range forever however if you fail for if you fail for
two consecutive weeks fixed rain will begin immediately they will we will distribute criminal
report button whenever you meet a person who is suspected to be an avarice criminal just press
the button if a citizen gets reported once they will receive pre-averice criminal badge if twice
they'll be judged as an avarice criminal who should pay a fine or get arrested you can check
the number of criminals searched out during the week in real time through the billboards in
fountain square names of excellent reporters and of places where avarice crimes are frequent will
also go public we're hoping for the day when agic city is reborn as an avarice crime safe city
without the help of fixer thank you i ain't reporting shit i ain't reporting anything
good look look at your face enjoyed a lazy weekend huh definitely arrested look at that
greedy face i'll never i'll never let me display it what if it's a place with a lot of avarice
crimes you better not go there i'll get the report their neighbor is so ruthless all right
see that's where that person's ever been arrested all right did you get the morning broadcast just
as it said let me give you the report button you can press it right from today and can you see the
small display above it on its left is a count of your reports for the day while the other is a
count of your reports for the week please don't be afraid to press it in the face since they cannot
know if you press it or not okay here will be the total number of criminal arrests of the week for
the city this is getting so complicated oh emergency meeting this is a badge for
preliminary criminal if you report someone without this badge they'll soon be listed on the criminal's
list and receive this badge however we will arrest or levy a fine on them in a matter of
minutes if they already have this badge i forget to check the bulletin board at fountain square
upstairs shows the name of the citizen who most actively pressed the button in real time the names
will be announced throughout the city and receive special benefits special benefit sounds good the
board also displays the name of high crime spots on which the store can also get nominated once
average criminal customers visit here often or anyone outside reports your customers a lot and
nobody all right whatever i don't like i just sell fucking toys what if we never press it you'd
better not take it as an option for the city unless you make at least one or two reports every day
and we'll get hit with fixer show your responsibility as a citizen of agic city okay so i have to do it
okay mr i am from age of capital i'd like to tell you some sad news unfortunately age of capital
is terminating its domestic business soon and the fix ran comes if it does there will be no more
floaties to loan money to but before that happens i wanted you to know that you can take out an
emergency loan if you need one mister you should look onto it the guy from the simpsons have a
great day mister i don't need five thousand dollars right now i manage my money well
you can kindly leave i got the registration i did be the official manager of darcy's cool
by the way you got that report button i was going to give you something useful today but
i guess it might be too much for you now that uh we're being overburdened with that stupid button
life is full of challenges uh well yeah this might be a great chance for you to grow up
as you can see this is a vertivo hoverboard but let's say the customer who brought this
in doesn't know that you'd probably start thinking like if i share the card vertivo
the customer will surely expect more money but what if i don't share it that's what i asked
four hours ago however as you know the card allows you to put a higher price when you resell the
hoverboard exactly when the private slot should come to the front do you see the new piece of
equipment underneath the card slot try and find the card vertivo from the manual and put it in
the private slot did it really take them five hours of gameplay to get here to do this okay
well this is a brand vertivo okay you just successfully hid the card using the private
slot hiding information that you don't want to share but if you hide cards that have a
pricey information on it you might get a complaint or a nasty rumor okay you can hide up to two cards
cards here will be kept secret until you successfully buy the item and they go public as you display the
item okay i get it be careful if you use this too often customers are going to notice by the way
darcy is there any problem with your watch screwdriver oh about the screwdriver i got
it taken away by the stabilizer i'm supposed to get him lobster phone but i failed that doesn't
mean you deserve to lose the screwdriver where did he learn all that torturing torturing skills
truth is that he's been taking my back every time i scavenge from the fixie area find the lobster
phone the authentic one disappeared asking to recreate it yeah yeah yeah i don't give a shit
about any of this just please let me play the game i don't care about your dumb lobster phone
when i pick it up and fucking elmo's on the other end i don't care go buy one at target it's just a
black telephone and a lobster more breaking news stabilizer won first place in last weekend's
non-possession spirit competition he's chosen by a citizen's vote one female citizen said he had a
sense of restraint especially i loved his closed lips get in here stop all right the flawless
shoulder bag on the showcase how much is it maybe 500 skipping the lore 429 that's uh i'll take it
by the way you look suspicious suspicious bob dear now i can finally speak with you
once who's been missing his treatments and fading away so i've been a total mess
i think to stop being a total pain in your neck oh no no no what has happened around him is just
all because of me and my occupation but everything will be fine eventually you know that right
anyway guess what i brought for you it's a gem appraiser that can give you a help when you're
uh appraising items with our gems i don't know why i said that in a mario like accent let me
show you how to use it garcia used to separate gems by their surprisingness or unsurprising
gems all he wanted to know was just their kind it analyzes the kind and the quality of a gem
and then you get gem cards at sight it's a beautiful ruby ring and the price is
1050 now click the gem appraiser and move it onto the ring there's like a picture of it
i just do wait now there must be a card that only seen by you can you see it it's a garnet not a
rupee am i right i assume the price dropped big too like this gem appraiser is the only way you
can check a gem's actual name so don't forget to use it especially on accessories uh you forgot
to mention the card brand eraser you must check if it's if a gem is missing or broken when a
customer brings branded jewelry that's the case it cannot be classified into general accessories
such as necklaces and earrings its brand effect falls too there's a lot of info okay sure sure
now i remember that card the brand eraser in a situation like you said you can bring out the
card brand eraser to reduce the price fuck you game oh dear i have no idea what's happening in
my head these days anyway it's time for me to get back to work have a great day sweetie okay
this is giving me a headache there's too many mechanics i like to buy the silver glasses over
there how much are they 400 thank you i have a lot of money what's going on here would you just
press the button sorry if i was too sensitive i did not press the button i'd like to know the
value of this fancy item how about 729 dollars wait a minute okay this is made out of what is
that silver this is silver right it's made out of fucking silver but i want 729 i might be in
danger if i get what i i don't know what that was even saying okay so let's check should i do the
gem enhancer 2067 and i'm there no signature all right this is oh shit you know i'll give you the
764 i'll give you the step that's a that's a fair offer i think so i can put this on after right
yeah yeah sure so how do i put that on wait hold on holy shit it's worth fucking like 3000
all right uh get this out of the way this thing's fucking worth this thing's worth
i'll do 3500 can you please appraise this what the fuck is this a mug shot i i think i want to
this is a this is a little suspicious here it's very damaged 264 got a signature on it
is there anybody is this anything important who is this i don't think so
on hang gong check the owner of the autograph i don't know i don't know who this um this is
just like a mug shot it's suspicious artwork i don't think this is a mug shot it's not artwork
i'll give you five dollars for it i'm not buying a mug shot and by the way suspicious how much is
the painting a hilarious centaur 400 um yeah take it it's not mine i don't care i picked it up off
the ground a while ago seemingly meaningful paper okay looks sentimental do you know what it is
really shitty condition i hereby declare every chippy will be separated from their potato chips
and sales and imports of potato chips will be prohibited this sounds like the plot of like a
mickey mouse clubhouse episode what's what's the big fat cat's name bluto what's the cat's name
peep blue house from puppy they're the same character okay they're the exact same character
i made it a paper 2060 oh the anti-chippy act hold on a minute this is significant wait wait
wait a minute i don't think i i don't think i want to tell i want to hold on to this
and who signed it oh shit who is this oh who's that so hon the former president he enjoyed great
popularity for legendary speeches this is a product of soul hand it's the old president
and everybody loved him plus 20 this is a politician i'll tell you this is a politician
national hero i'm gonna say national hero i'm gonna hold on to that one
and what else can i tell you um this is a this is a politician i mean like this is not worth
anything price drops significantly this is a politician that they're out of the country
they're all have them for the fixies you don't want this okay i you know what i you seem like
a nice person i'll um i like it but best i can do is five bucks you know what yeah i mean you
came all the way here six is good i think i couldn't even report oh do you need any help
oh no no no i was giving it a second thought if i could trust your recommendation the truth is
i'm in graphological study club and the club holds meetings every monday so i thought i could rely
on you to get something with an autograph for today's meeting it occurred to me that your
recommendation may not be satisfying to me if your recommendation turns out to be reliable i'll come
back get all this shit out of the window somebody buy this bracelet uh sell the hoverboard for 200
and then okay i want i need to get rid of these paintings it's not really fancy but that doesn't
mean you can't buy it right this is by uh buzz fly it is actually this is this is very damaged
that's nitpicky no it's not it's very it's clearly damaged what's what is made out of
carbon fiber you got that right wing it fuzz flies 2076 insignificant there and signature on it okay
what about fuzz fly okay mr brand's fuzz fly where's fuzz fly all right oh no this is wrong
this is made out of carbon fiber no it is carbon fiber never mind okay once middle zian hoverboard
brand that lost its reputation after being sold to a corporate republic to avoid taxes
well sorry to say sorry about that uh wing it fuzz fly wing it fuzz fly that's accurate
this is actually from fuzz fly the only thing now that i have to determine is who signed this
you did once a business man but he later became the first person accused of an
adverse crime he was charged with using chippies to build wealth luxury but was some what was
acquitted okay so this is by an artist it's a fake signature how do you know that's real
this is a real city what are you talking about oh shit the top right report that person um yeah
this is this is fake man this is worthless fake autograph um this is worthless i'm not gonna sell
this get out of here does aviac know you're doing this you chucked this off just because it's not
fancy i know that you probably did that yourself do you dare bring me a fake autograph oh you look
even pity pittier than i you're locked up in that small desk here's what i brought please be gentle
with it strong ring interesting it's perfect condition what we got here damn randorite push
and cut what's the material here let me tell you something what you got here this is not a
stainless steel ring this is a platinum ring that's a platinum ring my friend i am the judge yeah it's
worth a lot more than you think it is let's see if we got anything else significant on here
fixer 1.0 and okay what about uh anybody sign this ring no it's a really nice ring it's a very very
nice ring and he had it wrong it was actually platinum so i mean like you're gonna get more
than you thought you're gonna get more than you thought what i can get for you here i'd say
somewhere around 1500 but i could probably do 1200 that's all my money it's a good a thousand
great get that shit right up there immediately for four grand for you just like what i expected
this place always looks like junuk of sing sing you know i don't know what that means
chessboard by everbrown it's in i wouldn't say valueless it's pretty damaged i wouldn't say it's
junk or anything this is it is the correct brand yeah miss everbrown wouldn't you got it right
yeah accurate 377 all right yeah uh but unfortunately for you they're pretty valueless
what wait what happened wait wait what what how did it become more money minus 25 what happened
what happened this is an easy way to lose reputation it's junk i'll give you eight bucks
for it uh i think we replaced the brand card with the garbage card oh seems you're utilizing the
private slot very actively at least now i don't know if you can definitely fearless just be careful
bye grandpa hi do you remember me i do i'm eggy we met on the street last week your mom
won't like you being in places like here when i read citizen discourse data there were my mom
my mom and dad aren't with me now because i ran away i mean daddy you're now
i'm not gonna report a kid get out of here uh i would love me anymore because they were hit by
the rain i mean fixed rain but i couldn't even see the rain i was sick and stayed home for a few
days you know that fixer just clears up everything of you but your body just erases all things inside
of you i saw the fixer erasing my mom and dad's spirits into nothing it's just like me being
erased from this world one day i left home by myself hoping mom and dad look for me they didn't
day after day i just kept walking and i ended up in this city you live on the street no i live
together with a lady she said i should not tell anyone about her i don't know why but she's nice
anyway it always puts on some ugly dark clothes when she goes out but i think she'll look better
in bright ones anyway i'm hungry i gotta head home now see you around i don't know where she's eating
the blonde lady i like to buy the picked up hoverboard over there how much is it
you wondered sounds reasonable do i report this i have to report everybody has one of those
am i doing that wrong can you spare some minutes i brought some bad news for you what is it darcy
or i think it's time for you to move out what if you don't now we will try to rip you off with
monstrous rent you got so upset after she found out that i've been letting you live in that room
for free but perfect timing new roof is finally reopening oh is it then why don't you try it
tomorrow morning it won't take long since it's on the b3 level of this building i bet it won't
take you a lot more move out since there's cheaper options i'm doing peter griffin you have till next
monday morning i mean two weeks from now after that nari will come and ask for rent i can't help you
from then it's also written on the calendar good luck then i have to move out by two weeks from now
day is over our day's work run home oh this is a hundred and twenty two dollar handbag what the
heck is that any other scraps around here arrested for crimes full stream thanks please remember
oh his soul is always with us like okay don't sell things from you to know right i miss you daddy
i can't help this girl i think there's a bunker i forgot about the bunker oh bob have you seen
wansu i have not seen once i don't know where he is i got a taco well you needed a crunch wrap
awesome right they're working together come on nari i told you you need to make it much brighter
we're still waiting for the art collector i don't know if the art collector is ever going to show
up i'm starting to believe that there is no art collector there's probably no art collector
hey loafer now i remember who you look like you look like my loafer uncle i hated him the most
a rick art collector yeah i don't think there's an art collector i think it was a big
complete lie that you guys did can you pay the fine i i pay the fine or you'll get arrested
morty i don't know who that is but i feel so bad objo isn't he the manager wait what better watch
out the watch out for the pawn shop what are you talking about what happened what did you do
give the hard work seems like you need my cleaning service what do you say it'll cost
90 dollars cleaning service you're the informant of the week you were the oh you are the informant
i thought they said that nobody knew that data uh sure i'll clean cleaning service out of what
is he's gonna clean in oh i thought he talked about inside all right well whatever it's clean
oh it's you bobby look i brought my little gullion he's very shy and not so friendly at first
but oh my god how evil she's cute i knew you'd like her ah gullion well what should i do she said
gullion is her everything did you see which way gullion went this is why i chose to be a dink
which by the way that's double income no kids if you didn't if you didn't know i like to buy
the luxurious bracelet over there how much is it 3500 oh oh that's a big sale you're the one who
reported me huh you don't i can't confirm or deny that i saw your name in the billboard it must be
you who are you to report me when did i ever get so greedy i told avac that i did nothing wrong that
you reported me wrong so when the avac guy comes and asks tell them the truth that you press the
button by mistake got it you're already here you've raised an objection to the average criminal
report sent from this store right yes it was claimed that you mr joe bob made a false report
is that true if you admit it you will be fined and it's 200 i don't okay is there a third option
i don't understand the question because i fucking don't i'm supposed to report
random ass people i don't like i don't know what it even means what am i reporting them for
i don't even know what i'm reporting them for fuck them i know you did it right i did it right
it's for being greedy save him save him it's for being okay so if they're greedy i report them
well i'm greedy well what are people reporting me kill him i i'm not i don't i'm not gonna do that
look now that i okay now that i understand how that works i have to report greedy people i may
have reported this person inaccurately i made a mistake i i made a mistake 200 dollars case is
closed please leave now i understand how the thing works and by the way i just reported him again
okay wait i can do it twice i double reported this guy um i reported him twice i was wondering
if i could see darcy today but today's not the day i guess i'd like to show you something it's
not very valuable it is nice triple report all right how greedy are you gonna be are you gonna
be super greedy are you gonna be kind of greedy which one this thing is in dog shit condition
dog shit made out of plastic 2020 oh that was last year somebody signed it who signed it
this is signed okay by who sang hoon lee after claiming to have come from the future in a time
machine and warning about the future very via various media he disappeared in 2079 what kind
of celebrity is that is there like a time travel celebrity uh i don't know uh this one an activist
journalist names that are holding on to yeah i probably just a mere celebrity yeah
i'll give you that he's a celebrity on here you can get a little bit more another dollar i guess
like anything else is not worth anything else i mean whatever maybe 10 bucks for it let's not
waste our time on a few vanis i'll take your offer okay that's not very greedy don't need to triple
report because i'm not an expert i don't know the details can you give me the details handwritten
score of warm ocean what is this uh this is like this is pretty much slightly damaged
it's pretty cool it's not a bad piece of work here made out of paper 2038 okay yeah we sign this
it is signed by whom appear uh a musician of the founding period he wrote the national anthem
the bunker of freedom this is a huge deal founding period he wrote the national anthem uh
this is a great figure in world history would it be artist or would it be a huge figure national
hero have you found something now not really uh okay so i'll give you you know what this is
worth a little bit it's not it's a fake it's a fake what do you mean it's a fake how is it fake
i could do this yeah it's an artist pretty cool huh it's missing the dot no it's not it's there
okay so i'll give you i'll give you four i'll give you 400 for it turned out i got scared for
nothing it's going to be no one that can turn to whatever okay so i'll sell this for 700 180p
chat oh hold on he's talking right now and it's gonna skip i know it hey when are you going to
give me my lobster telephone you do that for me you must have been really desperate i already
promised my customer i get a lobster telephone so you must prepare the lobster telephone i don't
okay throw that screwdriver into the ocean fine don't forget it's friday no one's coming with a
lobster telephone dude uh let's sell this for 180 put the music up here for about 800 no 750 let's
be fair it's weird cup sell it 18 all right are they ever going to come in and buy this shit
it's honest to god i don't think anybody comes in you guys are just lying to me this whole time
there's no art collector it's been like an hour and a half there's no art collector it needs to
be on display well okay on display on display it'll be the next fucking guy if you sell them
all right whatever it's good to see you're keeping the store as it used to be it's still rugged
all right i got this thing everbrown stuff is worthless you should know that i don't even
want this any gems in there yeah it's everbrown but everbrown's fucking worthless it's everbrown
yeah it is uh they're they're absolute garbage though and i'll lose reputation if i have this
in my store so get it out of here on display on display one just just leave okay i'm going to
immediate decline if it's ever would report him no i can't report somebody for not knowing
i thought that was a fish okay it's a uh rotivo well you know that how damaged is it it's not
that's that's not it's not that damaged it's not that damaged okay what's it made out of
authentic i think right yeah it's authentic yeah all right what else you got in here
uh its products are popular for dolphin like wait what year 2061 uh royals say that those produced
before 2068 are ugly uh i'll give you this one i'll give you that one i'll give you that one
it's signed by lee sang hoon that's another celebrity signature i will hold on to that uh
that would be a celebrity never played this game this game can be 15 hours oh well whatever i'm
still i'm gonna stop when i'm done having fun i'll give you um i'll give you 300 for uh 315
i'll give you 300 i'd like to buy the strong ring over there oh how much is that ring that
would be 3500 please 3377 i'll take it handshake i'm getting to that bunker i'm getting to that
goddamn bunker i meant to buy something but instead i gotta ask you a favor i just got into trouble
somebody made a report about me a few minutes ago but i can't afford the fine i have to pay
for my daughter's treatment i'm asking for your generosity to give me 1100 bucks i can't promise
you a golden ring but i promise i'll spread good words about you i swear as you can see i have
nothing to lose that means i won't feel sorry even after making a report on a total stranger
so wait was that a threat did he just threaten me that he was gonna report me i'll report you
i feel like we're both holding like cell phone cameras at each other oh you're recording me i'll
record you we're both recording each other now yeah it's two karens like videoing each other
screaming at each other the karen mirror karen battle you know it's really i can't i mean if
you think about that like okay if somebody's being like filmed being going like crazy or something
like a karen and then they go oh yeah well i can record you too and then they hit the record
button so do you think they watch that back later and like bite their finger and go holy shit fuck
oh i look i look weird here oh do you think they like try to post it on facebook to be like look
what this person said to me i feel like it's kind of a 50 50 coin flip i feel like i would watch a
video like that back and be like holy fuck this is what i sound like what the hell am i doing
what did i just say that for holy shit delete this now in fact recover my iphone in fact
recover my iphone recycle the iphone and go get a new one all right i what i would have fucking
disaster i want that i don't want to i want that cut out of my life completely all right um uh
what do i do here what was that was that a threat was this a threat did he say i would report you
if you don't so should i just say yes and report him it was a threat okay so we report him he
reports me i say yeah go spread the word about the store being good take care of the daughter
and then we'll go from there daughter is i i'm okay with giving a thousand dollars for the daughter
so report daughter you get reported report me back that's fine report and cut the crap
before i didn't say no he's scamming you but i don't want to report i'm scared not a threat
give him the cash you know what we're gonna do the right thing we're gonna do the right thing
if i won't forget to spread good word about you look at that look at that i can afford i can afford
it whoa were you aware of it too that the avca was targeting me i wish you could understand what
it's like to live his own gmo and you might understand living as a huge star is never easy
my guess avac hates me not because i'm against fixer because i'm too popular must be that they
want to arrest me to fix me and take me away all the love and popularity i will never let
that happen because my fans love and attention are what i live for as you know when fixed rain
comes there will be no one left to love me which means there will be no more reason for me to be
alive but you won't even bother to think that way once you get fixed oh i did try to imagine my life
as a fixie and it might be easier than my current life i don't know everything to sell human nature
my fame popularity natural born talent and the love i'm receiving and what
belonged to me i can't let either avac or fixer take those from me you get what i'm saying you
don't that's still not your fault anyway don't forget to drink some warm milk before bed since
this is the second time we've met i believe you'll find your own way to fall asleep see your own
i was drunk i was drunk okay whoa cat the masterpiece la giancina on the showcase how
much is it it's 2000 i'm just gonna sell it no you don't i want to be a thousand leave
i did not say la giancina i didn't who's talking now you killed my mother don't you remember what
i begged you for an umbrella but you never listened you cold-blooded monster we had no choice
umbrella sales are not allowed shut up you're nothing but cowards did you hear what he said
he just asked if your dad's alive i don't feel good if i sold the umbrella i would get arrested
and i would probably get fucking killed bob is there any way you can report me to avac what i'm
exhausted i can't wait for fixed rain in any longer i just want avac to arrest me and would
be really happy to hear that huh mama's gonna have a way better life without me i've always been a
burden for her sorry for this crap bob i'll just leave well no it's all good you don't gotta leave
hey look who's here jane's looking for you like crazy again but i'm not a six-year-old anymore
yeah but you know why jane's so worried about you so go home and save your mom son
all right see you soon bob what about the cat the cat just left wait the cat is gone which means
less hair in the air now oh i love breathing by the way why do you care that much about wonsu
hanja see your secret son or what come on they say near neighbor is better than a distant cousin
anyway it seems once who wants to rely on you bob just like you did a decade ago oh
what no wonder because you and your brother book who used to protect him whenever wonsu got bullied
by other kids for being a son of jewelers before you and book go each got away to bluebird and
haga city of all of a sudden and that changed him don't get me wrong i'm not blaming you the
kids who bullied wonsu are guilty for all this not to mention the silly kidnappers who blackmailed
jane after kidnapping wow how why do you know all this just don't try to explain your way of
talking is not i'm just very confused report i don't like this info i don't like hearing this
such a lonely boy you know i'd like to give a damn about my loneliness day's over our day's work time
to go home please go find wonsu for me please seems like an indoor cat i like this cat donate
for zero okay we can't take a rest tomorrow's already wednesday i wish i can go to bed with
ease tomorrow i got a badge so i've got to be careful those criminals just look normal
all right well i'm good you need to report more people no i don't almost there i don't want to
report more people hey i have something to what's up nothing please go ahead what's going on dude
what's going on report more people or get the funny rain let me know if you need anything dude
the cat's in my apartment oh no it's not you have to report people i are i've reported like five
people chat that was 16 left not 16 total who cares about the ranges use an umbrella but i'm
gonna get arrested okay i have to move out too yeah how much does it cost what did they say was
third level third level right no where is it b3 this isn't this b3 b3 would be the bottom i already
live on b3 don't i in the other area oh it's this above the store okay it ain't easy being
cheesy where are you i saw the cat uh i know where the cat is i can't tell her though informant of
i'm not on there that's good my name's been posted here can i sleep well at night
okay well what up make it a society or whatever how do i look there has been my exterior upgrade
last night it's a gift he raised all the three reputations by at least one level each yesterday
fy this is the hue that emulates darcy look poke me if you want my former look back i'll catch your
signal and get it back and there's more didn't you see what's over there there's a chime bell
above our door the guy who received 1100 dollars from us came and left it last night he said he
paid for his daughter's treatment with the money and wanted to repay for that oh snazzy i don't
have to worry about being reported we caught enough criminals right i found this at home how
much can i get for it threw it only a few times you're reselling for high prices you must buy them
for high price too right i was expecting 15 bucks first of all what is this the gems in here eat by
go do speak see oh it's everbrown since i'm not an expert i don't know its details but you're an
expert you can find something i report all everbrown they come in here and they're worth like three
dollars and they come and they try to get fucking like 20 bucks every time get out of here this is
that guy's doll uh it's a made out of cotton made it actually he's made out of cotton by the way
2076 okay and is it signed that looks like a fake signature it is it's not real this is fake
so i'm sorry um this is a fake boy so i believe i'm sorry i'm gonna have to report you for this
because this is you're being reported or what exactly i don't remember um but it's because
you have brought fake merchandise into here i'm trying to sell it for a price it's not fair
you didn't know stop reporting the quote is done you know what i'll give you a dollar
can you take a good look whoa i don't really want to let it go my dad has been pushing me to
hard to sell it let's take a minute here our watch screwdriver is not ready yet which means
we can't check its movement i assure you it's not fake and i didn't replace its movement so
you don't need that screwdriver what excuse me it's damaged first of all second of all you
could have just looked the other way i could have looked the other way this thing's made out of
fucking clay this thing's made out of clay what are you what are you trying to do here
reported what is this even made out of this is made out of like dirt you've brought me a dirt
watch you're going to jail that's not leather this is dirt it's it's yeah hold on what there's
no signature 2068 what's this thing lab between sass and casual catastrophe let's take a look at
this fucking brand i don't see this listed here yeah okay you gave me a dirt where's this casual
catastrophe wait a minute this is the leather okay so is it real okay this is a i thought it
was like fucking minecrafter a bag brand widely recognized as cursed um it's loved by thrill
seekers but it's cursed the biggest fires broke out in 69 and 73 those products in the years are
both rare and popular holy shit really 69 and 73 oh you missed it by one year all right well this
thing is cursed just let you know superstitious people are very upset about that i thought you
would be an expert i am i didn't intend to sell it anyways i'll take it back yeah well get reported
you just you get you got ip bands from my store you're not allowed back in 800 bucks you got it
all right news a recently arrested avarice criminal made a shocking statement before getting
fixed the criminal confessed he was the arsonist responsible for the brutal fire in 2035 he stated
sue mongeau the arsonist was actually a hero who helped citizens escape saying john and the
national hero was nothing but one of the victims new hero is born john and already became famous
so what's he got to lose next up the recycling committee has announced that this week's target
of material is aluminum alloy citizens who are actively participating in aluminum alloy collection
will be given footrest made to recycle material you know we can't partake in that we're shopkeepers
but somehow i feel bad they changed the gift from pew to footrest am i equivalent to a footrest
this reporter say woo anyway aluminum alloy yeah yeah yeah it's expensive yeah yeah yeah
sell it yeah yeah yeah i got aluminum how much is the picked up lunchbox bag how do you know i got
it from the trash bob you haven't heard the news have you this is huge hondja was attacked last
night guy came in and asked hondja if she's the father of the owner the second and suddenly
attacked him i guess that's the guy who came to us to buy an umbrella maybe he thought hondja was
your dad what anyway hondja is not seriously injured but he won't open his store for a week
to recover from trauma is that the repair guy happy darcy safe you are too right come on you
could nod or something oh shit is a lobster do you want it yeah i'm just giving it away yes i'll i'll
take it now we need a phone i need a phone i have a phone lying around in my house you do i'll bring
it tomorrow i don't need it anyway all right cool yeah bring it report the lobster you again can't
hide it i saw it all a lobster i guess you just need to get a phone now let's be black to look
the same as the real one got it painting girl with pearl earring on the showcase how much is it
thousand bucks wait oh there it goes imagine getting like a 40 million dollar painting for
a thousand bucks i'd like to show you something it's not very valuable but nice what is that i
thought that was an organ that looked like a weird like cow stomach or something okay a hoverboard
it's not it's in a good it's not that bad um any gems in it wasn't made out of aluminum alloy
oh you know what it's it's made out of aluminum i wasn't expecting that yet my reputation let's
go up a little bit uh swoosh swing see if this is the real deal 2074 i think okay here we go
this is signed by none other than lee salute gel became a scholar after his grandmother got
alzheimer's which eventually led to his discovery of its cause and solution in his later years he
put raincoats on the apes and said you are not human but nature okay so he's a scholar and that's
authentic limited edition uh you're a scholar but that's a it's bad for the price it's bad for the
price it's not a fake it's real uh all right swoosh swing let's make sure this is real
actually swoosh swing now go back swoosh swing aluminum alloy okay so hoverboard brand notorious
for frequent breakdowns until 2078 oh shit this product's got failed in safety tests but it's
still popular this thing's a piece of shit this thing's a piece of fucking shit um look i'm gonna
put this in here it's popular so i'm gonna use that for my advantage uh swoosh swing before 2079
i'll get that one too right because that's yeah so i can i can pocket this and then i'll give you an
offer the offer here i'm gonna do is uh 90 bucks been easier than i thought thanks with a good
reputation all right i got umbrellas let me put this in here it's sold sold sold sold sold sold
so nobody wants to buy this uh monalisa what else we got what is this for no it's already up there
one friend of mine gave this to me so i don't know much about it fixie made bag okay perfect
condition by the way this is beautiful this is absolutely beautiful very beautiful okay what else
have we got here this is a nice stitch this looks like a custom made stitch by the fx fx xx brand
whereas fx xx where is it come on gwen where are you come on gwen where is it there's uh this is the um
ff fabric you got that right good this is also uh royals love these eco-friendly objects
i'll hold on to that one uh what else we got what's the year 2080 yeah we'll get a signature on it
okay well who's this it was on it you or there you go who's this a painter in protest against
the fixer project in 2079 she donated umbrellas with her signature on them in the fixie okay so
this is an artist that's correct dead she's dead i don't think she's dead just because you're fixed
it doesn't mean you're dead because he doesn't mean dead yeah how do we how do you know fixie
means dead is it dead that's only for art fixie counts as dead fixie equals dead i don't know if
i believe that but you know what we'll do this have you paid attention yeah but a fixie makes
you like a zombie person doesn't kill you you are you considered dead well let's see how how if you
guys are right please don't say if you're not sure shut up okay um dead dead artist if you guys are
wrong i'm gonna be upset dead artist is it a lie i think i just made this up no no no no no no no
whatever it's not a piece of artwork yeah you guys are wrong you're disappointing i never thought
how could you hide cards to make a deal you've been doing it more than once or twice
that made you a huge profit right i can't believe you're not yet reported
you're meaning to report me you want me to do it you want i would never report you
i may not report you but for now i may say something bad things about you how much is
the seemingly meaningful paper oh shut up i have verified it three times hi i'm trying to get a
gift from my cousin do you have anything to recommend what about some filters well it's
a gift anyway so i want some branded thing but at the same time i want it to be special
you know there's some products of the that that the brands genuinely don't make
marks of the brands genuinely don't make do you have anything um i have the mona lisa you want
a hoverboard genuinely generally i look i'm i'm reading a book for six and a half hours i'm gonna
say a word wrong sometimes um is this a this is like a branded thing i don't think i have
anything do you want this it's branded but too ordinary it's branded many of these things
branded no i don't have i don't have anything sorry absolutely destroyed on fixer water
what the fuck i don't have special secret branded stuff that you want i don't know what you want
there we go it's a big sale i also gotta think about when the stream is gonna end tonight
because i'm starting i'm starting to get a little winded let her see the secret menu
i want to see the secret menu yeah we're gonna add the secret menu sure i'll show you the secret
menu what we do is we put this fucking orange goo all over everything and say it's a secret
nothing do you like thousand island dressing because it's on everything as a secret
but he said oof where are the animal style hoverboards right you get it you get it oh what was it
uh i thought i thought i was like what's happening with the cat i'm sensitive okay
i kind of want to just junk this i don't want this in my inventory um all right so i i wonder if i
do i need to see the end i kind of like feel like we need to see at the end how this game ends right
how much longer do you think this is maybe have more than like an hour or so i don't know oh shit
b3 right is there a long time left probably i don't know it's hard to tell all right where b2 so b3
about two hours maybe it says it says about eight hours on how long to be
three houses left um i can i can i not buy this b3 right one room new room it's not open there are
30 days in the game and you're on day 12 oh like halfway you have to go in the morning oh it's
apparently 30 in-game days huh hmm what do i want to do about this um okay i got a plan i got a plan
here's the plan plan is so the the streams next week next weekend because remember i'm a
weekend andy i was gonna do delta rune sims 3 mod apocalypse and this let's do this so we'll
probably do okay so now that delta rune has been out for a day how long is delta rune chapter 2
is it possible to do both of these about four it's like four to six four to eight depending
hmm okay interesting like three to four four to eight three to five okay i think we can do
them both it's like yeah i usually go on the longer side i we need to see the end right
but i can't stream tomorrow i want to see the end all right if we have to do if we have to do three
days next week i'll do that but i don't think we're gonna have to current speedrun is it can
take one hour or 12 depending how much you dig around why don't you speak up streaming the week
uh i'll explain this for a lot of the new people here so i used to do like four days a week i
streamed like oh tuesday thursday friday and like sunday right i do like three four days a week
uh but i ran through an annoying medical problem that made it so it was hard to sit down or stand
or even the same place for more than three four five six hours of time and it was actually causing
me a lot of problems um i dialed back my streams because it was physically painful to just like
kind of sit here or stand i tried kind of it's difficult so i pulled the streams back and since
doing that i've actually felt a little better i'm able to kind of move around i'm able to do some
more things and it gives me more time to work on the big projects that i really want to work on
so it's kind of a win-win in a way streaming less means i feel a bit better and way more interesting
kind of projects can be worked on too at the same time gives me more time but if i'm able to and
that's why a weekend andy makes the most sense because streaming like saturday all right you're
gonna see me on saturday and i'll see you next saturday or like hey i'll see you saturday and
sunday right that's easy so doing weekday streams is always kind of like well which what day do i
pick i guess i'll just do it on tuesday or i guess i'll do it on friday right having those set in
stone it's gonna be like friday saturday or sunday makes it a little easier to kind of plan what i
want to do uh but i'm not against streaming more but i don't want to do what i was doing before
so it's going to be very rare to see more than two streams a week on this channel and sometimes it
might be one i don't want to fuck around with this because i've been feeling a little bit better
and one of the big contributors has been i'm not sitting in this chair for like eight hours four or
five days a week because my streams used to be way longer too i used to i used to sit here till
at least it was like my stream average was like seven and a half to eight and a half hours
so i really want to keep myself honest here and do that kind of explains why but it look if i feel
like i'm gonna do it i'm gonna do it it's never a guarantee but we'll see so i think we can do
this next weekend simpson's hit and run imagine you're a streamer and you develop anti-streamer
disease i mean sometimes it feels like that i'll be honest anti-streamer disease uh yeah so all
right i'll see you guys next weekend we'll call it here i think it's a good place to do it thanks
for watching as always i'm gonna go get some food because i don't want to go too much longer if there
really is another like four to five hours left in this game i kind of want to see the end i feel
like we're invested at this point and again my only complaint of this game is i wish i could
not have it go through the text before i press the button that's okay that's one of the only
complaints uh but i'll see you on let's go with uh friday friday we're gonna do sims mod hell
saturday we're gonna do delta rune and possibly this if delta rune takes a long time then maybe
you'll see a stream on monday we'll see i will see you next week oh sunday sorry i'll see you
next weekend let's see how many how many people subbed there's a lot have a great night see you
then psycho uh yeah friday at 2 p.m and after we do the sim stuff uh i'm trying to think of some
there's a lot of other things we can do i have a list of games to play after next weekend there's
probably going to be a couple of pre-stream polls so those will come back because i have a lot of
options and i'm not sure which ones to do do any one of them to be honest and that's right it's
my birthday week coming up this week so it'll be 36 pretty old getting up there not 40 yet though
that's the big one 36 that's old that's not too old but it's old enough hub happy hobbit day
are you gonna be a 40 year old streamer i don't know i have no idea retire at 39 retire 39 364
days you gotta make it to 37 um i have no idea it's the rest of the time that i spend on the
internet here and do content creation in quotes like influencer e-clown it's when i'm not having
fun anymore when i think i've had my fill and i think it's over i mean you'll know i this is
really important though i don't want to just turn this stream on because i feel like i have to or
like i'm forcing myself to i want it to be fun i don't want you guys to think that i'm just like
turning it on just because like i fucking has to that's the number one thing that i care about on
this stream is is it a fun environment am i having a good time am i actually enjoying myself
or do you think it's fun i don't want to be like a old crabby like washed up asshole that like
should have probably stopped but just didn't you know what i mean like i don't want that to happen
so i don't have a set date for that i don't have a time frame for that stream till you're 80 he's
already washed up uh-oh so it's too late now i'll see you on friday have a good week everybody
we're gonna do the sims 3 first because i really want to get that out of the way it's been ready
for like three weeks i just didn't want to be a sims andy and we'll uh we'll see soon take care
of yourselves good night goodbye uh i had to come back for a second this is an emergency schedule
change i just realized i have an appointment on friday emergency schedule change it's gonna be
saturday sunday and possibly monday emergency schedule is changing sorry about that all right
see you saturday see you saturday goodbye take care good night emergency meeting