Hello everybody. Sorry I'm late again. I said last night I was like, you know, we're not gonna be
late today, but then I had to get some stuff ready. I had to do some stuff like it typically is.
I want to be starting at like 3 33 ish pm pacific time, but man am I pushing that forward now.
This is an outlier though. Don't expect streams to start like this.
Really gonna be trying to stay consistently like we were for the first couple of months here
at like 5 to 6 pm eastern around like three ish pm pacific. Oh I got the wrong,
what's even on the title right now? Bird? How is this done? Pretty, oh fuck, hold on.
Hotline, yes this is dog. I don't know. I just, I need it for it just to, for a second. I'll
change it in a second. There we go. Okay, is it changed? Because I want to make sure that
the VOD's gonna be all fucked up if I don't do that. That's, that was a, I had a tenth
of a second to figure that. I'm gonna change that title, don't worry. I'm gonna play hotline
Miami 2 tonight. Oh I need to put these teabags somewhere. I have two teabags that I don't know
what to do with and I'm not putting them on my nice desk. I guess they can go right here.
Hello, yes this is dog. Yeah I know that's a terrible fucking shitty title.
Just give me like, just give me like a 15 second minute. I gotta get these teabags out
of here. Go through, right? Well I'll just get rid of them when I take a break here in
a little bit. But anyways, I hope you guys are doing well. Let me just make a tweet and
we will get started. Give me one minute. Okay, as the motorcycle goes by. So yeah, hotline Miami 2.
Welcome everybody. I'm gonna make sure from the birdhouse yesterday, the chair isn't on
the right spot. I need to move that. Why is it? All right, there we go. Is that better?
Does that feel better? My mouse pad, this is a gamer game. I gotta make sure my mouse
pad's in the right place. Oh, sorry I bumped ya. Okay, think. I think I'm ready. How's the bird doing?
Uh, bird's doing all right. What bird? What? Oh the birdhouse. Okay, I got a bird now.
I'm never gonna finish this game. Well I finished the last one. Is this one
worse than the last one? All right, I'm gonna do a new game. I'm ready. I'm gonna get the
first act coming in here. And you need the audio too, don't you? Uh, it's kind of quiet,
like very quiet. For some reason. I'll put it on in a minute here. Hold on, don't worry.
Uh, man, this party stinks. I fucking hate these people. Who invited all these
morons. Dot, dot, dot, dot, dot. Uh, what do you guys think about tonight? We gonna do it?
Um, I have my door. I gotta close my door. Okay, there we go. He's talking about chat.
Where's the face cam? No, I'll, I'll, just, I'll, god damn it. Do you guys really want a camera?
Do I have to put a face cam on? All right, well, let me get to the end of the cut scene. Just
wait. What do you guys think about tonight? We gonna do it? I don't see why not. I'm sick
of this shit. Yeah, let's do it. Uh, I like the duck bill guy's my favorite. The weapons
are in the car, right? So we are actually doing this. I thought he was gonna scream. He
has a screaming face. Game audio. I know, I know. I just gotta get to the end of the
cut scene. I can't, if I hit escape, then I'm gonna like fuck it all up, aren't I?
Let's do it. All right, here we go. Why was that so loud? Why is this so much louder than
the game? What the fuck? All right, this, is that better? Don't ask me why the MNU
for some reason is five times louder than the actual video game. I feel like I'm shooting
you guys with a fucking laser. How's that? It's a little better, right? Louder. Ow! Uh,
I don't, I can't, why can I not go any louder? What the fuck is happening? Why is my volume
mixer so fucked up? Does that help? No, dude, I'm at max fucking volume on Windows.
Well, that's okay. Odd, but whatever. All right, so that's, I guess that's as long
as I can fucking make it. That's what it's gonna have to be like, apparently. All right,
here we go. Uh, party sucks. W A S D, just like the last game. It's got puking in there.
I can leave through here, get in the van. Ow, it's so much louder. What the hell is happening right
now? What is going on? It just shouldn't be like this.
All right, what in the name of God was that all about?
That can't be that fucking loud. That's too loud. I think that's a reasonable level.
Maybe like one more. All right, I don't even need a fucking tutorial. I'm a goddamn natural.
Look at how loud this is. Are you sure about this? What the fuck? Turn on face cam.
Oh my God, fine. Jesus Christ. I gotta go through this door, I think. Yep, I think it's
okay. How do I open the door? Can you not just open doors like this? No, you can. Something's
wrong with my audio sync. I can't really fix it, so I'm gonna have to deal with it
for now. Ooh, that hurt. There's no bullets in that gun. What the fuck? How many bullets
do I have? Where do I see? Oh, just empty. Combo beginner, nice. Okay, that's cool.
Got it. Ooh, I almost didn't get it. No, give me that. What are you guys saying? Get it? Okay.
Ah! Oh my God. Okay, I gotta pay attention. Oh, shift. I forgot I could do shift. I forgot
about that. Damn it. It's gonna go fucking fast, man. Fuck it. No, I'm not. Damn it. Holy shit,
how did I stay alive? All right, slow it down. This is like kind of hard for the first
level. I guess I could go in the left room. I need a melee weapon. I'm alerting the whole
horde. Okay, that works. Who the fuck are you? Oh God. Play one more guy and then
that's it, right? Just one more guy? All right, got it. That was fucking ridiculous.
I got these bags, though. Whatever. Go to car. I don't... Where is the...
Was the car down a level or what? No, it's right there. What are you guys saying? Entire stream
is broken. What's wrong with my stream? I don't know what you guys are talking about, but
I don't know if there's a problem with the stream that I can't really fix it, so
I'm sorry. Happy Halloween, sir. I'll give you 14 tithes or your pizzas are on the counter.
Okay, cool. Enjoy your meal and watch out for ghosts tonight. Okay, bye. More free food.
That's pretty cool. I like that. What? I don't understand. Turn off the cam? What the
fuck are you guys talking about? Fine. Turn cam off. What's going on? Turn it back on and
sync it. Is it fixed now? Is it better? Don't even look good. Are you... Okay. In a
stressful day, you wouldn't believe what they have been doing. Stand up. I...
Stand up. I don't understand. Stand like... I don't get it. What? What's happening? Stand up.
It's fixed. Jesus. I don't know... Oh, this is falling. Hold on. Hold on. I fucked it
up. There we go. Okay. There we go. Nice. I believe what they've been doing. I should
probably go home and get some sleep. All right, you have a nice night. You too,
sweetheart. Okay. I don't know what that means, but that's fine. Go to the car,
I guess. I don't... I mean, I think I have to... Second scene. I... I'm playing
without fucking headphones tonight, guys. I don't like the sounds. They scare me. Got
it. Got it. That's blocking the... That's blocking the shit. Hold on. Got it. No,
wait. Watch out for the guy in the room. I gotta be careful here. Sound effects
are too loud. The music is... I... Hold on. I can fix it. Hold on. Let me
give it... Give me a second. Maybe that'll help. Better? What happened to
my cursor? Okay. There we go. I think that's good. Yeah. I think we're
good. One guy in here. Two guys, actually. Let's go... Let's try to get a
door and then smash, right? Oh, that guy didn't see me. How? Empty. Empty.
Empty. We're good. There we go. Up the floor and we're good. That should get us
up there. This way. Oh, I thought that... I didn't think that was a wall.
Oops-a-daisy. Fuck. Fuck. Damn it. Oh my god. This is too stressful
for me. Can you believe this shit? I think I got him. Ah, I just gave it
to him. Oh, that was close. That was real...
Anymore? I don't think there's anymore. Ay-ay-ay-ay-ay-ay-ay-ay-ay!
Fuck! Oh my god! I blown it! Oh! Fuck. All right, I'll get it. I'll be fine.
Don't worry. Everything's gonna be fine. I got it. All right. Let me think
about this logically here. I'm gonna say punch through door, kick guy,
get them both in two shots. One shot, three shot. Got it. Nice.
All right. Just... How many guys down here? Just the two, right?
Oh, come on. That was lucky. All right. Oh, we got one guy.
What about down there, though? I'm scared to even go down there. It's just
one, two, three. I should get them very quickly here. The door got the fucking
way again. Got it. Okay. Go to the car. Well,
this isn't good. Do I have to fight this? Am I in trouble here?
Drop your weapon and get down on the ground now. Don't shoot. I'm
detective. Here's my badge. I'm sorry, sir. Lower your weapons, boys.
What's the situation in there? Look for yourself. It's a bloodbath in there.
Man, sometimes I hate this city. What about the car? Okay.
That's kind of interesting. I go to the car. Which car? My car or their car?
Okay. There it is. Nice. C+. All right. That's fine. It's first
level. C plus streamer strikes again. That was the worst joke this year.
That was the last... What do you mean? You don't know what you're talking
about. Turn the face cam back on. I'll turn it back on
when I feel like it's necessary to turn back on. Another murder case, huh?
Yeah. It looks like you've got a serial killer on your hands. Same MO as the
guy you found last week. Message and all.
I'm innocent. They forced me to do it. Yeah, right. I haven't heard that
before. The guy must be some kind of psycho, huh?
Creeps me out. Guess it'll make the press happy, though.
Guess it'll make it happy. Okay. I don't know. I have no idea.
Seems they need... Oh, look. It's a love for the...
This just seems a bit too standard. No gore details. God, the city sure makes
your skin thick, doesn't it? I was born with thick skin. Have you
guys found any clues? Not really. He got his throat slit.
Haven't found the murder weapon yet. No fingerprints. No witnesses. Nothing.
I'll let you know. Anything turns up. All right. Fucking bye.
Bye. You do that. I'll head down to the station and get started on the
paperwork. All right. Have a nice night, sir.
Yeah, we'll see about that. I don't know about whether I...
What? Who knows? I think it's a kind of an issue.
Yeah. I'm sorry. You're a fucking dork? Hey, I'm just trying to enjoy Hotline
Miami 2 with camp tonight. Yeah. Let's see what happens here.
Oh, what the hell? Who am I? A new character?
Good day. This is Eric from Miami Auto Repairies. I'm calling to tell you
that we have finished service. Hello, who is this? Let me talk to
your boss, okay? Swing on by Northworth 12th Avenue place
and pick. Hey, I'm talking here. We guarantee the
best service in town. Don't you hang up on me, damn it.
Show some goddamn respect. This looks like fat me.
Let's watch me fucking ace this round. So this is a new
character? Third scene. Hard news. This is where it happened. I gotta
get the fucking cam on for this one, you know what I'm saying?
Lethal throws. Yeah, let's get it on. Let's fucking jam this.
This side over here. There's a window. Oh, they can shoot through windows.
Somebody's there. Nah, I gotta get these two. Hit the guy
at the door when he comes out. Take his gun. He's slow to kill with
melee. Lethal throws though. I gotta remember
that. Lethal throws. Lethal throws. Whoa!
Wow, fucking window. Actually, fuck it. All right. What about the window?
That can see right through the window, right? One guy up here. Guy through the
window. I'm gonna get the guy through his own window.
Like that. One more bullet for the guy in here with the gun. Watch this. Ready.
Three, two, one, action. Whoa! Okay, I'm fine.
Ah! Oh, my fucking keys. I hit caps lock. Lethal throw is... fuck. All right.
Get up with the guy over here. Yeah, I had the same idea, dickhead.
All right, guy through the window. That's not a lethal throw.
I hit the door. Okay, that's fine. Anybody? Is there another guy in this?
Right here. Oh, that didn't go through. Fuck, it's empty now. He's coming for me.
He's coming for me. No! Pick up the... Oh, fuck!
Okay, I'm fine. I want that gun on the ground right there.
Get... get it! Okay, I got it. Okay, who do we got for guns?
I don't think there's anybody left with a gun. There's only the guy up there
with the gun. There's a window. So we're gonna have to go... we're gonna
have to snipe somebody. This guy right here. Let's see if
I can get him. Okay, got that guy. Did it pull anybody
else? I'm still paranoid for this guy right here.
Dammit, I was even trying to shoot you! I was trying to shoot him!
Oh, that guy's a gun. All right, I'm going the other way.
Didn't get a double, but that's fine. Where's he going? All the way around?
Give me your gun. Uncam on each corner of the screen.
No, I can't do that. I'm gonna get sniped by somebody else. I'm gonna be
so angry about it. Holy fuck, that was so panic
inducing. I don't know what the hell I was thinking.
All right, anything else in here? Give me a fresh gun.
What else I can grab? People are gonna get so angry with me.
Dude, you missed the mask! Go get the mask, dude!
Did I really hit the plant right there? What do we got? We got a guy with a gun.
Watch out for the guy. Get the seat through the glass.
Ah, and I didn't get shot. Holy fuck, how? Holy fuck, I'm being so stupid
right now. Okay, stop, stop. Cool down.
This guy right through the glass. You stupid idiot!
Oh, damn it. Oh, now I'm going too fast. I can slow down.
Fuck, I had it. I just had it too. I had it. I had it.
I think I got two people there. Holy fuck. Let me get a closer look.
There's nobody with a gun in there. There's a guy with a gun up there.
What happened? Why did I just spin around like that? That was wild.
Guy, there's a guy. What was that? Why did I just like spin
fucking around like 180 degrees? Turned my aimbot on for some reason.
I'm not using one of those. Ass right here. All right, one guy here.
Sorry, he's gonna come all the way around and I'm gonna throw it at him.
What happened? Is he dead? Is that a lethal throw? What the fuck did I do?
Oh my god, what did I do? Oh my fucking god, what the hell?
Does every throw kill? All right, I'm sorry. I have to turn
the music down. It's so loud in my ear and it's
fucking my brain. All right, here we go. It's the, I shouldn't,
don't even lock on to somebody. He's gonna come through. Shoot him.
My goodness, Jeremy. Get good. Get good. You know what I mean? That's what people
say nowadays. They go, get good. No, hold on. It's better than that.
They go, get good. I can't do it. I drank too much fucking tea and my
like throat is all closed up. That means you're allergic to tea.
I don't know what I'm talking about. Okay, that guy's a gun.
How safe am I here? This is only rebel chill.
This is only rebel deadedated rare. Right? Somebody laughing at that. Wasn't
that funny? Fuck. Yeah, remember that like funny
video? That like, that was like, cute video.
I don't have a fucking gun. Oh, what do I do about this? What do I do?
Still throws. Okay, we're good. That was a real life reaction.
Yeah, dude, if somebody is chasing you with a knife,
stabbing forward at you, you're gonna go, oh no, what the fuck do I do?
That was a real reaction. Is that it? Can I throw the briefcase at him?
This fucking boomer using auto lock. I was told to use that.
I said, somebody said, use auto lock. It helps sometimes. I don't use it all
the time. There you go. That's the C plus
content you signed up for. Now, okay, like a one out of ten
stream is if somebody has a black screen and they were just sleeping,
right? Two out of ten stream is if somebody is
streaming themselves sleeping with the camera on. Three out of ten stream is
building a birdhouse. Four out of ten stream is playing
Hotline Miami with auto lock. Just wait till you fucking see a five out of
ten stream. You're not even gonna know what hit
you. I just went back up. How am I locked? I know it's out here.
All right, it's gonna be more than a C plus. If that's the case, this is a
seven out of ten stream. That's a seven that that's a seven
out of ten stream or sixty nine and ten. Seven to one.
Got a new mask. Ervin. 20 face cams are right. I will crash my computer.
Hi there. Welcome. What can I help you with? I'd like to get a tattoo.
Right, you got anything particular in mind? All right, so every time I see
this guy's face, I keep imagining, I keep seeing like a
hippopotamus mouth. Like where his chin is, that's the
top of the hippopotamus's mouth and there's a big bottom half that's
underneath that. I want an old dixie right here. Okay, sure.
Let me see. Right, how does this Friday sound? That's what you look like.
I don't look like this. Friday, what do you mean? You can't do it now?
It has to be today. It's a special occasion today. I'm celebrating.
Sorry boss, can't help you. We're all booked for days.
Does that so? What kind of business are you running here? You just lost
yourself a customer. You Russian asshole. Whatever you say, boss.
Yeah, just you guys wait. Just you guys wait for the Bionic Boomer stream.
It's gonna be a lot of fun. I'd like to welcome our next guest on the show,
famous from critically acclaimed movies such as Blue Ocean, The Calm, and Land
of Trees. Here's Martin Brown. Hi Martin, how are you?
I'm good. Now your latest film is a bit of a step in a new direction for
you. A lot of people are surprised by this.
Some are even calling you a sellout. Bionic Boomer tonight
or Riot. Do you understand that I can't get keyboard pants and like laser eye
tracking devices that this is gonna take like a couple of weeks to put
together. A lot of people are surprised by this.
Some are calling you a sellout. What's your response to that? A sellout,
huh? How do you mean? Well some are saying
that Midnight Animal is just another slasher flick.
That's not how I see it. I have wanted to do this for a long time.
Kill kids. Strangle them. Beat people's heads in.
Rip their eyes out. Just listen to them. Oh my god.
What the fuck? I finally get to do that. Okay.
Don't look at me like that. What? I say this is a dream, right?
What do you mean? This is all, this is just a dream, right? I'm not sure I
follow. Okay pause. You think this is a
dream? Well then maybe it's time to wake up.
Who are you? Who am I? I'm not the one being interviewed here, am I?
I think I should be the one asking the questions. This movie you're making, you
know how it ends. I believe there's a pretty big twist at
the end. I doubt you'll like it. In fact, I don't think anyone will. Maybe
you ought to get out before it's too late.
I don't think so. You really enjoy hurting other people, don't you?
It's just a film. Just a film, huh? That's one way to look at it.
Oh and then right after that, Batman and Superman are like shitting in a
stall together. And like you can hear the loud fart
poop noises. Nobody, nobody knows what I was just
doing there. What are you talking about? That's,
wow, I must be out of touch. That was a robot chicken segment and we moved to
another one. Like don't, what are you talking about?
Don't you remember like robot chicken? It would do like the shh and change to
like the superheroes that are really cool but
they just like fart in each other and like get,
just get it, right? Does anybody get it? You generally aren't in your head.
Are you sure? It looks like the police is here.
The girl must have told on you. You better go along obediently, they'll take
you to her. What's that you want? Well that's what you want, isn't it?
Click. Hold it right there. Why am I wearing this mask?
We're here to arrest you. You need to come with us. We'll take you down
to the station. Do you understand what I'm saying?
Apparently not. You can't tell me that robot chicken
is a boomer show. That, that was, that's like still on the air.
And if it's not, it was off the air like five years ago.
You know what you've been up to and you're gonna fry for it. Girls upstairs
giving us her full statement right now.
It's gonna be on their way down here for you. Until then you're stuck with
me. I'd like to ask why did you do
what you did? Do you even know you, you don't even
know yourself? Do you, what, can the phone fucking, somebody pick up the phone?
Look at me. You're fucked. Completely fucked in the head.
Aren't you? Why else would anyone be killing kids in a pig's mask, huh?
Oh my fucking god. It's the phone. You should answer it.
I'll say it again. There is no phone. I don't see no phone and I don't hear no
phone, okay? It's just a figment of your
imagination, you hear me? You're insane. A maniac. And soon enough
you will pay for your crimes. The telephone. You're not gonna answer.
There's just no point talking to you, is there? What the fuck?
You know what needs to be done. It's not like even looking. It's like he
wants you to click. Do I, is this the, what the
fuck is this game? The last game was like answering phone calls
and like fighting people. Why do I have to be this like creepy guy?
And like, anything else? This one has a strange elaborate story.
Whoa, I could break the toilet. I know it was a TV, you know what I'm saying.
You guys are like inside my head, you know what I mean by that.
I, get off of him. What are you doing? Hi.
Okay, all right. Both dead, right? I'm not gonna shoot any weapons. I'm not
gonna shoot a gun. Let me just see if I can do this without.
You guys coming around here? Am I safe? Oh, not safe, not safe. Oh, damn it.
I would have had it potentially too there. Fuck, what am I doing?
What about up there? Let me try going, no. I'm gonna wait for this patrol to go
by and I'm gonna go up. Actually, no, no, no, no, no, no. I
get a better idea. Never mind.
Yeah, I used to get shot right in the fucking face. It was a decent idea
and it still is. I'm gonna try it again. Give me a fucking break.
How did it, you don't even notice that you, how do you not notice this?
What the fuck? How did you not notice that?
Why do you have the intelligence of the orcs from Shadow of Mordor? Come
on. Where the fuck did you guys even
come from? I'm gonna do that. Shit, I'm gonna
throw it at him and then I'm gonna sit in this room.
Okay, give me the gun. I have items in here now.
Now it's just a question of trying to get this done.
Okay, so now I can get, I should be able to cleanly kill this guy right
here without a problem, right? One, two, three, go. Guy in this
room, I'm gonna get him. Holy fuck you! Okay, calm down. The
trolls are gonna, I'm gonna forget about them.
What about over there? Yeah, this guy that way.
These guys don't have guns though. Oh shit.
No! God damn it. God damn it. Oh come on man, what the hell was I
doing there? There's only a couple guys left. Oh
you fucking door. Oh you fucking door. Is that guy live?
Just gave them a wall. I hate, I hate it, I hate it, I hate it, I can't
believe it. God damn it, this level is
really fucking hard. Come on man, I had it right there too.
This shit was done. How did he not throw it?
Holy shit, this is insane. All right, get like the sweaty fucking hand
syndrome out of here. Light my fucking hand, I'm like
covered in water. 13 bullets. Okay, good. I think I did it.
Okay, just, I'm gonna keep the pistol. Just be very careful here.
There's no reason to freak out. I'm gonna wait till they turn around. There's
only three guys left. Four. That guy doesn't have a gun.
Nine bullets. That was a monster energy spread.
I don't even know what that means, but I guess I'll agree with you. There he
is, right here. One, two, three. Where's the
patrol? They're up there. That's a monster
energy. Stop distracting me. Oh my lord, I almost lost it right
there. I almost just lost it and I thought I didn't, I didn't. I just
barely got it. Oh man, okay. Anybody else have a gun? These two
guys don't have guns. Only one guy has a gun in there, but
he does have one. No, two guys with guns. Got me the
gun here. Okay, let's go for it. Nobody up or down,
right? No one's gonna like snipe me. Oh, give me your gun. Oh,
just go? What do you mean just go? Stay in here and you'll be safe. I'm
gonna go see what's going on. Don't open the door until I get back
no matter what. Just go. That's easier said than
oh, the fucking window. I didn't even know there was a window here.
Well, I didn't know those things. How did I not shoot the guy with the gun?
What's this guy? Why is Death Eater here? What's no, Reaper?
Why is Reaper from Overwatch? Death Eater?
Whatever his name is. Reaper. I am terrified to go over here. This
only has one bullet. Alright, where's Reaper? There he is.
Oh, fuck you. Oh my god, is he dead? He's dead, right?
Is he? He's not dead. Is he dead now? He's not dead now.
The head off. Okay, got it. I can't take his guns? Oh, oh, wait a minute!
Oh, no! Oh, fuck. No, god damn it. Damn it.
And I have to fight Reaper again. I think that's the only way you can
kill him. You have to like rip his head off.
Alright, this time I'm not gonna just run over there. There's
one, two. Anybody down there? I think there is. I can't see that far.
There's a guy right there with a gun. Oh, no. Is he running up here?
I don't know which way he's gonna go. I'm hiding. I don't have any guns. I
don't have any guns. Guns, guns. Give me a gun.
Like, pull him into the bathroom? He has a shotgun, but I gotta get into
this room, I think. Is there anybody else in that room?
No, there's not. It's, it's, it's of these windows.
Oh, my goodness. Why can I not go over there?
What kind of aim do you have? What kind of aim do you have?
What kind of aim? What's that? You shot,
I locked onto him and he shot to the left and he shot to the right of him.
What is the aim that I, what kind of aim is that?
Oh, fuck. This is bad. Maybe not. No, I need, give me the gun.
Fuck you. What do I do about Reaper? I can't believe it.
I had it too and it was done and I did, I just didn't get it done.
Because that, the bullshit shitty aim thing.
All right, get over here, Reaper. Come on.
Why is it always holy? What do you mean holy?
Like, there's nobody else over here. We're gonna shoot Reaper, break his
neck. Sorry, my throat.
I wish I could take his guns. Honest to god. Okay.
Do it again. Maybe I should just go that way.
What is that way? I can't believe it didn't hit.
Actually, no, no, no. I'll be fine. I'll be fine. Oh god,
Jeremy. How did, I got stuck in the wall.
Who the fuck is that guy? Okay. Yeah, I needed
two shots to kill like the, whatever that guy was.
You stupid game. No fucking way. No way. No way. There's no way.
I don't believe it. I don't even believe it was possible.
That's impossible. Yes, I'm doing the movie villain thing at the end of the
movie, but it really is. I understand the villain now. I
know what he's saying. How it's not possible.
Damn it. Why did that have to happen? He just like
instantly fucking 180 pixel turned on me.
Give me a break. I got stuck on the fucking wall.
I wish it would prioritize guns that have ammo in them.
How do I check that box? Get in this room.
Room to room. Guy over there. They both have guns. I have four shots.
Did I get them both? I did not get them both.
Okay, now. I didn't. My brain wasn't prepared for a guy to come around the
corner like that. Oh my god. Why?
It was over. It was fucking over. It was done. And this guy right here.
You don't even have to know. I won't get to walk across the whole map. Did I hear a gunfire?
Have I heard gunfire the entire game? The whole floor?
Now I'll go out on this 600th shot this time. I think I heard something.
I broke the mic. I'm gonna get it this time. I'm gonna be prepared for
guy on the left. Got them both. I did. Okay.
Wait a minute. Wait. No, he's not here.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. I only have two bullets though. I need a
different gun. Does any- I only have- I gotta get
the guns that these guys dropped. Okay. I turn to like Vince McMahon sometimes.
Like I'm casting a wrestling event. Anybody hear that?
Did anybody hear that? Is what I need to know. I only have two bullets.
I have to make a count. Pick up the gun before I do something
where I scream. Okay. I think I got it.
There's that one last guy. I'm not fucking around. I'm gonna go all the
way around because he can shoot me through the glass.
Because there is glass down here. Don't shoot me through the glass. I want to
shoot you through the glass. Okay. Get the keys. I can't go in
here? Who has the key? Oh, Reaper does.
I'm not your fucking girlfriend. Wait. What happened? I have to-
Wait. Wait. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. What? What?
What? Okay. I was about to freaking freak out.
Cut. No need for a retake. That was perfect. This is a movie.
Good job, guys. Spectacular performances. So this is the movie that
the guy was talking about. I only got a few more shots to shoot
before we can move on to editing. Why don't you go grab something to eat
while we put in the new set piece. Make sure you're back in 30 minutes, okay?
Time is money. You heard him, Martin. Time to get up,
Martin. You spent all that time in rage on a movie.
71,000 is the total. That's a pretty good score so far.
I got a better than an A. I got 110 points. I got extra credit.
I remembered what the teacher's favorite candy was because that was the
extra credit question. Good thing I got it. I would have had a
probably a C-. Second act rising. 1991 Miami, Florida.
Ah, the defendant claims that he was ordered to commit these murders through
messages left on his answering machine. Did you investigate these claims? Yes,
we did. And what did you find? Well, the
defendant's answering machine was empty. The tape had been removed.
Did you find anything supporting these claims of threatening phone calls?
No, sir, we did not. I see. No further questions.
You say you found no physical evidence supporting my client's claims. Then
what about phone records? Surely the police would have
no difficulty accessing such information. Indeed, we didn't investigate
the defendant's phone records. And did you find any calls on record that
could support my client's claims? We did, sir. The defendant seems
to have received phone calls that match the time frame which he
suggests. But did you manage to trace these calls? If so,
where did they come from? We traced the calls to a nightclub
called the Golden Truck Stop. Yes, now my client claims that he was
coerced by the Russian mafia to commit the crimes for which he was
now being prosecuted. Do the police have any knowledge of
ties between the Golden Truck Stop and the Russian mafia that could
support my client's claims? The venue has been linked to several
mob related crimes in the past. Yes, however, that would be all. Thank
you. No further questions. The witness may step down. The court will
now be adjourned. Proceedings will continue tomorrow at 11am.
Meanwhile, the defendant will remain in police custody. Who's
that? I think that's supposed to be me. Food in the trash? No. Time
to make a phone call. Leave a message on somebody's machine.
You've reached the Miami Police Department. How may I help you?
I'd like to talk to Detective Pardo. Tell him it's from Evan.
One moment, please. Click. What do you want, Evan? I'm in the
middle of something here. Hi, Manny. I'm at the courthouse doing
research on that masked maniac. What's that got to do with me?
Well, they mentioned the Golden Truck Stop. Something about mob
connections. So, I was wondering if you know anyone that I can
talk to. That's privilege information. You know I can't
talk about things like that. Look, I'm really busy here.
1-800-HIGH-SCHOOL-MUSICLE. Don't be like that now. You owe
me one, remember? Fine. Go to Northwest 37th Avenue. Ask
for Petrov and tell him I sent you. Can't promise he'll
talk, but it's the only name I've got. Don't call me at
work again, okay? No more favors. Okay. Why is this just
the courtroom from Chrono Trigger? When you get tried?
These are the same models. All right, let's go. Okay. Why is
everybody holding a boombox? Are these the guys playing the
music? Is it a protest or something? All right. Cameras.
Fifth scene. First trial. Here we and here we go. The
Joker. The Joker. The Joker. The Joker. The Joker. The
Joker. Oh my god. Did he just make a Joker reference? I'm
here to see Petrov. Tell him Detective Pardo sent me.
No, I don't think so. If you don't have an invitation,
you better leave. Okay. What the fuck was that? Am I
bringing him back to life? Hold on. I killed him and now
I'm bringing him back to life.
What? What the fuck was that, Jeremy? It was the
fucking Joker. Help. Somebody call an ambulance. There's
been an accident. Is there anyone here? Oh, pick up
the gun. What are you doing? Why can I not pick the
gun up? What? Am I like non-violent? Oh shit. Okay. I
gotta go. Oh, you idiot. You idiot. Idiot.
What about the guys with the guns? Oh, you idiot. I get
it. I get it. I get it. I get it. Okay. I get it. I'm
disarming the guns. I get it. I understand it now. So
they can't use them. I get it. What's that guy with
the fucking gun right there? Oh, you idiot. Oh shit.
He got up. Oh fuck. Okay. Get it. Go get the gun.
And excuse me, all of you watching at home. I'd like to
know what killed me behind the corner. I'd like to
have an explanation as to who did it. Oh, that
guy. Okay. Thanks. Thanks for the explanation. Okay.
That's actually pretty good. I'd rather go.
Does this guy fight? Is the guy gonna attack me?
Okay. So after they get knocked down, they don't
care anymore. Is that what I'm understanding? All
right. Okay. And if I, I clearly very clearly like
I punched him. I did. I punching him. He's being
punched. That's all I wanted. Fuck. Oh my God.
Oh my God. Now that they all see me. Okay. Is
there anybody? I can't tell. I need to get that
gun. I need that back. I need that fucking thing
back. Nobody else, right? Nobody else. Nobody
else. Oh, I didn't do it right. I didn't do it
right. I didn't do it right. I didn't do it
right. You can knock them out with space bar.
What are you talking about? Isn't that what
I'm doing? Okay. So that's why I didn't do it
because it takes fucking forever to do that. I'd
love to know what world that was. What fucking
world are we living in when that doesn't kill
them? Okay. Put this down here. Disarm. Disarm it.
I can't disarm that. Okay. Well, I don't even need
to. All right. I'm gonna get this motherfucker
right now. And I threw the fucking thing. I just
want to put it down. I just wanted to place it
below me. I didn't have to throw it. I just
whipped it across the game. I'm gonna go
around. Too long. Too long. Too long. That
takes too long. Okay. I got it. Don't fuck
this up. It's an easy throw. Okay. I'm good.
Now the knife. Holy shit. I didn't even see
him. Guy with a gun. Anybody else around
the corner? I'm fucking paranoid. Hold on. Let
me go this way. I don't know. Is there a guy
with a gun up here? No, there's not. Okay.
Wrap around. I just want to see. There is
a kid. There's more. There are more people
up here. I'm gonna go the other way.
Because I gotta throw it at this guy. I got
it. I got it. But the other guys have
guns too. What? What about? What do I do
about that? I think I have to go the other
way. Ugh. No, I don't. Here he comes. Oh,
fuck. Anything else? Okay. I disarmed the
gun. Just two guys with melee and a guy
with a gun. Just wait till he stand up.
I'm not taking the- I'm not taking the
time to do the animation. How far up is
he? All the way up, right? It's good,
right? He's done. Spacebar's not doing
anything. One guy left. I have to sneak
up behind him and throw this in the
back of his head. Holy fuck, he
turned around really quickly. Okay.
Thank god. There's more of this shit.
There's more of this shit. I can't hit
him through the window. All right.
Disarm. Who's left? Two more guys. Oh,
fuck. Not through the window. Not through
the window. Don't get me through the
window. Disarm their guns. This is too-
No, that guy can see me through the
window. Oh, Kenny? Is anybody below? If
I go over there, I- you know what I'm
saying? If I do this, he can see me
through the fucking window.
Oh, fuck. Dude, do it. Do it. Get off
of him. How do I get off this guy?
How do I get off this guy? Oh, okay.
I got it. I'm good.
Okay. This game's- this game is so
stressful. It's too- how am I gonna
get into this guy? I have to throw
it at him. I have to throw it at him.
Oh, my bike. I just like-
Okay, I did it, right? What's left?
Somebody down here?
Are there windows down here? Okay, no
windows, but I gotta make this good.
Oh, should I not be killing?
I just threw him in the fucking bathtub.
I need those.
Who's this? Who the hell are you?
Oh, hey. There's a cutscene going on
here. Ah, I-
Do I not- um, are you Petrov?
I'm writing a book about the mask maniac.
Detective Pardo told me I could talk to
you about it. Detective Pardo told you
that. A friend of yours.
That's right, sir. Not a very good
friend. I take it I'm ready.
Son sending you here all of all
places. You know, I reckon you're
right about that, sir. Okay, give me
control back and I'm gonna get it.
Guy in the- hold on, I gotta look at it again.
This book you're writing must be very
important. Risking your life to come
talk to me. Sure, you've got- you've got
balls. What is it you want to know?
You get two questions. Then you get the
fuck out of here.
Okay, I have to turn around. I gotta-
ANS. Hold ANS. Swing around. Swing.
All right, the police claims the
Masked Ritterers were part of a
vigilante movement. Are you of the
same opinion?
No. I don't think they were
vigilantes. They were much too
organized.
They knew our exact locations and had
insight into our inner workings.
I don't know what they were a part
of, but it was a group. No group of
vigilantes.
Why do you think they targeted the
Russian mafia?
What were they after? I can't tell you
what they were after, but
they effectively destroyed our whole
organization and then they were gone.
They knew what they were doing and
they seemed to be trained very well.
We caught a couple of them alive,
tried to break them. None of them
talked, not a single one.
All right, no more questions. Get the
hell out of my sight. Here we go.
Okay. What do I do about this? Okay,
we're fine.
Okay, we're good. Bad end. Bad end.
Why is it the bad end? What do you
mean bad end?
Actual maniac. You killed someone.
I accidentally, because I was panic
pressing the button.
Don't listen to them. Don't listen to
chat.
Well, that's all right. That's a D+.
That's the first time I've had a D+.
I've only had Cs in the first game.
And Bs and As. Still passing grade. I'm
okay.
What a day. Did something happen?
No, well, yeah. That guy Petrov, he
wouldn't see me.
Almost got beaten up just trying to get
in. Hey, you actually
went there. Didn't figure you would. Man,
sometimes I wonder why I hang out with
you.
When did you become such a douchebag?
Well, I did tell you to write about
the Miami
mutilator instead, didn't I? A much more
sophisticated case.
Really, and you wouldn't have to
talk to them all.
People will have forgotten about those
vigilantes by the time your book's
out.
I accidentally stomped a guy's head to
the wall and blasted his brother's
torso with a shotgun.
Come on. Besides, I bought you a beer,
right? And you didn't really get hurt,
did you?
Let's call it even. Thanks for the
beer and all, but you still owe me one.
All right, all right. Don't forget I'm
putting my job on the line.
If anyone finds out I'm giving you
leads, that'll be it for me.
You'll be fired for incompetence or
misconduct before that happens. I'm
surprised they haven't fired you
already.
I'm tired, let's get out of here. Yeah,
I should get some sleep too. You want
a ride?
I'll take my chances on the bus. Wait,
who the fuck am I? Okay, I'm the
different character now.
All right, did you just try to kill him? I
was not trying to kill him. I just pressed
space on him
to see if there's extra dialogue
sequences. September 2nd, 1991.
So we're going somewhere special
tonight, eh?
Yeah, my friend Jack told me he built
this place down on Northwest AA 184th
Street.
A real shithole. The whole building is
occupied by junkies and lowlifes.
Kind of like this place, huh?
Uh, fuck you, Mark. Anyway, his
sister's been hanging out with these
assholes. Hasn't been
home for weeks. He figured we'd get
her home
and teach her friends a lesson. Wait,
we're doing house calls for your
friends now?
Isn't that pretty much what we did
last time? I didn't hear any
complaints back then.
We can't patrol the streets looking
for scumbags.
We'd be in jail in no time. Yeah,
but I didn't sign up to be no hero
rescuing women and shit. That's just
not my thing. I just want some
action. So you got any better ideas or
should we just stay here and argue
all night?
I sure as hell ain't staying here. I'm
ready to roll. Am I gonna get the
the quack mask?
Fine, I'll come along. But if anything
happens to the girl, it's not my
problem. Got it.
Sure. Okay. Well, whatever. Let's go.
Slot machine? Nice. What is this fucked
up like?
Ghostbusters mobile. Moving up.
Okay, roll dodge. Killing punches. No
weapons. What is roll dodge?
When did I have this? What the fuck?
I guess I just didn't even know I
had this.
Rewind. Killing punches. I like this.
Look glee. All right.
Nice and easy. Left. Right. Look both
ways before you cross the street.
It's easy enough. I can't even pick up
weapons.
Okay, we got gun guys gotta go first.
It was pretty sloppy, but whatever. Guy
with a gun. He's gotta go first or I
can bait the guy with the knife.
Wowee. That was fucking close. Okay.
Lots of guys with guns. Might have to
actually go the other way.
Yeah, let's take these guys out
first. Another door opening down here.
Okay, that's it.
All right, I can go through there.
There's a hole in the wall, but
there's also a guy with a gun.
So it's all about the bait. I could go
down.
I don't really want anyone to shoot in
the middle here. That'll alert
everybody.
I'm thinking, I'm thinking straight
through try to kill both of them in one
punch.
Or eight. That's fine. I see windows.
No, I'm good.
One guy. That guy almost blended in
with the ground.
I almost just ran in here and
screamed. All right. So far so good.
This guy. I don't think, I don't think
this guy has a gun.
It's just the two guys up there and
then one guy. No, that's it, right?
Okay, here we go. I'm just gonna
ambush.
Not yet. No. Anything in the toilet or
anything? Nothing over here? I can't
really go anywhere from here.
All right, ambush this guy. Don't look
at me. Don't look at me. Don't look
at me.
Holy shit. That was almost very bad.
Okay, only got two guys left.
Three, actually. That's a mistake to
call it two.
No, no, no. Go back around.
This has been so clean. I haven't
died once. I'm not gonna ruin this.
I'm gonna go back around down
here.
You actually can't pick up any
weapons. All right, here we go.
Once this guy moves. Oh no, I...
fuck. Where am I standing? Okay.
Almost a disaster. Almost a fucking
complete disaster.
That's it, right? Only one more. Only
one guy left down here in this room.
Clean. As clean as it can be.
Dogs. Does me punt... Can I punch the
dog once and kill it?
Damn it. Okay. There's another guy with a
gun down there, I thought.
Is there? Oh, fuck. There was. Geez.
Geez. Geez, and a dog. Geez.
They're fast, right? They're very
fast.
I knew it was fast. I knew it was
fast too, and I just
wasn't ready for it. My muscle brain
to computer memory.
Where's the other guy? I know you're
down there, you little asshole.
Okay, dog. Get ready for it. You gotta,
you gotta be the aggressor.
Right, you know what I mean? None of these guys have guns.
This should be fairly simple. Holy shit.
He had a gun. I thought that cigarette
was a knife.
What happened? Holy fuck. Why would
they do the animation like that?
I can't... How am I gonna do that room?
I don't know how the fuck I'm gonna
do this room.
Holy shit in my pants and my fucking
face.
Get over here, man. Oh, well, I'm
thinning him out.
I'm gonna try to go around and see
if there's a better opportunity.
Doesn't look like there is.
Is there somebody down here? Somebody
with a gun?
Yep. Yep. Wowee.
How am I supposed to get in this room?
With just, with one punch man?
I have to go in that room on the
right, don't I?
Or I have to pull them out. Holy
shit.
I'm so disappointed. I just, I went
all the way back in my chair and
wrapped my head.
Christ. Oh my god.
Fuck. Damn it. Focusing on the dog.
Jesus Christ. Dog.
Like, how did I get this guy last time?
I debated him and he...
Fuck.
I just, I felt those bullets.
They missed my character and hit
me.
Come on. Why? I'm not, I'm just
clicking on the dog.
I'm not hitting space on him. Jesus.
This level is fucking brutal.
I just almost missed him. Okay, back
to where I was before.
I'm getting like, caught on my keyboard.
I forgot about the dog, but it's okay.
I got it.
All right, can I... Here's the question.
All right, I'm going for it. Go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
All right. Now I have to bait him over
here.
Who has a gun? These two have guns.
Was it all three of them? I got all
three of them.
Just this guy up here. Okay, slow
down. I'm gonna get shot in the
fucking head.
Wowee. That was fucking rough.
That was rough. I say wowee a lot. I
know.
Stay back.
Whoa, take it easy. I'm just here to
get you. Your brother sent us. We're
not going to harm you.
My brother? You just killed all my
friends.
Look, we've got a car waiting outside,
so drop the gun. It's time to go.
We'll drop you off at your brother's.
You accepted to go with you? Are you
insane?
You murdered my friends. You're not
taking me anywhere.
Now leave me the fuck alone.
Fine, you have it your way. We're out
of here.
What was that? Okay. Don't do it. Don't do
what?
I'm back. All right, so that's not
part of a cutscene thing.
That actually just did happen.
Okay.
I'm...
Don't do it. Don't do it.
Don't fucking do it. How did you...
All right, I'll take that as a sign
that I...
I fucking found a new way to do
this. Dog...
Ah, come on. Come on. I beat it. I
beat it. The fucking girl had to shoot
me. Don't do it, Jeremy.
Oh, Jeremy. God. Oh, I'm standing. I'm
standing up right now. I can't... I did
this.
I already beat this mission, and I
beat it very well, too.
I took my fucking time. Oh, man.
I need to turn on like a fucking...
something in my ear. I need like a
Secret Service person to be like,
don't touch the girl.
I need someone to feed me lines
through. A fucking earpiece.
Oh, my god. I'm so salty right now.
That's the perfect word to describe
how I feel right now. It's just like,
just a...
Oh, man. Oh, man. Man.
I... I already did it.
I... I'm... I'm full fucking... Shake the
fucking pinball machine, man.
Seriously.
Just shake it up and spray it all
over the fucking ground.
I'm gonna take my time. Fucking come
on.
No. The only way to play this game is
go fast and lose fast. No, I...
Not me. I play this game with fucking
patience.
I'm trying to time my hits and shots
and getting
things where I want them. Okay, now I
can go over here.
Open this door. Bait him through the
door.
Not... Won't be long now. How did this
guy not see me? Dog! Get the dog
first!
Ah, fuck! Okay, whatever. What the fuck is this guy?
Why is he... He's right there with a gun and I
can't...
Fuck. You get... Where's the last guy?
Over here, right? Yeah, there's a
couple, right? Oh my god, I remember
this part. I remember being so scared
here.
I remember this part. I'm being
terrified. Is there no other way to
go? All right, there's
one guy with a Uzi and I can't get
there any other way. I have to bait
him.
Will he see me from here? I don't
have to run up there,
but I can't see.
Okay, just go! Done! Just fucking get out
of here. Get the hell out of here.
I'm not touching the girl. I'm not...
I'm not gonna...
Go, let go! Punch! Punch! No, no!
Why would I ever stay back? Yes, hold
right mouse button to skip.
Go, bye! Thank you for playing. I'll
see you later.
Get the fuck out of here. I forget
where I'm going. Where am I going?
Where's the car? Why did I park my
car?
All right, down here. Oh my god, thank
goodness.
I can't believe I had to do that
again.
How is that a D plus? I... I...
All right, I got Alex and Ash.
Didn't get any high combos. Damn it.
Down anytime soon. It's not a good
time to be messing around if a cop
came by. Sauce like this.
It ain't gonna go faster with you
bitching, okay? Besides, I've been
telling you to get the van fixed for
weeks.
Right, I still don't see any of that
be my job. It's not my van.
Just fucking do it.
The only one of us who ain't busy with
work all day.
Take it down to Andy and the chop shop.
He owes me one.
Fine, just get the car running and
I'll do it tomorrow, okay?
Yeah, that should do it. Try starting
her up and let's see what the hell's
had to happen in here.
This is my Stardew Valley character
all over again.
Am I like a... am I like a billionaire
apartment?
What's the matter? You look a little
nervous. Well, boss, something you need to
say, just say it. Look,
we've known each other for a long time
now. You've done a lot for me.
No need to be polite, cut to the point.
All right, I want out. I'm getting too
old for this. I'm feeling too soft.
Too soft? Too soft for what?
Shooting people, putting my ass on
the line. I've had a feeling I'm not
going to last much longer for a
while now.
Been having these dreams. Dreams, huh?
You want out? You're out.
But first, you have to take care of
some business for me, okay?
What business? Nothing big. A chop
shop downtown.
They're with the Colombians now. Won't
give us our cut no more.
Don't worry, they're just hoodlums.
Nothing you can't handle.
And then I'm out. Yes. Though you're
free to come back anytime you change
your mind.
As a parting gift, grab a sample of
our new product here. Might spice up
this new boring lifestyle you've
chosen.
Best voice acting ever? You want me
to go for it? Fine. Here you go.
Give me the next line. Give me the
next voice line. Well, there's no
more lines.
I don't get to take the eagle car,
whatever it is.
No mercy. Okay. Damn it!
I'm trying to go for- I'm trying to get
combos.
It's never gonna happen, okay? This
game is so
fucking fast-paced and so hard to
lose. It's so easy to lose.
Is there a skateboard on the ground?
What can I do with this? Oh.
You know how you get combos in this
game? You have to beat the level
like five times and like recognize
exactly where to go every- that's
where the combos come in.
You're gonna get a fucking D plus
on every mission.
Or a B. It's gonna happen every time
until you can sprint through and know
every kill and get like a 10 hit combo.
Really? What the fuck is that plywood
on the ground blocking?
Jesus god, give me a fucking break.
He's gonna shoot me through the
fucking glass. Look at all the glass
everywhere.
Jesus Christ! Oh come on.
Eat shit. That's enough time? That
gives me- that gives me enough time to
do this?
One guy over there. Is it that- is that
a bomb? What's this? Is that a bomb?
That looks like a wire that's
connected to a bomb.
Can you shoot through couches? Oh fucking
god. Jesus.
Last guy. Two guys. Got it. Okay. Good.
Floor cleared. Let's move.
Where's the next floor? Oh okay. So
it's just at the edge of the level.
You got it. All right, let's go.
Holy fuck! Where did you guys come
from? Down here? Oh shit, you did.
Damn, I didn't know you could shoot
over the car. I don't have enough
bullets for this.
I have enough of that and then I
gotta wait because I don't have any bullets.
So where the hell am I gonna go?
This way. Let's go to the left.
There's a lot? Okay. And there's a
where did the third fucking guy come
from? Find him.
Why was that guy here? What the heck?
Restart it. No, don't restart it. Just
die.
A third guy. Fucking glass.
Glass. All right, got it. Give me one
of your guns.
Glass him. Other side of the Pac-man
level here we go.
Ooh, that wasn't good. That wasn't
good either.
That wasn't good either. Panic! Panic!
Panic! Panic!
What the fuck shot me through the
glass?
Okay, can I, let me just be real for a
second.
Do you see where this motherfucker
shot me from? I was down here.
This guy shot through the glass over
the car.
Over the fucking disco machine.
The guy shot from across the whole
level.
I didn't shoot the dog. Relax. Dog.
Nobody up here. That's the guy that
shot me through the glass last time.
Glass? Anybody up there? Just check
to make sure I'm not gonna get shot
by somebody.
It's a glass shooter. Money? Can I
pick up the money?
Last guy up there. Dog. Fuck.
Good thing I saw that right when I did.
I'm just gonna wait for this guy.
I don't care if I lose points. Who's
left?
Don't just fucking sprint through. It's
not safe until everybody's dead.
Which I cannot guarantee I know where
they are. Okay, he's right there.
All right, good. Get the bag. The bag
of money?
Is that gonna be, is that a bomb? Is that a
bomb on the car? Okay, get me out of
here.
There's a bomb on the car. It's gonna
explode. I can't fuck around in
levels anymore guys. I don't know
which levels are gonna kill me or
not.
Well, who the hell are you? Thought you
could get away, huh?
Get away. I just work here. Who are you?
You're freaking me out, man.
It's your lucky day today, kid. This
bag here just saved your life.
I'm getting out of here. You should
probably do the same.
Now, out of my way! Voice acting.
Time bonus. Special. I'm not getting any
of those bonuses.
That was a C. I feel like I did
that one pretty quickly.
That one was, I felt like that one
was pretty good.
All right, here we are. Hi honey,
welcome home.
I made you dinner. It's in the fridge.
I'll eat it later. I'm not that hungry
right now.
Oh, had a rough day. All right, you want
me to be an actor?
Fine, I'll be an actor. I'm not sure.
I quit my job. You quit your job just
like that
and your boss just let you? I thought
you said,
look, I'm out and that's that. Speaking
of which,
I've got a surprise for you, but what
what is it?
You'll see tomorrow, okay? I'm
feeling a bit too tired right now.
I'm gonna head straight for bed. Are you
gonna stay up for a while?
I'm just gonna finish this show. I'll be
up in a minute.
Don't you know, acting guys, if
there's a question mark,
make it sound like a really big
question. Like, for instance,
acting class 101. If the
line is,
for instance,
did you go to the supermarket today?
Right? Did you go to the store
today? Did you go to the supermarket
today?
That's a guy with normal human talks,
right? But if you're, but an actor, but
acting,
did you go to the supermarket today?
Did you go to the supermarket today?
Just, just talk like people don't
talk and you're an actor.
These pretzels are making me thirsty.
Yeah, instead of just saying,
these pretzels are drying me out.
You ever, do you have water or
something? These pretzels are really
drying my mouth out. Do you have any
water?
These pretzels are really drying my
mouth out. Do you have any water?
These pretzels are really dry. I mean,
these pretzels are really dry. These
pretzels are really dry.
That's how you be an actor. It's drying
me out.
Uh, all right. Okay, this is, this is
different.
I'm just driving away with money in
the bag.
You're listening, here you go, oh
right, by the way, actor is also radio
host or YouTuber.
You're listening to WYL Miami Radio,
bringing you fresh new music each
day.
What you like, whenever you like.
That's our motto.
It's a beautiful day today, the sun is
shining and the sky is clear.
Let me read that like a normal person
now.
You can't go wrong with weather like
this, that's for sure.
Later today we'll be premiering a
hot new single from, uh,
Perturberator.
Meanwhile, uh, here's another song by
everybody's favorite,
Mitch, see, acting. We interrupt the
broadcast for an emergency weather
report.
A tropical storm is heading towards
Florida, coming from the Atlantic.
It's estimated to reach Miami by 7
p.m.
We caution all residents to, my sky
got here,
where are we going? I'm going away, far
away, anywhere, it doesn't matter to me.
You sure, do you even know where
you're heading?
Well the directions, a lot of people
wind up going round in circles.
And this road doesn't look too
promising.
I didn't ask for your opinion. What if
I told you that this road leads to
nowhere,
or rather that you're heading for a
dead end, that's where you're going.
You're closing in on it, it's closing in
fast,
but you already know that, don't you? I
have no idea what you're talking about.
You'll see soon enough. By the way, did
you forget to bring your girlfriend?
Caught the lesson I was giving you
there, I was being a fucking real
actor on the chicken,
and I was being an actor on the
fucking, the other guy, the driver.
Mary? Mary? Mary? Fucking Garfield on
the couch.
How do you guys pick up shit like
that, so quickly?
There's a note. Hi honey, I'm sorry, I'm
not doing the acting thing anymore.
Hi honey, I'm so sorry about this.
You would have done the same thing if
you were me.
Love, Mary. He does it anyways, yeah
whatever.
This is called Execution. Okay, you
have reached the wrong number.
That's the title of the game. Please
hang up and try again.
Beep beep. Listen to that baseline.
This is a good baseline. Oh hey, hold
on.
Chainsaw and guns. What the hell is
this?
What the fuck? Hold on, you get your own
ice climbers?
How does this work? What the fuck? Oh my
god, it really is the ice climbers.
Oh, whoa, this is weird. Okay,
this is kind of cool. I kind of like
this. Who's left?
One guy over here. I thought that was a
guy. Okay, no we're good.
I can't go in there? I guess not.
All right, so how do I pick up other
guns
with the, uh, what is it? What are the
names of the ice climbers names?
Does he reload? Do I have to, I think
I have to pick up the guns on the
ground, right?
Yeah, there we go, okay. Fuck, I had it.
Okay, I, I, I understand. That's it.
No, I want to pick up, I can't pick up
the other guns, okay.
All right, grab this other gun on the
ground over here. Got it, okay.
One guy left. Right through the front
door.
No, in there.
Oh, these guys are fun. Oh, these
guys are really fun.
Can I do anything else? Oh, I wake up
here. Wait,
oh, I have to go in there? Look, I don't
know.
I told you. There's something strange
going on, you know what I mean?
Can you see that? Look right there. Can
you see it? What is that?
Someone must have slipped me
something. I mean, this can't be
happening.
It's like, wow, are those masks? Are
we in the jungle? I want to go to
the jungle. I quit. You know, did I
tell you that?
No more, I tell you. I'm out. Done.
Finished. Holy shit.
What? Are you hitting me? I just want
to go home. Can you call Mary? She'll,
she'll come get me.
Am I bleeding? Do I need to go to
the hospital?
Guys, I just want to go home. Holy shit.
That was a little, that's too bad.
All right, we got
B minus. That's right. I'm gonna,
I'm gonna march
back home with that in my hand,
and I'm gonna be playing
fucking show tunes in my head,
while I march back to fucking hold it
in front of me to show bomb.
That's, I'm opening the door with it
out in front, holding it out.
Mark. Third act, climax. Climax.
I don't know if it's the heat, but I
feel a bit drunk.
Me too, I'm thinking about heading back
to camp.
I'm good for another round or two. You
guys head on back.
I'll catch up with you later. You don't
tell me what to do, okay?
I'm gonna show you how to drink, you
hear me?
Well, I guess we'll see you guys back
at camp then.
Just remember that we have a job to
do tonight, fellas.
Okay. Excuse me guys, you have a
second? I'd like to get a picture of
you if you don't mind.
Sure thing. Could you send me a copy
if I give you my address?
No need, we have a Polaroid. Would you
mind stepping out into the sun here for
a bit?
Uh, do I have to do something? No, no.
All right, good luck out there, guys.
Thanks for letting me get a shot.
No worries, man. Good luck to you too.
Okay. Now what? Why is the world
spinning?
Uh, oh, I had to take the Polaroid.
Okay, are we
trying to move out? Choose your
weapon wisely and make
them shots count. Lord knows how many-
So, are we at like war? I don't
understand.
Do be careful, my boy. Don't want any of
my men dying on me.
Got a special delivery coming in
tonight. Wouldn't want to drink all that
bourbon alone.
Not in this goddamn place. Uh,
I'm gonna say shotgun. No. Yeah. Well,
I have to use it now.
Okay. So, I can't put it down.
Ambush. What the hell is happening
in this game?
What the hell is this? All right,
we're-
Okay. Good thing you didn't look that
way.
Oh, I can take a knife out. So, I can't
pick weapons up off the ground in these
levels. All right. Whatever.
Area clear. Can I reload?
Not conserving ammo. Oh, shit. Oh, all
right. I'll conserve ammo.
Caught him. Caught him. Really? All
right. Conserving ammo.
How does that guy not shoot me? I
don't know. All right. Let me pay
attention.
Can this guy shoot over this? Oh,
conserving ammo.
Aye, aye, aye. Nobody down. Okay.
Just don't worry about this guy here.
Put down there. I'm gonna have to shoot
that guy, aren't I?
I have to shoot this guy. Well, fuck.
Is that-
Is this ammo boxes? Where are they?
Are there any ammo boxes here? Shoot
the last round.
Shoot once. Okay. Get ammo. Okay.
There we go. Look, we're fine. I
didn't get- I got played. I would have
been so upset that way. Okay.
Were you guys trying to bait me and it
actually worked out in my favor?
Oh, damn it. That would have been like
10 combo there.
Oops-a-daisy. Who the fuck am I?
What? What? Okay.
Okay, that was stupid. All right. We got
guy with the gun, guy with the blade.
Guy with the gun first. Bingo. Bingo!
James here. I'm done, uh, weeding out
the garden. How's it going with the
yard?
Hank here. I ran out of fuel for the
lawn mowers. We're at the gas station.
Headed over and we'll share the
ride back. I'll leave the area.
I don't think I can do anything else
here, so
mine will just go. That had to have been
pretty good. I- that's gonna be at least
a B.
I'll take a B minus. Better than
expected.
I'm even prouder to show that to mom.
Mom doesn't expect me to get aids.
Weapon unlocked big and heavy. Hmm.
Looks like he- we got our hands on
some good intel here.
We should get this back to the
Colonel as soon as possible. Not sure
what to do with the captives,
though. Maybe we should just let
Barnes have his way. Would make the
jog
back to camp a hell of a lot easier.
This is the- this is- we're watching a
movie right now.
Oh, pause it right there. Oh, hold on a
second. You're trying to tell me
that a Bluetooth brush. Uh, all right.
Did you guys catch the news on
channel six last night? Looks like
we're famous now.
Yeah, looks like we got our five
minutes of fame. I'd say it was
more like two.
Damn, I didn't catch it. What did
they say?
Do you think you can call the news
station and ask for a copy?
I mean, I'd pay big bucks to see it.
Why don't you call the police and
turn yourself in while you're at it?
Yeah, that probably would be a good
idea. I'm sure they'll run another
story on us sooner or later anyway.
I'm not so sure about that we'd have
to off more people first, you know?
He's right. Not sure what to do
about that. We can't just go out and
kill random people now, can we?
I might have an idea. I bought- hold
on.
I can't do Donald Duck. I bought
some weed from a couple of
creeps a few days ago.
Okay. He's choking.
He wants to go treasure hunting for more
drugs.
No, I can't. I don't know how people do
Donald Duck. It's fucking hard.
Well, there might be more assholes
there. I don't know. You got
anything better to do?
I wouldn't mind going for a ride.
Let's check it out. We could always
grab some pizza if we don't find
anything.
Yeah, there's one thing of being
able to do a duck, like
blah, blah, you know what I'm talking
about.
But being able to form words in a
coherent sentence,
as the Donald Duck voice, is so hard to
do. Two machine guns.
I'm staying with these two. These two
are fun.
Leave or die. The back? No, no, no, no,
no, no.
Okay. I cased the joint successfully.
Let's go. Right into his gut. That's
it.
Done. Whoa. That's all there was to
it, huh?
Did you hear that? Hear what? Sounds
like someone's in that room over
there. I already checked it. There's
no one in there.
Oops. Okay. Well, we're going down even
further.
I don't understand these walls. Are these
walls? Not really.
Okay. Well, I didn't get it. Okay.
That's
three. Shit. I missed.
Come on. Bring it on. Bring it on.
Bring it on. What we got? Guy with the
gun?
That's no problem for me. Keep going.
Fast. Hurry up.
A plus. Let's go. Weee. Don't go crazy
here.
I fucking, my own partner just shot me
in the head. That's what it looked
like.
I'm trying to rush. What the fuck
happened there?
Give me a fucking break. How did he not
get shot by that?
Damn it. Trying to focus too much on
the shooting.
The shooting is the backup
to me.
I was right clicking and it
wouldn't shoot.
Okay. Relax. Seven bullets. Okay.
Dog. Don't forget about the dog. All
right. Good. Good. Good. Good.
Good. Holy fuck. I almost missed. It's
okay. Anybody else?
Guy down there. He's melee. Just drag
him up.
Shit. Okay. Whoops. Whoops.
I got one. Fuck. No. God damn it.
What the hell?
This bullshit. Come on, man.
That was such dog shit. He just like
fucking
insta-turned. I'm so fucking mad about
that one.
I wasn't even paying attention. Missed
the chance.
Another dog, right? I'm surprised that
didn't get it.
Get that gun. Pick it up. Pick up the
gun. Is there a reason why you won't
pick the gun up?
There you go. Okay. Jeez. I guess he
does it himself. Okay.
Nobody else up there, right? Just this
guy with the gun. Down. Down. Down.
Down. Down. Who's down here?
Okay. Same deal. I just gotta shoot that
guy.
He's in such an awkward spot too.
Okay. Fine. Bye. Faster. Hurry. Hurry.
Hurry. Go to the car. I'm going faster.
Secret. Faster. Faster. Faster. Faster.
I'm going. I'm trying.
I got some pretty decent combo. I got
like it almost times nine times
ten.
Small time bonus. It's okay. Got it.
A minus. Boomer speedrun strats. That's
called a regular strat.
Good strat. Does this change? Change
perspective so many times in this game.
Who is it? It's the police. Open the
door.
Fifty second. I gotta put on some
clothes. Okay. Wait. That was the duck.
That's the duck costume. Police are
already in here.
Can I go in the car? Okay. Who is
that?
How did you get in here? The door
wasn't locked. I let myself in. I hope
you don't mind.
Blind. Blind streamer. What are you
talking about?
Well what do you want? I'm looking for an
Ash Davis.
This is listed as his last known
address. Well as you can see he's not
here. I don't know where he is.
He doesn't live here anymore. Was there
anything else? Will you tell him to
contact Miami PD next time you see him?
You're his sister aren't you? I can
see you got the good genes.
You're very pretty. If there was nothing
else I would like for you to leave.
Now I have to take it.
I'm just switching control. Who's the
protagonist in this game?
Dead ahead. Oh that's interesting.
So I gotta pee. We're taking our
first break in the night. I'll be
right back.
Pee time. Sorry for the static. I'll
mute it.
All right be right back. You know what
might think would be funny?
If I use this
on every view right back and the new
viewers just have no fucking idea
what's happening.
What my cam's on? Oh okay. I've
refreshed the page and I had no
idea what was going on.
Uh all right we're back.
And by the way hold on let me just open
up this uh
fresh beer. Coors light.
Now you are a boomer. It's I'm drink
it's a coca cola. It's just a
fucking coke.
Is it monster? Why would I drink a
monster energy drink?
What the hell would I ever do that
for? What? Wait what's down here?
This is like really this is like
really thick coke though.
Like this is this supposed to be like
this?
You know what I mean? Chewy. Is this
supposed to be chewy?
That's weird. What the fuck happened?
What? What character am I? Oh it's me
right there.
Come on keep it up. Keep it up. Come
on. Keep up the punch.
Wow. My god. Fucking guy with a
machine gun.
Hmm I got an idea. Come over here.
You god come over here. And you hit
me behind a wall.
I'm trying to bait that guy. Why
would the guys look at me?
Just staring at me and he just won't come
over here.
You fucking dummy. All right get the
fuck over here.
You. You come over here. Okay who's left?
That guy. That guy. That guy. I gotta
throw.
How the hell am I gonna do this? I
gotta go up to here.
Gun. Who's first? This guy right
here.
Oh and I right clicked.
Yeah um why is it going over him?
What the fuck is happening? I don't
know.
He's. They're ducking. I get it. I
understand. I get it. I get it. Everybody
watch it.
I get it. Stand up. Gotcha.
Fuck. I have one bullet. Oh that's not
good.
Oh I can't. I can't duck.
This is a fun game. You know what? Dude I don't know how the hell
you could beat this in 10 seconds.
You gotta be real damn good at
this.
Don't want to. This guy's gonna
collapse on me if I don't take him out
right now.
Almost died again. All right here we go.
I gotta get a better spot. I like this
spot up here.
Because it's near more guns. I can get
this guy while being blocked.
You fucking stupid video game. Who even
plays these anymore?
Who even plays these anymore?
Seriously. Fucking video games right?
Like oh why why would you play them?
You gotta be kidding me. Who even
fucking plays them anymore?
Who even fucking plays them? See me.
All right. Oh boomer rage.
Why did he not stand up and his friend
underneath him did?
He has a clear shot and he doesn't
stand up but the other guy does.
I can't even hit the first guy
anymore.
I'm so fucking angry at this.
They don't make video games like
they used to. Remember how easy they
used to be?
Do you remember? God I missed like
the golden age of video games.
Remember back? Remember Mega Man 4?
You remember that one? Yeah I do.
Yeah I remember being unbearable and
almost unplayably difficult.
And you had to start the whole game
over again if you lost like three
times.
Remember that video game used to be
so much easier?
Oh my god. I remember Castlevania.
That was such a fucking fun game. I
loved having
one item to attack with and and get
you get bounced around.
Hey remember Donkey Kong Country? That
game was fucking... Remember how awesome
that game was?
Hey go play one of the bounce around
and the barrels levels and you tell
me how great that game is.
Get past like the second world in
Donkey Kong Country and then you
tell me
if games used to be fucking easy.
Yeah!
Wowee! Where'd you come from? Oh wowee!
Is that like my new fucking catch
phrase?
Did you... is that as you pull the
cord on my back and that's what I
say?
I have four phrases.
Wowee!
What the hell?
Suck a fart out of my ass!
Dude I keep forgetting that's not a...
this is not a wall right here. I keep
thinking it is.
Sprint sprint sprint sprint sprint
sprint sprint oh no don't sprint.
All right there's a there's a spot
right here that I'm not gonna get
shot because I can walk past that.
All right so easy now. This is a
safe zone.
Why don't you come over here? After three
attempts I finally got the gun.
And if you miss don't worry you always
get a second chance. All right what
is left in here? Oh my god I almost just
didn't...
okay. Stage clear. Fast one two three
go!
You fucking dummy. All right who's left?
What the fuck was that guy? Where was
he?
Did what happened? I'm so confused
right now. What happened?
I don't even know where the guy
where that guy was. What the heck?
Did that guy shoot himself?
I fucking tried to throw.
I got stuck in them. Fucking doorway.
It's like my guy's body is made out
of magnets and when you touch a door
you just get sucked into it. Bring the
other fucking dog up here.
Just do it. I mean just do it. The
dog's coming. Just bring it.
Oh my god damn it. Why? Where the
fuck are you?
Okay don't let some random guy get
out of bed.
It's like fucking Minecraft bed and
come get me. I need a better view.
All right so there's nobody with a gun
over there.
So I can get down into that room but
I gotta be careful because of the
windows.
Anybody in that room? Okay there's one
more guy.
All right I think I can get. I got six
shots.
Nobody in there has a gun. This guy's
I did not expect that to happen that
quickly.
Got it okay. Ooh tough game we got
here. Tough game.
Is that it? No. Hold on let me. Tough game
we got here.
Whoa shit there's a window.
What the fuck are you doing? Get up you
fucking idiot.
Why?
Okay we're safe. Just shoot the
duck as I walk by.
Oh fuck. What am I doing? Why would you
even walk up there? There's no reason
for you to do what you just did.
My hand's in the air.
That was pretty good too. That's
pretty good.
Oh it's a dog.
And it's is one fucking pixel away
apparently.
Okay easy. I'm just I don't care.
Line them up. I'm just testing my it's just
a patience test.
This is a gear check for me to see if
I'm patient at all.
I'm eating my coke. I'm chewing on my
chewy coke.
I'm just trying to go too fast. Okay
get guns? No. Anybody with a gun in
there?
I don't know. I don't know. That's the
only good. That's what comes with rooms.
Hey hey hey hey hey hey hey oh
oh oh where do I go? Oh my god what am I
doing?
I don't know what I'm doing. I gotta
go this way.
What hey wait a minute.
Fuck. I'm so I had a gun.
I didn't even think I had a gun. How
was I supposed to? No.
I was supposed to. Oh my fucking
god. Who made this game? Why did you
make this game?
Why did you make this game? Why did
what did you make this game for?
Fucking door. I made this game for you.
Why are they there? No.
Oh I'm gonna unravel. I'm gonna
unravel.
Mm-hmm. No that's gonna happen. We're
already like three hours into this and
I'm like I'm already fucking
unraveling.
All right. Okay how many shots does
I shot three times?
I don't want that guy to even see me.
I've unraveled completely.
Wowie.
Where are we?
Fucking god. They just have so many
angles.
There's so many angles on me. It's
horrible.
Give me the fucking god. What? Why
does it
not? Why? I want to pick the gun up off
the fucking
ground. I'm gonna go I'm gonna literally
just gonna say I'm gonna take 15
straight minutes to beat this. I'm
gonna go as slow as humanly possible.
Ready? I'm literally gonna take 25
fucking minutes starting now. Count.
Where's the gun? I need another gun. I need
another gun.
Oh my god the fucking perfect angle.
Give me a fucking break. Oh my god
this is just
pain the video game. Oh and like all the
sudden that guy
that that guy let me look at that guy
just fucking sprinted down to shoot me.
Where was that guy? Why was he the
only one that
sprinted to my exact location? He's
the only one that saw me.
Only guy. I'm just gonna sprint to
his exact location to shoot him.
What? Why did this fucking guy not
see me? This guy.
That guy. This guy. No guy like a guy
all the fucking way up here was
like yeah that's right I'll go this
way.
Oh no noooo.
This level is a pleb filter.
Oh it's called I'm unraveling. I had
the fucking level beat already
and one of these dickheads accidentally
killed me up there then I got the
whole fucking thing over again.
And there's another this is another
dog. Well this is just fucking
wonderful. What the hell am I
supposed to do about this?
Jesus god give me the gun for the
love of all the desacred.
Up there. Guy can shoot all the way
from fucking there down here.
Fuck off. You know we call that we call
that bullshit.
Oh my god. Why do those fucking guys
have to exist in a game where
everybody dies in one hit?
The guy that takes like five. It's
just oh my god.
It's driving me crazy.
Fuck this level. This is the longest
I've spent on a level in the two
fucking both of these games.
I'm so angry that I didn't hit any
of those. I hate the doors. Remove
the doors.
Is there like a cheat I can put in
to remove all doors from the game?
They just they're just a hindrance. They
just get in the fucking way.
All doors. When are they gonna can I
patch that in? Oh fucking god I don't
have
him god. Somebody said this is the
this is one of the worst missions in
the game.
All right I don't I don't get it. So
you shoot the big guy. They literally
don't die for like five straight
seconds and then they die. You only
have to shoot them once.
I hate this level. This is ruining
the whole game for me.
This level. I think this is the level
that made me stop playing. Is that are
you really for real?
Is it not just me? I heard a dog.
Where the fuck is he?
I only have two bullets. Now what the
fuck am I gonna do?
None of those guys have guns. Don't get
seen by these guys. That happens
every time.
Oh my fucking god.
Why?
Uh where did that guy come from?
Did he shoot me from? Oh yeah oh
well sorry you shot me.
Is it the guy that shot me from across the whole
game through the window?
I was just curious.
Now what the fuck. I gotta make it across but oh
there he is.
Okay got him. What are these fucking
patrols?
How many more people you got in that room
with a gun?
Why is this guy still in Anor Londo?
I have to go around this way.
Anybody with a gun over here?
No there's not. Okay. I have two
bullets.
Fuck. I'm gonna get sniped from
across the map aren't I?
I thought the waves was a gun.
All right nobody else has a gun but
neither do I.
This is not good. This is really bad.
I need to get one of those guns.
Preferably the shotgun. Got it. Okay.
I'm going back. No. Stay over here.
Is that it? Don't. There's anybody coming around the
sides. There's anybody coming around the
sides. Just kill me.
Where's the other guy? Where is this
last person?
Oh my. Thank god. Oh my fucking god get
me out of here.
I hate this. This is the worst level ever. I hate this. No. This way.
There's more.
I'm gonna cry.
I almost just cried on stream.
Doing it right. Look. What are these
guys?
It's the windows that just do it to
me man. I just can't handle it.
Okay. There's too many things to pay attention to.
Like somebody can if someone when people
can just shoot you across the whole
map.
This makes you so paranoid. Like that
guy right there can shoot through the
whole game over here to kill me.
God. Oh you bastard game with the
fucking door.
Fucking door. Man rip it off the
hinges.
Is there a character that puts a
mask on that could rip the fucking
door off the hinges?
Gee. And where did you come from?
This is a guy with a shotgun up here
apparently somehow.
Fucking god. I can do it too asshole.
No god. Fucking windows
are everywhere. I'm so paranoid.
If I step foot out there I'm dead.
I'm gonna can I go down? I'm gonna try
going this way.
Window right there. You gotta be
fucking kidding me. I like
the windows man. That just just makes
it so easy
for you to get shot from anywhere.
You can win by just spraying but
yeah but I
I'm gonna alert the whole room and then
I'm gonna get collapsed on.
Where the fuck did that guy come from?
What was he doing over here?
Who is the AI director spawning in
these enemies?
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
Goddamn game man.
This goddamn fucking game.
Did the same guys make the first one
and the second one?
This is the same team that made the
second one?
God damn it.
He's supposed to die. Fucking Jesus.
Only shoot him once and he'll die.
He did.
I feel like way more than the first
game. Like moving a quarter of an inch
kills you in this one.
Am I right on that?
Is it like moving three inches kills
you in this game?
He's like I feel like I just have to
stand in the same corner
the whole time. Because if I move
it's just there's a hundred people
that just have 20 different angles
with like sniper rifles.
I'm out of bullets. All right so
give me this.
One guy with a gun. There's more
than one guy with a gun.
Empty. Anybody have a gun over here?
Somebody has to have a gun.
What the fuck was that aim? What the hell
are you shooting at?
Try another one. Try to try a shotgun
this time.
Shoot through the game. I think that's
it. Get me out of here please.
That was the worst one by far. Where the
fuck am I going?
I forgot how long ago that was
because I hated that part too.
You haven't seen the worst. There are
still more horrors.
Really? You know you shoot it out.
Really? There's a level later on that
turns your keyboard into acid.
You know you should really wait for
backup in these situations.
It's not my fault you guys took so
long to get here, is it?
I got here first. You got a problem with
that? What are you doing? You're reckless.
Your actions endanger this whole
operation. Give me a break.
Operation? What are you talking about?
You don't like it? Go complain to the
chief. I'm out of here.
I'm out of here. Is it right? Just
get me to the next level.
I can look at the game with a fresh
new start after that one.
A nice chill stream. Somehow I got a
C plus on that. It would take 40
minutes to do that. How did I get a
C plus on that one but like a fucking
D on the other one? And I did the
other one way cleaner.
This one took 40 minutes. How did I get
a D on the other one and a C on that?
I don't understand. Let me guess our
serial killer has been at it again.
What gave it away? He left another
message for us, mundane as ever.
Please don't make me do it again.
Well at least he got a bit creative
with the victim. Poor kid.
Maybe he was upset that the papers
haven't made a bigger deal of them.
These scumbags seem to crave
attention. I gotta relax. I'm so angry
at that last level.
I can still feel it. Red check.
Am I like fucking red? I got like a red
nose.
I'm like red down here. Not really.
All right, well that's fine. I'm
looking at the wrong camera.
You expected it at out of sync. Don't
we all, huh? You might be getting your
fair share once this gets out.
Think you can handle the pressure? All
eyes will be on you now.
I'm sure this guy will slip up
sooner or later. Speaking of which,
what have you got from me? Any
findings?
Not much. No murder, weapon, and no win. I
gotta relax.
Change of plans. I need like a
meditation video.
I need to do a meditation. Guided
meditation.
Hold on. I'm gonna mute this for a
second. I have to do this, guys. I'm
sorry.
I'm like, I'm all fired up. It's
supposed to be instructions.
Thank you for being here, dear soul.
I'm Kenneth, and from my heart, I
will... Is this the cheers for you guy?
This is the cheers to you guy? I think
this is the cheers to you.
As comfortable as you can right this
moment.
Allow yourself just be here and now
observing the words I share with you
like a soft breeze on a summer night.
Noticing whatever it is that you
notice.
Your body may begin to relax more
and more. This is not fucking helping.
As you listen to my voice,
go deeper within. How would somebody be
able to sleep to this?
Could you imagine? All right, seriously,
wait a second.
Wait. Can you imagine if you were
trying to go to sleep?
Okay. You lay down and you're like, man,
I really wish I had something to help
me go to sleep. And I'm like, I only
help you there.
And I go right up to your fucking ear.
And I'm like, very soon you'll be
sleeping.
And just to let you know, it's so
relaxing in this room.
And very soon you'll be going to bed
just like the breeze of a sunny
summer Monday morning.
That's the way that you'll see the
world. Like, you're gonna be like, what
the fuck? What are you doing to me?
Like, I'm trying to sleep. I need
complete silence. And I need nobody
talking.
And I don't want any lights on. All
right, let's see if we can... Now I'm
even more
fucking on edge than I was before. It
didn't help. At all.
I just like burped. Where is my
meditation?
I just had it. Where is it? It's on a
different window. What the fuck is this
window?
Why is it down here? Help me! Come on!
Find its best way to let go naturally.
You don't need to relax. It may be that
your body needs to heal in other ways.
It's good to know that you're
unconscious.
Mine is an expert in healing and
balancing
in a safe and natural way while you
can just
flow with the experience. Change
is a natural aspect of life. Like a
tree
Turn this shit off!
Stubborn! Let me fucking relax!
That guy just made me so fucking angry!
Imagine now that you're breathing in
that life energy.
Electrician found him like this. He
must have been taken here.
Found cut marks around his wrists and
ankles. Death by strangulation.
The killer gutted him post-mortem.
Thank God.
Thank God. Anything else? Yeah seems
like the killer may have robbed him
on like previous victories.
Uh not victories. Couldn't find the
kid's wallet.
Who knows? Might have been someone else.
People have no morals these days.
Will have to run his prints. Fucking
god damn it. I'm on.
I'm off completely right now. I'm
gonna head back to the office. It's
been a rough night and I'm about to
get it. It's gonna get even harder.
This is ruining the game for me. I'm
too angry.
Just too hard. Oh it's gonna get so
much worse.
I'll let you know if you find anything
else. All right. Why does that guy have
that move? Why does that guy die?
Why does that guy die in one hit? He
should die in one hit.
The same people who make this game.
This is a great song.
Chicken delivery. Hey guys just got
the masks we ordered.
Pretty cool eh? They're all chickens.
Well how do they feel? You like
them?
Guys?
I think I just heard something. What are
you guys talking about?
I'll get it. Hey none of these phones
are ringing.
Sorry it's me. When did you get a
cell phone? I took it from that guy we
clocked at the bar.
Just charged it up this morning at
Dean's place. What should I do? Do I
answer?
I don't see any reason not to. All
right here goes nothing.
Hi it's me. I know you want it out
and I respect that but I just
figured I'd give you a call and see
if you've changed your mind.
You wouldn't believe what's been going
on the last few weeks. That was just
one of those outdoor frog sounds you
hear at night and in the fall.
We're calling the shots now. Top of
the game. No one can touch us.
The new product is in full scale
production. Get a new place.
Three floors up on northwest 20th
street. Who would have thought?
Why don't you swing on by and
check it out huh? Hello? Anyone there?
Click. Hey guys I think I just found
us something to do tonight.
Let's go right now. I'll tell you
all about it in the van.
What's somebody saying? Somebody's
saying the hardest level in the game?
Coming up. Best song in the game coming
up. Death wish. Can you open the door
already? It's getting pretty late.
They might be heading out soon. It was
your idea to stake the place out for
two hours. I'm working as fast as I
can.
Well we couldn't just barge in. You
gotta have a plan you know. At least
now we know where they are.
Dot dot dot. Just fucking open this
thing will ya?
Maybe you would like to take it over
then. I'm sure you'd get it open in
no use.
Yeah I didn't think so. I think I got
it now.
All right see you guys on the roof.
Don't forget to stay in touch with
the walkie talkies.
About the roof. You sure will be able
to jump across to the other building.
It looked a bit far to me. It's not
that far. Well at least not for the
rest of us.
Damn listen to this. You may have
some difficulties with it though
big guy.
Yeah fuck you too. Restart it. I
didn't mean to do that.
See you on the roof. Let's go. Bingo.
I'm ready. I don't know if this detail is
gonna be hard. I'm fucking putting my
game hands on.
Hold on. There's one glove. You can't
tell because the slap
of the surgical glove. Okay that guy
wasn't not that guy was alive.
What the hell is this?
I didn't do the cool thing. I just T
posed.
Jesus.
Who's left? Anybody else?
Okay two guys on that side. Nobody
left in this room so I'm safe to
stand here. So I've got a guy with a
melee. I'm gonna go top right.
If you aim down through here through
the window.
I don't think I can get him from here.
Shit. Oh god. The fucking windows.
Oh I'm so sick of the windows man.
Damn. I'm gonna try going down. Forget
about these guys right now. I'm gonna
get these guys through the window.
All right give me another gun. I'm safe
to go in here and shoot these guys
now.
But I'm gonna do it through the
window.
Oh come on Jeremy. Really? He's coming
down here.
Where is he? He's coming down here.
Die. I'm done here. Ending upstairs.
Next part. Let's go. One two.
Didn't know you were up there. Look at
that gun. Two melee.
Holy fuck. Okay. Geez.
Um. I think it's gone. Window. Of
course.
Window. Of course. You got to be
kidding me sir.
My god. That instant. Bug like
reaction time. Where is this other dude?
Is he all the way up there?
No windows here. It's safe to go up
here.
I can see that they're all dead. No
windows.
Up and in. Nobody else alive. All right.
Give me new gun.
There's windows. What do I do? I'm
freezing. I'm panicking. I'm frozen.
I'm frozen. What do I do? All right. I'm
gonna go back down.
This is it. Just this room and there's
a dog up here.
Get rid of that dog first. All right.
Only one way in this room.
You stupid game.
God damn it. Come on.
God man. Why did that happen?
Fucking hell. Shit. That was the end
too.
Come on. This is so hard. Those guys
can't be stopped.
Oh. I'm actually angry right now.
I was backpedaling but I got stuck
on a couch.
Those guys have to die. Those
people. You have to focus on those
people.
Because if those people...
Fuck me. I was so close too.
They just never stop running at you.
You have to shoot them with a
shotgun. I'm not gonna go in the
other room unless I have a shotgun.
I promise you guys. Just the
slightest
little minuscule tiny teeny mistake
and the whole thing is over.
Oh. It's so stressful.
Absolutely no mistakes are allowed to be
made. Damn it.
I went in here first last time. All
right. Shotgun this dude.
Has to be a shotgun. I can't let
those guys just fucking chase me around
a room and not die.
There's a guy right fucking there.
Jesus.
That's not a knife. What? Is this not
a knife?
Have I lost my mind? That's not a
knife. What?
Let's try this again. I can't see that far.
God damn it.
Oh man. But is there somebody still up
there?
I can't see. Okay. No.
Okay. For the future if I die again
there's only one guy that's up
there.
All right. Make sure I have a shotgun. I
believe that's it.
It's just that room now. All right. No.
No. No. There's a guy over there. It's
all right. Give me a shotgun. Is there a
shotgun?
Looking for a shotgun. There's it. Okay.
Here's one right here.
Plant it right in his head. Got it.
Okay.
Now. Oh fuck. A guy's coming. Which way
is he going?
Holy shit. It's a dog. What? That guy
turned into a dog.
That guy turned into a dog.
Why? Where was the dog?
Give me a break. How?
Oh. Guy runs out of the room and all
of a sudden dog is running after me.
I can't even believe it. The guy was a
fucking werewolf.
Give me a fucking break, man. I can't even
fucking believe it.
That is un-fucking-believable. Got the
guy up there.
Where the fuck? Who are you guys?
I don't even... I didn't even know I had
the fucking role. I keep forgetting
that it's in this game.
And great. You got... you came out
this time. Nice. The one time you
ever opened that door.
The whole game is running after me
now. Anybody else like... running
after me?
Who the fuck was that guy? Who the
fuck was this guy?
What the hell was that? One of the guys
on the ground was not dead.
What the fuck just happened?
I'm losing it here. It's really only...
There's one way I can do this. This is
the way I was doing it before.
And I'm so fucked. How are you
like reliably supposed to go in this
room?
Like isn't part of this game about
going really fast?
How would you ever do it in this
room?
It's just... you have to wait till
they get in a certain spot where you
can get them both, right?
Like dodge roll around them?
What are the iframes like in the
dog?
Okay, that's kind of a huge deal. I
didn't even know there were iframes.
Well, that changes a lot.
Ah, come on.
I gotta just focus on beating it.
I'm not gonna do dodge rolling
shit. Not now. It's way too late for
me to learn how to do that right
now.
All right, I need another gun. Try it
again.
Dodge rolling sucks in this game. I
mean...
I don't know. I feel like it's going
to cause more problems if I try to use
it.
Did I kill the guy up here? Okay, I did.
One, two... this one guy right here.
Holy shit. Okay. A guy patrols in that
room.
So... that guy will kill me. Okay,
isn't that right?
Shoot him. Did I get him? I don't think
I did.
He's right there. Oh my fucking god.
A goddamn computer.
I shot the computer. I shot the
compu-
Calm down. I need a gun. Oh my fucking
god. Give me a break.
Kidding me. How did I not get the other
guy?
The worst part is not being able to
see down here. You know what I mean?
It's just like
taking a guess. When do I unlock the
guy with the mask that you can see
further?
A door. You don't get it in this
game.
Okay, there's a dog. I need a weapon.
Where's that dog?
I'm gonna get- I gotta find that
dog now. All right, he's in that room.
He's over here. He's sniffing me out.
This dog is sniffing me out right now.
He ha- I gotta get rid of him now. All
right, that was the one of the- I'm just
like bumping the microphone. I'm so
fucking on edge.
Don't know where the hell you came
from, but that's fine. All right, back
around.
Where's this guy? Where the fuck is he?
No, he's gonna come around this way,
isn't he?
I don't know. I can't see. I can't
see where he is.
I'm like trapped right here. Dog.
I didn't even know you could- I
forgot you could go through that way.
All right, I'm almost done. Way to go.
Last guy. He's over there, and there's
nobody else, right?
I think that's it, and I'm pretty sure
I'm out of here after this.
No. Where's this fucking hidden person?
Oh, they're down there. Oh no!
No, I'm so scared.
Give me a gun. I need to come with a
lot of bullets.
This'll do. Just two, but I have to
go all the way around and down.
But what if they see me? They're
gonna shoot me
from a hundred miles away, because I
can't see where they are.
You understand? Like, how the fuck- fucking
god,
get me out of here! I think I'm done
here. How are you guys doing?
There's more. There's another one.
There's a whole other floor. All right,
this is punch time.
Oh, okay, you can- all right. It's two
punches.
Well, you have a gun. Come on in. I'll
take you all.
Guy with a gun right there. All
right, he's at the window. Let me get
this guy first.
Okay, no guns, right? Only guy with
a gun is over there.
Window's here though. Where's the guy with
a gun? Up there. Oh, come on.
Out of line of sight, guys with guns
across the map.
It's starting to become tiring. How am
I gonna kill this guy?
Uh, how am I gonna kill this guy?
What the fuck are you supposed to do
about that guy? Punch up through the
window?
Oh my lord. I gotta get rid of this
guy.
Use the gun? I can't. This character
cannot use weapons.
Another guy with a gun. So that's
that.
Any more windows? Yep, plenty of them.
You're down knowing. Let me take a good
look at this. So
there's tons of people with guns.
There's only one way to get in here.
I have to go all the way down and
around. That's the only way I can get
in there. So I have to go down here.
Okay, can I like, can I get them to
run this way?
I think so. I have to bait them.
This is gonna be a pain in the ass.
All right, one more guy with a gun.
Watch out for that dumb window.
Oh no, not a window! Am I safe if I run
up there? No, he's got a gun.
So if he, okay, if I walk over here and
these guys see me shoot through,
but if I run up to this room, this guy
will shoot me.
I wonder if I can bait them. Okay, I got
one.
Holy shit! Oh my god, my body just,
I, my whole body hurts. That hurt.
That actually hurt.
Okay, just this one guy, but I gotta
bait this guy because if I run up
there, I gotta make sure he comes over
here. Come here.
All right, here we go. One punch. Last
guy.
No, this is not the last guy. Oh,
cheesing the level. How the hell are
you supposed to do this on your first
try?
I've never played in the game before.
How the fuck else are you supposed
to do this?
Oh damn, get me out of this. Go get
me out of here.
I think I heard something. All right,
fine, finally!
Can you get the door out of the way?
Why? Really?
You're like fucking hack accuracy.
That's great. Let's go.
Hmm. What the fuck, man? That's such
bullshit.
Honest to god. Oh, that's so infuriating.
How did he not get cut? Dude, I hate
the doors. The doors just make the
enemies fall down and make it harder to kill.
He's left. The whole second part of
the level.
We're, and I don't understand where
he even came from.
I just looked over there. I just
checked.
He's not even dead. I wish you could
just shoot him on the ground.
I really do. How did I not kill him?
Ah, somebody heard it. I'm dead. I'm so
dead.
Hold on, I pressed the razor button.
Sorry, I pressed it twice apparently.
Why waste bullets when you can hit
space and kill them for free? Because the
animation takes like six seconds to
kill them.
When I kill them but they're lying
on the ground and I press space on
them, they take, it's like a full
animation.
Okay, what's down there? Got any guns
down there?
Two guns. Uh, I'm going back up.
Because I think I got the dog on me.
I think I'm coming all the way around
the whole game.
Goodness.
Actually, I want to, I'm gonna, let me
drag the whole fucking level over here.
Seriously. I'd rather just sit over
here.
It's so difficult to even get out
there and even take two steps
forward.
I mean, I just, I wish I could see
further. Like, ugh.
That's it. Here comes the dog. All the way
around the whole game. Come on, all the
way around. Come on, dog.
Start from here and make it all the
way over. You know exactly where I was.
You could smell me, right? See, my problem
is just,
I, walking down this hallway, I might
just fucking die instantly by the,
somebody that's over here.
Hotline Miami 2 in a nutshell?
Why? Oh my god.
Did that dog hear that? Bring him on
over here.
Oh no, hey, come on. Everyone, bring
the pets into French.
Oh, I can't even go over here.
Shoot? But I don't want to shoot because
I don't want to bring everybody else
over here right now.
Ah, here's the issue. Again, here's the
same issue from before.
Am I just gonna step out and die? I
don't know. I have to go this way.
There's no other way to go, so I
have to, I have to, like, sneak in
this room and not die. Go.
There's a guy right there, okay. Here
comes the two guys with the guns.
I don't want to shoot here because
it'll pull everybody and it'll be a
mess.
I can't see. Did they move? Here they
are. I'm gonna follow them.
He's dead, he's dead, he's dead!
Holy shit, I just turned and clicked and
spam clicked.
Fuck, man. This is so ridiculous.
I know I could do it a different way,
but I don't care.
How did he not shoot me? Why did you
not shoot me? Why, thank God, why did
you not shoot me?
But, oh no.
He fucking was behind him. Oh man, I
would classify this game
as extreme difficulty.
I've played Dark Souls, I've played
Demon's Souls, I've played them all.
I would put this one into the category
of, like, holy fuck difficulty.
This is extreme. This is extreme
difficulty.
And there's a hard mode, holy shit. How
do you even play that one?
How do you even do that? I can't
believe there's a hard difficulty here.
How the hell, how does that even work?
You die in one hit anyways.
I fucking panicked. How do you make
this game harder? You add enemies?
What's the hard mode? Guns have
half as many bullets and there's more
enemies.
They're coming. I saw them. Oh, how did
that not cut through them both?
Oh my God, oh my God.
You have to be a corner creeper in this
game. Did you have to do that in the
last one? You didn't do this in the
last game. You didn't have to, like,
shoot a wall and bait a hundred
enemies that have guns.
I don't remember that happening in
the last one. I just played it two
days ago.
Oh fuck.
There's a dog. Come on up here, dog. Come
on.
Just a guy with a bat. Jesus Christ.
Okay, I don't, I need, I need another
bullet. I need another gun. Give me
that gun.
This is, that was a mistake. What are you
doing over there? Get over here.
He's not hearing that? Why are you
not hearing this?
Uh, oh, just shoot.
My goodness. To the roof. We're on the
roof. How are things going for you guys?
Hello? Is anyone there? Guys?
They're not answering. Maybe your walkie
talkie's busted.
I don't think so. It seems to be
working just fine. Should we go back
and check on them?
Mmm.
What the fuck are you waiting for?
Wait, do I not have access to those
two characters? They have, like,
my favorite characters in the game.
I'm not gonna get D. C.
Why is it always the level, the levels
that take me 40 minutes and make me
the most angry.
I get Cs on them. Hey, but to be fair,
let me give myself a little bit of
credit here.
40 minutes is the cap, man. That's
like the hard cap before I hit my
enrage timer. Don't you understand?
And then it's just, I beat it. Hey,
you're not supposed to be here. We've
got this under control. Sure looks
like it. I'll take over from here.
You can't do that. Just watch me.
That level was the pinwheel of Hotline
Miami 2. That's bullshit,
and you all know it. It's fucking hard
when the game is, the game is,
start quote, tough as nails, top-down
shooter that will really test your
patience, end quote. What do we have
here? We're in mass. Another set of
vigilantes, I presume.
Don't shoot. I give up. I'm through
with this. Just arrest me and get this
over with, okay?
I'm done fighting. Oh, you want your
15 minutes of fame? Well, I don't
think so.
You know what happens to thugs like
you?
That's what happens. Are you all right,
sir? What happened in there?
He came at me, had to take him out. It
was him or me. Not even true.
Looks like my job here is done. I'll
leave the rest up to you.
Okay, bye. That's it? That's it,
apparently, okay.
Fourth act, falling. So all the
animals are gone.
Good morning, honey. I didn't want to
wake you. Took Jimmy to school, left
you some breakfast. See you tonight. Love
Sharon.
Okay. I'm having trouble
following the story here.
We have like a Kingdom Hearts level of
shit going on.
Hey, mister. Spare some change?
Sure, here you go.
Boy, look like I want your dirty
money.
Excuse me? We barely got enough money
for rent.
Maybe you should stop trying to be a
writer. We've got kids to feed.
We need a real job, dear. This just
isn't working.
Sharon, what's going on here? I'll
leave you. I'll take the kids and
leave.
You won't have to do that. This book,
it's gonna be good, I promise. I need
more time.
Time is the one thing you don't have.
Maybe you should reconsider your
priorities.
What are you saying? I said I don't
want your stinking money.
Organization 13!
Oh, I thought we were still on the
subway. What?
Well, this is one of those missions
where I can't kill anybody.
It's one of those guns. Guns.
And why would you stop there? Why did
you stop there? You saw where I went.
Why would you freeze there?
Where did you even come from?
The Green Goblin. That's fine. You can call
me whatever you want.
But what the hell? I'm trying to get
this guy to
fade over to me. And he just won't do
it.
He just won't do it. Guy with a gun?
Oh, fucking guy with a gun!
There's another guy right here
coming over. Come on. I got stuck on
fucking wall.
Kill the guys on the ground. I
thought I'm not supposed to do that.
Wasn't I specifically not supposed to
do that?
Yeah, what are you trying to bait me
into doing something that I'm not
supposed to do?
Really? Don't let yourself succumb to
the hate. I'm not.
I'm all right. I can't walk through
this?
Oh, there's a very- you have to go
the right way. I get it.
Windows. Oh god. All right. This guy's-
everybody pretty much has a gun in
that room.
So if I'm going to bait people, it
needs to be
these guys up here. Maybe not. What's
down here?
Nothing. All right. There's a safe spot
over here.
All right. What about- is there any that-
they can come through there?
They're already aiming over here. What's
up here?
Aye aye aye. Aye aye aye.
Give me a break. I did it too and
I clicked it and I
fucking clicked it. What happened there?
What happened there twice?
Two times. Twice. Two. Two times.
All right, there's three guys. Where's this other guy going?
i don't want to go through the turnstile now he can see me from there
this is our turf now boys let's tear it up what's that okay well is somebody in like a mech suit
up here okay well we're gonna have to run him around oh he's he's attracting them i get it
i get it who's left oh shit where is he doing that what's he doing that shit is there another
guy with a gun up here where is he all right all right that that one was not as nearly as
bad as the last one he was building a century he's gonna find rage mode soon i i'm sorry i couldn't
get the door for you my legs aren't what they used to be you're that writer who called earlier
right that's right man i was hoping you could tell me a bit about your son he was the sweetest
child i don't know how he got mixed up in that mess i'm sure it must have come as a
shock to you yes well i noticed that he was behaving differently he was always a bit of a
loner you see suddenly he was going out to meet old friends i never knew he had any
i didn't think much of it a man that age shouldn't be alone all the time
i always felt i was holding him back he was taking care of me you see
did he tell you anything about what happened i only visited him a couple of times when he
was in prison he wouldn't tell me a thing about it said it was better if i didn't know
have any idea what happened to him after he made his escape has he been in contact with
well i can't really talk about that now can i look i just really would like to talk to him
well if he does call i could maybe give him your number that way he can decide for himself he'd
like to talk to you or not that sounds more than fair thank you while i'm here i'd like
to ask you if it's okay to have a look around please do it's upstairs on the left
that's my son's room i've kept it just the way it is that the way that he left it
okay what about like in the trash all the tv's flicker okay march 10th march 16th
hmm dot dot dot dot doesn't remember crts yeah i do crystal retina televisions the end
i made it to beat the game so we're watching tapes who's watching the tapes i've been
thinking oh yeah thinking about what when i get back home i think i want to open up a bar
well you do like drinking i ain't being serious i think it's a bad idea
they used to work as a bartender what are you gonna do when i get back i'm a teacher remember
i have a job when i get back i'm sure you'd make a great bar owner though barns who wouldn't
want to have a sociopathic drunk as their boss yeah fuck you too how about you lieutenant
got any plans i'm not sure the bar sounds nice anything where i don't have to carry a gun and
shoot people maybe i'll find a little convenience store or something put a little tv next to the
register just sit there all day relaxing sounds like you've got it all planned out
i try not to think about it too much this is where he quits the game
things never turn out the way you expect them to anyway i'm gonna go see what's keeping the
colonel this is where i quit the game it's really bad oh god now i now i'm ready i'm
ready for it jerma you will quit this the army levels are ridiculous okay we were supposed
to move i'm gonna give it a try sun's been up for an hour now lieutenant i just received some
good news looks like i might be promoted they're considering me for lieutenant general
you don't look too happy about it sir it's something troubling you now can't you see i'm
celebrating why wouldn't i want to be lieutenant general well besides the fact that we're going
to lose this war on a more positive note you and the boys are being sent back home soon
unfortunately we've got one more mission before that the hardest one of the game the
one you briefed us about last night that's the one charging an enemy camp with just four soldiers
good thing you're an elite unit huh what a piece of shit mission even he's ready for it nothing
good about it son you boys stay frosty don't get yourself killed for nothing you hear yes sir
all right godspeed oh i need to pick a gun i don't know if this is one of the hardest
missions in the game i have to be prepared i'm taking the super machine gun 14 scenes
stronghold okay this is what everybody told me i was gonna rage quit at this mission this is the
one where i'm going to rage quit apparently i'm gonna prove you all wrong it's time to prove you
wrong oops all right let's take a look i'm gonna go all right there's a big guy and we've got
these windows here got a gun can i not pull said don't know i don't need it
careful with the ammo right all right got a guy one two guy on the left let's get that guy first
get another good view i can't see that far wait for him to come down oh there's a guy right
there oh fuck that just scared the shit out of me okay i still have bullets is that guy still
gonna see me that guy's gonna see me do this shit oh no can't see that far ahead let's take
a look we got a guy with a window i don't see anybody up here i have to get rid of this guy
you're not gonna you don't hear this what's wrong with this dude i only got one bullet
save it emo right there the fuck is that guy the we come get me come and get me
fuck the door blocked me the door fucked me up again it took the door to fuck it up again
unbelievable unfucking believable man this these doors are so rage inducing
like i can't just blow through the fucking door why it just seems so stupid like why can't i just
fucking shoot blow the door off you're telling me a little wooden fucking minecraft door is
it gonna stop a fucking like m16 or whatever the hell this thing is seriously still people
over here i gotta i i probably shouldn't man i'm gonna i'm gonna screw it whatever
all right where's the big guy okay i'm gonna go back down all right we got
guy right here don't let this guy fool me i thought i thought i died okay what else is up
here another side where ah interesting okay i gotta get up into the left door here everyone
over there on the right is dead where'd you go where'd he go there's another guy where'd he
go there he is it smells like up dog in here what is uh what's up a dog i don't know what that
is right not yet not yet no no no no where's the ammo is there ammo in here that i'm just
gonna unload and fill it's up here right what no uh i thought i thought i was gonna
okay well whatever that didn't hit you six bullets not good i got a guy here
guy there through the window watch it through the there's a lot of windows here anybody up i can't
tell no there's not okay right here that guy's a machete oh the fucking treat and this is
blocking me all right i need ammo is there a box over here there's no boxes the only
ammo box is over there it's right there fuck all right i gotta bait holy fuck you almost
got me almost got me not this time almost who's up there has it got the gun there i gotta go the
long way just in case if somebody's fucking over here i'm in deep yes there is is that a
wall though is that a full wall it is good last guy actually two more guys and then you
but anybody else check it before you get wrecked all right let's go whoa you you're a
guy okay yeah that i know that okay you saw me i'll give it to you damn it i just got so
greedy i have to shoot them twice i'm sorry i know i'm not supposed to what oh fuck they
have guns right i'm gonna get easy another guy where's the other one there's another
big fat guy there he is okay we're gonna run them all the way around oh no fuck
i did the same thing again i forgot that they they anybody can insta shoot kill you
instantly it doesn't matter they just and you're dead i forgot that's where i gotta go in here
okay that's two there's probably another one i did miss one guy over there but it's not
gonna be a big deal i don't think i need ammo where the fuck am i gonna get that i don't
know what's up here okay yeah great good yeah uh keep in mind i was just looking up there
i was just up there just i was just looking there that's fucking wonderful i think i pressed
the uh razor death adder button again it's not necessarily the i mean these levels this
level is just i don't know it's stupid but the more important thing the thing that's really
throwing me off is the ground it's almost like hard to see the game now i'm dead you know like
the it's like the yellow brick road is just fucking messing with my brain
fuck that guy's still alive i that what why did you get i don't understand why he got up
like what made him get up was he just there i don't understand um i'll take it i'll take it
no more fat guys okay this is i'm gonna i'm gonna walk out here and a guy's gonna walk
down this road because i'm almost out of ammo i think that's ammo down there okay here we go
here comes here comes another guy just walking in a circle all right i'm gonna move is this
an ammo crate i wonder i'm trying to get sniped oh my god and i went at the worst
possible fucking moment oh fuck um god damn it just was not fucking far enough away i should
just shot him i don't think i shot him okay it is that box he's doing the quitting voice no
i'm doing the like what the hell is this voice how is this hotline miami yellow brick road
wartime i thought you had to click it there's another fat guy i'm i'm going a little too
fast here hold on no i got him both okay so that guy's got melee i go up to there not
yet because he's gonna snipe me from down there when he turns his back does he go this
way i wonder if he goes over here i might just shoot him okay one guy with a gun did i get him
no all right last few guys are down here but i have five bullets i kind of need to save them
though the only one guy with the gun so this shouldn't be a problem unless i'm missing
something this is a dog right i would have fucking screamed i would have screamed you
would have heard me like on the las vegas strip if i had just screamed right there
okay is there one guy left let's check two both in separate rooms it's just gonna take a little
bit of just walking over there from this side it's not hard it's just easy just go in there
and just just bop them just do one bop that's all you need to do it's really not a big deal
just uh i'm like i'm having problems because i'm scared to go over here just bop them oh my god
dan here i'm done cleaning out the suites upstairs i have any new guests arrived
this is mike i'm outside greeting the vips all right i'll come down and collect their luggage
fuck oh man that one wasn't that bad it was i just don't like the ground it just kind of
hurts my eyes i thought that the one that i got stuck on for 40 minutes i thought was
way worse than this i just don't like the way this one looks outstanding work soldier thank
you sir i wish my men were as well trained and capable as you we've been trying to seize
this enemy camp for weeks suffered some heavy casualties well i'm glad we can put this all
behind us now yes sir why don't you go back set up camp and get yourself some rest got to go
round up my men got company and i will join you later understood it's the next soldier
mission there's a much much worse ones later oh yeah yay zero points from boldness new weapon
sniper rifle we're going home after this that's what the colonel said i guess that's
a good cause for celebration damn straight we should see if the commies left us anything to
drink this is heat is killing me i wouldn't mind drinking myself when do you think the
colonel will get here i'm sure he's got a bottle or two stashed away somewhere it'd be
a while the roads around here are pretty rough i should probably settle for some water
for now and catch some sleep i feel a lot safer here when d company arrives that's me i'm
gonna get a deal on this mission didn't you hear those guys are pussies we're better off without
them we took down this place on our own didn't we what do we need them for huh i guess you're
right barnes but there's always safety in numbers i'm gonna lie down for a while i
didn't get much sleep last night why are they using the song for intense dialogue um guys come
i'm expelling like all of my mental energy trying to play the game i can't like i i can't like give
you i can't give you like voice acted cutscenes too i'm gonna go lie down for a while didn't
get much sleep last night wake me up when the colonel gets here hard rock all right here we're
back again as this guy this is mary from daycare center on northwest 159th we're having
a parent teacher meeting tonight got it i'll be there uh click hello where'd you go do a fat guy
voice no i can't it's all been sapped from me hello there we're just about to close up here is
there anything i can help you with i'm a member that's how i'm glad to hear that thank you
for your support nobody said fat guy what sounds crazy just think about it for a little
while i think i might be on something fake here i have okay you may as well just use your own voice
and your like your head can in here because i'm just like i don't know what's going on
this plan of yours is make sure it's quick and i really need to be on my way i'm getting
strange phone calls strange phone calls i wouldn't know anything about that look just hear me up
these phone calls are telling me to do stuff they sound like they're some kind of misplaced
calls but they're not and if you don't do what they say well let's say you don't want to
disobey them leaving business if you know what i mean what do you think this has to do with our
organization 13 i don't know i was thinking that's all you're getting it was awful
i didn't have enough brain power for it what if we set up a similar operation
like we go after the russians free america of our oppressors you know i mean you have
all these members and all the very so i'm i'm doing a terrible job i'm doing the thing where
your mother is reading you a story and she's falling asleep and her words start to run together
many of us have military experience if we'd wipe them up we could start a simple movement
free ourselves i'm not sure i follow we're a peaceful organization we never force anyone
to do something they don't want to i'm not sure what you're accusing us of man you're
not listening i'm not accusing you of any oh i get it you're the ones it all makes sense
i can't believe i didn't figure it out sooner my god in here i was thinking i had this great
oh man look here sir we're closed okay if you don't mind really like for you to leave now
can't talk about it here i got you don't worry i'll keep your secret safe you can count on me
why is this garfield why is this garfield the monday killer doing bits we're both patriots
right i'll just go now i have something important to do if you know what i'm saying huh
okay well withdrawal i really miss the masks is there how does it how the masks even work in
this game i feel like this is only the second or third time i've been able to even pick one
lethal throws are nail gun uh i guess i'm gonna use the nail gun did they just remove
that whole mechanic from the game what happened i got did i get shot started over
oh nail gun all right we got down up left right one guy nailed all right two guns
this nail gun is actually pretty cool dog and i got two guns but a dog and i gotta get the
dog with the last one got it okay oh that's gonna be tricky give me a gun what the
fuck was that all right two guys i gotta be careful hide behind here and let's try to
make this quick oops oh my god i almost didn't win oh boy i might be getting a little rusty
okay i didn't even see that guy wow well that alerts everybody one two three keep going
14 bullets i got a big guy oh i did holy shit what the fuck is happening here get it
jex is back and he's fatter than ever fuck i got greedy what's going on what what happened
what we told you what i'm playing the game okay how dare you focus on the video game you
should be looking over here what he's not gonna talk is he well i don't want like spoilers
like hey by the way don't die on the third floor because it ruins the rest of the
game and it is a cutscene you're gonna miss i don't want to know that i mean i
just lost whatever i'm not gonna talk got any last words asshole that's it isn't that the
equivalent of like just telling me spoilers for the game because if i do know that then i'm gonna
hope i would like play differently i probably would still have lost so you didn't is not like a
i probably still would have lost don't die game ruined well it wasn't don't die it was
apparently specifically don't die on the third floor don't die on the third floor do not die
on the third floor it's like why why not oh okay something will happen if i if i don't
okay did you find anything uh well no nothing substantial we're good now right no more favors
me too okay october 30th so tomorrow's our last mission huh yeah they can't find another
bullshit reason to get us killed uh-oh but once i agree with you barnes why are you always
picking on me we're in this shit together that's for tomorrow i don't get it i really don't
how the hell are the four of us gonna capture a power plant they should be sending
in a whole platoon the place is likely booby trapped too risky for a whole platoon
i guess we're more expendable do you see this can you see my face this is my true nature
you see don't you this is who i am this is who we all are we're animals there's no denying it a
bunch of goddamn animals they're sending us up to slaughter or be slaughtered and here we sit
until they tell us what to do and how to do it no will of our own just mindless obedience
we don't even know why we're fighting now do we only knows that the deep down somewhere
in there we just enjoy destruction and violence it's just part of our nature
i really am reading these like fucking garfield bits sir are you okay
oh i have had a bit too much to drink i'm feeling a little bit tired maybe i better go to bed
that might be a good idea sir i wonder what kind of fucked up shit he's been drinking
okay new weapons so i choose a weapon or not not yet lieutenant yes sir i don't feel very good
today a bit much to drink yesterday that's dog i've got nothing to do with it unfortunately
i've got word that they're sending you boys home tomorrow lord knows whether they'll be
lying or not but that's not the issue i'm afraid this might be your last mission son
and that they'll be sending you home in body bags you've seen the plans you should know
you'll be walking right into a trap and there's little i can do about it i've already said this
to the others and i'll say it to you too it's been damn good commanding this squad lieutenant
we may not win this war but i couldn't be more proud of you boys thank you sir good
luck out there you'll need it see i'm acting i did some acting all right so we just got a
sniper uh i think i have to i'm gonna stay with this i'm staying with the with the
fucking heavy machine gun what sniper pick up the sniper what's what what what what's going on here
what should i not die on the third floor it's in emote only mode now i was gonna go with this
because it's powerful but somebody said this gives me the giraffe power up if they better
you better not be lying to me level 15 casuals some giraffe this is unbelievable thanks for the
giraffe lie thanks for the giraffe lie those guys are real i thought they were part of the
environment holy fuck okay i needed to reload the gun i'm okay fine fine fine fine fine fine
we're fine we're fine why did it hit the this thing sucks oh yeah give you the giraffe
powers Jeremy they get one of the giraffe powers see how far it goes she made it she made
it she made it she made it she made it she made it she made it i need to get a drink
i have to get a drink of water or something all right everybody relax he's kind of
they don't have heat stroke what the fuck are you talking about all right that's blocking
them right there i'm gonna wait oh my god why are you still doing it then Jeremy i have to
um
it is the giraffe gun what did i just get reverse baited is that solid i think it is
all right i think that's the only two guys left here so i gotta be very careful
very careful is he dead
wait for these guys to come down and then go where the fuck did you come from
where am i going i can get that guy i'm just gonna go faster just like that that's how you
get it done that's how you get it done oh whoa oh what did i freeze for i fucking didn't even
see him i missed and here we go time to die dead dead dead oh my god will you die
i actually might be better off just wasting this shit here we go i got him get ammo all
right now get this guy you stupid motherfucker how is it fucking possible i had you lined up
perfectly it was perfect everything about it was perfect no i'm taking why were you not together
that's the first look at only time you've ever not been right together we didn't get it it's
all right yeah you know my favorite part about Miami is uh the hotline portion of it you know
i love Miami i love like the Miami scene i love playing hotline Miami i love Miami it's
Miami's wonderful this time of year i hear i gotta go this way this is i you gotta go this
way you have to oh you can get them both okay i only have one bullet
what the hell is what the hell is this wait for the other guy did it hit him i don't think it
hit him no it didn't hit him i don't need this shitty sniper no it's still locking on
and locking off locking on locking off only you could see further but i can't i can't go back
oh man fucking Miami sure is nice this time of year get in i know i know i know what this is
not Miami that's the point i want to be in Miami i don't want to be in like war zone where
does that know it's gonna restart the whole thing isn't it maybe i need to have the sniper
rifle i don't know i'm just so fucking over this part of the game i'm so fucked i have no bullets
i have to like go over here now i'll be fine i'm gonna be fine no that's a regular guy he was
yelling at chat no because i picked up the sniper rifle and everybody told me it was awful
it was like don't pick that up don't pick up the sniper rifle put it back it sucks and
i'm just like all right i need the i need two bullets for these big guys is one all right
don't not yet hold on don't do it yet this guy's gotta get the fuck out of here i'm gonna wait
i'll wait the whole damn time i've lost my damn mind oh i have i've lost my mind okay here we go
shoot him once and then hide okay now what do we got there's a guy right here but what's up
there too bad i don't have the sniper rifle to be able to see what's down the way
maybe you should have picked up the sniper rifle got you what what is that what did this hit
i hit the wall i have one bullet okay i gotta be careful for real i don't even know where
any enemies are i don't know what's down here ah is there anything over there is somebody
through that door i don't know i think this okay this one guy i don't have any more bullets
oh yes i do yes i do yes i do yes i do i'm having a good time here fuck but what um
what i what uh i don't know what else is over here am i okay all right i got him
now now there's one guy here that corner is safe but is it though because there's a guy
right here what the fuck are you i need to take a second i need to break hold on i need i just i
need a second for hold on i will accidentally run over there and get hit okay um if you can
put okay listen this is important uh there are people with superpowers living among us
there are you see that movie with bruce willis let me tell you something if you can do this
on hard and just fucking walk through it like there's no problem you are seeing the
world at like 0.85 you know 0.85 speed you just are and you're super human i am very convinced
that some of these like esports players some people that are very good at video games and
just like have lightning you're seeing the world at like 0.9 where everyone else is seeing
at 1.0 you just are you have to be you have a superpower because how the fuck is this is
ridiculous okay i got nine bullets got it thank god you're seeing the world in 1.2 times
i might be i don't know but sooner or later someone's going to figure it out some scientist
is going to come out with a study yes it's really it's quite interesting you see uh a
tenth of the human population is actually perceiving the world at 0.97 speed it's
remarkable that's why you know there's you know baseball players have this superpower uh
football players soccer players video game esports players i'm telling you it's going to
happen oh i don't shoot redo it no just kill me i can just bait people out of here
what the fuck were you look at that fucking super human eyes that guy has that's bullshit
i get to see the world at like 1.14 why do you get to see it at like 0.92 it's not fair
that's why it's not a fair i slow that person's game down now speed that person's game up
i can't leave that's the problem i can't leave once i get in there what why am i not allowed
to leave i can't leave you it's so you can't cheese it well that's wonderful i need to at
least be able to get rid of like one of these people i can't shoot through this
oh nice horn oh listen my mind
all right who has a gun who has a gun who has a gun this guy's a gun he's dead he's dead who
else has a gun oh okay you idiot you idiot that's ammo right there shoot this guy through the
fucking window and then get the ammo what about the guy with the gun right there
i have cover it's just a guy with a machete there's nobody with a gun here go up and just
touch it and get the ammo oh fuck that guy saw but it's okay relax why did you do that why
did you do something like that why would you do nothing why would you do that okay everything's
fine i'm not gonna say it i'm not gonna say i'm not gonna say peter i'm not going to
you thought you were gonna get it out of me this stream nope i may have lost my fucking
mind but i'm not gonna say it one of these guys has to be baited out here get over here
you already did i know i did not i'm certain of that i am 100 certain i did not say peter
i didn't i am a thousand percent certain god fucking damn it stop who cares if i said peter
i don't give a fuck why does it matter that shouldn't matter that shouldn't matter of all
things to matter right now and i was going well oh yeah he said peter hey hey hey peter
hey what do you think he's going psycho i'm losing my mind man i really am
oh he shot me through the window i'm gonna fucking win i'm gonna beat the fucking level
that you guys said peter you know what i'm saying i'm gonna do it big guy big guy can
you see i did a game okay watch out for the guy in the window guy in the window
i don't think i can do anything about this at mom it's over it's over let's go one two three
four five six i have to shoot the big guy through the window you fucking stupid game
why is it impossible this is the guy i need to shoot right now go done
okay listen to me peter is there anybody else with a gun
stop moving for a second i need ammo i have two bullets okay okay i'm safe right here for now
what happened what happened no uh what the fuck happened why you shot i tried to shoot the guy
and i couldn't and i thought that summons the whole fucking room i'm going this way fuck it
okay i can get in there this is horrendous this is horrendous because now here comes everybody
all right like is it i seriously please i'm not gonna rage quit i'm going to beat this level
as stupid as this level is and it's just like hey i have an idea let's just like make it
impossible hey you got a fun game yeah it's called hotline in wartime shoot through windows
and walls uh miami too what do you think meter oh my fucking lord the fact that i can't go
backwards is just like give me a break i have to shoot this guy otherwise the fucking whole
thing is already standing this can you bait to the room no you're not allowed to leave once
you come in here for some reason it's the only level in the entire two game series where
you can't walk out of the door in the whole two game series why why die die die die die
okay one guy with a gun i i gotta i can't shoot him though every time i shoot at that guy the
whole fucking entire rope level attacks me what no guy with a gun rights no guy with any
guns right i don't know if they cross paths here i gotta get ammo and i gotta go in this
room but i can't be seen so just do it now why did that happen why did it did i click do you
have i didn't didn't pick up the fucking ammo until i clicked i want to test something here
for real like hold on okay so you have to click so if i clicked it just shoots the fucking
gun well that makes no sense it's right click i'm just gonna inhale the fucking universe
so huh let me ask a question to chad a real question when you got to this level were you
like this is the stupidest game i've ever played in my whole life did you did you did you get
there did it happen at what point in this mission did you go hey this is probably the
dumbest thing i've ever done as an adult when when did you do it all right i'm slowing
down all right lord true from outside the building but that i i i have to get like the
perfect angle here no i can't you can't wait why could i just do it there why was it allowed
there and not where it was fucking lord no i'm fucked again i think we need to meditate no i
why is this in the game why is this in the game okay let me cheese ball the whole level
is this what you're supposed to do is what you guys talk about is what is what i'm
supposed to do i'm not done though a guy's gonna come right through here and start
running at me does it happen last time all right right click here comes the other guy with a gun
don't shoot him i need to where the hell do i even go from here i'm okay two guns one
i got machine gun machine gun i have to stab this guy i think i don't know maybe i can't
because if i shoot it's gonna everyone's gonna sprint in the room there's a guy over here
two machetes so let me bait out this guy right now he didn't even see me somehow
some somehow you just god damn it man oh my fucking lord and now i'm back out here again i
can't cheese the level anymore kill me going to the right room well i that's where i was
planning on trying to bait and now i have to do this thing they'll like cheat to beat the
level thing just rush the level how on earth am i supposed to go fast what are you talking
about well how am i supposed to do that if i don't know where the hell fuck i'm supposed
to go just go fast and die okay let's see if i can pull this dude you know fuck it just
get in here right side is clear new ground reached rushing in is the way it's played oh
i agree for 90 percent of the game but i can't do that here everybody has an assault rifle
that's the top of the level oh god okay there's no windows right so let's try this
i don't have any ammo there's so many people in this room i need to get the ammo just don't
shoot me please nobody over there right just get it one two three four guys with guns
baiting is going to be fucking nightmare stay right here okay only one more guy with a gun
i'm fucking losing my mind i'm panicking okay that's it right last guy
what the fuck jesus christ oh there's more of this shit okay what the hell else is here
i need ammo is there a big guy in this room in this level i can't tell space part execute i
didn't have brain power for that oh my fucking god all right let me how far away is this at
the end of the game or is this just like the hey throw this fucking dumb shit in the middle
of the game what the fuck happened there i tried to click whatever no guy with a machine
gun coming up here i try oh it's not throw weapon oh man i'm getting to the point where i
oh boy is this it's no it's right click to change not right click to throw big guy there's a big
guy in that room let me go down do you see me apparently you did no guns down here not that i
can see right i don't see any guns what the fuck is that okay i'm fine i just he's got a
gun i can shoot him through the wall is it where's the big guy i've not seen big guy yet
he's definitely over here i think the big guy might be the last person in here now it's that
room big guy and a guy with a sword okay back around looking for windows okay guy with a
machine gun big guy and a guy with a knife i can kill the guy i can knife this guy right
now and then it should be not that big of a deal i just have to shoot him and then run
out the fucking door make sure this shit is open there's no ammo in that gun dude i did it i
fucking did it i did it get me out of here i don't care what's in here exit no that's not
it that's not it i need ammo was what did i what did i say it was kind of like difficult
like really like sort of difficult oh no i said that's the worst thing i've ever done
as an adult oh that's right i forgot i've done so many more worse things think about that the
worst thing i've ever done in my life as an adult okay it looks like their boss totally lost
it no point going in there now is there because i think we better get out of here
what did you do as a kid what the fuck how do i get out of here 40
yeah each shit level my name is ben smith my car's broken down on me
i need can you repeat that my name is fuck it look we need a case back here
1942 51 55 28 then step on it he's bleeding out hang in there buddy they'll be here real soon
no need to thank me kid it's on the house you would have done the same for me right
i think i hear the chopper coming maybe you should take this so you don't forget who saved
your ass is it is all right is there i got c-minus on that level and it was 32 minutes
oh wait wait that felt like four hours how is that less than the other level that i
freaked out at i feel like i was there for four hours i don't remember what we've been
talking about okay i got a flamethrower sorry to hear about that things like that are
never easy well yeah you know what they say time heals all wounds right so you remember
that photo we talked about from hawaii did you ever get around to sending me a copy of it
right well whenever you get a chance man look there seems to be something going on outside my
shop i'm gonna go have a look okay all right talk to you later bye all right this is this
happened in the first game there's a guy beaten up over there or no time is being
melted away the tape fucked up time to put in a new tape act five intermission so this is
we're at the halfway point made it to 50 of the way done the phone hello evan speaking
hi this is you spoke to my mother i didn't do a coca-cola classic i'm sorry guys
i'll be right back you guys didn't know i've been here the whole time down here uh is it a
bug on my monitor yeah i've been sitting here this whole time i thought there was like a
bug on the monitor but yeah i love i'm gonna turn the camera off now so just in case you
guys curious i'm going off i don't even like drink soda i've been drinking so much like
soda lately uh thank you nico for the 50 dollars earlier thank you so much
it's a lot of fucking money dude thank you i said you did it well yeah i i went i was
kicking and screaming but i did do it all right let's go so how many more temper tantrum
levels do you think there are hi this is you spoke to my mother she told me to call you
said you wanted to talk it's about the mask maniac right right i didn't think you'd call to
be honest well if you've got time i'd love to hear your story i've got time all right but
it'll cost you see i need a plane ticket i know it's a lot to ask for but i'm sure
it'll be worth your while do we have a deal well i can't promise you anything but if your
story is half as good as you say then i'll see what i can do fair enough so where do
you want me to begin right from the beginning i want to get the full picture all right well
it all started with these strange messages on my phone at first they were pretty straight asking
me to do things small things like calling random numbers leaving cryptic messages
going around town painting these marks at certain points marks yeah i circle with three
lines across anyway i didn't want i don't anyway i didn't do what they told me to figured it
was all a prank after a while the messages started getting threatening a few days passed
and one morning i woke up to find my car torched and there was this message on my
machine saying i better do what i was told or bad things would happen the phone let's listen
you've got one new message hi this is susan from miami funeral we've got an appointment
scheduled with you today for the funeral of uh rosa burg come whenever you like
we're open all day our office is on ne 139 click whoops a daisy no go back what the
hell are you doing all of the rules of 17th scene first blood wish my happy anniversary to
your girlfriend okay well i got fist this is a big bar all right knock the guy out
i watch this one no never mind watch this one instead i can't go that way
okay wait wait wait i gotta use the door all right use the door
fuck fuck fuck hey nice nice door there's a guy with a gun over there where's the guy the
shotgun i have one bullet fuck what was i thinking uh just talk about guy with a shotgun
shit no wrong item i don't know this fucking like a hundred melee weapons on the ground
and somehow i keep picking up the shotgun like there were seven explain it to me i'm standing on
a pipe why did it pick up the shotgun why i'm standing on top of it it prioritizes it on this
level that's bad fuck that priority bullshit no that's not how you have to use the bandwagon
it's faster all right slow it down i don't give a shit about the combo right now
it's hard to kill seven people ten people in the same spot all right give me the shotgun
oh fuck jeez i didn't even pick up one with it i didn't pick up all the ammo get that fucking
gun out of here um excuse me could you what the fuck was that ah he saw me is this guy
gonna come over here or what are you doing man a lot of people down there oh yeah okay
that's it right there's two guys in melee look how much better you are after the hard
mission though yeah but fuck that man i lost like a year of my life just c minus these levels are
like fun that's like that's cool trying to figure out a fight like 10 guys in the same
room that's cool five stress years mom what are you doing down here i was hungry so i decided
to have a snack i can take care of myself you know you don't have to worry about me so
much you know the doctor told you not to move around too much i don't care what the
doctor said i'm not dead yet i'm deleting that from my obs source like i don't know why i keep
doing that i'm not dead yet i still got some fight left in me i'm gonna just delete it
from my my obs window because there's no reason for that to be there anymore it's the same
like lean in you want to do a face cam for one of these like a real one fine i'll do a
real face cam no that's the wrong one okay hi guys how are you why am i so this camera
was like in the wrong spot that's better look at okay look at how my i want to see
i want to see something funny look at how my hair has changed i look like fucking crazed
ready for this look at this shit don't i look fucking crazed right now with my hair all
fucked up see it's like slicked back i look good this is like months of stress which
one's the real one the one that looks like shit that's this is like after six hours of
me slowly slowly dying all right that's fine is that in a good is that in a good place
all right time to head out you get to see the fucking dumb faces i make and how fucked up i
look something urgent i was hoping you would give me a bath i'm feeling a bit cold
uh sorry mom i'll help you with the bath this i don't like the fact you can see me drink
this uh i see well where are you going then is it another job interview i'm sure you'll get
it this time i'm sure you'll get it uh don't get your hopes up mom finding work ain't he's
you're such a bright young man you're such you're missing out you sure missing out don't worry
you'll find something eventually yeah well i gotta go i'll be back as soon as i can okay
uh you run along now dear you don't want to be late use a straw to save your teeth to
damage them or i'm gonna i'm gonna floss after this you got a new message hello this is andrew
from package express you have some goods to deliver the shipment may be fragile so make
sure to handle the package carefully don't be late and don't forget to wear your uniform
here we go all right this is why like i don't have face cam returned on you're about to find
out why i'm making a weird corridor can we go like this so i don't look i have the
fucking lady from the brady bunch hair again i don't know how this keeps happening what's
what's her name the the chef on the show alice yeah demolition level 18 scene 18 okay
this one's a little darker than the last few okay i gotta throw okay bait punch punch grab throw
grab throw smack throw punch swing why am i doing this oh i can't do that can i go over here
is it only the can i go in the back door why would i be able to even come over here
okay that's not a glitch i gotta throw that at the guy over there can you even kill the
big guys with melee i don't think you even can no you can't so i have to throw melee at guy
with gun grab gun shoot big guy well he was in the wrong spot fuck all right go now
damn it fuck you it prioritizes guns it prioritizes guns oh look at me look at me
it prioritizes the guns
all right where's the gun shotgun oh i fucking missed and that was the one right there
i don't understand why well it's not picking the shotgun up the weapon priority
it just doesn't matter it's just it's just random it's a random number between one and
fucking 12 damn it man in a world where it's it's so hard to like actually
i've run over the gun like three times and try to pick it up it just picks up another
item what in the name of fucking god does it keep doing that for why rush the guy with the
gun he has a he has a gun it's fucking locked onto him too and i can't understand why it
continues i'm trying to press d and s at the same fucking time what am i locked onto of course
where are you going you gotta be close enough to throw it at him but it's an open fucking
area it's just open everybody can just look at you i gotta be close enough to throw this at him
and then just run to him okay what kind of level is this by the way what is this like
level design it's just a giant fucking all it what there's no level here where are we
oh we're on a roof what is this why these people where the couches where the tvs
and it hit the fucking wall and bounced off and just stopped oh my god i gotta i have to
just like go i have to go like this just move in fucking erratic patterns no it doesn't matter
kill three melee and wait but i have to be close enough to throw the thing at him
if once i get to a point where i'm close enough to throw it at him i'm just dead every time
it didn't even it didn't even matter that time there are other doors i can't use the other
doors look they cannot be used i can't go over there and get it it was no there's only
two bullets in that gun any of the guns oh why this is so fucking painful it's like got you
bullshit how did i fuck it up because i couldn't pick up the gun the first time
it's very easy when you run over and press the pickup the only thing that exists it's all it's
pick up weapon on ground stop locking on and throwing it well what how else do i make sure
i could like get it on him and sometimes he just runs over here no fuck he's got that like
bodyguard with him to try to like ambush him around the corner it's like you run into the
fat guy and the fat guy just punches you why did this game turn into like hitman go by the way
like what happened hug the wall you talk about like when he comes down here hug this wall but
then the fat guy is going to punch me in the face oh my god all right so fat guy still so i
have to go like right there and then sprint and punch him where's the other guy wouldn't
there three people in this level what's he doing all the way over there no no oh good you
beat it you beat level four and hitman go all right look at all these fucking people with guns
man holy shit get rid of the fucking dog jesus they can't ah damn it so so they heard a
silenced gun did that i don't even know what happened oh there's not even a door there
what the fuck i thought there was a door here the fuck am i gonna do this i need that
shotgun to shoot the big guy oh come on through the door hi give me that shotgun
oh this is the maddest you've ever seen me it's because this game is fucking ridiculous mad
because bad yeah sure sure i wonder what your first playthrough looked like that's where let's
let's let's see your video of you playing the first time huh i think you did a thousand
fucking times all right back up hey i beat it already what's your excuse i'm my monitor don't
that's not funny the like monitor falling backwards is not like a thing i want to do
tonight all right where's that there's a dog did the dog is dead and the guys just rushed
it and what why do the other guys don't come in i don't get it why do these guys all don't
run in just the guy these people heard that somehow turn the brightness up give me that
gun same deal all right now give me something better than this the shotgun is all right i don't
the shotgun i'm not a fan of the shotgun i mean look at how many guns are just pointed at this
door it might be better off just going around here but it's gonna it's gonna pull everybody
i'm gonna have to know but as these guys will shoot me too i really don't i don't know i
think it's just kind of pick them off from here all right there's only a couple left
question is when i shoot this guy i think i'm gonna go through here
give me a break i fucking can't believe that didn't kill them all
god damn it it's just so many reflexes in a second time just takes like a quarter of a second
he's dead and stuck on the fucking wall use fists when they rush you when they are all
shooting guns at you you would use fists you want to use fists when they when the seven or
eight people with a shotgun you punch much faster they're rushing through the door you
instead of shooting just punch um how how much is actually left in the game
before i literally strangled myself but how many more levels are there do you think how many are
there like six the six more chapters to this game you're on the first level i dropped it
i can't i couldn't see where it was on the ground rage quit well is it a rage quit if
the game is like 10 hours long and six hours of this is like mind melting you can't you
don't have to be the whole thing in one sitting they heard that i gotta get i'm turning the camera
i gotta go camels yeah i'm losing it it actually might actually i think i might
have to take a break build a gun where's the fat guy go my lord take a blip break and play
katamari damacy no if i take a break i'm not playing this game again tonight dog he's did he
actually see me through the fucking door is there a gun all right that gotta be dead let
me i'm gonna try it let me a few more times this is the nightmare scenario that this that's this
room and then you got to punch my fucking right weapon at the problem shoot shoot shoot it's just
blah i this is a silenced gun though okay there goes that guy once somebody shoots here it's
over let me what's down here no i'll get i'll get caught up in there i gotta go this way i
think oh fuck all right it's okay there's only one guy with a gun here but that door is
open now i only have three bullets before everyone's gonna hear me i gotta make these count
all right one more shot i want to get the guy with the gun oh fuck that guy that guy came in
the room that guy's got a gun i should be able to get rid of him nobody else in there right
that's it i think he can see right he can jesus no oh man oh man oh man fucking hell
wow okay you know how if you go to the playstation trophies menu thing and you go to like how many
people got to like the cleric beast and bloodborne i wonder what that looks like for this game
seriously claret yeah claret beast is the first boss i just i need like a shotgun and i'm just
gonna bring them in here and see if i can just clear it out i feel like that's been a shit
load of this game though am i crazier to think that oh let me just like go like this
and bring everybody in here i is that like you know what i mean shoot and then they just sit here
this seems to be the strat for this game okay i i guess i mean i eventually i'm gonna do this
i don't know i'm gonna pull everybody over here all right this big guy don't just stoop
don't just shoot i missed him all right i got one fucking bullet make it count and i hit the
fucking door god damn it man and hit the fucking door like give me a break that's unbelievable
that's the strategy most people use and complain about but take it from someone who's done s
rank on every level that's not how you do it well if most people do it like this isn't that
potentially a problem with the game itself you know i mean if like most people do it
like this isn't that kind of like a shouldn't it not be like that i don't remember doing
this i do not remember doing this type of shit in the first game this game's a lot of
fun i'm like having i'm having a good time i think the game's like a very fun it's fun to
like run around rooms grab grab what's next but like shooting a wall so people run into the
room i mean like what the heck is that fuck i didn't have i gotta stop picking up the
shotgun damn it i want to at least get to the end of this level i feel like i'll do
it eventually no again i did it again i wish i would didn't drop the gun when i do that how
good why am i doing that try this again all right i mean that room is clear nobody in this
one this is the guy up here i gotta be careful big guy two big guys left nobody in that up top
room okay i gotta i just gotta shoot them once i might even just pull it back no i should be
able to get it okay that leaves these two guys up top which there's line of sight here
holy fuck i almost lost it okay i'm not i'm not enough why would i do that right now
don't make any like dumb jokes they're almost done with this part oh my god oh my reaction times
are so slow they're so slow right now my brain is to process like 400 milliseconds of lag
it's serious i just saw that guy and it was like please shoot guy oh okay oh there's only
one more guy with a gun and i've got to get him first got it okay done oh my goodness gracious
again like we talked about before man like i've got to give it up to the people that can play
this fucking game that well how it is like it's it's so ridiculous i'm gonna watch tonight like
youtube videos of guys beating this in five seconds i'm gonna be like what the fuck happened
you're you're like made out of other material besides brain matter what happened here where
are we going are you oh you're going i'm about to put i'm about to put you in the trunk
no that's not the person that was in the trunk at the beginning of the game
that's your mom okay where am i
oh shit
i'm sorry i'm like i'm fucking fading
so do we go somewhere do i put her on the couch
okay stop doing that to me game put mom in front of the tv put mom in the chair put mom
in a sofa mom where do you want to go i don't know where mom wants me to put her oh i need
to go over there oh okay here you go mom stop getting stuck on the stairs i must have passed
out i was going to take a bath and then i don't remember what happened are you okay you
want me to call the doctor no please don't i'm fine i swear just a bit cold and tired i'll be
good as new in the morning are you sure you don't look too good i'm sure a cough i'd like to get
some sleep now if you don't mind you got one new message hi there this is dan from bush and
flower we've got some gardening work for you uptown a nice old house up on 66 shouldn't be
too hard it's pretty straightforward you'll know when you see it just put your suit on
click 682 deaths house call right through the window actually if i'm quick enough
oh plenty plenty of windows i'm thinking through this door over on the right this whole thing is
a window that we got there's a guy with a gun down here gun lots of guns not really safe
anywhere huh is this covered i don't think it is whoops a daisy is this cover no no i'm done
i just want to see what this level was about the door is covered though i fold them so i got
a gun hold on all right like the video game what the hell was that what was going on in that
video game there watch out for the window although i can do it too but not a good idea
does that guy have a gun no okay machine gun machine gun can get in this room over here
let's get it i thought that was gonna bump into him but apparently not empty give me
another gun all right we got one two i might be able to knock this guy out that's risky
just shoot him okay got it oh i couldn't do that oops wow okay wow i gotta get that out of his hand
right now give me the give it oh i fucking threw it whoops fuck no i don't want to get on top
of them okay i figured it out i gotta get the gun i gotta um god damn i think it was a big
guy no shit okay i know i know what i gotta do just gotta be careful big guy comes out
shoot him with a shotgun where did the guy with the gun come from okay watch it for that
guy with the gun i don't think i have any bolts damn what do i do about this guy thought i hit
him with the what's over on the left i wish i could see i could throw it up there but i don't
know if that's a good idea because if i run in there somebody could probably shoot me from up
here damn it and then it doesn't even matter damn it where did you come from whoa okay i
got it but i don't have any guns okay this is not a bad spot to be in i just got to
shoot this guy once i got it i got it okay that guy in there is gone but what's all the okay that's
the end of the level gun gun gun i don't think nobody has a gun that guy has a gun
that guy does have a gun doesn't he no more guns just this guy no there's a gun up there
okay i got it i actually fucking yeah i shot the guy back there okay it's just a bunch
of chumps in fact give me a melee weapon because there's no reason for me to you
actually give me this i'm more comfortable with this thing right now so we've got a bunch of
guys over here i'm just going to try to get this dude in fact i'm going to get this guy
with a melee no i'm not just okay wish me luck there's nothing else right are there
is there no secrets in this game either plenty of secret shit get ready for the best level
all right am i am i missing something here what what why am i lost already over there exit
the game now exit the game now he's gonna quit on this one this is where i either break or i
transcend hold on a second gotta go fetch another notepad not not yet i'm i mean i'm
getting it to that point where i'm starting to feel it i know we're getting it's getting
really late it's like 2 a.m eastern right now let's see if i let's see if i transcend
okay i'm gonna give myself like 10 attempts to transcend and then i'm gonna i'm gonna call it
because i don't know how much longer my brain can think 10 is so few all right 20 i'm back
so i'm in there just waiting for the trial to start and i can tell you time moves slow when
you're locked up this one day i get a visit that's one of these good afternoon who are you
i told you he wouldn't recognize us why are you here tying up some blue sense just a
little precaution seems like it wasn't really necessary i'm afraid i don't understand oh we
didn't expect you to while we're here we might as well say our goodbyes goodbyes yes after all
you served us well but it looks like your time's up now do i recognize them um you figured out
i'm sure it was nice seeing you again but i'm afraid it's time for us to leave is it the
janitor you take care 20th scene release the hell say your prayers asshole no no no no wait
all right people are throwing bottles so i used to get hit in the head with a bottle right
i'm just gonna oh my lord oh what was that fucking hitbox survive you must transcend
like it's hard to transcend whoa somebody's threw back i did it what the fuck is happening
okay what oh boy so i just have to escape i just have to escape right
everybody the gun all right i think i think i'm at my boiling point i think i've reached the
point where i'm done for tonight holy fuck we made a lot of progress yeah i i don't know if
i can handle this one right now this isn't even the worst room why jesus what the hell
fuck who's left up there okay i'm safe to go down here i can get into the gun i got stuck
it's all right i'm fine all right oh they can shoot through the window fuck god the window
oh my lord now this is it it's the last try but streaming this game again it's like what an
hour or two left of the whole game just all right let me ask you this is this the like
hardest part of this part of the game just it's the six more all right yeah then i'll do it
another night before i actually fucking go crazy all right now's the time as any
transcendence delayed when are you gonna do it again um so the plan here yeah i gotta i gotta
stop unfortunately it really is too much for my brain right now it's about seven hours
or i might even you know like it might i might even just do no it's like 11 30
that's it's time to go so let me go with the plan so i'm not going to be streaming
tomorrow or tuesday because monday and tuesday here i want to set up completely hopefully
their work days to get the christmas stream ready to go so i will not see you guys until
wednesday and we will just probably we'll probably just come back to this and try to
finish it 739 deaths i can't even that's a number i can't count to and depending on
how long that takes us and depending on where that goes can you die one more time yeah that's
okay that was way more than one all right that's gonna be it thanks everybody for coming out
getting addicted yeah it's getting really really late this time to go i had a lot of fun i
did the game's a great game but if you want my honest true opinion i think hotline may
be one is like a more fun game it's almost it feels like hotline miami 1 was a lot of fun
and it was hard but then they made hotline miami 2 and they were just like hey let's let's just
make it even more ridiculous because i i loved hotline miami 1 that was like a fun great
experience i it was frustrating sometimes but i feel like some of the levels in this game
were just like designed to just make you hate yourself it's still really fun though like
you see i kind of can't stop playing it and if you like more of a extreme kind of challenge if
you like more challenge than one then absolutely i think they're both great games i think they're
definitely both worth playing for sure but yeah that's my opinion on it i think i'm definitely
going to finish it and i definitely would give it a recommend but yeah uh let's do the oh we
got a lot of bits holy shit there's there there's like a there's a lot of you guys
give a lot of money tonight holy fuck 158 000 dollars raised so far with hashtag charity all
right so here's what we're going to do because uh because it is so late i'm going to quickly
go through the bits so i'm not going to read very many messages i will try to pick out some
but there are eight hours of bits and it's almost 3 a.m eastern time so we're going
to keep people up like another three or four hours so let's go thanks for coming up see you
on wednesday and let's start with uh seven hours ago thank you craft tech for the one dollar
thank you to bit slay for the one dollar hey everybody german95 here just want to make a
quick vlog real quick i'm in my new leopard fursuit bit slave you gave what what is what
you gave like 30 quarters thank you thank you super seal for the one dollar
what am i going to spend the dollar on uh can of coke thank you cloud 59 for the one dollar
thanks for going live anxiety's been skyrocketing recently and your streams always help
absolutely thank you hope you feel better anything that i can do if you can have fun
here and unwind not on the stream like this i guess but thank you snoozing copter thanks
for the one dollar all right german do you remember this uh do i remember what oh the guy
is like a head being punched his face i do uh do you know the movie or series is from i don't
know what movie that where the guy gets his face punched around the circle and if i have not
watched i need to watch it i don't know what it is i remember using that gift a long time
ago thank you sticks renegade for the one dollar how do you feel about the fact that
thousands of people watch the stream of a dvd logo hitting the corner i mean the dvd logo
i don't know what that means uh and now i'm an enamel and thanks for the one dollar thanks
to the stream today german watching you scream with a hotline too is the best birthday gift
hashtag charity thank you happy birthday sawdust bunnies thanks for the one dollar
divas thanks for the three dollars miss pence thanks for the three dollars
uh daddy i need to see your face oh thank you for the three bucks thank you heath cliff
the friday thriller thanks for the one dollar garfield alter ego hey guys and welcome to the
germa 95 fan club podcast joining me is our resident germologist otherwise known as the
unofficial expert in all things germa bit lore uh germa news germa drama and or germa memes
we'll be discussing this week in developments why do you how many more of these are they going to
be uh there's no more like cartoon cats that exist right you guys are going to be more
cartoon cat than actual fucking humans thank you heath cliff for the one dollar thank you
b beard for the two dollars thank you jamie for the five dollars hey germa just want to let
you know that you're a wonderful human being and are without a doubt my favorite content creator
thank you that means a lot thank you so much jamie for your five dollars
carrot thanks for the one dollar good joke you goddamn evil mastermind i don't know
what's real anymore that's why i was late today by the way i was trying to like get
that done i was just recording that and then looping it and then putting it into obs thank
you bit slay for the one dollar don't worry germa i got a c on my uh arabic test that's all
right yeah george thank you george for the four dollars george bye thank you garfield the monday
killer here's another cat my name is garfin i'm here to say disney animation is getting pretty
cray cray seriously germa disney animation sure is breaking new ground garf's gonna say he's
pretty impressed check out the latest garps group i can't believe they allowed this to be
there because they're good or bad okay what is it it's record ralph doing the thing that
the guy did when he used to dance and sing and it was the original gnome and now the gnome
took it over and then it's the rick gnome thank you garfield but they say disney animation sure
is breaking new ground i can't believe they allowed that in their movie rick gnome extra
cheesy thanks for the one dollar you'd be a pro this game if your keyboard was built into
your pants i know it's too bad i don't have one of those flying flying trolley thanks to
the one dollar die die die death eater uh thank you bit slay for the one dollar nice
noise sounds about right uh novi thanks for the one dollar they say uh they say vigil
aunties vigilantes hashtag charity thank you chicken foot thanks for the 15 dollars chicken
foot hey germa wanted to thank you for all the great content i've only discovered you
recently but i've been watching your backlog on youtube it's been really helping me stay
busy while i deal with carpal tunnel happy holidays and don't get too mad at hotline
miami hashtag charity thank you so much chicken foot welcome uh well we we did get very i did
all right did i get mad at hotline miami too or did i like just i fell down like the insanity
hole i don't feel like i was very angry i was i was angry but i feel like i was not angry
all right whatever i was fucking really mad i was very angry i was fuming it was horrible i
felt so fucking mad i was i was insane angry yeah i wasn't like actually physically angry i was
video game insane angry this game does it to me though it's because it's so quick it's just
it's it's just the game is so fast and it's so easy to make a small mistake even in other
like hard games you can make small mistakes you make one it's just quick quick go go go
bang bang bang bang restart go go go go restart go go go go go restart mistake go go go restart
it's like boom your brain just explodes what what made me go more insane this or dark souls
oh definitely this because dark dark souls you have time to you know you get hit you fall
down you screw up you come back this is just it's like a lightning round dark souls
thank you to d man fun for the dollar and 12 cents thank you germa thank you
lieutenant campbell thanks for the one dollar what are your thoughts on the new godzilla
movie coming out this summer hashtag charity i think it's interesting it's from a long time
ago i mean those monsters they've made those movies a long time ago so i think it would
be interesting i don't know if it's gonna be a good movie but it'll be worth at least
maybe checking out uh but thank you bin hayden for the one dollar hello germa wonder for me
about hotline Miami 2's editor i'm part of a small community that creates entirely new
levels and stories using the tool which there's plenty of fan made content available in the
steam workshop that's really awesome actually it would mean a lot to us if you to check it out
and any attention would be appreciated for hard work we put in to make new content for a game
we love i didn't even know that was in the game that's fucking awesome uh on wednesday when
we start and we complete the game we'll go take a look we'll go take a look at some of
the community stuff on the workshop derma will never look at the game again no i got to beat
it i have i'm so i'm close enough i'm only like two hours away from beating the whole the whole
thing but yeah i'll definitely check it out extra cheesy thanks for the one dollar they should do
a hotline game where instead of taking place in Miami it takes place in some sort of snowy
region and there is sword fighting and dragons and magic and then release it on every platform
with four different editions also i'm drawing art of you i'll show you when i'm done
thank you hey Freudian weapon thanks for five dollars Freudian good night germa hope you're
able to do what you planned for the xmas eve stream either way i will see you there
i'm gonna try and it looks like there will be something interesting on christmas eve
i'm gonna spend the next couple of days seeing just how much stuff i will be able to do
thank you swiggity swanky for the one dollar i think this is my favorite moment
it is it really it's the same sound effect uh captain worgen thanks for the one dollar
excuse you germa i can't believe you'd say such naughty words on stream i'm telling mom
it's okay uh thank you she xoxo for the one dollar germa comet hashtag charity thank you
flank tank thanks for five dollars it's my birthday today cake and ice cream are on the
way i'm such a good boy this year i'm gonna open up my gifts while you all cheer
happy birthday flank tank can we everybody please say happy birthday to all the birthday
boys and birthday girls in here there's a lot of them it's like five bad wolf thanks for
the one dollar germa heart thank you fender mcbender thanks for the one dollar hashtag
charity take a breath speedy t thanks for the dollar 50 i spent at least an hour on the boat
mission on hard mode it's a pain i hope you enjoy death wish no i did i did thank you though
thank you double d11 for the one dollar all right so welcome everybody to the 67th meeting
of the biaz as you know we do this meeting every single month to make sure we agree on
things so let's get started water beer fly fishing beer spending quality time with our
children beer motorcycle revenue beer all right that's it the meeting of the biaz has
commenced i'll see you all next month hashtag charity thank you double d thank you uh
thank you dong for the five dollars it's a bit personal here i struggled with substance
abuse for a long time i'm coming up on three years sober in the early days of sobriety i
found your channel and now stream some days are really hard and your videos have always
helped me laugh and smile when i didn't feel like it you help people more than you know
just by being you thank you much love hashtag charity thank you don't that's awesome that
you're coming up on three years sober good for you that's fucking fantastic hope you stick with
it stay with it you're doing a fucking awesome job so hell yeah and thank you for being part
of this community that's a really fucking hard thing that you're doing but serious
serious much love to you thanks for the five dollars thank you to tae dole swift lure thanks
for the five dollars derma is a tall streamer who did not die to pinwheel what a god of a
gamer seriously thanks yeah i mean everything you said there was was true so i can't disagree
with them uh jinsie bow thanks for the one dollar extra cheesy thanks for the one dollar
whatever you're amazing at lurking and luring those enemies into your traps a masturbator
such as yourself must be good at chess also i want to see if you fell for the joke i made
or indeed a clever boy and stopped yourself i just i'm just tired and i just read it i
didn't even care thank you uh semi per for the one dollar ice wallow ice wallow ice wallow what
is this is this like an emote oh fuck wow wow wow what i didn't even read the next part
whoa and i'm tired as hell too and i'm fucking gamer exhausted i almost got it nice try but
no no no no no oh no no no way thank god i didn't say the second half of that
unbelievable all right thanks i thought it was an emote robot spike thanks to the one dollar
hotline miami too is like 90% baiting luring engaging i know just pretend the enemies are
fish you're a fishing pole with a gun yeah it's just it's just different and frustrating but
i still want to play it i still want to finish it uh thank you to uh robo spike by the way
thank you h rockwell for the two dollars and 50 cents guy through window has a 208
slash 56 kda it's 208 yeah internet internet uh hor hey thanks for the five dollars germa don't
tell me you're miffed was i was but it's hard like all right your first hotline miami 2
playthrough was it just like sunshine through your window and this is wonderful how many times
did you like make a fist you know when you're just in your room by yourself and you're just
like fuck this game this game's fucking stupid like yeah you know what i mean like everybody does
that everybody just starts complaining about stuff you try to find the one thing well here's
the reason here's the reason why the game's fucking dumb let me tell you let me tell you
whether and there's nobody in the room with you you're just like talking you just say you're
just venting frustrations they might not even be based in reality you know what i mean and
then you get to the end or you get to a part where you're like oh actually no that was
i do like get concerned sometimes because when when i play a game like this and it's very very
difficult and it did a lot of timing and you got a very precise aim and it's very hard
i always get scared and kind of sad that maybe people will take the things that i'm saying
and i say like oh this is fucking stupid this game sucks you know what i mean but like it's
not real it you know i really just don't want people to think that like oh this game is
stupid because it's not you know what i mean i really hope i don't come across that way but
i always like feel like sometimes i could especially during like the you know dying
40 50 60 times in a row and you just get so frustrated you just fucking
fuck this this is stupid what is this design what's with this design it's like the game
is fine the game's fun so i hope i don't come off that way because i feel like that
would be if you know a lot of people have now i don't want to come off as like a dick
or like an annoying person you know what i mean that's why it's hard sometimes it was the door's
because i don't you know the rage gamer was just like fuck you and fuck this and fuck this game
but just know that i don't you know it's all in fun and it's all in just frustration you
know but let's keep going dr clay thanks for the one dollar hey uh beater five streams in a
row can we go for six but for real i think you went temporarily insane i did i absolutely did
i definitely went insane there's no if so there are no way hey super hacker thank you for the
ten dollars super hacker uh i don't think you ever pull witness to this awful trash i made
you last year what am i like ready for this right now what is this i don't know if i'm
ready for this
i don't think i'm ready for this
what the hell is that what the fuck is going on this is like freaking me out
it's over not after hotline miami too i have i have no reaction i'm so drained
that was here it is i feel like i didn't stop playing but thank you super hacker for that video
that was that was a wild ride that was very good though it was very well made
uh nico gave five dollars earlier thank you so much again you did it i tried but thank you again
so much for 50 dollars if somebody asks who german is send him that video hey timmy tim tim
thanks for the one dollar sorry to hear about your dementia boomer i hope you spend your last
month here on this earth having fun thank you hashtag charity thank you internet whore
hey again for 15 dollars here take this for better gamer gloves uh this is when i was
losing my fucking mind uh thank you bang con pj salt content is dangerously high yeah
that was like an hour and a half ago i remember that unconquer uh b thanks for the one dollar
hey jay i'm running real low on fuel right now so i'll make it quick i can't tell you
how much i love the streams even though they run pretty late eastern they're pretty damn
fun to watch i can't wait for the christmas stream hope everything works out the way you
want to i plan on sticking around for much longer and await the goofs of the future
take care and good night ps please do more face cam bits i think i can speak for what
for chat when i say that we adore it thank you and yeah that's that's why i may have decided
to keep playing because i'm just sucked into it but it i i am on the other side of the
universe right for everybody it's almost 3 a.m i never went this late back when i was streaming
in massachusetts so but yeah i'm looking forward to it too i hope you enjoy the christmas
i sincerely do it should be fun uh thank you to oh hold on let me get it right drosophila
see got it thanks for the one dollar i hope this game doesn't ruin your perception of the
series i really disliked hotline 2 but hotline 1 is still a great game and i go back to it
frequently 2 is a disappointment because of all the open corridors windows and out of sight
enemies as well as your inability to choose your mask but you can always replay 1 hashtag
charity thank you yeah i mean i've i set my piece on the two games it kind of just feels
like they tried to dial two up like like really like all the way and i mean it's just
a challenge for people and that's you know that's the way it is you could choose the mask uh
only in a couple of missions i think there really was only about two or three missions
so far and i've been up there's only two masks i even had the whole time but yeah i feel
like that opinion is not like an unpopular one though to say that i don't know how split is like
the hotline miami community people that like love these games it does kind of feel like i
love people like two more i love two for the story not the gameplay it's pretty split i love
two but it's more frustrating just still split there's a split it seems it's a good game
but the first one yeah it seems like there's a lot of people that like it that's why
you know it's they're both good games i personally i think i enjoyed one more if one had like a few
more levels then i would probably put it if it's just there's so much more in two it seems like
at this point but i'm not sure but almost done thank you to graveyard ghoul for the
one dollar inaccurate depiction of germa after six hours of hotline miami more doesn't always
mean better no no it doesn't all my bones are gone john hey dinky duper thanks for the one dollar
i don't have much to say but here it goes just want to say thank you for all that you do
whether it be making videos or streaming whenever i know there's a stream coming up the next day
it really gets me motivated it gets me excited for the day i love coming into chat early and
seeing the community interact and talk really makes you feel like you're a part of something
special anyways that's all i wanted to say you can go back to making bird houses or whatever
hashtag charity thank you dinky duper yeah it's great it's great i love just kind of coming to the
stream and before i start because i'm nice i'm usually sitting here setting something up and
there's just people hanging out chatting the discord so full of people it's wonderful
i wouldn't trade it for anything you know it's great i'm very very happy mods are sleeping
it's time it's time for bed uh saturn saturn saturnian ocean thank you the one dollar
i've been a little bummed today because my favorite let's play channel super best friends broke up
today i know it might seem silly to some people to be upset about something like that but i've
been watching them for like a quarter of my life just want to thank you for still being
here to cheer us all up hashtag charity yeah i mean if here's the thing about any type of
entertainment right right type of media when you especially something that's long form right
television shows especially you get you kind of get attached you know you get that feeling
of oh wow is we're in like season 12 of this show and that's like a that's like almost a
third of my whole life and it becomes a part of you know who you are so i don't know if there's
anything i mean you think it might sound silly to think like that but man you know it's
you liked the content you're a fan and you it was something that you watched all the time
it's not like it's just entertainment it's it's something for you to unwind with and
it's like when a when a tv show is done it is oh it's the final season of uh
seinfeld that was like sad for a lot of people because it was just like oh wow that
i love this show you know but the one good thing about it because we're on the world of
digital media that and you can go back and watch any of those episodes right now there's
a lot of content that's available that you can just kind of go watch again really wait
hold on what i can go watch it again really the all caps is what's getting me
holy shit the internet but thank you saturn i don't have any plans on leaving or going away
or stopping anytime soon so uh i i i would definitely let you know i don't know when
that will be i don't know i'm just i don't i can't even give you an answer for when
that would ever be but thank you thank you chrome fox for the one dollar where can i buy a glue man
shirt soon soon soon enough soon enough you'll see it soon tod thank you tod flowered for the
one dollar hey guys where's felix the cat kappa hashtag charity somebody's gonna make it now
and then i'm gonna get like a three paragraph message tomorrow about like felix's world of
fucking horns and like fucking baskets of strawberries whatever the hell he did hey
ghoul champ thanks for the three dollars hard mode adds harder enemies in place of others faster
enemies reversed levels less doors more windows and your ammo is cut in half every time you
pick up a weapon it's really messed up damn i don't even know i don't even know how you
would do that it's like that's so much the game already is a lot and adding that on top
of it all the windows and the more enemies faster people oh but thank you for the three
dollars thank you timmy tim tan for the one dollar didn't you say something about sort of a solo
podcast type thing a while back is that still something you want to do yes 2019 is going
to be when i start to implement some of the things that i would like to try i wanted to
give myself at least a few months to settle here and i mean i've already done something
you know in a studio or a new thing and i'm doing it again but i mean it's not like that
those streams and some of those ideas haven't happened yet but i think i wanted to give
myself a little bit time but that's definitely something you'll probably be seeing in 2019 not
really like a podcast but i don't know i have a few things that i'd like to try we'll see 2019
thank you up quark for the one dollar have you ever done speed running if yes what games
if no why what games would you want to no i don't have the patience to speed run i don't
even if i tried the you know the whole make a mistake and you lose time and you have to
the this is the speed run for me every level in hotline miami is like a new game
there it is the speed run and try okay go go go go that's the reset but if i were to actually
try to speed run a game i think an interesting one to do it with um i don't know the dark
souls games are just so interesting speed run a speed ran dark souls is just cool it's fun
to watch speed runs are about being impatient every time you die you gotta play around
fortnight uh thank you very in for the one dollar hey jeremy just wanted to you know your
messy hotline miami stress here was looking good today thanks for the stream thank you and
then clue the sniper thanks for the one dollar and siroc thanks for the one dollar to end it
clue the sniper says hey jeremy felix the cat here just kidding thanks for the fun stream
and helped me cope with super best friends breaking up well um i'm glad that you can find
at least some fun here on a day that's not that you know you're watching some of
the youtubers right i'm sorry that you were big fans and that now you kind of their show
or whatever is not happening anymore i know i don't know the details but um yeah i don't
really know them at all i just knew that they did videos so and uh siroc thanks uh hey jerry
the fbi uh closing in it's only a matter of time until you're behind bars justice for santa
or everything's gonna be fine thank you bet three for the five dollars hi jeremy hi thanks
for five dollars and thanks for the enormous amount of support tonight there was a ton of
messages tons of money thanks a lot guys let's run the sub credits why don't we and see how many
of you guys have subscribed or resubscribed let's take a look here comes a list of all a
bunch of great people that constantly support this stream and it's fucking amazing thank you
that's all i can say no i just got here well you've got you've got like four hours of hey
this is fun and i'm having like a great time and it's hard then you got like an hour and
a half of i don't even know i don't even know what to say this is i don't think this is like
fucking dumb and what is this and who made this and then like another hour of should i keep going
do it should i keep going and then a bunch of loud like grovely in my throat noises i really
went through all stages it was fun no i had a good time look just because you get frustrated
and annoyed at a video game because it's hard i mean that's that's what's gonna happen
doesn't mean i didn't have fun on the stream i had a great time on the stream the stream
was fucking a lot of fun it's always fun don't you know don't you understand i was okay i was
wondering what i was hearing i thought my stream was fucked up that's the hotline okay there
we go that's better it's just been a heartbeat the whole time local streamer frustration
frustrates himself into highly accurate tom weights impression i don't know man there
was a part in the middle there where i don't even remember what i was saying i was just
blind just saying anything that was in my head did it complete the whole game no i did not
i have about two hours left we're gonna finish it on wednesday i'm on the prison level stress
induced amnesia uh up quark just came in with a doll up can you make a sound clip so i can
make it my alarm to wake up weird request but i think it'll be interesting yeah sure
oh it's time to get up up quark it's time to get up quark it's time to get up quark
or if you want a softer one that's not as crazy it's time to rise the day is just beginning
please get out of bed and brush your fucking teeth and go be fucking there and take a
fucking shower okay see you on wednesday now do a clown one okay hey it's time to get up it's a
clown it's time for you to get up it's the morning time what are you crazy all right i'm
getting out of here i'll see you guys on wednesday haha clown god damn it all right
bye i'll see you wednesday have a great couple of days i'll i'll see you soon