It's been one minute. It's been one solitary minute. Sorry. I had to pee. My mic seems really fucking loud
Hold on. It's a loud mic. Why is it so loud? It's probably better. How's that? That's a good thing. It's good like that
It's good. I don't like being loud. It's scary. Peek the mic. I have a compressor on but no
I'm not peeking any mics. Not right now. We want to hear your beautiful voice. All right. I'm not supposed to be here
I'll be back. Just enjoy the intro. Okay. Well that tweet was not supposed to say that I
Started writing. I wrote mall making stream and then I put some words in front of it instead
That was gonna be like chilling making a mall, but now it just says chilling in my mall making stream
Well, I guess that's accurate
It's like two distinct thoughts. It's accurate though. The first response is what?
I'm chilling in my mall making stream. That's easy to understand
That's fine
Anyways, hello. How you guys doing? Hope you had a good week and
We are back for the next few days
Next few days is gonna be a lot of grab bag stuff
There's the week after this one. We've got Halloween. Whole week of scary shit
Both VR and non VR. We're also gonna be going back to House Flipper for a night
That's not scary, but I got to play it because the VR mode is coming out at the end of this week
Finally gonna play saw 2
Yeah, you will finally see saw 2 on this channel
Next week. We got three or four VR scary games to play
Some of them are probably dogshit, but whatever we have some non VR games to play as well and chubby bunny. Yes
Chubby bunny is next week too. Why is that such a big announcement for everybody? You know what I mean?
Why is that such a big deal? Oh, we've also next week. We've got a big stream chubby bunny
Not that it's really not that cool. It's gonna be stupid. You're not even gonna think it's funny. It's so cool
It's the best dude
Well, I will tell you
I'm probably the only streamer on twitch that will have a chubby bunny segment of their stream. So
Gotta get those accolades right where I can get them
Wrong. No one has done chubby bunny on twitch. I'm almost certain of that who has done chubby bunny on twitch that oh, wow
Yeah, I'm no one has done chubby bunny on twitch. I don't believe you. No one has don't do it though
Oh now I know why nobody's done it. Now. I know why nobody wants to do it. This is dangerous
I'm gonna be very I'm gonna have like a doctor in my room. No, no, no, no, no, no Jeremy. That's too many
You've done eight if you do nine your chance of dying goes up by eight percent per
Bunny you put in a marshmallow you put in there. I'm being audited by the IRS
Well, you fucking shouldn't have lied on your taxes. Holy shit and speaking of taxes 20 community subs from lag X
That's we're talking about taxes. Thanks. That's a lot of subs. Thanks for the 20 subs like an
ink cat gave five oh
Taxes but dude dude, how do you taxes on stream? No, that's like the
Okay, I would rather
I would rather turn the webcam on and be 100% naked
No socks on either and have you do my taxes with me on stream
Like I'd rather do 20 jumping jacks
Completely fucking naked and have a camera over my shoulder while we do my taxes together
I
know dude
Like can I do the naked stream ten times like Satan pops up?
Jeremy you have two choices
You either do your taxes on stream or you're naked on camera for a stream
Can I do ten streams of being naked on camera instead? Oh
Yeah, yeah, I guess I would rather do that. Oh, okay
Right
Disappears
Anyways today, we're gonna play the mall game. That's TOS. Yes, it is. I'm not gonna do that. These are hypotheticals
So this is gonna be like kind of a chill stream
I can't even say that because that always ends up being untrue. This stream is going to be very exciting
Okay, it's gonna be the most exciting stream you've ever been to there now the opposite can happen
This is a game where you build a mall and there's a bunch of little characters that go to the mall
You can build whatever kind of mall you want. It was recommended to me. So I was like, yeah, dude
Let's have like a just chill resident sleeper fucking pogchamp stream
Casino ink to know this is a lot less wild than casino ink. This is more like city skylines, but it's it
concentrated
Microscope on the mall aspect of city skylines and I think it's a little bit easier for somebody with a fucking
Dumb person brain like me. I'll show you and it's got like nice cute. Everyone just relax. It's gamer time
No, it's relaxing time
Relaxing time. I was trying to figure out what I want to do. I could either do normal
By the way already did the tutorial don't need it. Although there's probably some detailed stuff another interesting thing about this game
I don't know if this works, but
If it entered apparently like it's pulling people from twitch from this
I don't know if you guys are gonna be in the game or something. I don't know. So there's four thousand
51 people in the chat. Maybe it's gonna be I don't know. I don't know how this works. Holy shit
We get to fuck up his ball. All right. Well right now this I think I might have okay looks good
I don't know. There's no like accept or submit button. Is it just pulling these names or K Andy Omega Lo
What?
4k Andy that's a shitload of people. We're in 4k Andy
It's a lot of people
That's tons of people. No, there's no there's only
35,000 people watching up football Stadium Andy. Is that what you guys say to like the top streamers on twitch?
Concert Andy only like a hundred thousand people here concert Andy. Okay, let's go. Look at that number fucking climbing
Forty six hundred, let's see what I've refreshed it again. Oh
All right, the audio broken it shouldn't be. All right, let's get let's go. Well, there you are. That's you. That's you
4.6 K Andy it's been ten minutes. Who cares? All right, so we have to make a mall now
Here's the question. Do you want me to play the video game or you know, and you know, there's mild rat infestations
Mild shoplifting. I don't know how that works. Would you want me just to start with money and just go for it?
I I'm kind of know what I'm doing. Let's go for it. All right, let's go. Look if I can't do shit
If I'm like having a hard time
I'll just go to the standard mode and we'll have a fucking resident sleeper pogchamp stream
And that's what that means. It means it's like oh, this is kind of relaxing for like cool game though, dude
All right, $200,000. It's enough normal research. It's fine mild severe rat and I don't want to do that
That's probably gonna be such a pain in the ass
Wait staff have hunger and bladder needs that's the default. I don't know if I want to do that drop lifting normal
These are the people that I don't have so much play default
Severe severe severe severe. No, I'm just doing normal standard demands standard prices. Okay, here we go
All right. This is what we got to start with pretty tiny. This is our builder. Are they in twitch chat?
They are
Double zero trash man. Welcome. I don't know who the fuck you are, but you're like the first person therefore
You're the most important person. This is the most important person in the stream right now
Double zero trash man. Apparently you're 28. Is that real? Is it pulling the person's not here?
This is not a person they left the stream. Oh, man, it's too bad. It's too bad
They took that 4k Andy joke to heart. It's me. All right, let's see
All right, so this is what we got. Look at this shit. Do you see how fucking crazy this could be?
Let's all right. Let's do this right every mall I've ever been to pause the game. I don't yeah, it's paused
Every single mall I've ever been to always has to start out a certain way
I hate with a passion malls that have parking in the middle where they people have to walk out around
No, no, no parking in the fucking middle. It's a disaster
Parking in huge parking lots on the outside
I hate this shit when there's like a road that leads into the middle and there's like parking here and then like
Shops all around it. No, no, no, no, no, no. No, I don't like that. I want big parking lot
Huge part of the mall big parking lot huge part of the mall big parking lot get those cars out of here
They're a distraction. Let's start that here. Okay road work 300 bucks for a road
What is this? Why is this little bill? Why is this like a little big center here? That's not a mall. This is all right
There's four parking spaces. This is like the maintenance person, right? Yeah, that'd be the builder
This is the builder hut they vape wait that they actually you they vape and they they can't and they've been continent
What why are these here can't resist e-cigarettes and bladder can't go below 50 can't resist diapers
Okay. Well, this is a got a little more interesting. All right, let's go. So I'm gonna say let's start our building here
We need a foundation. So I want the first store to be
Should I just do like a giant fucking box? Well, that's
$942,000 never mind. I cannot. Oh shit what I do. How much money do I have? I have 200 that fuck this mall sucks
It's gonna be tiny. How do you make a mall with 200 grain? You need like 200 million
All right. Well, it's gonna do a little store first. We'll expand right here. Ready? This is just be like a fucking CVS
27 fucking thousand dollars do what the hell is this shit? Okay now we're gonna we're gonna build that up
Build is gonna go double zero trash man. I didn't start building you pause the stream. I need to go pee
I'll be right back. No, the mall. Is it open? Yeah, you walls one Wendy's
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. No. Wait, who's this? What? Who the fuck are you?
ASF max it very then there. Okay. This is you manage. Where did you come from?
It's fucking bugleberry. All right now. I know everyone's like, oh wow a mouse over and see where I am
There's gonna be like 5,000 people on the screen eventually like I can't do that. They're not here either. Not a real wait. Hold on
Okay, yeah, okay
6k Andy
What you just every every time we go up in numbers you just add an Andy after it
Alright, so that's it. We got that now we're gonna build we need to have so this is like anybody like a CVS
Foundation how much money do I have cuz you have to have a store room. I need a wall here do it
The fuck is going on that's too small build them build them. Oh, that's a foundation. Oops. Okay build it
What's what's good, what are they doing? Why do they just have like a panic in there? Oh, there's no door
There's no door. I need a door here. Alright staff door
I don't want anyone just going in here and then a little double door here. Okay, build that shit. There we go
Look at these two. Look at these two hard workers
Okay, this is like that can I put like a couch in here?
All right. Now I need I mean I need a door here staff door and then this is gonna be the storage room
So we need to assign that look I did the tutorial already like a fucking stupid idiot
So that you have every if it's a store it has to have storage
Otherwise, you can't stalk the shelves. It's kind of a tongue-twister. This is storage and this is the store. Well, hold on bathroom
Oh shit. Hold on. We need a I need a wall. You're good at video games
It's not even five minutes man fucking stupid idiot
Okay
Okay, Andy, I need a bathroom. Is that too big?
How big is this door? This store is a storage room in a bathroom. This be a staff bathroom
Is this gonna be like half of those stores you go into and it's like, oh, do you guys have a bathroom?
Oh, yeah, but you ain't going in it. Oh
Okay. Thanks next time that happens. It's just just hold up a $20 bill. You guys got a bathroom. Oh
Oh
Mr. Albertson right this way and then they leave me out the back exit close the door and lock it
I need a door pause this I don't want this thing to be open yet. Okay, we need a door a see-through door
Isn't that kind of weird? All right bathrooms gonna be right here. Then I need a toilet
Toilet cubicle toilet sink. Wait, is this a sink toilet combo? No, what? Oh urinal. Okay. Wait, wait
I have to assign this as a bathroom. Okay, this is a
No, that's not the store. Oh fuck. I messed that up. Wait, delete that warning
This action will delete at least one active zone and will fire any staff. That's fine. All right restroom
Oh, fuck you. Okay. This is a bathroom. I need to rename these the restroom two is not gonna cut it
Can I rename this? I don't think I can how do I rename shit put a bowling alley in the bathroom restroom two
Where's where's where's restroom one? What? Oh, okay. I was gonna say why is it a bathroom down there?
Okay. So now let's put it. Let's put a toilet in here toilet cubicles. Yeah, I like that way better
That's three stalls. Let's do a sink which is right here and then we'll do urinals on the other side
Beautiful done build it turn the toilet into a store
Not hold on. I so I gotta get a feel for the game. I build this up. Nice
Okay, so we got a bathroom now. We need this is the store part, right a sign
Store wait, what do we want this to be a store or a bar security center coffee shop?
Oh, I need to like research this shit. Alright, let's make a store. This is like a CVS. No, fuck
How do I make the same store?
shit
Delete that. How do I make store three? Okay. There we go. Perfect. Cool. Okay. Now what what kind of store?
What do you think we should do? Okay. Hold on bill. We need objects. I need shelves
Is it make it a Best Buy positive they get a Chuck E cheese. No, this is the CVS. I get a gas station
No, I can't I can't make it again. What's going on in the lower, right?
Okay for a second. I thought an ad was opening in the bottom right of my screen
I was like this is no like ads, right? I thought I was like, yeah, right. Did you feel that way?
I build we need shelves
Okay shelf bar shelf just a regular shelf
Look at you can have look at how much shit you can have here that and like that and then okay. Hold on
What should we kids gonna be like toiletries and shit may leave yeah, they can get out. Okay. Okay, that's enough
That's enough. Now. I need a checkout queue check out counter shit. Okay, hold on only three people can go here
Oh, there we go. Wait, wait, wait. Okay here nine people can fit here. Oh fuck. Hold on. There we go
All right, right there. All right. There's a checkout queue right there. Now we need staff
We need a I need to like have deliveries come up here. Don't I wait wait wait manage the store. I got a link
Okay, this this is the storage for this. So link this link it to storage here. Okay staff. I need a cashier. Okay
Tacky 108 seems like somebody that's in the chat and these are made-up names tacky 108
We kind of have to wait. What are you a good cashier though? Pretty good speed. All right higher cashier starting
You start at nine. Oh, it's military time. I don't I don't like that
Valerie $11 starting at nine o'clock set work duration eight hours since it's 17 good. Okay, cool. It works now
We need a stock clerk. How about a coal Schmidt? Oh, mr
Sark coming in dropping mad subs Sark coming in just dropping mad subs. What's going on Sark?
Thanks for the like 50 community subs you've given in the last couple of weeks. Thanks a lot, man
You don't know who mr. Sark is. Well, you've got to get educated. We'll follow mr. Sark streams every day
That's not true. I don't want to give you any pressure there. Sorry. Okay, you streams every day. I couldn't do it
Now thanks a lot Sark one of the most hysterical funny internet men I've ever seen. All right, we're gonna do
Store clerk. Okay, it's gonna be Schmidt. What happened to the twitch chat. Where is everybody refresh? Is that what the problem is for French?
Seven K
Excuse me
Sorry bumping into people seven candy coming through. Okay, let's build that store three
I want to call this something else and I call this something else. I hate that managed store
Oh, I opened a business. How do I change the name of this place? Oh, here we go
It's gonna be called a CVS. Is it on fire? Why is it red? You're gonna get sued how it's
Okay, managed products health and beauty the back shelf is gonna be diapers diapers on the back shelf
You got your diapers if you need them. That's what a CVS has diapers
They have that one random stupid toy section with toys that are from 20 years ago, it's like three shelves
Okay, then they have
They have like tampons
No car tools. There's a no no cookware. No dishes the held up. What else health and beauty toilet paper and
And like sex stuff, right? There's like condoms and and condoms. What was that? I don't have any way
I have to like research new things
Reading cards there is greeting cards at CVS. Isn't there isn't there like a greeting card section? No medicine
I think I have here sports ball. There you go. All right, let's see
Doc it up. Oh shit. I need a I need like a loading zone. Oops. Hold on bill bill bill. I need a
Loading zone land loading zone. Here we go. Oh fuck. Hold on
Okay, we need a road that goes over here and then up here. All right, build it
Well, the mall's not open yet sell the Funko pops. No, this is just a this is just a road
Okay, this is done. There's no pharmacy. So it's just a shitty Walmart. Okay loading zone. Oh fuck
I don't even need to do that. All right loading zone build it. Come on trash man 101, whatever your name is
Oh, can they go? Come on. I need to see who this is
Ed Hughes. Oh, no, we broke. I think I broke the twitch chat integration because I refreshed at Ed Hughes
Okay, so this is the storage for this. This is gonna get stocked. What are you doing in here? You need to fix it
Alki's bloom, I think I know it's still working. I know what it is. It's pulling from the original
4k Andy reset. Wait, let me save it first save game
save it as
Mall save game. I'm gonna exit game quit to the menu. Here we go. All right, those of you that are here now
I'm not doing this again
Hopefully it got you. Let's go
7k Andy
Okay, so there we go. There's there's that person what time is it 1 a.m.
Or what else can I do here? So I need my set products. How come it's not being stocked. Where's my stock?
Where's my shelf stalker? Oh, this person doesn't work until like 8 in the morning. They're off work, right?
Well, how can I why can I why gotta be 24 hours add lights? I don't how do I add lights build objects
Oh trash can we need these table clothes rack?
Anti-theft detector. Oh, I don't have those people just walk out with stuff
That's not good
Restaurant table kitchen pass movie projector. Wait, you can make a movie theater bowling lanes. Okay. I mean, I'm very interested
Oh, yeah pog you kidding me. This is gonna make all the money. Wait, how about outside now right here? This is $2,000
How much money man? Yeah, you gotta have at least one dip and DOS machine. Okay, that's good
ATM take out a bunch of money ATM in the corner CVS always has ATM arcade cabinet. You make an arcade
Oh my god pitbull machine. Oh my god. Oh my god. Okay. Oh my god. I can do a ton of stuff
I'm down. I can't I can't all right. We have a bathroom. Look, this is our first store. He's germa
I have a job. What relax?
You hey, no, I'm excited. We have enough parking doesn't leave
I always hate this shit how many times you guys were pulled into a store and they have like three parking spots and they're all
Taken up. It's like okay. Guess I'll drive around in a fucking circle until I can park my car. Yeah. No, that's bullshit
I'm not doing that here. What do they expect you to do? No, I don't need filter objects. We need we go
Customer parking right here. Yep, bang bang bang. I'm not gonna be one of those people that has it
But they have to walk across the road
kind of dangerous
Fuck I'm just trying to get diapers your luxury streamer. How do I get lights?
Okay, keep going. I gotta make go another store. Don't I how much money do I have? All right, let's do another store
Let now we're gonna do an arcade over here. Fuck. This is too busy. All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, calm down
Calm down road
Let's go
I'm already going up. So what the hell this and then over here? Okay, cool
Oh, it's almost time to open the store. Oh shit. Oh my god stores is open
Jackie 108 and coal Schmidt my two best employees. Oh, there we go
He's stalking the shelves. I get it. Oh, look at this
Those are diapers. Oh, is that minute? But I don't know if that is I make how much the prices are
Products
Selling price profit. Oh, no, it's just just automatic. You're obsessed with diapers. Whose car is that? All right, here we go
We open in ten minutes. Are we ready? I don't think we're ready. How many people are gonna show up?
Don't forget. Oh the light just turned on. Oh, who's that your what?
That's the delivery person. I don't know who that was. All right, the stores open. Hey
Welcome hey get off your phone get off your phone. Oh first customer
It's Gabriel McIntyre
You know him from twitch. What's he gonna get diapers? Uh, what was that? What'd he buy?
I don't even know what to say. That was fucking weird. That was really weird
Megan Drake, okay. I get a
We go
Parking spots are okay. Wait research allows operating business between Oh alcohol license night hours night hours
Oh, I need to build an office and hire office workers. Oh shit
Build office. No, no, no. No, this is the shittiest mall on earth. Hold on. I hear Otto. Let me get Otto. Okay. Sorry about that
He just wanted to have me open the door and have him sprint around
Hey, by the way, German pet Otto is available right now. I
Don't have to do chubby bunny for a month. Okay, how we doing? I need to build build build build build foundation
What is this place in here? Okay, we need a we need an office
I'm gonna put the office down here. So it's not connected to the mall
How big does the office need to be like this big as a little cubicle? That's big enough, right 12
That's a lot of money about that. That looks good. I think I need some more builders. It takes forever to do anything
I don't have one builder. All right. I need a I need a staff
There's my staff tab
Marketing. No, no, no manage. Okay. Here we go staff. I need we need a builder
maintenance center
CVS
Yes
How do I get another builder? We have this one person doing everything. Oh, there's new me new me three three three. There you are and
Penny Vargas. All right. Good bill bill bill. He's a fake viewers
view bot names
Like out myself as a good view border. Oh
Dude this twitch chat integration cool. I hate coal Schmidt. Yeah, you're here man. Why are the fake viewers?
But I just hired him. All right, hold on a higher stock clerk. Oh
There's a viewer
Complex spins you hired and fire the view bot. Okay, let's get rid of the view bot all Schmidt
How do I fire Colesman I'm sorry Cole you are fired for being a fake viewer
There's like it's like a little bit of a cue here
Daddy, Deutschland
Toby Walsh
It's just fake
fucking iOS app reviewers. Oh
Dennis Parson says great app must download. I had much fun on app Chelsea Duncan says
Pleased to have downloaded. Oh, these are real people
Office office office office office. Okay, we need to do sign this as an office bingo
Office for now. We need to put in
Shit in here. Okay office for our office worker all Schmitz back on the
wants to work again
I
What is watering a waiter ring? I was like was he like a gardener? I am back. All right, what do we wait?
Hold on office work grace is a much better office worker. I got it. Well, I'm higher on both shit
She's gone. No, she's not right there. All right, I'm gonna have two office workers shift planning too. That's cool
Okay, we need to do how many doors obviously double door and let's put a trash can here and
Let's get a we need like computers in here right or office. What do we need an office office desk? Okay, cool
We should just go now. That's too close. I would hate that. There we go
You we can set up a net here and you guys can play ping-pong
We gotta give him a plant too there. See it's so comfy in here
Drab horrible place to be
This is just like dictator what's the problem you've got a plant
And you have company and a trash can. All right, where my where my office workers in there. Where are they?
I have a hundred fifty five thousand. Ooh, that doesn't look good. All right manage office for when do you work in nine at nine to?
Seventeen. Oh, come on. We just ended the workday. This is closed. How much money did I make?
Upcoming events back to school season. Oh shit. This is really a mall or is just a gas station
It's hold on a minute. I this is the entryway to the mall. You gotta start small
CVS closes at five. Why I build it now we're gonna do I need another store. I need something more specific
What should be right here about a?
Try just do this like back-to-back. Okay, make another CVS this mall sucks
I do we just is just this is not even the mall. This is the city
Of course, there's a CVS like next to the mall just like how there's a movie theater right here, too
And yes, I am gonna make a movie theater here. All right, we need a huge parking lot
I'm getting let's go. It's time huge parking lot right here. Yeah. No, fuck that. We're just gonna make a huge
Yeah, okay. Here we go. We're gonna make a huge road down here
This is just like the little stop before you get to the mall. Here we go big big big ass parking lot
You cannot build two by two roadblocks. What are you talking about? Why wait? Why not? No money?
I have a hundred fifty five grand. This guy works all night. We can't get another worker
Okay, I did this kind of wrong this is wrong it wants to be a turn
Uh-oh good thing you fixed it. Thank you. I got all night to figure this out. Oh shit
Okay, um, I don't I kind of messed that up a little new businesses people want a grocery store
Open a store with 50% of food to create a grocery store open a store with drugs creative pharmacy
Well, that's what this is supposed to be. What is this? This is a good
This is a gas station
This is not even a store. This store is horrible. It's what is in here. There is
Action figures sports balls tampons diapers and toilet paper. This is just a toilet paper store
That's so bad. It's a huge bathroom
Yeah, you go in here you use the toilets and then you buy the toilet paper right here on the diapers and stuff
It's just a big
Yeah, that's okay. I'll just rename it
Uh
The big bathroom, how about that?
Toilet store. No, that's that's like a Steve Carell joke
Alright, so I need to figure out what the I pause this before I lose my mind
Alright, do you I do you guys see do you guys see like a chimpanzee with his arm up being like hey like like
Do you see that you see it right? He's doing kind of like a look at me three legs
Okay. Well, let's focus on that. All right, the big bathroom that gross profit. Look at this
$297 it's a $99 net profit salaries and maintenance. Look at this shit. We're making money on that
All right. I need to do I need that. Okay research research research, right?
allows opening business you are researching this project at the
24 man hours left what well, let's see if they get anything done. Okay build I need to have a customer parking
Wait a minute. I really really blew this high didn't I so this is all wrong
Well, these are gonna lead I don't where these gonna lead to and I delete roads
Staff only parking. Oh that makes sense. You can't save this. Yes, I can let me just figure out what I want to do build
I'm gonna do what I was gonna do before. I need a I need to delete this shit remove road work. Here we go
Get rid of this stuff. I fucked it all up. I didn't I look I'm learning
Okay, that looks a little bit now. We're gonna go this is for here and for here
We're gonna make this road go this way. There we go. Check this out
I can't hope this the beat doesn't drop and it just stays like this. It's almost time to open
The workers will get to work now. We'll do customer parking. Check this out. Here we go. Oh, yeah
Now this is what I'm talking about. That's it. Now. This is what I'm talking about
parking everywhere parking parking parking parking parking parking parking
More parking are they working? They are nice
All right stores open. There's a sevector. Oh, he's a former guard and he's a fashion victim
He's got security experience. No room left to expand. What do you mean? I'm gonna put something here. Okay build
Foundation this is a big one. This is a huge one. Whatever. This is needs to be big
That's a lot of money. That was a ton of money. I hope it was worth it
It's for extra long hot dog cars
That's for like a subway footlong. You're making the kind of mall you just talked about
No, but this is I know but this is not the mall. This is the beginning of the mall
Look, I can't just build the game mechanics make it so I can't just build like a thousand parking spaces
How'd they get into the mall right here? This is the mall. This is the mall right here guys
There's gonna be like five stores in here
Stop question stop questioning my
Ingenious ingenuity look you want to just go to the CVS go to the seat?
Well, whatever you have to go to the bathroom go to the bathroom over here. All right, it's time
Look at all these parking spaces. What else can I research?
Alcohol license. Oh, yeah, we definitely need a bar. I need all right
I need the office to be way bigger than this expand expand this shit right now
Expand it. We got like five people working in here. Hey, that looks good build it red stocks
sell
shit
This is gonna take this guy all week
Come on. Why is he doing it like this? He's like having fun
Is this like twitch chat making a dick on screen? It is just wait till I get my actual stores getting ready
He's doing pick for us. Why is he doing it like this?
Is he going home? Hey
No, don't go. All right. All right. We got we got this guy coming in. He kind of looks scary
75 years old
This is just you just fucked this whole thing up man
Leave him and they what if he dies?
Let's just say word of mouth new business people want to grow people want a grocery store so bad
Okay, okay. Okay. Okay. Look look look. All right. We could just do super kind of super fast speed. Let's get another
office desk and
Look, it's a fucking office. These two are friends these two are friends
We have two friends like buddies working together and there's one person in the middle. This is a call center
Omega low. Well, you know, it's an office center a middle dude feels bad
Okay, I need to hire some uh, some office workers higher often we need three more. Okay, we have camel lift
Sheep David. Sheep David's a cook. Um, how many people I think are good for this office work office work
You're all bad at office work. Can I get a new group? No, none of you are any good
Oh wait, you still have to do the rest of the parking
I need staff parking somewhere very like staff parking is gonna be right here
No staff parking is gonna be here. No that parking is gonna be here. Yep. There's so many parking spots
Well, just wait till I get my like stores in here. Wait till this 100 year old man finishes the building. It's alright
We're in our building phase. That means and let's not okay. I'm just gonna hire them
I don't care our office worker fine all resly research the big data project to uncover this person's traits one more and
And
Sheep David sure we're gonna convert sheep David into a waiter eventually auto salary. That's fine. Okay
Oh shit. This is not technically an office. Is it? Okay. There we go. Now it is
I don't office for that annoys me. They go the research done friend zone. Are we doing in products as a how's the big bathroom doing?
That's 22% margins main category health and beauty diapers and they're linked to the storage one
Okay, that duration opening hour so opens at 9
Those are terrible margins. I was okay. 22% is not bad. How is that a bad margin?
You get 22% profit every month margins are too big. Oh boy. Look at this. They heard about the big sale. Oh
Oh, no, these are just workers. I have to pay these people
No, I thought those were people coming to the big bathroom
All right, get to work hanging around traits
Satisfaction, okay speed patience and social ability. All right. Well, you can level these people up
Still going on this. I may have done this. I may have made this a little too big
Okay, here we go
sluggish
Motorola's
Justin Baker. He's browsing the pads and tampons
Good buy them. You can go faster than that scan it fast George Cheney
Nice. All right. That's that's a sale. He's a former janitor easy to put don't cross the street like that
Wait people can't get run over. Can they I hope they can hurry up and build this
I need to make a school supply thing. I need like an office space office max or whatever. They're called office Depot
Okay, this is exciting as to where it really begins
Yes, okay
Chill in there for a little bit. Let's think about a plan here. All right, we need
Okay, we need to we need to really think about this
walls
I'm thinking about here's all the parking. I get about this. The entrance is like right here, right?
Entrance will be right here staff entrance will be back here. If you think about that, let's have a staff entrance
Should I put this about like this?
Okay, that's one
Do I have to have a storage room for each store because these are all gonna be like little shops
Then oh, this is a bathroom
This is the bigger bathroom
No, okay the big bathroom the bigger bathroom and then the mall don't give me stupid ideas like that
I only have forty nine thousand dollars and then the biggest bathroom just have the back hole third be storage
All right, that's probably a better idea. So like this just have the whole thing
This is just huge storage for our like three stores bigger than the biggest bathroom the bankrupt bathroom
Money dude, I need to sell shit. Okay a sign storage storage five
Storage six and storage seven for the stores that are going to be here as it has to be different storage for different stores
It's uneven. Oh
Whatever fuck I was trying to
I want to do it to storage six storage six need to be used to be. Oh fuck. What have I done?
Storage six. Oh my fucking god. I know I want to do I can't even eyeball that you understand there
Okay, it's not even by one square who cares storage five is consumed all. All right. Here we go
Let's see what we got restroom. I need a wall. This is a big store. There's a list of three different stores in here
It's just gonna be a food court. No, no, no, I need like retail store
Okay, but I need walls walls. All right
So this is store fuck staff comes in through here and then let's see
How am I gonna block this out needs to be a grocery store? Okay
What kind of stupid shitty mall has a grocery store in it? What mall has a oh, yeah
There's a you know, there's a stop and shop inside of this mall. This is store one looking good
This is gonna be store two looking good store. Three is right here. Oh
Bingo nice. Okay, this is staff door staff door staff door staff door regular door regular door regular door bathroom
No, fuck. Hold on. Let's see what it goes here. Okay store. I can only do a store right now
Maintenance center store. All right. We need a grocery store. All right, how about wait wait wait?
Why doesn't how about this is just the grocery store and then I'll add a storage thing on the left
Then you can just go to this other stores in the grocery store
Like you're shopping around this would be sick actually like are you kidding me?
You have your shopping cart and you're going through the grocery store and there's like a Best Buy right over there
That'd be cool. You could just go in with your groceries and put like a TV in with your bread and eggs
My ice cream would melt. Well seems like we have a
We have somebody doesn't understand how to grocery stuff you do you frozen and you cold shit last
Why are you buying ice cream first?
You'd ice cream deli meat meat cheeses they all had that's all last
Although it you got you guys put
Cold shit in your grocery shopping cart within five to ten minutes of getting in there. Is that the first thing you do?
That's that's not a good idea. That's horrible
If you get ground beef and you're in the grocery store for 40 minutes and then it's like what?
1020 plus maybe minutes 30 minutes to get home you have ground beef
That's been outside of a fridge for like an hour and 20 minutes think about that
Alright, so this is the this is the grocery store and then this is the other stores. Oh, it's gonna be fun. Okay
Nice
Dude, this is big enough to be we just had three checkout lines and a bunch of food
40 minute Andy there's no bathroom here. Look you got to go to the bathroom. Just go over there
I can add it later over this way. All right, we need doors. Let me actually I gotta name these store eight
This is grocery store. There's groceries store seven store. Wait, wait, wait store nine. What's this?
This is gonna be DVDs. It's gonna be DVDs
What should this be DVDs, I don't think I have access to DVDs yet, are they even working? Oh alcohol license shit
Oh, no
DVDs, I need people in the office
expand
Expand expand please your CVS is not gonna cover the wage expenses of all this. This is the money maker
My my thirty dollars in net profit from the diaper CVS store is not going to cover the expenses
This is just shitty business management and business development 101. Oh, he turned a profit slightly for one week
Expand and then expand again. I only have 31 grand. Oh, I guess slow down. All right, we need to make oh boy
We need to slow down. This is an obvious drug front. I'm not really getting very many customers anymore
Oh, this is not good. Maybe it's because it's only
Tampons diapers and toilet paper. It's cuz there's no other product and now we're closed
Trying to make this huge ass grocery store mall. All right, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, I can fix this
Fuck the office is bigger than the store
Just relax everybody you tell me to relax you guys relax just relax
That's better the research den more office chairs, right? How much are these a thousand bucks?
How many I'd have so many employees this is too many employees. How much money do I have? Okay. Um, I'm just making a land
Can they get a full game of of like battlefield in here yet?
Can I do a full game of Call of Duty was it 12 on 12 16 on 16 a sign research den there we are
I don't this little lip. Whatever. It's okay. There's 29,000. I had build it
I hope I have enough money and once I get the grocery store going people want grocery stores bad. Okay groceries
I need a
Build a storage over here get the office thing out foundations. Okay, we just need this
This is storage for the grocery store ten fucking thousand dollars, dude. Come on
Stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop stop. This is like
$30,000 worth of stuff. I can't do this. We have to cancel this off
Inaccessible work order builders can't access work orders. What the fuck are you talking about? I need a grocery store
Okay, we have to we're gonna sacrifice all this stuff that we just put in here and it's build. Okay. Here we go. No
Object, how do I get rid of this? How do I stop him from doing this? I can't like stop him
This is too late
Sell sell sell I can't do I think I have to sell them as he builds them sell it
Does this sell this or is it just deleted? Oh, it's just delete
I
Didn't realize it's okay. It's okay. We have we'll have enough money. We're gonna have enough money. Oh
Okay, we just have a really expensive computer room. That's fine 15 grand. We just have to make a ton of desirable shit. Oh
Ten thousand, okay
9,000
8,500 come on finish it finish it before the next day so I can get this started. Come on. Okay, stop do that
No, don't stay come back. How do I get a loan? How do you get a loan?
Why did I do this many computers like what the fuck I
Wasn't paying it. I didn't know what the hell is doing. How do I get a loan? Oh, that doesn't look good. All right marketing research
finance
Okay, you must have at least two hundred all the average profit over the last ten days to take out a loan
I can't even take out a loan. They just have one lumpy
I
Had I couldn't go in there and prove. Yeah the toilet diaper paper bathroom store
That's not gonna that's not enough to convince us to give you a loan. Okay, I can I can work with this
You need to build doors to your stores. Yeah, I know I know I know I'm just trying to get this going
Double door here double door here. Actually, it's usually like that
Yeah, okay, and then we're gonna get a door here double door double door double door double door staff door
Oh, these are 200 bucks each. What a joke. Okay staff can go in there staff needs to be able to get in here, too
2,700 2,400 I gotta start firing people burning money. Oh my god have $400
What happens if you lose what happens if you don't have any money left you get you go to go to jail?
This is attempt number one. I didn't get it at first negative
1,700 bucks what is costing so much money? Okay, I can I can fix it. I can fix it
I can fix it now. Let's just we need to have shelves food shelf food shelf. Oh, I lose. This is trash household goods
Wait a minute. I can't even make groceries. Why not tobacco newspaper road network underground parking? Oh
I wanted to so badly have alcohol and night hours that I didn't do any food
Hey
Look at this saved
Alright now I get it. I get it now and we're gonna do this. Don't worry. I get it now not night hours
We're doing cold chain fresh fruits fresh vegetables, and this is gonna be a vegetable and fruit store
This is gonna be a this is gonna be a farmers market. It's not gonna be a bathroom store
farmers market
Farmer's market. Okay, let's make it a farmers market. Sounds good. I need an office while I have the money
I'm gonna fucking go for it. Let's go
Customer parking no staff parking. This is for the office. This is for the office complex
Yeah, you can't park there only the office workers can she did only the game
I didn't how did I cheat that I very I look I lost. Okay, I lost all my money and
Somebody bulldozed the bigger bathroom and then somebody else came in and took it over and they said well, this is fucking stupid
Why did you only have toilet paper? You're an idiot
Farmer's market. We're gonna turn it into a farmers market. I say new management. I don't like that
I want it in the middle like this ten thousand good. That's a good office. Fuck off with this shit. What me what I do
Fuck off with this shit
Yeah, I don't know if you're talking about me is our doors I didn't have them staff doors before okay computers office
We're gonna go hard right off the bat here. He's talking about me put an emote only
Why okay, we're gonna have a desk here a desk here and then one in the middle one right here there
We have three people that are just gonna be working in here. I want that grocery store
We're gonna make this a farmers market before the mall and I'm gonna get it right here this time. Okay, I have a hundred sixty four thousand dollars
That's plenty of money to do this shit. This game's cool. I like this game. This is kind of fun. All right
Products for the shelf. No, no, no, no, no, no take this all off. How do I how do I delete all this?
I don't want this stuff
Manage store products. Okay, there we go. Get this all off remove this delete. I have to delete the shelf
Oh, it's in the storage already. Oh
fuck
No, it's in the stored
Okay. Well, here's the deal
Once this is when I have access to fresh fruit, we're gonna replace the tampons with apples
All right, make this an office
Uh-huh
manage office, let's hire some staff
Office good. I just have to hire all three of them. Wait, there's three office workers
Researching fresh fruit and vegetables. Somebody said my store was way too small. All right, once this is done
We're gonna restock this shit. No, stop stalking this with tampons. Get out of here. Okay
Don't put tampons in here
Okay, I have we're doing our research. There we are. We're gonna get milk fresh meat fresh fruit fresh cheeses
I can't wait in the meantime. Let's do a let's get that. No, let's not get that going. Not yet
Super speed this shit. I went way too fast last time. I tried to expand too quickly
Look at this a good good money money money roll it in. I need better items. Okay set shelf
writing card games
School supplies it's gonna be school right bed sheets cookware. Oh
No, I think she's going for the tampons. Is that what it is? What is back here? Why the bags back here? What is this?
Action figures get this shit out of here bed sheets toilet paper can stay bed sheets cookware
We have to put some more miscellaneous stuff up here. Are we doing on the research six out of 24? Okay
We're gonna turn sooner or later. It's gonna be farmers market. You forgot to put the trash. Oh shit. You're right the customer
We're looking for some money here. Look it's a profit
It's all about the profit. You just threw shit on the ground
So it's disgusting. All right, pick up an expensive handbag. What is it? Oh
It's a beetle. It's a bug. How expensive was that? What's going on? It was $56 a handbag
No wonder this shit was so inexpensive. Yeah, ten bucks. That was 56 bucks
All these items in here are like five to ten dollars. This one's like 80 research. It is 24. All right, let me um
Don't need to hire a janitor or something higher stock higher cashier. How do I I mean, this is trash everywhere in a barber
Social ability what who cares does that person pick the trash up off the ground?
34% okay, 10 man hours 34%. I don't have to look at that anymore. No debt profits not going great sales
Only 14 sales. How's it possible? It's trash cans inside
Have you ever been to like a target before or like a Walmart? They're always outside in front of the door
What's the last time you saw a trash can inside of a target?
They're like outside in the front of the door there's both not here. That's too expensive
Somebody throw this trash away. I
Why would you want to shop in here? This is disgusting. Somebody clean that up
Why is nobody cleaning up the massive trash higher janitor? I don't think there is janitors. Oh
Shit, there's a janitor. Okay janitor. All right. This is a chatter Prince
Rapi
Janitor pretty good janitor Prince Rappi. All right, go ahead. I need 500 bucks today. How much how many salaries do I have?
Too many salaries, dude
Can't do anything yet. I need another couple days to go by until I can do fresh fruit and vegetables
That's a fake viewer. No, it's not he's here
Imagine being a janitor LOL. What's wrong with that? The job and that guy. Yeah, you don't
Ban that guy that guy for ten minutes oof. All right, where's the janitor? What's that? What is that? Wait, we have rats
Oh, no, he just killed them. He just sprayed them with like rat acid. Where's the janitor?
Okay, if you're like a building manager and you get the call, hey, we need you to deal with the rat problem
No, no, I don't have to do that
Why are you calling me or enter you need an exterminator?
Hi, German. I'm a regional manager for Walmart and all I really have to say is
Jeremy I'm a regional manager for Walmart and I really have to say to you is you're making a mockery of this business your store is
A disaster and a liability someone's gonna fall and crack this skull on the floor because you can't keep your shit clean
I've never seen a more poorly run store than this
I'd expect more from a short Bostonian streamer than what is short Bostonian have to do with anything. I could be a tall giant
Norwegian and I could still run a business bad if I was a short Bostonian guy. What are you talking about? Here we go
Janitor janitor, where's the janitor? Ah-ha good clean it up
See if we can get something else
Welcome to work. You didn't even do anything. What about in here clean this shit up
What you just pretended to work for five seconds? I need a dumpster. What do you mean a dumpster? Oh, wait a minute
Wait a minute. I actually think I need oh shit. Hold on. I need a
A
Where is it garbage pickup? Okay, right here. Okay now get in there and pick up that garbage and put it over here
But you don't actually put the garbage just on like a helipad you do why?
Why is there no trash? Why how does a dumpster? Okay, that's good
Good now go back to everyone's on their phones. Everyone is on their phone except for you. Okay
Um, how we doing on money or the paper good choice
Good choice, that'll be five dollars. It costs 500 a day to run this business
Thank you. You know what? This would make sense if I had like a ton of different scratch tickets back here
Oh the Charmin ultra soft what I used to hey, you know, it's double the rolls in one roll
Saves money saves time
Research 74% these are your viewers. They're watching your stream. Oh, yeah, I guess
28 beans, what is 28 beans getting everybody quick everybody act them thought toilet paper
All right. You cannot convince me. Otherwise that that's not a Koopa kid with like a human mask on cut his mic
Let me cut my mic. You are you you are using view blots. Oh make a low. What am I 8900 Andy? I?
Want to refresh but I don't want to break it
9k Andy. Okay. I got a question for all you twitch viewers at what point at what viewer count
Are you no longer a Andy? What is what number is it? Is it 20 10? It's 20
That seems way too. I
20k is if you're under 20k you are like
1999 k Andy
10k
What that's so many people. Oh see lion everybody under the chaplet
Okay, I have to play the fucking game man
Research hurry so I can actually make money
Finish it now
Frozen food. Oh, yeah ice cream frozen pizza vegetables. Let's actually start making money. Here we go grocery store health and beauty
Where is it boys and games health and beauty? Where is it? Oh, this is not food shelves. Okay, get rid of this shit
Closet. All right, delete all this delete everything get rid of everything. This is the okay. Let's do
How do I get rid of this? Okay, delete delete it
Why can I not delete it delete delete delete delete delete delete delete delete delete delete it all? Okay, go remove
Food we need food shelves. It's time to start making money fast food dispenser. Oh, okay. Here we go
Finally, this is gonna be like apples lettuce pickles ketchup mustard onion. Here's my fries
Hey, you know what I was thinking, you know how they're doing, you know, they have the Travis Scott meal
They have the what's this a new one now, too, right? What's the new one? Jay?
There's a new McDonald's like celebrity meal and I'm like, okay, they're actually this is this is becoming a thing now
They're doing this and I thought about like what would my meal be?
Right, not Jay Leno. It's like oh, yeah, it's a my meal is a Big Mac and a Oreo McFlurry
right
but when I go to McDonald's I
Order like eight things off the menu. I'm disgusting. I don't order one thing
So it's not like oh, hey the German on a five. It's a McChicken meal with coke. No, no, it's a number one
Two McChickens a ten-piece nugget and a McDouble again. I eat it to my stomach hurts. How do you how would they do that?
Did you do you order just one thing on the menu you guys don't am I crazy do it?
So when you guys go to McDonald's and you get like the number one with fries and a coke that's it
That's what you eat. You don't get like two other McChickens on top of that. Hey, it's me German on a five
So here's my meal. I get a number one. Hold the pickles. Okay, and a powerade cool
Not a second though two McChickens with extra mayo on them
Yeah, getting a little weird here and my ten-piece nuggets in sweet and sour sauce. Don't forget the apple pie
Bada Bada Bada
Your fucking stomach's gonna hurt. All right, that's enough food. That's a 5,000 count. I don't order just one meal at McDonald's
I just go hard. That's what I do. No drink. I said powerade. Holy shit. Here's another thing that I didn't even know this either
Listen to this. Did you I might be just new to this and maybe I didn't even care to think about it
I don't know why any size drink at McDonald's is a dollar a large like
2430 ounce fucking drink at McDonald's is a dollar. It's one dollar
If you get a powerade, listen to me if you get a powerade at McDonald's
That's like 24 ounces and it's a dollar if you go to the gas station right next to McDonald's a 32 ounce powerade
It's like three bucks
What stop with the ad this is not an ad this is real life. It's a dollar for NT any drink at McDonald's
I love this place. You guys know that how is this an ad? This is my life
Make sure you get to German an 85 next time. That's what the ad says. There's that
I know why would anybody ever sponsored this stream
You have to you watch ten minutes of the stream and you'll leave
If you are like in a business like a corporate business and you are like, oh this this guy's a 9k Andy
Let's see what he's doing. Nope. Don't like it
It's so show me the rest of the of the 8k Andy's that are on Twitch right now
And no, okay, check out check out counters there. We're gonna. Yeah. All right food. Let's go stalk this shit
Oh, they have to build it first, right?
McDonald's Mike captain on Nemo just gave $50 and said McDonald's Mike. I
Really actually really? Oh
Bob it about that dad dad dad
Can I just say by the way, what a stupid jingle what a duck like, okay, but up up up up. I'm loving it
I'm loving it. It's it's it's McDonald's if it's food. It's like fast food hamburgers. I'm loving it
You do love it. No, I don't
Okay, what's your alright juices? Wait, I gotta they're gonna plan this up. You just said you know, I love McDonald's
I don't love their ad campaign
Alright fresh fruit right in the beginning and food candies cookies breads rice and pasta pet food
All right pet foods gone on the back, right pet food
That food in water rather than the back there
Cookies. All right. We need a slice. Wait, where's my fresh food?
It was like the milk and the and the meat and stuff. Why is it just bread bread and
snacks bread and pasta and then right at the front usually, you know sauces and seasonings and
And canned food. Let's go dock it up. I need a fridge. Oh
Shit. Okay. Now this is tough, but this is fine
Wait, why is it a convenience store ice cream thing that you reach into what? Oh, okay fresh meat
fresh meat and fresh fish
Okay, that's kind of weird. Why would that be weird? It wouldn't it?
Fresh meat from a CVS. Well, that's not what change in the name
We got bottled water pet food bread sauces seasonings rice canned food fresh meat and fresh fish stock it up
All right. What are they working on now frozen food? That's right. I'm gonna 59,000
2007 spelling that's fine. I know what else can I do in here now that I have some food, you know
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no pause the game pause the game. Fuck that
This is the fucking refrigerated section back here. You know, I'm saying bankruptcy incoming. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no
No, I can do that all day. I could do that all fucking day. Pardon me next time. I way the deliveries haven't come in yet
I can move these we need more space. He's losing it monk as
Yeah
No, I'm excited. I don't know. I haven't done anything but this has been like fun. So you look at this is perfect
So much more organized. I'll hold on. There's no food in here. Is it open? We're not open yet
Not for another hour now, give me these much better much better. This is a cuckhouse. Don't know what that means
I'm gonna just assume that you all know what that means. I don't know what that means
I'm too old to know what that is. I don't know. All right fridge. I'm gonna need like milk and shit milk
Alright, perfect. This is perfect. Plenty of room for people to walk around and be like, oh, hey Julie
Yeah, we live like that. Let's drink from each other
Somebody just drop. You know what really would fucking pissed me off
More than anything whenever I would go to the grocery store is you would just walk down an aisle somewhere and there would just be a
Shattered salsa glass and salsa all over the ground. Did that happen to you guys at the grocery store ever?
Like somebody would literally just drop and shatter like a glass salsa
Like come on and nobody can go down that aisle if you want salsa like you like what are you gonna walk around it?
What if you step in it or juice? Yeah, like like an orange juice is just how does that even happen?
Most orange juices are sealed. How do you how does a full fucking orange juice like hit the ground and explode and go over five?
Isles, that doesn't make any sense. You're living in a 2007 comedy movie
Ban that guy for literally a year. I don't want to see their name again for a full year
Crack strip. Oh, what was I doing? Oh, yeah meat and cheese. All right, let's stalk this
By the type is here. Wait, no, no, no. Okay. Wait, stop. Stop. Stop. Stop
It's at stores about to open the software does not belong in it to any active zone. Oh fuck off
This belongs to essentials
Store. Thank you. Okay food, right?
We want milk and then we're gonna have dairy not the same thing as fresh meat and then fresh fish is back here
So we've got fresh meat fresh fish fresh milk and fresh dairy. There's twitch staff in the chat
Which staff is here ban that guy for a fucking year and the twitch chat for like a least a month
Is that it can even do that? Is that impossible?
I feel like they can just right-click their name and go now. I don't think so, sir. We go finally
I actually finally I'm gonna be able to make some money. Here they come. I need more parking spaces. Oh shit
I need more parking spaces. Oh god. Hold on
Bottled water get out to get it up there. What's wrong with the town you grew up in first the
Violating snowmen with their noses displaced now grocery store aisles that are a mess
I don't think that's so out of the ordinary to have like a okay. Hold on
so a snowman with the carrot but like it's dick and having like
Broken salsa bottles in sometimes in the grocery store. I feel like that's like not that big of a deal. That's
What that's not like bad. I can't believe you grew up there
somebody put
Carrot on the snowman's dick. Oh
Not in my neighborhood, but the workers unionized. I don't think I can even do that
Missiles opportunities customers can't access the center because there are no spots
Okay
Parking parking parking. There's so much demand right now. Look at all this demand. Somebody got think of Mayo
Whatever that is. I want the VIP. It wasn't even a real person. It was a bot. Oh shit
This is really starting to just pop the fuck off right now, huh?
Bob six interesting name jet hill
Gaming time 91. What do you got? You're a music lover. Is that true got mayonnaise and water the essentials
Bob six is about to buy mayonnaise Bob six. Is that you getting mayonnaise? These are bots. No, these are paw socks
Okay, doesn't paw socks has to be in this channel
Spongebob 69. All right, how much money am I making that number is about to come back up?
Alright good only a parking space is now
filthy acts I
Think I might need like another cashier. This is wicked. And this is a business is really booming
We got a line at the checkout. This never happened before
This person is buying fish. How much is fish? Probably wicked expensive
18 bucks. I need another cashier. We'll do it at close. I'll make two lines
Cashier is too slow. Yeah, he is pretty slow, isn't he? That's why he's going so slow. He's just he just doesn't care
He's doing the
Rotation sleeve really slowly. Come on. What are you doing?
Hurry up. All right, he's fine
Speed terms the walking speed of all characters
So he's wicked fast, but he's really slow. This person can explode. It's first it can explode
Ring them up. Oh, okay. We're gonna do this now pause
Check out counter
Okay, this person's actually doing monkey ass. I need to build I need more space
No one's even using the fucking bathroom. So i'm gonna get rid of it. What's the point of having this bathroom?
No one's using it. We'll make it smaller make the bathroom smaller
Let me have room for the checkout to get two by two. Yeah, it's gonna be tiny
There's gonna be a room over here for checkout counter
Wait, stop there. Okay. Now we're gonna
build
Found foundation. Okay wall remove this shit
This out of here quickly. Hurry up
Get it out
Oh
Sell 10 different types of products five thousand dollar reward. We just got our first reward
Remove these man
How do I do? How do we delete this shit? Oh, i'm so stupid
Okay remove
Now there's way more space good
Don't use these yet
Now let's have a checkout counter
Yeah, I got it. All right. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. I need to move that
This needs to move to like over here
Can I get that I can still reach that right perfect now we need to have another cashier
Uh, okay. We need to make the sign this
restroom two no
door essentials
What happened? I just fired somebody
What happened? What happened? What happened? I fired everybody. What did I fire? But I deleted the bathroom
So I fired everybody here. What fuck?
um
Okay, I got some time
Imagine that
Just oh I got my bottle of water. Let me just piss over here
I don't think they can't be a bathroom here. It's not gonna be a bathroom. It's not a space
Wait, I guess that technically is
I think there is technically enough space if I put this over here because then the cashier can stand here
Oh, fuck it. Let's just go. Let's build it a little bit further up
Come on do it. Uh-huh. There we go
Now we can move this over here
Uh-huh. Okay
That's better
There now we just whatever
This is the secret entrance
gee
there
There wait there perfect. Okay, we're ready now. I can have a second cashier. We're running this problem again
What we're doing on profit. I mean I made almost double the amount of money fix that wall. All right, hold on
I'm on it. I'm working on it. Okay. Hold on. I'm working on it. Hey, i'm working on hey
Hey, oh a sign bathroom. Wait, what the fuck is this?
Why can I not uh, how come there's no ground here? There's no foundation. How it's just grass. Not anymore. I got it
There we go. Yeah, that's much cleaner. Isn't it? There we go. Now. Let's get a cashier here vintage essentials
We need a another cashier. How about paul resley prince rappi is better. Yeah, that person's here. Of course
They're here dude. Look at this chart. This chart is so much better than this one. It's uh, well
We may have uh, we may have found a bottom there. I think everybody we found a bottom been two hours in this
Okay, i'm zoomed in right now and people like oh, wow. He's probably working on like one of his buildings
It's probably a shit. It's been two hours. I'm perfecting it. Okay. Oh, he must be really stretching this shit for content
Oh, dude, holy shit
You made a convenience store in two hours. This should go so much smoother now. Wait, let's get more product right here
We can have you know, hold on a minute
It doesn't have to be all food. It doesn't have to be all food. Why where does it say it has to be all food?
We're gonna have like a toilet paper rack. All right, that's fine tools. How about car tools?
Should we put toilet paper diapers right here? That's not a bad idea
This is all signed correctly, right? Yep. Let the day begin
All right. I'm excited. Are they researching anything?
They are okay frozen food is coming up and then we'll have we'll expand that out and have frozen food over here
I don't like the placement here change this i'd rather just be on the back wall
Right. What was here? I don't remember bottled water. What was there?
What the hell was here? Tosses and seasonings. What was here? I think that wait, they'll do it when they come for work, right?
Yeah, restock these shelves time for work. There we go. That's much better
Look at this cute little store and we have ample parking and then eventually we're gonna go even more of a frozen food section
What about the queue you mean the queue
Oh fuck, where can I put this? All right, just in time. Come on in. Let's go shopping everybody
Oh, of course the dairy section the yogurt. We have the finest yogurt. We've got cannibals back there
Somebody's pay for something and not take it
Pick the notifications word of mouth people want a drug store. I have a hundred customers on site. Holy shit
Queue is full. Yeah, we already did this parking queue is full. Not anymore. There's rats. We already got that
Come on, let's go customers customers customers customers
We want a drug store and a liquor store and a fast food restaurant. We'll just hold on. We're busy
We want a drug store. They want a grocery store liquor store. Yeah, we already know this who is buying this stuff
Oh, this is the queue line right here. Okay. How are we doing today?
We're already 82 bucks. Holy shit. That guy almost died
18 18 bucks 18 bucks 10 bucks. Yes, this double queue line is so good
How much money are we going? Oh man 170 almost at 200 today. How many customers we got?
18 sales. I got 11 people here with this is the highest and most amount of people we've ever had in the store at the same time
15 people
Got a sale on dog food
Time to expand. No, it's not. We're the viewers. It's not a viewer. That's not a viewer. That's not a viewer
That's oh, there's a viewer
Oh man, we're gonna be fine. We're gonna be just fine
And then where's the research at?
Let's bounce baby bounce
demand
Research the sales monitoring now
We almost have enough to do frozen food
Only six more hours remain until I can do a frozen department. That's ten thousand make a hundred total sales. That's ten thousand dollars
I'll take it. Thank you
plenty of parking
Good traffic road people getting in and out having to cross no cross
Oh
See how many people can hit
That guy's life just flashed before his eyes
We're already at the peak for yesterday. We're not even we're gonna get we got like six more hours left. Nice
Keep it going. Keep rolling in the money
The double queue line was a big deal
Look for viewers
We got here
Abe
uh
Cheryl
Cram one two three
Okay, I wish I could hire some of these people
86 percent and then okay, this is so this is fresh food
We're gonna have the little aisle over this way to be frozen food and we'll do some reorganizing
Remember that has not been a single viewer
Are you trying to tell me that double zero trash man is not a viewer of this channel?
So where who are the where are they where are they getting this person from? Can we refresh again, please? Ooh, woo
I mean, it's it's gonna fuck up. He's gone. Well
We'll find out someone to link them dude you were a huge part of the stream
Everybody was fucking talking about you man. All right, that's a pretty good day
That's a really good day not almost a thousand bucks net profit still not very good, but we'll get there
98 frozen food is done
You are not researching any project. Okay frozen food
restaurants big data alcohol
restaurants
sales monitoring
security cleaning technology
Bowling alley cinema fitness center. I kind of want like have restaurant in the back
Okay, you know how walmart has like a usually has no what who target?
Target has like starbucks in it in a bunch of in a bunch of locations
Don't say okay. So why can't we have a restaurant or like a like a like a puppaginos or something in the back?
Let's have a bowling alley in the back of the grocery store
That's gonna say I don't have the manpower for that
Uh, I could do bar too anyone here have twitch. I think everyone do an arcade
Let me do alcohol first because that'll sell a ton
Imagine not having alcohol
Here that's a huge sale. Okay. I just unlocked frozen food. Let's continue our grocery store
What do you think this way?
This way for frozen or this way for fro now we'll get rid of the bathroom bathroom demolition time
Nobody cares. Nobody uses it. How many is it like how many times a urinal has been used?
Does it say like used how many times?
Zero delete it. This is our frozen food section here to this shit
It's blocking the door
Yeah, we'll get rid of this shit. I don't want it. They got this too
You're getting in the way of our frozen section
Okay
Cool. So then people can walk over here
And then this will go that that's I like that so far this can go
Bang bang bang. We got the money. You got 158 000 dollars. We're gonna go bang bang bang go for it
Foundation like that. That's a big investment. That's a huge investment, but i'm willing to do it
Germa dot dot dot germa don't make this a restroom so people don't piss on the floor
All right
the type of customer that if they walked into a grocery store and
A five by five cubic feet area with a sign that says this is a bathroom pointing down
I don't think that person I
Know who's gonna do that who's going to just pee where that sign says? I mean, that's kind of funny
So delete an active zone. Yeah, there's no staff. No, not store two. Fuck off
No, stop doing that. I want this to be essentials
Don't do that
No, why is it doing this if your selection overlaps an existing zone of the same type the zone will be extended
What the fuck? Let's do uh, we got frozen food
Ladies and gentlemen, we got frozen food frozen
Excuse me freezer. Excuse me. Where is it? Wait, you put frozen
Shit into a refrigerator
Okay, i'm just gonna put more of these
um
Okay, that's a lot of them. I don't want that many
uh
All right. Fuck I want to do
There's gonna be something weird here like a couple of vending machines or like a pool table. I don't know
Put them next to each other
Nice, and then we can go wham shelf that works. The person just needs to stand right here
He can fit have you ever actually been to a grocery store?
No, no, never I I call someone and say hey, um, can you get me uh, two packs of
Totino's pizza rolls
uh three cans of corned beef hash
Two gallons of milk
Two full onions and eight pounds of hamburger meat. Thanks
Full onions. Yeah, like the big ones. Yeah, these are freezers
Ground beef it's called ground beef. It's called ground beef. All right frozen vegetables
frozen
Vegetables two in a row and i'm gonna do frozen pizzas
pizzas
Oh on the side ice cream ice cream ice cream
and then
frozen vegetables
ice cream
A whole row of ice cream. I love when you go to the giant ice cream row. This is a fridge
Uh, what's back here? We'll do
Fucking
more
Meat what's back here already? What's here? Is that fish? That's fish fish
Juice in here juices
and soda
Okay
And then over here we're gonna do
Um, we'll just oh right at the checkout counter. What are my stupid snacks?
and cookies
Looks good to me
It's a wall or i'm gonna explode
Uh, you mean this wall?
There you go settle down
our
Mall empire is expanding
Actually, just a grocery store research night. What are we researching now? Oh no, I want alcohol
I want to be able to have like an alcohol station over here
And then we're i'm gonna have to redo this
Once I get alcohol over here
I'm gonna expand this out and we're gonna have like four checkout counters. Where's the mall?
I'm working on it
Bathroom for fuck's sake no one's gonna use the bathroom in here
You want to make a bathroom for the the one person every five hours that actually uses the bathroom in the grocery store?
Yes
No, the employees need one. Jeff Bezos streamer. Jeff Bezos
Jeff Bezos doesn't have like a frozen food vegetable grocery store service. I mean he does he does now
But he didn't that's not how he started. He started selling like books
He had a bookstore online. How the fuck did that happen? Can we go over that real quick?
How did it I I have a a bookstore turn into I own the entire fucking globe
All shipping all services in all products. How did that happen?
People really liked books. Yeah
do you guys ever feel like
It was a scenario where he was selling books
and like
Somebody just said hey, uh
What if you delivered something else that wasn't books like pens?
What are you talking about? Dave?
Yeah, what if instead of books what if you did like pens and pencils and paper clips and stuff like office supplies?
Dave that's fucking stupid
Get the fuck out of my garage or wherever I started this business
You guys think Dave ever got like any royalties for that?
And then like one day Jeff Bezos was sitting there. He's like, you know, god damn it. Yeah, I got yeah
I don't have a pen on me
Where am I gonna get like a stack a bunch of pens? Am I gonna go to the office store?
Wait, oh
I'll just get her on amazon. I'll make it like pens and books
And whiteboards and office supplies
And then he like set it up and then he ordered the pens and he said how easy that was
Why is Jeff Bezos a surfer?
Uh, isn't from california
Everybody that made a business apparently was from california. No, he's not. Where's he from?
He's from hell
Not from hell
He's from like ohio
Dude, look at this money
That's what we call hopefully not a dead cat bounce
People are getting word man. Wait back to school
Hold on a second here school supplies pens
t-shirts and laptop computers
I this is jeff bezos way. I gotta get pens. I gotta get pens and paper and school supplies and pencils
All right. We're gonna move that i'm gonna make a pens pencils pencils physical buys by his office building over here
I got 150 000. Dolls
Ohio is a fine place. I've never been to ohio
I'll be honest. I've never had a reason to ever go there. It's kind of just a place
I don't I don't I don't have a reason to be I don't have any family there. I have no I don't want to go there
How much do we wake thousand bucks? All right, cool
I have enough money. I think we're gonna make a second store over here
Just a small one just for school supplies. Wait research team
Research team. What are you doing?
Shit, where's school supplies logistics? No bowling cinema fitness chemicals clothing
shit men's underwear, okay media
Mako e cigarettes we need clothing store. No, no
How much time do I have? I don't have enough time. When does it back to school start starts in?
One day. I can't build that in one day
I I can't I don't have enough workers that will do that back to school vapes
Just fill your grocery store with school supplies. I don't I can't even do it
Wait, hold on head sheets light bulbs
Reading cards
I'm doing like the gym carry. I'm sorry running out of parking. I need more parking
shit
more parking
About that. This is all right. I'm gonna have a store over here. Anyways
Hurry up hurry the fuck up. I'm serious. Mr. Green's business center
All right. Now we need to make a
This is all right. We'll have a section over here
We're gonna continue to build this out school supplies are gonna be up here
We want a ton of traffic because we we only have two queues
So we want people to really travel to get all this in-demand shit. Okay foundation. Let's go. I got money
Settle down relax. I got money small is too small
Yeah, we talked about amazon
The amazon was a computer in a garage. You have to start small. You can't just
You know what? I'm gonna make a ball today and it's gonna have 400 stores and i'm gonna own all property
That's false. That's a lie. Wait, is that just like a is that like propaganda?
Is that like straight up like, you know, he started with a computer in his garage with just impetus
This swollen like just charcoal covered like dirt hands that didn't happen amazon started in
It was trust fund money. Well, but his parents had a lot of money. Well, what do you want?
His parents were rich. Whatever
He still had his he still used his bare hands to like build the computer and then he built the warehouses with his hands
He used his bare hands to use to do amazon
This is propaganda it's not pro. Why is this propaganda? This is called i'm the miss i'm not informed correctly
This guy's a bootlicker. What?
Hold on. Let me just pop this huge zip that's on my grocery store. Hold on a minute
He's oh, he's a communist
Shut up. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up
He's shilling for amazon prime
No, if I was shilling for amazon prime, I'd say hey guys, you know
There's a quick button underneath your computer there and on the window if you click it you'll get your yeah
You know if you have the amazon prime all of us do
God use that all you know, you don't have to use it on me
But use it on me if you can but if you don't use it on somebody use your amazon prime
On me not on me, but not somebody else about me though. You're a sellout
Hey, it worked. I just have to say the words amazon prime guys. It worked
I didn't even do anything. I just said the words amazon prime and somebody gave five community subs
I didn't do anything. I just said those words
There's like an immediate triggering response to just I heard the word amazon prime five subs
I gave you money. He he
He's an influencer. All right. How about this? Let me influence you this way
have
Have a latte go have a latte and spend that five dollars on a latte
And then every five dollars you were thinking about giving me
Put it into like a little fund and after like a few years, you might have like
500 bucks you can get a goddamn index and you could do you could be in like an index
And then play vr games. It's too late for that
Oh, thank you admiral green for the five give me dirty subs and door open as well for five community subs
Preacher freshen. Oh grope clown. Thanks for five community subs. Jamie. Thanks for five community subs fell six
Thanks for five community subs of probably using those amazon primes
Stop actually actually stop
Actually, I command you to stop
Okay, you want influencer I demand that you stop looking let's do it. He doesn't like it. Don't do it anymore cut that out
Let's do it. He doesn't have negative reinforcement. Okay, do it. Give me all of your subs. I'm not gonna do that anymore
He told me to do it. He's a greedy asshole. Give him to me. You're more isn't you're insane
Can I I've been paused for like two minutes. I haven't even peed in like six hours
I've been streaming for six hours and I haven't even peed on almost uh
Agent nick fels
Jamie fell six. Thanks for the five community subs. Thank you weak for the five community subs. Hey harvey dent
Thank you harvey dent. Where is heart? What the fuck is happening right now? I need to stop do it
What's wrong with me today? This is all i've done in two and a half hours. Please. Let me get this. Let me do this
Dermot's wart it's gone by the way. Thanks for the five subs
What was this up here school supplies? I don't have much time pause
It's all we're gonna get a huge rush of customers all school supplies back here. It's gonna be a mad rush
Look at how tiny the entrance way is good luck
Sick, all right. What else should actually be back here? This object does not belong to an activity zone. Oh
Manage this is also part of essentials
Okay. So what else should be here school supplies?
School supplies tons of it. It's we're gonna get wiped out
What else could I put in here that I need?
diapers
They're not that they're not that young
people in like the
7th 8th 9th and 10th grade do not wear diapers
Reading cards like congratulations on your uh new day in school toys
construction toys board games
Backpacks derma's pants wrote up his ass. What is that clip? Why do you have that?
All right. I got 124 000. Let's not spend any more money. Let's make some money
I'm gonna have to expand the storage. I think a little
Yeah, I am
Is it gonna come out more we need more room hurry up hurry up and do it okay sign
Storage
What cancel what happened?
Storage here we go. Okay, that's a lot more
I'm ready
Stock those fucking shelves. What are you doing?
All right. All right, get it up there. The rush is here
Oh, no, there's too many. I don't have enough parking spaces to stick around. They are they're here. Yeah
Settle down they heard about the school supplies and I need more park anymore roads
Holy shit for customers are gonna get angry
um
How's it how much is that shit ton of fucking money? Oh
Okay
We can move we need another cashier counter at the end of the day. We will ignoring chat
Well, what do you want me to do? You guys have this a clip of like my
Apparently, it's like my ass
I guess you have like a photo of my ass
I don't I don't okay. So it's just it's just my ass in the camera. What do you want me to say here?
It's underwear wrote up his ass
How do you know how can you tell?
It's because wicked bunched up
He's not wearing any
All right enough enough
What do you mean we can tell?
Okay, I need to
why
Okay, this music is starting to like freak me out. Can I turn it down?
And if I was getting freaked out by this music, it's like scary. What was I saying? Nice parking job dick
Arrest that guy out of parking spaces and there's too many people
It's 26 people wanted to park and they couldn't they're just parking on top of each other
At least i'm making money
This is 600 bucks today. Oh, I need more stuff
What was I saying? Oh, right something. Oh, yeah
So that video that you just linked me has um, 2,500 views
before
Everybody else clicked on it. So
25 fucking hundred people have watched that video or maybe three or four of you
500 times each
This person is really angry. It's gonna be end of day. I know it's all right. We're doing all right
I'm gonna make this much much more sufficient. Ooh sell 20 different types of products 10 grand
Oh, I got my alcohol license now. Nice
All right, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful, beautiful. Okay, here comes school season
Irma click the link. What the hell are you guys doing now?
What is it?
Okay, that's I mean this is like what I order this is accurate. This is the germa 985. It's mine. It's my nuggets
Yep, it's my fry
My two mc chickens big mac and two mc doubles you got that on there
Um, excuse me. This is not accurate. This is not correct. This is completely wrong. We've made this first of all
I said powerade not gross two gross cokes
There's two mc chickens big mac meal six nuggets
Where's my sweet and sour sauce and the two mc doubles are there just in case i'm not done
Oh, can I get really pissed off at mcdonald's for a second? This is actual anger
True anger. They got rid of the regular mc chicken. They just have spicy mc chicken now. What is that bullshit?
It's just spicy mc chickens and the spicy chicken shit at fast food restaurants
Is gross go ahead and you can go ahead and at me, right?
I like the like the people say people say if the kids say these days
It's all the spicy chicken sandwiches at all these fast food restaurants. It's just like kind of hurts the back of your nose
It's just like a back of your nose like weird spice flavor. It's just like powdered spicy. You know what I mean?
It's it's a powder. It definitely feels like granular spicy powder. Where's my regular mc chicken?
I like spicy shit, but I don't like the powder spice
It's like a dusting that they put on it and the man is orange
True, but the regular one sucks. What eat a mc dick
Like you were saying like what the fuck
What like that's oh my god
If you're out i'm wrong
Okay, why would you read that? I guys the chat there's like almost 10 000 people there. I look over and I read something
You know how hard it is to read this shit
Sometimes it's just the first thing that happens. I just see it. He's 10k. Andy. That's fine
I can pull out stuff pretty well, but sometimes it's eat a mc dick
I'm sorry. I try
But no, this is wrong. This is wrong. I don't get two fries. I don't get
Two fries is too much. The apple pies are only occasionally close though pretty close
It's 9k smite. It's my smarties are great. Yes. They are this person's trapped in here there. He can leave
9.4k andy that's like so funny to me. Look at the fuck
All right. What should I research? I got uh alcohol now, right? Should we research a bar? Yes, we should was that even a question?
I need to make this a sign this
Oh you dummy
Control z fuck that looks good
Looks good
All right. Let's move some shit. What is this like random like megaman block? Can you get rid of that, please?
Oh my fucking god put it back. Thank you. These registers are wicked fucked up. I'm gonna don't worry. I got it
I gotta add another one two more
When how do I get self-checkout?
One more or two more. Yeah, one more. We got one more room for one more
Wait, this is wicked ugly, but it's okay. What's wrong with this? Oh shit. I can't have that there
Oh, um
There we go. What's going on? But move it down one man
Good right. Okay. Perfect. I need two cashiers twitch actor
Throwing for views you can't throw in this game. You can pause school supply section. I can put some more stuff here
all right, let me get the uh
What I want to do you already threw earlier, which way does the line go like this?
That's fine. This shit. You know what dude? Um, holy shit
Uh, I have enough money for this right? Do I have enough money for this?
I want to why am I trapped remove this road i'm going up here
Perfect takes a long time to do this, but it's okay
We're gonna have more parking here and i'm gonna have an exit here too term of the roof. I can't there's no roof
This is a top-down game. I am the roof. Okay, let's get some parking spaces. It is the ceo's parking lot
What the fuck? I can't build here. Why?
That's so stupid
Why not?
Why not fix the roof? There's nothing wrong with the roof. I there is no roof
There's no roof. This is nothing as a roof. What are you talking about?
All right. I this is a fuck save the game before I make any other dumb mistakes. I have 100 grand left
Uh, I had a roof what we're gonna leave. I don't have a roof
I hate this that I had to do this. I spent money on this
It'll go up somewhere to another store somewhere up here. Okay, it'll go up to another store. I'm gonna leave then
I can't put a roof. Oh nice. Okay, you can do different sections
Okay, stop distracting me. I gotta keep going
I need two more checkout cashiers
Checkout cashiers checkout cashiers. Let's go they come higher cashier
This is some okay store clerk
Shit, you're you're hired store clerk. You're hired
Okay, let's go
I need to move a little bit of stuff around
All right, get out there move it quick move those move them. I didn't even move them. Where's my builder? Where are the builders?
Are they actually there? Why are they like so what do they look like that? Oh, he's doing the tiles up there
I thought you just placed them like in the sims. All right, bring on the customers these poor people up here. Fuck
They got a long way to go
All right. Let's go spam the money new business any clothing store sell 30 different products. I need more parking spaces. Shit
um
Okay, we're gonna have an uh
An entrance over here. I think I can't build any roads anywhere. Everything is trapped. All right, fuck those people in their car
Let's go. Holy shit. We're about to be in the green. We're about we're in the green
That's a pog but it's 34 in the green. What are you doing finished building this? What are you guys doing?
What the car is in the way get that fucking toll that person. Hey, that's nine bucks in the green for the first time ever
Nine dollars in the green. Yeah, robert irvin came in tear down this wall. This wall doesn't need to be there
Open it up. You need school supplies back here. I'm fucking huge
Yes, yes, yes robert irvin you're huge I know i'm huge
That was a bad accent. I what i haven't seen the show in like five years
And look last month you turned a nine dollar profit
I did my work here
Flux into the camera like he always does. Why doesn't you okay? Well, I got a question for you
Robert irvin is fucking huge, right?
Don't you think you'd want to make that part of like a a schtick in the show?
like when he hangs something up on a wall and he's like
Move this uh, this couch over this way and then just bam just huge flex into the camera
That would be like cool, wouldn't it?
Like why doesn't he do? Uh, okay, you know like full metal alchemist, you know the guy the blonde here. I forget his name
Uh stretch armstrong
You know how he just goes like flex this way and like flex that way like i'm huge
I wish he would do that. It would be like funny if you did it like every episode
You're never gonna have a problem with fucking parking ever again. How much does this cost? This is a big expense
I hope it's worth it. All right, dave you got quite the work this afternoon
He's pretending he knows his name. I I know his name's armstrong
All right, we turn to profit. I need another entrance. No, we need another store over here quickly bar
a bar
We need a bar over here. We're gonna make a bar. I got 104 grand. Let's make a bar
This is a huge investment here
Oh
What happened?
This is a huge investment. I'm making a bar
Shit, it's nine o'clock in the morning. At least i'll be parking
It's under construction so you can just walk in
You just park your car walk through the grass and then you're at the frozen food section
That's so stupid
Okay, whatever speed it up
Customers customers customers 500 sales 20 000 customers more more more more more
Uh that sound that beep sound
Gotta love it
So much more customers can fit in here now and this is gonna be a bar. Look at that
Even though the money we spent come on
No
Buy buy buy buy buy buy buy buy
buy buy
Keep buying keep buying keep buying keep buying keep buying
Oh, it's getting a little overbought. It might be time to sell it
We did we did look at that. We did go 2 000 bucks didn't lose any money. All right, let's let's get to work on this bar
bar
What?
What do you mean? Oh shit, I need more mana. Okay
I don't want to run out of money. I'll do it slowly. We'll put some more stuff in here
We'll put alcohol in here and then eventually we'll just make it a bar. That sounds good to me
This is going to be essentials
Okay, so this is going to be they're going to sell alcohol here
And then we're going to eventually close the door and turn it into a bar
87 fucking k. Andy this parking lot sucks
At least it's turning into kind of an actual place
Why is the wall all messed up? Um, I don't know. I think because they have to finish building this shit first
Uh, okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Okay. Hold on. Hold on. This is so ton of this is so much parking
Oh
nice
All right. All right. I made a hundred dollars
I did it. I'm positive a hundred dollars for the day
Excellent
Good work everybody
Hi, this is really ugly
See, i'm doing okay. I got I got 90 grand in the bank. I need to have some doors over here though. Um,
Why is he gonna build this?
Oh what?
Oh shit, I get it. Okay, because it's sitting it's in it's in a bad spot. Okay, I get it
Hurry before they get here. Fuck. This has to go too. Hurry up get rid of it more profit more money
Oh, why are people using this?
Okay, people just using that for fun move that quick omega l l nice roof. There is no roof
They don't have there's no roof in the whole game. I know this we're trying to mess with me
Don't mess with me dude two entrances. Ah, we got real customers coming in. They're still going through the fucking door
Yeah, I got it. Okay alcohol. This is assigned already. I need
liquor alcohol cabinet
Beverages beer. Okay, we can have a little beer stand dude. Why are you doing that alcohol right here?
And then we'll do like wine. That's all right beverages beer beer only beer. It's only beer. Why?
Um juices we'll have like juice
Like mixers, you know, and then um, get rid of these now just make them fucking who cares
For the bottled waters looks good
Doc it up now. We have alcohol. I need more research for wine. Okay. Well, whatever we get beers
It's pretty expensive. Look at please look at the link. All right. Hold on relax
This is just creepy
I'm just looking up and seeing that would you still shop here?
All right, what if the prices were really low like we're talking one dollar for a large soda at mcdonald's low if everything was like
80 off but sometimes that guy would just
Reach in and like pick up somebody and just go like
Just drop him and swallow him. He did it like once an hour would you
Would you still shop there?
No, okay. So let's say this let's say a thousand people go in there in an hour
That's a one out of a thousand chance
That's gonna be you
And like I I didn't say you couldn't like run around and like grab like something and like throw it at him and try
To get away and like dodge behind stuff. You can do that. He might not get you. He might just be like
And just go for the person over there still no talking we're talking 80 off everything in the whole store
Come on, give me some more money. We gotta fill these parking spaces. Nobody wants anything in here. What do they want halloween?
Candy and greeting cards. I can do that. Let's do that refill this candy and greeting cards
This is all school supplies get this shit out of here
I was oh we need food shelves. Oh candy candy candy candy candy school supplies things is done
Although i'd wait outside until I saw somebody get grabbed and then I'd go in okay
So that's that's not a bad strategy
What if you pulled up there and you don't know when the last time you did it was?
Like what if you pulled up there and he's sitting there just looking down
How can you tell how do you know?
When he did it you would just wait an hour
So you would sit there for a full hour and then when you saw him grab someone then you would go in
So it's worth waiting a full hour in the parking lot. Just sit the way listen to talk radio
Now with a parking lot is you can't sit in there for more than an hour
Every one of the parking spaces has like a meter on it and when you like pull in it's like
It's like a 20 minute meter goes starts to counting down if you don't get the hell out of there
You gotta pull out within 20 minutes or his eyes just
Go right over to your car and he just puts his hand up and he's like the hulk grabs you and like just
Throws you into the atmosphere
Still going just park somewhere else and walk
Park, okay
So if you park here you park it like over here and like camp out overnight and just with binoculars
And then just wait and see when he does it and then like what but it's good. What if it takes you
It's gonna take you like 40 30 40 minutes to walk this far
By the time you get here you have probably like 20 minutes to get the fuck out of there
How far do you live from the store? I don't know. You might like live here. You might be like camped out here
Play the video game
Hey, i'll tell you when i'm ready to play the video game. All right, bro
Will you research the bar already so I can do this shit? Come on. You're at a profit for the day
Take a look at that
Mm-hmm. Everyone thought it was over. Everyone thought it was over when we hit that bottom. No, we're back
It doesn't take you 30 minutes to walk less than a mile. This is not less than a mile
It's probably like five miles 53
Can I afford to put another two desks in here? What do you think? I think I can afford it
He's never walked in his life. He's a car pick him up
Yeah, guys like my like feet are like so like
sensitive and soft
Because i've never walked I I just like have somebody pick me up
And like walk me to to a car carry me and like put me in the back seat
And then they drive me somewhere and then somebody puts me in a carriage
And they push me around the store and I pointed stuff if I like walked two or three steps and be like, ah, ah, yeah
Somebody pick me up. I've never used them. I make them look no stop. Stop what just stop
Just stop get back in here and build that. All right, we need uh, another person in the way
We can do five. All right, five. We'll do five people in the office. I got money
I need three people. No two more people in the office who we hire. You're digging yourself deeper
Why do you assume that I have a shovel in my hand because of the grave what minus two?
Fuck you that sucked what i'm saying what what you assume that i'm like even aware of what i'm even talking about
That was that wasn't even a joke. That was me just like oh you're digging you're digging
Yourself deeper and i'm like why you think I got a shovel
No, that's like a rebuttal to like you think I what do you think I know what you're talking about is smart
It was very smart
All right, I gotta hire people. I can't keep up with this. Um, mute it. That's just mute the stream
That's how I do it 53. Okay hire. Uh, I need to assign this that would be good if I did that
I don't even like this game hire office worker
Actually, uh you you too
You're better. All right, that's that's a full office now. Thanks for breaking completely twitch. What happened? What happened twitch is messed up right now
Also, then I can finally convert this to a bar and we can have a grocery store bar guys
The stream is a lot better on mute. Try it out. It's really good. No, seriously
I kind of feel like it would be pretty shitty actually
All right, we got people working. This is going good
17 more man hours and we can finally have a bar
Here's the question. Should I have the bar just be over here or should I make this the bar?
Oh, there's an annoying dickhead talking
Like in a separate building
All right, we're gonna make it up here
Or like right here
That was low effort
High effort. Hey high effort
Oh, but apparently that's funnier than the I didn't bring a shovel thing. Let me write that down
I don't like this patch of grass. He's still mad about it
All right bar, let's go 70 70 70 70 we're turning a profit every day
I need more customers. I need a bar
This dude's unclippable
Are you sure?
Somebody just wrote good one
Uh, yeah, I know that was pretty bad hurry up and research this shit. I want to make a bar. Oh, come on really
300 bucks though. That's not bad
And then i'm gonna do night hours because then the bar can stay open 24 7, right?
I'm not gonna spend any money. I'm just gonna save it. Why are your employees in a broom closet?
Um, no, this is the staff entryway they come in here
I guess this is kind of like the little like
Room to get like and then put the hazmat suits on or they go through the thing
What's that? What's that room called?
D decontamination room, right staff solitary confinement. No, it's it's just it's like the staff entrance and look
It could be a little bigger. Yeah, that's an among us reference. That wasn't it was I didn't make that you did
It's an airlock. There you go airlock. I'm not spending any money. All right, let's start the new day
We'll get the bar here and then i'm gonna go this way with the bar minus two the person that said among us not me
Minus two worst stream. I don't believe that. I'm sorry. You can't just say it. It's the worst stream
I'm having fun. I don't know about you guys. I'm having a good time. I like my grocery store lots of demand lots of money
Coming in 96. Here we go. There you go bar. Let's go right over here. How big should a bar be?
Bars, not that huge are they they're not massive. They're not like this. That's that's how I don't know man
That's a lot of money. I don't have the money to do that
I'm gonna run out of capital if I do that. I don't this is not a smart idea
I don't have enough money do something already. What the fuck? I this is like a sim slow sim game
All right. I'm gonna do this
33 000
I hope it's worth it
After this, I can't spend any money. We have to just watch
Halloween shit halloween halloween costumes bars frozen food coffee shops sales security
logistics
bowling cinema scary movies
chemical supplier deodorant
clothing supplies
All right. We need to do well. I got I want clothing gotta work on clothes
Candies and greeting cards. Okay. Hold on just a minute pause this for real
greeting cards
All school supplies. Okay greeting cards
Greeting cards the whole thing greeting cards greeting cards greeting cards
Okay, we've got four shelves of greeting cards and we want a bunch of candy over here
Delete all this dog shit all candy and we're gonna have like a halloween theme here, too
Hurry, hurry, hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Where's the builder? Where's the builder?
Oh my fucking god. That's not good. Okay
I'm gonna try I got can I say he's gonna stop doing that they're building the bar hire more. I don't think I can
office worker
Maintenance center hire. Oh hire builder noodles
Kill piss or non
Bunnery build builder builder. Who's the best builder? They're all the exact same who's fast. You're fast
Okay, go hurry. Hurry. Hurry. Hurry. We're running out of time
All right, do it now the event is currently going on right now. I got a lot of time for this
I need a full thing of candy. That's the bar. We'll do that in a minute
Here we go. Give it all this shit tons of candy all candy
Candy candy candy go for it food candy
Candy candy candy. I do middle shelf something else. No costumes or anything, right greeting cards and candies
Okay. No, I have one for liquor actually not a bad idea move the liquor cabinet over here
We'll get rid of this. This is gonna be the halloween section
We'll do liquor candy and greeting cards this beer here put the beer over here beer in here as well
Good. All right. Now we have to have a halloween theme here. All right. Um, bow ties like orange something scary go for it
Liquor in the grocery store. What degeneracy is this? It's actually in a lot of places. Please click the link. Sure
It's been it's been updated. It's been updated. All right, let's see. Why is this guy a jogger?
Why are you jogging through the grocery store? This guy didn't have a cart. He's just here for the exercise
All right, can we get that trash?
Stock that please
Actually, I need to know I need to hire another stalker under his shelf stalker
Where the rats where take care of that, please
We got to stock this up quick
And then i'll fire them immediately
All right stalk stalk clerk stalk clerk. Here we go dan
Make you freak. You're the best one here. Let's go
All right, hurry up. Where's the crew? Daniter will get that. Don't worry. That's a bot. It's not a bot
It's from when I refreshed like an hour ago
Stock those shelves with candy and cards and treats. All right, here comes the crowd. Let's see. Come on
Here does everyone want we're in the middle of are we are we in the middle of halloween?
It's still halloween, right? It's not over
Upcoming event is this no, it's still halloween
So late to halloween
Usually people are super early for halloween shit. I was like three days late. No one's even going in here. Are you kidding me?
Really? What the fuck?
Somebody buy something over here
Actually, there is a lot of sales going on here a lot of waiting
We got 45 people in this store. How about the bar? I'm working on the bar in a minute
Here we go. Hey freeze 9292. He's a gamer. Of course he is customers are leaving the center because they are hungry
There are no restaurants. Oh, shut up. There's a lot of people
Money money money money money money money money money money money money. All right, it's christmas season books
Action figures games video games candies books dvds game consoles. All right, we need to just we need to
I'm really going with the bar aesthetic
You're all right made 100 bucks. Oh the store closed and they all had to leave
Wait, they didn't even pay for the growth. They didn't pay for this
They didn't even pay
They all just walked out shit. It's christmas time. Okay replace
uh
So this candy beer greeting cards, what else does it want books?
Okay books household goods
schools toys board games
Greeting cards school supplies, what do you get books from where books? All right. Well, let me make the bar first
This is a bar
There you go
Okay, I need
cashier stock clerk
Bar counter bar shelf and storage. Okay, so let's get some
I need storage for this place
It doesn't have to be that big or it's the bar build that up, please. Thank you
Door, okay, you stay right there again. I need you back in here. Okay storage
Sign storage link these two together
bar or storage storage one no storage five
What does it link to?
All right, can I link this?
Is this storage for this?
storage capacity for what
I'm gonna piss my pants
I gotta rename this stuff. This is this is grocery storage g store
And this one is going to be bar store. So what I can't connect this
Oh, there we go link storage. Here we go. Okay
Opening hours we open at 9 a.m
And we close we close at midnight. No 2 a.m
I'm gonna we open at 10 and we close at midnight an am to midnight. I can't do overnight anything
I have a bar that closes at like
Imagine having a bar that closes at like 10 o'clock
What are you a fridays?
Okay, well whatever it's gonna have to do we're going to gotchas
Shout out to the uk bars in the uk close at like 10 o'clock at night 9 o'clock at night. They do
Yes, they do. Oh, it's a covid thing. Okay. I thought you meant like in just they did in general
I was like no they didn't
All right. We need bar bar counter bar shelf bar counter with stools. Oh nice. All right
Oh cool. Yes. Look at this sick. Okay now we need a bar shelf back here
Oh, fuck that has to be hold on just build it so I can do this
Oh what the storage people can't get out right? Um, we'll go this way instead. Give me this. You just made mows
I'm not done a bar shelf
Uh, I need like a table dinner table restaurant table coffee table lounge table. How about just uh, uh
Dinner table like a diner. This is like yeah, this is like a restaurant table. Can't place this object here. Fuck off. Okay table
Why is it green? I don't want to be green
Need a bathroom i'll make a bathroom. Don't worry and build. Uh, I need a little bit back here
A bathroom bathroom will be right here
Or yeah over here the builder get over here. Why does this have the thing on it?
There's no product assigned for this dude fresh bread
Fresh bread
What fresh fresh fruits we can have fresh fruits. Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Give me another one of these this bar is gonna be sick fresh fruits and fresh bread. All right, let's make a bathroom
Uh, this needs to move
In fact, just delete this what the fuck is this here for? Is this a vegan bar?
How is it a vegan bar? I need to hire a waiter. Uh,
Okay waiter probably you is there was there a bartender starting at no you have you worked till midnight
Start at 10. You work till midnight. That's a 14 hour work day
Shit, okay. That's not all right. That's not okay. Let me just finish the bathroom rest room six
Get in there
Now we need a door
Okay, toilets toilet. You know what I mean build those we have a different tile in here, dude. That's so funny
Hmm, we need like bathroom tile, but it should be you know, it should be a little swanky
But I think I haven't built where the fuck did the build the toilets go what shit? It's almost 10 am 25 grand
Don't do anything else. Okay, we're good. Do I need anybody here? I don't need anybody here, right?
Do I need anyone here? This is a bar and I got a waitress here
Waiter, it's open bar is open. It's incomplete requires cashier and stock clerk. Fuck. I mean cashier
Is there a checkout line at the bar? No, the bartender does that what is the bar store? No, no, no
Okay, that's storage our cashier. Oh shit kill piss you look at you
Okay kill piss and then I need a what else would I want? I need a cashier and I want stock clerk
Here we go. Look at that. All right, we're good get to work. Yes
All right, who's coming to the bar? Come on in. What can we get you? How much do you spend here?
How much money have a seat have a seat at the are you serving them? Are you just smiling? Um, something's wrong
What's happening? I don't have any supply
Where's the worker? Where's the person that's supposed to be doing this? Oh, that's not good bar store. What? Yeah
What the fuck is going on bar storage? I didn't set it up. No loading bay. Oh
Shit the bar shelves need to be in there. Yeah, I hired somebody staff stock clerk waiter and a cashier
I need a loading bay. Okay. Hold on. Uh, let me fix this loading zone. I can't do it right here
Why why get rid of that load it up?
Load up the storage. Why is it not get hurry somebody get in here and put this in here shelves
Wait, I need bar shelves. What the fuck is going on? It's a high effort link. Hold on. This is wrong
What's going on here? Oh, I got clothings. So why is somebody not working here and like is there's a staff door there
They can get in why the person just don't want the person just doesn't want to work
All right, we're gonna do sales monitoring set storage cap in the room storage capacity one
Desires 100 percent
So especially wait
Oh
I I get it. Okay, because it's it's too small. It's way too small. Okay, click the link now yet
Click link hurry before mods get rid of it. Why wouldn't mods get rid of it? Is that gonna be enough?
Finally, okay. Go go ahead. We're open open for business. Let's go stock it up
Holy shit. It's so much money to buy drinks 30 bucks a pop
Yo, oh this fresh fruits and fresh bread too. Perfect
All right. Look at it. Look at what let me show it to me. It's just
I have to it's a video. Hold on. They even added audio. I don't hear anything. All right. Wait, I gotta piss
I really do so bad. I'll be right back. I really do have to pee and then we'll watch it. This is paused, right?
It is now all right. We're back. Hello
All right, let's take a look
Why is there one miss why is there a mcdonald's bag in there and a mcdonald's drink did you you didn't what'd you get?
How'd you do that?
Okay, cool
Your mcdonald's hand it over
Okay time for our fresh fruit and fresh veggies and fresh bread
We went down some money because I made the bar but I have a bar now and you
I don't know what you are doing
You have this person's been sitting here the entire time and they won't leave. It's currently how late is it?
What time is it? There's nobody here at midnight. And uh, what are you leaving with? Hey, it's not you. It's fresh fruit
You see the bag you had a bag of groceries get back. You told her to work that late. Yeah, because I wanted I
I wanted to have a bar open till like two or three
Are the bars ready? What are we researching right now something frozen food? No sales, right? Right sales. Okay. These people are still working, right? Yeah
All right. Let's let the money roll in for a little while
Need a bigger staff room
I mean not really
Going home
All right. See you later
Anything I can do for small improvements. I only have 20 grand. I don't want to spend it. Not even a coffee pot
I don't look i'll look i'll help
Here how's this? This isn't a staff room. It's a maintenance room
Coffee shop counter. No, I can give them a plant
What can I hold on? Let me look at some of this stuff. I could give them a table with some fresh bread on it
Do your homework?
Give them a microwave fresh vegetables. Give them a water cooler
I'll make this a little all right a little bit bigger. It's just this is too small
It's four grand that i'm not going to get back. This is all messed up
Uh, I hate that I hate it. There you go bigger staff room move the fresh vegetables over here
We'll give you a little place to sit down
Uh seat sit
Sink
Seat oh I could give them like a reclining chairs. Not yet. See much better environment. Oh, wait
Okay maintenance center better fresh vegetables. Let's start the day. It's not a prison cell make an actual staff room
Um, I don't know if there is that storage a store fast food ticket lobby movie theater
I need a I need cinema maintenance center bowling alley office
bar security center
Coffee shop food court fitness center. Yeah, there's no staff room christmas supplies. Oh, right, right, right. Okay, so we need
uh winter starts in one day
We need construction toys action figures. I can do that. This is a food shelf
Okay, construction toys toys action figures
construction toys action figures
What else is what do you want board games greeting cards video games? Okay candy candies. This is candy here, right?
candy candy or candies
We'll turn this into
Oh wine. I got wine. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, let's get some wine over here wine and liquor bingo
The member of your staff has died
That game is
Precious. I love that game so much
Seriously, I wish there was a casino ink two three four and five
Why couldn't there's been there been at least one more wasn't I researching clothing alcohol bar sales?
Didn't I do clothing? I did I did I did I did I did
Okay, we need clothes. I need a clothing store. How much money do I have?
Why did I make a fucking bar? What a useless thing to have here? Um, I we're gonna put clothes. Oh my god
Okay, hold on pause. This is the holiday section. Um move this close. What kind of clothes game consoles?
That's not close. We're still gonna put it here clothes clothing
uh
Men's underwear don't have access to more stuff than just men's shoes. Okay shoes and underwear
Toilet alert what this place even open? No, not yet. There we go. It's a janitor
I don't know. I'm losing a lot of money. I'm spying too much shit. Let's let it play out 10 o'clock bar open
Let's let the money roll in looking good there at the table. Yes, you guys said the tables were a bad idea
You guys said the fresh bread was a bad idea
Oh really? Oh really? That was an order of fresh bread right there 26 bucks fresh bread and a beer fresh fruits and a beer
Really?
What was that? Oh, you're doing on money good. Look at this profit for today
Way better than it was before
all these alerts
Wait
Drugstore bookstore bowling alley, there's so many alerts customers are leaving the center because there are no restrooms
There's a restroom. There's a bathroom right here
Oh, you fucking assholes want one here. Okay, fine. Sure
I'll put a bathroom in here. Fine. Fine. Fine. Fine
Whatever here. Here's your bathroom
There. Mm-hmm
There done door one-way swing gate what oh sales monitor, all right, there's a bathroom now
All right, that takes care of that
That's the biggest profit we've had in one day. That's 1200 bucks in a day. That's a pretty major profit
I'm running low on cash, but I should be fine now. We're gonna coast
Sales monitoring allows the automatic monitoring of sales, which you can review in the demand menu
Oh shit demand people want books real bad open a bookstore. How do I get a I need books?
research books
Books right here. All right, get on that. It's amazon. Yeah
I got a bathroom. I've got this is a bathroom too, right? Yeah, nobody's using that bathroom
next up
We're going to make a bookstore because this is I I don't this is turning into every store in one store
I don't like that. We're gonna convert this to the liquor section. We're gonna move some of these
Grocery store things around i'm gonna have a bookstore right here. I need to make some money first all these alerts
I know I got I look bathrooms fine people want a drug store
It's inaccessible builders can't access a work order. Yeah, I fixed it people are hungry
Well, go to the bar and get the fresh bread already. What do you mean? You're hungry
There's like meat cheese potatoes onions
Women's underwear men's underwear
Plenty of stuff here shoes shoes are made of the leather you can eat everything here. This is the worst mall
It's it starts slowly and then you build up your empire
I'm gonna turn this into like a shoe store
Like I only had two hundred thousand dollars. All right, I had a small I had a small loan of two hundred thousand dollars
It's that it it's doing it's done. Okay, that's how you know, the stream is really gone off the rails
What's wrong with this? It's expired. Oh, well somebody look at it
No bartender dummy. Yes, there is that who thinks mr. With all the drinks
2016 meme
I know
Oh turn a daily profit over 500 smackaroos. Wow, jimmy kimmel funny
Okay, you got me there you do wow that was jimmy kimmel level funny
Hey, guess what?
Like a quarter of a billion people turned in to jimmy kimmel every afternoon when he's alive
Okay, so he's doing something right, isn't he? All right. I'm just gonna look at I got 18 grand. All right, we're gonna coast
It's just coasting time. We got plenty of parking. We got our drugs
This is booze. Wait. Ooh, look at that profit
Look at the profit here, too. I am not losing i'm slowly winning
He has more viewers than you
Yeah
Yes. Yes
Jimmy kimmel has more of a larger audience than germa 985
Yes, that is accurate by probably a few million people
Oh mega love these he's a nobody
You know in the grand scheme of things guys, yeah
I'm not like jimmy kimmel
yet, not yet
Let's see
Holy shit, man. Look at all this money. I need another I need more cashiers. How slow are these cashiers?
Not bad. I think they level up. I need another I need more checkouts
This is naughty. This is bad
Okay, is it weird that I want to just build a checkout counter here with like five checkouts
Connected to the same store essentials. So then they have to walk across the street and check out there's no more room
It's surrounded by roads
I guess I could take some of this out and put it here
Our is really not doing that. Well, i'm not happy with the performance here
Nobody's coming in to drink
All right. We're okay. We're doing all right almost time to start the bookstore profits. Not bad. What do we got?
People want to go see major movie release. Fuck. It's too many things
Almost have enough for books when that's done. We're doing books. How many people will work here?
Is there all right?
Parking lot's getting a little full
Hope you don't plan on becoming an architect
No, i'm 35. I don't think that's a career choice. I'm gonna start now
I don't think i'm gonna just go to like 10 years of architect school. I don't think so
Not something I was very good at anyways
So it's already something I know i'm not very good at and I have to go to a lot of school for that
It would be 45 or so when I started
Maybe 50
I'd work on maybe one or two major projects and get fired from them because I screwed something up
52 get fired. Okay
I don't know if I want to do that camel has 2.2 million viewers. You have 1.1 million. No
That's not how that works
You didn't want to have an enclosed mall with parking. Yeah, I did
I wanted it to be parking this huge parking lot around it and then everything inside
And then like we got a bar over here, but that's not I don't even own this
Big money today. Come on
growth more growth
Growth growth growth don't let these people leave without paying come on. Bring them up. Don't close the door
Close the door lock the door lock the door
That's so much product that would just let them go for free. How could you be angry?
Imagine being that angry and getting out of here with like fucking 180 dollars worth of shit for free
Why are you so mad about that? All right, we still grew almost ready for the bookstore. I need another cashier
I'll put it right here
That's more that's another employee though. Can I afford that?
Let's move some stuff around
All right, move some shit around here
This is going up. We need to really reorganize this place. This place sucks the complete reorganization of this place
M move up here
move
Here move here move it put it right here
A little off. I hate it, but it's okay
This is gonna be plenty of room for checkout counter
That one little thing
It's all right. Don't matter. Let's do that first so I can look at what it looks like
Yeah, you gotta move this stuff I already said make it all vertical, please i'm begging you
All even how vertical this is so much cleaner you do all your shopping here
And then we'll do some checkout line. This is gonna be so much more efficient
Make it symmetrical. I don't know what to do with this guy. I do I can't make it symmetrical doesn't matter
This down here. This is like the checkout line people in the checkout line can kind of browse
Need more room though check out that
Uh, no put this
Over here. No, no, no, no idiot. That's where the other checkout counter is gonna go
You dumb
You're not even smart like me
Okay, then this can we just wish up with these?
Remember, this isn't a mall
Okay
When a bookstore gets opened here
It's gonna be a mall. You'll have a grocery store and booze
Emporium a bar and a bookstore. That's like a strip mall
All I just the only thing I need here is I need a sub shop in a verizon store
And then what would you call it? That's a mall
The bar that opens at 10 in the morning
Just make it a walmart you redditor
This is a bunch of storefronts. Yeah, you park your car and you can like go into the verizon store
And then you can go into the sub shop
and then you can like go into the grocery store get some stuff and you can just
Have go over here to have a have like a fucking fresh fruit platter
Get a drink to go
And like well, no not like that
I mean like in a to-go glass like take one of these and then like bring it home
But you don't even have to why is the bar even here?
You can just buy alcohol here. Why is this here?
If I sell alcohol here
Why are you gonna go over here to buy alcohol?
You don't go. Hey, i'll pick up a couple bottles of wine
Hello, sir. I'll take a bottle of wine to go, please
Here you go. Thank you
Oh, by the way, here's sixty dollars
It was twelve over there in the grocery store. Why is there a bar here?
But you can drink at the bar
Yeah, I guess you know the people sit at bars. I know you can sit at a bar, but what?
It's for the atmosphere. This person no parking allowed here. What are you doing? Oh, no, that's a staff member. Okay
All right. What was I doing moving this get rid of this fucking trash. The trash is fucking this all up
Why is that so off? Oh, it's backwards
Okay, no one wants to drink at a shitty bar. That's not true. I'm really sorry to tell you but that is completely inaccurate
How would you know you guys don't think i've been to like a bunch of you guys?
They don't think i've been to a shitty bar before
I'm 35. I'm not like
20 looters
No, 35. I've never been to a bar. That's not that's not even accurate now. We have tons of room. Look at that
Oh bingo. That's probably enough for now. I need two more cashiers man. That's money. I don't want to spend what's going on
Views are full. Yeah, people are hungry. Whatever people want a drugstore. Sure earn a daily profit of two grand
Okay, word of mouth people want a drugstore people want a bookstore people want a drugstore people want a liquor store
People want a drugstore people want a grocery store people want a grocery store
I already have one people want a drugstore
Make 2 000 sales total and you get 30 grand. Okay, you want a drugstore people are getting car accidents or something
One drugstore people get 100 people on the same time sells 20 people
It's all so many different people things. I don't know. Oh, it's snowing cool. All right, let's uh
Clothing how we doing on clothes almost time to open. It's a christmas miracle
See they're eating it. It was expired. Somebody ate it getting close to the bookstore
That's a pog moment. Uh, we need a cashier for essentials two of them actually
No, we're going with hester and
Cashier cashier speed and social ability. Let's go
All right, we got it i'd open stock it up. We're so ever closer
To the time the guy at the disresident sleeper. Here we go. We need to make two thousand dollars in one day
Extra checkout lanes much more efficient placement of all goods. Do you think even in here? These are all empty. Okay are
Opening here we go. Excuse me, ma'am. Can I interest you in some kiwis and a tall wheat barley beer?
Oh, I made thirty thousand dollars by having a bunch of sales efficiency
This is pretty efficient. Come on. Let's turn that profit
Be funny do something funny already time that guy out for five minutes
All right, you know, okay, here's the thing. You know, like I made was it how much money not enough?
Okay
So if you went up to like a professional athlete that was about to go up to to hit at the plate a baseball player
And you said hey, you're the home run next pitch. They're gonna be like I
I'm gonna try
Do you better hit a home run on the next pitch and then they swing and they miss hey
You were supposed to hit a home run on the next pitch. I told you man
I hit a home run like once every three games, dude
I can I can just do it. I can't just hit a fucking home run when I feel like it
Yeah
Well, guess who?
Mo von could move on hasn't played baseball in like 20 years, man
It's i'm on the team now
Yeah, I wish it was both on now you okay
Okay, and I swing and I missed again. Let's try two man. You're in my head
analogy andy
Jimmy kimmel could yeah, that's what i'm talking about. Like on jimmy kimmel's like funnier than you
care
Hey, jimmy kimmel swallowed five eggs on camera last night. Why didn't you do chubby bunny to one up them?
You got a low batting average and i've said this before
But you guys understand that if you go up to the to play in baseball and you strike out seven times in a row
Well, you hit the ball into play and you get on base three times out of ten
You are one of the best baseball players to ever live
If you can hit if you can get to get a 300 batting average
You're like one of the best players to ever play the game
So that means i'm allowed seven wicked shitty jokes as long as I tell three good ones
I'm one of the best joke tellers to ever live. This is not baseball
You got to draw some walks. No swing and miss only and then hit ball baseball isn't funny
You got a long way to go, buddy
All right
I got 48 000. Holy shit
You are such a quintessential american
uh
Oh, okay. We can do a bookstore now
Like thanks, I guess I don't know. What does that mean hand tools power tools?
I want movie theater
I i'm not gonna do this yet. I'm gonna after the close today. We're gonna make our wait
Do people even care about books anymore?
No, they don't
I'm so late to every one of these events. What's coming up next valentine's day wine jewelry candies. Okay, we still have that up there
We won movie theater
Books are cringe
Uh, okay
My big profit today
Is it the car bases?
I need more customers. We're getting them out very very quickly
This is really really good efficiency though. Come on. Give me that big big money big money. Got it. That's it
That's uh, what is that? I have 2 000 bucks in a day, right?
Oh
What?
After hours what happened turn off the stream cringe chris connect the roads for the love of god
I mean I committed to the bookstore idea, but now
Um, who wants to go to a bookstore at a mall? No, I want like an arcade
I'm making an arcade or maybe movie theater should be the next thing move the garbage check demand charts
fast food
soda milk
Okay, and this this is the quintessential american not me
This is it. This is it fast food soda and milk. How do I make a fast food?
I'm already doing like a cinema restaurant. I have restaurants one looks fast food restaurants. Damn it
I need okay work on this. I'm gonna expand the office a little more too. I have money
I think I can do it. What do you guys think? Yes or no? Hey chat. Andy. What do you think?
Make a fast food movie theater. That's actually not a bad idea. I'm gonna regret this I think but whatever
There's a lot of money, but I I want that research. It's just too slow
All right, then I need how many more people do I need?
Manage assign
This oh you dummy
What are you doing? Okay office
Manage we need okay office
There's one two three four. There's five people that work here. How many seats are there?
One two three four five six seven eight nine ten eleven. I need six more people
Jesus
Office work. Come on in
I just have to hire everybody. I don't it doesn't matter how bad they are
All right, we're two more. It should really speed that up. We should be able to get a fast food soon
39 man hours. Jerma is not a redditor and I use reddit
Like look stuff up sometime. I thought you were ocd fix the roads
Yeah, I like I like that's
I can't even like
No, no, no, no, don't don't don't don't don't
So slow down slow down slow down
Connect the roads like this. Oh shit. That gives me more parking spaces. Thanks, dude
What do I do on money 31?
Look at how much faster this is going up. We'll get that in one day movie theater going right here
Come on. What about the hole? I got it. There you go. I'm done pretty good. Not bad
All right, we got 50 percent. We got one more day or so. I'm making money. I'm not losing any money. We're fine
Fix the fucking corners. I what do you I can't
What do you want to do? It's not a big deal
What the fuck is that?
How would you even get out? Okay, if somebody was parked here
And somebody was parked here
What do you do? You're in deep shit. No, stop. Fuck whatever. That's why I can't connect the roads
Actually, wait a minute. Oh shit. I can lead this up to here to a new world. Who cares make it loop
No, because this will this can go out this way eventually this can go up here
All right, I got 29 000
Please connect the dotted lines
Wait, hold on. Do you mean this?
Like that, please no. No, what do you mean connect the dotted lines?
I can't do anything with these
Move the trash zone
actually pretending
You mean like this?
Like that like a loop like this
No bottom. What are you talking about? That because this is gonna go down and around
Odd washers skip growing for content. I don't know what you guys want me to do with this
I just auto is yelling at me
Delete the one parking spot
Right in fucking front of you
I do it. Okay. I know that there's a dotted line here, but what the fuck are you talking about?
What do you want me to do with it?
What do you want to do with this?
Remove this road talk about this. It's a dead end. Yeah, but who these these these guys these are these people are like
Ants they just go around and going it out now down down. It's not like they actually have to park here
It's like an ant algorithm that parks them here
Please do click maps. I don't have click max and click maps enabled
Exit. Oh my god
There I did it. Hold on. Hold on. I gotta get my dog get back out there and do that
No, fuck. I'm trying to get this to connect good enough. Yes, I know that's what I hold on. Hold on
I don't I've replaced my brb video with this. I forgot. Okay. I wanted a snack
I just want to dump minus twos
We have an image. Hold on
There's an image
You want me to go through?
Hold on I still I don't don't dump that
I still don't know what you mean
This is what you want. I'm trying to figure out what this means. Where is this?
This is what you want. You want me to do this. Let me see if I can get it
I'll do i'm gonna do a stream reveal when I get it. Oh
Ladies and gentlemen, he got it sick
Okay. Now just put put like a statue there or something how much money 28 when do I get the movie theater soon movie theater?
That's all I want. That's all I care about
I care about making money. I don't care about serving drinks. I don't care about any of this shit
I care about making a movie theater and a fast food restaurant. I don't care about anything else
Just like wake me up when he gets to the part where it's 100 for the movie theater
And the fast food already turned to profit for the day
Wipe that feet up
90 then we do move we finish movie theater. We got fast food movie theater right here bang. It'll be sick
Restaurants are done fast food restaurants ready. Hold on a second
Let's finish the cinema. That was pretty much halfway, right?
Cinema. Oh still got a ways to go, but it's all right
Fast food restaurant, you know where it's going
Right here. I got 28 000
There's none have to be big fast food restaurants are not big a fast food restaurants like this big. They're tiny 20 grand
They're bigger than that
That's that's enough
That's the size of a bedroom
Odd watchers unfollow
Hey, why are you being so mean? Okay. This is
a
Fast food restaurant movie theater fast food restaurant. Here we go. There it is
Now what do we need in here? We need border counter soda dispenser fast food warmer
Cook storage. Oh my god. This is tiny. Where's the bank? How do I take it along?
Loan duration 10 days loan duration 100 days interest rate 4.7
Mountain loan 21 000 interest 10 000. What a fucking joke
30 day loan and I want okay, that's only 700 in interest. I'm gonna get eight nine grand. I'm gonna pay this
Okay, let's go. I got the money loan. Yeah
Imagine imagine loans being more than like fucking three percent interest
Oh, yeah, I mean it's uh, I gave you like five grand and now you owe me, uh 80
That's how it works. I'll get you a good interest rate like a 75 interest rate annual. Oh, I gave you
212 dollars
Well, i'll see in 10 years when you give me 50 fucking grand over the course of your life the canadian homer what?
All right. Let's uh expand this a little bit. I got the money this thing's gonna this is gonna print money
It just is let's make it a little wider
That should do it, right? There's so much money. How are you supposed to make any money?
There's so much money to do this. Hey, uh, hey, uh pooh, I need some ice cream and some extra cola
Why I know what the exact line is why you have to say that we are going to assign this is storage
Right here is really all we need just a little bit like right there. Ah, we need a bathroom too
Um, this can be the fast food restaurant this this is bathroom and this is bathroom restroom. Okay. All right
I'm okay with that now. I need to buy some shit. I need uh, what the hell do I need in here cashier stock
Lurk fast food cooking range fast food fucking range. This is the I need a kitchen. All right kitchen is gonna be
um down here is the cooking range and we also need a
Uh cook we need fast food warmer. That's usually like right up here isn't it thousand bucks for this shit
This is like the kitchen and then we'll have a little bit of a dining area too. Okay. This is the warmer
soda dispenser
Order a counter. All right. Here we go. We'll have two of these right here
Yeah, right here and then right here sec and then a soda machine
So this would be behind the counter and they're not usually behind the counter, right?
They're usually kind of away from people can go up to it after cooking range
All right, let's take a look wait. I need a place to get in here. We need a wall here
Need a door. Yeah, usually you walk into like like hello. Welcome to mcdonald's and there's like just people there
I mean you walk in past the line
Um shit, I gotta think I gotta flip the whole restaurant. I think I have to flip the whole thing
Yeah, we're gonna flip it just have to move some of this shit. Okay, we'll get some move some stuff
Actually, you know, that's not that big of a deal. That's okay. Wait, they can be blocked
All right, move this we're just gonna flip it there. Yeah, okay
Rest room need a door here. This is such a small bathroom, but whatever just a place to piss
That's all assigned correctly bathroom toilets
Now we need doors actually to door
Staff door and a staff door. Perfect toilet cubicle
We don't need a urinal because look look you can just piss in there. That's whatever. I mean we all right. That's fine
It works. Is that enough storage? Hey dude, get in here and do that. Where's he going? What are you doing? Build these?
Why is he not building that build this? What are you doing? No door. This is door right here. Why won't he do it?
Um, why won't he come in and build this requires toilet cubicle? Yeah, i'm trying to build it
All right. So now I need a cashier. I need a cook fast food restaurant. Okay, this is gonna be called call this place
um
I don't care. What about the money? All right. I'm doing all right hire cook. Who's a good cook the govna
Janitor cook no way. Okay, blombo is the best cook but look at this speed
You're gonna be standing in one place. Okay hire cashier, right?
Okay, we have a store clerk here stock clerk or in business
Why won't they do the bathroom? This is like kind of weird
How come nobody's coming in to do the bathroom? Oh, I need to I need to please sit down
Oh, um, that's okay. You can go behind the counter
Finally you came in and did it. All right. Yes
Good, it's done looking good. Okay, people are hungry
Oh, I need another clerk. Whoa
Everybody move don't do anything. All right, no more. I don't want to buy i'm not gonna buy anything else
I need to just make money. Just let it make money because i'm i'm burning money fast
9,300 bucks in debt. Okay
So such demands for the fast food restaurant, you mean no one I mean literally no fucking person is coming in here to eat
Two people an hour. I gotta get that movie theater built
69 percent
Okay, I made 600 bucks. Thank god. Why am I always a day late with everything? No market research
Well, yeah, I I it takes a lot of time and a lot of money
I need to research marketing before I can market demand is huge. I need that fucking movie theater
Why did I build a I knew I shouldn't have built a fast food restaurant
Too many office workers
movie theater
Bar was a mistake
That was the biggest mistake. I mean i've only i've made 220 from the bar
That's so bad
How much money have I made from here? I've already made 20 bucks in one day. No one's even going here
Read this you're making this what you are you are making is a promenade not a mall
Malls are interconnected. How do you not know this you boomer?
Well, I didn't have the money to make a giant mall
Oh, so what it's a promenade
This isn't this is a mall
Okay, we're doing we're all right got it movie theater ready us to take out another loan
I'm still making money. So i'm all right
All right, it's time to fire a bunch of people
Yep, it's time to fire three people from the office fire them. I have to
Okay, who's the least efficient person?
Okay office work. You're pretty good office work. You're good. You you're okay
Goodbye
Sorry
Office work. You're okay office work. You're okay office work. Not so good office work. You're good office work. You're good officer
Well, it's who is it? It's you
Sorry
one more
Office work, you're good
Office work, you're good. You're okay
You okay, we freed up some capital a month. Let's work on something. Let's work on
Like electronics or something. That's fine
Where are the rats? There's no janitor
Okay 500 bucks. I just freed up probably like 150 200 a day fire them right before the holidays
um, oh
Shit, I did money's saved families destroyed. I gotta get that movie theater. I didn't even know what day it was
I don't know what day it was. All right. Can we get somebody to take care of the rats? I need a um,
I need a janitor to take care. This is like getting to be green
How do I I can't hire a janitor here?
Stop looking at your phone. This is like it's green like gas in here
I'm making people sick
Thank you
Why am I minus a thousand dollars dude?
What just costs so much money people are actually here people are using the bar
All right, we just have to sit here for a minute
Just a few minutes. How much is the movie theater you think stop doing big projects?
Well, the idea is eventually i'll have
Oh fresh meat
Fresh meat fast food's back on the menu. I got fresh meat
Close it if you don't have staff
Bar, I mean people people are doing it. All right, where is it? It's called gotchas
starting
Okay, it's gonna we're gonna open it at
At 15 we're gonna close
at fucking 5 a.m
6 a.m
I can't do that. All right. There you go
Now we have like an actual bar here right there. All right, you open at 17. We close at 23. Why why hold on a minute?
The it's only open for six hours, but somebody is here for 12. Why why are you here for this long? Wait, what?
Wait, it's only six hours
Holy shit, dude. Have I been overpaying everybody here? Oh my god
Yeah, I have
Uh, that's a lot of money. That's for that. We're gonna make more money than I've ever made in one day
Still not enough. That's enough for a movie theater. I think what if it's an outdoor movie theater
Don't expand. No, don't don't don't don't don't don't don't okay. All right fine fine fine
Oh sick, we're still open
Still making money
Oh pretty cool
Pretty cool. The rats are back. All right. First of all, just delete this people are actually people are using it though profits
Eh, let's get rid of it. Okay. How are we doing? Something needs to be up here movie theater is gonna go up this way
Like here, right? It's a promenade. Whatever pay off the debt. Yeah
Yeah
Get rid of it pay it off bingo no debt. We're good and I got eleven thousand dollars. Let's just let it ride
Just i'm gonna sit here. Let it ride. Let's make money wait fresh bread demand serious. Oh my god fresh fucking bread demand
Bingo right here check this out fresh bread a big deal going on at the grocery store today fresh bread
Might as well just put rats on the menu have people work a night shift. Look at you. You're right. Okay manage essentials
Uh, we need a stock clerk you I need another stock clerk
Overnight your job is to start work you start here and you end start at 18
9 you start at 20 and you end when we open 13 hours shift
So start at 19 end at 5 10 hours start at 20
End at 4 that's better. Come on and stock that shit. Are you not working? Where'd you go fresh bread?
Come on fresh bread get it out there before these fucking weirdos come in
How much does this cost six to twelve dollar profit big demand for that bread get it up here. Look at that
Oh, yeah, you're gonna make a lot of money
Bread bread bread bread bread bread. It's a rush for the bread. Come on make money
What's up the demand?
Come on. I didn't make shit today. Oh fresh bread my ass. I made four hundred dollars today
Open a bakery
No, I don't have I don't have a bakery restaurants one restaurants two. Okay. Wait coffee shop. Where's a bakery big data?
Security logistics cleaning bowling fitness. I feel like that's up here the restaurants two fine dining locks coffee shops
Do I have access to it? It's security you're getting robbed. How do you know that because we watched it happen over and over wait
Okay
Where do you see where do you how can you tell is there a way I can see how much shoplifting there's been
It's been happening for hours
What are you talking about net profit peak daily unsatisfied theft?
Holy shit
There's been 55
Thefts about the last two
Okay, the last five days. I've been robbed like fucking 200 times
People are running in and just grabbing handfuls of bread and running out of the store
Yeah, I lose I lose like probably five to a hundred to a thousand dollars a day in profit in theft
So I need security where's those things that when you walk by they go
Oh fuck, okay security
We don't have any cameras
No security in any store. I can't even tell you know, let's follow some people and see if they even go to the checkout
Let's see. I want to watch somebody pull in
Hey you
You're in chat. You just stole something out of the trash
Like I took something out of the trash. He's going home now
Is that stealing or is this person just gross?
Uh, okay. I think that person just went in and grabbed something and left
Oh my chest
People really have been just walking in and taking things for the last five hours
You wonder why I haven't been able to build anything and make any real money
It's because like 30 of all my margins are destroyed by builders walking out
Why do I have so many cashiers? I think there was huge demand you missed it
All right
Let's let this run out for a second and then I need to make a movie theater
You haven't fixed the person at the bar working when it's closed
What?
What do you mean? Oh shit. All right, that's better gift planning. All right, we're good. They just live here now
Oh, you come out here with a couple of buddies and have a couple of roos
They're not stealing this right now. You have to pay up front. What are you doing here? Oh, this is the overnight
Uh stock person who kind of only needed you for one day
Oh my god
Okay guys
You can just open these doors and just grab a jug of milk and leave I need to
Oh, you have to only be able to come in from one place. You don't even need to step in the store. You can just
Reach in and grab something and before even putting your body into this store, you can leave
Do not know that I didn't know I I kind of didn't I didn't know you could do that
I thought the security was like people fighting. I don't know. I thought like every time the security in a video game. It's usually
Just like a security guard stands here. And if there's a fight they break it up in every sim game ever played
Hey, how's that? Did you steal that? Did you steal that? Did you steal that?
Did you steal that you stole that you just grabbed it off the table and walked out you stole that
You stole that I can't believe it. I can't believe this much isn't going by. Okay. Wait, wait, wait. He has something
He has something too
Why is it just free food at Jeremy's? This is ridiculous
He had a bag of groceries
I don't even think these doors are locked. Can people just come in?
This is why you need a two-entrance mall and not a promenade
Oh, I can't I still can't believe
It's just people walking out with shit like more than 50 plus times a day 20 at least 20 to 30 times a day
You you know what? Go home. You're wasting money. Hey, hey, that doesn't mean you can take things
Ah, I got I can't laugh that hard right now. That's very that's very funny that this has been going on the whole time
Oh, well, is there a way I can see how many times a specific thing has been stolen from that would be so funny
Like if I could look at that and see how many times somebody took out of it, dude, you're so charitable. Thank you
Are you treating your employees ethically?
Well, um, I bet you half of them have been walking out with free groceries every day. So sure I guess
There's no metal detector here. There's no cameras take only what you need
That's a guy that doesn't work. You know what happens to the halloween
Bowl that says honesty one, please
That whole bowl is gone and i'm not just talking about the candy inside
I'm talking about the bowl too is gone within five minutes of it being out there
And then and then that sign that says honesty take one
Is covered in some kind of shaving cream that policy doesn't work. The sign is gone, too
Yeah, oh the signs kicked over and there's like five or six distinct foot like shoe prints all over it
He knows because he was the one that did it
No, I never did that. I never did that. I didn't even take candy out of that bowl, you know
You could do
Some people did this I remember in my neighborhood. There was somebody that was like just dressed up as like a scarecrow
You know
They had like a scarecrow outfit and a costume and they were just sitting in a lawn chair in the front lawn
It's like wait, is that a real person?
I don't know and then you come up to the door and they go like
All right kids happy halloween right they're pretending to be a like a monster just sitting there
Are they a statue or are they are they alive or is it a stuffed person?
I have the honesty ball there and
When people come up and you see then they you know
You're dressed up as like the scarecrow guy or like in a monster costume sitting there
When they come up and they grab more than one
You can get up and be like you took more than one candy put it back and they'll be like, oh, so i'm sorry. Mr
Anderson
That's right
That's how we learn
You little shit no, no, no, no, you can't do that old man arrested
There's only one box in here
Go clean that up. No pick up the trash. Don't just spray the trash
You can't just walk in here and spray trash with febreeze and think that's gonna solve the problem
You gotta do you have to deal with the solution to the solution to the problem not mask the problem
Just leave a trail of candy get full-size candy bars and like put them in like a line on the ground in a gigantic
Like big line that goes around
You know all the front yard and then it leads up to the guy that's sitting in the chair
He's a trap
Ah, I see you've completed the challenge of taking all the candy in the line
Now put it back exactly how it was
Did you do chubby bunny? I did it's fucking hilarious. I'm glad there's no debt. All right fast food delicious
Office workers are doing okay. How what's our demand look like? Hopefully it's movies
Uh theft has gone up theft is going up. It's in a high
Upward trend I wouldn't be surprised people were just going into the store room get security. I have to research security
It's not done yet
I'm making a movie theater. I'm making a movie theater. You can't steal you can't steal from the movie theater
That's my biggest problem. I should have done things you cannot steal from you cannot steal from the movie theater
You have to sit in and actually watch the movie
Sure. Yeah, you could pirate the movie
But if you go to the movie theater, you can't like take the screen
All right. Let's make it
Taking another loan out. I don't even care
smartphones, oh
Finance. All right. I'm taking out a loan. Where's the loan button? Okay
Loan duration
I'm taking up
35,000 dollars. I'll pay this back
movie theater time
In the promenade fuck that's too expensive. All right movie theater. Let's go buy another loan
Otherwise, we wouldn't have to just sit here and wait. I don't want to wait. I want
I want my promenade to look good and be good. All right sign movie theater movie theater. Okay requires access
Sure movie theater. I need a ticket lobby
Buy tickets such as movies
Mandatory from movie theaters. Okay ticket lobby
All right ticket lobby here and then go right is the theater
What do we need? We need let's pause it
need a wall first
door
Uh put a staff door like back here. This is an adult theater. No
We're gonna be playing frozen back to back to back to back. All the kids will show up. Oh, is this a mall?
um movie theater bar fast food restaurant office
uh
grocery store and at knickknacks
And shoe store. This is a mall. None of these are in malls
uh
What do you mean? Yes, they are. I have two different theaters
I need a movie projector and spectator seats spectator seats. Oh, all right. How many of these do I need stadium style?
How many do I need 20 1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10?
Okay, um, we're gonna have two different movies though. Shit. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait
All right, you build some of those i'm blocking the door. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait
Get up here and fix this stay here. I'll pay you extra if you stay with that wall there. And now I need
Uh, we don't need that many seats. Hold on. Delete this for now. Hey there. Okay, three six nine
12 15 18 we need two more now. We need a screen movie projector
10 000 fucking dollars. Oh no order counter get back in here and build that man. Where are you going? Get back in here
Money, I need to can I take another loan out? What's wrong with this? It's obstructed by what give me a break
I have to wait. I can't I can't sell anything. Can I?
Oh my god, I took out so much money to do that and I don't have any money
I have no money. I have to start firing people. I think we're gonna okay. We have to fire everybody in the office
I'm, sorry everybody, but you did good, but everybody has to be fired
This whole thing is gonna get wiped out. I got security research is almost done. Let's research security to the end
And then okay, I got security now. You're all fired. Thank you for working. I appreciate it everybody
But I can't afford I can i'm 52 000 in debt and I only have 6900. I can't pay anybody
I have to fire everybody. I have to i'm sorry everybody. I don't have any money. I I did some bad, uh
bad
Capitalist bad venture capital movements. I opened up a bar and nobody cares and I didn't have enough money to make a movie theater
Um, what are these? What are they? What are they? What are they?
Super mario 2 the things that you throw at mouser those little like weird like the little block mushroom
Look at the things like you pull it and throw it mouser in mario 2. That's what they are
I've been bugging me for like 10 minutes
You have a hundred days
I have to fire at least I have to fire half the workforce here. I'm sorry. I have to
Yeah, these this is like four or five hundred dollars a day
Uh, who has who's the least productive?
that's you
you you're good
sorry gig bean and
Uh, you too. All right. I just freed up some money. What about essentials who's working who's who how much do I have?
Too many cashiers. Do we have too many stock people? There are too many stock people. We just need one. All right stock clerk
you're
worse
You're fired. I'm sorry
We can get we can get rid of one cashier. I think who's the worst cashier we have
That person's in the green that person's staying around for a long time
Yeah, i'm sorry z impulse if you're in the chat. I'm really sorry, but
Yikes, man, like come on. That's not that's not very good
You don't have any stock clerks
I thought I fired one stock clerk
Okay, I freed up some money
Speed it up. Now. I just have to wait till I have ten thousand dollars
That was the guy you just fired
Well, I I don't know. I pranked him just kidding. You're hired with an extra five dollars an hour
And I peel off the mustache. You know, this is undercover boss
It's me your boss
I know that this whole show. I mean I I I gotta question about undercover boss
Um, I feel like if I worked at a place where undercover boss was happening
I would know who that person was
They have like these weird prosthetics all over them and fake mustaches and they they're still the same person talking
You don't know what your boss sounds like. Okay
So if I if I walked in to the stream, right if I sat down here
And I turned the stream on and I had a mustache on a big wig on and like a prosthetic chin
And I was going like this. Hey everybody. I'm new to the channel. It's uh me dave. I'm a new hire
You'd be like that's fucking jeremy. What are you doing? Take that off? I and I know it's you. Oh, yeah
I'm doing the job now. Yeah. Hey, uh, so what do you think about jeremy the boss?
I heard he's kind of a dickhead. What do you think?
I bet you at some point during the film of that the dude's mustache is kind of coming off the right side of his face
Like there wasn't enough glue on the right side and it's like, uh, I could really point that out
But i'm not going to it's just a wet coming down from the mustache
It's just so uncomfortable to have on for more than an hour security two. Oh, I have security now. Wait, how much money?
How am I losing money still? How am I losing money? I just fired like five people fucking theft. I swear god. Damn it security
Auto dispenser. No security system guard. Where was it called office desk auto theft detector?
All right, you ain't walking by you're not gonna get by with me anymore
Good things come to those who wait, that's 40 000. I can finish the movie theater. Okay. What do I put this?
Does it block the entrance?
Okay, good. It works
Catch all those thieves. No one's fucking getting by not anymore
Good luck
You're under arrest
Nobody stole anything. Well, okay. What what happens if they get caught? Okay movie thing. What what just happened to ten thousand dollars
What the fuck was that?
How much are these?
How much are those there a thousand bucks each?
What a ripoff
Projector, okay. I need a ticket lobby. You got one here. I need a cashier and I need a linked business
linked business ticket lobby
movie theater
What does that mean linked business? Is this not open?
I have requires a ticket lobby. That's right here
Buyers a cashier and a linked business
They stole the detector who
What no they didn't
That's stealing the detector
You got to connect the movie theater to linkedin
How do I do this?
Look at that. Look at that sharp decrease
sign
I have to link them together somehow requires a linked business
uh
Everybody get that
Link like in storage. Yeah, but okay, so manage
Ticket lobby, there's no
I can hire a cashier ticket lobby
need to
uh zone ticket lobby
Connected to the restaurant a restaurant
Movie theater. Oh, there we go link lobby
There we are. Okay. We're ready. I don't think we need anything else
Let's start showing that movie. Come on in
Double matinee. There are no screens here
Uh, I need screens. You must place this on a wall. Hold on select
It doesn't say I need anything. I think it just goes on the wall. How much is a ticket for a movie theater?
This is something around
So what you're actually going to see is you're going to get to see thanos's
Right arm and zoomed in background. There are no cashiers. I just hired them. They show up tomorrow
Why is every movie infinity war? Um, because that's every marvel movie. They was the biggest crossover event in history
Fucking spider-man is in that movie
Understand, okay. Wait, wait, wait. Here we go. All right coming in to watch a movie
What movie are you gonna watch?
Here we go
Fill up the theater. Let's do it
Show me a quarter of the movie
Facing the wrong way
This movie's not even on
Okay, why do I feel like this is the depiction of the last ftk stream?
This is how I feel right like this is like, oh look at this elaborate thing. Doesn't this feel like the last ftk stream?
Finally, we have somebody wanted to actually watch the movie. You know, i'm just hitting him in the eyes this hurts
Hey, hey, they're paying for it. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa trash. Excuse me
Let's watch the movie again
Hold on. They're watching it again
This actually will print money. I think well, what's what this person gonna puke?
Uh, I need a janitor in here
Oh, okay, if every
Square pixel is going to have trash on it. I wonder what happens this person puke. What about a concession stand?
Uh this lady these people all had groceries
He went to the grocery store
He filled
bags of groceries
Movie
When the movie was over you dumped the grocery bag onto the ground
Dude dinner in a movie, uh grocery shopping in a movie
The new date taking the world by storm
Okay, actually somebody has to clean this up for real
Uh, I need a I need a janitor. Like I need a janitor
maintenance
Higher janitor. I need one
please
One of the projectors is
Split the theater and stop pretending to be dumb. What are you talking about split? Isn't a split the theater?
oh
Hey, I see what you mean. Okay
No, dude, there you go. Okay, two different movies are going on now. They need to be linked though movie theater 13
And movie this is broken
Now there's a movie showing on the left side. Do I only have enough power in this building to show one movie at a time?
It's linked to the lobby
Linked to this lobby. All right, we're good
Just make it one. I got it. I got it. This this is done. Where's the janitor?
Uh, I just realized something I need another one of these
Add I need a garbage pickup zone
Breathe need 20 seats
In each theater. Oh fuck. That's not good. Okay. Hold on a minute. Hold on. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait
How many are here now? I need 10. Are there any 10? Is there even 10 spots?
All right, that was a good movie. Okay. I have another garbage zone guys guys
They're still paying for it though. It's okay instruction in the middle of the movie. Somebody said
coach coach movie
I can't I can't even uh
It's coach this is what movie theater. It's like anyways burn the theater down. It's worthless. Oh, uh, excuse me
How much money did this thing make today?
um
Yesterday's sit. Let's look at finance. Excuse me. Why can I not make 30 dollars now?
Well, just give it a minute now. I think I got more these bags of trash have been there
So I need another janitor. Look people are buying your detector is gone. It's all right. No one's stealing anymore
So I need to actually I think I need another janitor
The seats are backwards i'm not going to go through the process. They're still watching the movie. It's fine
Okay, I need I need some staff
I need at least one or two more janitors. This is ridiculous
Please no, no, no one's coming to the movies anymore
All right, get back in here and watch the movies
Okay, pretty cool so far. I need a trash can. Yep
Here we go. There it's gonna get cleaned up now
That's better much better much better much better much better. It's currently movies were really in high demand
I hit it pretty well movies are still in high demand yesterday's sales. Look at that. Come on and go to the movies already
What the fuck is this?
there
Clean the seat is a trash can the trash can is a seat either or however you want to do it movies close at six
Oh, that's stupid. How do I um change that?
Take it lobby opens 9 a.m. Who goes to a movie at 9 a.m. Here we go. That's better movies at midnight
Matinee 11 10 that's good. And now the workers have to be doing that too. This is nobody here
What is all this going on? You start here? What is going on down there? That's the sales. All right, let's keep going
I've not all the parking spaces are there but the whole thing with a drugstore. I don't get it
All right movie theater is made dude. Look at that. How does it make any sense? I don't understand how this works. Um,
I've sold like
150 tickets
I made 38 dollars. What's up with that? Hopefully that changes increase the price. I don't think you can
I think it's just automatic. I just realized i've been streaming for five and a half hours
This is in in new new vegas arc. This is longer than I thought I was gonna be here for
How come there's nobody where oh right because it doesn't open till later
All right movies theater is about to open
Nobody's stealing anything movie theater is open in three two one open come on in movies are open
Really come on, what's with the big showing I need a big showing how's it still 38 dollars
60 000 investment and i've made 38 bucks from it. That's nice. It can't even be accurate like the employee hours shows the sales
Okay, we had a big spike
18 somewhere around like 15
I mean that there's nobody wants to see a movie. What the fuck spiked two
Should be the morning overnight. Okay, we're gonna do shift planning. Okay you oh, I didn't even do this
Take a look at that. Now there's infinite overlap. We're gonna open at four and we're gonna close at midnight at 21
Infinite we open at four. We open at six. We close
23 there you go. Now we got a lot of time here fill it up. Imagine seeing a movie at six in the morning
Yeah, I would not who watches movies at 6 a.m
I don't know but they'll it's available if you want to see we got a sale this person by tor
777 in the chat. You're the one that's awake at 6 a.m. Going to the movies. Oh dude. Hold on. Yo
What happened? What what happened? Why'd you leave?
One guy in the whole parking lot. It's an early bird. I should make a diner. Okay, here comes the crowd
Here comes the lunch crowd
Um the okay the profit stuff doesn't make any sense this oh this I had this open for
Almost six hours. We've made way more than three or four thousand dollars here. Oh security too. What can I guard?
What can I do? Let me look at that demand fresh meat. I got it arcade games. I don't have that
What's the research? What was security to self-balancing scooters security guards?
How do I hire a security guard?
I can't make a security guard. I need a security area like a building for them
security center
Just a little one. It's the tiny one just big enough for them to be somewhere like over like here security center
Okay
I need to make door here staff door. This is for security people only. All right. So now what do I do?
manage the security store
hire guard security
You okay pick a patrol for your guard. All right edit patrols
I want you right here here here
here
Uh here here here here here here here here here here and here and here
Okay, there's like a couch. He's one person
Yeah, I know he'll get the job done. I'm like the stream's over in like 10 minutes. Anyways, I don't care
Where are they something's wrong? Wait, what it's definitely this is where all the money is made in here
Just right here. Is that better patrol edit patrol? What's going on with this left click to extend patrol?
Oh
You have to actually draw this shit. Okay, that's good. Let's do it. What does he work?
Why is it why is it such a low battery? Is he working? I just want to see him
Make sure they're doing their job. Yeah, I just wanted to walk around here. No more theft
I'm not gonna get robbed anymore. This game is pretty fun. I kind of really like this. It's really fun
Now imagine if you had all this
Here's the thing though. If you're gonna do sandbox mode give yourself like 50 million dollars
Because it's very expensive and we didn't even get to crash the surface over here
I want to see him and then i'm gonna call it here. I'll call it here. I want I gotta get up
mall fortress
This is definitely made more than 200 bucks that's lagging data. That's like two months behind
There is uh, don't you have a route? Excuse me. Go out go out the door, dude
Go out the door and do your work. You can't cross the parking lot
Why not? Yes, he can fire me from this hellhole. You need to click the route
Oh, okay. Go for it. Do it man. Okay. Go I just gave him like the dog zoomies
That's all I did. Is he catching anybody? Oh, he's on a scooter
Arrest somebody pokemon ai
No, not pokemon ai this guy's doing this
He's just circling in the grass over and over again because he wants to he's shiny hunting all of a sudden
It's just gonna go
He'll be here for like the next six weeks the loan the loan the loan
I have so much time to pay that loan. I'm fine. I have a hundred days to pay it
I think this is pretty cool
Okay, we got a restaurant. We've got a security spot. We've got a bar
There's a movie theater
There's like a shoe store. There's a grocery store fresh bread
booze beer
Hey, what is this place for people to fuck just slack off?
A bar in a theater that no one go to
Well, just wait until it's be like another expansion this way with like another big thing
I'm making money. It's not making a lot of money, but i'm making money
All right. I'm out of here. I'll see you guys tomorrow
Tomorrow we're going to
That's a mystery. I don't know
There are a few I didn't think I was gonna play this for six hours
Yeah, it'll be a mystery stream tomorrow. I'll find something
This week is mystery streams. That's for sure
Next week is horror stuff. We're gonna do vr stuff, too
This is a lot of fun though. I feel the same way about this that I felt about something like city skylines
Do you actually understand design and architecture?
I mean, it's just fun to do
Want to make your own like little storefronts I give this a stamp
Of I think it's good
Recommended a fun little game
But we'll see i'll see you guys tomorrow
Let's do the credits. There was a shitload of community subs earlier from when I you know said the word twitch prime
It was a lot of them
Take a look. Thanks all of you again. Oh, you just said it again
Uh, actually, let me see we had detroit. Thanks for the five subs
Medallion owo. Thanks for five ten community subs from the drum major on twitch. Thanks for the ten subs admiral green
Thanks for five subs right now. I just said it. You're right. This is going by pretty quickly
This is a fast scan. Did we get raided when we did did we I don't see right remember you are stinko
Sometimes oh my god a human. Thanks for the five. I like your name. Thanks for the five subs dude jimmy kimmel raid
Okay
If jimmy kimmel raided the stream that means it'd probably be like
200,000 concurrent viewers and I would have to keep the stream going. No, you know what I probably just leave
That's I am that streams over two hundred thousand people raid. I'd be like guys. I'm leaving
Come tomorrow if you want to hang out. That's toxic. Is it?
I'd be like, thanks so much. Thanks so much. Mr. Kimmel for the raid. Welcome everybody. My name's jerma
I'm a video game guy and I like play games
We do all kinds of crazy quirky stuff here if you like crazy stuff go ahead and follow but i'm done
I'm not screaming. I said I was gonna stream for six hours. I'm not gonna go any further
Thank you. Thank you so much. I'll see you guys tomorrow show up tomorrow. Thanks for the raid raiders
late night voice
Am I getting ha ha'd you're ha haing that come on
Do eight more minutes for six full hours?
nah
Yeah, whatever. It's okay. I don't need to do that
Finished it exactly six hours. We'll get pretty close. Let's see. Thanks for all the subs though guys
They were like a couple hundred today
Thanks finished at five fifty nine fifty nine
Uh, I don't you know, it's really hard to do that because when I hit end stream
I think it actually takes a few seconds for it to actually turn the stream off
Oh, by the way, uh, also something uh that I forgot and I didn't really know
um
This is dead serious
I mean this with all of my heart
This is not me making something up
the ow thing
When the janitor walks over and bumps into the thing and you guys say ow I thought
For the last two straight years
That you were talking about like oh he bumped into me. He bumped into my face
I didn't know there was a loud sound on it. I did not know that until three days ago
I thought it was because here he comes. He oh he bumped you
I did not know there was even a sound effect on it. That's not why
I was doing it because of the bump not the sound but wait, is is there a sound?
How come I don't hear the sound when he does it? I'm curious
How come there was no sound there? There's no sound there
It was how come I didn't hear it there is sound it's like a wet slap
All right. I'll see you guys tomorrow. Thanks for watching as always
See you guys soon starting probably around the same time probably around one o'clock pacific. Have a great rest of your night
Take care guys. See you soon. Can I get it? Can I get it? Can I get it? Can I get five five five five?
I'm gonna try i'm gonna go for it. Here we go. What do you think two three seconds early close five five five five five
Come on i'm gonna I should probably do like one or two seconds early
Go around like five five five five three or five five five five four. I'm gonna do it on five five five five four
Here we go. See you later. We're gonna do it at five five five five four. See you tomorrow guys