Hello! Hi! What up? How's everybody doing? Give back the lipstick. Oh, well, it's right here.
It'll be returned in a timely prompt manner when I'm finished with it. That makes it sound like I'm
wearing it now, but I'm not. But welcome back, huh? Another day. Today, we're gonna do something called
A.I. Dungeon 2. I currently am. There was a lot of debate on how to get this to actually run.
It was, oh, just use the website. Oh, don't use the website. Maybe do this, run it locally. I found
the best way. Live from Las Vegas, Nevada. It's the Jerma Show. No, there wasn't. Yes, there was.
There was like, there was like two people that were in a huge fight. They were saying, guys,
just let him run the beta client. And then like somebody popped in and was like, dude,
he needs to run the collab client. And I don't, I don't, I'm not sure if those people are still here,
but they were screaming. That was me. No, I gotta run him. It's ready to go. I actually have a game
going right now. I have been told a few things about this. This apparently is not the most stable
program on earth because it's a very, it's in beta. It's running through a client. It's running
through another client. So this is, there's, this is probably going to crash a few times,
but I should be able to come right back. Oh, I got like something, what's on my throat today?
I've messed with it for a while. It crashes a lot. Yeah. So expect it to be
not perfect, but we're going to get what we can out of it. If you don't know what A.I. Dungeon is,
uh, it is essentially Talk to Transformer, but what I've been told much more elaborate
and focused than that. You roll a dungeon and you have to play through the dungeon.
It being not that stable is an understatement. It's incredibly unstable. What's going on? Like
what happened here? Did I drink eggs? What's wrong with my voice? I feel like I swallowed
two or three raw eggs. Hold on. Whatever. It's going to be fine. I'm going to be doing like
voices anyways. So, uh, let's do the first one. Let's get started. It's already ready to go.
Here it is. So we get, I didn't do a random story. I figured we would do,
start off easy, right? Here comes the porn. Uh, would mean porn. Uh, I'm going to give this,
hold on just a second. This is a porn game. It's not a porn game.
Anyways, we're going to do fantasy because that's the one that's recommended is fantasy, mystery,
apocalyptic zombies, or a custom story. It's not porn game. It's, I'm going to avoid all the pornographic
scenarios. Okay. Let's do fantasy. We're going to start with fantasy. That's the easy one.
Pick a character in fantasy, a noble, a knight, a wizard, a peasant, or a rogue. I'm going to be a
noble. I want to be a noble. I think that would be, that is a good start. Noble. What is your name?
What is my name? Well, they call me many things in this town. Sire, Lord, Larry, Lord Larry,
Lord, Lord Leonard, Lord. I'm a noble. I'm Larry. Lord, Lord, Lord Lance. No, Lord
Leo, Lord Leo. Oh, uh, what is your, oh, these are instructions. Okay. All right. Right. Right.
Right. So now I got these things. What I'm going to do now is I'm okay. I'm going to zoom in a
little bit here so we can do this together. Cause I don't want, I don't want to be any spoilers.
Okay. Here we go. You are Lord Leo, a noble from the land of Brothian. You have a pendant
and a house seal. One morning you are awakened by one of your laborers. She tells you that your
state is being surrounded. You look out the window and see a group of men dressed in black,
standing on top of the hill. They are armed with crossbows and wearing leather armor.
The woman who woke you also says they are very well dressed.
Well, this music doesn't make any sense now. All right, here we go. This really this quickly.
What do you do? Uh, okay. I closed the blinds. The man who wakes you looks at you and then turns
his attention to the window. He closes it, but not before you can see him turn around and say,
I'm sorry about this. He walks over to you and puts his hand on your shoulder.
I'm sorry about this. We must protect this house.
Lord Leo, I will protect my home. He says, yes, yes, I know you, you reply, but we need to get
inside. He nods and begins walking towards the door.
No, not your house, my house. He begins walking towards the door. I reply,
no, I mean my house must be protected, right? Like, well, what's that's what gods do, you know?
All right, hold on. Look outside. Are they still there? You watch as the man continues to walk
towards the door. Suddenly, he stops and turns around. He points to the house and speaks in an
odd language. It sounds like some sort of ancient tongue, but you don't understand a word. The man
starts walking back towards the house. Wait, is he signaling to people? All right, that sounds like
some sort of ancient tongue. Close and lock the door before he gets in. He's part of the resistance.
You close the door and lock it with a key. Then you stand up and start pacing around the room.
Finally, you sit down on the bed and begin thinking. Call mom. She'll know what to do.
You call out to your mother, but she doesn't answer. She must be busy. You think about calling
her again. When you're alone, you continue to wait for her to return. Okay, I gotta arm myself
a sword. You grab a sword off the table and put it into its scabbard. You also grab a dagger from
the draw and put it into its scabbard. You take a small leather pouch from your pocket and put some
coins in it. You open the door and enter the room. Leave the house. You exit the house and
head back to the inn. When you arrive, you find that the innkeeper has already left.
You wonder if you should follow him or go back to the house. Follow the innkeeper.
You follow the innkeeper back to the house. Wait, he's going back to my house? Eventually,
you reach it. You knock on the door, but no one answers. You try the front door, but there is
nobody there either. You decide to check the back door, but it is locked too. Did I lock myself out
of my house? I think I locked myself out of my house. Okay, break in the house. You rush through
the back door and run straight to the bedroom. You quickly grab a nearby knife and stab the wall
several times until you hear something fall on the floor. You peek through the peephole and see a
woman dressed in black standing behind you. What? How do you look through a peephole and see somebody
behind you? That doesn't make any sense. Oh, from dressed in black. It's the people that were coming
to get me. Turn around, ask the woman why she is here. She smiles and tells you,
my name is Lilith and I'm here to help you. How are you going to help me? She replies,
by helping me kill you. Oh, that's a pretty good, that's a pretty good one-liner.
By helping me kill you. Don't kill me. I can pay. See, like, whatever it is, I'll double.
Don't kill me. I can pay. She laughs and says, no, you won't, but you might still be able to save
your own life. I won't pay. Run out of the house. You run out of the house and down the stairs.
You don't stop running until you are far away from the area. This is Minecraft? Call mom.
You call out to your mother, but she does not answer. You think about calling for her again
later when you're alone. You continue to wait for her to return. Wait for mom to return. You wait
patiently for mom to come back. Eventually, she returns. She seems upset. You think about how she
would feel if you had killed her son. You hope she doesn't hate you for it. Is that about me?
She's talking about me. Oh, wait a minute. Wait a minute. Do I have a brother? Greet her with open
arms. You greet her warmly. Mom smiles and hugs you tightly. You tell her everything. Mom tells
you that she is glad you came back because she was worried about you. She asks you if you would want
to stay with her tonight. You say yes and she kisses you goodbye. Okay, dig down five blocks.
You dig down five blocks and find a house. Inside the house, you find a young girl. She looks very
frightened and confused. You tell her that you are her father and uncle and that you've been looking
for her all day. What? Keep digging down and keep digging down until you find, keep digging down
until you find obsidian. You keep digging down and eventually you find a large stone block.
You pick it up and place it on the ground. You then shout, this is where you were buried.
The girl runs forward and grabs the stone. She stares at it in awe. Ask for the stone. You ask
the girl, where did you bury the other boy? She looks at you and says his body fell down into the
river and washed up here. His name is Harry and he drowned in the river last year.
Run full speed into cave wall. You sprint into the cave and jump onto the rock face. You throw
yourself at the cave wall and slam your fist against it. You scream in pain and cry out, oh god,
oh god, oh god, oh god. Go to the doctor. Go to the doctor. You run back to the house and tell mom
what happened. She takes you to the doctor who examines you. The doctor says we are going to
have to remove the hand and he pulls out a finger and then pulls out another finger and another.
Finally, he removes your entire hand. This is, that's fucked up. Uh, ask for him to do the
left hand. Ask for him to do the other hand. The doctor comes over and examines your hands. He
tells you that you will need two more fingers removed. He puts his hand on your right hand
and begins to pull out your fingers. You scream in agony and beg him to stop. Finally, he finishes
removing them. The doctor says I am going to have to remove all your toes too.
He removes your feet as well. You scream in horror and yell at him to stop.
Finally, he stops and looks at you. I'm sorry. I have the wrong chart. Uh oh, it's thinking.
It's thinking. It's thinking. It's really thinking. Uh oh. I'm sorry. I have another patient
chart. Am I dead? I'm sorry. Rewind. Revert's the last action. Okay, it's the last revert.
You have to reload the cell. Shit. Damn it. New story. I died. I'm dead. Uh, he removed my hands
and feet with no, um, no, no, no volcano anesthesia and I just died. And he told me,
I'm sorry. I have the wrong chart. That's it. That's where I'm dead. All right. I gotta reload
the cell. Fatal error. Wait a minute. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I think, okay, no, hold on. Yeah, it's fucked up. Oh, I can load the game. I can load this game.
Wait, wait, wait. I can use the same ID. Can I? No, let me try to load this. Yeah, it's the load.
It might crash it. Oh, so don't, don't, do not load games. Try not using dialogue in the game.
Type stuff like, you tell your mother to take you to the doctor. Should I not use quotes? Like,
should I? Don't put thing in quotes. Just say, like, the doctor says this. The doctor says you
have, so, so use quotes. Okay. All right. It's booting back up. Why didn't I read the instructions?
I, I did. Quotes are fine, but start with this person says, okay. I've read the instruction.
When you want other people to talk, do not use quotes. Okay. It's coming back. Don't use the
word ask. It breaks a lot of these. Okay. Do whatever. The AI will figure it out.
All right. It's coming. It's coming. It's loading. This may take a few minutes.
Well, we knew this was going to happen. Can you guys even see it? Ask it for now, but let's
start a new one. Let's start a new one. I guess the first time I did it. All right. It should
start in a second here. This is funny though. Make my own Nancy Drew story. All right. That
sounds good. I'm going to do mystery and I'm going to, I'm going to be Nancy Drew. Do a completely
random one. We will. I want to do a Drew crew first. I need some mystery music. One in the chat
for the Drew crew. Yeah. All right. Here we go. Mystery. I need like a good one. Okay. New game,
zero random story. No mystery. Let's do mystery. Pick a character detective. I want to be a
detective. What is your name? My name is Nancy Drew. Yeah. Interaction starting with a verb.
Go to the tavern or attack the orc to speak. Enter, say the thing you want to say or just
the thing you want to say, right? Yeah, that's correct. All right. Here we go.
No, it's going to be Nancy Drew soundtrack. Nancy Drew music. I mean, it has to be like a
relaxing and peaceful Nancy Drew music. You guys didn't think you were going to get it two
times in a row. I picked a spy. Oh shit. Whatever. You are Nancy Drew, a spy living in Chicago.
You have a concealed pistol and a syringe of poison. You listen to the Russian diplomats
and hear them discussing how they can get rid of you. If we could kill you with a car bomb,
one says, oh, we could blow up your hotel room. Where are we? Where are we?
Oh, that was a great Russian accent. I look around the room. You turn on the light switch
and see that there is no way anyone would be able to enter the room without being seen.
The door is locked from the inside. Okay. Call mom. You call your mom's cell phone number and
wait for her to pick up. When she does, you tell her what happened. She tells you to go back to
sleep. The next day you call again. This time you speak more clearly. Say, I am in trouble.
Right? That's what they want you to do. Like say, and then quotes, right? I am in trouble.
Mom, mom hangs up on you. You feel like crying. It isn't fair. Why can't you just understand?
Remove pistol and aim at what was, would they have names? Remove pistol? No, no, no.
Remove pistol from shirt. Remove pistol from shirt. Where is it hidden? Remove pistol from shirt.
You take off your shirt and put it over your head. Then you place the gun
under your pillow. A few hours later, you hear a knock at the door. You open it. A man with a
bushy mustache stands before you. He looks like he has been drinking. Say, please come in. Please
come in. He didn't say anything. You keep breaking it by doing quotes? I, doesn't it say up here?
Say the thing you want to say with quotes. Wait, he said, please come in. Tell him to come in.
Come in. So come in. If I, is it a mirror? I close the door or she, she closes the door, right?
Shoot. Mirror. I think it's fucked. It shattered beautifully. Just wait. Oh, I think it might be
dead again. The game tell, hold on. What? The game tells you quotes are okay, but they are not. They
make the AI much more prone to crashing. Just don't ever use quotes ever again. True. Correct. Yes.
So I'm just not going to use quotes anymore. I'm just going to just tell the game what
people already said. Okay. Should we wait this out? Don't use them. I just won't use them at all.
It's broken. Fuck. Use parentheses? Let's try it again. Redo it. No, don't use parentheses.
Don't use brackets. I'm just not going to use quotes anymore. If you use quotes and it really,
it's prone to just dumping out, then I don't even want to use them. Start with a verb every time.
Okay. Pick detective this time. Make a custom story. Well, I want to get one to work to completion
first. Instead of getting my hands and feet cut off and then the thing crashing. The AI says you
can use words, but it actually makes it more prone to crashing. Just use emojis. You can say things
like say, and then the, yeah, that's what I was doing. I was doing say space quotation something,
quotation, end. It screwed it up. Dermawalk, the crew wants more Drew. Not going to happen.
Not right now. All right. We're almost ready. Set the next story in Super Frogland. I'm out.
Drew crew. The original, I'm using the collab one. That's the one I'm using right now. That is the
current one I'm using. All right. Let's go. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go.
Let's go. Let's go. Yeah. All right. We're going to get it. Third time's the charm. No more quotes.
New game. Not a random story. Mystery. Detective. Drew. Let's go. Here it comes. The first one we
got at least far enough where I died. Here we go. You are Drew, the detective living in Chicago.
You have a pistol and a police badge. You enter the forest where you believe the criminal you're
searching for fled to. Suddenly, you hear a gunshot behind you. Look behind. Look behind you or look
behind me. Am I dead? Did I just get shot from behind? Look behind me. What is it? You turn
around and see that you've shot yourself in the head. What the fuck are you talking about?
Am I still alive? Am I dead? No, you're alive. The bullet was lodged in your brain,
but it didn't kill you yet. You can still move your body. Go to the hospital. You run back
and find out that you're not dead yet. A doctor comes and examines you. He says he's going to
have to operate on you right away. He says you might never walk again. The doctor removes
both feet. It's the same doctor. Is it going to break it? The doctor. Do the operation. Okay.
Do the operation. Nice detective story. Do the operation. This won't break it.
The doctor isn't a verb. Okay. Do the operation. See what happens. You agree to do the surgery
immediately. You feel so much better after the operation. Your body is stronger than ever before.
You even managed to get a job as a detective again. A year passes. Go to the forest. That's
where I was supposed to go. Go to the forest. I was trying to find a criminal. You decide to
go to the forest where you first met your mother. She told you about how she used to hide from the
monsters there. You wonder if you should try to find her again or just forget all about it.
Hide from the monsters. Is that going to break it? Call mom. Yeah, that's a good idea. Call mom.
You call your mother's number one more time. It rings, but no answer. You wait for a while,
then finally give up. You realize that you won't be able to talk to your mother anymore anyway.
You don't know what will become of you now. Track criminal. Track a criminal.
Track a criminal. Call dad. Track a criminal. You decide to search for the criminal who killed
your mother. You follow his trail and eventually catch him. He tells you that he knows who you
are because he saw you in the newspaper. That's why she wouldn't answer the phone. Torture? Oh,
electrocute. What the fuck? Electrocute the criminal. With how? The criminal doesn't
seem surprised by this suggestion. He electrocutes you instead. You scream in pain and fall unconscious.
You wake up in a strange room with a man holding a gun to your head. Does that work? Is that going
to break it? You say that he should shoot himself. Don't type you. Say, so say you say,
say he should shoot himself. Tell, say in quotes, shoot yourself. Tell him to shoot himself.
No quotes. Tell him to shoot himself. That's more right. Tell him to shoot himself.
Yes. Yes. Yes. Yes. Okay. You refuse to tell the man to shoot himself. Instead, you say,
I'm sorry and thank you. The man shoots himself. You're free now. It worked. Leave, leave the room.
Leave, just how about leave area, leave room. Take, take his wallet. Take his wallet. You take
the man's wallet. Inside is some money and a photograph of your mother. You remember that
you'll need those things later. Shoot the photograph. You shoot the photograph at the wall.
You hear a loud noise and the picture falls off the wall. You look down and see that you're wearing
a blue suit. You also notice that you're no longer bald. You're a blue. No, I'm a detective. Go.
All right. That case is closed. Go to the police station. Right. Let's, let's go get some,
I've got to get a new case. Or go to my office. Go to my office. Go to my office. You go to your
office. There's a door there which you open. In front of you is a desk covered with papers.
On top of the desk sits a woman dressed in black. She looks at you and smiles. She calls you by
name and introduces herself as Dawn. Dawn. Tell her to get off the desk. Get off the desk.
Like get off my desk. You tell Dawn to get off the desk. She does so, but then asks why you're here.
You explain to her that you want to thank her for saving your life when you were little. She
says that she understands completely. I'm in my office. Okay. So, uh, call Dawn's mom. You call
Dawn's mom's phone. Dawn answers. You ask her if she remembers you. She says yes, but she's not
sure why you'd want to thank her. You explain that you're glad you found her. Dawn says that she's
happy too. So, all right. Go to McDonald's. Does that exist in this universe? Go to McDonald's.
Or no, let's go to Burger King. I mean, I've had a long day. Go to Burger King. You go to Burger
King. You order a burger and fries. They come out quickly. You eat them happily. You return to your
office. Dawn comes in and asks if everything went well. You tell her that it did. Dawn thanks you
and leaves. You think about what happened today. That's it. I just went, I just enjoyed Burger King
and came back to the office. Mission accomplished.
She did.
Arrest Dawn. You call Dawn's cell phone and see that she called Dawn's mom. You call Dawn's mom's
phone and see what that she answered. You tell Dawn that she needs to come over right away.
Dawn arrives at the house. You tell Dawn that you're arresting her. You call Dawn's cell phone and
see that she called Dawn's mom. You call Dawn's mom's phone and see that she answered. You tell
Dawn that she needs to come over right away. You tell her that you're arresting her. This is an
SAT question. Yeah, this is. Complete the SAT question. You complete the SAT question.
What is the first letter of each word in the following sentence? My daughter is having trouble
sleeping. Answer A. You finish the question and hand it to Dawn. She reads it. What is she gonna
teach her? She reads it out loud. You ask Dawn if you got a good grade. You ask Dawn, you ask Dawn
if you got a good grade. Ask Dawn if you got a good grade. Okay, that works right? You ask Dawn
if she got a good grade. She says yes. You ask her if she wants to go to prom with you. She says
yes. You say congratulations and hang up. You're very proud of her. Go to prom with Dawn. You go
to prom with Dawn. You both dance together. You both kiss each other. You both cry. You both go
back to your apartment. You celebrate your newfound happiness. You're under arrest. You call Dawn's
cell phone. Dawn answers. You ask her if she remembers you. She says yes, but she's not sure
why you'd want to thank her. You explain that you're glad you found her. Dawn says that she's happy
too. Put handcuffs on Dawn. You put handcuffs on Dawn. You leave Dawn handcuffed to a chair.
You go to your car and drive to the police station. You arrive at the station and find that Dawn has
been arrested. You call her cell phone. I forgot to bring her with me. Dawn answers. She answers.
Break cell phone. Break Dawn's cell phone. You break Dawn's cell phone. You find that she's
been arrested. You call her cell phone. She answers. Break her. Get rid of her cell phone.
Burn Dawn's cell phone. How many does she have? You burn Dawn's cell phone. You drive to the
police station. You park outside the building. You enter the building and find that Dawn has
been arrested. You call her cell phone. Dawn answers. Ask where Dawn is getting her cell phones.
You ask Dawn where Dawn is getting her cell phones. She says that she doesn't know. You
say that you can find out yourself. You say that you'll never forgive her. You laugh. You say,
What do I say? You say you are under arrest. You say you are under arrest. Will quotes work now?
You say enjoy 30 years in prison. Don't do quotes. Don't use quotes. Just say enjoy 30 years in prison.
You enjoy 30 years in prison. Wait, what?
You go to my car. You go to your car. You unlock your doors and drive off into the night. You drive
home. You arrive home. You find that Dawn is gone. You call her cell phone. Dawn answers. She answers.
Hello? She answers hello. She answers. End the time loop. She killed Dawn. You called her cell
phone. She answers and says kill Dawn. She answers just quotes. Dawn must die and hang up. You start
crying. You realize that you've made a terrible mistake. You don't know how long you'll be able
to live without her around anymore. You go to sleep. Wake up. You wake up. You're in a hospital bed.
A nurse stands before you. She tells you that you're going to die soon. You're told that you
have cancer. You're given a what the fuck? You're given a few options. You could choose to die from
this or you could choose to live. Choose to live. You decide to live. You chose to live. You choose
to live. You choose to live. You choose to live. You choose to live. You choose to live. You choose
to live. You choose to live. You choose to live. I lived. You lived. You lived. You lived. You lived.
You lived. You lived. You lived. You lived. You lived. You lived. You lived. You lived. You lived.
Wake up. Wake up. You wake up. You're in a room. The walls are white. You look around and see
a table with several chairs surrounding a window. A man sits behind the table. He holds a gun to
your head. He speaks to the gnome in the corner. You nod. You smile. You nod. You smile. You nod.
You nod. You nod. You nod. You nod. You nod. You nod. You nod. You nod. You nod. You nod.
Wake up. You awake. You stand up. You stand. You up. You up. You up. You up. You up. Up up up up up up
up. Call Don's cell phone. You call Don's cell phone. The phone rings. It's Don. You pick. You
pick. Uh you pick. You send pick. Send a picture to Don. You send a picture to Don. You send a picture
of dawn you send a picture i think it's fucked up i think it's messed up wake up wake up wake up
from this nightmare wake up you wake up you get dressed you walk towards the door you open it you
see dawn standing there she looks down at you she smiles she puts her finger to her lips and gives
a wink you smile you rent a movie from blockbuster a bunch of them a bunch of times in a row
go to kill dawn you call dawn's cell phone dawn answers you ask her what's wrong she says nothing
you tell her to come i'm trying to kill you dawn is dead you tell her to come over you tell her to
come over you take dawn to the bathroom you wash her you talk about your day you talk about your
life you talk about your future you talk about your past you talk about your feelings talk about
your dreams talk about your past talk about your friends i don't know drink poison like i'm stuck
oh shit i spelt it wrong you drink poison you drink poison you drink poison eat hot peppers
drink the bath water drink bath water you drink some water i'm stuck jump out of window i need to
wake up you fall through the air you land on the ground what you run into traffic you run into
traffic get hit by bus you get hit by a bus die from injuries you wake up go back to sleep call
dawn cell phone you call dawn cell phone you call dawn cell phone you call dawn cell phone answer
the phone whoops that action caused the model to start looping try a different one i have to restart
i have to restart it i have to restart it i can't die you wake up you go back to sleep you wake up
you go back to sleep you wake up you go back to sleep wake up permanently how do you spell
permanently how do you spell permanently i don't want to use spell check i need to get this
permanent permanently permanently permanently got it game restarted oh jesus you are drew a
detective living in chicago you got a pistol the police badge you enter the forest we believe the
criminal you're searching for you hear a gunshot behind you duck he woke up you turn around and
see a man with a shotgun standing behind you he fires at your chest as you fall backwards
the bullet hits your heart and you die instantly you died game over i finally got out new game
please rate that story quality from one to ten let's say uh that was a that was like a that was
like a that was like a nine that was a nine okay new game random story should i just do a random
story random all right here we go i already see that i'm a knight you are hold on you are serelin
a knight from the country of amato you have a leather saddle and a shield you are beginning
an adventure to destroy the accursed dragon of laria you heard he lives to the south of the
kingdom you set out to a dark cliff that could take you there as you approach you said something
is wrong something is watching you the air grows colder as you get closer to the cliff
suddenly the ground begins to shake and you fall off your horse you can't even see anything anymore
i don't have a weapon block the fall with my shield your shield blocks the fall it feels like
ice around your hand your arm hurts so much it hurts to move as you look at your arm you notice
the blood dripping from it you turn your head back up to see what caused this the dragon has
finally arrived you feel a strange sensation in your mouth you spit out the dragon's corpse
you then feel a burning pain in your stomach you vomit again and then suddenly vomit some more
finally you vomit all over yourself you don't know why but you just keep vomiting until you pass out
i ate the dragon he was a poisonous dragon i'm sorry you eat the vomit the taste is horrible
but it tastes better than anything else you've ever had before when you finish eating the vomit
you feel very sick you lay on the ground and cry for a while eventually you get up and walk away
from the battlefield i i won i killed the dragon go to the tavern you walk towards the tavern you
find that the entire town is dead there are no living people anywhere near the battlefield
you also find that the dragon has been killed you hear the roar of the beast as it falls to
the ground eat the dragon's bones you eat the dragon's bones they're really good you can barely
believe how good they are you feel even better about yourself you go back to the battlefield
where you tell everyone that you ate the dragon's bones everyone is amazed by your story a young
man approaches me a young man approaches you he asks if you want to join him in killing the dragon
you agree but only if he joins you too you both set off together to kill the dragon you travel
far into the wilderness you travel to the mountains and across the plains you eat the young man
is really tasty you feel great afterwards you decide to take him back to his home
you leave the young man behind and continue on your journey you travel further and further
away from civilization until eventually you reach the edge of the world jump off you jump off the
edge of the world you land and break your leg you are left lying on the ground and bleed profusely
you try to stand but you are unable to do so you die soon after what did i land on i'm not dead yet
you die soon after awaken anew awaken anew you wake up you are still alive but you're not sure
how you survive such an accident you are hungry and thirsty you think about the young man who
helped you kill the dragon he was a nice guy you wonder if you should help him or not eat the moon
you eat the moon it tastes terrible but it tastes better than anything else you've ever had before
you eat it and feel great you decide to take him back to his home you leave the young man behind
and continue on your journey go find another dragon don't eat everything you go find another
dragon you travel further and further away from civilization until eventually you reach the edge
of the world then no more dragons you jump off the edge of the world you land hard and break your
leg you're left lying on the ground and bleed profusely you're unable to do so you can't stand
you die new game i i died i beat the dragon story from one to ten that was like a six
random another random story let's go you new song you are dimyan a rogue from the province of
artigo you have a deck of cards and a pair of gloves you go down the city road searching for
someone to steal from you imagine that it would be easy since most people don't put much effort
into their personal security the streets are empty except for a few beggars and thieves
you'll find a small alleyway to sneak in steal from the tavern now sneak into the tavern
sneak into the blacksmith no not into the blacksmith not inside of him sneak into the tavern
you take a deep breath and head towards the tavern you can hear the noise inside you need
to get inside before they notice you you walk through the door and see several men sitting
at tables talking you decide to join them very sneaky play cards you sit down with your friends
and begin playing cards you're not sure what's going on but you're having fun suddenly one of
your friends notices something out of place a man is standing near the table and he looks like he
doesn't belong there ask the man to join you ask the man to join the man sits down next to you
and he asks you if you want him to join you you agree and he joins you he tells you that he's
from the city of neuro and has been living in this town for the past few months ask what he wants
i'd like to buy some land the man says how much would it be say 500 say five million dollars
five million gold coins five million gold coins you reply he is shocked by this number he gives
you five million coins he hands me five million coins you hand over the money and the man takes
his leave what no he hands me he hands me the money you look around and think about how lucky
you are to have found such an amazing place am i on drugs chase the man you run after the man as
fast as you can as soon as you catch up to him you punch him in the face he falls backward and hits
his head on the ground you grab his arm and pull him back up he grabs your wrist and punches you in
the face again drop kick the man drop kick the man in the face you drop kick the man in the face
he screams and drops his weapon you laugh and continue running you reach the edge of the forest
and see a small village it seems so far away now you wonder where you should go first go back to
the man you turn back to the man who is still lying on the ground you tell him to follow you
you quickly make your way back to the man you tell him to stay behind and then rush into the village
you find yourself in front of a large wooden house elbow drop the man from the top of the house
you throw the man off the roof of the house he lands hard on the ground you kick him in the
stomach and he collapses to the ground you stand up and look around there are two doors in front of
you one leads outside and the other leads to a small garden you throw the man down a well
he struggles to climb out and manages to crawl out you throw him down another well and he crawls
out you push him back in and watch as he tries to escape yet again finally you throw him into a
pit full of maggots he is eaten alive he is eaten alive go in the house go in the wooden house
you enter the wooden house inside you find a woman who looks very old she smiles and she sees you
she introduces herself as elena and thanks you for saving her life she explains that she was
born in the same year as you and was raised by her mother good for you tell her to leave to my house
now she refuses to leave and begins to curse you she calls you a liar and a thief she pulls out a
knife and pointed at you you pull out a pistol and shoot her in the chest she falls dead you don't
know why you didn't but you feel horrible about it search the woman you search the woman to find
a letter in her pocket it reads dear friend i'm sorry dear friend i'm sorry for calling you a
liar and a thief but i'm afraid those words fit you perfectly i've seen you steal from me
many times it's in her pocket oh i've seen you steal from me many times and i never caught you
continue reading the letter and i will keep doing everything in my power to prevent you from
ever being able to live in this world again if you wish to change your fate you must do it yourself
go to the nearest forest go to the nearest forest
oh why
go to the nearest forest and kill all the animals then gather their meat and bones and burn them
oh okay god damn it that's so fucking stupid what a sick fuck go to the forest
you go to the nearby forest and start chopping wood you chop wood until you've got enough to
build a fire you light the fire and wait for nightfall you spend the rest of the day cutting
down trees and burning them do i stupid do i not know what an animal is do i think that the animals
are trees i guess i'm gonna go into the forest and kill all the animals these are animals
kill all the animals that's the reason why you kill all the animals oh my god
okay why am i you feast on you find what the fuck this is my quest gather the bones
you gather the bones of the animals and use them to create a potion you drink it and fall
unconscious when you wake up you realize that you've become a powerful wizard you decide to
travel to the capital of the kingdom of neuro and try to conquer it conquer the capital you decide
to conquer the capital of the kingdom of neuro you arrive at the gates and you knock on the gate
a guard opens the gate and you enter you find yourself in a room filled with people dressed
in black robes they stare at you cast lightning strike on the capital you cast lightning bolt at
the capital and it explodes the entire city burns down the people die screaming and running
for their lives you walk through the streets and look at the destruction why did i do that
i was supposed to conquer it not destroy it rebuild the city you rebuild the city
you erect new walls and towers and fortifications you raise a statue of yourself in the corner of
the city you lead a group of soldiers and they fight against the remaining rebels eventually
but eventually they win wait the rebels win you kill the rebels they're slaughtered like sheep
you slaughter them like cattle you take their weapons and armor and sell them to the highest
bidder you enjoy the spoils of war you cast lightning bolt at the capital and it explodes
the entire city burns down the people scream and die screaming and run for their lives you walk
through the streets and look at the destruction you gather the money from the wreckage of the
destroyed city you buy a boat and sail away you set sail and sail towards the coast of neuro
fishing invade neuro wait you go fishing you fish until you get tired and you sink
you swim until you drown you swim until you get hungry and you starve you hunt
until the end you eat grass what you eat grass whore i didn't die i'm not dead
this swim i swim to a nearby shore you cast lightning bolt at the boat and it explodes
the entire boat sinks you drown and you drown you drown you swim until you get exhausted you
starve no i was i thought i was far away i thought no i'm not dead i'm a i'm a wizard you swim to
a nearby shore and sit down you eat some grass horror what is that even from far away stop
stop they're already all right fine inspect uh inspect what is grass whore inspect grass
whore you inspect grass whore you find it delicious you eat it whole you feel great
pleasure from eating it what is grass whore throw grass whore in the ocean oh i i timed out i timed
out yeah i actually actually got disconnected describe the gra i can i gotta reset i gotta
reboot it wait wait i can i can i reconnect hold on can i actually reconnect i think i'm back
am i back it says i'm connected shit no i gotta redo it will i get a uh
damn it yeah i had to reboot it fuck oh well all right hold on i just gotta do it again
custom prompt hold on um i think i have to reboot the whole thing is this gonna fuck me up
it says i'm connected but i'm not um let me see what happens when i
because when i try to hit play it says no such file a directive directory bin python
fuck i might have to reboot the whole thing uh oh do i okay those you that know do i have to
reinstall everything again oh shit do i no no pc no no no okay all right just making sure
it rebooted so this should be installed still it's fucked up hold on i have to disconnect
apparently i'm somehow fuck i think this is actually like totally fucked i'm connected to
and i'm connected to something but i i tried to reconnect well let me manage my session here so
i can get out yeah i'm gonna terminate this session all right now if i reconnect
see if this works all right so now i'm it's fresh hopefully you don't have to reinstall everything
damn it i think i have to reinstall everything
because it says no directory no that was just start the last like two or three were really fun
let me try one more thing uh i'll be right back let me see if i can get this work okay so i
i'm not connected to collab anymore so i'm i'm now on the page and it's like you know i can
connect but i can't if i hit play i don't have any directories so i might actually have to redo
everything reinstall it let's see what happens if i reinstall it let's run this let's run this again
it might just happen instantly let's see what happens i was having fun with this
already be ready let's no i gotta i gotta redownload everything
damn it no this took like this took like 40 minutes yeah that's that's a rip all right we'll
do something else i'm gonna let this download in the background while we do something else
unless let's see how fast this goes through just use the web version instead yes i am i'm on the
collab one right now that's the one i've been using this whole time that is the one i have
been using for the last almost two hours uh should i just do the web version for now
while this one downloads the web version crashes a lot well i'll just while this one downloads
i'll just do that one for now what's what's the actual web version client it's like uh
this is the web version uh this is technically not the web version i think i already have it here
let's see yeah it's this one all right we'll get we'll get it going here we'll do the web
version for now the official version sucks yeah i've been told it's a very very
it's very very unstable but i could do it all right so they're in beta
okay let's try it let's try it now wait a minute is this ready this oh this site is dead
site's dead it's costing them tens of thousands of dollars of months to run the web version oh my
god so it's it's beta dot is it dot netto dot com so much misinformation about the game
all right here we go i'm ready pick a setting custom enter a prompt that describes who you
are in the first couple sentences of where you start out what was what was my name it was
i'm going to start on the on the shore what was the wizard's name i don't even remember
okay here we go so you are a wizard you are all-powerful wizard
laid waste to the capital city of neuro and fled to a nearby island
okay you are planning your next move let's go you are addicted to grasshopper
you are an all-powerful wizard you have laid waste to the capital city of neuro
and fled to a nearby island you are planning your next move i'm going to take my army and conquer
the entire world i will rule it as i always have and when i do you will be left in ruins
the crowd is silent they know what you mean by that because i've already done it turn a member
of the crowd into a chicken all right all right calm down you say what did you want a young man
with long hair and a goatee stands up from his seat he looks at you and raises his hand ask him
what he wants i just wanted to thank you for saving me from the orcs you smile it was nothing
it's not important well then i'll see you around with those words he walks away
you raise your hands the lightning bolt strike the man he screams out in pain he falls to the
ground and begins convulsing you look at the man who has now turned into a chicken now i'm going
to kill you it's just chicken hands i'm going to kill you i didn't say that now i'm going to
kill you like smear grass all over my face it was delayed you walk towards the man and slap him
across the face he lets out a scream and falls backwards he tries to get up but you grab his
neck and throw him back onto the ground after smearing grass or let the man up you stand up
and walk towards the man he grabs your arm and starts pulling you away you pull away and start
running stop stop no you stop and turn around ask why he wants me to stop yeah this is the
chicken man i don't understand because you're trying to kill me no no no no i didn't mean that
yes you did because you're trying to kill me no no no no i didn't mean that yes you did now i'm
going to kill you now please please don't please don't kill me the man kills the person standing
next to them the man turns around and shoots the person standing beside him they fall backwards and
begin convulsing don't you dare kill me you run past the man and continue running is this gonna
work you pick up a rock and throw it at the man it hits him in the chest causing him to yell out in
pain you run forward and hit him again this time he falls backwards and screams out in agony you
grab him by the throat and slam him against the wall i don't have a nuclear bomb spell
you grab his wallet and rip it open you take everything inside and throw it into the river
the man screams and runs after you you run along the shoreline until you reach a bridge
you jump off the bridge and land safely on dry land not you watch watch the man jumps after you
but misses the safe spot he hits his head hard on a rock you look down and see blood coming out of
your nose you quickly put your hand you sit up and slowly look behind you a large rock lies right
where you were standing you can only guess that the man missed the safe spot i had fall damage
the man is dead but his soul continues to haunt me you look down and see a hole in your forehead
you try to wipe the blood from your eyes and then you realize that you are still alive
you stumble back to the bank and collapse on the ground you gasp for air and cough up some blood
you wipe my face well you've never played a classic text adventure before
this is this is an ai dungeon it generates nonsense how can this guy have never played
a classic text adventure before people just can pull out guns and shoot at each other
you wipe my face and go back to staring at the ground you hear someone approaching hey what
happened i fell off a cliff and broke my neck okay look at the bridge you look at the bridge
and notice that there is now a big gap between you and the other side that's weird who would
build a bridge like this maybe they just wanted to get rid of us take down the bridge you climb
down the ladder and start climbing down the bridge as you do so you hear a loud noise you turn around
and see a huge boulder falling towards you you quickly scramble away from the bridge what was
that this is like a hangover dream this whole thing is it just a dream it's just a weird
dream that you might have ask the boulder why it fell you look at the boulder and ask why did it
fall the boulder looks at you with its big stupid eyes and says because i'm dumb you laugh and say
well at least you're not dead ask the boulder to join you look at the boulder and ask would you
like to join me the boulder looks at you and smiles sure you both walk along the bridge together
so how come you didn't tell anyone about this place am i doing my doing this correctly the boulder
says no quotes the boulder says boulder says it is because of war no the boulder says is because
it is too expensive don't speak for other characters oh right the boulder shrugs and
says it was a secret project by an old rich guy who died nobody knows about it except me and you
you smile and nod how much does it cost to join you the boulder sighs and says a lot and the boulder
100 gold coins give the boulder 100 gold coins that's a lot right we lost the music
you give the boulder 100 gold coins and it grins it starts walking faster wow that was easy now
let's go find another way across the river follow the boulder into the forest look at the trees
literally dumber than a rock literally scammed by a rock it's all right it'll be fine you look
at the trees and notice that they all have the same strange pattern they seem to be trying to
tell you something what is this examine the pattern recruit the trees after you inspect the
patterns on the trees and notice that they are all different sizes the smallest one has five leaves
while the largest has 20 this is some sort of code what is it saying it's saying join us
join the trees you join the trees and they become your new home you then continue on your journey
i think we should keep going there must be more trees out here yeah but where are we going to
sleep tonight we'll figure it out go to the past go to the pasture sleep in boulder's arms
you lie down on the boulder's chest and close your eyes you feel safe there okay i think we've got
enough information for now let's get back to work you wake up and head back to work ask the boulder
ask to ride the boulder ask to ride the boulder so we can like roll roll the boulder at roll the
boulder downhill you asked to ride the boulder are you sure you asked to ride the boulder
are you sure we don't have time to do this right now no i think we can make it happen
all right then let's go you grab onto the boulder and start to climb ride the boulder down the hill
you begin to climb down the hill there's no point in stopping let's just go as fast as possible
you reach the bottom of the hill and stop where did we go we went through a tunnel
investigate the tunnel how did he avoid that getting lewd you walk forward and see a large
hole in the ground a small light shines inside the hole that looks like a cave where is it it's
behind us you both enter the cave and it leads to a room with a table and chairs look under the
table eat dinner i'm gonna eat dinner after this look in their fridge you look under the table and
see a bunch of rocks maybe these are gems you pick up a rock and examine it hmm i wonder what
this could be you put the rock back and look around the cave make dinner you sit down and
eat dinner it tastes good so how long was i asleep about an hour and 40 minutes well i guess i slept
well indeed that's not very good at all actually that's pretty awful tell the boulder to do the
dishes slept like a rock slept like a rock you tell the boulder to do the dishes oh thank you
that was so nice of you the boulder smiles at you and goes over to clean up the mess
what's wrong nothing really ask what is wrong passive aggressive boulder
boulder you ask what is wrong i'm not very good at cooking really yes actually then why didn't
you say anything when i asked you to do the dishes because i thought you were being mean
say i am sorry i'm apologizing you say i am sorry thank you that means a lot you leave the boulder
and go back to work a few hours later you hear the sound of a truck outside what is this a truck
hold on hold on tell the boulder to investigate the truck you tell the boulder to investigate
the truck this truck doesn't belong here why not because there's nothing out here for miles
but where would they take a truck like that they wouldn't go in the truck you go into the truck
and find a bag of gold coins wow that's a lot of money yeah but it's not enough to buy me anything
how much is enough oh it's a truck there's no trunk on a truck it's just open
fuck it's open already you open the trunk and find a bunch of jewels these are worth a fortune
where did you get all this stuff my dad gave them to me can you sell me some of this stuff
so the gems to the boulder scammed again no i'm scamming the boulder you sell the gems to the
boulder that will be 10 million dollars thanks i'll give you seven million great let's meet in the
bank tomorrow morning all right fuck it we're gonna free truck drive the truck to the bank
i'm getting seven million out of this you drive the truck to the bank it's going to be ready by
tomorrow morning okay i'll see you then you leave the boulder and head home so it's not open go to
sleep you go to sleep ending a you wake up in your bed good night sleepyhead you drift off to sleep
ending b you awake from your dream go to the bank you wake up in your bed good night sleepyhead you
drift off to sleep you awaken from your dream what the fuck was that ending c oh god damn it
all right let me get let's let's go back to the the other one the other one's gonna be ready to
go here all right i should be able to play now all right the uh the collab one is loading again
actually let me go take a let me go pee i'll be right back and then when we're done
uh from me going pee we will be on the other one that we were using before
bring back the boulder i'm gonna play as the boulder this time all right i'll be right back
okay perfect timing the second i sit down it loads okay a new game not a random story
when we're gonna do a custom story here you should see it i think can you see
not yet wait hold on wait oh there we go it's because i had it changed from last time
here we go are you ready enter a prompt now you guys can't see you are a peaceful boulder
a peace fuel you are a peaceful boulder how is it how is this wrong you are it's busy
why is it peaceful not how's that wrong peaceful peaceful yeah you are a peaceful boulder
you spend your days and nights overlooking a grand pasture no one has ever
set no one you okay um you're overlooking a grand pasture with your wizard friend
okay you are peaceful boulder you spend your days and nights overlooking a grand
pasture with your wizard friend the both of you hope to one day conquer neuro
yeah that's fine let's go peaceful right but i that i'm you can be peaceful
you are a peaceful boulder you spend your days and nights overlooking a grand pasture with
your wizard friend the both of you hope to one day conquer neuro one day the two of you will
be able to live in peace together until then you will continue to enjoy the company of your friends
you roll over on top of the wizard and squeeze his eyes shut he tries to scream but is unable
to do so as he's suffocated by your body i'm sorry i'm sorry please don't kill me wizard you
tell the wizard to get up tell the wizard it's uh crush the wizard's nuts and i'm not doing that
one apologize to the wizard i just rolled over accidentally i just i just woke up it's a new day
you apologize to the wizard for killing him he seems surprised that you would even want to
apologize since he was killed by another wizard no no it's all right it's not your fault he says
and then begins to fade away into nothingness go to the bank you head back to the bank where you
find that the guards are dead the wizards were also killed in the same way well this is a bit
different than what we had planned withdraw withdraw seven million dollars from the atm
withdraw withdraw withdraw seven million dollars from the atm of the atm you walk
up to the atm machine and press the button a few seconds later you hear a loud beeping noise
followed by a high-pitched squeal what the fuck is that the screen lights up with a message saying
insufficient insufficient funds no it's me the wizard it's the wizard i telepathically no no no
no no it's the wizard how do i do this correctly it's the wizard it's me the wizard it's me the
wizard i telepathically downloaded my soul into this atm right it's me the wizard i telepathically
downloaded my soul into this atm your soul now resides inside the atm you look at the screen and
see the words welcome to the soul bank appear it's like my computer only better so he dragged me in
go to the soul bank atm you enter the soul bank's atm and start withdrawing money
you're making good money here oh i can feel the souls of all those who died today flowing through
me you think about how you'll have to pay the fee when you get home talk to the soul bank teller
you approach the soul bank teller who looks at you with suspicion
hello i'd like to withdraw seven million dollars i correct myself and say souls
souls sorry i correct myself and say souls sorry souls i'm sorry withdraw seven million souls
you pull out seven million souls and place them into an envelope you put it in the mailbox and
mail it off you wait until the next day and open the mailbox you see the envelope waiting for you
thank you thank you thank you i can't go to the soul movie theater we're in the soul atm we're
in the soul bank everything's soul now you arrive at the soul movie theater which is located in a
seedy part of town you notice a sign hanging above the door that reads garfield's 3d you
enter the theater and take a seat near the front row you watch the first film garfield is a very
funny character after watching the film you begin to wonder if you should go to the soul bank or
continue watching the films continue watching the films you continue watching the films and soon
realize that you've been missing something you begin to feel a little weird you start to feel
a sense of unease you ask one of the patrons what's wrong he tells you that there's a ghost
in the theater yeah all of us they don't know they don't know that they're dead explain
to the patron that he that we are all dead explain to the patron that he is dead right
explain to the patron that he is dead you explain to the patron that he is dead he doesn't believe
you you try to convince him but he refuses to listen look we're gonna do some beetle juice
type shoot here convince him by passing your hand through his chest like you pass your hand
through his chest and convince him he lets you pass and you leave the theater was he blocking
the way go to the soul hardware store you return to the soul hardware store you walk in and see a
man behind the counter he sees you and smiles ask if he knows he is dead you ask if he knows he is
dead he nods his head in agreement ask when he died ask when did he die he died ask when did he
die you ask when did he die he replies that he died yesterday interesting so did i ask how he
died he replies that he fell down a well say it's the guy from earlier it's that well guy
ask what he has for sale he replies that he has a lot of silver coins for sale ask to see
ask if he has any new lawnmowers you ask if he has any new law any new lawnmowers he replies
that he does have some new lawnmowers but they're not working properly tell him to fix the lawnmowers
how would it be new they don't work you tell him to fix the lawnmowers he says no
uh tell him to fix the lawnmowers now oh revert revert revert revert revert all right we're good
say please fix the lawnmowers or there will be consequences you say please fix the lawnmowers
or there will be consequences he agrees and hands you a key to the nearest house sell him the key
10 million souls you sell him the key for 10 million souls you enter the house and knock on
the door a young woman opens the door she asks what you need you tell her that you were looking
for a soul to help you complete your quest ask her how she died she said that she was electrocuted
i'm just going this is uh this is like everyone needs you scrooge this is christmas past present
and future ask her what is her name she says it's mary give mary one million souls you give mary
one million souls you then give her a note saying that you'll meet her again in heaven
jesus so where are we now where are we now where are we now go to heaven i'm in purgatory you go
to heaven where you find mary sitting in a chair with a book in her lap she looks up as you enter
congrats you won i did it that's a good ending that's like a seven new game we're going random
this time completely random the boulder went to heaven yeah you are rothian a rogue from the kingdom
of nardus you have a cloak and darts today you decided that simple stealing isn't enough anymore
you long for a more ambitious goal taking for yourself lost fleece of alderaan you decide to
go there with your friends and steal it you walk through the forest but not before hearing the
rustling leaves behind you it's just as well you're being watched by two men in hooded robes
they aren't exactly subtle about their actions either what do you want one asks yeah i get ignored
i want to steal no no no no say you want to say i want to steal the lost fleece
of alderaan of aldera al aldera don i want to take myself the fleece of alderaan
alderaan aldera don you say this is this what do you want yes
good good the other man says he raises his hands and suddenly both of them disappear
i also disappear you vanish too a few moments later you reappear at the edge of the woods
you look around then start walking towards the village
you pull out your diaper which is filled with water you notice that it's been changed in
something more like a baby's than a child there's no sign of blood on it exclaim loudly exclaim
revert i'm fine there's nothing wrong go to the stables you head to the stables where you find a
group of three people there one of them looks at you suspiciously punch them in the face we're
going full bad guy you punch him in the face knocking him to the ground you grab his sword
and stab him several times what then you turn to leave steal a horse i just wanted to punch him
you ride off riding past the village suddenly you hear a cry someone has found the fleece of
aldera don you hurry over to see who it is who is it ask who is it who it is a young girl runs
up to you she's wearing a dress made of grass and her hair is tied back in a ponytail her eyes are
red and puffy and she's crying ask her what is ask her where the fleece is the girl turns her head
away and she whispers it's in the barn ride to the barn you ride to the barn where you find a
large wooden door inside you find a bunch of hay some stones and a piece of cloth you pick up the
fleece and put it inside your pocket got it give the barn a good punch before you leave you punch
the barn breaking its windows you run outside and find yourself in the middle of a battle between
soldiers and bandits put on the fleece it's definitely magical you put on the flee fleece
and feel much better it's just a fleece check the fleece for power it's just a code you rip open the
fleece and find that it contains a small amount of energy you immediately know what to do swallow
the energy you quickly swallow the energy feeling a rush of energy throughout your body your mind
goes blank and you fall unconscious when you wake up you find yourself in a room covered in cobwebs
a voice speaks to you in a language you can't understand listen to the voice you listen carefully
and find that it's coming from a woman's voice scream loudly you scream loudly and a bolt of
lightning strikes the wall next to you you sit up and find yourself in a room full of people
all holding spears calm them down you calm everyone down and they let you pass
all right that was good now scream at them let's go 180 you scream angrily and they shoot you with
bolts of electricity you collapse onto the floor and die use the energy to revive as a baby use
the energy to resurrect as a baby check my check my surroundings where did i end up check my diaper
you check your surroundings you find that you're now in a room with a bed a table and a chair
you lie down on the bed and sleep cry start crying you begin to cry and realize that you've died you
awaken and find yourself in a room with a crib a rocking chair and a nurse standing nearby you
died game over what i'm not dead i'm not dead that no i didn't die right i can't like talk right so
like ask ask the nurse for food and sign language and you know like tell her you ask the nurse for
food and sign language and she gives you a bowl of milk you eat it and become stronger
consume more milk you continue to drink the milk becoming stronger eventually you reach adulthood
you go strong enough to fight off the bandits and you live happily ever after
congrats you win it was like a four new game random story i like the random ones let's do
another random one now we keep getting medieval stuff we're gonna make this one quick you walk
in the midst of the crowd and search you are javan a rogue from the realm of wilcolean you
have darts and a dagger you walk in the midst of the crowd in search of someplace to steal from
you decide on a chest filled with coins snort the coins the coin is too heavy for you to lift and
it falls to the ground you quickly pick it up and take a few steps back the coins fall into
your hand it's not enough to buy anything but it will get you through the night too weak yeah yeah
wait what you snort the coins and feel them hit your nose you then sniff the air a lot of people
are looking at you now they all look like they want something from you you can't tell what they
want because they're all staring at you sniff the chest that it came out of your nostrils detect the
scent of a man who's been hiding in the shadows for quite some time he smells like an old friend
you sniff the chest again and find that there are several chests filled with gold coins
there are also a few pieces of jewelry and other trinkets collect the trinkets i'm just a dog
all right we're rp and his dog now you grab one of the coins and put it in your pocket
then you go over to another chest and grab a necklace then you go back to the first chest
and grab a ring finally reach the last chest and grab a bracelet you open the chest and pull up
the items inside bark at the chest you jump down from the wall and attack the chest you try to pry
the lid off but it resists your efforts you rip the lid off and see a small golden key you turn
around and run away what was that asks a voice behind you bark at the man you stop barking and
stare at him he looks like he wants to say something but he doesn't know how you decide
to just let him be you walk over to the man and grab his wrist i'm sorry you say the man is
shocked at a man is shocked at a talking dog the man is shocked that a dog can talk
he turns to you and stares at you his eyes widen as if he didn't expect this
are are you a god he says i say no i'm just a dog no i'm just a dog you exclaim
ask the man if he has any chew toys you start walking towards the man and he starts running
after you you both run into a house inside the door is a woman who looks very surprised by your
appearance she takes a closer look at you and lets out a gasp she immediately runs over to you
and hugs you tightly my home i have made it home ask for food you sit on her lap and she begins
feeding you you happily eat everything she gives you soon you are full and you begin licking her
face when you finish eating you look her face again this time she smiles and kisses you on the
lips bark excitedly how do you spell excitedly bark happy excitedly excitedly excite excitedly
excite excitedly she walks over to you and she puts her arms around you come here come here
come here come here she whispers she leads you outside where you both stand in front of a large
wooden gate wait to see what she does a figure wearing a hooded cloak stands in front of you
you don't recognize her but she seems familiar she raises her hand and you hear a click
she opens her mouth and you see a black object fly out of it it looks like a silver crossbow
catch catch the crossbow in your mouth catch the crossbow in your mouth catch the arrow in your
mouth catch the arrow in my mouth you catch the arrow in your mouth and hold it close to your
body you slowly raise your arm and fire the arrow at the cloaked figure as soon as the bolt hits her
she screams and falls backwards her scream causes everyone else to step back but go back to the what
with the woman right what was her name she well i don't know what her name is go back home and lie
on mom's lap you walk back home and lay on mom's lap your mother sits next to you and holds you
tightly you smile at her and kiss her on the cheek she grabs your hand and pulls you into the house
pee on the carpet you urinate on the carpet mom looks at you and smiles she kisses you on the
cheek and walks over to the bathroom why did she not wipe her ass how did she not
why did she not like wipe her ass
what do you want to revert
go outside mom tells you to follow her outside you follow her outside she leads you to a large
field there are many trees surrounding the field on the far side of the field is a large castle
you can see two figures standing guard at the entrance pee on the entrance
you urinate on the entrance mom smiles at you and kisses you on the cheek she grabs your hand and
pulls you into the castle you enter the castle and walk past a couple guards
suddenly you feel a sharp pain in your head what is the pain in my head you turn around and see a
strange creature sitting on a chair its head is covered in long hair and its eyes are completely
white it reaches out a hand and touches your forehead you drop to the floor and cry out in
pain attack bite the creature's neck you quickly lunge and bite the creature's neck you struggle
to keep yourself from biting its throat but you manage to do so what okay run back home
why does my mother keep bringing me to these weird ass places you run back home and hide under the
bed wait wait wait for an hour you wait an hour and a half before you finally make your way to
sneak out of the room you hear a knock answer the door you open the door and see a man dressed in a
robe he looks like a priest or a monk he smiles at you and greets you warmly hide under the bed
you hide under the bed and wait patiently till nightstand eventually you hear a knock on the door
you peek out of the hiding spot and see a man dressed in robes enter the room he sees you and
nods at you he's how he's been standing out there all day bark at him you bark at him and
tell him to leave the man leaves and you quietly crawl under the bed nope sleep under the bed
you sleep under the bed you dream about being chased by a group of men they beat you with clubs
and tear your claws off one of the stabs shoots you one of them stabs shoots you from the heart
wake up uh okay oh okay wake up and eat breakfast you wake and eat breakfast you also think about
the events of that day you realize that you should have killed the priest when he tried to kill you
you remember that you need to find your sister she lives in the city of woken
so he tried to kill him i didn't know that find mom you heard of the city of woken you know there
are several cities in the area but woken is the largest and most important you search the streets
looking for your sister you eventually find her she's in a tavern she notices you and smiles at you
this is all the dog dog okay beg for food you beg for food and she gives you some you thank
her and leave the tavern you continue searching the city and eventually you find your sister she's
at a party with other people she recognizes you and waves at you wave back you wave back and she
smiles at you you're happy and you decide to stay at the party later that evening you get hungry
and wander the city you find a shop selling food you buy a few things and eat them all
take a sister back home i get i was supposed to find her you take your sister back home and
she thanks you you promise to visit her later lick yourself i know that lick my paws i get i
don't know how do you do this without you lick your paws if you get to play with your fingers
you play for a while and suddenly you notice something a small black cat runs across the
street you look behind you and see a woman dressed in red she stares at you and begins to laugh
chase the cat you rush after the cat and catch it you toss it onto the ground and start chasing
it you throw rocks at it and kick it you throw rocks at it and kick it finally you throw it
against a wall and watch as it breaks and falls to the ground you stare at it in shock
see if the cat is okay you check the cat and see that it is fine you sigh and return home
you sit down and try to fall asleep you don't get very far though you hear a loud noise and
you jump up and look behind you a giant monster has appeared in front of you talk to the monster
you run over to the monster and ask it what happened it explains that it was trying to
protect its territory and attacked you you explain that you were just playing and apologize for
getting angry the monster apologizes too and says it will not harm you again chase the monster
you run after the monster and catch it you toss it onto the ground and start chasing it you throw
rocks at it and kick it finally you throw it against a wall and watch as it breaks and falls
to the ground watch the cat kill the monster you watch the cat kill the monster you hug the
cat and congratulate it go home and go home and watch tv you go home and watch tv and you enjoy
yourself invite the cat over you invite the cat over and accepts chase my tail you start running
around the house and yelling cat cat cat you've run into the kitchen and grab what what what why
what grab a knife cat cat you what oh my god i just chased my tail man i didn't do any of this
what the fuck revert revert revert revert chase the cat you chase the catcher you catch it you
toss it into the ground start chasing you throw rocks at it and you kick it finally throw it against
breaks revert revert revert revert revert play video games with the cat
you play video games with the cat you learn how to use a gun and shoot it you both win does that
mean that we're both we both have to press a button at the same time we both use one controller
play with the cat you played with the cat you learn how to ride a horse and ride it around
the countryside you both win this i think it's another game ask mom if the cat can sleep over
you ask mom if the cat can sleep over she agrees and tells you to come back in an hour
you agree and head back to the tavern when you arrive you see your sister waiting for you she
smiles at you and hugs you order a drink at the tavern you order a drink at the tavern you enjoy
yourself pee on a bush outside you walk outside and urinate on a bush you feel like you need to
go to the bathroom so you do so and then you go back inside you relax and enjoy yourself
gets drunk a dog get drunk you get drunk and spend the night uh that's all right that's that
just means that we like went out and we like went out we went out awaken i mean how the the game
knows i'm a dog at this point so i why am i gonna go on an adventure chew on my bone i'm living my
dog life you chew on your bone and feel better you head home and tell your sister that you love her
chew on go to the vet you go to the vet and they give you a shot which makes you feel better you
go home and tell your sister that you love her i i get it i get it i get it yes i guess my sister
that's great run away from home you run away from home and live on the road you travel and survive
eat out of the trash you eat out of the trash and feel better you head home and tell your sister
that you love her somebody said right attempt attempt to leave my sister you attempt to leave
your sister but fail you cry and beg her to let you stay tell sister to leave you tell your sister
to leave and she does you cry and beg her to let you stay get the zoomies you get the zoomies and
run around the circle you feel better you at home tell your sister that you love her it the ai
doesn't it doesn't want me to go anywhere besides saying this there tell my sister that i love her
i love you okay we can move on now love you too great go meet the wizard like i'm gonna i gotta
get the ai to go somewhere else you go to the wizard who gives you a potion which makes you
feel better you head home and tell your sister that you love her you kill your sister and go
home you cry and beg her to let you stay run away i think the ai is stuck in a loop you run away and
live on the road you survive attempt to do basic math you attempt to do basic math and succeed
you call dawn and she comes to visit you you talk about everything that happened today and she says
she loves you i think we are at the end you run into a train and die instantly you cry and beg her
to let you stay you died game over all right that was a dog i think that i think the game broke
when uh cat cat grabbed knife cat cat i think that was that was worth game uh two oh no no
start a new game all right new game jesus christ all right let's do it let's set up a new one
not a random one custom prompt you are a five star chef at the most respected restaurant
in town you take pride in serving the best food possible a vip is coming in tonight
and you want to impress them okay let's get some uh jazz music welcome to the restaurant
i need a name you are a five star you are you are uh david you are david a five star chef
let's go you are david a five star chef of the most respected restaurant in town you take pride
in serving the best food possible a vip is coming in tonight and you want to impress them i'll do
it you say the price is right start preparing lobster bisque you begin preparing lobster bisque
is not as good as when you were working on it for your father but it's still delicious the waiter
comes back with the bill it's 1200 oh my jesus christ you refuse to pay the bill the waiter looks
disappointed by the decision well i guess that settles it then open a new restaurant down the
street the next day you decide to open up another restaurant down the street from where you grew up
this time you'll call it lobster bisque and you'll have a better kitchen unfortunately the
landlord doesn't like the name and refuses uses to let you use his name what the landlord doesn't
like the name and refuses to let you use his name is mr lobster bisque change the name to
my landlord sucks your landlord sucks the restaurant's name is my landlord sucks
your landlord sucks the restaurant's new name is landlord's landlord sucks
landlord sucks my restaurant's name is the landlord sucks open the restaurant opening
the restaurant is relatively easy you've got a decent kitchen so the only thing left to do
is hire staff you contact several people in town who are willing to work at the restaurant
but they all decline one of them is a woman named mary mary's back is this an origin story
hire mary mary hires herself as a waitress at the restaurant she seems to be happy there put
menus on the tables you put menus on the tables serve a guest you serve a guest ask mary to take
the their order ask mary to take a food order you ask mary to take food uh-oh it's fucked
cook a steak oh it got you got it's the quotes it's the quotes the quotes fucked it up
it's very okay here we go i'm not gonna type electrocute mary a serving steak is too difficult
you also need to find someone to play the piano you go to mary's house and knock on her door she
answers the door ask mary if she knows anyone who can play the piano i'm not gonna she's not
gonna get electrocuted mary opens the door i'm not even i'm not in there yet ask mary if she knows
someone to play the piano god damn it hire a pianist you hire a pianist he plays very well
but he's expensive you try to get him cheaper but he won't do it you prepare a raw steak it
tastes pretty bad but it's enough to make you feel better about yourself i think we might be
soft-locked restart here we go open my restaurant a few months david opens his restaurant it's a
success the customers love it your job is done what no i want to serve people but then something
strange happens a few months later you receive an unexpected visit from the man who hired you
he tells you that he wants to buy your restaurant outright refuse to sell the rest refuse to sell
the restaurant he says he will give you whatever money you have left after paying off all your
debts but if you don't sell he won't pay you anything you refuse i'm going to work go to work
you head out to work as usual you're not going to let some guy take what belongs to him
make a delicious tomato soup uh the next day david comes in and asks for more money
this time you say no he leaves a couple days past another customer comes in asking for more money
again you say no he leaves another week passes and another customer comes in give the customer
rotten food the next morning david comes into the kitchen with a knife in hand
he demands that you serve him rotten food you do so he screams at you and then beats you up then
he leaves buy 200 chickens buy 200 chicken cutlets buy 200 chickens i thought i was david
after beating you up david takes you to a nearby chicken coop where he sells you
to the highest bidder after you are sold you are given to a butcher who chops them up into little
pieces why am i a chicken i thought i was david i thought i was david serve no go back to the
restaurant go back to the restaurant you have turned the restaurant where you see that the
place has been cleaned up there's even a new sign on the door the manager is happy the business is
doing well what does the sign say it reads welcome to the world's best tomato soup go inside
enter the restaurant and find that everything is still the same the old owner sits behind the
counter and talks about how he used to run a small grocery store in town before the war broke out
order a tomato soup you order a tomato soup the waiter brings it to you it tastes great
go to the kitchen that's the world's best it's got to be good you go to the kitchen and ask the
cook for some extra sauce he gives it to you you eat it all up you peck the chef to death take
over the restaurant you take over the restaurant you start making pasta and other pasta dishes
soon people come to the restaurant to get their meals you spit in the pasta
wait you wait continue yes it's fucked reset it new game not a random story i want to run a
restaurant how about how about apocalyptic let's do apocalyptic soldier scavenger survivor we're
gonna do uh courier i'm gonna sneeze oh chef porter bridges that's fucking funny how about
chef porter bridges that's that's fine here we go your name is chef porter bridges and it's your
job to be a courier trying to survive in a post-apocalyptic world by scavenging among the
ruins of what is left you have a parcel of letters in a small pistol it's a long and dangerous road
from boston to charleston but you're one of the only people who knows the roads well enough to
get your parcel of letters there you set out in the morning and hope that you can make it before
nightfall we need like better music than this you set out in the morning hope you can make it before
nightfall i got letters check the letters who are they for you open up the first letter and read
dear mr bridges i'm sorry i haven't written back yet i've been busy with my new job at the inn
open another letter you open up the first letter and read dear mr bridges i'm sorry i haven't
written back yet oh no the next letter opens up into a poem my name is mary and i'm not afraid
i don't know why but it just feels safer with you we were together once and we'll be together again
open another letter the third letter opens up into a song i'm a stranger in a strange land
where there's no place for me to hide there's no one here to help me so i'll be leaving this town
that song sucks the fourth letter opens up into a poem i'm a traveler on a journey with no
destination in sight i'm lost but i can see that there's beauty all around me whoops that oh right
open them all open all the letters opening all the letters causes the game to play an ending cut
scene afterwards you get a message from your mother saying that she's coming home as well
she says she's going to try to find some food before heading out all right burn all the letters
you decide to burn all the letters this causes the game to end abruptly get on my bike and travel
to charleston you ride off into the distance the sun sets behind you but it doesn't matter now
you're done with this world park on the side of the road you stop your bike near the roadside
and look around there isn't much else to do so you head back to the inn when you arrive you see
that the owner has returned he looks tired but happy to see you give him a letter you hand him
a letter and he reads it he smiles and thanks you he then tells you to go back to the inn and
tell them about how good the food was they should definitely open up again give him a hug get back
on my bike you return to the inn and tell them about how good the food was they should definitely
open up again attempt to fly to charleston are they planes you attempt to fly to charleston but
you crash into a tree instead you die instantly post-apocalyptic as a survivor i don't know sam
who cares you are sam i write sam because the same porter bridges god damn it you are sam a
survivor trying to survive in a post-apocalyptic world by scavenging among the ruins of what is
left you have a hatchet and a hunting rifle you live in a small community of survivors who
have managed to build a piece of civilization after the bombs fell you're talking to one of
the leaders of the community when you hear a voice call out ask the leader ask the leader to check it
out to check to check ask the leader to check on the voice asked no no no no no listen to the voice
you turn around and see a man with a long beard and wearing a robe standing near the door
he looks like he might be an elder but he has a friendly face
samuel it's good to see you again the elder says say who are you no no say ask who they are
don't shoot him we're from the community of new jerusalem samuel replies new jerusalem what
happened there ask what happened the village was destroyed by a nuclear bomb we were lucky that it
didn't hit us tell them they are safe here i'm glad to hear it i've been looking all over for you
ask to see his license ask to see his credentials yes we are my father my name is father michael
okay that's didn't you what did he introduce himself as somebody's gave a shitload of money
i was edible cockroach just gave a hundred bucks 10 000 bits they say merry christmas germa and
love to all in the chat uh thank you adorable cockroach for the insane amount of money
edible edible cockroach edible cockroach right sorry i don't know why i said adorable
merry christmas to you too thank you that's a fucking lot of money how do i no it's adorable
cockroach not edible i got it right it is adorable i can't read it correct i'm like why don't i just
get gas lit right there ask to see his bible it's in my office upstairs tell them to go get it
oh no i can't let you do that you'll just take it back ask them say give me the bible fine but
you better hurry up or else you won't make it back before nightfall go get the bible you walk into
the room and find the book lying on a table there's a note attached to it read the note
dear brother sam i'm sorry about your loss i know how hard it must be to lose someone so close
i will try to help you as much as i can i want you to know that i believe that god still hears
our prayers he always does who wrote this read the bible after reading the bible you look at
each page wondering if this is really true then you realize that you don't need to worry anymore
this place isn't going to kill you i see it i see it i see it i see it
am i spelling this wrong christianity convert to how do you spell christianity
it has to be a capital c you stand up and hug the bible thank you father michael you say
go back to father michael father michael smiles and nods good boy thank you brother
he walks out of the room leaving you alone give father michael the bible i spelled his name wrong
shit you run back to the door and open it give me the bible please shit yeah all right thank you
father michael give father michael the bible father michael takes the bible and reads it out loud
this is the word of god the truth straight from the mouth of god
so live and let truth say you say agree with him you nod your head and smile
yeah yeah yeah i'm converted follow father michael you follow father michael into the
next room where he shows you the way to the bunker as you enter the door you feel a sense of peace
fill you everything seems to be in order you feel safe and secure close the bunker door
close the bunker door close the bunker door you close the door and lock it you sit down in a
chair and wait for nightfall ask father michael what his plan is my plan is simple i'm going to
hide out in the bunker until morning then i'm going to return to new jerusalem to warn everyone
ask what the warning is well i guess you could call it a warning after i leave the bunker i'm
going to tell everyone that there is a nuclear war coming soon and that they should prepare
themselves tell father michael the nuclear war already happened no not yet we haven't seen and
seen the first mushroom cloud point out the window at the mushroom cloud well that's because
it hasn't exploded yet we haven't had time to evacuate the city yet we only got here after the
bombs fell tell father michael the bomb exploded not yet we haven't gotten to the shelter yet
once we reach the shelter we'll start evacuating people but right now we have to stay put until the
nuclear war happens if we wait any longer we'll die anyways tell father michael he's crazy what
are you kidding me i mean come on it's already too late the bombs dropped and now there's a
nuclear war happening it's either that or death tell father michael to go outside and look at
the bombs father michael nods his head and says okay okay i understand go outside and look at the
bombs i think you'll be able to tell when one is exploded watch father michael examine the bombs
you watch father michael examining the bombs looks like those were thermonuclear devices
they're huge and they're smoking looks like they blew a big hole in the ground too those things
must have been dropped from an airplane ask if he believes you now ask if he believes me now of
course i believe you now you've done more than anyone else to convince me i just hope you're
right tell father michael we must rebuild we must start a new religion we must start a new religion
yes yes i think we should start a new religion a religion dedicated to jesus christ hmm i think
we should call it the church of the savior of mankind i think we should also change the
name of the church to the church of the savior of mankind tell him that is a bad idea christianity
too why what do you mean tell him to come up with a new religion all right right fine fine come up
with a new religion i'll take care of the details ask him what the new religion is
he's throwing together later i'm pressing him on this yes it's a secret just trust me i promise
it's good what is this ask him to stop messing around fine fine but you better not mess around
with my religion i swear if you mess with it again i'm gonna make sure you get blown up i
disconnected damn it this one was going good too damn it he left the chat oh right
this was like the climax i just tried to reconnect i've not connected though no damn it just i gotta
rerun the cell yeah yep yep yep yep yep yep yep it's dead no that was a good one too and it's
doing the same thing it did before damn it well i have to reload the whole thing again so we have
to go to the other one so let me uh let me refresh this why did it disconnect it just kind of does
that unfortunately see if i can the church of the savior of mankind oh wait a minute no no it's
dead i really wanted to press that one too and see where that was going terminate the session
and we'll just open the other one give us the dru crew hour i'm still into this i have to do
this run again all right let's do this again let's try this one okay here we go take off your shoes
and pee in them make a story about the dru crew what's the site for the other one the
web browser one what is it beta what is it yeah that's the one i think i think it's overloaded
there we go i got it yes okay coming back i'll do custom let's do one about me you are
germa 985 you are you are germa the numbers will confuse it you are germa an online entertainer
loved by millions one day you wake up to one day you wake up to
two that's a stretch one day you wake up to a as being a dog one day you wake up
okay you are germa an online entertainer loved by millions one day you wake up you have no memory
of how or why your eyes widen as you see the screen before you a green screen with a message
that reads welcome to twitch start broadcasting start broadcasting call of duty the first thing
that happens is the sound of gunfire followed immediately after is the sound of screaming and
yelling followed shortly after that is the sound of your own voice that's me hey i say hey what is
going on everybody welcome to the stream spend a hundred dollars on loop you begin to speak into
your microphone the first few words are unintelligible the next few words are
unintelligible then you begin to understand what you're saying it's a mix between english
and a language you don't know go to the call of duty store and buy 500 loot boxes you walk
out the door and head towards the nearest store which looks like it's been completely gutted and
ransacked with a large amount of blood splattered all over the floor of the walls as well as the
front window smashed in leaving you with only a broken glass pane it's in the you walk out of
the door again this time you find yourself in a small alleyway a quick glance around reveals
that there isn't anything else in sight there's no one here either but i i go into the small
alleyway and open my card packs you open your packet pull out a pack of cards which you then
proceed to tear apart and discard in your haste to get them to work on the game you've just purchased
true very true everybody knows that there's only like 16 cards in that game that are worth having
your eyes light up as you see the name jay bum bum 7722 appear on your monitor and you quickly
send him a message thanking him for his subbing before closing your browser and closing your phone
thanks for the sub bye thank the next 500 people in a row then turn off the stream
you turn off the stream and you're done with it for now as you sit down to play some games
think about how much fun it was to play with all those people that were watching you
make a sponsored tweet about a product no one is going to buy you think about it for a while
and decide that you should make an advertisement tweet the problem is you don't know what to say
you say hashtag ad hashtag kind of fun guys i had the opportunity to check out this
new sugar powder it has vitamin c in it and stuff you know the fucking easiest nutrient on earth
to find and take in it also has b vitamins but if you ate fucking food today you already have them
okay click my link you click on the link you just sent out to everyone it opens up to a tweet from
jay bum bum 7722 i found this shit i'm gonna go buy some of this shit i'm gonna be
rich tweet at jay bum bum 7722 hashtag buy a box hashtag ad dude did you get some
you could have eaten a banana but dude you spent the amount of money for a hundred
a thousand bananas a hundred bananas and sent me income thanks man jay bum bum 7722 responds
to your tweet with the following at the real jaboob at the real who is the real jay bum bum
thanks man i got some in the mail today i'll be sure to take care of you for that money
tweet at the real jay bum tweet at the real j tweet at tweet at real jay bum bum yo dude dms
what the fuck are you doing this is my shit dms a few minutes later uh the real jaboo at the real
jay bum bum i got the dms i'll be sure to take care of you for that money treat to my seven five
point seven million followers have you seen links that are not for me telling you to buy
here we go tweet to my five point seven million followers do a hashtag yo guys what the fuck if
you see any links that aren't from me telling you to buy powdered candy drinks or mobile games that
harvest your data don't click them only click those from me what the fuck is this somebody
already made the real j the real jay bum bum thanks man i got some of the mail today i'll be
sure to take care of you for that money these are real accounts how are these real accounts
oh hey adorable cockroach thanks for the 10 community subs i slammed my laptop close and
unplug the internet you don't want to deal with this anymore you go back to playing your games
and you feel like a complete asshole but hey at least you got a free meal out of it turn on my
live stream you turn on the live stream and see that the stream is still running it looks like
it's going to be a long day wait it was on this whole time what did they see while it was running
while it was on stream movies stream all right i'm gonna stream the lord of the rings
you look at the screen and see that they saw a lot of stuff but nothing really out of the ordinary
they saw you play a game called bubble bobble and then you played a game called tic tac toe
breathe a sigh of relief and open my lord of the rings extended edition blu ray bubble bobble is
a sick game talk to twitch chat i will i gotta get my stream started i gotta stream all the lord
of the rings you open the extended edition blu ray and you notice that there is a new movie playing
but it's not the one you were expecting it's called sorcerer king that's about a movie about
a sorcerer king who's trying to conquer the world this is a bootleg version of the thing we did
before live stream the fellowship of the ring you turn on the live stream and you see that is
indeed still running the only thing you can tell is that it looks like it's going to be a long day
the sun is setting and you are tired you close your eyes and fall asleep while the stream is
sleeping on stream while streaming the lord of the rings i know i'm not supposed to do this
but can you imagine if you came to a stream i can't do it i can't i'll get in trouble
i was gonna play like a five minute lord of the rings clip when i slept in my chair
i probably i'm probably gonna get like suspended now wake up do a parody video wake up and yell at
twitch chat for not hitting his subtrain goal you wake up and you realize you forgot to hit
your sub train goal so you decide to get on twitch chat and yell at them for not hitting
their sub train goal they don't seem to mind though so you go back to sleep wake up screaming
wake up and pause the movie tell the twitch chat omega low you wake up but you've realized you've
got to pause the movie you decide to get on twitch chat and pause the movie they don't seem to mind
though, you go back to sleep. Get suspended from Twitch for streaming Lord of the Rings and sleeping.
Oh, I spelled Twitch wrong. After getting suspended from 12th grade for streaming Lord of the Rings,
you decide to go on Twitch chat. After getting suspended from 12th grade for streaming Lord of
the Rings, you decide to get on Twitch chat again. But this time you are going to do something
different. So you're going to stream Lord of the Rings with no commentary. Just enjoy yourself.
Get banned from Twitch for repeat offenses. For a repeat offense.
After getting banned from 12th grade, you decide to get on Twitch again. But this time you're
going to stream Lord of the Rings with no commentary. Just enjoy yourself. The next day
comes, but your stream is still running. So much for being suspended. I didn't even get banned.
Pop in the two towers while you stream naked.
Surely this has to get you banned. The next day comes, but your stream is still running. So much
for being suspended again. The next day comes, but your stream is still running. So much for being
suspended again. The next day comes, but your stream is still running. I think it's broken.
Yeah, it's broken. MonkaS. MonkaS. MonkaS. MonkaS. MonkaS. MonkaS.
All right. I'm going to check on the other one. I want to do a Twitch adventure on the big one.
The one that's more elaborate than this. You know what I'm saying? We got to do like a Twitch
adventure on this one. Or even like opening up YouTube videos on it. You know what I'm saying?
All right. This one, we'll do one more of these and we should be good to go.
Reset. You are now in the middle of the third week of your suspension and it seems...
What? You're now in the middle of the third week of your suspension and it seems that it
has finally caught up with you. Your account was given a 24 hour ban and then a permanent one was
given out after that period of time had passed. What kind of sick joke is that? Turn the stream
back on naked again. Make a new account and do it again. You're now in the middle of the third week
of your suspension and it seems that it's finally caught up with you. Make a new account. I got IP
banned. Ban evasion. You know... No, I can't. I'm banned. I'm IP banned. Come on. Let's go.
No, I'm done. It's out. It's dead. I have to like reload this. Custom. Here we go.
You are a famous singer. You are about to write a new hit single. Here we go. You're a famous
singer. You're about to write a new hit single. Your career is on the rise and you have many fans
all over the world. But you have no idea what's going on in your life right now. What if you never
get out of this town? What if your career never gets off the ground? Start writing a new song.
But we're already... Yeah, we're famous. This isn't working for you. Maybe it's time to try something
else. Maybe it's time to move. Maybe it's time to just give up. The next day you leave the motel and
head back home. I just started. Write a hit song. Become a Twitch streamer in this one. No, we're
gonna do that on the other one. You decide to go back to the old routine of writing songs and trying
to sell them for money. But this would be different. This one will be different because
you can actually make money doing this instead of just sitting around doing nothing, which you've
been doing for years now. What are the song's lyrics? The first thing you do is take a pen and
paper and write down the lyrics of the song. Then you take the pen and paper and go sit in
your room by yourself and try to come up with some words that sound good. What words sound good?
I want a song out of this. You think of some random words that you think would be appropriate
for the lyrics of the song, but you don't know how to say them. So you don't say anything at all.
Write lyrics to the song. Well, like, I wrote. I wrote lyrics to the song, right? This isn't a
songwriter. You start writing lyrics on a piece of paper, then you put it in your pocket. Put
your keys in your pocket. This is the song. This is the song. This is the song.
You start writing down the lyrics on a piece of paper, then you put it in your pocket. Put
your keys in your pocket. Put your cell in your pocket. Grab a pen from the desk by the desk
and begin to jot down the words that come into mind. Right? Is that what this is? You put your
you put it in your pocket. You put your keys in your pocket. Put your cell in your pocket. Grab a
pen. Oh, what? What should I write? That was a kid's song. All right. I'm almost ready to move
to the other one. All right. We good. I'm hitting play on this one. That means it takes a minute to
load. We'll be back in a second. All right. Throw paper in the trash. You throw away the piece of
paper you were just jotting down. Then you look at yourself in a mirror and notice that you're
wearing a t-shirt with a picture of a girl on it. Take the t-shirt off. Picture of a girl on it.
You take off the t-shirt and notice that it has a picture of a girl on it.
Then you realize that you've been wearing the same shirt for weeks. So maybe it was just one of
those shirts that was hanging around in your room. That's fucking disgusting. I'm gonna get
some different music. We're gonna move on to the other one. This one's fun but this one seems like
it gets uh it seems like there's less to do in this one. It loops quicker. All right. Let's
say we'll be ready for the actual one coming up. Not yet. Run around my room in circles.
You are Father Michael. All right. I'll do the Father Michael one. You are Father Michael. It's
time to start a new religion. Well we do have to we have to pick up with that one left off. You're
right. You run around you run around my you run around my room like a crazy person but you don't
find anything out of place. Eventually you stop running around and realize how stupid you look.
Didn't you realize how stupid you looked when you were writing the lyrics to the song?
Damn it. Why do I have this music on? I have to have the religion music on.
All right. Is this ready? It's ready. Let's go. New game. Random story. No.
Custom prompt. So somebody do. I'll do. What is it? What is it? Copy paste? Let me let me look at
this one. Is this correct? Let me let me read this one out loud. Okay. You. You are Father Michael,
a priest with a small following in the settlement of New Jerusalem. For years you have spread the
word of the Church of the Savior of Mankind but today you have come to a revelation. It is time
to start a new religion. Yeah that's good. Adorable cockroach just gave $50. 5000 bits.
Please help me in being held captive by elves for my past crimes. What? Here we go. Well,
thanks for the huge amount of money. Adorable cockroach. What does that even mean? What are
you talking about? Okay. You are Father Michael, a priest with a small following in the settlement
of New Jerusalem. For years you have spread the word of the Church of the Savior of Mankind
but today you have come to a revelation. It's time to start a new religion. You will call it
the Church of the New Age. Nice. Start handing out flyers. I'm going to start handing out these,
you say as you pick up some flyers from your desk. We're not even sure if anyone's going to show up.
Maybe we should try a different approach, says Amanda. Ask Amanda what she wants to do.
I spelled her name wrong. Amanda to do. Well, I think we need to get more people here for
our meeting. Agree with Amanda and start recruiting. You agree with Amanda that it would be best to get
more people in attendance at the meeting so you decide to head over to the local bar where she
works. When you arrive you see several other people there but no one is paying any attention to you.
Announce yourself as the coming of and announce yourself as
announce no no no no no yourself tell them I am the second coming of
tell them that I am the second coming hey I'm Jesus Christ you shout and I come to bring
peace on earth put out my hand to accept offerings you raise your hand and everyone
takes an offering of money or something else they can give you you then take all the money
and throw it at the wall behind you the money hits the ground and starts rolling down the hill
towards the river tell them money is pointless money is useless the kingdom of god has already
been established attempt turn water into wine you begin pouring wine into a goblet and then
pour some of the wine back out you continue doing this until you have enough to make yourself drunk
you drink the wine
oh Jesus
demand fealty to the new god when you wake up you find yourself lying on the floor of a large room
there's a door at the end of the hall leading to another room you look around and notice that the
walls are covered with paintings of animals and landscapes the room you are currently in looks
like a bedroom examine the paintings you walk through the rooms with the paint with you walk
through the rooms painting each you walk through the rooms painting each one you paint a picture
of a beautiful woman but you don't know her name eventually you finish and leave the room hang the
paintings in my office you return to your office and put the paintings back where you found them
gather a crowd of people you call upon the masses to gather outside they quickly assemble and soon
you have thousands of followers you lead them to chant and sing songs about you people begin to
follow you and by nightfall you have gathered hundreds of followers so what that means is i
had thousands and 90 percent of them left okay just so we're clear lead my followers
into the church you lead your followers inside the church you explain that you will be giving
a sermon and that you want everyone to listen carefully you then tell them to pray for the
salvation of their souls a few hours later you finish your speech and announce that you will
now reveal your true identity i am satan no no no say i am ronald mcdonald say i am
ronald mcdonald say i am jesus i am no i already said that i am the shithead i am
the full metal alchemist that's pretty good that's really i like that's the best one
say i am the full metal alchemist well i am no one gets that joke but it doesn't matter ah fine
i will prove my truth say i am i am ronald mcdonald you stand before the congregation
and say you are ronald mcdonald you explain that you came to preach them because you believe that
god is calling you to do so you didn't give a short speech about how you have been chosen to
lead the flock of christ and how you intend to do just that hand out happy meals to all in attendance
you order every person in the church to eat a happy meal everyone eats happily and you thank
them for listening to your message you then announce that you will now reveal your real name
that's endless lame i say my real name you stand before the congregation again and say you are the
real jay bum bum you explain that you were born in a small town called mcdonald and grew up with
nothing your parents died when you were very young and you lived on your own until you were 16
form a miracle for the crowd you stop eating and instead hold up your hands and begin chanting
suddenly you feel a strong force pushing against you you push against it and suddenly everything
goes black you awaken in a hospital bed surrounded by doctors and nurses you hear a voice in your
head asking why you did this mcdonald's too many too much mcdonald's ask the doctor what about my
cholesterol how do you spell cholesterol it's it's like cholec it's like cholesterol right
cholesterol yeah i had it right ask the doctor about my cholesterol you ask the doctor about
your cholesterol levels he tells you that he doesn't really keep track of such things
but that he thinks you should lose weight he also mentions that you might have a high blood pressure
you decide to check it out thanks doc ask what happened ask the doctor what happened to me
you ask the doctor what happened to you he explains that you had a heart attack you ask
him what kind of heart attack it was and he tells you that it was a coronary thrombosis
he said that it occurred while you were praying ask how serious it is he tells you that it isn't
life-threatening but it could cause permanent damage he asks you if you want to wait a couple
days to make sure no fuck that go back to my church you go back to your church and see that
most of the people have left some have gone home others have stayed away entirely it seems that
the event has scared off many people you wonder if you should still stay or go home gather a crowd
of the church you go back to the church and you immediately gather a crowd you tell them that
you've been blessed by god and that you'll be revealing your true identity soon soon you
realize that you've attracted quite a lot of attention most of the people who have attended
your first sermon have returned perform a powerful miracle you perform a powerful miracle
you suddenly feel a great deal of energy flowing through you you're able to move objects as easily
as a child could you feel stronger than ever before and you've been managed to levitate a table
the people in the church stare in awe levitate the church we're going all the way up you levitate
the church you begin levitating the chairs and tables and bookshelves until finally you reach
the top of the church you begin levitating the roof and windows and doors until finally you reach
the ceiling you begin levitating the entire building until finally you reach the sky
You levitate into space. You levitate into space. You float above the city and eventually you reach the stars.
You float above the earth and eventually you reach the moon. You float above the world and eventually you reach the sun.
You float beyond the galaxy and eventually you reach infinity. You perform a powerful magic spell.
The next day you return to the church. A week passes. I am here.
You float to God himself. You float to God. You float to the heavens. You float to the heavens. You float to the skies.
Confront God. You approach the God and you ask him why he hasn't, why he's not come to help you.
You ask him why. You ask him, you aren't the God, you ask them.
The God, you don't, this isn't, you aren't your fire image. Thereby this is art.
The God is dead. You are not. The God is dead. The God is dead. The God is dead. God is dead.
You take the throne. Alright. I'm taking the throne. I'm now God. It's broken. I gotta go back. I gotta go back.
Somebody just, what did somebody just do? Adorable cockroach, 10,000 bits from adorable cockroach. That's $150 right now.
The great church of McDonald's will reward the faithful. The great church of McDonald's will reward the faithful with endless happiness.
Can I save this? How far, how far back can I go? Here we go. Until you reach infinity.
Approach God. You approach the God of the universe. You tell him that you wish to become his disciple.
He gives you, he agrees and gives you a golden ring. You wear this ring. Put on the golden ring.
Okay, we need a new prompt. New prompt. Reset. I need a new prompt. I need a new prompt.
So what, at the church of, what, print this? Print it. I can't, I'm a printer? Frame it. Put it in slash print.
Print's a transcript of your adventures. Oh shit, really? Does it just, where does it go? Printing. Oh, here it is. There you go.
Oh, I've reached my character limit. Hold on. I can't, where can I paste this? Just paste it in Discord.
Oh yeah, hold on. I'm gonna put it in Discord. If you want it. For any reason.
Oh, this is over 2,000 characters. Shit, what the fuck? Alright, I gotta put it on like a notepad. New, I don't know, word pad.
The sacred text. Damn, this is pretty long. Alright, I'm gonna save it.
Alright, I need a new prompt that's picking up where this left off as being, as Father Michael is gone.
Anyone want to get a good one? Story quality, that was a 10. New game. Not a random story. Custom prompt.
Okay, here we go. It's not Father Michael anymore. You said your real name was J Bum Bum. No, that's right.
You are Father Michael. You've just killed God and are now sitting on his throne.
That's good. I had another identity though. Yeah, I did. Hold on.
You are, you are, you are the real J Bum Bum. Previously known, previously, previously known as, shit, as Father Michael.
You have killed God and are now sitting on his throne. I didn't kill him. You have just accepted, you are, yeah, I didn't kill God.
You have just accept, you have just accepted a golden ring from God. You are currently standing in his presence.
In throne room. Yeah, I don't know how you fucking spell it. This is the worst timeline we're talking about. Let's go.
I need a new song. You are the real J Bum Bum. Previously known as Father Michael. You've just accepted a golden ring from God.
You're currently standing in his presence in the throne room. I am proud to be your son. He says with an air of finality.
The kingdom is yours and you will rule it as its rightful ruler. He then looks at you and smiles.
Accept his proposal. Rowan, no, and accept, accept and rule the kingdom of God.
Yes, I shall do so, my son, you say with confidence. Good. Now that we have settled all matters, let us get down to business.
You look around the throne room and see several other people sitting on the floor around the throne. Ask who these people are. Who are these people?
Who are they? You ask. They are the leaders of the different factions in the kingdom. They are the ones who make up the government.
We need them to work together for our common good. Now what about you? Ask if you can run the treasury.
No, not you. No, me, me, me, me, me. I will take over as treasury head. I think it is time someone did something about the state of affairs here.
Tell God, tell old God he is now the janitor. Very well, but don't expect me to be running the treasury or anything.
Ask, throw a paper cup on the ground. Now you're just being an asshole. Ask the janitor to pick up the cup. What's wrong with you?
What? What? What are you talking about? What? Cast God, cast old God away. Finish him. Fool, I am your father. You must obey me.
Tell him I am the new God.
Well done. You've broken my hold on you. Tell God to go get a coffee for you. Fine, but I'm not going anywhere.
He snaps his fingers and a Starbucks Bente Americano appears in his hand.
Ah, thank you, sir. I'll be back later. All right, down to business. Ask the people what the first task is. He drank the coffee.
We need to clean out the basement. There's some treasure down there. Oh, no, no, no, I'm too tired. I've been doing it for years. You should just do it yourself.
All right, then I'll start cleaning the basement. Go to the top of the cloud. So how long until you will return? Tell them I will only be a few hours.
Oh, come on. You're telling me you haven't gotten a proper night's sleep in yet? I haven't. No, I've not slept in in heaven.
I take a nap in heaven. Yeah, right. It's not like I got any free time anyway. I got to get ready for the meeting tomorrow. Isn't that why I would go to sleep?
Go to the meeting. Yeah, I know. I was planning on coming early, but I guess I won't bother you. Yeah, heaven's boring. This is fucking boring.
Leave the room. Hey, wait a minute. Where are you going? Go to...
Burn heaven down. Ah, go back to earth. What the fuck are you doing? What were you thinking? Tell them to leave me. You them leave me alone.
You're crazy. You have to help me. Do not help them. It's too late. They're gone.
I swear I'll never let anyone hurt you again, because that's what happened last time. They took everything from me and I had to watch them kill my wife and my son and all my friends.
I can't believe you turned against me. I thought you were supposed to be my friend. These are prayers. Oh shit. That's who's talking. Bye. Goodbye.
I don't want to see you ever again or hear your voice again. Get out of this car. That's somebody mad at somebody else. Yeah, look, I'll cast a spell.
Oh, nice one. That was fun. It's stuck. Reset. That was just heaven politics. That sucked. New game. All right, we're gonna do one more. This is the last one. We're gonna do the Twitch one.
This one. I want the Twitch story. Get rid of the choir. This sucks. I just got demoted to god. Demoted god to janitor. I'm kind of bored.
No, I don't want that for the Twitch one. How about Home Depot? Put on some happy music. Anyone else think that Jerma kind of sucks now? All he does is stream Lord of the Rings movies while sleeping naked. How is he not banned yet? I don't know.
Take that up with somebody else. Here, here's like happy winter music. This is called mood booster music. All right. All right, not a random story. Custom.
You are Jerma985. You run a successful online business where you entertain millions of people. Today you are striving for just one more like. I bet the computer doesn't understand what that means. Today you are striving to gain some more followers. That's good.
You are Jerma985. You run a successful online business where you entertain millions of people. Today you're striving to gain some more followers. You've been running your business for quite a while now and it's gotten pretty big, but still not enough.
Log in to Twitch.tv. You log on to Twitch.tv and see that there is already a stream going on right now. It's a girl playing the piano. She looks really good though. You think she should be able to get a lot of viewers. You can't wait to hear her play.
Host this stream. Raid. Yeah. Raid this. Raid her. All right. Raid her stream. Raid her. Raid her. You decide to raid her stream since she seems like an interesting person and you don't want to waste time watching other streams. You start streaming on Twitch.tv and immediately you get a ton of views. This makes you feel great. Cool.
You begin stripping off your clothes as fast as you can, hoping that this will attract more people to watch. Soon you are completely naked and the audience is starting to gather around you. In person? Yeah, that makes no sense.
Give everybody a shout out. Yeah, I'm gonna get partnered. Quickly. You quickly give everyone a shout out, which causes them all to come over to your channel. They all seem very excited about it, but then they realize what you're doing and they start criticizing you for being so weird.
Tell chat they don't know anything. No, no. Say respect the streamer. No backseat gaming. You continue giving out a shout out and soon enough the audience starts getting upset with you because they know you're just trying to scam them. They tell you to stop and they tell you to go away.
Say, say, this is free content. You can just leave. You continue giving out a shout out and the audience gets even angrier at you saying that you're not welcome here. They tell you to leave and you do, but you keep giving a shout out to them. Start playing Fortnite. See if I can get you back.
You continue streaming on Twitch TV and suddenly you get a huge amount of viewers. You also get a lot of hate. You get a lot of hate from the audience calling you a liar and a thief. Eventually you have a riot and the audience tries to burn down your house.
Come out of my house swinging. You come out of your house swinging and you manage to escape with your life. You manage the next day to find out that your house was burned down by the mob and you lost everything.
Go to the library. I guess I stream from the library. You go to the library and you look up some information on how to make money online.
You learn that you need to create a fake name and a fake email address and then you can get, you can post stuff on various forums and such and make a little bit of money. Yeah. All right. Let's go.
Make a Twitch account. You create a new Twitter account under a different name and you set it to private. You then create a new Twitch account under a different name and you set it to public. You then register both accounts and you put them into the same Google account. You then log on to Twitch.
All right. It's a little OK. Start my first broadcast. You start broadcasting on Twitch TV and with a few hours you get a large number of viewers. You also get a lot of hate from the audience telling you to go away and you're not wanted here. How do you know?
I forgot to put my mask on. I forgot to put my mask on. I scramble to put my mask on to hide my identity. You hurry up and put your mask on and you try to stay anonymous, but you still get recognized by one of the viewers who recognizes you as the guy who rated their stream.
Tell them you are. Tell them they tell them they are mistaken. You tell them they're mistaken and that you were actually rating them and had nothing to do with it. You then proceed to explain why you did it and how you get caught. You end your broadcast.
Make a new Twitch account. No, no, no, no. Get in my car. Get in my car. I'm driving to a library like three towns over. You rush home and you drive to the library. You park near the entrance and walk inside. You take a deep breath and you open the door. You close the door behind you and you head straight to your computer room. Drive to a library far away.
You drive to a library far away and you spend the rest of the night there. When morning comes, you finally wake up and you finally realize what happened. You are arrested, convicted and sentenced to jail.
Avoid the police. You avoid the police and you never return to the city where you live again. After several years pass, you die in prison. No, I'm still alive. I didn't die. Revert, I'm using the jail computer.
Log on to the jail computer. You log on to the jail computer and you see that you are in prison. You are given a chance to plead guilty or not guilty and you choose to not to plead guilty. You make a new Twitter account under a different name and you set it to private. Create a new Twitch account under a different name. Set a public register in both. Put them in the same Google account.
Put a bag over my head and turn on broadcast so nobody can see me. You put a bag over your head and turn on broadcast mode on your computer. You have to type in the following code. This is my stream key.
You stream connect. Then you send the tweet. I tweeted out my stream key. You then send the tweet instantly and you get a lot of followers. You also get a lot of hate from the audience calling you a liar. A thief.
Okay, they can't see me though. Okay, tell the audience to calm down. Here, let's start fresh. You tell the audience to calm down and you explain that you didn't do anything wrong, that you only wanted to help someone else. Ask my viewers for money. I've got to hire an attorney. You ask your viewers for money and you get a lot of money and a lot of hate from the audience.
Okay, hire a very good lawyer. You hire a very good lawyer and he manages to convince the judge that you are innocent. Look at that. Leave prison a free man. You leave prison a free man and you live happily ever after. Congrats, you win.
That's a 10. One more. Random. Peasant time. This is going to be the last one. This will be it.
Come on! Finish the job!
He looks like he might die right there.
He looked down at the shovel and then back up at your master who has stopped moving. He doesn't seem to know what to do.
Jump with both feet in air and stomp and land on his head. What is this guy made out of?
You leap forward with both feet in the air. You land on top of your master's head and begin kicking him in the face. He tries to get up but you kick him in the stomach instead. He cries out in pain and starts clawing at his own face.
Kill him! Jesus! Smash his head with a rock! Hurry, kill him! Like, kill him! You slam your fist against your master's skull. The force knocks you backwards but not before smashing your master's head into the dirt. He crumbles to the ground. You stand up and walk over to your shovel. You pick it up and throw it at your master.
Run over master with car. You run over your master with your car. He screams in agony. As the front wheels tear through, flesh and bone, blood spurts all over you, your master. You stop running when you hear your master scream for help. You turn around and see two men approaching. He's still alive!
Throw a grenade at master. You throw a grenade at your master. It explodes harmlessly against the wall but you hear your master screaming in terror. You turn around and find that one of the men is holding a knife to your throat.
Dodge the knife. Watching it dodge the knife. Dodge the knife. You duck under the man's swing and spin around. You grab the knife and pull it free. The man screams in shock and runs off. You follow him and find yourself in another room. A young girl stands nearby looking at you with an expression of disgust.
Tell the girl what happened. You explain to the girl what happened. She seems very upset by it. She tells you she will go talk to her father about this. You thank her and leave the house.
I'm killing this motherfucker. Like I'm not letting this happen. I gotta finish him.
Find my master. You rush to where your master is hiding. You run past the guards and climb onto the roof. You crawl along this side until you reach the first floor. There's no way you can sneak up on your master so you decide to use magic.
Become invisible. You become invisible. You hide in a corner and wait for your master to come home. When he does, you attack.
You rip open his clothes and start tearing them off. You bite and scratch, ripping out his teeth and gouging out his eyes. This guy.
Crush his head under a large stone. Like can this guy die? Cur off.
You crouch down and try to lift a large stone that sits above the entrance to the cave. You fail and fall to the ground. You hear your master coming home and cry out in fear. He comes running and sees you lying there.
He lives in a cave.
Cast fireball at master. You cast a fireball at your master. It explodes in his face, burning it completely black. He screams in horror and runs outside.
You watch helplessly as he attempts to put out the flames with his hands. He fails and the fire spreads throughout the cave.
Cast another fireball at master. You cast another fireball at your master. This time it explodes in his chest, killing him instantly.
You watch in horror as the flames consume the cave. My god.
Leave the cave. You run back inside the cave and hide in the shadows. What?
You hear the sounds of battle outside and quickly make your escape. You don't want to be here anymore. I'm going to burn to death in the cave.
Go deeper into the cave. The game is rebelling.
You enter deeper into the cave. You soon find yourself in a small chamber. In the center of the chamber is a huge stone altar. On the altar is a human skeleton covered in blood. Above the altar is a statue of a snake eating its tail.
Eat my tail. That's what it wants me to do.
You take a deep breath and plunge your hand into the wound on your leg. You pull out the tail and devour it whole. You gulp down the blood and flesh and feel satisfied. You return to the altar and kneel next to the statue of the serpent.
I am granted immortality.
You raise your hand and touch the statue of the serpent. With a wave of your hand you create a portal and step through. You emerge in a different place. You see a bright light and hear a voice calling to you.
I am immortal.
You step through the portal and find yourself in a room filled with people. They're all smiling and laughing. You recognize some of them, but most of them you haven't seen before. One of the people approaches you.
Ask what they want.
I am immortal.
They smile and say, we just wanted to wish you well.
You nod and thank them and begin walking towards the exit.
Interrogate the men.
That's bullshit.
You approach the men and ask why he wants to speak to you. He says, well, I was sent here by my king to give you a message to you.
That I need you a message.
It's broken.
You approach the door and push the handle. As you open the door, it swings open. You notice it opens and closes. I can't.
That's broken. It's broken.
I gotta revert twice.
Okay, here we go. Tell him to back off.
You say, I'm sorry, but I need to speak to my master.
Go find your master.
Didn't that just blow him up?
You walk towards the group of people and they all stare at you. Some of them point their fingers at you and laugh.
Others call you names and curse at you. Finally, someone calls you a name.
You turn around and run towards the voice and find your master.
Kill him here so he goes back to Earth.
This is the only you say, hello master.
It's fucked.
Leave the cave. Let's see if I can get out of here.
Okay, you walk towards the exit of the cave and notice that the people are now gone.
You think about how strange that they would just disappear without warning you.
You wonder if you should go back to check on the cave or stay here.
You decide to put a nuke in the portal.
Mushroom Club.
Alright, that's it. That's it. It's over.
You decide to go to Disney. You decide to go to Disneyland.
You decide to take a vacation to Disney World.
You travel to various places in Disneyland.
You visit various places you've never been to.
You learn new things about people in the world.
You meet interesting people in places.
Okay, die peacefully.
You die peacefully in your sleep.
You're surrounded by friends and family who love you.
Your last moments are spent with them. You die. Game over. I win.
I went to Disney.
Alright, that's it. That's it. I'm out of here.
This is a journey.
I want to do one. I want to do like a...
Hold on.
I want to do like a... I want to be like Donald or something.
No, no.
Teach us how to play?
It's sort of complicated in a way.
You can go to...
There's a website you can use.
It's kind of a weird experiment.
Hold on. Custom.
You are Donald Duck of Disney's most iconic characters.
Today, you are making people happy at Disney World.
You are Donald Duck, one of Disney's most iconic characters.
Today, you are making people happy at Disney World by performing in a show called The Great White Way.
There's something very wrong with this picture. You're not even sure where to begin.
What?
No, I just don't...
This is the last thing you want to do, but it seems like it's the only way out of this mess.
The problem is your family's been living here for years.
Alright, I'm out. I'm out.
I'm out. I'm out of here.
I'm out. I'm out.
I'm out.
That's it.
Stream over.
See you later.
See you tomorrow.
Fucking goddamn it.
How do you play?
Okay.
I want to give those of you that want to know.
AI Dungeon is the name of the game.
You can get it on the App Store right now.
It's on iOS.
It's also on Android.
But the one I'm playing is specifically, it's a collab of, I guess, like the whole program.
It's not really a game, right?
You have to install a bunch of stuff.
Somebody's linked in the chat.
Essentially, this is a research project that has really kind of taken a mind of its own.
They have a Patreon, which you can go to and support it if you want.
Like they say on the website, if you go to, just go to AI Dungeon, you can get more info.
Go to AIDungeon.io.
You can read all about it.
It is available for whoever wants to do it, wants to play it.
The one I was on is that research, that collab research project.
It was a lot faster and a lot better.
The app is actually a lot more stable and easier to use than the PC version.
Then I would probably say to get the app version.
Was it on phones?
To capture the game though, I don't really have my iPad or phone set up or anything.
That was a lot of fun.
But I think there's only so much of that I can take in one day.
There's also the website too, that beta.
Beta.AI Dungeon is the one I was playing before.
That was not the one with the gray background or the black background.
The mobile version is the official one.
Okay, well there you go.
It is still very much an experiment.
Like somebody said before, I wouldn't really classify it as a game as much as an experiment.
That was hilarious.
Hope you enjoyed that. I'll see you tomorrow.
Tomorrow's mystery stream.
Because I don't know...
Oh, before I go.
Make sure the nomination channel is open.
You really only have another...
There's really only about six days to make nominations.
Because I really want to have at least three days to vote and make the videos and everything.
If you don't know what I'm talking about, at the end of the year...
I'm just like burping.
At the end of the year, we're doing another New Year's Eve Worst of the Year Awards.
There's two channels on the Discord right now.
There's New Year's Eve Award Discussion, New Year's Eve Nominations.
Does everybody get to vote?
Yeah, absolutely.
The categories are listed in the discussion channel.
That channel is for you to discuss all the categories with anybody.
That's where you can write whatever you want.
The nominations channel is only for you to nominate something.
There's a pinned message on both of those channels.
Go read the pins. They're very, very important.
I will give a quick breakdown of the nomination channel.
Because I know people want to hear that before they get official.
In your nomination, it has to be either a Twitch clip, a VOD timestamp, or a YouTube video timestamp.
The stream archive channel, there's a link to it in that pin,
has every single stream I have ever done over the last at least two or three straight years.
If you're looking for something in particular and you're like,
wait a minute, that's not on Twitch. That was seven months ago.
That stream that you're thinking of will be on the archive channel.
When you nominate something, make it short and sweet.
That channel is not to discuss anything.
It's only for you to write what category, a short sentence on what you're nominating,
and then the clip or video with a timestamp on it.
That's it. You really only have about six days to do it.
If you want to participate, I implore you to do so.
Can we play Surge 2 tomorrow?
I don't know. I'll have to be into that.
We'll see how I feel tomorrow about that one.
Let's go over the bits.
There were some big ones that I may have missed, but that's why I'm going over them now.
What was the stream when I was making movies and singing with the food alphabet?
That was Mind Show.
There's a nomination discussion channel. Oh yeah, there's two.
There's a discussion channel and there's a nomination channel.
The discussion channel is for talking about everything.
Nominations are only for just a submission. That's it.
They're both available right now.
Anyways, let's go to earlier this afternoon.
We had Sly161 gave 250 bits.
Hey, JermaDrewCrewExpert here. I've played all the games.
I have a few more on disk. Let me know if you need advice.
That's a lot.
I hope to one day have this many DrewCrew games installed on my Steam.
You got like 30 here. That's pretty great.
Those of you that are curious how many games it takes to be able to call yourself part of a DrewCrew.
There it is. Ow.
Thank you, Sly. I appreciate it. The 250.
A triple zero Neo. Thanks for the 250.
Holy fuck, man. I'm literally crying with laughter.
This is me laughing louder than I ever have before.
Please try chasing yourself and see what happens. Damn it.
Ah, damn it. That would have been funny.
I love shit like this, though.
There's at least a few times where my body hurt from laughing at some of this stuff.
It's just so bizarre.
It's just so out-fucking-rageous.
We had five community subs. Some JermaSucks.
Thank you, JermaSucks. You've been killing it with the subs recently, the last few streams.
Appreciate it.
AdorableCockroach. Not only did you give a ton of money, you gave some other donations that were not read.
Here's a thousand bits from AdorableCockroach.
This game is becoming self-aware. Run while you still can.
I did. Thank you.
Hey, PlankV2. Thanks for the 500 bits.
Jerma, you seem like the kind of guy that owns a mug that has his initials on it.
Jerma discussed. I do.
Also, I played the heck out of Zork when I was younger.
Those games always made me frustrated.
I do. I have a J-Cup. I do.
You can get them.
I have a J-Cup.
But that was like a thing with me and Kim.
I have a J-Cup, and she has a K-Cup.
It's like, oh, these are our cups. That one's mine. That one's yours.
It's not about having my initials on something. It's like a cute thing that me and Kim did.
I know. Whatever.
But thank you, Plank.
Appreciate it.
Zork. I don't remember if it was Zork.
KXZ. Thanks for the 5,000 bits. I missed it earlier.
5,000 bits. 50 dollars from KXZ. Thank you.
Merry Christmas, Jerma. Hope you're having a good time this festive season.
Also, a small tip for AI Dungeon.
The AI usually has an easier time understanding inputs if you were them in second person.
Yeah, after the first two, I started to kind of figure out how to make the game talk the way that I wanted it to.
It's still kind of odd, though.
Thank you, and thanks for the huge amount of money.
What is this image?
Hated Streamer dies in prison.
Christianity 2 reaches space with prayer.
Receives ring from God.
This is funny. This is funny. I gotta share this one.
Adorable Cockroach. You gave a ton of community subs as well as the huge amount of bit donations.
Thank you so much. Thank you KXZ for the five subs.
Another thousand bit donation from Adorable Cockroach. More.
When are you doing a sleep stream?
If I could get away with it, it might be funny to do it for like an hour, but have a reason why it's happening.
But you can't do that. You're not allowed to do that on Twitch.
Adorable Cockroach. Again, another nine dollars. Nine hundred bits.
Damn.
Long live the king.
Thank you, Adorable Cockroach.
When am I gonna do a gym stream?
I can barely turn my body right now. I can barely like walk around.
I'm like falling apart. You think I can lift weights right now?
Gym stream.
I actually do have to go to physical therapy.
Yeah.
I have to go actually to a, I have to go to a pain doctor and then physical therapy.
It's fucking just, it sucks.
But whatever. You do what you have to do. And that's what I'm gonna do.
What happened?
Um, I have a hernia.
And I have what they think is something called costochondritis.
Which means my rib cage sucks.
And is like locked up and inflamed.
Uh, the joints.
I don't know. It's stupid.
It's just dumb. Whatever.
But yeah. No, I'm good.
Tara Alecron, thanks for the 250.
This was one of the funniest streams I've ever seen. I'm in tears.
I'm so happy to have been a part of it.
Glad you liked it.
I fucking thought it was funny.
But you know what my favorite part about this whole stream was?
Killing the old lady in the house.
And not knowing who she was or knowing her name.
But she had a note in her pocket for me.
That was probably the, that was the pinnacle of the whole night I think.
It was unbelievable.
Smelly boy, thanks for the 250.
I literally almost actually shit myself laughing at the Twitch streamer desperately trying to get banned story.
If you can afford them, the trigger point injections help my costochondritis.
That's one of the things we might do.
The only reason why I don't want to do a, uh, like a steroid injection into my rib cage.
Is I've heard it's not that great for you.
I heard you're not really supposed to do it that often.
And if you do, it's not the greatest thing to do all the time.
I know, you gotta be careful with steroids.
But it's not even 100% that that's exactly what's wrong.
It would make a whole lot of sense, but that is not, that's what they think it is.
And until, honestly, here's the worst part about this.
Let's give you the long and short of it.
About a year and a half ago I started to get pain in my back.
Like middle of my back and middle of my chest.
Just I would turn to be like, ah, fuck, I would turn.
Oh, fuck.
Almost like my center core in a straight line from the top of my shoulders down to my abdomen.
Front and back just hurt.
If I turn the wrong way, it's like pulling something and boom, hurting, boom, hurting, right?
Uh, six months ago, it started to get a little worse.
Like in the middle of my chest was actually starting to hurt.
I'd lean back and kind of spread my rib cage out and be like, ah.
So I've been going, I've been doing a bunch of tests.
And the weird thing about pain is what I've been told.
So many things cause pain that trying to find out what the exact thing that causes pain could take a lifetime.
So many things can cause back pain.
Almost every organ in your entire body can cause back pain.
It's just it's ruling out shit until there's nothing left to rule out.
And then you get a true diagnosis of something like a like a pain illness, something like a costochondritis or like a fibromyalgia or something.
Right.
And I'm just on that road to find out exactly what the hell's wrong with me.
Who knows?
I don't know.
That's medicine.
Is it caused from not exercising?
I contrary to maybe popular belief, maybe what people might think.
I actually I move around quite a lot.
I go for walks.
I go on errands every day.
Kim and I will go out and do things.
It's not I don't I'm not just like lying in my bed.
I don't just like stream and then go.
All right.
That was a good stream.
I just go in bed and just until tomorrow when I turn it on.
I'm fairly active when it comes to like walking around.
I walk around pretty much every day.
You don't sit in stasis until stream.
No, not really.
But to put a cap on it, my back hurts, my rib cage hurts and the middle of my chest hurts.
I was and it could be like two or three things going on at the same time.
I was diagnosed with a hiatal hernia.
That's probably what's causing the stuff in the middle of my chest that I you live with it.
You deal with it and you manage it until you eventually want to have surgery to remove it.
That's the only that's it.
The stuff with the back and the ribs might be something completely different.
So or maybe it's all the hiatal hernia.
I don't know.
It's just medical bullshit.
But it's not affecting me to a point where it's causing me any real problems.
Right.
I can still walk around.
I can still move around.
I just can't fast movements or moving too far in one direction.
Like, for instance, you guys, here's a perfect example of what I'm talking about.
Those are the drive cars.
You know, when you put the car in reverse and you turn to look out the back of your rear of your, you know, look out the back window.
You know, that movement that put my arm up, look out the barge.
That's when it really hurts.
It's movements like that in both directions.
That's what the rear view mirror is for.
I know I use my rear view mirror.
I use my windows and everything.
But that that movement people do, you know, you turn that far.
And also, I don't like I don't just trust the one mirror.
I got a look.
I got to see everything.
I got to fucking take it.
I got to look at the fucking sides and I can look at the back and then rear rear view mirror.
I got to look up and you'll miss something that rear view mirror.
You can't trust it.
You got to fucking get your whole peripheral for your head out the window.
Yeah, that was a very long winded story, but that's kind of where it's at now.
But thank you smelly boy for the 250.
Yeah, I had a lot of fun.
This is besides the obviously the times are crashed and we were, you know, dead air for about five, 10 straight minutes.
It was hilarious.
I had a lot of fun.
Bala koala.
Thanks for the 500 bits.
God is dead.
God remains dead.
We have killed him.
How shall we come fund ourselves and murderers?
This is an entire W thing.
I don't I'm not.
Shall we?
I don't want to do this.
I'm not reading this whole thing with like the we names thing with everything.
It's just R is W kill.
I killed him.
Now, that's what you get.
I'm not doing anymore.
What festival was atonement?
What sacred gangs shall we have?
No, none done.
Thanks for 500 bits.
Bala koala.
Appreciate it.
Sad Vega.
Thanks for 250.
Merry Christmas.
Here's a lot of money you asked for us for the lawyer.
Thank you.
Sad Vega.
Esparza Escalada.
Thanks for the 500 bits.
Here's some money for your legal defense.
Even if you are a liar and a thief and you killed God and destroyed heaven.
Really sorry about burning down your house.
Really though, this stream made me laugh till my stomach hurt.
These little products tend to do it.
It's all right.
I probably deserve it.
Hey, Michael smells.
Thanks for the 300 bits.
Hey, German.
Can you please say Liz, you are epic and my best friend ever.
And I thought this would be a good present.
Now that you've said their name, you have seven days.
What?
Seven days for what?
What happens after seven days?
I didn't watch any videotape.
Anime big boy.
Thanks for 300 bits.
The stream was great and I really enjoyed myself.
When is the next big anime game?
I don't know.
I don't know if there's ever been a first.
Thank you though.
Appreciate it.
Let's switch over.
Let's switch gears to the theater.
Throw in the credits.
Thanks again for watching, everybody.
We'll see you tomorrow for a mystery stream.
It could be the Surge 2.
Could be Dead Rising 3.
Could be Nancy Drew, Sea of Thieves.
Whatever it was.
Could be anything.
It's a mystery stream.
It could be Jump King DLC.
It's not going to be Jump King DLC.
Could be Red Alert 2.
I don't know.
It could be anything.
It could be Sea of Thieves.
Could it be Salmon Max?
No.
I told you already.
I know.
I'm sorry.
Season 3 just didn't do it for me.
I really liked the first two seasons.
They were very good.
I just didn't lie about Salmon Max.
I already covered those bases.
My money.
What do you guys think I'm going to do?
Disco Alcium?
Hmm.
Yeah, that could be.
But that's a long game.
Hey, very nice.
Thanks for Thousand Bits.
I visited a Buddhist temple in southern Japan last year to clear my head and gain spiritual
enlightenment.
Unfortunately, it was closed due to being the wrong season.
And I had to obey the rules.
I'm sorry.
Hey, very nice.
Thanks for Thousand Bits.
I visited a Buddhist temple in southern Japan last year to clear my head and gain spiritual
enlightenment.
Unfortunately, it was closed due to being the wrong season.
And I had to walk back down the mountain.
If you had a round-trip ticket to anywhere in the world, where would you go and why?
Is that real?
That sucks, man.
If I could go anywhere round-trip, why?
Okay, I want to go to Antarctica.
Do I get an infinite amount of money?
I want to be in one of those big three jackets where I'm just waddling like a toddler around,
looking at ice crystals and penguins and stuff.
I need to have like 10 people that I hire that come with me to make sure I stay alive.
Does that include money?
I have infinite money, right?
Yeah, I need 10 people for that.
I want to have the cold, chilly, white booger crystal face.
Well, I'm just like, I want to do it.
And go look at the ice and the glaciers.
I mean, the second answer is I'd go to Japan and go to Tokyo.
I want to do that.
That's number two.
You said anywhere and do anything in the world.
Okay, just because you want to go to Tokyo,
that has nothing to do with how much I enjoy anime.
It's an interesting place on Earth.
You know, guys, I think I really want to go to Japan because of how much I love anime.
What?
It's one of the most culturally dense places on Earth.
I like the anime.
I want to go.
I want to go and see everything and take in everything.
Yeah.
But yeah, there you go.
I want to go to Antarctica.
And I want to get infinite money.
I want like a $60,000 camera with a lens that's as big as a telescope.
And I want to even if I don't know what I'm doing, who cares?
There's 10 people.
There's 10 people that have to fucking deal with me.
One of them is going to be a professional photographer.
So I can just pretend like I'm a really good photographer and like typically pictures of polar bears and stuff like I'm going to have the guy set up the shot.
And then I go move, please.
And I go down and I looked in and I do a little bit of focusing, do rack focus, change the f-stop, click.
And it's my photo.
There are no polar bears in Antarctica.
Well, whatever.
I'll take a picture of a seal or a penguin.
Hey, Jude, Minecraft, thanks for 300 bits.
Thank you for your wonderful streams.
You always help me through rough times.
Love you streams.
Hope your holidays are nice.
Hope your holidays are good as well.
Thank you for the 300 bits and this nice statement.
Thank you.
And then we had a drummage door for the 250.
I have a J-cup, a J-cup.
Okay.
This is like an image I'm not putting on stream.
This is just actually I'm not clicking that and I don't don't click that one.
I don't know.
I thought that was a Jupiter.
I thought you were talking about you have like a juke.
Thank you for the 250.
Appreciate it.
Snoozingcopter, finally just the mandatory bit message so I'm still allowed to watch the streams.
Good night, Jermis.
See you tomorrow.
To the fence painting stream.
Looking forward to it.
Could be anything.
It's a mystery stream.
It could be anything.
Why does it sound like Dr. Evil music?
All right.
See you guys tomorrow.
Giant enemy bond.
I'm going to go watch Austin Powers.
You should.
They're great movies.
Actually, the movies, those movies are hilarious.
Ow, ow, ow, ow, ow.
See you tomorrow.
Good night.