Hey, what's up? Yeah, I know I'm late. Yeah, it's meh, well, not really.
Not really. Well, I was going to stream yesterday, but moved it to today.
It was going to be six o'clock at night, but reverse delayed after a delay to noon.
So you got both a delay and a reverse delay. My favorite econ. I appreciate that.
We should all play Valorant so I play it. A lot of people already play Valorant and I don't play it.
I'm definitely not going to play Valorant. I'm telling you right now.
Any shooter game that requires a ton of brain power to learn. Is Valorant a high brain power game?
Or no, people are going to laugh at me for saying that, aren't they?
Am I going to get laughed at for saying that? No? I mean, it feels like kind of a high brain
power game. You played TF2. I just told you a story a few days ago about how
I AFKed and spawned with the flog and ate chocolate until I fell asleep.
I don't think you can do that in Valorant. So I'm not so sure as some of these
some of these shooter games are for me. But anyways, hello. We're going to play more
Halls of Torment today. It's going to be a very short stream. I have to prepare.
A stir is coming to Vegas. So I'm going to spend some time. It could be really interesting. It's
been a while since being stirred. Spent some time hanging out. How short? Probably like two
or three hours. That's very short. But hey, let's hang out. I also plan on opening some crates
in Team Fortress today. I have a whole backpack full of keys and shit. I'm just like, do I? How
do I? What do I even do about this? So you're going to get a Halls of Torment, one or two
Halls of Torment runs, and then a TF2 box opening stream. Welcome. Welcome to the new Jerma.
Oh, boy. He's going to just open crates for an hour and leave. Oh, oh, oh. Oh, this is this is
the end. This is the we're at the end. No, no, it's I just I have a lot of cases that are old.
I've got like winter, like 2020, like 2019, I think crates. I don't even know what's in them.
I've got, I don't know. I got 25 keys. When are you going to play viewfinder? Yeah. Winter cases,
omega low. Don't open. Are they bad? Should I not have gotten the winter cases? Well, I didn't get
any. I just have had them for like half a decade. The winter cases are dog shit. What? That's like
half the inventory, I think. Is that how I think that would be? Oh, well, you're okay. Well,
you're not even going to want to watch that part. The most expensive item you can get is five cents.
What on the marketplace? Oh, whatever. I got 25 keys. Okay, Tony Montana. I have guys I haven't
opened a TF2 box. As of like the last seven days. It's been almost. It's been like seven or eight
years. It's been a very long time. It's just I have a lot of these boxes in my inventory. I did
a full inventory cleanup. And you know what happens when you do an inventory cleanup in Team Fortress?
You. Well, this is what I do. Each backpack slot is another class slot. So one is scout,
two is soldier, backpack slot, three is pyro, right? I like to keep it very organized. And when
I did that, I realized I had like 80 crates. I'm just like, what do I do with all these?
And then I was told, don't open all these ones because they're terrible. But I got war paint
cases. I've got cosmetic cases from the last five years. I don't know. I'll just open them.
Sort by type. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I'm terrified to click that button because there's
no undo. All right. Okay. Stop stalling. I'm going to be for like two, three hours. So no stalling,
no stalling. Yeah, no stalling. Let's go and play halls of torment for a little bit. And then we'll
play some TF2. Open it up some cases and crates. Play the game. I know, I know, I got to go. I know
I have to do it. I like this game. All right. So we left up halls of torment a few days ago.
Give me all the loot for safekeeping. Wink, wink. It's kind of funny because I've, I know, go,
dude, go. You only got two hours. Go. But let me tell you a story. Hold on. Let me just get,
I've got 3000 gold. Yeah. All right. I want to refund all because I'm playing the burn character.
So we're gonna do some crazy shit with the burn character. Start talking about Diablo four.
I should give you guys my takes more often because I saw a few comments of people saying like,
oh man, like this is like one of the only things he's ever said that I like agree with.
Should I give you my takes more often instead of just, okay, the only takes you guys get from me
are like dog food flavors. And I'm just like fucking around, right? But like you never get
like a real take from me. So you can never get my real opinions on anything. So the only opinion
you do get from me are dog food. So that's why all of you think I'm, I'm like a psycho
because I never give you a real take. And the comedy takes I give are about eating dog food.
So I get it. I completely understand that now. All right. So this, this is the fire character.
He's so fake. I'm maxing this out. What do you think? Projectile size and attack speed.
I think that's fine. Dog food takes. Revives are pretty big too. Say something controversial,
please. Um, no, I don't. What should I put the last one in damage, damage and defense?
What are your thoughts on the new Airbus? Like the new airplane? I don't know. Uh,
I'm actually going to take away regen and get movement speed with this character.
All right, cool. What do we have for items? Oh my God. He hates the Airbus.
What's so new about it? What does it, what does it do? You need to go on a rant, dude. Hey,
go on a rant. No, you don't want a rant. Like you don't want a bunch of takes from me. Trust me.
But back when Diablo two came out, what's a good item? I should dig. You don't know. You don't.
You really don't. I'm telling you. Three of you are going to go based and 10,000 of you are going
to go, what is it? What? Shut up. That's a good one. That's huge too. So this is 40% crit damage
and 10% base crit chance. That's cool. I remember getting those. Uh, we're going with this. I'm ready
to play one of my new favorites from 2023. I think I'm strong enough to try. Should I try to actually
beat the boss? You have an NA education? Yes, I do. What do you want to say? Yes. You want to deny
that? No, I don't. Shut up idiot. No, I don't. Yeah, I do. Yeah. I, I, I have a North American
education. Does that make you angry with me? All right. So I have auto attack on which holy
shit I am. I'm way stronger than I used to be. Okay. This is going great. We're going to do attack
speed. What was this doing before? Like 20 already leveled up twice. It's always damaged. WM one
gameplay. Yeah. Well, this is my favorite. It's probably my favorite character so far.
Is it always movement speed or should I finally do pick up range and have the people that were
very mad at me last time that I didn't pick it up, pick it up? Time is moving too fast.
It's so fucked up that it's August of 2023. Why is it? What happened to 2020? Well, I think I can
explain what you're feeling. Uh, COVID deleted two years that COVID essentially just absolutely
liquidated two full years. That's why it feels like 2021 because 2020 and 2021 and some of 2022
barely even happened. So yeah, we time traveled from 2020 to 2023 in a lot of ways. Um, I don't
know what to do here. I'm doing pick up range. I know that is not great, but if somebody put
their hand through their monitor, but sorry, we should make a petition to petition to go revert
back to 2021. That's kind of interesting. That's weird. Ladies and gentlemen, we have decided in
Congress, we are going to be introducing the rewind time act, uh, myself and Senator Stevenson
over there thought it was a good idea to rewind time back to 2021 because COVID fucked up everything
for two years. You've already used two rewinds. We made up time anyways. Isn't there like a wild
theory that we're in the wrong year? I heard that somewhere that it's actually like,
it's not 2000. It's not like 2000. We're living in like the, like the 1400s or something,
right? Isn't that what I heard? Isn't that what you heard? I heard that. Did you hear that? Bro,
you talked about this already. No, I didn't. I heard that we very, we could be like way further
in the future or way earlier. You heard that theory? I probably heard this theory on a fucking
YouTube short that I scrolled by every time I opened up YouTube shorts. I just got to tell you,
I, I think I'm getting older. I'm getting a lot older. I can definitely feel myself growing up,
but I scroll through YouTube shorts and I just go, what is going on? What is happening? I'm like,
am I older? I'm too old now. I'm, I'm too old for this. What's happening? That's a cool theory.
I'm 22 and I feel that way. Go to the blood trail. I want to get strong first. Hold on. Dude,
you're crazy. I don't, I don't know. I don't think so. I will scroll through YouTube shorts
and I just kind of, I, after like 10, I just stop and then I go back up three. Cause I go,
there's no fucking way. That's what I just watched like a minute and a half ago. Is it?
And I give that person like five more views in a row. You know what I mean? It's just like,
no, there's no way that what I just watched was what I just watched. Oh, it was, was it?
If you don't understand skibbidi toilet, you're fine. I've seen it. I've seen it. I watched it.
I don't think I saw the whole thing. These are all good. That's the one where the people with the
cameras for faces are like punching the people with the toilets, right? And it's,
they're like in a gigantic, there's like a big fight. Who told him? What do you mean who told
him? I saw it. And I was just like, oh, what the fuck is happening in this? Okay. Let me,
let me pay attention. He's becoming too advanced. I want the burn chance and no,
I'm not going to be playing this optimally. I know this is a good game for me to hang out
and just talk and chill, which is I like doing that. It's fun. So if I pick the wrong thing,
I'm just hanging out. We're just chilling. Don't worry. Zoomer humor. Enjoy your Andy.
I've made this statement before and it's very, very real. Oh yeah. Zoomer humor is,
is very, it's over very quickly. I brought up this very important point.
When you talk about zoomer humor, I can decide if I liked something in literally eight seconds.
Boomer humor, I might have to sit there for 30 minutes while they explain like a whole thing
and then tell it to me, like at the end of that. So it's like the one good thing for me about zoomer
humor is it's either good or it's not very quickly. So, but I do love that Boomer humor style where
you kind of have to tell a whole elaborate story, but one thing that might be kind of funny in the
middle. I very much enjoy the Boomer humor style, but zoomer humor is quick. It's to the point
and it gets going very quickly. I want health defense or let's do region. There's no setup.
Yeah. I like a big setup. I think that's pretty obvious if any of you have been here for long
enough. Honestly, the setup to me is a lot of times more fun than actually telling the joke
and sometimes way more fun. If you don't like to do Airbus, do you prefer the 747, the 787?
I don't prefer, and I don't, I don't, sure. I don't have like an airplane preference.
Although I guess maybe the newer ones are just, they're outfitted better with
more amenities. I guess, I don't know. What do you mean what? I said the newer ones are outfitted
with more amenities. Is that, but wait, is it, you literally flew a plane. Definitely this. Wait,
probably the dragon's breath carried that entire time I got close. You did? No, I did. Me and Austin
show. I was on his flight show. That was really cool. That was a great time. How come you hate
the council of sorcery so much? I don't. Do you have a private jet? I feel like if I flew in a
private jet one time, it would be over. I would like probably wipe out my entire bank account,
everything. I don't think that's a good idea. That's probably a really bad idea. I don't even
know how much even is. Okay. If I were to take a private jet, a private plane, how much does it
even cost? I don't even, I don't even know. It's $10,000 minimum. Yeah. No, no, no, no, no. I don't
think so. I don't think so. Not worth it. No, I don't, for me, I mean, I hate flying. I don't
like airplanes. I'm not afraid of flying. It's just the whole travel experience to me. It's like the
having to go through into the terminal and go through the security area and wait for everybody
to get on the plane and get on the plane and then sit there. And then it takes, it takes like three
hours to get on an airplane. Sometimes I hate it. I don't hate being in the air. I just, I just don't
like the whole prospect of the amount of time and how annoying it is to actually get into the plane
in the first place. Ooh. But is that worth like 9,000 extra dollars? Because even a first class
ticket on some of these airlines, that's already a huge premium on that seat. I don't think I would
want to pay like a thousand percent premium to get on like a private, I don't know. No,
no, you could afford it. I think a lot of you guys may be overestimating my finances a little.
Dude, bro, you can do it, dude. Just take a private plane everywhere you fucking go. It's only like
20 grand a flight. You got the money, you'll be fine. It's like, I think you guys may be
overestimating my financial ability to fly on a private plane all the time. What is it? I already
own all of these. You rented a baseball field. Yeah, that was for, that was for a stream that a
lot of time and a lot of energy went into. Me renting a baseball field out versus getting on
a private plane? That's, those are two very different things. Those are not even close.
I guess I'm just going to take it because I can deposit it because I don't have it yet, right?
This is physical attacks though. Do a private jet stream. No, no, I don't want to do that. No,
thank you. That whole stream is what? Just me flying on an airplane and reading a newspaper
and grabbing the sprite out of the flight attendant's hand. Just being like, thank you.
Thank you. That's it. That's the whole, that's all the content. Thank you. Thank you. And then
maybe like an hour goes by and I'm like, excuse me. Do you guys have headphones? Thank you.
Regen. No, multi hit. Didn't bring your own headphones. Headphones is always, I just,
I don't really do. Okay. A lot of you here, headphones might be a very important accessory
you take everywhere. I do not. Headphones to me are something that has to be packed.
I never carry them. They're never on me. It's never, I don't really. Oh, I've got my earbuds
in or whatever. Not really. So headphones to me are not an object I carry on me frequently.
You need to go down. Yep. Yep. We're just talking. All right. I'm going up. I don't want to deposit
this to the well yet because I might get a better item. Do you just sit and stare at a wall during
a plane ride? I mean, no, I'll, I'll do stuff on like tablets and stuff. Or sometimes, you know,
you get TV in front of you. Sometimes that's, that's fun. I'll load up. You know, it's great
on an airplane. It doesn't matter how many times you've seen it. Is it what? Here's the
strat. You ready for the, are you ready for the strategy? If your plane ride is more than three
hours long or about two to three hours long, go play the curb your enthusiasm roulette. You go pick
three random curb or four random curb your enthusiasm episodes. It doesn't matter what
they are. Just pick them out randomly. Cause even if you've seen it already, it's still going to be
good. That's the strategy for every airplane from any season. Doesn't matter what it is.
That's a boomer show. I want that person actually timed up that, that, that was what you just said
was offensive to me. Time them up for two minutes, at least a minute. I'm going to pick up range Andy
right now while I'm still doing pretty good damage. They got timed out. I'm saying Andy,
we don't even say it here. I do. What do you mean? I, I'm saying it right now. I say it all. What
do you mean we don't say it here? I say it every stream, like a hundred times the stream.
Maybe you don't, but I do. Did you, I've read that wrong. Oh, did I read that wrong?
What'd you say? You're overusing, you're overusing it. We love Andy here. We love saying Andy.
It's just such a quick way to get a point across about anything. It just really is. Like I told
you, zoomer. Well, that's, I don't think Andy is zoomer. That's more millennial, but like millennial
versus boomer, like me sitting here and explaining this, what you're seeing on the screen, this
character. Well, this character, I'll tell you at some point throughout the last hundred years or so,
fire became a device that was able to be used coming out of a propulsion machine that has oil
and a propulsion mechanism with an emulsifier in it. And what that does is that allows the fire to
go forward and be able to do what you're doing, wiping out all those monsters that I see. And it's
pretty wonderful invention versus flamethrower Andy. I can get my point across very quickly.
Oh, yes. You just lost a hundred viewers. It's all right there. They're going to be back or they're
not. Don't worry. Don't worry about how many people are here or not. They're going to come back or
they're not. Don't worry. Don't worry. I'm at work. Say hi. Am I on a work TV?
Yes, man. I'll tell you that the finance department is doing such an unbelievable job.
If you can hear this right now, a lot of the departments that are working for this company
are doing fantastic. So a great experience I've had working with them. I've never worked with them,
by the way, just for complete transparency sake. I've never worked with anybody here. I don't know
what this job is and I don't condone or support anything that anybody's doing in this. It's proven
to what that could be otherwise. So that was a joke and I have no idea what you do and I have no
idea what's going on in this business. It's too late. Centrist Andy. I don't know what the fuck
I'm talking about. That person could have just made that up just like I did. Verify your information
everybody before you make any, make sure you verify info. I love how that turned. I love
how that dumb joke just turned into verify info. Okay, you turned it into a PSA. Yeah, I did. Can
you please do your Adam Sandler bee sting on tongue impression? Is that close? I think that's
what you meant. Is that what you meant? I feel like that's what you meant. What happened to night time
streams? Well, the reason why I'm streams are early is because stir is coming into Vegas.
So I want to get prepared for stir. I'll be hanging out with stir. You're going to do an
IRL stream. No, something new. Oh shit. One of these is good. What do you mean prepare? I don't know.
When you have a friend coming into town, you want to make sure that like things look a little cleaner.
Things look better. It's not like a, I don't know. I want to make sure I got like an itinerary to
fun stuff to do. What are you talking about? You don't prepare for an arrival for someone
if they're coming in that week. What are you talking about? I think it's these. Are you guys
going to watch Barbie? I don't think so. What are the specs of your PC? I don't even know.
It's been a long time. I think I have a command. Isn't there a command to tell you guys what's in
my computer that I used to have one of those? Oh, there it is. Okay. Let me tell you. I have
eight 64 P. That's not right. Did it pop up? I'm so I'm still pissed off that you called me ball
fondler instead of bomb fondler during the day of the diver. Oh, that's your okay. Well, but you're
still in the ball fondler category though, because there's three X's before your name and you have
ball after the three X's. Come on. You got to give me a little bit of credit. The chat goes by fast
a lot sometimes. Yeah, I've got a 3090 and a I don't even know. Is it AMD or Intel in here?
AMD 5600 X. I got 64 gigabytes of RAM. I know that these ones are probably better, but I'm going to
take these and I'm going to deposit this because I think it's fun. And that's what I'm playing this
game for. Now I'm going to deposit that when I come back up, try wear it 10 crit or I don't
think you can compete with 10% base crit, but it's crit damage better than having skeletons
run around. Probably not. Are you going to shave before stirr is here? Stirr prefer bowing or air
bus. I don't know. Please choose range for the love of God. This is just a warm up round. And
plus we're just talking. I'm just hanging out. I'm not trying to optimally play the video game. I'm
trying to survive long enough to talk over it. That's kind of funny, but look, look at how much
better this is than range. I'm getting a lot of items. Okay. I feel like phantom needles is good
here. This is just now. Transfection is amazing. Just does so much damage. What is stirr's
astrological sign? Um, I don't know. He's a night elf. I don't know. Hmm. Range. Take the range.
All right. Now I gotta go up here. I gotta start doing some survivability here. I'm going to
deposit the skeleton ring. That's a good idea. This 10% fragile chance. What is fragile? Let's
see. Breach stack. Affliction increases the damage taken from damage over time. Well,
that's amazing. Modifies the chance to apply effects on enemies for every a hundred percent
chance. One stack is guaranteed. Hey, Jerma, let's go. What are we, where, what are we going?
What are we going? I want to be, I might, there's an opportunity to beat the actual boss here.
All right. I got to stop going down. I gotta go up. Great chance. All the blood stains, bro. Am I
ready for the blood stain yet? Should I get a little bit stronger? Am I ready to do it? Because
I'm imagining that's going to summon like a hard boss or something. I don't think I'm ready for it.
Watching you play this makes me want to eat my own hands. Uh, I could probably think of a few other
things you could be doing if you really wanted to not do that. This one. Yeah. I'm not, I'm not very
locked in right now. I'm, I'm looking over at the chat reading. This is, this is more like a podcast
stream. Ooh, it's a lot of area. Okay. I, what am I getting hit by? Lightning. Let me at least
deposit this. I mean, there's just, I can't take anything else. All right. Last pass. I'll get the
last pass here. All right. Now I'm going up. I'm going to go get the magnet too. We have a return
to the Sims. Yeah, definitely. Sims is a great game just to open up and just play it whenever,
even if there's no mods on it, it's just fun to start a new person. So yeah, it's kind of a staple,
isn't it? The Sims is always fun no matter what, but I never want to overdo it though.
I feel like the Sims is one of those things where it's really fun for like a week and then you kind
of let it go for six months, come back and it's a whole new, fresh, fun experience again. You can
kind of do that over and over again. You'd like Project Zomboid. I thought about playing Project
Zomboid. I want to, there's a lot of games to play and there's, I have lots of, I have lots of
potential streaming stuff to do. And it works out a lot, especially for somebody, I mean as a, you
know, the stream reduction that a lot of you guys have been used to this. Well, not even reduction,
but hold on, I don't want to die. You can play Borderlands 2? Probably not. Zomboid is boring
and overrated. I think I just never played it because it reminded me almost of looking at Path
of Exile the first time. Where it's just like, this is, look, this seems very, this seems like
a lot going on here that I don't know if I want to give the time to learn about it. Is that correct?
Kind of? No, actually, yeah. All right. That, that one guy saying pick range, I hope they're happy
because I've picked it like eight times in a row. Definitely this. Let's deposit this so I can do
Skeleton Friends eventually. It's a hard learning curve, but it's really fun. It does look very fun,
I will say. Max out Dragon Breath as fast as possible because it's the best ability in the
game from what I've seen. Ouch. Jeez. What is hitting me? Hurry up. Die. Okay. Firewalker boots
or I can't really take these anyways. Do I, am I missing anything? No. This is cool for this
character, but these really don't seem like they're that good. I mean, I'm the fire character, but
the fire doesn't seem that great. 15% movement speed seems just good no matter what. The boots
are amazing for bosses though. You use them, they suck. I use them with the not fire character and
I feel like I have a lot of burn and a lot of bonuses to fire right now. You should try Baldur's Gate.
I've heard a lot about Baldur's Gate and I'm kind of afraid to put any time into it because I feel
like it's one of those games where you need to know an entire encyclopedia before you start
playing it. Is that true? Not true. I think any, because Baldur's Gate is a D&D kind of, based on
D&D, right? All I remember was hearing about, oh this game is like kind of built on top of D&D,
it's like a D&D game. Oh cool, it was Neverwinter. And I remember being like, whoa, I mean I can like
play this as a ton of like characters and classes. And I remember playing this character just, I was
so disappointed in the game because I was playing it wrong. And I remember just like playing it and
the character I made, the only move that the character had was they went like, they did like
a whistle or like a sing and that was it. That's the only move I did. And I was like, this is,
I don't, I'm not having any fun. I like one move. I was like, why do I, I don't, I don't, I'm playing
this so wrong, aren't I? I think I was playing like a musical character, like a bard or something.
That was a pepino? God damn it, it was. I'll take them.
Is it weird that sometimes I just go to YouTube and type in a pepino scream and just listen to it
like 10 times in a row and then go on with my day? Is that weird? I do this not that often,
maybe once every couple months. What about Mortal Kombat 1? Yeah, I'll play it. I'll play
Mortal Kombat 1. You guys can all queue up and just absolutely shit on me. We'll make a fun
night out of it. More area, yes. I gotta start looking for health because I'm almost at the
30 minutes. I beat the boss last time, right? Yeah, I did. I got to the end with the other
character. Do the blood trail? No, I'm afraid. I'm scared of it. Why did that person just write
stimulus? Why did you do that? WM1, Andy? Yeah. You know what else is really funny too about
getting a little older? Kind of starting to feel myself grow up a lot. Back when I first played
Team Fortress 2, I remember. I remember being like, oh, WM1, come on. You could do better than that.
You suck at this game. What's with this? You're on pyro, of course. This pyro sucks. Now I'm just
like, oh man, I like this class a lot. This vlog class, I just can walk forward for a second.
It's funny. Everybody talks shit about pyro until they play pyro and then they're quiet,
right? You even notice that? Sit there, you get killed by a pyro and it's like,
you fucking idiot. What do you fucking even know about this game? What do you even know about
aiming? And then you pick pyro and you just kind of silently play it and you're like, wow,
this is a lot of fun. I'm quiet. I know I'm not having any fun. No, don't say that. I'm
not having fun. I've definitely come to appreciate pyro a lot more in like the,
in the second kind of half of my kind of online life. It's like, wow, pyro is good. I always like
pyro though. All right. I got to pay attention. I actually, I'm going to be quiet for real.
It's funny. I'll say that about spy too, right? You get, you get absolutely dominated by spy.
That's just kicking everybody's ass in the server. And you're like, oh, what the fuck? Like, fuck you.
Fuck you. And then you play spy and like bump into three walls and don't hit anybody. You face stab
a person and die instantly. And you do, you're zero for your team. And it's just like, oh,
right. This is like kind of like, it takes like a lot of skill to really kind of do this reliably.
Forgot. Yes. All right. Three minutes. And then I'm going to pay attention.
I'm actually kind of excited about opening those boxes. It's been a long time since I've done
something like that. Really. It's time for some loot get. That's right. Where's that magnet?
There it is. This is the second one too. Oh, burn chance or yeah. No, I think I'm taking crit
because the boss is about to run in. I'd rather be able to do damage quickly.
Yeah. Holy shit. That's so much. It's hard to even see because it's coming in so much.
What is going on? Okay. More crit. Level 60. More crit. All right. I'm ready for the boss.
I'm only going to take health regen now if I see it. Health and health regen is the only
thing I'm going to pick up. I got to turn on auto attack. There it is. Because I want to
auto attack the boss and just focus on moving around. Nice. It's got a health push, I think.
What about viewfinder? That's what we will open with next week. That's the
because I do really want to play that game. It looked really just like a nice experience.
All right. 40 seconds or so. I'm getting kind of collapsed on here. Good. Oh, I think taking the
50 health is better because in the amount of time it would take me to get 50 health from this,
it would be too late. All right. Let's do it. Yeah. I want to beat it with a second character.
Come on. All right. Here we go. Fucking that pole just screwed everything up.
I'm good. Get away from these poles. They're ruining everything.
Actually just ruin the whole run. Oh, shit. I didn't have enough movement speed and those
poles ruined everything. When he does the three in a row, they're like, if you don't have enough
movement speed, you're going to get hit no matter what. All right. Oh, let's do it again. What did
I? Well, shit. I didn't look at the unlocks. Where is it? Milestone story swift is an arrow.
There it is. All right. I got 750 gold for this one. I already got that money stream of fire
traits. What did I unlock? Are you going to abandon sorcery? No, we'll at the very least,
we will conclude. We will conclude sorcery. I'm telling you. Didn't I deposit the oh shit.
I have to buy it. That's right. I want that. You have 4% additional damage for each burning enemy
up to 60%. I like the fire character. It's very good. I think I'm good with this attack.
Maybe just more damage. Just straight up damage. This is becoming a problem. So more health and
regen in the beginning. It's a new game you're looking forward to the most. The Elden Ring DLC.
I don't think anything even compares. All right. I'm going again. That hasn't been announced.
That was a great spawn. Radiant aura. Cast light that distributes its damage equally among all
foes in its range. Automatically cast in intervals. Let's try it. Ah, I like this a lot. They announced
the Elden Ring DLC. They didn't announce when it was coming out. They announced it was being
worked on. I actually just shit my pants. I feel bad for you because it sucks when that happens.
Genuinely, it's really not fun. Yeah. Sorry about that. You know what's funny about what
you just said though? Imagine shitting your pants and sitting there after shitting your pants. You
just did it. And typing into a chat, hey, I just shit my pants for real. Why are you just sitting
there? Like, okay. You should probably go take care of it first, then talk about it. I think
that that's probably a good order of operations there. Now, it would have been even funnier if
you wrote, oh my God, I just shit my pants comma space. What do I do? That would have added a little
bit for me because that means you're just still sitting there and you're just like, I don't know
what to do about this. Please stop. I'm eating. Sometimes I forget that because I'm this way too.
Anytime the TV is on or anytime I'm watching any media, food is part of the picture at least 70 to
80 percent of the time. That is a food activity, sitting and watching something for me. So I forget
that sometimes that if I was just sitting there, oh my God, I got my delicious spread. I've got my
lunch and my dinner. It's right here. And the person I was watching was just like talking about,
yeah, I get it. But then again, I'm going to talk about what I'm going to talk about.
And that's it. That's all I'm going to say. I'm not going to change it.
I'm stacking health regen first. Open crates. I probably shouldn't have told you guys I was
going to do that. We're getting all caps open crates now. I probably shouldn't have even said
I was doing that. Open those crates. Hurry. I will. I will just chill crates now. Stop playing this
game and gamble already. Hey, by the way, when each crate opens, we all have to like rub our
hands together like this. Hey, buddy, the. Hold on. Hey, buddy, the blood trail alters give you
buffs. I thought it was OK. Well, thank I appreciate the spoiler. I actually kind of do.
I mean, I like to kind of figure these games out sometimes, but sometimes you really just this is
no way to know what the hell is even going on in these games. I thought when I picked up both of
those pieces and went to the altar or whatever, that it was going to spawn a hard boss, but it's
going to give me an item to help with the boss. So I guess I'll do it. One of these two. Can you
please put family guy clips in the corner? No. Blue ones are special. Wait, which ones?
Needles is probably better for this exact build right now. What? I'm playing the new version of
the game. I forgot the beta is out, right? So there is new stuff here. Oh, cool. All right.
Yeah, this is the beta is out. It's in beta. There's a bunch of new stuff. I can be so mean
to us. I'm not. You're interpreting me. My. Sorry, I lost something. I want to. There we go.
Is this the beta version? I imagine so, because I didn't have this light radius thing before.
You have to subscribe to the beta to access it. Oh, well, shit. You have to put the game.
You have to go into the beta change on Steam. I'll be playing this again. So it doesn't matter.
This is a fun game just to kind of play for like a few hours. It got caught lying.
I didn't get caught lying. I didn't have correct info. I thought that there was a patch to the
game that was because it was like, hey, the game's going into beta. So I'm like, oh, maybe it's I
guess it's in beta. Steam auto updates everything. Steam is auto updating, right? That's not how
betas work. All right. The game is an early access game. I thought it was just going to
be. Hey, we're in like we're considered to be in beta now. We didn't update.
It takes like five seconds to do it. Is it going to mess with my save file? Does it make a different
save file or can I just do it after this run? You'll be fine. Yeah, I'll turn it on. What pizza
topping should you get? Pepperoni is easy. Doesn't weigh it down. I don't like when pizza gets weighed
down. You pick the thing up and the thing flops over like a fucking like it's a t-shirt. Like
coming out of the fucking dryer. Like, no, no, thanks. To me, toppings on a pizza should always
be always small enough to be able to not cause a flop problem. For instance, meat lovers pizza,
I find to be just I don't find I don't want to order it because it's not a it's a lasagna
because you're going to get it out of the bar. You're going to take the piece out. You're going
to put it on a plate and it's going to just be falling apart like a fucking lasagna. It's a
lasagna. Just eat it. Just eat a lasagna. He's a meat hater. No, it's just it's about weight.
I love sausage on pizza. I love, you know, like hamburger on pizza. I like pepperoni on pizza. I
like bacon on pizza. I just don't want all of them on piled on at the same time. It's all about
just, you know, the distribution. Meat haters pizza. There's just a bunch of lettuce on it.
This build sucks. It's been five minutes. I think I'm doing okay. Veggie pizza does go hard.
I like vegetables on pizza, but again, the same rule applies. Peppers and onions. Okay, nice.
Peppers and onions. Peppers and onions and olives though. No, that's one too many. No,
peppers and onions. Please don't say go hard. Just trying to fit in. Does he know that this tomato
sauce on pizza? No, I had no idea. I thought it was um, that's a boomer Andy take. I don't think so.
I don't think that's a boomer take. I'm going for defense this time. What about flavored crust? I
think stuffed crust pizza is amazing. Something about the way that it bakes inside the dough. I
don't know why, but it, it doesn't taste like any other cheese I've ever eaten and I can't,
you cannot, it's impossible to replicate. It's impossible. However, stuffed crust pizza gets made.
I don't know how, but it just tastes so much better than if I don't know. It's a completely,
it's like a weird unique flavor. It's really good. What's the worst pizza topping? Um, probably ham.
I don't get, I just, ham to me is just, what do you mean? What, what, what wrong, wrong? I know,
but it's just not, a lot of times you get ham on pizza. It's like that cubed ham, the cubes.
I don't really want cubed ham on pizza. He does actually hate meat. I don't know if you were here
three days ago, but I talked about eating corned beef hash out of the can. Not in the way that you
think. I don't, that's not accurate. What should I take? I'm going to take these and deposit them
because this is like a tank. So maybe eventually I can make like a tank run. They sell corned beef
hash in a can. I, yeah, that's like how you, that's how you get it. Unless you go to a breakfast
place and they make it kind of fresh to order. The egg hash corned beef hot sauce concoction sounds
fucking awesome. It's, it is, it's wonderful. For those of you that weren't here, I'm going to,
I'll tell you again. Serving of the corned beef hash out of the can, put it in, you heat it up
on the stove. Get it nice to exactly where you want it. Do one, one like over medium egg or over
easy, over hard, however you like it. That goes on top. You're going to doop, doop, doop, doop with
Tabasco right on top of the egg. You're going to have one slice of toast and you're going to have
three heirloom tomatoes that have been cooked potentially in the oven. You're going to make
more than three probably because you know, you're making this just nice and slow, low.
Those tomatoes, you know, you're not trying to cook them. You're just trying to kind of heat
them up a little. That's stoner food. No, it is not. That is, that is a great breakfast. If you
go to a breakfast place, they definitely have a corned beef hash meal and it is what I just
described to you. It is the exact thing I just told you. Make it for me then. Some of you are
going to do it. Even if you don't do the tomato part, I would say you should probably put something
on there. That's not just eggs and meat. You know, something to give you a little bit of your
vegetable count for the day. I'm going to go down. You'd add rice to that. However you want to
make it yours, right? Go for it. That's just how I do it. Bigfoot or Sasquatch? Do you confirm or
deny? What is it? Is it Bigfoot or Sasquatch or is it Bigfoot and Sasquatch? What's your question?
Are you asking if it's Bigfoot or Sasquatch or are you asking if I think they both exist?
I think it's two different people. Are there any cryptids that you believe in strongly?
Um, not necessarily. I mean, I do think there's probably stuff in the deep sea that we haven't
seen that could be to the level of what you're describing. Look at the weird animals that are
down there. There are animals that have lights on their heads. There are some really wacky deep sea
creatures. We have not really seen it all. So I'm one of those people where if it's kind of possible
then it's possible. But I'm not going to sit here and tell you that the Loch Ness Monster is,
you know, 10,000 feet deep in the ocean. I know it. I don't know. Maybe. Possible. I don't know.
Do I think there's a big naked guy walking around in the woods behind your backyard?
No, not necessarily. I don't, I don't know. Like do I think there's like a like a 15 foot
hairy naked guy that's walking around just kind of hanging out in the woods? I don't think so.
I could, I don't know. I don't know what the answer is. If you ever do see Bigfoot,
I feel like, I don't know, would Bigfoot just run? Oh, shit. Oh, shit. Another person saw me.
Oh, I'm naked and I'm running around. Or would Bigfoot be like, listen, I know this is fucked up
looking and I know, you know, you found me. But let me tell you something. I've got a secret bank
account in that secret bank account. I've got fucking $6 million. Don't say shit. And I will,
I will fucking sell you the money. I'll sell you a fucking $10,000 a day. I don't know.
It's piercing work with the fire. He can speak. I don't know. Scammer Bigfoot.
You can just listen. Let me tell you something. I've got a bank account with $10 million in it.
All you need to do is you need to send me 50 and then I'll send you 10,000 next week.
Bigfoot's a scammer? That's not, that's not what I meant. But that's funny. You're my favorite
popsicle streamer. Can we, can we do the email that has not been put in the chat in like six
years? I think that's what they're referring to. Yep. Always take that every time. If you're the
fire character, it's a quick tip for you. The movement speed is what absolutely killed me last
time. So I got to focus on it for a little bit. I'm never going to play this game. Don't give me
any tips. So let me, I have to tell you, don't say that you're never going to do something.
Trust me. I have experience here saying you're never going to do something in the one small
off chance that you do, that you end up doing that. You're going to think back and go,
I should never have said I'm never ever doing this. I'm not though. But what if like in like
a year you come back and it's like your favorite game, dude? You never know. I want that archman.
I will never trust Bigfoot. You're calling me Bigfoot. Like, oh, Jerma is Bigfoot. He's
Jerma is a cryptid. He's Bigfoot. Don't you guys make fun of how small I am all the time?
What's going on there? Yeah, there's, there's a lack of consistency.
Like a consistency, small foot. That's not even, that's not even funny. That's not, that is so
easy. Come on. You're not Bigfoot. You're small foot. That's easy. That's way too easy. So boss,
that thing is doing a lot of work. I'll take this again. The boss. All right, back up. Did I pick
anything? Yeah, I did. I'm going to deposit the boots. There's no way you can be Bigfoot. You
smell like ranch and there's no ranch in the woods. Why can't I just take a bottle of ranch
into the woods and drink it in the woods? Well, I don't understand the logic behind that. There's
no ranch in the woods. Why can't I just have it in my backpack while I'm walking around? I kind
of shredded that guy. Um, I'm not going to use this, but I'd rather deposit these because I want
to be able to make a tanky character. Why are you not denying that you smell like ranch? I don't
smell like ranch dressing. I don't even like ranch dressing, ranch dressing to me. And you're
going to think I'm gross. This is the take that a lot of people determine if they like you as a
person or not, which is like relax. I think that ranch is just a, it's just to me, I like blue cheese
better anywhere I would be putting ranch blue cheese is used in that scenario. What should I
take here? Ranch to me is just not quite there. And I would prefer blue cheese to be the thing
instead of ranch. I get that opinion because I'm a huge Buffalo chicken fan. Buffalo chicken is
probably my favorite food. One of the top three favorite foods ever. And that combination has
just been burned in my brain forever. This dude eats crayons. He's lying. If they're dipped in
blue cheese. Um, no, I don't, don't give them any more. Don't give them anything else. Don't
give them anything else. That'll be, that'll be, that'll be, that'll be on like Twitter.
Everybody eats crayons. Everybody eats, everybody eats crayons. Everybody eats crayons. Hey, did you
hear? Everybody eats fucking crayons today. No, don't give them anything else. Don't give them
anything more. It's X now idiot. Oh, oh, that's right. It is. I, okay. All right. What are you
talking? Okay. Well, whatever. I'll see you on, I'll see you on X. Is that what it is? That it is
what it is. Yeah. No one said that. Don't call it that. I, I don't pay very much attention to
Twitter. I don't even use social media. I don't know what the fuck is going on. Guys. I use
Twitter to like DM people and tell you when the stream is taking this DMing, like other content
creators and streamers for, Oh, Hey, you want to, I'm doing this like house flipper thing.
Like that's what I use Twitter for is, is for like talk, talking to colleagues.
How come you didn't DM me because I'm not going to bro. I actually think I had a pretty good one.
Let me see. Let me see. Let me look at my notes. Let's see. Did I have a good one? I feel like I'd
had one recently. Maybe not. Really? I thought I did. Damn. I still have the whole, um,
Adam Sandler movie notes. No shit. I fell off big time. Yeah. I fell off. Absolutely. I completely
fell off. I thought I had a couple of like draft reads for you guys. Yeah. I fell off. That's all
right. He's well, he's washed up now. He's all washed up. Hey, I'd rather be all washed up than
dirty. Hmm. Okay. Dad. Minus two, minus two. No, no, no. Stop that. Minus two dad. That's something
that I would be. Cry me a river, small foot. Ban that person for life. Do it actually. Execute order
number 666. Too many, too many Dantas. Too many Dantas. Too many. Somebody's on stage doing that.
And like the whole crowd's like, too many. These are too many of these. Stop it. Boo. Stop. Too many.
Too many. This dude's just got the microphone going.
He will get up and leave. All right. No, he really, he really just fucking washed up now.
Yeah. Like that was, that was awful. You hear how many times you do the Star Wars, like interlude
thing. Like he fucking fell off. All right. I'm going to the well. I can take a lot more hits.
This is great. I'm actually happy about this. All right. Well then magnet. I went to hash house
at Gogo recently. It was pretty nice. This is great at the link. All right. I'm depositing the
tank boots. It feels going to be better. All right. And then I'm going to do well. Then let's do blood
stain first. Blood stain first because I want to see what that does. I need movement speed
and damage going forward. Really, really, really important because I'm way too slow right now.
Whoa. Really? Double flamethrower. Is it a double flamethrower? Oh, that's actually kind of insane.
All right. Attack speed or let's just max this out. It's so much worse now. It's a,
that's going to be a boss killer though. I think it should be really good against boss.
All right. Let's get the first one and nine, eight, okay. Burn chance. All right. Now we go
to the other side or should I get the, I'm going to go, while there's still 10 minutes,
I'm going to get this first and then we're going to go to the well and then get the second piece.
All right. So when I have the full pieces, where do I take it back to that? They alter. You don't.
You just hold it. Oh, what does it do? All right. I need movement speed now.
Stop. I got to stop picking stuff. That's not moving speed. This is becoming a problem.
You married into it. Oh, why would you come back then? We'd be closed.
Movement speed. Take it. Yes. Just do it. I know the other one's good, but I'm going to get a bunch
of levels right now. Again, do it again. Back speed again, moving speed, more health, more piercing.
All right. I don't even think I don't have to get the magnet anymore because I just got two of them.
Putting it up your whole life. You just don't know. You need to call it.
I need to know what I stand to win. Stand to win everything. Call it. Well done. That is my favorite
scene of any movie ever. I think it is. Look at that melting. This is, and this is an act boss,
right? This is like act two. Gone. Dead. You think Bigfoot would enjoy your screams?
No, Bigfoot's probably one of the people in here just like talking shit every day.
I wouldn't be surprised. I imagine like, you know, like a lot of like the boxing is like really kind
of coming back. Like a lot of people getting involved in boxing. There's like chest boxing and
there's like, you know, creator clash and like there's a lot of like boxing events. What if
somebody boxed Bigfoot and Bigfoot just beat the ever living fucking shit out of this person?
It's like, oh, like German versus Bigfoot. And we find somebody that's like literally fucking
eight feet tall. That's like three or four hundred pounds jacked. Unbelievable in unbelievable
condition. And I think I can win. And I just get the absolute fucking shit beat out of me.
Like it's ridiculous. It is ridiculous. And it shows me before the fight signing a bunch of
documents saying, do not stop this fight. I will win. And he just like picks me up overhead and
like throws me into the fucking crowd after like six straight minutes of like, like to my face.
And then zoom in on some people in the front row that are holding stacks of money,
the cigars and the emails cheering because it's like, oh my God, this was free money.
This was so much fucking. This was so free. Now, why would you lose? Because that's funny.
I don't even want to throw one punch. I want to taunt in the ring when the bell rings
and then it's just me being hit in the head over and over again.
I go out to the outside of the ring and I'm picking up like objects to hit him with.
Like this is illegal. Like, like it's over. The fight's over. I've been disqualified.
I'm picking up like mic stands and trying to hit him in the fucking head with it and stuff.
Like I've already lied. I've been disqualified. It's personal at this point. This is a Yakuza
sub story. No, I'll never truly step into the ring. I couldn't. All the medical problems I
still have now. It's a fun little thing to think about, but no, I really want to just stand still
right here. Oh, I can't fuck shit. All right. All right. Don't I've got four minutes. Don't lose it
now. Where's my movement speed? Pause the tank boots and we got to go. Oh, wait, the other
blood stain. I'll do that right now. Am I going the right way? It's not here. There's so much
shit here. I can't get it all. How do I feel? I still feel like I'm so slow. All right. Get in
the ring with Bigfoot and it's like a big deal. We do weigh-ins. Yeah. Let's take, let's take a look.
Bigfoot has a about 40 inches of reach on a, on German 985, which is not surprising.
Only 40. I don't know. I don't know much about how that works. All right. There's the other piece
coming to my eye. Come on, get out of my eye. All right. I got the whole thing now.
So now what? What does this do for me now? Do I have to do anything special or just fight the boss
with it on? I'm looking for health and movement speed. Just fight the boss. Okay. You're never
going to open crates. Uh, we're going to do it after this. Whatever happens in this run.
Face damage. Yeah. So short. There's money down here. Okay. I think, uh, like I said,
in one of the tank boots, I think that's an interesting thing to build whole health.
Holy shit. All right. All right. All right. There's no excuse now. I see movement speed.
I have to get it. It doesn't matter what else is up there. I still feel like I'm a little
too slow, but I'll, I'll concentrate. I'll try these. This is the boss killer build right now.
It's not the clear waves build. Ooh, head this way quick. Oh, get it all. Attack speed damage.
Yes. Movement speed. Uh, crit chance or attack speed. All right. That's going to be it. I hope
this is enough. No, it's hard to see the fire in front of me. Healing potion. Oh my God.
Movement speed or health. What the fuck? He's dead. I already, I don't, I see, I killed him.
He's already dead. What did so much damage? Something hurt a lot. Whoa. Trying to keep
him close. Not that close though. Oh, the item. That's right. Ooh, you survived and I got the
item. It's the item. Holy shit. That thing is incredible. Thanks for telling me that.
Unlocks trait type, spin and puncture, money, and then the rat ring. Very nice. Is it available to
buy? Or is it just now in the item pool? Cool. I think I'm getting ready to be able to do the
second level. What is this one? Level 100 kill 50,000 enemies with effects. All right. So this
character is all the upgrades are available. Everything is available. It's just money now.
Cool. All right. Let's open some crates in TF2. Probably only going to be live for like another
30, 40 minutes. I know this is a short one, but yeah, I'm just streaming when I can. And when I
think I feel like it, when I think I'm having a good time. Here we are. It's time to gamble.
Gamble. Oh, I'm not going to buy these yet because I don't know which one I want. All right. I'm
going to just take a quick pee break. When I come back, we'll open some crates. We can examine them,
see if they're any good. I've only got like 20 keys. I know that's, that's a lot, but I don't
want to like overdo it. I'm just trying to clear out some of the old cases that I have. We'll see.
I'll be right back.