So I feel a little bit bad that I haven't been covering as many games as I used to on this channel.
I used to go over patch notes, game updates, how I felt about them, and I haven't done it in a very long time.
So I wanted to play catch-up with myself, in a sense, and go over all of them.
All the patches and updates that I wanted to cover that I didn't get a chance to cover over the last three years.
So this one's probably gonna be quite a long one.
We're gonna go over all these patches and we're gonna start with Team Fortress 2.
Team Fortress 2, the invasion update.
Get yourself excited. Are you excited? Well, you should be.
We're talking about patches here. Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the patch video.
So Team Fortress-
Hey, hey, hey. Whoa, whoa. You're fast-boarding right now.
I just wanna make sure your fingers hold. You're doing that intentionally? Is that another mistake?
I added a drop-down area to Red's last and adjusted lighting in various areas.
What's interesting, though, is they finally fixed the direct deck settings on light poles.
Remember how annoying that was with the light pole?
Okay, listen, I-
I sometimes- you don't have to skip all of Overwatch.
That was a pretty big deal of games coming out soon.
Look, this video took me like three months to make, so I don't wanna be like a dick about it.
But if you could just pick something so I could at least feel like it mattered-
There's one for Nazgoth here.
Sonic Boom actually finally got the nerf it deserved. It's now under eight seconds for a cooldown.
Yep.
And they fixed a couple of crashes, the desktop launcher, the crash on exit.
Thank God we can now not have to deal with that.
And the game will never turn on ever again after May 31st.
It's true.
Moving right along, we got another patch-
No, look. There's no reason for you to go this fast.
Okay, I'm just gonna be very frank with you. Take your finger off that button right now.
Right now. If you have any respect-
The first sin.
Why is Dark Souls 2 even on here?
I'm just gonna hang out. I'll be over here on my phone.
Got a couple new apps to check out. I downloaded FaceSwap. You know, FaceSwap, you can do it with your dog and it's really funny.
I got a new keyboard app, too. I'm not sure if you've heard of it. It's called Key. It's up in Key.
You can make a little tune, it's pretty bold. I got a couple more games for the tune as well.
What the hell is this?
Hold on.
Pause the video for a second. Pause it!
You're in a different video right now.
I haven't even made this video yet. You are at least 20 to 30 uploads in the future.
So you're going to listen to me very closely and very carefully.
You're going to rewind a few months and you're going to stop, okay?
Very simple instruction.
There you go. Right here, right here. Stop, stop, stop.
Doesn't matter where. Stop right here.
In fact, you might-
Yeah, I'm overlapping here.
Pull it forward like two inches or so.
On the bar? On the bar?
Almost there.
Almost there. One more.
Got it. Perfect.
These are my patch notes.
And these just came out today.
I haven't even seen these yet.
You picked a perfect place to stop.
So, let's see what they changed.
They're actually shrinking me again.
This is the second time it's happened.
We should all look for Dermot's current height.
He's been causing performance issues.
He couldn't easily fit into a clown car.
With this change, clown car videos are now much more accessible.
I don't want to do clown car videos.
What are they talking about?
My lumberjack outfit is going to get removed too.
No, that is bullshit.
I'm keeping my lumberjack outfit on.
What else do we got?
This patch is fucking terrible so far.
40% more vacation vlogs.
No, I'm not doing vacation videos.
No way.
I would rather do 100 clown car videos than one vacation video.
So, opting out of this one, as you could say.
It's downloading.
When did I do that?
I didn't press any button.
I didn't accept anything.
There was no cancel or anything.
Nothing's working here.
Do I seriously have to rip out my ethernet cable?
I do. I don't want this patch.
Hold on a second.
I had all these installed.
I'm connected to my whole damn house.
I think that's it.
Is it?
God damn it!
Ow!
That's the cable.
I gotta put that back in.
I want to watch Better Call Saul season 2.
I can't...
Hello?
Look, you are going to have to call back at a different time.
I'm in the middle of some shit right now.
And I need...
Look, please put me on the do not call list!
Fucking asshole!
Ah!
Your service has been temporarily disconnected.
That's not it.
I think I might throw up.
I hope not.
What is this?
What is that?
Why do I have a sneeze switch?
Please leave a message.
This is it, right here.
Whoa!
Colors!
Gone.
I can't see anything.
I'm blind.
I must have pulled out the HDMI.
Oh boy!
Somebody's gonna have to call.
Where's my mom?
Where's my phone?
Mom?
Fuck!
How much time do I have on that?
I don't know.
I can't tell.
I can't see.
I'm deaf.
I don't know if it feels like there's a part of me on this one.
This is a weird feeling.
I kind of just feel like I don't exist.
I can't hear and I can't see.
Is there a way I can...
I can't come to it.
I'm gone!
One...
Two...
Three...