Hello, everybody. It is Jerma again. I've got a medic gameplay for you today or
Tonight I've done like three of these in a row, but um this is on gold rush
People hate gold rush people think it's dumb people think it's newbish people think but whatever you know a lot of people think the
Things that I do potentially be newbish, but I don't care
Before I start I think this is really funny
this sniper up here
Kept on getting hit over and over and over again
By a scout that was going into the resupply and getting a ball and hitting him over and over again
Like I thought that was great, and I'm gonna start to do that because I think it's funny
But I'm medic with Chris Krieg and the Crusaders crossbow and the ubersaw
Kind of an odd combination, but I hate the Blutzogger. I think it just gives you
Good for battle medics not good for people like me that don't really like to shoot
I mean, I'm pretty aggressive as a medic, but I don't like you know shooting people with
Like needle guns or the crossbows I do it every so often but not as much as I want to I crits this engineer
Because there's a reason for it there were no real offensive people on the team
It was I think the two pyros and like three engineers and three snipers or something
So it was kind of hard to to get anyone I get this soldier though
Which was I was pretty proud of that I was actually surprised that he didn't kill me
But um I think I fixed the audio
Softness from the last video the first one that I did and the video should be a little clearer now, too
hopefully
But let's get back to talking about this this by his is dead. No he's not
I remember because I remember this part. I freaked out because I didn't expect to get ubered and
after getting ubered you know
you think that the person would stick with you maybe for at least a second or two, but I he was doing the
Typical you know run around and uber like eight people in one shot. You know what I mean, but I crits this pyro
He kills one person and then just stands here, and I'm saying over Mike
I keep saying dude. What are you doing like and we lose somebody caps it behind us, and I think right here
I was complaining to that pyro saying things like you did a wonderful job
And I commend you for your hard work, but he was just standing there
I don't know if it was like somebody messaged him or something
He killed somebody and it was just standing there
whatever
This is the next part of dust bowl
I'm sticking with the medic. This is gonna be mostly medic gameplay. This is actually pretty cool. How we do this we
We don't really have any sentry guns built up these and one of these engineers
I think skit gets one in the very end of the gameplay, but for the most part we do not have a
Viable sentry gun so I
End up rocking with a soldier, and we we do pretty well
It's this guy up here. He's he seems like he's a pretty smart guy, and he doesn't want the crits Creek
He's like. I don't think I want this you'll hear him. It's pretty funny watch ready. Oh
Come on say it
He's like okay
Where is it? Come on say it
There it is. I do not promise anything, and I keep saying it's all right, dude
Just go so he shoots a couple of rockets in there crits. He kills one or two people I think
Which I'm totally fine with
It is the you know the opening of the doors you know
There's nothing really unless you give me ubers are popping out and stuff like that unless you're like some crazy person
It's hard to kill a lot of people because most people stay back
You get a couple of people that will just run out, but not very many see I'm pretty scared right here
I get like stuck on the stairs. I think I'm gonna get killed because their whole team started to come out
And I make my way out of here I figure oh, we're still you know they're all out there and
This is a spy hi, and I kill him, and then I took a walk out here
And it's like oh my tea. Oh my god, and it's their whole team and I
Die and if you're wondering I have the medic girl hair. I think it's the funniest thing in the world
I will never take it off. I think it's so funny go the wrong way with this soldier for a second
Don't know why I played this map
at least 500 times
But as you can see we are trying to defend for like 16 minutes
I I don't understand why people do that I
Assist on killing this engineer this spy I get him
But oh boy. I'm out of here. I I don't understand why why servers
Make it 16 17 20 minutes still for defense times. It's just stupid. I don't know it
It's just it doesn't make any sense like Chris this guy. I thought we were gonna lose he gets backstabbed
I go on this guy instead doesn't matter. He was using the direct hit which is not the best thing to crits
But he was the only thing right there
He the guy said sorry Jerma, and I just was like it's all right. There's nothing we could have done
But that was the first time that they had a good push, and we stopped it
And it happens to quite a few times actually happens at least two or three more times
Spy snaps that engineer, but I can't do anything about it. I can't be bothered with that right now
But yeah, they they they do two or three really really big pushes
And we don't even have a sentry gun, and we seem to stop it. I was pretty amazed by that. I thought it was really cool
But they are really starting to push now
Spy gets on the point, but he dies immediately
see right now, this is this is where they're they're really starting to push and
Obviously I thought we were gonna die, so I'm just kind of standing around healing anyone I can and
It's at this point. We know when most people kind of just give up and they go let him cap it whatever
But we kind of were pretty resilient. We didn't we didn't let anybody take nothing from us
I got that soldier with a good crit and I I know I don't like the ubersaw that much
I think it's a I think it's fun, but I mean I know it just makes me a bad medic
And that was a complete fail over crits right there not over as a complete fail crits right there
Both on both parts my part and his part. I probably should have told him. I was doing it. I just kind of did it
but like I was saying before I
I'm not a big fan of the ubersaw because it makes you really start to think aggressively and you'll jump into fucking death
You know I mean like oh, I got my ubersaw
I want another uber for free and you'll just start swinging madly and get yourself killed which I do quite often when I have
The ubersaw and I get back stabbed right there. I bumped into a spy, but I was too stupid to think about it
So I'm gonna get near the end of this gameplay here in another minute or two
these guys really start to push and
Like I said we push them back a couple times and I was pretty impressed with the team
Holding this point right here without a sentry gun because usually this place just drops within a second of it being available
You know what I mean like right now. It should be over
we stick with it and
Ultimately, I'm gonna spoil it for you like I just said I'm gonna end it soon because we lose and it's right here
Oh, no, maybe not
Jerma saves the day
But it's ill-fated. I crits this guy one more time. I think we get a couple more kills with it
He kills this push that they were had on the right side here
Four or five kills actually it was pretty good
But it ends up not being enough because as you can see how all of us are at like less than 15% health
so
they push and push and push and we pull
I guess you could say
No
We stopped it one more time. That was the last time we stopped it and this is when it starts to get ugly
You GL why you ain't got no alibi because you are fucking ugly
It's hard to do commentary for a medic because you don't you kind of really do the same things over and over again
You know you kind of just yeah, I like it. I wouldn't be able to do like a scope sniper
Commentary because you don't mean you yeah, I scoped in I shot that guy and it's actually pretty cool
We got rid of their the medic was in this tunnel back here
And we got rid of the medic and we got rid of the it was a heavy and a pyro
So we ruin this push, but yeah, it's good. Oh
Backs to have our us
That's a good spy. He got me a couple times
but yeah, like I said, it's kind of hard to do to do commentary for medic only because
You're kind of just running around you know over healing people and
Unless you really start to swing people and swing people you know you take them to swing lessons
Unless you really start to to go crazy with like you know
Like you use the blue soccer or the needle gun and you get like ten kills in one life like a battle medic or something
But for the most part it's hard to do commentary and lose at the same time like we just did
But yeah
Hopefully you guys enjoyed this video, and if you did let me know like subscribe do whatever you want, but yeah
There's more coming