Hey, what's going on everybody? Welcome back to Germacraft. I know it's been a quite a
while since I came up with a Germacraft episode, but I'm going to give you a whole list of
excuses right now. All right. So the holidays were around and why am I holding my bed? What
happened last episode? Did I, did I, my bed should be in here, right? Yes. Okay. So what
happened is obviously the holidays came around and I didn't really have a whole lot of time
to play this game because it takes a while. You got to sit down and really do stuff for
a couple hours. And I didn't really have that couple hours to really sit down and play.
So, but now I do. So let's start playing, huh? What, what is going on here? What is
going on with the side of my house? Jeez Louise. Oh, okay. I know I want that there.
I want that there. So today we're going to do a couple of things in this episode. I'm
going to do this. I'm going to go on a grand adventure because obviously if you watched
from the very beginning in episode one, I said, Oh, don't worry. By Christmas time,
I'll have a castle. And as you can completely, totally tell that is absolutely not happening
and did not happen. So I'm going to go out and go on a crazy adventure and try to kill
a bunch of stuff. Okay. I got the sword now. We're good. Do I need anything else? Oh, got
to eat this rotten flesh before I die. Keep eating it. Oh yeah. Poisoned. So let's, let's
just go. I'm going to go out there. I'm going to try and find, I'm going to try and find
a new spot to hang out. Cause in reality, realistically, this is just too far away from
all of civilization. So I'm going to have to find somewhere else. So say goodbye to
this house for now. I don't think, I don't know if I'll ever come back to it or not,
but yeah, let's say goodbye. Let's wave to the stupid sea house that never really went
anywhere. So I'm going to sing a goodbye song to the castle that never was. So as we see
it in the distance there, let's all wave goodbye to it. Goodbye. And let's sing my song to
the castle. It starts raining. It started raining. Oh my God. Perfect.
My castle never ended up completing. And I'm scared of what's going to happen in the
next episode. But it's okay if we stay true to each other. We get up on a mountainside
and find some other place to live. Goodbye castle. I got to find my way up and down the
stairs. I'm going to find my way inside of this mountain cab. We're going to go goodbye
castle. And that's how we go. We end the song there. Let's just, why am I going this way?
Goodbye castle. It was great knowing you. Let's go. You're probably wondering why I'm
back in the castle. It's because I didn't take any of the stuff that I'm supposed to
take. I left it all here. So I'm going to take that. That stuff can stay. I need the
bed though. The bed is an absolute must and I didn't, I left without it. So okay, bye.
Bye now castle. Bye. Trying to get up this whole mountain here is kind of being a little
more difficult than I initially thought it was going to be. I have to scale this whole
mountain and I'm trying to do that. And while it's cold here, oh well, I'm trying to jump
up here. I just can't get over here. Maybe I should just make it. I'm like really seriously
trying to think of a good way to do this. How to make it. Maybe I should make the next
house on top of this mountain maybe? I don't know, but I'm, whoa, what, what? Oh God, I'm
starving to death again. How many times is this going to happen to me? Eating raw beef.
Oh my, you know what, I'm going to eat the whole damn thing. Oh hey, that's my ring tone.
Hold on, somebody's calling me. My ring tone is a duck, if you can hear that. Hold on,
I've got to answer this. Hold on. Hello? Hi mom. What's up? I'm making a commentary for
YouTube. Yeah, so I made it on top of the mountain. That's a good thing. So do I build
my house here is the real question. I don't know, I know, you know what, I'm going to
build it down here because this is just going to be a pain in the ass if I ever decide to
do anything. So I'm going to come down here. I'm going to die if I jump down there. Do
not die. If I die right now, it is a very, very bad thing because I really don't want
to come all the way back here again. All right, we're good. We're doing some scaling, some
good mountains. Oh, look at that. Look at that parkour. All right, right here. I'm going
to do it right here. The house is going to be built right here. Good shore view. Got
a nice little spot right here. Going right here. Eventually, I'm sure I'll put wood here.
Or maybe I might even just go back to the old house to, you know, scavenge the supplies.
I don't know. But I had to get out of that place. That place was ridiculous. And that
reminds me of a story. Story time. Okay. We can talk about story time right now. So when
I say get out of this place, it brought me back to when I was in college. When I was
in college, hold on, let me, because I got plenty of dirt. I can make a little quasi
fake house. Okay. So when I was in college, I lived in the dormitories for a couple years,
and then I decided to move, obviously, when you're like a junior and a senior in college,
you want to move to like the bigger, cooler, like apartments, because you want to be like
a cool person. Like I'm not in the dorm. I'm in the apartments, because I'm the man. That's
kind of what goes through your head sometimes. So I got an apartment, and I got the apartment
without looking at it. I didn't really know, because I was late to put my thing in to get
signed up for the dormitories. So I kind of had no choice. I had to just kind of run and
find an apartment last minute. And I found this little place. I didn't see it. I just
knew that it existed. It was about, I don't know, maybe half a mile away from the college.
So I made a phone call, got the whole thing secured. Okay, let me get the lease. Where
is it? Blah, blah, blah. And I came to realize, I came to find out later, when I actually
went there, that it was a box. The place wasn't even a house. It was just literally a box
like this. Just like, it was like this big. It was one little, it was a studio apartment,
right? So it was one small room with a bathroom like right over there. And it was horrible.
And I had to live there. I had to share it with somebody. So I had this one box room
that was probably, I'm going to be realistic, it was probably really as big as this Minecraft
room I just made. And I had to share it with two people. Well, one person, so we had two
people in there. But I just remember that it was one of the most ridiculous things ever,
and I had to stay there for the whole year. So I guess the moral of the story is if you're
going to live somewhere, make sure you like check out where it is first, besides like
just buying it and being like, yeah, I'll show up, thanks. Because I had a lot of bad
experiences there. It just got to me after a while. It just stressed me out. The fact
that there was just this tiny little room, and I couldn't have, I had no privacy, I was
sitting right next to the person that lived right next to me. So it really, really was
a real pain in the ass. And yeah, but that's the story of Jerma's box house that he really
actually existed and lived in. I eventually moved out of there, though. I got out and
I went back to live with some of my friends in college. But yeah, don't ever buy real
estate without seeing it, or you'll puke. All right, let's get this thing. This should
be the last layer right here. And then I should be able to make the roof, put the bed down,
put a couple lights in it, and go to sleep.