Hey, what's up? What's going on? We said that the sponsors were still in the description.
Yeah, well, whatever. That's fine. I fixed it. It's all right. Stop. What? It's a free ad.
No, I mean, look. Hey, they supported that show. Okay. I'm fine with that. I don't care.
You got a mustache? What do you think? Do you think it's still there? What do you think? Should
we do another vote? Hmm. We could. Yeah, I mean, you can't if you guys want to bet on this. You
absolutely can. I just want to let you know that I have this is on you. If you bet and you lose and
you lose all your channel points. I'm that's not on me that you decided to do that. You don't have.
I would not bet on this if I this is it could be anything. This is actually just flipping a coin
in the air. You have no idea. I just do a regular poll. Don't need to do a bet. Well, there it is.
All right. Is it there? Oh, okay. I have nothing to do with this. I'm just saying if you get mad
at me after this, if I open up the chat over here and I look over and I'm like, dude, what the fuck?
Like you fucking scammed me out of my point. No, I didn't do anything. This is I'm not telling you
to do this. I'm gonna say this is easy points. How would you know? You wouldn't really know
that it was easy because you don't know if it's there. Are you Kappa in right now? I'm not going
to tell you anything because the voter the poll is still up, so I'm not going to say anything to
you. We get some more gif emotes as sub emotes. I'm the worst streamer on Twitch in regards to
this kind of stuff. I just I don't know emotes and new things. There hasn't been a new sub emote.
I think I have like 100 slots and like 24 of them are taken up right now. Maybe I just I don't know.
But what would they even be? You know, okay, here's the thing about emotes and emote slots.
I don't know if I had this opinion years ago. Leather jacket. I fucking clicked on the button
to start a prediction and it blue screened my computer. Okay, well, wait, is it over?
All right, hold on. Hold that thought. Hold that thought. Is it still there?
All right, is the voting closed? Okay, here we go. Are you guys ready?
Oh, is it still there? Oh, God, is it still there? No. Sorry, everybody, if you voted
that it is there. It's not there anymore. It was it got it was so gross. I had to get rid of it.
I'm sorry. It was just it was causing me physical pain. I know people said, dude,
you have to trim it. I'm not a facial hair person. I'm not. It looked good. No, it looked good on a
fucking webcam through the internet, which you guys don't understand. I have to make this very
clear to anybody watching this stream. The amount of pixels that exist on any type of webcam or
camera or anything, even just this right here. You're not seeing a clear picture of my face.
You're seeing a kind of clear picture. It's good enough. It's 480p or 720 or something that's
scaled down or scaled up. But the issue is you don't really this blends together a lot.
For instance, huge zit. You probably didn't even notice. Maybe you did notice that. But let me tell
you something in real life. Like if I go in the mirror and I lean in, it's it's ghastly. It's
ghastly. But you just can't see that. You can kind of tell that there's something there. But if I when
I had that mustache and when it's blurring and blending together from the webcam, it looks fine.
But when I lean in and I'm looking in the mirror and I got a light on, I look like a scarecrow. I
look like the scarecrow from The Wizard of Oz. It's just like it's just these spines that they
just point in random directions. It looks bad. I mean, it's ghastly. It is. Dude, you look normal.
Yeah. You didn't even do a full shave. It's still there. Yes, I, I, yeah. But dude, okay. It's been,
when was the last time I streamed? Three days ago? Two days ago? You look like you got smoothed out
by a clothing iron. That's a really specific compliment and insult together. I know exactly
what you mean. And that's funny. But anyways, yeah. Okay. So when I shaved two days ago, three days
ago, this is what just happens when it grows back. Smoothed out by a clothing iron. Tiny face cam.
It's not tiny. It's a, it's a perfectly normal size. All right. So here's the deal. Here's what's
going on. Let me explain a few things. Ah, you're a grease ball. My hair is wet. I took a shower and
it's going to dry in an hour. And you're going to be like, whoa, what does your hair look like?
Why does your hair look like shit today? It's because it's just wet and then it just dries.
I didn't put any product in my hair. I'm going to turn this way and it's going to be like this big
poof. And people are going to get a screenshot. Like zoom in right there. See his hairline is
going back. Do you see? Yeah, it is good. I can't wait to be ugly. Can I tell you? I can't wait till
I'm a gross old man just sitting there like, like skin sagging down like to here. I can't wait till
I'm fucking gross and old. Cause I'll tell you, well, let me, when you cross like 30, like 35,
yeah, I, you kind of don't really care that much about, oh my, I say when I turned 30 on my 30th
birthday, uh, I noticed that I had some thinning hair and I was like, no, no, no, no, no, no,
it can't be. No, not yet. I'm 30. No, no, no. Maybe if I can individually give each one of these
vitamins, dude, I would put olive oil in my hair, olive oil and tea tree oil. I would do like this
slurry and I would put it all in my head. I would put olive oil all over my head back when I was
30, 31. I was terrified of losing my hair. I was like, no, I can't, I can't, I can't go. Uh, so I
just, you know, read all these concoctions and, oh, you know, like tea tree oil stimulates hair
growth. I started drinking a lot of, uh, you know, a lot more water, a lot of green tea. Uh, and
I mean, at some point I kind of just gave up on that. I didn't really care anymore. So, uh, after
like 35, I'll tell you, if you're concerned about kind of your hair, if you're a guy and you're
concerned about hair loss, you go from this mode of, oh, this can't be happening to me. At some
point in, in your, in your twenties or your late twenties, early thirties, whatever it is, whenever
it starts to thin. And then you kind of just go, you know what? People age. Who cares? People age.
That's what happens when you turn 30, 40, 50. You age. Who cares? That's fine. I don't have a problem
with it anymore. How come you do the lamest shit when you get back from an event? I mean, like
Pac-Man? What are you talking about? Pac-Man world is, is lame. I, I mean, I guess that's your, you
know. This is my first what? You don't like Pac-Man world? Well, I'll tell you, Chatter. This was voted
on before the stream started. This was voted on by a bunch of your peers. So, um, you got other people
to be upset with. Your classmates, yeah. Dude, the olive oil. What'd you say? Dude, do baseball. It's way
cooler. Dude, I should just do another baseball stream. I actually like want to. So bad. I so badly
want to do that again. But it, you know, whatever. You move on. The next one. But anyways, we're going
to play Pac-Man world. What was I just talking about? It was something I was going to bring up
and I don't remember what it was. What the hell were we just talking about? No, before hair. Before
the hair loss thing. It was after mustache and before hair. Being old. No, that was part of the
hair. Eh, sorry. All right, I got a controller here. This is Pac-Man world. Oops. Being old?
Showering. I don't remember. Who cares? Does it really matter at this point? Camera. Yeah, we're
going to play Cult of the Lamb. That was on the poll. I'm telling you, you had. This is very. Why
is this so loud? Yeah. Cult of the Lamb and Sorcery Part 3 are going to be this week as well
as something else that I will be participating in. Um, I don't want to like announce it before
somebody else does. Maybe let me ask. Let me see if I can just announce it. But maybe I shouldn't.
Oh, fuck. I already said it, didn't I? I already did say it. That's right. I said it in the pre-stream
chat. Oh, oh, whatever. If I get confirmation, I'll formally announce it. Leak Andy. No, not
Leak Andy. All right, I'm ready. We're going to play Pac-Man world. The lamest thing I've done
since baseball. So let's go ahead and go. Start with English. OK, yes. Um, I have to be really
honest. I've put up this facade for a very long time and I'm like coming to terms with it right
now. I don't care about Pac-Man at all. Like I don't really like, oh, here we go. Pac-Man world.
Everyone, let's go. All the Pac-Man music. I kind of like don't care about any. Like I'm sitting here
going, oh, man, let's get hype for Pac-Man. It's a Pac-Man party. I mean, I think Pac-Man is cool,
but do I think he's this cool? I don't think so. All right, let's turn it up. Got seen. I mean,
he's cool. I do. Have I been pretending that I have to play every Pac-Man game that comes out?
Pac-Man made you. Now that's fair. Who is this? Who is Pac-Man?
Pac-Man's naked. Doesn't have like Spongebob pants on. Why is it weird for me to look at right now?
Isn't that weird? Something's weird about this. What is it? Why is it so different?
I don't know.
Pac-Mom. Doesn't he have pants on in Smash Brothers? Hold on. Whoa, this is actually 3D.
Oh, God, this is 3D. All right, hold on. Probably just got cut off. Wait, hold on. What does he look
like in Smash Brothers? Pac-Man Smash Brothers. Yeah, he does have. Yeah, that's right. I guess
I'm just, I just don't remember. I don't know why this is so weird for me to look at right now.
Okay, I'm back. All right, welcome to Pac-Man world. Over there is the ghost area. Watch out
for ghosts and eat all the Pac-Dots. The big dots are power pellets. Eat them to power up Pac-Man
and get the ghosts. Don't get careless. Power pellet effects wear off after a while. Yeah, I've played
fake fan. All right. Oh, wait a minute. This is actually pretty sick.
Wait, you can break stuff? What does B? How long does this last? All right, cool. Very cool. Oh,
Pac-Coins. This is a slot metal. Hang on to it and you'll be glad you did later. Wait, you can
throw shit? Wait, you can throw grenades. All right, cool. What does it want to do? Be careful,
Pac-Man. There are a lot of enemies up ahead. Try taking them out with the button dots. Okay.
Do you have any Pac-Dots? You can press B to perform a Pac-Dot attack. You have lots of dots
hold to charge a bomb attack. Is there a lock on? All right, that's pretty fun. How do you open chests?
What was that? Wait, this is like a Yoshi thing. Go back, go back, go back. Oh, did I miss something?
I mean, I'm 100%ing the game, so I feel you. What did I miss? No, did I miss something?
I already said Dollar General Andy. What does that mean? There's bananas up there. Oh,
there are bananas in the trees. You're right. Cool. All right, let's go. Oh, that's how you...
Ah, all right. So, that's what I'm missing. Cool. Oh, my God. It's been so... I've been waiting this
game for like 10 years. I'm going to really cherish it. I press A to float to the surface.
All right. How do I get down there? Oh, you can just float. So, if you're not a big Pac-Man fan,
that's fine. This is a remake of an old game for a big PlayStation. Pac-Man World, I believe,
was 1998? Scream already. I've screamed twice in 10 minutes of the stream starting. All right,
ban that guy for as long as it takes for them to understand what they did wrong,
which is probably two minutes. Okay, press them with a butt bounce. The green switch
only works one time. What does it do? Oh, all right. This is cute. What's wrong with this?
This is cute. This is a cute game. This is way better than Glover. I'll tell you,
factually. What matter of absolute fact? This is way better than Glover. A hundred times better.
And I love Glover. Glover is like one of my favorite N64 games.
Okay, when the switches effect wears off, this one only lasts a certain amount of time.
Just testing. That's a trampoline. Aim at the center with a butt bounce and bounce into the
air. But not before I go get the sneakers. Okay. Cool. All right. How do I get? Oh,
you can do a Sonic the Hedgehog bounce. Cool. Is this game hard or is this for actual kids?
Jump at the water surface to do a dolphin jump. Use it to get items above the water. Yep. Butt
bouncing. Treasure chest in the water. Needs something to do that though. All right. That's
fine. What's in here? Metal dot from the treasure chest. Metal dots allow you to walk underwater
while you're metallic. You're invulnerable. What's that? What's a goal? What's the actual goal of
this game? Is it like Banjo Kazooie? Is it kind of like Mario? Do I have to collect stuff? I think
I'm going to beat this game like in the next three hours. I think I'm going for it. Okay.
You've reached the checkpoint. Yep. Start over. Have you tried the rev roll? Hold Y and let go.
You can climb steep hills by using a rev roll. Really? Don't. I'm gonna. You can take those
enemies by hitting them with the rev roll. That's actually kind of fun. Oh, this game is pretty fun.
Okay. That's a elevator. Hit on a press Y to open the gate in front. Did I miss anything?
Look out. You can fall from here. Hold X while jumping to hang in midair. Try it if you're about
to fall. Okay. Easy enough. What's that? Oh! All right. What's this mean? What does it say? Two?
What does that say? Is that a two? Did I miss something? Blue switches are the strangest
switches. Pressing one lets you press two. Okay. Go back and. Okay. That's what it means. I get it.
This game looks pretty decent so far. Yeah. It actually kind of does. All right. Fuck all that.
What? What just happened? Okay. Cool. All right. What does that thing do? Is that just a button?
This is a fruit door. There are switches, bonus letters, and other things to find on the other
side. Sometimes there are even keys to rescue your friends with. Open all the fruit doors to
rescue your friends. How do you open the fruit door? I need an apple? How do I get an apple?
Pressing the yellow switch will cause DOS or power pills to appear. Oh, there we go. All right.
Do I have? Oh, that's what I got with my inventory. Cool. Let's go. The ghost boss
Hawkman statue is up ahead. See if you can smash it. I don't. Oh, I missed the thing with
top. I didn't think it was going to do that. Oh yeah. Here we go. Let's do it. Slot bonus.
So how do I bet? Okay. I got three coins. Do I have to stop it? Is this an? Is this a? All right.
We're looking for a banana. Banana. Stop. What are you doing? That wasn't a banana.
That was not even close. That was a lemon. Idiot. Banana. Stop. Do it again. Okay. So you need to do
two, one or two before. So where's the orange? Orange. Okay. It's banana. Orange. But what's
before banana? Cherry. Okay. Cherry. Stop on cherry. What are you talking about? I have no idea
what's going on. Can you read? I mean, can I read? All right. Peach.
I just made a million dollars. What did I just get? No miss. 10,000. One 10,000 one up.
All right. Cool. That's a good start. Corsairs Cove episode unlocked. Oh cool. I think should
two headphones go in for this? Oh man. That's actually kind of fun. I'm kind of excited. I'm
kind of excited. Pirate ship area. Choose your destination. All right. I guess I'm just going
to do this. All right. What's this? What is this thing? View movies in credits. Oh, we didn't watch
this. Oh, we got to watch this. We have to see what happens. Happy birthday. Whose birthday is it?
Oh my God. That looks good. If we wouldn't see them up there.
Pac-Man, just pick up a rock and throw it up there. Who's the dog? Is this a Pac-Man dog?
What? So wait, Pac-Man has to eat a pellet for a ghost to get hurt. What is that? What are the
rules there though? Like if I eat a power pellet and I throw a rock at a ghost, will it hit? Will
it hurt them? Do I have to physically bite them? Well, that doesn't make any sense because they
just pick, they just pick that guy up. There's obviously physical stuff going on. They're able
to touch and pick up things in the world. So you're telling me if I threw that, if I,
if I smash that glass pitcher over a ghost head, that it's going to go through them. That doesn't
make any sense. You're a fake fan. I'm just kidding around. I'm just messing around. I'm
just kidding around. I'm just messing around. I'm just messing around. I'm kidding. I'm just
messing around. Okay. But what if one of the ghosts, okay, what if, hold on, I actually have
a question. So the ghost, when Pac-Man eats a pellet, he turns into the Pac-Man thing. You
can eat the ghost turn blue. Could, could a ghost get like struck by lightning and die?
Like, could a ghost get like an anvil dropped on their head and die if it had nothing to do
with like a Pac-Man pellet? They already did that. All right, let's go. I'm ready. There's one.
Can you drown? I need a, I need a metal Mario. Is there a metal thing here?
Shit. Lemon. All right, let me up. All right, let's blow through this. Oh, what? Oh, cause they're
ghosts. Okay. Well, that fucks my whole logic up. Wait. Oh my goodness. All right. I got it.
All right, let's go. You're an idiot. I'm not an idiot. I didn't know that you had to, whatever.
I didn't know those were ghosts. They were pirates. Fuck off. Wait, give me this. Is there
another metal Mario anywhere? There's right here. Hold on. How do I get up there? How did you not
know? I mean, I know, I, I know how it, how it works. I just, it's a 3d platformer. Is it not
here anymore? So I need another metal Mario thing. Is there one over here? I don't think you can
drown. I don't think so. It doesn't feel like it. Can't go that way. Wall jump. This definitely,
I probably unlock it in a minute. What about the door? Oh, you definitely can't drown. I would have
drowned already. I feel like I missed a bunch of shit. Did I? Go back, go back. That made me so
mad. Did you see it? I'm glad I have the camera on because I was actually fucking mad for one
tenth of a second. It was just like, why'd you do that? Here we go. All right, we're good.
All right, gotta be quick. Strawberry. Can I get it again? Yeah, I felt my, my face go
like this. Oh, this P for Pac-Man. Idiot. I like the sound when he walks. I think this is a cute
game. How much is this game? There it is. Is the A? I don't know, dude. You bought it. I don't,
I don't know. I don't remember. I bought it a while ago when it first came out. Still don't have that.
30 bucks. I knew it was under like 30 or 40. There it is. Dude, you were waiting at game stuff at
midnight for this. Imagine getting that phone call. This is GameStop, where you can buy and
sell used games and make sure to check out Sonic the Hedgehog. It's coming out. By the way,
can I get an interview and pre-ordering Sonic the Hedgehog? No, thank you. When does, do you
guys do a midnight release for Pac-Man World Repack? Yeah, you betcha, man. Okay. Yeah,
should I write your name down as literally the only fucking person that's going to be here?
Yeah. Okay. Ooh, nice, nice, nice. Give me it. And then at midnight, I just don't go.
It's like, no, that's actually, I don't like, that's dumb. Don't they usually do the midnight
releases for different, you know, at the same time? Like it'd be, oh, you, but you can get
Pac-Man World Repack or The Witcher 3, right? Don't they usually do that? I need to see. Yeah,
where is it? I'm looking, I'm like looking at chat. I'm not looking. Yeah, guys, I might be
going like moving the character, but I'm, I'm reading what you're saying. Stop reading chat.
No, I will never stop reading chat. I will never stop picking up the one person here
that says that my hair looks like a mustache or that it looks like my room smells like fucking
pee, but I'm not going to, I'm going to always read this. Like, Hey dude, it looks like your
room smells like pee. I'm going to read, I'm going to read that. So like, I'm going to all be,
I'm going to be looking over here all the time. Where is it? Where is it? You guys told me I
missed it. Where? Get the C. I don't, I don't, there's no C here. Where is it? What letter is
that? Oh, how do I get that? Where's the C? Did you actually see it somewhere? Do I have that item?
How do I look? I want whatever that is. Did you guys actually see the C? I promise I'm
not being a fucking weirdo. Did anybody actually see it? No, I got to go back.
I'm going to die in this game and it's going to be embarrassing in level one.
Hmm. Oh my God. I just got so much. Now what? I can open the door down here. What is this?
You got a maze. Oh, okay. I've got to get everything. If I don't get every single one
of these out, delete my Twitch channel. You have to stick around. That was actually really close.
That was way too close. I was very uncomfortable. I know it's a joke, right? But I was uncomfortable
that whole time. I was, I was, I was not doing okay. Okay. You would have done it. No, I would
have found some dumb way to say, oh, well, I'll delete my Twitch channel in, you know, eventually
in 10 years. Or I would have said something dumb. Don't worry. I have really all that did.
Where? I honestly, guys, where's the C? I'm going to, if I'm going to do it, I'm going to do it,
right? Oh, wait, careful. Those are metal enemies. Oh, there it is. Perfect. Wait,
I don't have that. Sit. There we go. I'm going to be able to do a lot of slot machine stuff later.
All right. Sneed the end. I thought I just got hurt. Change the music. Uh, guys, I'm sorry. I
cannot, I can't just turn on a different OST. This is what the game soundtrack is. And it's
cute. It's fine. You can't just put on blocked OST for every single game I play.
Give me, come on, give me some slack. All right. I got all, I got Pac-Man.
I thought I had to go in there from the bell or something at the end.
Oh my goodness. There's a lot of shit back here. Uh, let me get, hold on,
don't get too far ahead. No, not yet. Can't jump this. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. What's that?
Ooh, a key. Why would you want to change this music?
Pac-Man music. Doesn't everybody universally love, whatever. I thought everybody universally loved
Pac-Man music. Ooh, wait, I'm going to do this. Yep. Oh, wait. Bonus stage. That was a fake
reaction, but whatever. I'll take it. Bonus stage. Oh, okay. I got it. Oh, I can't get it.
Got them all. What do I do here? I got five spins. This is going to be huge. All right.
Can I max bet? Can I bet everything I have in one spin? Yep. I got to try to get the, uh, the
spaceship. Where's the spaceship? Okay. It's one, two, three, four, five, six. One, two, three,
four, five, six. One, two, three, four, five, six. One, two, three, four, five, six, six, four,
one, two, three. How did I do that? How did I mess that up? How is that possible? I don't know
what happened. That's fucked up. One, two, three, four, five, six. One, two, three, four, five,
six. That's okay. What a dork. Give it. Let's do it. I'll get it this time. Ready? One, two,
three, four, five, six. One, two, three. This music beat is fucking me up. One, two, three, four,
five, six. One, two, three. Why is my voice getting deeper? What's that? Whoa. What the
fuck is going on? No, I was like going, I was getting, I was, I was, what the fuck kind of gas
was I just inhaling? Two, one, two, three. Oh my God. Whatever. I got, I won once. I'm fine.
I have 14 extra lives guys. Sorry. 18. I have 18 lives. I don't think I'm going to use more
than two of these. So don't worry. Crazy cannonade. I almost have the area one boss. When are you
going to finally play Eve Online? Um, isn't that the game where sometimes it takes like five years
for there to be real like geopolitical fights and stuff. And after like a half decade,
there's like a battle and you just lose everything. That's that game is intense.
You want to talk about a roguelike. One run could take four or five years.
That's a really cool concept for a game. I will say, but I just, I'm, I'm way too impatient for it.
You didn't think I was going to get up here, did you? It just excels spreadsheets in an MMO.
Wasn't there something that happened? Uh, not that long ago. It was like the biggest Eve Online
fight ever in history. It was like thousands of people. It was like the ultimate, it was like
the infinity war. When was the Eve Online end game? It was pretty recently, wasn't it? Five
years ago. It was the fountain war. Why are people batch testing? Oh, it's because I said, I said
Marvel. Oh, I got to get up there. Did I just ruin my chance to get up there? The enemies respawn.
Come on. Did I really ruin it? I don't think I can get up there. There it is. All right, we're good.
Is that, that's not the fruit I need. I need an apple. The Eve Online big battle nearly cost
$400,000 in damages. Oh my God. That's crazy. Oh, okay. $400,000. I would be so scared to play that
kind of game. And whenever I play an MMO, I always want to hold onto every single thing I've ever
collected. So thinking and knowing that I could, you could lose a half of a decade of progress
and you just spawn and that guy stole it over there. Part of that group or that team, whatever.
Hold on now. That's the first time that's been possible. It looks like Mario 3D world. It says
Pac-Man world repack. Wait, what am I doing? Why can I hit the back wall? The wall, that's the
the art in the background. How is that possible? Why can I hit the background art?
Hold on. Let's go. I thought I could move it.
I thought I could move it as the big easy mode. Oh my God. What is easy mode?
I'm getting, I'm getting Luigi right now. What is that? No, no, you can hang for a long time in the
air. Okay. Let Luigi play. You know, I always say that I've never played that game. I just know that
that's, you know, maybe I have. No, I didn't. I hated it. That's right. That's right. I played
Super Mario 3D world and I hated every second of it. I really did. I thought it was the worst Mario
game ever. I thought it was so awful. I hated every waking moment of playing that game. I'm sorry. I
had the same conversation a couple of years ago about it. I know it's a weird opinion, but I really
did. I just, I didn't like it at all. And I always go into stuff with an open mind. I really do.
Especially a Mario game. You know, Mario Galaxy. Oh my God. Right. Mario Galaxy. Mario Sunshine.
Mario 64. I love that shit. 3D world or 3D land? What was the side scrolling one?
Oh, the side scrolling news. New Super Mario Brothers Wii. That's what I'm thinking of. No,
not 3D world. New Super Mario Brothers Wii with the two tones. That one sucks. That one sucks.
Ass. That's the one I'm thinking of. I need the A. No, not Mario Maker. I'm talking to... Oh my God.
Where's the A? I don't think, I think I can't get it. I can't go back. I can't go back.
The A is gone forever. I can't go back. Oh well. Wait. No, I can't make that. I can't go back.
Yeah. New Super Mario Brothers Wii. The one where you stuck the walls. Oh my God.
That was so bad. That's how far you can throw this? Can I aim it anywhere else? That's so bad.
Do I have the orange? Wait, that's not right. Wait a minute. This is a long one.
I think I just walked out. No. That's the M. Shit. Oh well. You can't get everything.
All right. I got to come back here because there's a bonus level. Can I climb that or anything?
Jump on his head. There it is. Okay. Made it. People play the Pac-Man games actually?
Um, yeah. I mean, I'm doing it right now. I'm here right now playing it. Wish I could have done
that before. Don't come over here. If I don't get all these, if I don't get every single one of these,
I will, I will eat my Twitch channel. You already did that joke. Yeah. Reuse joke, Andy. I guess
that I missed the A. All right. Let me ask you guys this question. What do you think is the best
Mario video game that has come out ever? And I'm talking across every platform. By the way,
there are some that are grayed out. Mario 64 is grayed out as well as Super Mario World for the
SNES. Those are both grayed out. You cannot pick those. They're grayed out. There are,
there are SS tier. You can't touch them. Odyssey. Odyssey was very, yeah. Odyssey was very good.
Honestly, it was very good. I still think it's probably Galaxy. Although Galaxy made me puke.
Well, I didn't actually throw up, but it made me feel like I was going to.
What's the wrong button? Good thing I have a lot of lives. What did I say? I was going to go through
the whole game. That was inaccurate. I need to switch that right now. Okay. In every single
video game you've ever played, is it hang in midair? Is the jump button again, but I can't
make it that right. It's usually like a, right? A, but it's a in an X. That feels weird.
God damn it. I want to hover. I don't want to fall straight down. I want to go like this,
but I have to hit the, it's not jump. What is this? Oh, okay. Let's go.
Oh my God. Get out the fucking way. No, I missed the other A.
Greedy Gary. That's me. All right. All right. Let's go. Did I miss the end? I might have.
I don't even know why this moves in the game. It's truly bad.
Lower the game volume. I'm trying to sleep. Dude, just lower the stream volume. Lower the stream
volume. You have a volume control. Hold up your, just click, click, click, click down a few times.
You can do that on your own. I don't have to do that. What, you know, what would have been really
funny is if you said, Hey, Jerma, can you turn down your screams audio? I'm too lazy to do it myself.
That would have been like, all right, that's funny. Why does it feel like I can go down there?
I don't know why. I just, I saw the sand, whatever. I spam and spamming lower your voice.
I'm watching this at full volume at my mother's funeral. That would, that would, that's very odd.
Full volume. You see, the thing is you're just going to look like a fucking lunatic, right?
That's, that's, I have nothing to do with this. Oh, it's ticked up. They're not going to think
you're watching a stream. They're going to think you're playing Pac-Man really loudly.
That's all. The only thing is that you can really decipher it. You're just going to hear like,
blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah, blah. You're just going to be like this. Oh my God. What are you
doing? Stop swearing in front of your mom's coffin. Imagine. I can't believe this. I hit my mom's
funeral. This guy. Can you, can you believe what this guy's saying? Oh my God. I'm so bad. All
right. I'm going to try to actually get it. One and a two and a three and a four and a one and a two
and a three and a four. It's gotta be faster. This is how I can keep tempo. Six, five,
two, three, four, five, six. You gotta be fucking kidding me.
One, two, three, four, one, two, three. Start over. Two, three, four, five, six, seven, three,
four, five, six, one, two, three, four, five, six, whatever. I'm sweating through this shirt.
What's happening? I wonder what the bosses are like. Hey dude, can you speak up? I'm in a
construction site. Okay. This is important. Okay. I got something. Bear with me for one minute.
I'm going to try to be very straight faced about this and see if I can do it.
Oh, like this is, this is just a ton of work going on. They're building a skyscraper next to me.
This sounds pretty good. 10 hours of construction sounds. This is challenge. Watch the full video.
This is too obvious. It's gotta be way louder than me, right? Like I gotta turn myself down.
Is it fine now? Okay. That's enough. That's enough. That's enough. I don't know if I can take that.
I was like, why is it still on? That was this. It's still on. We're good. Oh, it's because I,
whoops. Uh-oh. It's evil Pac-Man. Oh, I had to turn that off. This is still on.
Windbag. This will be the time for you to be able to throw a grenade, Pac-Man.
I don't get it. I mean, does it have to hit something? Did that work? Why is this audio
sound like it's a compressed YouTube video? Oh, it's firing back. What? Oh, shit. All right.
I knew it was going to get faster. Um, what? Do peach? All right. One more hit and that's it.
Got it. This is your worst stream. 10 out of 10. Sorry about the construction, dude.
I'm really sorry about the construction. Yeah, I banned that person. I banned that person for
like at least a day. I banned that person for a full day and missed everything because of that.
I want that person banned for a day, at least 24 hours. Oh my God. I missed everything.
What the fuck? That was everything. That was so much coins and shit.
Permanently banned that person. No, no, no, no, no. Permanent ban is like 10 minutes.
Saying I'm going to ban you for a day means you're going to be gone for like a month.
Saying ban that person for 10 minutes means don't actually ban them at all.
I'm looking at the mod chat. So do you actually want us to ban that guy or not?
Question marks. Like four people have written question marks in the mod chat.
Five, no. Um, no. Three, five, six, go. One, two, three, four, five, six, go. Fuck you.
Is it Lemonworth? Yeah, it was so confusing. It happened at a weird timing. Whatever.
I thought this was Pac-Man. It is Pac-Man. There's slot machines in Pac-Man.
Please don't ban me. I'm not going to ban you. I'm kidding.
All right. So I think we're almost. Wait a minute. Our best friend Dig Dug is here.
Oh, this is Pooka. OK. Oh, so we have like a friend. This is pretty sick.
Pac-Man will go to any lengths to beat you, Pac-Man. Be careful.
You kind of look like Pac-Man. I think I did it right. Or is this a.
Yep, that's a wooden bag. All right, let's go to the next area.
You have a void expression. Pac-Man is very. Look, this is a void expression.
He's smiling. Really? That's a void expression.
He's looking how happy he is. Like, yeah, that's fine.
Oh, there's a space area. Oh, and let's go to the first level.
Oh, I can switch between them.
Fast travel. I guess that makes sense eventually if you want to go back.
All right, let's go. I think we're going to get a cool music change.
People are going to be very excited about this.
Da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da da.
That hurt. Wait, something up there?
No. All right. That's good.
You do the jackhammer sounds with your mouth.
Oh, probably.
And tried. Oh, lemon.
I want maximum coins for maximum gambling.
I'm not even touching it.
No, I don't get that.
I don't get hit. What am I supposed to do?
Am I having fun? Yeah, I'm having fun.
I'm having fun.
I have an itchy face.
Can somebody explain to me what that is, by the way?
Like for some reason, randomly, just pieces of my face will be itchy.
It'll be like scratchy. Oh, like, hmm, hmm, hmm.
What does that mean?
Why do it? And I'll be normal for a whole day.
And then it was my face will just start itching in random places.
Dead skin. You have too much skin there.
Somebody just say, I don't know, dude, take your shirt off.
Well, that's not what I asked.
I was asking. That's not what I was.
What are you talking? Why?
And that person for 10 minutes.
Did I get a I did. OK, I got to go back.
I don't don't only see what I'm talking about.
It's like itchy right there.
And it wasn't itchy there five minutes ago.
What the fuck? OK, whatever.
It's because there are worms in your face.
All right. I've done two out of two.
Let's see if I can do three three.
And they get hit by those beams, too.
No, sorry. You can't hit a ghost with a glass bottle.
So they can't get hurt by that.
I understand. I remember the logic from earlier.
Could have gone the other way.
That's a classic rookie pack in the state.
I should have gone the other way.
Actually, a rookie mistake.
What the why is that even here?
Come on. I was fine. I had it right there.
That was dumb.
It's stage hazards on a Pacman game.
This game has ass cheeks.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
I thought it looked really weird doing that.
How weird did that look?
That's why I never have the camera on.
Very. OK, good. Holy shit.
Whoa, I'm too big to fit through here.
No. Oh, why does it feel like such a failure?
What are you doing?
When are you going to play Splatoon 3?
After I play Splatoon 1 and 2, which I have not done yet.
I don't like Splatoon. I told you already.
Because it reminds me of that old Tony Hawk multiplayer game mode.
And I would just get infuriated at it.
I think I got one of these, right?
In their door back there, I can do.
You're a monster.
No, I saw the Tony Hawk Pro Skater had this mode
where I think it was called tagging or graffiti mode or something.
And I would always get so screwed because a buddy of mine would get a one million point streak
because how it worked is everything you touched in a combo,
you have whatever you touch during the combo would turn into your team's color.
And I would just be playing and getting areas.
And, oh, yeah, I got the railing.
I got this ramp.
And then somebody that was really good at the game would just fly through,
do a million point thing on it across the whole game.
And then I just had to literally sit around and do nothing
because I could never get it back.
I played Splatoon for the first time,
and it just brought back those awful memories of, oh, let's go.
I'm going for it. I'm doing a good job.
I painted so much.
And then I turn around, the whole thing is gone.
And we just get absolutely dominated.
So you're bad. Yeah. Yes.
Yes, I'm very bad at that game. Yes.
OK. Is it mad because bad?
No, no, I'm not. I'm just bad at that game.
That's it. There's no more. There's no argument.
There is no argument.
I know people like expect. OK, this is a funny thing.
Like, oh, mad because bad. Oh, you suck at it.
That's why. Yeah. But no, you mad.
You got to get mad because you're not good at it.
Like, no, yeah, I'm terrible at it.
I'm dog shit at it. That's why I don't play it.
Oh, shit. All right.
Well, thanks for the scream.
How do I get out of here? I'm stuck in here now. What?
You need to wash your neck. What's wrong with it?
You know where I do get mad, right?
Because, for instance, if you say, dude, oh, why?
You just you don't like it because you suck at it.
You're just shitty at Splatoon. Yeah, Splatoon.
Yeah, no, yeah, absolutely.
Please, please continue to ridicule me because I agree with you.
But if I'm playing Elden Ring and I see like mad because bad,
it's like, shut the fuck up.
How fuck you? How dare you?
I know that I'm playing this game pretty well.
And like, I'm having a lot of trouble on this boss.
How dare you? Right. There's a difference.
Where's the end? Well, whatever.
If this is a game that you know you like
and you're having trouble with it, as somebody says, wow, dude, skill issue.
Like, fuck, I like this game.
Don't I want to be good at this game?
I didn't even mean to do that.
I just literally pressed the button three times and I just got it.
All right. I get too much rice.
Cherries are kind of worth nothing.
Why is the cherry so hard to get?
It's not even that big of a deal.
I thought I saw red.
I got it once.
You do a ball pit stream.
Oh, I might get lost.
That would be one of those streams.
Be like, guys, I'm here.
I've rented out a whole play place and let's go and have cameras everywhere.
It's oh, wow.
I can't believe it. It's just so fun.
And then we just we go to a BRB at one point.
I'm in like the tube hanging out.
Wow. He went down the slide.
All right. We'll be right back.
And you come back from the break and I'm just gone.
It's like, where is he? Where the fuck is he?
I'm just like in the ball pit.
I'm in the ball pit.
There's a line in the lap.
And it would be it would be the first BRB.
It would literally be BRB one after 15 minutes.
The ball pit is gross.
I I'm not I don't.
Yeah, I don't I would.
Yeah.
Ball pit of despair.
Anything over here?
Dude, you've eaten boogers.
You can't say that ball pits are gross.
Would you eat somebody else's boogers?
Would you eat someone else's boogers?
Yes or no.
The answer is absolutely no.
So what are you talking about?
If you've eaten boogers in your whole life before.
And by the way, can we just back up a little bit?
Can we just take a quick little break and understand?
I don't I don't do this shit.
I don't eat boogers.
When what are you describing?
When did I eat boogers on stream?
I'm a grown man.
What when did I eat boogers?
I'm not following when this happened.
When when you said you were going to drink stirs loogie.
That's no, but that's your hold on.
But that was for a very specific joke routine
that I was going to commit to.
I wasn't sitting there like, oh, oh, boogers.
OK, shut up.
Everyone stop talking now.
Are you fucking up my game?
Why the fuck did I just do that?
I hate. Oh, my God.
What an idiot.
What a fucking idiot.
I forget that people just will click that and share it with everybody.
Look what he said. He said boogers.
I'm too old for this.
I'm too old for this. I am.
I'm way too old for this.
Oh, my God. I'm getting flustered.
I actually am.
I like this music.
Wait, what?
Oh, my goodness.
All right. Relax.
Can't hit it.
OK, they got electrified.
I can't hurt him.
This is going to be sick.
Oh, my God. And look, look what happened.
Look what happened.
Look what I look what's going on over in this chat.
Everyone's talking about it now.
Oh, Grandpa Pac-Man is here.
I rescue Grandpa.
Pac-Man, there should be a key out here.
You need to find it.
Oh, come on.
What? What is this?
I ate the booger. I'm a booger reader.
OK, I just have a... This is a booger eating stream.
I'm just eating boogers.
When the webcam isn't on, I just dig up there and I eat the boogers.
That's what I do.
What is this from?
Why did I say that?
What was the point of me saying this?
I don't get it.
I ate the booger. I'm a booger reader.
OK, I just have a... This is a booger eating stream.
I'm just eating boogers.
When the webcam isn't on, I just dig up there and I eat the boogers.
That's what I do.
That's a stream from three years ago.
Oh, my goodness.
No, never mind.
I thought my microphone was messed up.
It actually might be.
Oh, yeah, it is.
Have you been hearing double this whole time?
No? OK.
That's from three years ago.
But yeah, it was definitely a joke, though.
I was probably just making a stupid joke.
Can you imagine admitting
to 700,000 people
concurrent viewers that you eat boogers on stream?
I mean, what the fuck?
Where's this key?
Jesus.
700,000. Yeah, my channel's like really dropped a lot.
You guys weren't here three or four years ago.
I was averaging three to five hundred thousand concurrent viewers every day.
I mean, the stream kind of fell.
And once I started doing like the booger reading stuff and
like jokes that people thought were like shitty.
I lost a lot of people, I think.
I was actually really surprised that I thought, you know,
they're doing a routine where I like eat a bunch of boogers on stream
was like, oh, maybe it was funny for a minute.
But I lost like three or four hundred thousand people concurrently.
So like I try to see like if the joke will land first before I do it.
That's kind of frustrating, but whatever.
That was my favorite stream.
Yeah, I mean, like some people thought it was funny.
But let's rescue Grandpa.
Thanks, Pac-Man. I'll wait for you up ahead.
I know the Apple. Oh, now I do.
I got to make sure I don't die.
That scared the shit out of me.
I didn't think it was going to go that far.
Oh, Jesus.
I'm not reading that one. It was fucked up.
Oh, secret.
I don't. I got to bounce from here.
This is going to this is kind of hard.
How do I get that?
Not like that.
Oh, my God. I haven't gone all the way back, aren't I?
Thank goodness. Thank God.
Where am I? All right, I got it.
All right, let's get it.
There's the A.
Oh, oh, read it.
Read what? I mean, read, read what?
What am I? What is a read?
How long is? Oh, that looks like I can get it, doesn't it?
And oh, hey, I got it.
Pac-Man is going to be a big one.
Whoa. Got them all.
I died. Whoa. Big one, dude.
Yeah, I know. I was pretty hogged up that one.
We're good. Oh, whoa.
Oh, my God. I'm fine.
Oh, my goodness. How do I get back up?
Dude, get up.
What the fuck is this here for if I can't do it?
Do you look like you know French?
I don't. I don't know any other languages.
I can't learn another language.
I know everybody says that.
Like, oh, no, you know, there's this program you can learn.
It's really easy. No, not for me.
Yeah, I, I definitely could not.
I would need a reason.
Um, I mean, you can learn a language to, you know, have to have a reason
to learn French or Spanish or you can just do it just because
I speak three languages and I'm not even 18.
I mean, that's that's a huge skill to have.
It really is. Think about think about this.
It's oh, I can only truly communicate
with a very limited amount of people.
I only know English.
My communication ability is much lower than yours.
It's weird to think about that.
Ever heard of Google Translate?
Yeah, there's a huge difference between Google Translate
and truly being able to be at a restaurant and talk to the person
or be able to communicate with somebody online and just be able to speak
fluently and just completely understand.
I'm not talking about like opening up a little book and being like, OK,
where do some how do I go to the bathroom?
No, I'm talking about you truly fluently understand the language,
like in and out completely.
Because even if you use a translator, you are not truly understanding
what you are saying.
You are just phonetically repeating something because you know
that's what it's supposed to sound like.
You're not truly comprehending what you're saying.
You're looking at a thing that's telling you what to say.
You don't know exactly why or how,
unless you actually learn the language fluently.
See, that's pretty.
There's no way to even gauge where your heart are you jumping.
It sounds like a teacher.
Hold on. Sorry, let me correct that.
Oh, boogers, right?
Is that is that what you want?
OK, is that what you're looking for?
Let me rephrase that.
What I meant to say was,
oh, probably probably move, Franch.
Let me make it so you guys can understand.
What's wrong with you? You get it.
You understand why I just did that.
If you don't know why I just did that, come on, Gwyn.
You know what I mean? Come on.
Wrong. I'm pressing A to hover.
No, I don't want to play in easy mode.
I'm holding A to hover because every other video game I've ever played
was hold the jump button to hover.
Every time you've seen me skyrocket to the goddamn ground.
God!
X, X, hold X, hold X, hold the X button.
Hold X to do this.
X, hold X, no depth perception.
No, it's called remembering muscle memory
for every single platforming
video game with a jump that's ever been recorded in human history
since when the cavemen were making video games from.
All right, settle down.
This game's not that fucking hard, man.
I got it. Relax. I'm going to be fine.
See, I figured it out.
Where's your face? I'm here.
Oh, yep. No, no, no.
I want to explore.
Yeah, the grenade works on those guys.
Pac-Man, please. Enough of that.
Yes. Game is this.
This is called Pac-Man World repack.
It's on Steam and maybe somewhere else.
I got it on Steam.
Yeah, it's a remake from an old PlayStation.
I got everything right. Yep.
Hogman. Yeah.
All right. I'm not going to screw this up.
I got plenty of time to do this.
Let's go. Go do it right.
I don't need to jump.
It's good. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh.
I got everything. Yeah, I'm good.
Remember, your hair looks like it would fit really nicely on a groomed dog.
If I saw this kind of hair on a dog, I'd be very confused.
That would be very confusing.
Like, why does that dog have human hair?
It's like a one, one, two, three.
Oh, damn it. I'm going to sit further back.
They're all blending together.
Why are they all blending together?
Oh my God, there's so many strawberries on this one.
I thought it was one, two, three in a row, like one then whatever.
Oh, you suck. Hey.
All right. Where's the boss?
Get hype. Why do you look so mad all the time?
That's just my face, dude. This is awesome.
Pac-Man is a power pellet.
When you grab one, cannons are powered up for a short time.
That's a bomb dot.
You can take out all nearby enemies and obstacles.
I missed it. Sorry.
Excuse me. How did I not get that?
Oh, my God.
Oh, that's got way harder for no reason.
I was talking to this.
Who's my favorite character? Grandpa.
Pac-Man, for sure.
King Calaxian. That's a G.
What am I supposed to do about this?
He dodged that.
Oh, good placement.
Oh, I had I had checkers or Raleigh's.
I want to give you a review on it.
I forgot about that.
I want to give you a review about how I feel about Raleigh's.
Remember how I never had it before?
I had it. I had Raleigh's.
Let me tell you something very important.
Is it Raleigh's Raleigh's checkers, Raleigh's, Raleigh's, Raleigh's?
How I don't know how you say it.
I'll tell you after. OK, but yeah, I had it
during my tier list, my fast food tier list stream.
People were like, you've never had checkers before.
You've never had rallies before.
How is that possible?
And I was like, I never had it.
And I said, if I ever have it, I'll update you.
And I had it. So I thought, well, should I need to update you guys?
And I have a couple of very strong opinions on it.
I think I'm going to think I'm going to confuse a lot of you.
We don't care.
But whatever. I mean, I just want to let you know, dude, we don't care.
No, I don't care. Really?
OK, run a poll in the chat right now.
And I don't think don't.
Oh, whatever.
I like the streamers going off on like a story or a tangent.
I want to hear it. No, no, no.
They truly tell me the truth.
Yes or no.
Do you give a shit about that?
I've eaten at rallies and be very honest, like the take away
the fact that like, oh, you're here and hanging out.
Do you actually give a shit about what I'm about to say at all?
And I mean, truly be like, no, I really don't give a fuck.
I want to know if at least 40%
of you do not give a shit about this.
I won't talk about it.
And I'm very curious.
It's R-A-L-L-Y.
I want to see just how many people don't care.
That's so funny to me.
God damn it.
Yeah. Yeah.
R-A-L-L-Y-S.
I have no patience at all.
All right. What does it say?
How you guys feel?
Whoa. OK, it's a lot so far.
That's a very that's a big initial one.
Where 39% say no, I don't care.
OK, stop.
OK, it's this one right after.
God damn it.
They're the same shape.
All right. We're at 37%.
That means enough of you care.
So I'm going to do it.
Thirty six percent. Yeah.
I told you have to get over 40%.
So where's the next area?
Did I do it all?
Is there a next area?
How do I get there?
All right. That's it.
I'm going to talk about it.
OK. All right.
You've spoken.
The Rally's French fries
are the best fast food French fries I've ever had
in my entire life, in my entire life.
They are the most un fucking believable French fries.
They are unbelievably good.
It is so mind boggling how they could be that good.
They're that good. They're unbelievable.
Everything else is dog shit.
The whole fucking rest of the whole restaurant.
All right. The chicken strips were OK.
They were fine.
But everything else, I was like, this is kind of not good.
But I'm telling you right now, I would go to Rally's
and just get French fries and get a bunch of sauces and shit.
It's worth going to Rally's just to get the French fries
and just get about just get a three large French fry orders
and split it with like two people, three people.
How bad were the other food items?
They were they were just OK.
It was like, OK, dog shit was probably rude.
But the chicken fingers were just they didn't really taste like it.
It was just they were very like five or six at five out of ten.
They were literally dog shit, although they were five out of ten.
You got chicken at a burger joint.
I got a burger, too, and it was OK.
It was like fine.
Every other burger I've had from any other fast food place was better.
It was fine.
But let me tell you, the French fries are so good
that I want them so bad, so badly right now.
They are so crunchy and crispy and they're just perfect.
They're always perfectly hot.
It tastes like they came right out of an oven and they're like,
they're so unbelievably good.
I could not tell you how good they are.
You can buy them at the store.
That would be amazing.
They sell frozen frozen version.
I don't know what they're doing to those fries, but OK,
everything else is like a four or five out of ten.
But the fries being that good makes that like a C or a B tier place
that I would go to.
If I were to put rallies on that tier list, it'd be probably low B
only because I would order French fries and maybe like something else.
But just get mainly French fries.
It's literally a B for sure because of that.
You have to have them.
If you're like, dude, what the fuck is this fast food French fries?
Just eat them once and you'll be like, well, my life is forever different.
I don't know. Where's the next area?
Did I not complete enough stuff?
Was this dude?
I regret it. I should have said I don't care.
Oh, here we go. Two, one.
Oh, that looks cool.
I love McDonald's fries, but they can just they can be very bad.
I have had McDonald's Burger King Wendy's fries before that were just just sad.
And you just don't really want them.
It's just not something. It's just not good.
Hang it up there. Fries are inconsistent.
Yeah. I was actually going to make a tweet about it.
I was going to do a tweet where I took a bite out of one of the French fries
and was just going to be like, look, like, guys, listen to this crunch.
And that was going to be the whole video.
And it was going to be like, oh, like, Raleigh.
This is listen to this.
And I was like, that's a fucking weird video.
So I just didn't make it.
McDonald's double cheeseburgers.
Yeah, it's just I know a lot of people say, dude, McDonald's so bad.
Why do you have the pallet of a five year old?
Something about it.
Those did somebody just said the double cheeseburger from McDonald's
is unmatched from any place I've had.
It just is.
And it's not that it's the best.
Oh, it's the best quality hamburger I've ever had.
It's just it just tastes good.
It's just good every time I've ever had a child pallet.
Well, I didn't tell you about the salmon that I like.
Kids don't like salmon.
I can't name you a five year old that's like, oh, yeah, fresh salmon.
Can I have some? Sorry.
Oh, I can't hurt the big ghosts. Whatever.
Kids will eat anything.
I don't know how many young how many kids have you ever talked to?
Kids do not eat anything.
Huh? When I was a kid, I didn't just eat anything.
I had Captain Crunch for dinner half the time because I told you that story,
how I would be like, I want Captain Crunch for dinner.
And my mother would be like, oh, OK, yeah, you can have Captain Crunch for dinner.
But you've got it.
You can have it, but you have to eat dinner first.
So I would be like, oh, my God.
I can't believe it. I get to eat Captain Crunch whenever I want.
So my mother would I would eat all my dinner and be like,
I can't wait to eat Captain Crunch for dinner.
And she would give me this little like it had to have been ten pellets.
It had to have been ten pellets total what I would get after dinner.
And I thought I was a scammer.
I was like, yeah, mm hmm.
So I just have to eat my dinner and I can eat Captain Crunch for dinner.
Oh, I'm the most intelligent kid in the world.
And she was giving me the equivalent of like two spoonfuls of shit.
And I thought I was the smart one.
Oh, I need whiz metal.
Oh, that's just dessert.
Yeah. But in my five year old of six, whatever, your old brain, whatever it was,
it's the same story with the if what the hell?
OK, we're good.
Missing the A, but whatever.
It's the same story with the if his arm stays up, he's asleep.
I've told that many times, but there's probably a lot of new people on the channel.
Maybe should I tell it again?
OK, so when I would be and my siblings were younger again,
we thought we were the smartest people in the room.
Uh, you know, when when when you're when you're a kid and you're supposed to be
asleep in bed, you're supposed to be asleep, it's bedtime.
And no, I'm staying up and I'm going to talk and and do stuff.
And then, you know, you hear the here comes
becomes mom or dad to see like what's going on in here.
And, you know, you don't want to get in trouble, you know.
No, no, I'm asleep. I'm asleep.
So it's like you put your head down and I'm asleep.
I'm definitely sleeping. I was not talking.
We were not messing around having fun in here, right?
I was not having any fun in here.
And then they would come over.
And my mother and my father would say, oh, really interesting.
OK, they look asleep.
Yeah, I think they're asleep.
It's really one foolproof way to know if somebody's truly sleeping.
And they would come and take your arm and they would just lift it up and hold it.
And they would say, well, I mean, if his arm stays up, he's asleep.
And I would be sitting there going like this and in my brain going, yep.
Gotcha, motherfucker. Mm hmm.
That's me asleep.
And then they'd go, oh, oh, OK.
Very asleep. Oh, really asleep.
Asleep. OK, that's OK.
So it wasn't having any fun in here.
And I thought I was so smart.
And then eventually, eventually I caught on.
And I did this soccer flop.
Right. So instead of going like this and holding it up,
oh, his arm stays up, he's asleep. OK.
It turned into this.
Like, no way, I'm not falling for that one.
So exaggerated that I just flop it.
And the same thing would happen.
You were a stupid fucking kid.
Aren't we all, though?
He did this when he was 22.
I was a real smart kid.
I was smart. No, you think you were smart.
You were shoving crayons up your nose like everybody else was.
Come on.
I don't have banana. Oh, shit, it's right there.
Get up there.
Did I lose my opportunity to do this?
Oh, shit. Were you a glue eater?
No, I actually wasn't.
What was the tooth for?
I don't know. No, this is so annoying.
I actually can't get that.
Oh, yes, I can. I'm just stupid.
I was just do. Oh.
All he gives Derma 10 pellets of Captain
Crunch after he finishes all this hamburger helper.
This stuff is so good.
Oh, man, you just made me think of a hamburger helper.
What a bunch of junk.
What a bunch of fucking junk.
But it is the best shit in the world.
It's gross. No, it's not.
Don't stop.
Look, something can be weirdly unappetizing,
but still be one of the best things you've ever eaten.
It's got to stop. Come on.
I I know it's it's gross.
OK, maybe it is a little gross, but not but it's still delicious.
It's just so yummy.
Food snobs.
Um, I mean, I get it.
I get it. It's kind of filthy looking.
It kind of looks like somebody puked into a pan.
There is that period where you are making hamburger helper,
and it's at that gross phase where it's not really combined all the way.
And it just looks like somebody threw up into your saucepan.
And you're sitting there thinking, oh, help, this thickens up.
This is fucking awful.
It happens every time.
Every single time I've ever made hamburger helper, I've said the same thing.
I do like the Sims shit.
I'm sitting there cooking and I go.
Oh, yuck.
And then when it's done, I eat it.
And it's actually very good.
I'm very happy, though.
Get them all, get them all, get them all, get them all.
Yay. Perfect slop food.
That's the best way to describe it.
It's so weird because it doesn't hamburger helper have as many flavors
as Gatorade does.
There's like 15 different boxes, isn't there?
There's so many different kinds. Variety.
Yeah. You know what else is really good about hamburger helper?
It it'll feed you for a long time.
It's filling.
It'll keep you full for a while.
And you can put that in the fridge and keep it there and just heat it up.
Imagine it with chicken and not hamburger.
There is absolutely probably a bunch of TikTok videos
of hamburger helper hacks that are all all what you are describing.
I don't think you have to look very far.
Is there chicken helper?
See, that to me would be kind of strange.
Chicken's a little different.
How would you what do you chicken helper?
I don't get it because the whole thing with hamburger helper is it's ground beef.
So you just brown it in the pan and then, you know, drain it.
How do you you just dump it in with a bunch of chicken
patty strips or something about a ground is a ground chicken,
shredded chicken, this tuna helper.
I could go for a big fucking egg salad right now.
I make a great egg salad.
I make probably the I'm not.
I'm trying to be very clear here.
I make the best egg salad you've ever had in your life.
I mean it. If I sold my egg salad, it would I'd be a fucking trillionaire.
I would it would be it would be a story like, oh, yeah, I now own
and operate like 50 restaurants where we we all we have is that we have a bunch
of egg salad. That's like what we do.
Imagine the main menu item on your restaurant is an egg salad.
You guys have prime rib?
No, not at all.
Oh, do you have any like seared chicken or any, you know, tuna or no, nothing.
We have we have egg salad sandwiches. That's it.
But they would do what you're good at.
I'm telling you, I make my egg salad and you're going to fucking freak out.
Why am I acting so weird?
I don't know. Literally show me how you make it.
It's this it's a secret.
It's an actual secret recipe.
The secret recipe.
The secret is it's something else you add to it.
It's a secret recipe.
I'm not going to give it to you.
I have to be able to pass something down to my kids.
That's not watch me eat boogers on stream.
You know what I mean? Like there has to be something else.
Oh, yeah. What did Grandpa pass down?
Oh, he was a fucking weirdo online.
That's pretty much it.
No, he left behind his secret.
Grandpa left his.
I'm going to write it.
I'm going to write it down on lined paper and leave it out
and make sure it's old and fucking shitty looking in 50 years.
Make sure it's all stained and stuff so they can get it.
But what would they wait on this?
Grandpa's secret egg salad recipe so I can leave something.
Why am I back here?
To one was to two.
Here we go. It's not a secret.
It's paprika.
I don't it's I don't put paprika in my egg salad.
And what an amateur move that would be, by the way.
He puts hot sauce in it.
Oh, OK.
Oh, he puts hot sauce in it.
Yeah, that's what that's what it is.
That's the secret recipe.
Damn, that looks like it hurt.
No, I'm not going to tell you because I need to leave a note for my grandkids.
This is all I'm going to have. This is it.
If I say it right now, then it's then it's over
and I can't write it down on a piece of line paper and like burn it.
All right. I'm going to take a lighter and light it on fire.
Burn it. Put it out. Put it out. Light it on fire.
First, put it out.
So it's this old document that they have to find.
Throw it in a fireplace.
Yeah, like put it in a fireplace and then like get it up, blow it up, blow it out
and make sure it makes sure it's all old and fucked up and right on it.
Grandpa's award winning egg salad secret.
And hey, bro, roll up a few hundreds.
You know what I mean?
Roll up like 10 hundreds and like roll it up together.
So it's like, holy shit, we found this.
We found this shit.
Grandpa rolled up 10 hundreds.
You thought you would just get an egg salad?
No, you're getting like five grand in cash, too, at least.
What if they watch this VOD?
Well, I'm not going to say the recipe. That's the point.
Oh, I think I screwed it up.
Can I get back up again? All right, hold on.
What if the paper got destroyed?
Then I'm so I don't know.
You know, maybe I should mess up the text a little bit.
So you have to actually decipher it.
I actually want to do this.
So I got to get the plan.
Do you really want to you really want to get weird here?
Yeah, there will be.
So you guys right now,
my great, great, great, great grandchildren
will be able to watch this stream and potentially see what you're writing.
Do you understand how fucking strange that is?
You understand how bizarre that is?
We always look at photos of old stuff.
It's just a picture of your great, great grandfather.
Like that. And that's it.
And he was a he worked at a he was he was a he was a blacksmith or something, right?
Every booger eating comment I've made,
my great, great, great, great grandkids will be able to see it.
So this is where it starts.
Hi, kids. It's your great, great, great, great, great grandfather.
What I have done is I have buried secret family treasure somewhere.
And you are going to start your journey right now in the attic.
There is a piece of paper on that piece of paper
is a note with some instructions on it.
And I'm going to tell you the one hint you'll get here.
Doll doll.
And I'm going to put it in a fucking doll or something.
And that's how they can start doll.
And then they're going to go on an adventure.
You spoiling it in the Vod.
Well, what? No, no, no. What we'll do is we'll clip that section
and then I'll delete the Vod. Right.
I'm just I'm just losing. I'm not even paying attention.
How cool would that be, though?
Can you imagine? I'm going to do it.
You guys think I'm screwing around. I'm going to do this.
I am going to make it.
I'm going to do a big treasure hunt thing for my great, great, great grandkids.
You know, the equivalent of OK, imagine the old photo.
You're right now your great, great, great grandmother or something.
It was like like on the back.
You turn it over and it's the secret is in the doll.
And then you remember, oh, wait, great, great.
Yeah, the doll that's up in the attic.
What does that mean?
And they like take it apart or something.
And oh, there's a there's a there's a map in here.
That's what I'm doing for my grandkids right now.
So just wait, just wait another like 400 or 500 years.
And they'll figure it out.
And it's going to be so cool.
And I'm going to go on.
They're going to be a news article about it.
It's going to be awesome.
It's like, oh, it'll be like on Reddit.
I found an old buried stream post
from my great, great, great grandfather.
He put us on a treasure hunt.
Oh, yeah, old school, like subreddit, right?
And then when they get to the treasure,
like I say, I'm going to do all this, like, oh, wait, wait,
there's a secret family recipe.
No, it's just me like smoking crack, you know, like a Polaroid.
And that's all it is.
And then, oh, they're going to be they're going to feel real bad
about writing those articles.
What if you don't have grandkids?
I don't know.
Then just delete this because then I'll I don't know.
Why would anybody have left?
By the way, if you want to give me shit for that,
why did anyone leave a secret fucking family treasure recipe for anybody?
No, no, I'm not going to leave the treasure hunt.
What if I don't have grandkids?
At that point, I would have known, right?
If you're that old and you don't have grant, you're like,
of course, it's not going to happen.
I can give it to somebody else.
Remember, you don't have to leave family treasure hunts.
So write the clues in the library books.
Yeah, let grandpa have it.
Yeah. What do you mean? What? Oh, why?
Why? Who cares? Why wouldn't you?
What if you if you wanted to?
By the way, grandkids be the letter B.
Look for it.
I may have wrote it on the ceiling in the bathroom.
And then underneath that fucking ceiling tile,
there could be the next step in your journey.
Look for the letter B somewhere, right?
Where do I go? Where do I actually go?
Why would they watch this VOD?
How would it be a secret treasure hunt if I made it easy?
There's thousands of pieces of media that I've been in.
Do you want me to make it easy?
I want to be a secret family treasure hunt.
Jerma is trying to give his ancestors a lot of leeway
if he's expecting a random ceiling tile not to be replaced in 400 years.
That house probably won't even exist.
Just like bulldozer.
Well, how did anybody leave anything like that? Right.
But just have to bury it somewhere.
How would that even work? Yeah.
How did anybody find anything secret?
This doesn't happen in real life, dude.
Hasn't it once? It has. Yeah, it has.
Yes, it does. Yes, it does.
Yeah. So what the hell? Yeah, I could make it happen.
I know I'm going to probably jump on those, right?
One of these I'm going to jump on top of. No.
Your grandkids are going to see a really enlarged picture of your ass.
Yeah, I know.
Why do you think I'm trying to figure out and food stuff to leave them?
They're going to take one bite of the egg salad and go, wow,
this is actually on par with that ass photo.
I'm so glad he left it for us.
Wait, that's a key.
Are we going to be trapped here?
I jumped over that. Oh, it's the dog.
That was a triple right there.
Adjusted for inflation, you're going to give them like three dollars.
I'll do the math and shit. I'll calculate it.
Let me out.
So in like a thousand years or something, they find it.
What I said I was going to do by five grand.
I'll put like, I don't know, put like five hundred grand in there.
Well, no, I can't do that.
No, I'm not. Never mind.
No, no. How about this?
The only way you can get the money is there's I don't know.
There's a code attached to it that you can only know if you
if you like spread my recipe on whatever tick tock of that time is
I got to figure out a way to make it so like you got to.
I've got to be popular.
I've got my recipe is going to be popular.
It's going to be a huge deal.
And like only then when this exact account that, by the way,
I made an account on on tick tock and this account.
Here's the username and password.
This account must get five to ten, at least 5000
likes on a egg salad video of my recipe or it will not unlock.
That's kind of fun.
And the first thing you're going to be in a video with like a suit on.
I go, you found it.
Like, you know, I always do that.
Like the rich asshole is here recording a video.
And let me tell you, oh, so you found it.
What you need to do is you need to make sure that you.
Yeah, I'll go and I'll do a whole spiel.
Did I miss something over here?
He's a goose laying his own eggs.
What does that mean? What's that? What's that?
What's that mean?
It's going to be a sentient AI of you by then.
Not if I have a no sentient AI clause,
not if I make sure to tell my lawyers that under no circumstances
am I going to be a sentient AI and when we all sign it and it's fucking,
you can't do it.
Not if I put it a clause somewhere, I'll do it illegally.
But you're going to have to answer to the estate because I put it in a contract.
I like the fact that you're asking for clout even after you're dead.
No, I don't want the clout.
I want my recipe to have the clout.
Your consciousness is going to be free by then.
No, it's not.
Yeah, I only want my recipe to have clout, not me.
Your consciousness is going to eventually enter public domain.
Bro, I have not had enough beer to talk.
I have not smoked enough fucking weed to have this conversation
because what you just said is crazy and actually somehow makes bizarre sense.
Shit, this is a perfect run.
Stop talking about drugs.
My daughter watches you.
Hey, put your audience warning with this room.
Is this game pretty poggers?
It's it's all right. I think it's fun.
It's look, this would be a great game to sit down and play
with your grandchildren.
Hey, grandkids, how are you?
It's me, Jeremy again.
We're Aunt Pot, Jeremy.
I heard you found the note that I left you.
Let me tell you something.
Hold on. I don't want to lose.
Why would it be the same bot?
That's not fair. This is OK.
Remind me in like five years to do this again.
Because they need the second half of the code.
What's happening here?
Does it work?
What's going on?
Wait, what was I supposed to lose?
Oh, I already saw this cut scene.
Wow. I was not paying any attention.
OK. OK.
All right. All right.
So they're all they're all yellow now.
Now what? Oh, OK.
I get it. I get it.
I was supposed to go, go, go, go, go.
When I accidentally went, went, went, went, went, went.
Those are supposed to do it the other way.
No, not as hard as music sounds like fantasy.
Oh, oh, not as hard.
Why are there still people here?
But stop.
Oh, my God.
OK, this is just annoying.
Everyone's a hate watcher.
You. Oh, my God.
You'd be a great politician because you have no soul.
Whoa. Whoa, man.
Do you need to relax?
Oh, you want something insane?
OK, so last night, please.
Last night or the night before, I had 10 dreams in a row.
And Holly was was next to me.
And I kept on being in a dream.
I would go to bed.
She would hear me go, hmm.
And she'd go, hey, hey.
And I go, oh, and it happened like 10 fucking times in a row.
I was stun locked in a dream.
It was ridiculous. It was so bad.
Because, you know, anytime you dream
and you wake up from a dream and you go back
and you have a second dream right after immediately after, it usually stops.
After the second, third and fourth time of that happening,
you sit there in this weird, panicked mode where you go, oh, my God,
I don't want to go back to bed.
Is it just going to happen again?
Why am I a dog?
Yeah, like.
They always do that.
They always go.
But no, and so in one of the times, I'll tell you, it was so strange.
After the fourth or fifth time,
and they were such small, short dreams that made no sense.
I remember one of them.
Remember, I had to try to remember five to 10 of these in a row.
One of them where it was, I was in the hallway
where the bedroom is over here, I was in the hallway.
And I went into the opened up the bedroom door and it was like,
but there was no bed in there.
It was empty.
But in the room instead was just an empty room with no bed
and in a line facing the other way, one, two, three, four.
And then another line, one, two, three, four, looking this way,
which is these people in and they have white hair
and these black capes, just black cloaks
all standing and staring away from the door.
It was strange.
One of the other times.
So eventually, I know who fucking cares if I'm losing in this game.
Do you really care?
When I woke up
one of the last times because Holly had been waking me up over and over again.
And again, I fall asleep, I wake up
and will wake up in the dream, essentially.
So I fall asleep and there I am in that same area away from the bedroom.
And I was maybe 10 feet away from the bedroom door again.
But this time I knew that Holly was going to wake me up,
but I was sitting there going, oh, shit.
No, I'm too far away.
I'm not in the bedroom.
I won't hear her wake me up next to me.
I'm too far away.
I can't I won't be able to hear her.
It's hard. You want psychedelics? No.
What is he talking about?
I'm talking about a dream, dude.
And apparently, every time I was just I was just doing the
just breathing, just
did you eat before bed?
I think I mean, I usually don't get that close to bed.
Dogs are so funny, though.
I don't get it.
I know that they're just built so dear.
I can't beat this because I don't.
I'm all right. Let me listen to me.
I'm why I just pause the game.
So Otto will put his head down to be OK.
It's time for bed. Oh, yeah.
He gets comfortable asleep.
I wish I had that ability.
Dogs can just go right to sleep in a deep REM sleep immediately.
I envy it so much.
I'm not going to lose this again.
It's embarrassing if I don't beat this now.
You're so bad at aiming back, man.
All right. Here we go.
Oh, this is itchy.
What do I go for that?
I don't know. I don't know.
I last month.
Take a booger snack break.
This is it is going to be so huge in like a few days and I'm pissed about it.
From the umpire mask.
Would you rather fight this boss of the nameless king?
When is the Elden Ring DLC?
We're going to get me. What do you think?
That was a huge burp, and I'm so glad that you heard it.
There 100 percent will be.
I saw this thing where people said the time frame
between when the other from software games came out
and when DLC came out, we're pretty much at that point.
We're after about 10 months or so, right?
It's when we should think about maybe getting an announcement.
Depends on how big it is.
Maybe it takes more time to do this one.
Excuse me. Give me a break.
Pay attention. Please have help on you.
What the fuck?
What? Well, I'm alive.
What? How am I alive? What happened?
What the fuck just happened? Why am I alive?
I had no help. I'm dead now.
How are you supposed to avoid getting hit by that?
You have to hold this.
I don't know how you avoid that.
I have to dash. There's no area to dash.
Why is it so much harder than the whole rest of the entire video game?
I only have eight lives left.
I have to run towards it.
I don't know. How the fuck did you beat millennia?
Yeah, you think I'm paying that much attention to the Pac-Man game
because I am a good player in Dark Souls games.
Doesn't necessarily translate to a Pac-Man remake game
that like we're just talking about.
Like we're talking about my descendants
and me eating boogers and stuff.
I'm not locked in playing against millennia.
You can call that Kopeem if you want, but I did.
I beat millennia.
So I'm sorry.
You cannot say that I'm a bad gamer because that exists.
This I'm having a bad day.
OK, I'm having a bad day.
I have my gamer license.
I don't need to renew it right now.
I don't need to renew it at Pac-Man World Remake.
My license is not up for renewal yet.
I don't have to do that.
It's not remake, it's repack through.
All right.
I just have to beat it before he does that again.
Like a few more times.
What the fuck? It's broken.
No! What the fuck?
I keep missing it.
Good thing you slept mid fight pretending to be a dog.
I didn't do that when I played against millennia.
There you go. There's your difference.
I wasn't pretending to sleep like a dog when I was very focused.
Hey, what if you wore roller skates and got pushed down a hill?
Like an old Jerry Lewis movie?
You mean, I don't know how to roller skate.
Whoa!
And it's a bunch of comedy where I'm going really fast.
And I block my eyes because I'm about to hit a truck.
And then I go under the truck and I go, oh, oh, baby carriage,
baby carriage and mom.
Oh, and then I go, I hit the baby carriage and boom,
I got the baby in my arms.
Oh, oh, my God.
And then I make it to a bakery, right?
And like the baker, I drop the baby.
The baker catches the baby in a bunch of like dough or something, right?
Yeah. And then finally, I make it all the way down.
Excuse me.
I was about to think about stopping playing this game
until I just saw the next area.
So I'm sorry, we're staying.
I was literally I was literally about to say, hey, let's go.
Let's check out another game.
No. Cool.
I mean, some of the music really just kind of sound like it's coming out
of an AM radio in a car.
And am I the only one that's hearing that?
It sounds weird. Where's the two?
That was simple.
I could have made that any easier.
Can you please get the world record for clapping?
Yeah, sure, I'll do it right now.
How many is it in one second?
I could probably do it.
How many how many claps in one second is the world record?
How many? The one minute record is eleven hundred.
Eleven hundred in a minute is how many in a second?
Eighteen claps in one second.
OK, I need to slow this down.
Brrrr. Brrrr.
How many was that was?
But the the the the the the the the the I think that's ten.
Brrrr. You can't do 18 in one second.
Think about how fast that is. Brrrr.
I think that was me doing the like
that was like the the the the the that was probably 15 times.
How do you physically do that?
I can do like the the the the the the the the the the the the the the the the the.
I probably do like six or like ten.
That's crazy. Watch the video.
There's a video. It's time to.
OK, there's an ad. Just hold on.
OK, so this is the world record.
This is the world record you're saying right here.
World record most claps in one minute.
Well, they have to show it.
Wait, what?
Hello, my name is seven.
I'm going to try to break the record
of speed clapping.
We're going to start.
So, you know, the market said.
Wait, what? Oh, what is happening here?
This music does not fit.
Can I just say, wow, I'm so confused.
So he is essentially sliding.
This is one hand clapping.
What? But in slow mo, I don't even have to.
OK, so I see what's going on.
So he's he's hitting the bottom part of his palm
with the top of his fingers on the opposite hand.
So he's going like tick, tick, tick, tick, tick.
Let me try.
So it's it's like here and then here.
So that he's hitting.
This is where the contact is, is here and here.
Ah, how do you do that for a full minute?
Bad form. How do you do that for a minute?
Go for it for a minute.
All right. I'm going to do it for a minute. Time me.
You guys, should we time me?
Turn the. OK, let me let me get my noise gate off.
Hold on. OK. All right. That's fine.
All right. Let me try it.
Is that better? Is the noise gate gone?
OK, here we go.
Three, two, one timing.
My arms are fucking burning.
I'm still down there.
Don't do it down there.
Don't do it down here.
Don't do that down here.
You do not want the sound of me playing while I'm doing it down here.
That is so much strength to do that.
Even just fucking faking it, even just faking it.
That hurt bad. That's unbelievable.
That takes actual talent and skill to do that.
OK, let's go.
You had me for a little bit.
Pac-Man. Oh, yeah.
That was such a weird. Oh, yeah.
Don't even turn his whole arm weighs five pounds.
Yeah. What do you think?
Now you say that again.
Let's say that again.
That's what you think.
I got a big fucking arm.
The same thing happens again.
I'm going to scream.
Nice turkey arms.
Ah, that's fine. Call me a turkey.
Oh, he's got a turkey neck.
He's got turkey on turkey.
Turkeys are one of the most vicious fucking animals on earth.
They're so deadly and they're crazy.
They will attack you and they're very deadly.
They're incredibly strong.
You ever seen a turkey?
You guys actually seen a turkey in real life?
They are massive, majestic pieces.
They're huge and they're very dangerous.
Turkeys are docile.
Turkeys are very, very strong.
You know, like the zodiac signs.
I wish mine was a turkey.
These games get pretty good graphics.
This is a cute game.
Is there a game pivot coming soon?
Oh, you know what?
Did Vampire Survivors have an update?
I feel like it did.
Did I play it?
Dude, another game came out that was just,
it looked just like Vampire Survivors.
It came out like two days ago.
Is that one any good?
It's really good.
It's got something else, survivors.
It's just, it's just, it's just,
it's just Vampire Survivors is what it looks like.
Oh, come on.
Taco Bell or McDonald's?
Well, that depends on what you're going to order
from Taco Bell.
If your order at Taco Bell is the cheesy Gordita crunch,
then that's what you're going to get.
If you get some other weird bullshit from Taco Bell
that's not very good, then I'm sorry.
I'm going to have to tell you that's,
I'm going to recommend not.
Oh, I like this level.
Doritos tacos.
Doritos tacos are, I always feel so bad eating them
because I just know there's almost nothing
that I really want in my body from that.
But you can't deny that it's one of the greatest tasting
things in the world.
How am I doing?
I'm doing okay.
I'm doing good.
I'm doing as good as I can be, right?
I'm on a fast stop.
I'm so sorry to hear that.
Yeah, that's, that's hard.
When I had my colonoscopy done,
I remember you have to fast for three days.
I think it was like three, four days.
You can't have food.
You can have clear liquids.
And I think that there's one or two very,
very basic small things,
but you can't eat food for three days.
One of the things that happens,
it's not the fact that not eating food
that is what caused me problems.
It's like, I can handle that.
Look, after a day or two where you just,
God, I just want a fucking steak.
But what really is the problem for me,
it's not that, it's the fact that the headache,
that kind of, like you haven't had no real nutrients
for two or three days.
You just have this migraine that is just awful.
At least that's what happened to me.
Yeah, the actual procedure is simple.
It's one of the easiest things in the world.
It's the prep for a colonoscopy that sucks.
It's not, the procedure is easy.
It's 100% simple.
There's a fruit that's fond, oh, you can get it.
All right, open that drawer.
I mean, how did I miss the first N?
Anybody pictures from the procedure?
I'm definitely not going to share my colonoscopy photos.
I think that would get me banned from Twitch.
I don't think you can, I'm not sure you can do that.
You have to drink, yeah, they give you this drink
that you have to drink over the course of a couple of days.
And let me just tell you without giving you too much detail.
It makes you do something over and over again.
Just distort the image.
What, I wonder what?
You can use your imagination.
I want to see what the boss of this area is
and then we'll play either Vampire Survivors
or I want to, maybe I'll try that new one.
You guys are telling me,
actually figure out what the hell it's called.
It's called, it came out like today.
It's called Soul Stone Survivors Prologue.
It's not the full game, I guess.
Is that one any good?
I tried it.
It's pretty good.
You know, I kind of wish there was a retro mode
to see what this looked like 15 plus years ago,
whatever it was, 20 years ago.
Are you going to rage with Pac-Man?
No, I'm not.
I was just considering a pivot.
I feel like this game is pretty long.
It's probably at least six to seven levels long.
Remember, I'm the never complete a game Andy,
unless it's a from software game.
Ooh, what's in here?
I wouldn't need this.
Water or somewhere that I missed?
Oh well.
Do a BRB then switch game.
Yeah, that's what I'll probably end up doing.
I mean, is there, how far am I to the end of the game?
Is there another area?
There's probably at least one more area after this.
Two more worlds.
World four of six.
Hmm, do I want to complete Pac-Man world
just to say that I did?
Or do I leave this up to interpretation for you?
Because you guys, you could find out for yourself
what happens in the end.
Does the evil Pac-Man kill everyone
and take over Pac-World?
I don't know.
I guess, but I don't know if we're ever going to know.
Ooh, hot plates.
Hmm, why?
I supposed to be the clown boss.
And then, all right, do a poll right now.
Should I play the new vampire survivors?
Vampire survivors like,
or should I play vampire survivors?
Let's do a vote.
Don't even fall.
What am I looking at here?
Wait, can I not?
Oh, right here.
Ultra kill got an update.
I don't know if I'm in the first person shooter
crack mode right now.
I don't think I'm in crack mode at the moment.
Next thing we're going to do,
we're going to go back to sorcery part three.
That's what we're going to do on Wednesday.
And then wait, hold on.
All right, all right.
So I can officially announce.
All right, it's time for the official announcement.
I, Jeremy Elbertson, AKA German985 on Thursday.
Ladies and gentlemen,
I'm going to be on Name Your Price.
Austin show.
Oh my God.
Why can I not just remember to press?
It's not the jump button.
I will be on Name Your Price.
I think I'm going to do a pretty good job.
What time is it going to be at?
I don't, I think somewhere around two Pacific.
I think we're around somewhere between one and two Pacific.
It's a game show.
Who am I going to be against?
I actually don't know.
You'll have to, you have to watch.
You're going to play Glover?
Ah, how do we watch it?
It's going to be on Austin show.
You don't know Austin show.
I would go follow it now.
Follow the channel.
Follow Austin.
He's a streamer.
Is it going to be on Twitch?
Yes.
It will be on twitch.tv.
I'm very excited.
The concept of the stream.
It's a game show, obviously.
And it's kind of like, they show products
and you have to guess how whoever gets closest
to what the actual cost of the product was or is.
Kind of like, almost like the prices, right?
Kind of style.
I think I'll do a pretty good job.
Sounds good.
Yeah, no, it should be fun.
I'm excited.
It's going to be in person too.
So it is.
Ooh, that was a tough jump.
That's this Thursday at 2 p.m. Pacific
on Austin's channel, Austin show.
Are you, I'll tweet it out.
Yep.
I'll make sure to tweet it so you know where it is.
Are you going to be cringe or funny?
I'm going to win.
I'm planning to win, guys.
Do you even buy household products?
No, I haven't bought cleaning supplies in 10 years.
I don't even know what aisle it's in.
What are you talking about?
All right, this is it.
Please don't embarrass us.
I'm going to.
You're going to be ashamed that you know this channel
after Thursday.
I just fall.
I like to clown ghosts, that's funny.
All right, what's the boss?
Oh, cool, it's the same song.
Oh, I thought you were actually happy about that.
How many songs did the original one have?
Oh my God.
All right, if I die one more time,
I'm changing to the van first.
Wait, did we even do a pole?
I completely forgot.
Did we run a pole?
So what happened?
Wow, I still died.
I'm so, I feel like my eyes just went frost.
Flutter to the end of the level.
Oh shit, I can't.
I'm not high enough.
It stopped, it actually stopped.
I didn't stop that.
That, I hit the limit.
That's quite the limit.
Why even have a limit?
Why is there a limit at that point?
Is it even necessary to have a limit?
All right, I just want to hear the clowns laugh.
Boss clown.
And then we'll move on.
No, I don't care, nevermind.
All right, what's this game called?
That was Pac-Man World, it was actually pretty fun.
It was actually a fun game.
I just, I don't care.
It was fun, it was enjoyable.
I think it was definitely worth playing.