Hey guys, what's up? How are you? We're here currently live, technically live.
I cannot guarantee that we're gonna be live for very long. We've had cocks at the house for the
last like six straight days and they may have figured out one of the issues. So it's just like
the first Red Dead stream, that's right. We'll see how long we can go. This is gonna be one of
those mystery boxes that you open. The stream might be two hours. It might be 10 minutes.
It might be six hours. I don't know. I can't some mystery. Just literally RNG the stream.
I know it already already already dead. No, no, we're okay. Are we? No. Hey, I'm here.
We just almost dropped though. That's probably gonna happen like every 15 minutes.
That's one minute. Oh shit. All right, when I press the button, it's probably, it's probably
gonna do that. So let's ride it out here for as long as we can. We'll do my, do my best to.
Oh, this is getting ugly. And before he moves back. No, there's no going back.
Damn, it was just green for so long too. It was just so solid green and now it just doesn't wanna,
it just doesn't wanna do it. Let's just, what's with the music? You might be hearing the PS4
sound effects. Let's see. It's there. Moved on from Comcast and got worse internet.
I have no idea. It's almost like a bad joke at this point because this is a gigabit line.
This is a, this is a thousand megabits per second down. This is what we get for down.
And they're, they just have some major, major issues that are apparently,
take a lot of work to solve. So this is happening way more frequently than it just was.
Nice, already buffering, getting a buffering pop up already. Yeah. Well, we're, well, let,
let just, just hang out with me for a minute. We'll sit here for a moment because we do get
these spots of like a few hours where it's perfectly fine. I'm getting back in a balloon.
I'm going back to Boston. Let's see. What do I take this screen off? What if I do this?
Like you can see that, right? Cause that's, that's red dead right there. Come on. Just like,
just like feed me through to the line that I need to be on. So I cannot guarantee the authenticity
of this current stream. And I'm, I'm so afraid to press the story button. I'm going to press
X and it's going to crash the fucking node. What a social club. I think it's the rock star thing
when you get online, right? Press X. Should I? I'm so scared. I'm so scared that it's not going to
work. Oh shit. Here goes the node. I'm doing it. I don't care. I will fight through the frame drops
here. Cause you guys wouldn't even believe this is nothing. We would lose internet for 12 straight
hours. It would just be zero. All right. I'm going. Um, here we go. Wish me luck. Ready? One,
two. I did it. Okay. Okay. I'll turn it up a little bit. So this is, so this is red dead
redemption too, by the way, you weren't aware. This is a new Western game that came out.
I mean, is this supposed to be somebody talking here? Spoilers. Well, what are you doing at a red
dead two stream? If you're scared about spoilers. I lived in Vinnie's dryer for a week.
No, that's not out of the ordinary though. I pay rent and the age of outlaws and gunslingers was
at an end. I have to turn this up. It was like a volume control on this dumb thing.
There we go. Turn it up. It's got to do a cowboy accent. I've even the wish had mostly been tamed.
That was until they showed up. Bill Bob, Barry, Borg, a few gangs still remain, but they were
being hunted down and destroyed. I can't read cursive. I got taught cursive. I don't know how
to read it. There we go. That was a cursive. I would have been upset about that. Rockstar games
presents red dead two. Why does it look like horror movie text? Here we go. I'm so excited for this.
Give me my internet. I deserve. I deserve an internet.
That's a lot of bird shit. All right, stop. I want to make a joke about a million birds
shitting all over them, but I can't stop it. Don't stop soon. We'll all be dying.
Whether it's May, I'm just hoping the law got as lost as we did.
It's me, right?
10 FPS with gameplay. You might be referring to my internet. Chapter one.
Byron. I don't know what that says. I'm not gonna read the subtitles at the bottom. I'm gonna try
to read it. This game is like an hour long tutorial. Hey, just long enough to us to make
sure the internet will stay on. Hey, welcome to the stream. Oh my god. Ms. Gaskell, get that
fire. Thank you. Nothing more you could have done. What are we gonna do? We need supplies.
Well, first of all, you're gonna stay here and you were gonna get yourself worn.
And I sent John and Mike scouting out ahead. Thank you so much. See if we can find
wait for some time to deliver these bits to you. It's great to see you back in action,
especially after you had to once again deal with some internet issues still are.
Listen, still are at the moment. Listen to me for a moment. Now we've had a bad couple of days.
I loved Davy, Jenny, Sean, Mac. What's his last name? John barf bag. We don't know. Something like
that. But we lost some folks. Now, if I could throw myself in the ground, in their stead,
I'd do it gladly. Quit Comcast? I don't have Comcast. I have a different ISP across the country.
And it still follows me. Everybody. We're safe. Now, there ain't nobody following us
to a storm like this one. By the time they get here. Well, we're gonna be we're gonna be long
gone. We've been through worse than this. John McFar's stun. That was the guy. Mr. Pearson,
Miss Grimshaw, I need you to turn this place into a camp. You may be here for a few days.
Now all of you, all of you get yourselves worn. Stay strong. It might be the modem router. Oh,
no, no, no. Single option is big. So they both must have headed down the hill.
Oh, are we like dead dead now? Oh, boy. What really went down back there on that boat?
We missed you. That's what happened. Come on. Hey, you need horses? Oh, yeah. Hey, Mr. Smith,
get yourself indoors. I know I can see it over here. Get indoors, son.
All right, I get to play the game, though. Need you strong. Okay, it's deep snow.
Ain't sure what we're gonna find out here, duds. We have to try. Stay close. We'll do our best to
stick to the trail. This goddamn weather. It's been two days or more like this now.
Yeah, I didn't think it was. There's Jabba Dab's $250 coming in. Again, thank you so much, man. I
know I'm like trying to bounce and monitor my connection and play a game and thank you so
fucking much, dude. It's a huge amount of money. It's coming up. Take it easy. Big delayed money.
Yeah, I don't know why that's happening. I don't know what it is with Rockstar and not putting
their flagship video games on PC. The first Red Dead's not even on. Red Dead Redemption's not on
PC at all. For some strange reason.
They're going northeast at the moment. Sick.
I'm sorry. All I heard was crouch in the corner and throw rocks at people. Is that what you wanted
me to do with my like Dalmatian horse? Oh, that's snow, right? I thought it was like a giant
Dalmatian. Is that someone coming towards us? Someone coming towards us. Are they friendly?
Ooh, cutscene. Bring it on. Guy on the left's gonna get picked off with an arrow.
Micah. Gentlemen. The audio's delayed. I think so. Found a little homestead down that
away. Okay. Anyone home? Sure. Place is blazing with light and noise. Sounded like a party. Let's go
see. Follow me. Is anyone is? How's Davey doing? Yeah, this is uh. Nor did little Jenny. Six B's.
Bob's Barry. Bunsen. Bugle.
John? He's talking about our John? My John? First game John?
How is it to hold? It just disappeared. Talk to Mike. Are you sure about this? Let's do that.
Mr. Morgan. I never thought I would be so pleased to see your face.
Things always turn out fine. Except for in Red Dead Redemption. Where's everyone else?
Old mining camp back up the hill. Hung for daddy to put food on the table. Gotta love these graphics
though. Snow actually permeates. I keep saying people tell me to keep looking at the balls.
No. I wouldn't do that in real life. Why would I do it in a video game?
If I was in this time period I wouldn't like go underneath the carriage like it was an oil change.
Like lift up the tail and look at the ball sack. What are you talking about?
You know me. I'm a good boy. You look under your car and look for your car's balls?
What would be the car balls? I'm trying to think what it would be.
The cars? The car balls would be like the muffler right? Okay. Let's keep it down now
gentlemen. It's just up ahead. Exhaust. Turn it down. Let's head down there. I can't fall off this
can I? Health is displayed in the lower left corner. That tiny little thing is health.
That's so small. How am I supposed to see that? Wait is this like Super Mario where there's like
three quadrants? Let's hitch up here. The outer bar shows you. All right but that was like about
an outer bar and an inner bar. Approach the hitching post. Let's get it on here. Triangle
hitches the horse. Now we got our first set of action here I think. Follow Dutch. I remember
Dutch. This is a lot of snow. Why does this have to follow me everywhere I go? I don't understand.
Go to the shed and press R1 to take cover. There's this shed over here.
Glad it took three weeks. Blame, blame Cox Communications.
Because these motherfuckers can't figure it out either. And it's their service. This is the shed
right? It's no. Oh the cattle shed. Like in this thing. This is not the cattle shed. Get up there.
Do I just take my glasses off? How do I get out of here? I'm sorry I haven't been paying attention.
Get in position. What cattle shed is he referring to? In here. Is this not the shed?
Stuck because no blip. No stuck because I have to look over here and watch five percent of every
frame drop. Because it's taken this company three weeks to try to fix a problem. Oh my fucking god
it's infuriating. Go back. Go to the shed. Is it the shed that's like straight in front of me here?
That looked like a cattle shed to me. The huge yellow thing. That's
isn't that where it just was? Like isn't this this is where I was. Isn't this where I was?
Highlighted in yellow. This thing here. Isn't this where it just was?
I just did this. Didn't I just do this? Excuse me. Hello. I didn't hide. Hello friend. What you want?
Very sorry to disturb you. My friends and I. Well we got in some trouble up the way. Lost in the
storm. Gentlemen. We can't help you mister. What's he gonna do? I got folks. Arthur we got a problem.
Protect Dutch. Okay. Is this guy gonna fire at him? I think you should go now.
I just like holy shit this is aiming is a little weird. What's with the aiming? It's like why is
it pulling me? I gotta change the sensitivity here. Great soundtrack. Yeah. All right. Where's it this
way? He's not gonna last by himself out there. Now he won't last at all. You didn't handle it. I had
to do something about it. I'm gonna follow him. Fucking internet companies man. Hold screen your
items. Pick them up while searching the house. We need the essentials. Food. Okay. Medicine.
Whiskey. They're gonna open pots and shit. It's cabinets. Hold near items. Pick them up while
searching. Canned sweet corn. There's a big price on Cuomo Drisco's head. Assorted biscuits.
Fruits. Whiskey is not essential. Are you serious? Your health core drains over time and is now
empty while empty you will experience negative effects. Do you have to eat in this game? Okay.
Slowly restores health core and moderately restores stamina core. Interesting. And then
we have to go bake beans so that I get a middle is your core. Slightly reduce restores health core.
All right. Let's just do this in the middle one first. Let's just try it out. Survival mode it
seems like. Better quality food will refill more core. Okay. I gotta like refill my four cores.
Let's look around for some more stuff. Just controls how fast you refill your health and stamina.
It's better than nothing. There's a lot of random shit on the mantle. Examine the
photograph. Sure. Let's get some lore. Poor bastard was married to. Okay. Flip it around.
Secret code on the back. Quake and ID wedding. Jet. I can't read it. Oh, there we go. Okay.
I'm just kidding. Oh look it's from the first game. That's the cottage from the first game.
All right. What's we got? $2.43. Have we dropped a frame in the last like 15 minutes? Can anybody
tell? Or do I have to like do I have to like scream as loud as I can? I have. God damn it.
Well I say it now and now I just did right here. I think that's all I can get.
Keep looking for stuff. Arthur go see if there's anything in that barn. Okay. Micah
you search the cabin. See what we missed. Sure. All right. Let's go investigate the barn.
I'm gonna go take a look and I'm gonna go examine it. No drop frames since the fight.
Now you can look at the current objective. What's that? Is that a bad guy? Good guy?
Another thing there. The atmosphere is great. Yeah. So far it looks awesome. That guy just
top rope shot. Hey what's happening in here? That guy didn't get one hit in. Should you kill him?
Not yet. Interrogate. Find out what they're doing. All right. Beat him. Oh that son of a
bitch would talk. This is just like the Punisher game. Where is he? Where is he?
Okay. What are you? Anything else? Why are you up here? Fiction to rob some train.
Gonna blow the tracks. No I don't know more. I swear. Thanks for the info buddy.
But say it looks like you have this Arthur. Anything else? What was the last time you shat
your pants? When you're done. Joven. When did it happen? When? When was the last time you shat
your pants? Let's try to grab him again. He's like come here I'm not done with you. Oh there
animals over here? What the fuck? What's happening? Wait what? I have to restart the whole thing?
Oh shit. Wasted. By walking out of the frame. Oh god damn it. Well all right.
Tell us. Tell us again. First passing hug. I can't keep up.
Wasted here. Near the light. What are you bastards? His clothes changed? Why? Fiction to rob some
train. Gonna blow the tracks. No I don't know the net. I swear. That's his worst mission boundaries
than in GTA 5. Well I would say it looks like you have this Arthur. Do what you want with him.
All right so now we get a second chance. Should I spare him? Remember saving Private Ryan.
This motherfucker's gonna come back. I don't want to do that. I don't. But what if he comes back?
Where's my gun? Focus on the horse. Where are you? In the barn? How'd you get in here?
How did you get in here? Well I can calm the horse. This is not my horse.
What if this is gonna freak out and start hitting me? This looks animatronic. I don't know if I
trust it. It's animatronic. Don't ever stand behind a horse. That's what I was told.
Check his balls. No. All right let's lead the horse. Continuing to bomb with your horse increases
its trust in you and improves its attributes. The horse has now become your horse as indicated by a
blip on the radar. Okay. Yeah figured he won't get far. We still fucking dropped. Yeah.
God damn it. This is like I'm like really containing myself right now. I'm like I am
like a I'm holding back but this has been like an infuriating process.
Hmm. Literally moved across the country to a different fucking state. Got a faster line
and it's worse than it was before. That's unbelievable. With a different company. A gigabit
connection. Thousand fucking megabits a second. Eventually it's gonna get fixed but who fucking
knows when. Maybe you're the problem. I don't think so. I haven't had enough time to be the
problem. Turned on the modem. Got an IP. That's it. Oh what the fuck? Get off me.
Hold on. Come in here boy. Let's go.
I didn't hit the wall.
Just keep going west until you get there.
I mean that fire wasn't bad. You could just jump on that thing and roll around and it would have
gone off.
Of course it's okay. We're bad men. We ain't them. It's okay.
Get on. We'll keep you safe until you figure out what you want to do. What's your name miss?
Miss. Adler. Adler. What is it that you're used to calling an easy during a blizzard?
He he was my husband.
Hey somebody's coming. Looks like it's Dutch. Hey everybody Dutch is back. We good. How'd you get
on? Micah found a homestead but he weren't the first. Colm or Driscoll and his scum they beat
us to it. We found some of them there but there is more about apparently scouting the train.
Thank you. This is not on PC unfortunately. Well it is what it is but we found some supplies some
blankets a little bit of food and this poor soul Mrs. Adler Miss Tilly Miss Karen would you warm
her up give her a drink or something and Mrs. Adler it's gonna be okay you're safe now they
turned her into a widow. He might never be on PC but the last one wasn't either. That's like
the unfortunate thing. I need some rest. I haven't slept in three days. You're over here. Miss O'Shea
I'll show you the way. Mr. Morgan we put you in a room over here. Thank you Miss Grimshaw.
Mr. Bell here with the fellas over there. Well how come Arthur gets a room and I get a bunk bed
next to Bill Williamson and a bunch of darkies. Get yourself to bed. Rocks are a bunch of idiots
for not putting it on PC. Yeah I don't know there's got to be some reason why. It does not but I
really wonder. He ain't been seen in days. The weather ain't let up. He's strong and he's smart.
Strong at least. Hello Arthur. Abigail. Arthur how you doing? Just fine Abigail and you? I need
you to I'm sorry I'm sorry to ask but. It's little John. He's got himself caught into a scrape again.
He ain't been seen in two hours. Two days. Your John will be fine. I mean he may be as dumb as rocks
and as dull as rusted iron but that ain't changing because he got caught in some snowstorm. Please go
take a look. Javier? Yes. Javier will you ride out with Arthur to take a look for John? You're the two
best fit men we've got. Now? We're all pretty worried about him. I know the situation were
reversed and he looked for me. Thank you. British accent? This way. Last I know John was headed up
the river. We know he kept riding north. Not like that. That emote is making my chat scroll
horizontally. Wait what? Wait what? Wait hold on. What are you talking about?
It's time to find John. Alright I need to like get happy. I'm like sad right now because of this
internet bullshit. I gotta get like excited. This is Red Dead Redemption 2. This is not like
another iPad game. Hey I see some smoke. Come on let's take a look. Let's hope it ain't more of
O'Driscoll's boys. Seems somebody left recently. Let's do some investigating reporting here.
Did he do it? Did he do it? Did he do it? Did he do it? Are we not going to like it anyways? What?
What? I loved the first one. The first one was great. Let's inspect the camp.
But what? There could be dust. There could be fingerprints or finger dust on here.
Fine. Alright fine fine fine. I wanted to fucking dust for fingerprints and he didn't want to do
shit. Watch out watch out. Hot hot hot hot. Ow burning burning. Burn. Burn my horse's legs.
Stamina drains when your horse gallops or jumps. I can't see anything.
We had the money. It seemed fine. Somebody turn the antennas around.
Bounty hunters? No Pinkerton. It was crazy. Raining bullets. That lake was steaming.
Well this is a beautiful mountain though. Watch out for this crevice.
To change camera distance and perspective press. It wouldn't even let me do the YouTuber joke. Come
on. Why? Come on. Oh what? Sorry. I got off track. Let me just look. Whoa!
The horse wouldn't do it. But you get off and you can do it. The horse is smarter.
See they continue up that way. That fall was so stupid too. It was like he lost control of all
of his body and function. And that like ahhhh. It was like Emperor Palpatine. He was thrown into
the thing in the end of the fourth movie. He just did the Emperor Palpatine scream.
We had the money. It seemed fine. Then suddenly they were everywhere. Hunters? No Pinkerton.
It was crazy. All right so I got the stamina bar. Take it slow. The horse bar has the horseshoe.
Okay so that's distance. That's what I want. Fps boat. Bad way. But it was a bad situation.
That ain't like him though. Okay not gonna do it. There's some tracks leading to the river.
It's not funny. I'm sorry. It's not funny. Wait that was a bear? What are you talking about a bear?
That was I was trying to turn around because I was making the fake.
It's not funny. It is funny. It is funny. Whatever. It was a bear? I don't think it was a bear.
We had the money. It seemed fine. Was it a bear?
Pinkerton. It was crazy. No bullets. It's not funny. Please stop. I'm sorry.
Take it slow. Big ravine here. Get me. I'm not going over there. Dutch killed a girl. My side.
Bad way. But it was a bad situation. That ain't like him though. Tracks go left. Down here.
Baby got shot. I'm not doing it one more time. Both shot too. Sean we don't even know. I'm
surprised we escaped at all. By the time you boys showed up from the other side of town.
Only just holding on to that business all right. Activate cinematic camera. Hold this button down.
Damn snow's coming in hard again. We'll lose these tracks if we don't move fast.
Automatically follow roads. Oh that's so you can. It's like watching an actual movie.
Nice. Change cinematic camera press R3. All right that there's a lot of there's a lot of use cases
for this I think. But am I still controlling the character? Oh shit yeah I am. That's hard to do.
All right I'm gonna play the whole game like this. I'm gonna be the first streamer on Twitch.
The first guy on Twitch to do it only in cinematic mode. Looks like you know when you
were 14 and you made that machinima. That's what I'm doing right now. I'm not gonna turn it off.
Why would I turn this off? Oh wow let's investigate. He was riding this horse.
Hell. Where? Up here. I heard it from this way. Is this the right way? Am I going the
right way? I gotta get it out of my system now. Oh shit. Okay don't. Okay no no no no. Just relax.
I'm not gonna fucking do it again. I'm sorry.
I have like the cinematic mode. I'm trying. I can't do it yet. Let's give me the prompt.
The first five minutes of the game. I'm having fun though. I'm actually gonna try to play the
whole game in cinematic mode. That'll be my schnick right? Like what the fuck?
Livestreamer plays entire Red Dead 2 in cinematic camera?
Okay here we go. No I'm not I'm not gonna jump. I'm not falling off another edge.
That is a 100% guarantee. Like I can 100% guarantee. If I fall off the edge in the
next like minute or two in this like little tutorial I will do 100 push-ups in a row on camera.
All right here we go.
I'm coming in hard again. We'll lose these tracks if we don't move fast.
Oh good. Take the germ attacks 30%. It adds the bars too that's important. I'm not gonna fall.
I'm doing the thing that's impossible. You cannot fall like this. It's not possible. I'm holding X.
Watch yourself. I'm tensed up right now like you wouldn't believe. Yeah a lot of fresh snow here.
I like this one. How am I gonna aim and shoot at people with cinematic camera? Is that possible?
So close to the edge yeah. She has to guess. You can't I can't just guess.
This is beautiful though. Let's get a different angle here. Let's see if he can hear us.
So John is here somewhere. All right I'm gonna follow him. Up there. Don't say up there.
Okay I'm gonna follow you. Don't push me off. All right here we go. Is it do I go over this?
All right we're good. We have to walk from here. Oh no. Oh no. Grab shotgun. Force weapons.
Okay so R1. Okay we can only heal one sidearm. So I'm gonna get the shotgun.
So did I lose cinematic? There we go. It's back. Wait hold on. Okay. Oh it turns off right when you
hold the button down. You can't do it. But wait is this an edge? Okay we're good. It's on. It's on.
It's coming from this way. Hey watch out here. I'm not cheating. I want to see from another angle.
I don't want to see. Holy fuck. I just that doesn't count. I fell off a ledge onto another ledge. I
didn't die. This damage is played in the lower left corner. I don't have it. Watch yourself.
Okay this doesn't count either because this is okay. Be careful here. Oh god damn it. Okay back
there. Watch your head. Yeah I'm all right. This is the most stressful thing I've done in a long time.
Am I running the lip? Watch your step. This is real slippery. Stay close to the wall. My stamina
core is empty. Square in this climb. Get access to the shaft. I need to eat something man.
That's what I need. Some stamina here. Classic oat cakes. Is there just a stamina one?
Just canned peaches is fine. That looks odd from cinematic view. All right we're doing fine.
Just eating peaches. Canned peaches are where it's at man. That's good shit.
John. John. John we'll be looking for you. John the street lights are on. You're in deep shit
when you get home. Where is he? He's in the game. He's in the game. Where is he? That's quite a
scratch you got there. Never thought I'd say this but good to see you Arthur Morgan. So he is in
the game. Wow. I don't look so good. I don't feel too good neither. I could probably do that if I
tried hard enough. Now we gotta we gotta cinematically walk him back to his car.
Oh we actually do.
I think I think this is just supposed to happen right?
If we go on the right is this supposed to be okay?
Uh-oh. Wildlife. We're being hunted by wolves. I'll distract him while you get to the horses.
Who's gonna distract him? All right yeah to get to the horses.
Keep the wolves away from both of them. Let's get you on that horse. That's just not gonna work.
Let's get away from it. No it takes it off cinematic mode. Oh well we tried.
Okay let's get going before any more of these bastards show up. Get him on the horse. You can
see you're gonna drive him? Okay do first person mode. That's actually a good idea too.
Okay where is he? Oh shit. All right yeehaw. We're gonna get a yeehaw.
Please don't commit to this. I'm not committing to it. This is not very cinematic.
Okay.
He just buried his face in the ground. Just slid.
Is this the portal soundtrack?
I don't think so.
It's really crazy that John Marsden's in this game and he just becomes Darth Vader in the next one.
You can see his origin story here. That's really cool.
Damn they're getting even the death ain't good enough for you.
We're good. I did it. I made it.
Super voice. Can I scream too? Does it help?
We got some help. We need some help. Come on help him down. Help. Here we go. One two three.
Come on let's get you warm. Thank you. Thank you both. This is a new love even by your standards.
Thank you Arthur. Thank you. Any other lost maidens need saving? Not today.
Have you and Dutch talked about how we're gonna get out of this?
I was just discussing with Herr Strauss when the weather breaks. I suppose we'll have to keep heading east. East into all that.
That civilization. I know.
The west is where our problems are worse. The west. Come on Herr Strauss. Let's get warm. Thank you, Mr. Morgan.
You never seen this game before? Is it on the Sega Genesis?
We've been running for weeks. We found shelter and been resting here.
I was just gonna scream yes, but I'm not a screamer.
Events and interesting locations are noted in your journal as you explore. Hold w to view. Hold x for details.
Log. Enter pursuit by memory. John hasn't returned from an earlier scouting trip. Arthur and
Javier ride out into the snow to look for him.
Okay.
Checklist. Kill all the wolves without taking any damage. Complete with the least 80. Didn't do either of those.
That's all right. Let's take a look at this.
Here's the journal.
I guess.
That's very bad drawing.
You know when like somebody asks you for directions
and you draw them a terrible map of intersections?
What's it just looks like?
Uh, okay. So, uh, and
Can I just draw in here too?
What is this book? Why would I not use this piece of paper on the left? It's a waste of trees.
Is it the white house?
We're safe. Stay strong.
Oh, okay. Blacksmithing.
I can't read this.
Oh, thank god it can be translated.
That's kind of cool.
Continue playing to unlock your bonus content.
Oh, I'm one of the suckers that spent 80 dollars to get like the one mission that nobody else gets.
I feel real great about that purchase, by the way.
All right, let's just go. Let's just do some shit. We got our mini map here.
Got a horse. Yeah.
Hold L2 to talk.
33 year old substitute teacher can't read cursing.
Let's go.
I haven't been a substitute teacher in a long time.
All right. All right, let's talk. L2, greet.
Another cold morning.
What? What is it doing? Wait, why?
Why did it make me get off for it to go to the bathroom? Get over here.
What are you doing? Hey!
Come here. Come back here. What are you going?
All right, relax.
Shit and run.
I guess we can do B or P.
Let's just do wits right here. Let's just do P.
B or P.
I don't feel like being laughed at by the likes of you two. Stop it now.
You fools punching each other when Como Driscoll's needing punching hard.
You want to sit around waiting for him to come find us?
All of you, we got work to do. All right, I have the team mission.
Are you sure about this, Dutch? Yes.
Pope's been through a lot recently. We hardly back on our feet yet.
And the last thing we need is to get Bushwhacked by Como Driscoll.
Let's go.
I know you hate him, Dutch. He's here for us.
I doubt that.
No, you're just doubting me. I would never doubt you, Dutch.
You always said revenge is a luxury we can't afford.
This is a right call, Arthur. Take this.
Why does he just sound like a pitch-shifted version of him?
They were talking about trains, detonators.
Here, Combe always had good information. Come on.
And you think now is the right time to hit a train?
Now you, my fancy living on deer piss and rabbit shit, I'm getting too old for that life.
Mr. Matthews, Mr. Smith, Mr. Pearson, would you please look after the place?
There are old Driscolls about.
Voice crack, voice crack. Everyone laugh at him, right?
You laugh at me.
And that guy's way stronger than all of you.
Southwest, right, Arthur?
You should follow the main trail southwest.
Right, point it out. Everybody point it out in the chat, right?
Let's go find these bastards.
All right, so we're gonna go. This is a robbery.
Cinematic mode, automatic. I didn't even.
Automatic cinematic. I didn't even do it.
Somebody turn on the AC. It's getting hot in here.
Automatic cinematic.
I'll scold myself for that one later in the shower, I promise.
I'm sorry. I've been away for like three weeks.
I'm gonna be in the shower being like with my hand up,
wicked hot water just going like, fucking stupid.
Don't ever say something like that again.
It must be this way.
You good, Dutch?
Listen, I know you don't think much of my eyes recently, but this is the right move.
Okay.
Debatable.
You know I'm gonna be back.
Stream the shower.
You learned a long time ago that you hit Como Driscolls.
No drop frames, by the way.
I get to get out of meltdown mode.
I'm in the fun, fun mode.
Just give it 10 minutes for me to pull off on another like audibly upset.
You know like the difference when somebody's like, oh, I'm pissed off.
What the heck, man?
Whoa, I can't believe I died there.
What's happening here?
Oh, damn it.
First, when you start talking like this, like this fucking stupid fucking thing,
like when you, that's how you know somebody's really angry.
And they start like, they get like kind of internally,
they're so hot and they're nervous and shit.
Like they start fucking getting angry like that.
It's not like, what the fuck?
Whoa, I died in the game.
Oh, I'm so mad.
Whoa.
Are we birds?
All right, gentlemen.
This is it.
We goddamn ready.
Ready, Dutch.
Good.
That was very, very good.
That was like a classroom attendance.
This morning, we're gonna head up here a little.
See if we can't get a sense of the layout of the camp.
Mr. Williamson, Mr. Bell, you two take up a hidden position just outside the camp.
Mr. Summers, Mr. Escuela, you two hold position here.
Let's go.
All right.
Throw haymaker.
I'm depleting.
This is absolutely beautiful.
You know, this is beautiful.
It's just beautiful out here.
That was at the same time.
Here they are.
That's definitely them.
Holy shit, this is what it looks like to look through his eyes.
I think so.
Gotta go to a doctor, man.
Yeah, that's it.
You didn't do prescription.
You got astigmatism, bro.
All right, headshot from all the way back here.
What was wrong with that one?
Who's he talking to?
He don't seem very happy.
They leaving?
Seem to be.
Should we go get them?
No.
Cole can wait.
Best to get some of them out of there.
All right, so we're gonna sneak up.
Metal Gear Solid 3 Neck Snap.
Two of them.
I was hoping I could see his big eyes.
Like Macaulay Culkin style.
Weapons not set on your load before dismounting will remain on your horse.
Pick them off from up there.
You got it, Dutch.
All right, so we got...
Approach your horse to view store.
Hold L...
Do it.
Okay, so where's the rifle?
Right here.
Long arm back carbine or carbine repeater.
Oh, that's just the slot it's in.
Okay, I get it.
And I'll take the shotgun too.
What?
Horse weapons.
We'll circle around the far side and go down that way.
Same as Micah and Bill.
Change sense.
Yeah, that's...
I probably should.
Like you said, revenge.
I'll get it right eventually.
We can't afford.
Yeah, just wasn't sure you agreed with me.
Arthur.
Does this stay winter the whole game?
Arthur, have you completely lost faith in me?
Our needs right now are supplies, equipment, and a way out of here.
Everything else, including coal.
Okay, there's enough of those bastards down there to deal with as it is.
All right, so we're gonna go carbine.
Not every area is snow.
Well, it's good at least that they put it in.
It's not just the desert and only the desert.
Take a shot every time somebody says okay.
All right, no fucking around here.
Look at how funny the streamer is jokes here.
You know what I'm saying?
And we already got that.
We got a cinematic mode.
Oh, LOL.
And then, oh, I fell off three times.
LOL.
And then, you know, I'm not doing that again.
Steve here.
Can they see us?
I don't think I should be crouched.
I can't do it here.
This is such a long walk down.
Wait till I get the game to open up for me before I do any dumb shit.
Baby, I'll take the lead on this.
What a terrible stream.
Hey.
They're gonna be gunning for you.
What?
They ain't got me yet.
Why?
What happened?
I'm just playing Red Dead.
Just jump off.
No.
One guy said that.
Yeah, and he's the one guy now.
Why do I always read negative feedback?
Gosh, I need to make sure everyone's happy.
And if people are not having fun, then I want to make sure you're having fun.
I really can't fuck this up.
I got to be on point here.
No, like, where's the shed?
Is that the shed?
Why am I dropping frames?
I don't...
No, I'm...
Is that a guy?
No, that's a good guy.
Take the lead.
He's giving me an opportunity.
Look at Dutch to give instructions.
Send in the gang.
I'll take the lead.
Wait, does the sniper elite thing?
Damn it.
Tapping R2 when not aiming.
Okay.
This is the last guy.
Oh, I'm on top of the roof.
God, don't fall.
Oops, sorry.
That guy was making a video.
I should have been quiet.
That guy was, like, recording.
He's definitely, like, laughing and, like, screaming right now.
Get over there.
Pocket sensitivity.
Lord.
I got somebody.
Oh, I'm not sure.
Right through his hat.
One more guy.
Where is he?
Right here?
Oh, he just got me right in the mouth.
He showed me right in the face.
I'm actually getting shot right in the face like that.
Damn it.
Just be dead.
What did I shoot twice?
Oh, that was the slow motion.
FP.
Oh, all right.
Is this 90 FOV, though?
This just makes me want this to be on PC.
There's so many corpses, though.
How am I going to get them all?
There is a slider in the menu.
Is there?
I don't know.
What?
A camera?
Okay.
Yeah.
It is there.
Get that fucking head bob off, please.
All right.
Cool.
Is it, uh, fly immediately?
Actually, that...
No FOV number.
It's just this one.
Bar.
Bar dragged to the edge.
Oh, hey, hey, hey.
More of them are coming in right now?
I didn't get a chance to loot.
First person.
Well, aiming sure is a thousand times better in first person.
I will definitely say that.
I'll say that.
Defend.
Is there...
Is there Deadeye in this game?
Damn.
I'm not going to knock this cat off.
I'm going to cover.
Oh, there is Deadeye.
I can even, like, see it.
Oh, shit.
Got that guy.
He's dead.
I don't have to worry about him causing any problems.
Shit.
Oh, my God.
I didn't...
I didn't want to...
I don't like that.
I didn't like that.
Holy shit.
Holy fuck.
That was insane.
All right.
New, uh...
Oh, here we go.
Weapon wheel.
Deadeye tonics.
Fully restores Deadeye.
Okay.
You can...
You release to use them.
Hides your identity while committing crimes.
Okay.
Let's bring it right back up.
All right.
Let's keep looking around.
I got this many bodies.
Do it with the shotgun?
Lord.
He didn't like it.
He loved it.
They're probably going to keep coming over here.
I guess I have to do it.
Is this...
You can actually cut people's heads off in the game?
My Lord.
Shoot the bodies with the shotgun.
Oh, man.
No way.
No fucking way.
There's, like, this...
That's...
That's insane.
It's just...
It's brutal.
Oh, man.
This is brutal.
This game ain't coming out in Germany.
Like, no way.
This game ain't going to release in Japan.
Is it out in, like, Germany and Japan?
What do they do?
It is out.
Okay.
Blood confirmed it is out in Germany.
As is?
Wow.
Well, hold on.
Yeah.
I have to loot everybody.
You can't give me all these exes here.
Got somebody's belt buckle?
I will.
But just hold on.
There could be money on everybody.
89 cents?
I'm just collecting bits right now.
What does this guy have?
What does this guy have on him?
Hey, thank you for the championship belt.
Big bits.
All right.
We'll look for, like...
Come on.
What do you got?
No.
That guy's not even...
That guy's not a sub.
Come on.
We don't even have, like, a sub?
What?
How many people here aren't even subbed?
All right.
I gotta cut that out.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
All right.
What do we got here?
He's on to us.
Because he's...
I'm just...
I'm not...
No.
I don't care if you aren't subscribed.
Don't worry.
Chewing tobacco?
Cool.
Pressuring fans.
No, you guys know that.
It's not a...
I don't care.
Oh, there's an upper le...
Oh, there's a Fortnite chest up here!
What's in here?
Epic!
Is it an epic?
Holy shit.
Somebody's...
Hey, the great Lord Walden just gave out
20 tier 1 community subs.
Thank you.
Thank you so much, dude.
20, 20 subs here from Walden.
Thanks, man.
Oh, my Lord.
No, no, that's not...
This is not what...
Thank you for the 10 subs, Afrik.
Thank you.
Oh, here it comes.
I'm just gonna keep my mouth shut.
But thank you, guys.
Unnecessary, but thank you.
All right.
I gotta search up here.
There's still things that I need to get.
Okay, that hurt.
What else is in here?
Sub...
Oh, there's a chest.
I told you there's a Fortnite chest in here.
Take.
Is it a knife?
$2.12.
And cigarettes.
Whoa.
What is it?
Is this dynamite?
How would I even climb this?
But thank you, though.
Those guys giving out those subs.
Really appreciate it.
Did we get everything?
Think so, boss.
Found this on one of them.
Thank you.
This is perfect.
Oh, yeah.
Interesting.
This is something about the train they was gonna rob.
Train mission.
I bought it.
It was $20.
A Mr. Leviticus Cornwall.
Mount back up.
Let's keep moving.
What does dynamite smell like?
All right, let's get out of here.
Proud of you, boys.
All of you.
Raisins.
Now that's tobacco.
Gunpowder smells like...
Not bad for some starving down in...
They can pummel us hard as they like.
It's hard to describe.
We'll always get back up and fight.
That's who we outlawed.
Wait until we have John, Sean back...
If you drop the frame, it's gonna happen.
I can't even get angry about it anymore.
This hit'll hurt him a lot more than anybody in the head.
You know, there's no sense crying over spilt milk.
Sorry, spilt.
It's just gonna happen.
But I guess we'll see about that.
Just thankfully it's not happening as frequently as it was the beginning of the train.
You know, he'll come after us.
Oh, of course he will.
Just like all the rest.
But we're gonna stay a step ahead of them.
Make sure we always know where they are.
Until they know where we are.
We allowed ourselves to get a step behind at Blackwater.
That won't happen again.
All right, hang in, fellas.
Let's make some ground.
Cowboy Skyrim.
Yeah, that's not a bad thing, though.
It really makes you feel like Spider-Man.
That's right.
Bring him back alive.
You got it.
Chase down and lasso Old Driscoll.
So do I get the la-
Hold and get the weapon wheel.
This is gonna bring up the lasso.
Okay, hold L2 to ready the lasso and aim it at Old Driscoll.
One of the most fun mechanics of the last game here it is.
Keep L2 held and dismount.
Let's interrogate him in the water.
Let's drown this motherfucker.
He got out.
Where did he go?
Oh, he's-
He actually is, like, getting drowned.
Give him a stone.
Yep, drop him on the back of the horse.
He might actually be able to drown.
Maybe.
Okay.
Yellow line in the radar is the shortest route in the yellow truck.
Press the thumb stick to pet the horse.
Yeah, I got him.
I pet him.
I gave him a little-
Hey, you're doing a great job.
Thank you.
Shut up.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on.
Come on, where is it?
Come on.
Trying to shoot the bird.
Can you throw dynamite at birds in this game?
Does it follow them like in the last one?
What bird?
The bird that was on the right.
Yes, that does-
That is still in the game.
You can try.
I mean, we'll-
Eventually we'll try.
Seeing birds from other dimensions now.
204 bones to go.
Bring him to the fire and drop him in.
We're eating good tonight.
Hold near your horse to remove him.
I would.
No, I can't right now.
We can't do that.
I'm not doing that whole thing again.
I thought I was going to start cutting him.
Uncle.
Mr. Williamson.
Tie this maggot up someplace safe.
We get him hungry first.
I got a saying, my friend.
We shoot fellas.
There's no need shooting.
Save fellas.
There's no need saving.
And feed them.
There's no need feeding.
We are going to find out what you need.
I can't believe it.
An O'Driscoll in my camp.
I ain't an O'Driscoll, mister.
I ain't-
Oh, whatever you say, son.
Well done, Arthur.
I'm just sorry we missed out on call.
Why am I still holding them?
Well, there's time enough for that.
Now, I gotta figure out if we can hit that train.
Okay.
That's a long saying.
Old friends complete.
Now we got P on the map.
Oh, excuse me.
I probably got an F.
Complete the mission without taking any health items.
One, two, three, four, five.
I got a 25% on the test.
Now, let's keep going through the tutorial.
Well, I don't-
I don't even need to get on the horse.
He's literally right here.
Stu, I'll take you.
I'm gonna starve to death up here, Mr. Morgan.
We're okay.
We have a few cans of food and a rabbit.
For what?
10, 12 people?
That was in the Navy.
I do not wish to hear about what you got up to in the Navy, Mr. Pearson.
We were stranded at sea.
For 50 days.
And you unfortunately survived.
When we ran away from Blackwater, I wasn't able to get supplies in.
Idiot streamer, idiot streamer.
Sometimes shopping trips need to be cut short.
We'll survive.
We always have.
If needs be, we can eat you.
You're the fattest.
I sent Lenny and Bill hunting and they-
Oh, ew.
Gross.
I mean, fucking disgusting.
Bill's a fool.
Unless those mountains are full of game they want to read,
ain't no wonder they found enough of this.
We'll go find something.
Come on, Arthur.
Wait a second.
Hold on.
Here.
You're gonna need something to eat out there.
Assorted salted off.
Starving will be preferable.
Come on, let's go.
Is it weird that these gross shit items that are in these games,
rotten can of beans and packed in spam that's four years expired,
I want to eat them.
If I could pull that out of history and eat it,
I would probably do it right now.
Nobody else does that?
I can't use it and you'll have to.
Bow and arrow.
Use a gun and we'll scare off every animal for miles around.
You're never too old to learn, I imagine.
You okay?
Yeah.
Yeah, man.
Match the speed of your cockspill.
Is that guy on YouTube that eats the old military rations?
Yeah, that channel's great.
I've put on that guy's channel and just fallen asleep to him eating old rations
and woken up at like 60 videos a player.
They'll be needing to feed.
I'm going to tap square when we're stationed from this move.
Oh, you can like hold it.
That's cool.
Is that just showing off?
I didn't wait.
I'm not saying what?
I didn't say that.
No.
I've done that to your videos.
Yeah.
Just happened.
Let's put this out on a tray.
Yeah, I know the line.
Come on.
You don't think I've ever seen it before?
Automatic cinematic.
Coffee instant cheetos.
Oh, God.
I wonder how big the actual map is when the game opens up.
But if it's too strong, they won't move.
Stay quiet.
Do a German impression?
Okay.
Stop here a second.
I see something.
I was about to just wildly make fun of myself.
Like just make fun of me.
No, I'm not doing that.
Why would I do?
No.
I've already done this before.
How can you tell?
I've already done it.
We'll track them on foot.
You're going to need the book.
Don't leave it on your whole gun.
It'll scare everything around.
Approach your horse.
Don't use the gun.
So use L2R to select a stowed weapon.
Carbine.
Bow.
That's the one.
No point setting off without that bow.
You make less noise and you crouch.
And slowly.
I'm not going to do it.
I'm not going to shoot him in the head.
You see the tracks?
I think so.
Maybe not.
I see them.
You can use eagle eye to highlight animal tracks.
Okay.
Focus on the track.
Nope.
Enable Eli to focus on the tracks to highlight them again.
Okay.
Yeah, I can.
I see it.
Your scent is also shown in eagle eye blowing in the direction of the wind.
Animals will flee if they smell your scent.
They'll remain downwind or far away when hunting.
So is this is that my smell going this way or are those those in his tracks, right?
He's going to be up here.
It's top track.
I mean, I'm just going to follow it.
22 miles per hour top right.
Which way is it going though?
This way.
Unknown animal.
It's going to be a deer.
22 miles per hour.
That would be very, that'd be a lot.
I don't see anything.
All right.
There he is.
Okay.
Am I close enough?
I'm going to have to do like a, is it bullet drop?
Aim for the head.
A swing.
Do I not go get the meat?
Hunt another deer.
Okay.
Well, we're going to, I want to get the meat here.
Select and call while aiming at it.
This will give you a chance of a clean kill as they raise their head before fleeing.
So there's one over here.
All right.
Well, I do have any luck.
I mean, we get the 21 stink meter up there.
Okay.
I haven't even played God of War, the new one for PS4, but I feel like this is the game.
Is that this happens in that game, right?
This is like the same game.
Something like that.
Yeah.
Which way is it going?
I mean, this, this is, is it going that way or to the left?
That I don't know the tracks.
I mean, those are tracks, right?
Or did I make those?
No, it's down here.
What's the button to call?
Fuck.
I don't even need to call them.
Why did I even call?
That was no reason for that.
I, I made these tracks.
Okay.
There he is.
Got it.
Okay.
We can stop this now.
Let's go.
Oh, it's actually pick up the whole thing.
This is realism.
The compendium tracks what you have discovered in the world.
It can be accessed from the progress section of the pause menu.
We found the realism.
You can increase the distance that the horse will respond.
Come on.
There he is.
Shoot the deer in the head.
I don't want to explode the team's head.
All right.
Let's go.
Yes, you do.
No, I don't.
I don't want to do it.
All right.
Meet up with Charles.
All right, Charlie.
I'm coming.
I want to see its brains.
Jesus.
Christ.
Uh, so you drop off carcasses to Pearson at the meat factory to contribute to gang supplies.
Okay.
I knew you'd be okay with that bow.
You want to see the deer's balls?
Everyone's freaking out about it.
All right.
Let's look at the deer's balls.
The deer doesn't have any balls.
Right.
Never.
Okay.
That's not how it works.
You know, there are.
See, I told you they weren't going to be there.
I missed you guys.
I really did.
I like, I unequivocally missed all of you.
Eat.
We give the cab cook five minutes to grab the essentials and go.
And he doesn't even bring a crumb of food.
Good that we caught more than one.
We've only been up here a few days and have already picked up two more mouths to feed.
One more.
I bet German doesn't even know me.
Boy.
What's your name?
Karen Salt and awful Pearson was kind enough to give us.
She has a wild look in her eyes.
Of course.
She lost her husband.
Even me, the one that makes fun of you.
Even you.
No, I'm not going to show the horse balls.
That's too easy.
I'm not going to shoot the horses balls with an arrow.
Like everybody wants me to do.
That's not going to happen.
No one said that.
Yes, they did.
Oh, shit.
Bears.
No, don't shoot him.
Am I losing?
What's wrong with my arms?
No, let it go.
Let go.
There you go.
You're going awfully fast.
Oh, the horses.
The horse is spooked.
Okay.
I'm going to hold L3 to make the horse not.
Can you see us?
Fight bear.
Right in the fucking head.
All right, let's get out of here.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
All right.
Cinematic mode.
He's screaming.
Where's my friend?
Come on.
Let's go.
Why is he standing there?
Is there a reason why he's just standing still up here?
The bear is gone.
Yeah, we're good.
I'm in combat.
No, I am not.
Let's go.
I have to fight the bear now.
Okay, I need to turn it off for a second.
Hold on.
Okay.
Okay, okay, okay.
Where's the bear?
I don't see a bear.
Give me the fucking carbine.
There's no bear.
He's not here.
Do you guys understand?
Do you see a bear?
I don't see a bear.
Wait, tracks.
Right there.
The fuck is he?
He's not here.
I see him.
No, you don't.
I mean, like, the red marker is over here.
Wouldn't it be over at the red marker?
I'm out of stamina.
I gotta eat.
Hold on.
Why did you guys make me do this?
I was so close to the end here.
Eat a can of beans.
Give me my horse.
You made you do this.
You did this.
There was never any bear?
Why do I hear it now?
Can we just leave?
We can leave.
Can't we?
He said, return to Charles.
I said, go.
Hurry up and return.
Where's my carcass?
Fucking carcass is on the ground over here.
That's what's happening.
I get it.
The horse is just as fucking stupid as I am.
All right, this is why I couldn't move.
It has nothing to do with the bear.
Just get back on the horse and let's go.
See, everyone told me it's because I was in combat.
This isn't World of Warcraft.
We can just leave.
All right, let's go.
Fuck.
Who is this fucking bear?
I soft-locked the game?
No, I didn't.
We're fine.
Shoot bear with arrow.
And my toddler brain was like, shoot bear with arrow.
Okay, I do think you say.
I'm a caveman.
Jerma, do that thing.
I do think me shoot arrow to bow to bear head.
Me shoot bear.
Chat say good idea.
We laugh.
We laugh at lowbrow joke.
Me stream on Twitch with bad internet.
Me try explain TCP IP to Bogo.
Bogo throw rock at head.
Well, it looks good.
I'm streaming at 6,000 right now.
I mean, when it's good, it looks great.
Right?
When it's bad.
The hell is calling me right now?
But I cannot answer that.
Thank you for showing me how to bow properly.
Takes a lifetime of practice to master.
Let's see.
So this upgrades.
Did they go a Fallout 4 route here?
Do I have to bring supplies and build stuff?
Just drop it down in here.
What a surprise.
Find a camp rat loitering around in the kitchen.
Is that any way to greet an old friend?
I feel like we haven't spoken for days.
I do my utmost to avoid you.
He loves me really.
It's his sad way of showing affection.
It's not forced, that's good.
No, it isn't.
Now shoot, get lost.
Well, see you gents later.
See, you got on just fine.
Charles is a wonder.
Have a drink, boys.
You earned it.
Have a drink.
It's urine.
Jesus, what is that?
Navy rum, sir.
It's the only thing.
The only thing.
Keeps you sane, it does.
Yeah, seems to have done a treat on you.
You go rest that hand, Charles.
I'll be fine in a few days.
You mind helping me with the skinning, Mr. Morgan?
It's easier if we do it together.
I'll get to skin you.
You're always one with the jokes, aren't you?
Come on.
This really isn't a job for a man with a burnt hand.
I'll see you both later.
See, that guy has the quintessential haircut of end of the plate of spaghetti.
Oh, yes, yeah, yeah, you can take this.
I'm done.
Are you sure you're done with that?
Yep, yep.
Arthur, come on, get that knife.
Just get him.
Now shoot the deer.
No, I'm not going to fuck up the tutorial missions.
That was very quick.
That's what it looks like in there?
Not too bad, Mr. Morgan.
I thought it was wires and components and shit.
It looks like that in there?
And pretty much any town, if you're looking to make a legitimate bit of money, of course.
I thought we just made animals.
They're like computers.
Well, if you catch anything else, sir, you bring it to me.
Sure.
Thank you, Mr. Morgan.
Heck, Arthur Morgan's first decent bit of hunting after all these years.
Well, we're on the run now.
Everyone's got to do their bit to survive.
You're not a Chuck E. Cheese.
It's like good stew.
The folk need it.
It's been a tough few days.
Few days later, you unlocked the master hunter challenge.
All right, tutorial complete.
It's been a bad few weeks, but Dutch, being Dutch, he is busy making plans and
Dutch being Dutch, those plans involve robbery and dreams.
Not yet, huh?
Who the hell is Epiticus?
I thought you was reading him his last rites.
Now I see you're introducing him to your other passion.
I'll mind you to show me some respect, Mr. Morgan.
Mind away, Reverend.
You're still here then?
I owe you.
And you'll pay me.
For the moment, just rest.
Arthur, I think it's time for the train.
Want me to come?
Of course I do, but look after it.
I was always ugly Dutch.
It's just a scratch.
Don't lie still, son.
What's that kid doing?
Get that kid out of here.
This is an M-rated game.
He's not allowed in here.
He's seen me now.
What's left of me?
What about you?
Guess I was hoping to see a corpse.
Bide your time.
You'll see plenty of them.
You're a rotten man, John Marsden.
He is an idiot, Abigail.
We all know it.
Fix the desync.
Now, railway men.
Tell me what happens here.
Ready?
At the water tower.
Just before the tunnel.
Ain't a problem.
Why are we doing this?
Weather's breaking.
We could leave.
I thought we was lying low.
What do you want from me, Hosea?
I just don't want any more folks to die, Dutch.
We're living, Hosea.
We're living.
Look at me.
Even you.
But we need money.
Everything we have is in Blackwater.
Of course.
You fancy heading back there?
No.
Listen, Dutch.
I ain't trying to undermine you.
I just...
Okay.
I just want to stick to the plan, which was to lie low, then head back out west.
Now, suddenly we're about to rob a train.
Now it's too fast.
What choice have we got?
The Viticus Cornwalls.
No joke, Dutchie.
Who is the Viticus Cornwall?
Can I fix it?
He's a big railway magnet, sugar dealer, oil man.
Well, how good for him.
Sounds like he has more than enough to share.
Dutch.
Gentlemen, it is time to make something of ourselves.
Get your horses ready.
We have a train to rob.
Better?
Bad.
Everything's weird?
No, it's not.
We're riding with the gang.
All right.
The street smells like pee now.
I'm gonna get hit by this train, I guarantee it.
Why is the audio playing backwards?
You know what?
Don't you be coming back here now.
I don't know why that just popped in my head.
That's when you go to jail in the Monopoly game for Super Nintendo.
I don't know.
That just popped in.
It just popped in saying hello.
I don't know why.
It just popped in.
You know, it just popped in.
I wasn't paying attention.
God damn it.
All right.
Rob the train.
That's all I need to know.
So what's the story about?
Group of bandits, setting up camp, getting deer, and fending off other bandits so far.
And John Marston.
Oh, he did?
He didn't die?
Oh, that's a close one.
Well, this is pretty.
Did we go to like zero?
What's that right over here?
Well, I was under the assumption that I was hopefully going to be live for at least a couple hours.
Let's hope it's safe.
Holy shit.