Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with FPS man. This is a
First-person free game by the way link is in the description really loud in my ear. It's a first-person pac-man
Terrifying adventure. So with that said it's pretty self-explanatory. It's first-person pac-man and here we go
I got a mini map in the top right. I should be looking at that. Okay, there's one
All right, there's the pac-man Superball I can eat that and all my troubles will be over. Oh, will it?
Oh, will it? Oh, will it? Oh, I'm gonna wrap around. We're wrapping around this way
That's a double kill
double kill
Come here you. All right. I'm good to go. Good to go. Good to go. Keep it rolling
Keep it rolling
2,000 points
All right. I got another one. I got another one right here. I don't want to just prematurely pick this up
But I think there's a ghost right there. Come on, bro. Oh
It's two of them. I need to take this opportunity. I got to go this way
There we are
I'm gonna be level one. Let's hope I beat this
All right, there's a yellow there's a yellow piece of crap. I think I just saw the pink did I I don't know
Horrible I can't go that he's gonna wrap around he's gonna wrap around
Keep going this way. Oh, he's trying to he's trying to close me in
Jesus. All right, finish finish that up in this corner turn that corner
It's a lot scarier than it might seem come on I'm waiting I'm waiting I'm waiting for the right time get over here
Yeah, I'm gonna continue this way got to keep going this way. I
Don't have very I think I only have one more of those balls left. I
think I can only put like one more ball in my mouth before I
How long is this level is this really this huge of a level or is pac-man really this big?
Come on. Come on. I want you all to come over here. Come on. Where are they going?
What the hell are you guys doing? Come on. All right
See, I this is my last shot right here guys. This is the only last one I can get
This is my last shot right here guys, this is the only last one I can get I gotta get rid of these dudes
Gotta kill at least two or three of them. I'll just hopefully I can finish this
They're all scattered around the whole damn map. I'm so dead. There's three over here. There's like five over there
Damn it. Oh
I don't
Do you have it well what I get 6400 6400
I wish I could hit M and see just how like huge this map really is
Because I feel like it's it's pac-man was not this big
Could be wrong though. Damn it. Oh, this is it. It was a yellow one. Let's go again one more time
This is it. This is the last try you talk about like jump scares
This game has like this is like this is like scarier than some of the games I've played
All right. I got a piece of candy ready. I got like an orbiting piece of bubblegum. I'm ready to take it
Let's go this way first one dude over here. Come on. Go the other way. Go the other way. Go the other way
Oh you he came from the other side. Someone's gonna come right over here. Yep. Yep, two of them two of them
Two of them. Come on run right into this eat that
That was three that was three of them
I'm gonna beat level one. Come on. I gotta be level one
Turn around wrap around wrap around wrap around. Come on. This is the end right here. This is it
I'm gonna do it get that that was not it. There's even more
What did I miss?
The whole nother section over here. Are you kidding me? Maybe not. Come on. It's the end
This is the end get it. I did it. I beat every level one of FPS man, but that's gonna wrap it up here guys
Thank you so much for watching. This has been FPS man link in the description. It's free
You can go scare the hell out of yourself and try to beat my high score
Which is probably gonna be pretty easy because it was just level one
There's probably some of you guys that are at like level 30 and I beat this whole damn game
But anyways guys, thank you so much for watching. I really do appreciate it and I'll see y'all next time. Of course, take care everybody