The question will be answered, tonight, who in fact is the supreme commander of the armies at hand?
What the hell, what the fuck was that?
I said I'm not ready.
Why are you not ready?
I got a cat.
You don't have a cat.
It's getting everywhere, there's hair in my mic.
You don't have...
You take your little guy, and you generate the power by putting the nodes on the things,
and you build buildings to build units, and then I just fucking stomp you.
I think this is going to take too long.
I don't think it's going to take too long.
I'm just going to kill you right now.
What did you just do?
What the fuck is this?
Gig.
Oh, oh, look at, look at what's going on on the bottom there.
Oh, Ster is cheating, and fucking like, it's just blinking.
It's just blinking on the bottom of my screen.
You could blink in StarCraft, that wasn't considered cheating, it was an ability.
I'm playing Protoss.
How do you cheat?
Cheat, activate.
How do you do that?
You open up the console, and you type the cheat.
I don't know what that is, I'm trying to like, make my units, I'm trying to like, feed my like,
soldiers and shit, and you overhear, cheat.
You teleported in here.
What is happening?
I don't know what this is.
This is like, my game is...
This is going to break the game.
I thought my game just broke, but I accidentally clicked out of it.
Alright, so gentlemen's rules.
No attacking.
Do not attack me, I'm not going to attack you, until we both have a thousand units.
Okay?
Yeah, okay.
Are those all air guys?
What the heck are those?
Yeah, these are all planes.
And there's so many units, dude, they have nowhere to go.
They're all turning into this one like, blob in the middle.
It's like sucking up, it's sucking up the planes into like, one giant plane.
Do you see this?
No, I'm busy making my own suck up planes.
It's like...
This is turning into like, just a...
Oh dear god.
I don't even want to know what's going to happen with this.
The game's going to start to freak out.
And not know what the hell is going on.
I almost have a thousand units.
Whoa, whoa, where are they going?
Where are you guys going?
I don't know, they're coming to attack me.
No, no, no, no, no, no!
Pull back!
What are they doing?
I'm trying, I'm trying to pull back!
I'm trying!
They won't listen!
They have a mind of their own, I can't...
They won't listen to me!
I guess that's just what happens when you have a thousand units.
Get out of here!
I'm trying to pull it back!
Holy shit!
No, you fucking idiot!
I'm trying!
Don't engage!
What are you doing?
You're not supposed to engage!
Now it's just a mess!
Just pull back!
Look what you've done!
You've brought everybody!
I have!
No!
You attacked one person in all of this!
It just looks like a firework exploded!
My game's running very slowly, by the way.
I can't even...
You did this.
You shouldn't have attacked.
No, you attacked!
All your guys were coming at me!
And you didn't pull any of them back!
You select and you right-click!
Select and then right-click!
I did!
Look at the gravity!
What is happening?
I don't know!
Where did those guys go?
What are they still shooting at?
I hope you're happy.
You're gonna build a bunch of turrets.
And I'm coming after you with GS Rats.
So you build as many turrets as you possibly can.
If you change your mind later, there's air turrets and there's ground turrets.
Don't be like, okay, now it's the air units.
Let's see how this goes.
Like, it's not gonna happen.
No, I'm coming at you with GS Rats.
I'm gonna build a thousand rats and you're gonna build towers.
You ready?
We'll start typing bling-bling!
If you select them all too and do the alt-T,
you can keep them in a tiny, a small area.
Wait, wait, wait.
If I select everybody...
Select them all and do alt-T where your cursor is pointing.
Alt-T.
Didn't do anything.
Oh dear, dude!
My FPS!
Oh man!
Why did you tell me to do that?
I don't know.
It looks like you got a little planet there.
Oh, don't zoom in and look at them.
I cannot zoom in, no.
Yeah, zoom out and just...
Oh dear, why did you have me do that?
Why did you make me do that?
I can't even look over there.
No, I need to spread them out.
I need to, like, pull them out.
Because I can't even go over there.
Wait, I heard a launch.
What do you mean?
No, no, no, no.
We spent so much time.
We spent so much time doing this.
We didn't spend that much time.
No, dude, please don't tell me you just dropped a fucking bomb.
I mean, you teleported them all there.
What a waste of fucking time.
No, that's so good.
You broke the whole rat colony.
Uh, here they come.
Okay, well...
Come on, rats.
I've got a good view angle of this.
Break through the defenses!
Let's see if they get even close to me.
Where are they going?
They're, like, wrapping around here.
Oh my god, I have so many, like, pop-ups
that's telling me, like, your game's broken.
No, they're not getting anywhere near it.
Come on, stop, like, bunching up, like, traffic
and push in.
They haven't even breached the wall yet.
Like, half of them aren't moving.
Yeah, what are they doing?
You idiots!
Some of them are just standing completely still.
Oh, wow, this is fucking awful.
They're all going up the mountain and instantly dying.
It's because of the wall, I think.
Okay, hold on, hold on, hold on.
Dude, they're just walking into the wall!
They're making themselves a choke point
and just getting shot to death
when they walk through it.
Like, over here by this stupid, like, fucking underpass.
They really are like ants.