Okay, so we're out here on the house, and I want to make sure I'm gonna try and do this.
I want to make a little little leeway room so when I dig out of my house I don't flood the basement
because that really does suck. It's kind of annoying because I'll dig out and all the
sudden water will just rush into my basement. Actually is that even technically a basement?
This is kind of my entire house. Oh well, whatever, patch you back up. So I want to make sure that I
can build outwards rather than have to keep on freaking out every time I build out of my wall.
And what the hell? Okay, yeah, here we go. Started to do it a little bit. Let's take it more. One,
two, three. See there's my wall right there so now this will not happen. And actually I've got a story
for you. I didn't even think about this but I have a story for you right now. It's a story.
Let me block off this stupid cascading wave of death. Okay, there we go. Come on. Come on now.
Perfect. Okay, now I can start to build outwards. So here's a story for you while I finish this up.
As a lot of you guys know, it has to do with flooding and it's actually kind of scary.
Scary time for me and my family. Not so scary for you because you are not part of my family,
or maybe you are. Maybe you are watching this and you are part of my family. But where am I
going with this? So I live in the northeast and a lot of you guys know that the northeast is
kind of a weird place when it comes to weather. We get the craziest, hottest summers. We get insanely
terrible winters. Like oh what is it like 25 inches of snow? Oh that's great. We get stuff
like that. We get heavy rains. We get pretty much every season the worst you could possibly get
that season. So talking about the rainfall while I'm just dropping sand into nowhere.
Talking about the rainfall while I extend this out. Oh let me try that again. Talking about the
rainfall while I extend this out. Essentially we had at one point, it was in April. I remember
it was April because April was the only thing I remembered because my brain only likes to remember
tragic horrible things and not nice things. So it was April I think of 2009 I think. Maybe
no it was 2009 I think. Don't quote me on that. So April 2009 we had crazy crazy rainfall. We had
rain that was I think we got like 10 inches of rain in like three days or two days or something
like that. Something insane. And our foundation of our houses around here at least in the northeast
is not really, can't really handle that. So my basement and my basement of my house is living
space. So my basement of my house got flooded. And when I say flooded I don't mean there was just
like you know there's like go up slopping around in like two inches of water. No no no no no like
the entire second level of my house on the bottom was like shin deep in water. Almost waist almost
coming up to like your knees in water. And that was one of the worst experiences of my entire life.
If I can safely tell you that that was that was probably one of the worst things that's ever
happened to me and my family. It was horrible. Every single room that was down here it was just
you were wading through water. Just like floating cats dogs like we had a big bunch of animals here
too. We have a ton of animals. It just was really really bad news. And it happened twice. We had one
flood. One big bad one. And we had to do a ton of cleanup. We had to get a professional team.
It was insane. We had to throw away thousands and thousands of dollars worth of stuff.
And then like two weeks later it happened again. And it was just it was almost like you wanted to
friggin blow your brains out. You were just like what is happening to our house? It was one of the
worst things ever. And it happened twice within the same two weeks. Oh like even thinking about
it makes me want to puke. But anyways let's uh while I patch up this little hole here I want to
try and do a like I was telling you a castle. So I want multiple rooms with a dining table for
me to eat with my kingsmanship. I'm not sure that even makes any sense. But I want it because I want
it. Let's make a boat. I want to be able to get out of this house fairly easily. Here we go. Let's
go over here. I like this way. Let's put the boat down. My personal little boat. Okay how do I get
in the boat? No no no get back here. No come here. Oh you. Oh how do I get in the boat?
Do I click on it? Oh I did it. Okay it's right click.
We are taking an adventure through the open world. Going to go to this tree I forgot to cut down.
And then I'm going to say hello to this tree. Hello tree and then I'm going to get out of the
boat. Out of the boat. How do I get out of the boat? How do I get out of the boat? Okay stay stay.
If you saw episode one this is the tree that I didn't cut all the way down.
It's the only damn tree with it. What the hell? This cow is dead. I will dig to you.
Oh my god. I actually killed him. I feel bad. All right now let's let's actually cut this tree down.
Oh delicious. This is gross. Okay I should probably stop doing that or I'm gonna die.
Come here wood. All right. The reason I'm doing this is because I want wooden floors. I want
wooden paneling on the ground. Because I got a comment somebody saying Jerma make some wooden
floors. What are you a caveman? And I responded with I guess I am a caveman. You're right. I need
to really think about what I'm doing with myself. So let's cut down this whole tree. Make sure I get
the whole damn thing. Nothing else right? No there's just one more here. I gotta use my torch.
Okay that should be it. Now will this tree disappear so I can put a new one here?
I gotta find new trees. This is bad. No there's more. What? This is like embedded into the mountain.
Is this tree in the mountain? Like embedded in the mountain?
If I see like another wooden plank right here I'm gonna lose my mind.
Hold on I want to I need to check this out. Because the tree is still here.
Tree is still here. Okay this is just odd. Look oh there we go. Found you. Found you.
All right let's go find some more trees. Wow this is different. Hold on I gotta get a better view.
There's coal here too. Cool. So this is just a giant lava fountain of death. Uh nice. Nice.
Give me a rest of this coal. I'll take it. I'll take it all. I wonder what so what does this mean?
A lot of people freak out and they get excited when they see this. A lava fountain or a big
lava thing. Somebody tell me in the comments what what does this actually mean? Does this mean
anything in particular or is this just really cool looking? Don't want to lose my way because
that's happened before. I have totally lost my way. So I'm gonna make sure I'm leaving a breadcrumb
trail of torches to make sure I don't lose my damn place. Oh aren't these things worth something?
Can't I get like a couple pennies for these? Taking them anyways. All right don't forget
your breadcrumb trail. I don't have a so look at all these cows. I could eat this stuff for days.
Come on. Should have bought a sword. Bought a sword? You don't buy stuff in this game. What
am I talking about? Uh oh. Come here. You've been a bad cow. You deserve death. Nice. There are a lot
of cows and none of them really understand that I'm going to kill every single one of them.
And this guy. See you're just joining in on the party. You see you're just trying to be involved
and it's not cool man. We're just trying to hang out here and kill each other as cow friends.
I'm all right I'm hitting you with the no I don't want to do that. I was told that was a bad idea.
More of this stuff. I think it's wheat. All right no off don't get off track. Don't get off track.
I've got to find trees. No more beating up cows. Let's keep going. The never-ending trek to find
trees and a creeper and two creepers. Two creeper bastards and a spider. Um I'm going this way.
I'm going up to high ground. Hey cow. Get off of my mountain. This is mine. Oh this is gonna be
funny. Oh he died. Oh my god. I kind of feel bad. Does that happen to everybody? Will he die too?
I'm the king of the mountain baby. Sheep. Sheep. Sheep. I need the sheep. I need the sheep. I need
to make a bed. I don't care. I need the I need the wool. Get out of my face. Go ahead. Blow up.
Come on. Yeah. Yeah. That was exactly what I wanted. Awesome. Thank you creeper for killing
all of the other things that were here and leaving me just to collect the delicious
sap of life. All right die. Come here you. There we go. There's two. Need one more and I have a bed
and I don't ever have to worry about dying ever again. Actually I kind of do but still. Come here.
Die. All right. I got the wool I need but I want some chocolate wool. I want some chocolate milk.
If you punch the get out of here. Come on. I don't get all day.
I can just ready. I'm using the same strategy as I did before.
Blow up. No it didn't kill anybody. You go in here and drown. Leave me alone.