Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with the Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight I'm gonna be playing as the Huntsman Sniper, with the Huntsman, the Vintage Huntsman, the Jarate, and the Bushwhacker, for those crits, baby.
So this gameplay is gonna sit in the background, but it's very, very intense. This is a double overtime gameplay, and things get really, really heated near the middle of this and the end.
So I won't tell you who wins, but it is a great gameplay to play out in the background while I talk about something very, very important.
Now what I'm gonna talk about is something that I touched upon a long time ago, more than four or five months ago, and I never really got back into it, and I wanna get back into it now.
I'll give you guys my advice and my own personal struggles with this, because it's something that I haven't really been doing lately, and it's exercising.
A lot of you old subscribers will know this, that I used to be a huge, huge advocate of physical activity and going outside and going to the gym and lifting and staying in shape.
I haven't been doing that lately. I've been just kind of sitting around drinking Dr. Pepper and just playing games and doing all kinds of indoor stuff.
Now there's nothing wrong with that, but I'm trying to get myself motivated and get myself back into the whole gym scene and the whole lifting scene, because it makes you feel good.
It gives you something to do. It gives you something to look forward to every other day, every day, whenever you end up doing it, and I feel like it's a good stress reliever, guys.
If there's one reason to get yourself into the gym, if you're a very stressful person, like me, I am a worrywart, I am an incredibly high, strong, stressful guy, and not having that avenue to release some of the stress and release some of the day-to-day activity stress, it can get to you.
It can dawn on you, and it's really, you don't want that to build up.
So again, if there's one reason why you should start exercising and there's one reason why I should get back into it, it's to relieve stress.
It is a very, very therapeutic thing, getting into the gym, because after you get out of the gym or after you're done lifting, and everybody I've ever talked to that's ever started exercising, that's ever been part of an exercise program, when you are done for the day, let's say you go to the gym for an hour,
or you go to the gym for 20 minutes or 10 minutes or whatever you end up doing, or even if you're doing it at your home, when you are done, finished with your exercise routine, you feel like a million dollars.
No, no, no, you feel like $20 million, and that is not an overstatement.
I remember so many times I'd get back from the gym or I'd get back from running on the treadmill, and I would just take in a whole breathful of air and feel like the world was my oyster.
And that's a saying we say around here sometimes in the Northeast, the world is your oyster, and you probably say that everywhere, I don't know why, but anyways, of getting off track.
But you feel great, you feel like you can do anything, and that is a feeling that we all need to have.
And that's why I'm a huge advocate, trying to get some motivation to get back into the gym, so I can just get back, sit back, relax, and go, you know what, I did something with myself today, I did something with my body, I did something physical,
I took the time to try and make myself a better person, and that's huge for not only self-confidence, but for everything, guys, like it makes you feel so good.
When I first started exercising, you know, talking about like relationships and women, I don't, you know, I don't really normally talk about this type of thing, but I will touch upon this very, very briefly.
When I got really into it, and I started taking it really seriously, and I started to see a lot of results, it made it a lot easier to talk to women.
It made it 20 times easier to talk to women, and if you have trouble, if you're the type of guy that you can't really talk to girls that much, you don't have the confidence, you don't know what to say, you don't know what to do, I am that guy.
That is me, you are describing me, and we are the same person, but how I try to remedy that is by doing this exercising and getting into a position where, hey, I feel great, I know I look much better than I ever did, why not just try and talk to some people and see what happens?
And you know what, it works, it really does work, so I have to get back into this, guys, I have to start to lift, get back into exercising, get back into shape.
Dr. Pepper's not going anywhere, I'm still gonna have Dr. Pepper, I'm still gonna drink soda, still gonna eat junk food all the time and stuff like that.
Well, not really all the time, that's not really true, but as long as you do everything in moderation, and you take care of yourself, and you do exercise program, even if you just run or you just play soccer or football or anything like that, baseball, any sport, you are gonna be in better physical condition, and you're gonna feel a lot better about everything.
So before this video wraps up, I am going to take the personal pledge that I'm gonna get back into the gym, I'm gonna get back into running, and that's gonna happen this week.
I'm not gonna put it off anymore, it's gonna happen this week, guys, and if you wanna take the pledge with me, if you wanna get back into physical condition, then absolutely tell me your story in the comments, I will read them all.
So that's gonna wrap it up, guys, thank you so much for watching, I really do appreciate it, and I'll see you guys all soon, and of course, take care, everybody.