I told you I was going to be precisely on time. I said it. I said I'm going to be on time today.
I was 10 seconds early. It's on time. I don't believe it. What's going on? Well, this time
I'm not I'm not on the ground. I am seated this time. I'm not on the ground. I have some changes
to my setup. I'm very happy with it. I had a dream you were playing Tears of the Kingdom.
Well, that sounds like a nightmare to me. I'm just kidding around. We finally made it on time.
Uh, give me one second. I want to drink needs a refill. I guess I've been doing this thing.
I've been doing water, but like 10% watermelon juice. It's been pretty great. Actually,
you get a little bit of flavor, but it's not all sugar and bullshit. It's been pretty great. Give
me one second. Okay. Hi. Uh, that was weird. I hope that doesn't happen again. Otherwise I'm
going to have to figure this out and I'll have to see you another time. Okay. So let me explain.
I may have tripped a breaker, but it's not like I'm, I'm just in a different room.
It's not like I'm doing any more. I browned out. I had a brownout.
How did I overload this? It's not like I added any equipment. What the hell happened?
Dude, this, this might happen again. I don't know. I was using the setup for like a couple of hours
yesterday. Maybe the streaming is like pulling extra power and tripping the breaker. Okay. Well,
everybody cross your fingers. That doesn't happen again, but, uh, I'm fully prepared. If it does
in the event, it does. I'm going to have to do a little bit of investigating
road to advanced. I mean, I'm sitting in a recliner right now. I did. It's not like I'm
streaming from a space station. Anyways. Hey, it wouldn't be a stream that I do unless something
goes horribly wrong for no reason. Right. I mean that I have to just accept it at this point.
Hey guys, I changed my whole setup. Spent the last like few days getting it all set up and all
these things. I got a recliner now. I got this cool custom made computer setup. Oh, oh, oh, you,
wait, you thought I was going to be able to stream. Time to brown out my breaker. Well,
that's actually, that's really good to know because that means that there's
essentially something to do with like the circuit that I'm on. Maybe I have to try plugging into a
different outlet. I don't know. I'll have to figure that out. Anyways. Uh, we'll see if it
keeps going. If we are fine, we're fine. And if not, if the stream turns off again and hey, it's
okay. I'll figure it out. We'll see you another day, but I'm here now and uh, yeah, getting brown
outs in your thirties. Oh, I see the joke. Okay. No, that's all right. All right. We'll find out.
Uh, I'm actually kind of scared that it's going to happen again, but anyways, good to see you
today. We're going to be playing resident evil four, a separate ways DLC. That's the plan.
Don't jinx it. Yeah. I got to keep my mouth shut about this now, but yeah, we're going to play a
DLC. I'm streaming from a new setup. Like you said, like you said, like I said, I am officially
in a recliner. I will show you, I'll be on cam for a little bit tonight. We are playing a scary game.
Everybody say your prayers that we don't get an electrical brown out again. Okay. Well, anyways,
yeah, I'm in a recliner. This is the new setup. Gets me more comfortable. I can actually sit back
now because before, I think I mentioned it when I was on the ground. Cause when I, when I was
lying on the ground last stream, it was not, I was not even 20% of the way through setting this
new setup up, but let's take a look. You want to see? I'll show you. There's the game. I'm going
to hit start game and it's going to draw extra power and it's going to turn the computer off.
I'm fucking scared to click. Yes. Let go. Oh my God. It scared the shit out of me. You can hear
it. I thought my computer browned out. All right, hold on. Here we go. All right. You ready? Here
we go. Recliner. I told you I was going to be sitting in a chair. I have this over. This is
not the final setup, by the way. And a lot of people were like, wow, you're just in a chair
this time. Look at this background over here. You got a mustache. Yep. Well, whatever you could
call it. No Reddit shelf. Hold on. Not done yet. I'm missing two or three very important pieces,
but when they get here, oh yeah, I've got a few things I really need to get. I need a different
little table over here. I need a whole section. I'm not completed yet. I still have to go get it.
Why don't I have the, why am I doing umpire Albertson again? There's a reason. There's a
reason. No, I'm not. I'm not an umpire again. I'm just saying there's a reason. I want to have a
mustache. Is that, is that so weird? And you look like a mafia boss. Come here. You, come here. Make
the cam smaller. Yeah. I just want to show you my, uh, my cool Pac-Man thing that I got there.
It makes me happy. My hair is a mess. I gotta work on that. Yeah. This is the setup temporarily. It's
not quite there, but it will be shrink this a little. Yeah. I can, I can actually go like this
now. This is how you should be streaming. Those of you streamers that are watching right now.
Oh, you're doing it completely wrong. I was doing it wrong for 10 years. Being able to do this. I
got the keyboard right here. I got the mouse on a table that's connected to the recliner armchair.
I've got all my little, uh, my little things over here. I've got my knobs over here. You're going to
get seasick. Like puke. Please don't turn the fucking, please don't have the computer turned
off again. I'm like terrified right now. I went, it's, this is so, of course it has to happen on
my stream, right? I sat down, I was wicked relaxed. I was like, Oh, I can't wait to fucking play
a Resident Evil's DLC in my new comfortable setup. And now I'm no longer comfortable.
Now I'm like, is my computer going to turn all the power off? But Hey, it is what it is. But
all right. I'm ready to play. I'm ready to chill and hang out and play the DLC. Look at this. Oh,
yeah. Okay. Separate ways, right? I'm just ready to go. Are we ready? Trim your toenails? Nah,
I'm just going to keep them going. Uh, only separate ways challenges can be earned in the,
okay. Yeah. That's fine. Costumes and accessories set in the extras menu will be applied. Yeah.
We already know all this. Wait, different. Whoa, wait, hold on a second. Oh, right. I already have
all these. So what should I do for a costume? Your new setup has a weird camera angle. Well,
this is temporary. This is a lot of this is going to move back. You're going to be able to see the
Reddit shelf when I decide to do cam, I'm not going to do it every time. Right. But the romantic.
Yeah, sure. This is really is, is Leon even in this? I guess so. Isn't it a storyline?
And who cares? Let's just go. Uh, I'm retired. So I'm just gonna play on standard. Do pinstripe.
All right. That scene. All right. Those of you that don't know, this takes place at the same
time as the other game. And you cross paths and shit. It's way too loud. I can't even hear
myself talk. Who is? Why is he dancing? I don't know. I think because he knows he's going to
escape. It's just a complete overconfidence. Turn the game up. You got it. Am I? I might
have to change some of the audio adjustments here, though. Oh, I was sick. There's no way
to finish a dance. All right. Is it weird that for one second I did not know that was Ada?
I was like, oh, oh, yeah, of course, that was Ada in the costume. Many things. You see,
how some annoying monks took everything from me, including the amber, never hidden just before
they grabbed me. Well, then lead the way. All right. Here we go. You guys ready? Scary game.
So the camera has to be on this way. All right. I did play this last night just to get the controls
down again. I kind of remember, but I kind of don't. You know that. All right. Let me turn it
up. We're saying it is low. Up all the way. It's weird. I think it's all right now. What do you
want with it anyway? Yeah, I think I actually I if I do that too much, I will puke. I actually
have to be careful. Is it? No, it's hold. Right. That arc. That's right. I'm going full dad mode.
Boss fight. I hope they give us a boss fight immediately.
Then we meet at the church. Let's not make it a funeral.
Is that do we actually have to do this right now? Oh, should I have to be ready?
Let's beat it. Ada has a machine gun. That's pretty cool. Oh, OK. It has a machine gun.
Oh, that's pretty cool. All right. All right. With the black robe, I can parry, right? Oh,
no, it's evade, not parry. C is evade. I might want to change that. Does Ada have like a move
where you can punch? Oh, I thought I killed it. I thought it was dead. I don't. Was this in the
original? I don't remember this. I don't run out of bullets. Oh, my God. They're everywhere.
Where's the real one? I got there's a real one. You know, died of him. Well, I just killed it.
All right. Where's the map? There's a map. OK, this is my favorite part where you go find every
item machine gun. Very cool. Volume is still low. Yeah, that's very strange considering.
I'll turn it up all the way up and I'll figure out later, but we'll just keep it up all the way.
Tell me if it's if it's too. Let's see. Oh, that's fine. Standard Andy, right? Hmm. Thank
you for telling me this. Five thousand people are about to scream it at me. Can I get in here?
You're covering up the weapon indicator. Oh, I got to go. Can I go up here? Is up here better?
Probably unfathomable. Remember, every time I do a Boston accent, I have to kind of move like this.
Oh, is that gunpowder? Why is that? Why? Control come in. Louise hit the amber, but I've sent him
to retrieve it. Control, do you copy? I'm listening. Into some unexpected trouble.
Wesker. Louise is already on route to the church. I'm tracking him every step of the way. Then I
suggest you hurry. Copy. Just need to confirm my route first. Heading out to get a visual of the
area. Whoa. All right. Hold on. I tried to run. It's a run. I was trying to sprint because I was
going to look around. That scared the shit out of me for some reason. I don't know why.
OK, I want to go back down there. I wasn't done. Stick to that. I got to get over there.
All right. All the way across there. So it's a lot. It's gonna be a lot of grappling.
OK, I want to collect items. I got to go. Headshots only for 10 straight minutes. Start
the clock once. Grapple gun. Oh, that's right. OK, cool. That's what her melee is.
I probably shouldn't have done that. Can I restart? Please let me just let me restart.
I'm restarting because I got hit by the meteor. I got hit by the fucking meteor. Hold on a second.
I got hit by the meteor. Just give me one minute. I got a new setup. I got to get used to. I'm too
comfy. I'm getting too comfortable. Maybe I should just not do that. Maybe I just not attack yet.
I can sneak up on people, right? Yeah, don't shoot me, buddy. What am I doing?
Oh, OK. Can I get up there? It'd be this close. Yeah, I looked down to see where she was.
Get over it. Oh, give me these bra. Don't. Hey, don't you rob me. I need to look sometimes.
It's a new computer just right there. It's got to be some kind of achievement, right?
Kill everybody without enough the alarm. All right. Get away from the meteor. Is it still
falling? How long does it take to land? I want it. This is why I came down here.
Oh, yeah, I'll take the jewels. Very good. Very cool. Very cool. Oh, my God. They're raining
hell. They're going to come out of his head. No, we're good. I got to kill the person on the
catapult, right? Oh, didn't hurt me. I'm fine. Stop shooting these at me. Oh, my God. I hate
these things. Oh, cool. Red herb. All right. Where? I need a grapple hook area. You look like
my dad. All right. I can't. Hold on a second. Where's the grapple hook? Am I safe down here?
I don't think so. You look like the owner of this castle. That's actually pretty good.
That was actually very good. That was an 11 out of 10. All right. There goes one.
Shit. Okay. So where can I go from here? There's got to be a grapple hook from here, right?
They wouldn't have emphasized the grapple hook if I couldn't use it a lot more frequently than I am
right now. Down to the ground level? You look like Gabby J, 10 years younger. Oh, that's actually
awesome. You look like a handyman. All right, keep them coming. These are great. What are these
doing over there, huh? Hey, what? You got a problem with your sink? Hey, give me a call.
I'm not going to fix it. I'm going to fuck it up. No more talking. That's about to kill me.
Where's the grapple hook? I don't think I can go that way. Can I? They gave me the grapple
hook tutorial and I only used it once. Dude, where's the grapple hook? She's like, oh yeah,
I'll use my grapple hook to get over there. Oh, just kidding. It's in one spot. Oh, wait.
You look like the third Mario brother. I like that one too. Okay. What the hell is going on here?
I can't reach from here. Can I reach with this grenade? What the fuck is going on?
Somebody help? Why do I not understand what's going on here? You have to go down? Well,
when I, when I walked over here, it was just unloading these bombs that I couldn't keep
walking and there's no grapple hook. Come on, Jack. Raise the cannon. Oh my God. This is okay.
This is what happens when you don't play a game and a DLC comes out like four months later.
That's right. I forgot that thing existed. All right. How do I open it up? How do I get in there?
Dude, how do I get in this fucking room? Okay. There it is. All right. Now we can start playing.
This'll do nicely.
Jesus Christ. I thought I was supposed to use the grapple hook and like,
no, shoot him with the cannon. Like in the regular game that you played.
Thanks. All right, let's go. All right. There we go. Now this is what I thought
I was going to be doing. Oh shit. No, I'm not. Oh, that hurt. Actually, you know what?
Uh, I have to use this now, don't I? No. Wait, is it red and green does extra health or you have
to do all three, right? So I shouldn't use that. Be very careful. How did that miss?
What are these cannonballs? Like tiny little bowling balls? Like candle pin? Yeah, they are.
All right, cool. Okay. There's one more up here. Yeah, there we go. All right. I really need to
find other health. I think there's one right here. I have to. I don't want to, but I'm going to.
Nothing personal. I just scared the shit out of somebody. All right. Did I miss anything up here?
How do you look like that? You look like you hate Sonic. I think I need to be a little fatter for
that one. Oh, but hold on. Do I be Dr. Robotnik for Halloween or do I stay with Count Dracula?
That's very hard now that you said that. I don't know. Do both. I don't think I can do both.
Cutscene.
You look old and pale in the new angle. I am old and pale. Sorry to ruin the surprise for you.
Separate ways.
Chapter two already? That was a whole chapter.
Okay, so what is that? Let me go. I got a scope, didn't I? What is this? That's a knife.
Uh, sorry about that. Okay. There we go. He's in an executive chair. Right. I don't know why an
executive is cracking his neck as in like, yeah, bring it on. I don't know what that was for.
All right. Let's, uh, anything else on the map is that, which is cool. Okay. I might brown out
my computer. I just want to make sure everyone's aware. Hey, I got a lot of testing to do if it
happens, but, uh, I, it could happen. It might happen right now. Uh, just to, uh, if I, if it
happens right now, then I will know exactly what's going on. So, uh, everyone say prayers.
I'm going to go down. Can I jump down? No, not yet. He saw me.
I got him. Well, this is going to be a chainsaw person down there. It's gonna be a chainsaw,
dude. I bet you there's a chainsaw person down there. Only handgun for a while. You look like
you own this castle. Uh, I, I want to write that one's going down in the notebook.
All right. Old man sounds. I probably shouldn't blow that up. I thought I was going to stand up
into it. Uh, how shitty is this set up? I have a lot of bullets. I think I got everything. Yeah.
I feel like I'm at an open mic night where one dude won't get off the stage. You go to open
mic night and the guy has an entire streaming set up on the stage and he's just playing
resident evil four to the audience. That actually is kind of funny. I, if somebody does that, I want
a 5% credit for it. Somebody should go like do a comedy night, right? Well, you have to get,
make sure you get permission first and be like, yeah, it's my routine. It's me. Uh, bill. Uh,
I am, uh, bill comedy. And Hey, let me talk about airplanes for a second and then stop talking and
just bring out an entire streaming set up and just played resident evil with a monitor facing
the audience. Looking back every so often, like, Whoa, did you see that? You're going to get booed
off stage as you deserve. Okay. Well, I got it. Don't reload at a time like this. You missed your
opportunity out of all the times to reload. Why that time? Jesus. Did I get hit by that? Oh my
God. I forgot about those. If they have the heads like this, that means they're like 10 times
stronger. Okay. Well I fucked that whole thing up by like running and like, I'm not that far. I'm
right here. You look like somebody that calls himself a man of culture. Yeah. I have to have
a craft beer here. I actually thought about it. I thought I was going to have a craft beer and just,
I was going to take a sip out of it every hour. Oh my God. Play the game. How did that hit me?
I'm looking down. Oh shit. My hand, my hand is a little sweaty. Hold on. My hand is sweaty.
Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck. He's dead. All right. I should be fine now.
I don't want to take this shit right now. I have to, that stinks. How do I do the grapple hook
thing again? It's shipped, right? How do you do the grapple hook mailer? Yellow. All right. That
went a little better. A little. Can we just get one katana pick? Like I have, like I own a katana.
You want a katana? I don't, I don't, I don't own a katana. Do all goofy men in their late thirties
own katanas? Am I behind on this? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, they do. All right. Where am I going?
I think I got everything. I got most, wait, what's that over there? You do the grapple,
you just need to hit the melee key from far away. Interesting. Put a fedora,
put a fedora on right now. I'm seeing quite the crowd here. I wonder what has them so riled up.
President's daughter. Couldn't have picked a worse time. Consider the village infected
saturation. I've read the file. I'll see what I can do. Turn on hand cam. Uh, I don't have one of
those. I'm not missing anything right now. Don't the treasure show up on the map? Oh,
wait, you guys gas lit the hell out of me last time I played this. That's not accurate. Uh,
let me sort this. I can craft right now. All right. What, what should I do? Should I just
get submachine gun ammo? I'll toss the monitor. Well, it's not going to be like this in the very
near future. I actually don't mind this angle though. I think it looks pretty fine, but this,
this wall back here, it's going to be a little bit, uh, I'll be a little bit closer. No,
it depends on how I do it, but I'll probably be closer to the wall.
And then this will be a little bit further away. I like the new setup. Well, it just,
it allows me to sit back. It's much more comfortable. I, I'll be really honest. Last,
I don't want to say the last couple of years, sitting up at a desk has just been, it's just,
it's just caused me so many issues. I don't want to get into it. I know it's a broken record at
this point talking about it, but being able to actually sit back changes everything for me.
I might be able to stealth kill like all these people. Yeah. I thought of, you know,
get a standing desk, but standing is not, doesn't, it's not great either.
This position I'm in right now is just the perfect position for me to do anything. Seated,
not really slouched, but have the support of my back at the upper chest area. Something about
sitting in a chair like this. Much better. I'm much happier. Not that I was miserable before,
but you all know, I don't have to get into it. I want to go upstairs. Wait, no, no, no. Check
every corner. I feel like there's probably something down there, but hold on. No, I was
already up there. All right, let's go. I always feel like I'm going to miss something in these
games and I always do. I'm going to get surrounded, right? That's how it works.
See you. Is that person still alive? Get off me. We're good. We're not good.
Stop exploding old people. You tried Baldur's Gate 3? Yeah, Holly and I actually played it for
a little bit, but I got a little distracted with other stuff, but I do want to get back into it.
We did the first maybe five to 10 hours. Nothing, anything past that. Can't I, hold on a second.
I need the two ovals, not, or rectangles, not the ovals. Try Voices of the Void. That game
is perfect for you. I'll try it. She has her trust over there. Oh my God. He said, he said it
funny. I did. I did say it funny. You're too self-aware. I have to be. I, sometimes I can't
even put up with my own bullshit. It's, you know what I mean? I have to be. Nice. Okay.
What's the goal here? Just to go down here. Okay. You forgot to clean the chocolate milk mustache
off. I can't, my, my, anytime I try to do something like this, it's just disgusting,
but I'm doing it. I'm doing it. I'm doing it. How much did this VTuber avatar cost?
What the fuck? He knows how to speak Resident Evil. Okay. Am I missing something? Nope.
Not surprised. So kind of you to keep our friends busy.
He's such a dickhead. This way looks promising. I'm not even looking. I'm not even looking. I
missed. Shit. I love this engine. It's, you know, I know, I know I'm the fuck Capcom guy.
I know that, but I think they actually might be, as of right now, probably one of the better
game company that exists right now. I think they've had, they've had like five bangers in a
row. And I can't, like, I can't deny that. It's like, I think that they've been doing,
they're doing a wonderful job, a wonderful job, but that was just, that was just anger coming out.
I didn't actually mean that I was mad because I couldn't change the FOV and I got very upset
about it. Like irrationally upset. There was no reason to be that mad about it. This is going to
fall. I think that's what happens when you play on standard mode. Oh, just in time, bros. Top
shit at the bottom. They both have little, uh, circles on them. Okay. I have to use the mouse
scroll. That's it, right? Now that I think, all right. Where's the other one? The two birds.
Is it that one? It's like the opposite to kind of either this one or this one. I'm pretty sure
it's that one. All right. Well we need the third one. I can't do it without the third one. Where's
this painted down there? Oh, he's going to get up. He's going to get up. He's going to get up.
He's going to get up. He figured it out. Wait, what's this? Oh, it's one of those. Get all the
blue things. Six spinals. All right. So are they listed? They are. So this one's right behind me.
Or is it? Oh, there it is. I see it. Did I see it? I think I did. Where are the other ones? Okay.
Uh, what is it? It is. It's the, I need to get this guy out of the way. How do I move this guy?
I think it's the two. How do I move this guy? I think I know which one it is. It's the double.
It's the two, one, two, and then I'll figure it out. Skip VOD watchers. Skip. No VOD watchers.
Stay here. Don't leave. Unless you've got something to do. You might have an appointment.
You have like other stuff going on. Maybe your friend's coming over. Maybe like school you got
to go to. Maybe you've got, um, like food to eat or something. Don't go. Unless any of those things
are happening. Maybe you'd like playing a game on your own. Maybe you don't feel like watching
TV or streaming today. That's fine. But any other scenario, don't go. Which one is it?
Is it this one? No. It's like a double bump. Is it this right here? Was it that? It had like two
bumps. Fucking one of these. One, two, but I, the guy is in the way. It's not my fault.
Does he despawn? Get the fuck out of, I don't care. It's worth it. What is on the right here?
That's what I need. Is it? Okay. One, two, wait. Okay. One, two, three. He's only covering 5%
of the design. Yeah, but it's important to know it. I think it's the one, it's one, two, three.
There's a third one right there. He's just in the way. It's one, two, three. It's three of those,
uh, squiggly swirlies, whatever they are. Right? I'm pretty sure this is it. There's only like two
options. Well, I want to do the puzzle. I don't want to just, I didn't want it to be handed to
me by a chat member saying that one third one from the left. That's not me. I don't think I
need to deal yet. Blue medallions. I'd want it to run that way. I didn't the church. I literally
turned around. I literally turned around. Oh God damn it, man. Well, can I go back? I doubt it.
Some shit over here though. I might actually have to restart. Hey, Red Dead Redemption figured this
out a long time ago. Old shift for two seconds to grab a hook. Tap shift is in a tap shift.
That doesn't work. Hold shift is run. Whatever. I don't know how to figure this shit. I don't know
how to fix this. I really want those that wins. Where's the auto save right now? Well, it looks
like we're not getting those spinals 10 seconds ago. Hey, that kind of whatever. It's okay. Hey,
we don't even need them. I don't want to miss the shit here though. I'm upset about that. I'm upset.
What do I do about this? Restart the whole DLC? No, I'm sorry. People are so mean to you.
They don't, they don't mean it. Sorry. I do. Well, you know what? Give a shit. I give a fuck.
Let's fuck up. Cut scene. Minus one. I know the vision, but the sounds weren't set. We're sad.
I like how I got a half point on that. Well, no, actually it's a half negative point. Hey,
I know the vision was there. The vision was there. I feel like I just auditioned for American
Idol and I was not very good, but you didn't want to tell me I wasn't good because you didn't want
me to like scream at you. Hey, what's that line? Where's everybody going? Bingo. Wait,
why is he dressed like this? Why is he dressed like that? Why is he dressed like that? That
didn't happen in my game. First time's free. Why does he look like that? Don't keep me waiting,
Luis. I didn't even know that was Leon. We're supposed to know that that's like a,
wow, this is that part that everybody thinks is funny and cool. I thought that was a different
character. Sir Mendez, isn't it? He has a house there. Could be worth taking a look.
Do it. I'll see what I can do it. Sorry. I just hear that and I just have to do trouble.
No stream while sitting on a camel next time, bro. Some of you guys need to fucking relax.
Okay. This thing is fucking filthy. Where do I go? So where, uh,
where do I go? It's locked. It's not locked. What if Ashley,
they're locked in the church to leave point good time. Trevor from GTA. Any other stuff in here?
He does. He does. That one was real. Uh, was it, is this a treasure map?
Somebody write that down real quick. Bird. What's up? Wait, can I break through? I can
definitely get through that glass. Yeah. Be kidding me. I can't shoot up there. Why not?
His bar is there. Well, did I miss something in that door or around the side? I would imagine
I could have grappled hooked up to the top there, but I guess not. Once we go back, wait,
can't get up there. Why don't we do that? I've asked this question before and I've
never gotten an answer. How come anytime you ever looked down or anytime you rub your eye,
everybody goes, what is the reflex in your brain that does that? Damn it. Oh, I was going to get
a lot of people to think I was cool. Glasses. Somebody has a bomb view. I'm trying to do the
melee when they're far away, but it's not, um, it's not doing it. Do I have to be really far
away? Somebody has a grenade. I can hear it. All right. So I need to go that way. Is it,
is the thing in one of the gravestones? It probably is, right? It's definitely, it's like
in or on the back yet over here somewhere. The worst place to put that. Okay. I don't see it
over here. I just have to backtrack this whole way. I do. I did. Thank you. Stranger. So what
are you buying? You've picked quite the place to set up shop stranger. I, and look what it brought.
That scared the shit out of me. Let's make our first time doing business. All right. I got money
and I, I do have that case customized shit. Don't I? I don't have any, um, key chains for it though.
Got something new for you. I trade it. Wait, let me, let me load these up first.
Blue. Uh, I could do one in one. That'd be good. Or should I wait? Is two better? Should I do two
red? I kind of don't, I don't want to lose all of them though. Two is better. Double is more.
How much more? 12,000. Yeah, let's do it. Oh, this is just for selling.
Well, killing me. Oh wait. Trade. Oh, you can trade for a spinals. Okay. That's interesting.
Got a itchy neck. Ruby's all rubbish. She makes no difference. The price. Well,
that's our choice. I don't need these glasses. Like Wesker doesn't get pissed off or something
like those are my glasses. You found them. Why did you not give them back to me? I don't think so.
Thank you. Anything else I can help you with? All right. Important. You'll get some bang for
your buck. I guarantee it. Sawed off. W870. First aid spray. I want the case upgraded.
All yours stranger. Plus 15% submachine gun ammo craft bonus frequency. I mean, why not, right?
Stranger. Should I get this or am I going to find a better submachine gun in like 20 minutes?
Get it? Stranger. I'm going to get a first aid spray because I suck at video games and I need
to make sure I have it in case I need it. You know, I'll just buy these. I don't always have
this in stock. Stranger. Punisher. That's, is that accuracy or is that, no, is that firepower
accuracy? Precision. Why not try your hand at a new gun stranger? I'm going to keep it. All right.
Tune up. Power. I think we're going to go power. Molding a weapon. We're starting to get an idea
of your tastes friend. I never used the submachine gun. I might as well this time.
Prepare the knife. Your valuables won't do you much good in the grave. I feel like I'm not going
to use this that frequently. I'd rather just not have this. It takes a lot of space.
What do I have here? Hold on. I need to make some stuff. Okay. I could make a ton of submachine
gun ammo. I can make rifle ammo too. Or handgun ammo. Yeah. Let's go submachine gun. Ooh, nice.
Okay. I'm going to hold off now. A lot of ammo. I got two heals. I'll be fine. You hate the
shotgun? Well, I mean, the last time I played this, I did 50 round shotgun and just unloaded
on the last boss and beat the game in 10 seconds. I didn't even have this equipped. Oh my God. I'm
such a dope. I don't know why I thought it was on automatically for some reason. Okay. Let's go.
So far, this is fun. I like it. Just more of a residue before. All right. This thing is ready
to go. So what's next? Into the village square. Should I make the rifle ammo and just have it?
I feel like maybe I will need it. I'll think about it. Let's go. I don't have enough money
to repair the knife, so we aren't going to do that. Get some thoughts. Unusual. Yeah. Yeah.
I said beast. Uh-huh. That thing is coming. Okay. Master, I beg you. All right. Okay. Boom. Oh,
I got to start doing 1080p streaming as well. I'm thinking about how I'm going to do that.
Maybe I just won't. 864p all the way. All right. I thought that was Darth Vader when I came over
here. Like right now, that was Darth Vader. Saddler, the leader of the cult. Make the switch
right now. We'll see. If anything, I probably would. What's the bitrate I stream at right now?
I'm pretty sure I'm at the maximum allowed bitrate for Twitch, but I'm going to look into
that again because I might be able to increase it by like 500 to a thousand, which might just
fix everything. Not that the stream looks terrible, but eh. Let's see. Make the rifle ammo.
I don't have one of these burritos. All right. This is definitely the actual fight.
Okay. What do we got? Parry. You have a knife? Oh, that's why they were saying you should repair
the knife. Jerma. Jerma, can you hear us? Jerma, please. You need to repair the knife. Oh, I see
now. I think I just did it though. You tell me to parry and then you tell me to press C on the
keyboard. Come on, Gwen. Where are you? Oh, shit. Tried to parry it. Does that mean it's locked?
Yes. God damn it. Not again. Oh, I got it. This is the real one. Oh, shit. No. I don't need to do
that yet. He's fake. It's getting thicker. You idiot. Mog-like. Kind of. Chief's house.
Thought I'd left that life behind. Are you reclined? My legs are not up. Hey, in the future,
might be an opportunity where I would be in. Legs might be up. All right. Let me just make sure I
get everything here. Let me replace all the stuff I just shot. Sausages? Corn. There are sausages
right behind it, guys. Glass. Anything else? Yes. Okay, so that was this house. You know,
I'm checking every single one of these, right? And we shouldn't. Every single one of these.
Shotgun. Boogers. Oh, Leon took it. Continuity. That it? Maybe. It's a quick rocking break.
What is the green smudge behind you? It's making me want to. Hey, will you settle down?
It's the whole Pac-Man crew. Settle down. Keep them. Oh, trust me. I will keep them.
I just want to put them there because it was fun. And I have a streamer room now.
All right. I could have. That's this one. There's one more. Two more houses I want to look at.
Anything else? I don't think so. Oh, egg. Nice. There is an Omega chest in here.
Oh, that's this one. This one. There's one. What? Two more houses? One, two. And over here.
That's it. Did I get the item I was supposed to get? No. Yeah, I don't think I did. I have to go
village chiefs. Now, did I get that item? I didn't. So what do I get that? Yeah, maybe up there.
Oh, no, it's broken. Oh, shit. I can go in here. Wait. Don't think I'm stupid. Don't think I'm
stupid. Don't think I don't think I'm stupid. Please don't think I'm stupid. I have a reason
for it. OK, but in actuality, though, I don't have the thing to put into the church thing.
It's some aviators. I just go all the way back. I didn't really accomplish much besides.
Yeah, sure. No, I know. I mean, I need that circular thing. I thought I was going to get
it from that little boss fight, but I didn't get it. Are you pretending? No. Every time there's a
cut scene, I go like this and just just watch what you guys say for five minutes. And then I turn back
when the cut scenes over and then the cut scene ends. And she has said the next step of the video
game. And I've been just like hanging out over here. It's like just like just chatting. You
you guys are the cut scene for me. That's so funny to think about. Not every time,
but a lot of time. It kind of works out that way. Name every bug. Beetle. Spider. Arachnid.
Selpigid. Scorpion. Wasp. Bee. Weevil. Death feigning beetle. Ant. Butterfly. Earwig.
Okay. Who cares? Oh, is it a cut scene? No, I'm paying attention now.
Has accepted the gift. The straw's not long enough. That's what she was during that cut scene.
Ada saves him. Ada saves him. It's pretty cool. That's my favorite chapter, I think.
Anybody else do that? I hate that I do it, but I do it. It's so obvious, but you do it anyways.
Something's on TV or a movie or a show or a game. Doesn't matter what it is.
And you know what characters on screen and you fall asleep for like five straight minutes.
And when you know that everyone else is awake and you're not,
you kind of wake up and just say the character's name. And then the thing that they were just
doing, like, oh yeah, I was watching like Ada on the roof. Yep. Ada up on the roof.
That was good. That was good. It was a good chapter. Pretty cool. What's, yeah,
that's like probably like the best part of the game, I think. And you were sleeping for five,
10 straight minutes. It's like, everybody knows you have no idea what just happened.
And it sucks so bad when that person is then like, yeah, dude. Oh,
the part right before that too. Like, remember that? It's like, oh shit. I'm getting quizzed.
Yeah. Oh, and then you make up shit that you started a new conversation. You say like,
oh yeah. Hey, did you upgrade? Did you upgrade that gun? Did you, that when you upgraded that
gun, are you going to continue to upgrade the machine gun? Then you get them talking
and make sure that they continue to kind of lead the conversation to a new area.
What a first world problem. I'll say that's social poker. No, that's, I don't want the
person to think that I don't care or I'm not paying attention or I'd be like, keep them busy.
That outfit, that outfit is so funny. I wasn't sleeping. You, you pick things that, you know,
you can ask an answer to. My sleepy dad does that a lot. I don't have a key. Okay. I need a key.
It's 3am in Europe. Why are you always alive at the worst times? Well, here's you and here am I.
There's 7 million miles between us. Sorry. Sorry. I'm really sorry. It's just the way it is.
You said I have jowls? Who just said I had jowls? Ban that person for real. Like,
don't let them ever come back. No, I don't. Whatever. Did anybody actually say that? I
actually need to know. What did they actually say? And at least their holy book looks interesting.
Jowls detected. Reload all these guns. None of us are thinking about your jowls.
They got permabanned. Let that be a lesson. Oh, you little shits. This could use some cleaning.
I can't leave empty handed. Oh, grandpa's coming out. Ooh, an extravagant clock.
Oh no, the recliner era. Yeah. I was going to have a cigar over here and have like a little,
like a lighter, just like take a break and be like, I'll be right back. Put it in and like,
just walk off camera. Maybe I still will. Just pretend you didn't see it. Pretend we didn't
talk about it. Okay. So cool. Very cool. Wait, check every single corner. Yeah, that's why.
What have we here? Wait, there was a, there was a bureau that a key could go into.
Back here. There was a key. There was a keyhole. Look at that. I think if I put that key
into the keyhole, I might be, where is that room? Is he cooking? Fellas. Fellas. There's a keyhole.
Holy. Okay. Whoa. This is probably important. Brothers and sisters. Our Lord is displeased.
Do not recklessly slay outsiders at will. All people have a right to fair. Has anybody else
found this? Henceforth, we shall deliver solemn justice without prejudice. Take any
when you capture the factory basement. Do the same with the traders. I bet they took him.
I think you might be the first. I feel like, I mean, that's, who would be able to put that
together? It's like kind of hard. Most people just would give up, I think. Okay. So now I got
to go down here. Sounds good. Let's go. Can I like run out now? Chest? No. Is this a fight?
Whoa. I, what happened to him? No. What? There's, there's going to be jewels and stuff back there.
I can't, whatever. You cannot be serious. There's no way you got a hold of me. That was just,
this lady was magnetized to my body. Can you, I wonder if you can kill him. No, you can't. Leon
kills him in like four hours from now. What am I talking about? Is there stuff in here? Who cares?
Ah! Grapple. Grapple it. Grapple. Just kill me. Kill me. That, no, this doesn't count.
I wouldn't have taken that much damage. Just let me restart. Everybody just settle down.
I bet they took him here. He's playing on standard. He's unbelievable. Ah, shut up.
Shut up. Grandpa skill issue. Yeah. All right. I'm not, I turn around and run. All of these escape
the guy. I always just take it so not seriously. And it's, you have to take it dead seriously.
She does not sound concerned at all. Looks like I gave them the slip.
He's too cool for this. Yeah. Have some new goods that might interest you.
If you turned around and started Fortnite dancing to that guy, do you think he would stop?
Do you think he'd be like, Oh, or if you like held your hand out, like, I think he'd be like,
Oh, wait a minute. What does that mean? What does that mean? Why are you doing that?
I feel like you would actually stop. Did I get, I haven't gotten any of these.
Minus two. Don't let them get to you. It's all right.
I can put a blue in here. 10,000. I haven't found any of these. I've just not been looking
or have I not found any? I can sell this, right? Yeah. That means I can sell it. I forget.
Don't play this game. I don't like it. I like it.
8% running speed. That's like, that's hacking a hundred thousand dollars. Okay. Nevermind.
Give that the care it deserves, mate.
And probably ammo capacity. Try that on for size. I've been using the knife a lot.
What can I do you for? Okay. That's a bird. Okay. Now I need to, some grubby thief has stolen
a jacket. One of those nice sheepskin leather ones. I think you can get it back. I think I saw
this. No, I didn't. It's inside here. Does this massage your back? No, that'd be really funny
if it did though. Let me do a little bit of moving around here. Okay. So I have these. Yes.
Nice. You need a sharper image chair. I have not heard that in a long time. I'm going to eat the
egg. All right, let's go. Why is the chair blurry? Like a felt material, like a upholstered.
Interactive retinal inquiry system. The iris will allow you to see clues that are almost
invisible. We get a Batman mode. Okay. How do I do that? Must be the big guys. Iris activated.
Okay. So that way, but what is over here? Can I turn that? No. This new different music is
playing right now. What? Wait. Oh no, no, no, no, no. Okay. Okay. I'm fine. I'm fine. We're fine.
Eat the egg. That didn't count. That was annoying. Must be the big guys. Let's go.
That's some, uh, that's some TF2 backstab shit right there. Right. Just bite me. Oh,
I got the jacket. Nice. Okay. I should go too. I'm going to go turn it in right now.
It's spinals, right? Crossbow last crossbow. Oh goodness. All right. I got to, I don't think I'm
going to keep that. That's kind of got to go. Yeah, that I don't, I don't think I'm going to
use it. Let me just go back and get this, uh, turning what you're buying. Oh, I have to sell
it. Right. Seven spinals. Okay. So killing me years haven't been kind to us for operative
resources, for operative large resources. What is the, what's the one I need to use?
Okay. So that's the, the larger, small at the maps dude. Yeah, that's a good idea.
Uh, it's large, right? Yeah. Good instincts. I might just get one of these too.
What's worth more purple or probably purple. I can turn this in now. You choose that one.
Okay. Welcome. What can I interest you in? I can upgrade some more stuff. Very nice.
A deal. Well struck. There you are. This thing is now disgusting. All right. I think I'm just
going to sell this thing. I don't think I'm going to use it. I not using really it, you know,
I don't think so. How much is it worth? Do you much good in the gray? Five grand. That's it.
You don't have to keep justifying it. I know that. Right. Hold on a minute. I always go,
you know, I, you know, you know, but the, the, the 40 people in this chat that are going to call
me names because I got rid of the crossbow. He's zipping up his crotch villain arc. I just, I won't
use it. You know me. I'll wait till the last cut scene and shoot it once and miss the guy's head
this way and then reload the save. I'm just going to get rid of the trouble. Decide in a deal.
Struck. Uh, where are the, I got to just get rid of the ammo for it too.
Oh boy. I can certainly do something with this. Give that the care it deserves.
Save my money. Got to select. Thank you. Do check out my wares again soon.
Oh, I have the new case. All right. More resources. This dude absolutely hates his viewers.
He hates us. Somebody said I'm soft locked. You're freaking me out. I know it's, I don't,
I don't think I am, but he hates us. How do I turn off the golden eye clock that's on the
screen right now? How do I get this off? Or is it just on? Oh, right. It needs to be on.
My legs are up in the air right now and I'm just swinging. May as well be at,
may as well be at the park. Now what? Treasure. Where is it? Bullets. Treasure in here. Oh,
it's a, are you in an AI generated chair? I'm going to, I'm going to lift my hand up to smoke
a cigarette and I'm going to have like 14 fingers. So I can't get that. Whatever.
These belong to Louise. That's a lot of money. Okay. So these, did Louise do this? Oh, I remember
this cut scene. Wait, is this where Louise was dancing? There's a lot of, nah, this is when he
was with Leon, right? Look at that. Okay. 4-2-2-1-6-2-5. Okay. Is this his frequency?
Nobody answers an unknown phone number. That's my job. Are you about ready to hand over the
amber? There's a big house just outside the village past the windmill. Yeah, I know it.
And where's the chainsaw?
Where is it? That was fucking scary. Is that loud? I'm sorry. All right. We're good.
Am I scared of the video game or did I put my hand on a fucking hot stove? What, what, what,
what happened? If I put my hand up right now, it's going to be bright red pulsing. Jesus. I need to
settle the fuck down. I don't have a key. And why am I using this rifle? I could have just shot him
one, one second with the gun that's actually upgraded. All right. You shot her a hundred
times in the ass. Oh my God. Is she still alive? I I'm not, I'm not dying there. I'm sorry. I'm not
dying there. I have to, I have to find it. Oopsie. Oh, somebody's saying, oh, so close. Oh, I'm not
going to hit every single bear trap on the ground. Okay. I'm going the absolute wrong way, but there's
money here. Where is it that? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Sorry. I'm turned around. I was
really scared. Where is this? Uh, there we go. Okay. Let's get out of here. Uh, I can't get this.
There is something here. He's shaking. I'm fine. Use some WD 40 on that chair. Oh yeah. It looked
like it did look like that. Oh no. Let's go. There's nothing in here. And I keep, I keep doing it.
I need to take a break so I can fill this back up. It is Wesker. To what do I owe this pleasure?
Stop wasting my time, Ada. Find Lewis, fetch me the Amber. I should probably thank you for this
room. Are you staying? Back me up. I'm not here to babysit you. See that you remain an asset.
I'm not a liability. I have absolutely no use for your incompetence. Easy with the threats,
Wesker. Just get it done. I'll be in touch. Wesker, Wesker, Wesker. Uh, where do you think he gets his
glasses? Yes. Just had some business to attend to. I'm on my way now. See you soon. Ciao. Hey,
there's a lot of treasure over there. All right. Let me, uh, take a quick break. I'm going to get
some, refill my, um, drink. I'll be right back. Give me one sec. Okay. I am kind of back. Just
need to move this back and we're good. Refilled the drink. Yeah, kind of. Well, I'm settling back
down doing some stretches, moving my legs around. You're going to stream on YouTube.
Uh, I don't know. I know I want to do some YouTube content again, but I'm kind of just
playing it by ear and just doing what I feel like on a day-to-day basis, at least in like the content
creation shit besides the off-brand stuff. Cause that is usually, usually spend at least a few
hours. I'd say at least a few hours a month thinking about what I want to do for this.
So I'm just saying words while I get this figured out. I promise I'm not high. I just,
this keyboard, there we go. You didn't deny hating us earlier. I, nah, but, uh, of like the,
the hours I spent off-brand a week trying to still figure out what the good timing to stream is. I
think I got a pretty good schedule here. I would say it. I'm glad you all, I'm glad you all get it.
I'm glad you all think it's humorous. Okay. Let's go back. Good. Make sure the camera's in a good
spot. Yeah. I was happening here. It wasn't tangled. Take a step. I looked in the mirror.
I keep thinking of that person that said I look like the guy that owns the castle. All right. Hi.
Okay. Are you ready? I'm ready. I want them back down. Actually. I love this little keyboard,
this thing before we get started and keep going that I can turn the volume up and down with this.
Okay. Um, take a look at this thing. It's one of these. It's one of those half keyboards,
not a full keyboard. It doesn't have the, uh, all the number pad on it. It's awesome. It's a steel
series apex three. The thing is awesome. Great to just kind of sit right on the lap here. Perfect
little ergonomic form factor, whatever you want to call it. Small keyboard. No, no sponsor. It's
just, I just like it. It's just works great for what it's I'm using it for. And that's it. All
right. What the hell was I just doing? Getting jewels from downstairs. Is this a scary part?
Hey, Hey, bro, bro, bro. Is this a scary part? Where's this? I have everything reloaded. You're
really into bro tonight. Yeah. I'm just hitting me. I'm in one of those. I'm just in a mood. You
know, you get in a mood, you just kind of run with it. Okay. So I need to just go up all the way up
here. I got to go out the front door. I can push out of the way. Yeah. It's going to be some mood
lighting back here. Eventually. It'd be nice. Not just the Pac-Man crew. Well, stereo. It's a Nell
S Ron reunion at Odo. El Mundo. Uh, Ness, a newestro brand. Well, I could've just clicked it.
The outsider is in the villa. Assemble the village. Awaken our great child. Okay.
Come take a look. New item. I've got something new for you, man. Laser sight,
rocket launcher. What you see is what I've got. Oh, a case upgrade. Do I have anything to sell?
Splendid. Uh, yeah, I can do, I'll get the case.
All right. Did I get a knife upgrade? I think I really should make up for a lack of skill.
Maybe just all the way I'll do. Yeah. Case upgrade. I'll do it too.
Shit. I need two bucks. Ruby's all rubbish. It makes no difference. The price.
That's our choice today. Thank you. All yours. Stranger. Where would it come back anytime?
Much better. Can I do any of this? Nope. Sell the shells. Oh, welcome. That's true.
I don't think I plan on doing shotgun. I'll save the money.
What can I interest you in? Nope. Next time then. All right, let's go. Hey, what the fuck?
I still have not figured out how to do the, um, I just almost got crippled. Uh, the grapple thing.
Oh my God. I beat the shit out of me. Hey, really? It won't work. Why is your webcam like this?
Uh, it's temporary. It's uh, it's not where it's going to be, but I think it looks fine.
You guys, you guys spend way too much time caring about the webcam angle and you should be asking
about how I just missed three headshots in a row. That's the real questions you should be asking.
How did you miss three headshots in a row? See, that's why, isn't that better? That's much better.
Okay. There's stuff here. I already got, where is this jewel in this house downstairs? No,
it's in the other house over there. There it is. Very cool. That's yep. Golden chicken egg.
And this is a key that I don't have. Okay. Uh, I want to get all the treasures. So sorry,
everybody. I know we might get bored, but I want to just go get them or at least the ones I can
get. So I'm going to go into the town hall, which is okay. How do I get back into there and why did
I not get it when I was already over there? That's the most annoying part for me. Wasn't I just in
there? Was I not? Apparently I wasn't. Oh, well, how long is the DLC? Um, if you, I think it's like
three to five hours, something like that. Usually about two or four depending on who's playing it
and I'm playing it. So two hours of speed run time and a lot of health. Oh, that's why. Okay.
Ooh, cool. Uh, I guess the best way to see how far I am right now is how many chapters are there?
Six. I imagine probably five, six, seven, seven. Yeah. Everything loaded.
Kind of. All right. So now I'm going to get over here. What's the best way to get over there from
here? This way. What time are you born? 12.00 AM. I don't know, like six. That's a grenade.
It's a bouncy ball. You throw a bouncy ball at me. The bounce on that was fucking ridiculous.
There's no reason why that should have bounced that high. Oh, I thought he went down into the
thing. Okay. Damn. You have an aura of a Looney Tunes physics character. I don't know. Something.
Shit. The knife is broken. Shit. I thought I was far enough away. Am I damaging the knife when I
swing at that? When I hit the crates in the ground? I actually might be. No. Okay. Anything
in there? Can't get up top. Hold on. I can't jump into one of those windows. Really? There's nothing
over here. What kind of horse shit is that? Sell those. Somebody has a grenade somewhere. I love
that you pulled apart your sectional for this stream. You mean all of them going forward.
It ain't just for this one. It's for the rest of them. So Professor X. It looks like Professor
X's chair. Does it? What does the back of Professor X's chair look like? Something's wrong with my
game. Oh, I got seen. I thought that was a baby crying. Sorry, big guy. Can't let you go that way.
Oh, go. Okay. Cool. I'm going to destroy this shit. I throw a grenade in his mouth. I have so
many holes in his head. No, I was trying to jump onto the thing. Get on. Get on. How do I get on?
Cool. Cool. Oh, shit. Let's get the fuck out of here. Is the game loud at all? Looks like it's
kind of loud. I need to drop it by like 10%. It's good. Okay. Looks like it's getting up kind of in
the yellow. Sweet dreams. Now I'm just going to loot the whole thing because there's going to be
a lot of items around, right? Usually there is. Hey, got a smoke? I do. The kind you like. Now
where's the amber? Unfortunately, it's not on me at the moment. And you really shouldn't be telling
me. What a good job I did. Didn't we just do this like an hour ago? Managed to hide it right before
I got caught. Which is why I'm still alive. The deal was we get you out of here when you deliver
the amber. No amber, no protection, Luis. Such a stickler for details, huh, Ida? Okay, then.
I'll go get it now. How about that? It's loud during fights but quiet during cutscenes.
Everything is up all the way. Maybe I should turn the effects down.
Fine. Yeah, it's all right. I'll just leave it. Chapter four. I feel like if those things were
real, you wouldn't. You would just fly into the air and just die. You would do the grapple hook
and you'd be going 50, 60 miles per hour. You would just go straight into the air.
Or straight into the fucking wall and smash your head. It would tear your arm off.
Yeah, you would dislocate your shoulder. Both shoulders if you had it with both hands.
They are both infected. They need this medicine. It slows the infection and I know it works.
I used it on myself. So, why does this matter to me? Because you two are infected. That's what
I researched for all these years, Ida. And I see the symptoms already showing in your eyes.
You must already feel the effects, eh? The medicine will stop them for a time.
Just trust me. A lot to gain and nothing to lose. Okay, but this is your last chance.
We do this first and then the amber. I'll let Leon know.
Hola, Luis here. Las Plagas is fucked. Imagine getting like, imagine seeing one.
Because I have a present I want to give you. Medicine that will help you suppress
the progress of your problem. I can't imagine having to like, see one.
Come to the courtyard. Who is this guy?
Meet up there. Ciao. Sorry to keep you waiting. Shall we? Ladies first.
How chivalrous. I didn't even look if there's any items in the room.
There's a hidden laboratory downstairs. My stuff should be there. Along with the suppressant.
I don't care about a laboratory. We're not going there. We're not going there. I don't want to go
there. We're not going there. There's way till Resident Evil 30 when you get to pick the path
you want to go on. Do you want to go to the lab? Highlight left. Do you want to go to the church?
Highlight right. And the whole time when you're making a decision, what other character in the
cutscene does this? Which way do you want to go? Hey, we don't go out there. I fucked up the line.
I can't. Sorry. All I hear in my head is beep, beep. Like a fucking microwave. The food is done.
I screwed it up so bad. What was I hearing? Was I hearing this?
Wait, what? Are you making fucking popcorn up here? Where'd he go? Oh shit. This is what I
get for not paying attention. Who else is in the room? That was a bugleberry voice. That was an
oh yes. Shit. No, no, no, no. Not yet. I want, I want apple cake. I want apple cake. You've been
fighting this one guy down here for so long. How many bullets did you shoot into this guy? A lot.
I want apple cake. I think three of you are going to know what that's from.
Well, yeah. Monster rancher too. I want apple cake. Uh, I need to heal. Should I just take the
golden egg? No, it's worth a lot of money. He's dying. What's wrong with him? Why is she running
so weird? Oh, he's fucking dead. He's dead. Like in five seconds. I want apple cake.
Get back here. Don't inhale the smoke. It's like he's breathing in as hard as he can.
Just don't breathe forehead. That's right. If you're trying to kill yourself, can you do it
after you've delivered the amber? It's all gone. Burnt to nothing. Why is this so important to you?
There are things I must set right, but that is impossible now. It's all over
and they can't help them anymore. Pull yourself together, Louise. Nice hamster step. You know how
just do it. Yes, it is possible. The ingredients are out here in the castle. Yes, I need time.
I can still get you your amber. All right, then let's go. How many times have I said shut up
that I can go back at least five and figure out our next move. I'm just kidding, though. Don't
worry. Am I? Maybe not. It's at least more than one. Maybe not. I got the item.
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Slow down. You'd rather be doing anything else right
now. That's not true. I'm having this is fun. I'm having a great time. No, I trust me. You want
about? Well, you can work for the devil as you get me out of here. I'm not. I'm you guys are
mistaking. Relaxed with bored. Boomer face cam gameplay. Yeah, that's how it is now. Sorry.
The way it is now. I think I'm having to join myself immensely right now. This is wonderful.
Oh, yeah. I'm a look. Where's the key? You should be able to use the sword.
Shit. You need a blankie. It won't be my finest effort. I might just work all the
all the way up to my to my neck, the bottom of my neck. Find these ingredients. And one of those
goofy hats. Just maybe I can make a new batch of medicine. I'm not a friend. You go way too hot to
do that. Not right now. Go grab the amber. Wish me luck. Maybe during the winter time. It'd be
funny to do that. Look like an asshole for a little bit. All right. We need red ink, gold
bottle, blue butterfly. They're probably just on the map. They are. Oh, there's a lot of shit.
OK, good luck. This is where we parked this stuff in here. Not really. Can you summarize the plot
in five seconds or less? Bugs get into your brain and control you. And Wesker has a vial,
but it keeps going like this. I think that sums it up pretty well. All right. First,
the bindery. It's this part. All right. Let me take a quick look. Nothing really in here. So
I'm not going to fuck with that. A raccoon. Guess this is fate.
Awesome way. Hey, that's a graphic stone like yourself.
Stones. Welcome. Somebody. Somebody is sub five dollars a month for me to say that every time.
I just want to make sure somebody pays five bucks a month for me to do that.
Ruby's all rubbish. She makes no difference. The price. A deal well struck.
Does this thing maxed out capacity? Dazzled. Does this have a maximum craftsmanship or no?
That's good work. If I do say so myself later, I think that's kind of it. Red nine. I don't
really necessarily care. I don't always have this in stock. Stranger.
Minus one gunpowder when you use my crafting. That's kind of good.
Flash. Actually, I should get that. Oh, remind me that that's their top shape.
Thank you. Check out my wares again soon. The worst. That's the worst harm.
Seem that bad. Do I just put a bunch of these away? Dude, green weed laughing my ass off.
Holy shit. Mod that guy or ban that guy. OK, I I got it saved. I just a compulsive saver.
I'm going to do it again. And let's continue. Green needle rainstorm. Green needle.
I just repaired this thing that's already broken. Incoming puzzle. Fuck. Not yet. Oh,
yeah. OK. Puzzle time. Puzzle time. All right. That's a that's a fan. This bird doesn't match.
Maybe. No, maybe it does. So what's you already did this one in normal mode.
Hear me out for a sec. Yesterday, when you watched the Resident Evil four playthrough
that I did and you watched this part. And today I'm streaming this. You have to remember
that was recorded four and a half months ago. So you got it right there. And here you are
one day later. So I just did this. I just did it on your screen in a while.
I was doing the smiley face. My hair looks so bad. It looks like there's a joke under here.
It looks like I'm about to lift this up and there's going to be like an animal under it.
I look like fucking Edgar Allen Poe. Do I? Holy shit. That's kind of cool. All right. I'm going
to rock it. I'm going to rock with that. All right. What was the point I was making? Oh,
yeah. I don't remember. It's been a while. It's been like two. Bird on the left.
And this be a square up here. I mean, there's only so many combinations this could be, right?
What's going on here? Doesn't this look correct? I'm biting my lip. Get off the cam.
Hmm. I just don't remember. I need another orange one, don't I? Is there another one in the room
that I'm just missing? Hmm. The fuck am I doing wrong here? What the heck? I'm subbed to this
dork. Oh, what the heck's happening here? Obviously, this needs to be a square. This
needs to be a I don't what I'm like, I feel like I'm missing a piece. I guess not. The hell am I
doing wrong? It's there's only so many this only like what, 16 combinations is only like 20
combinations. This could be. Hmm. I am munching on my lip and I got to stop. Hold on. True.
When a puzzle comes up, I just start tearing into my bottom lip. Dorito goes into the wind.
So you would need the bird needs wind. The dress needs a bird and the bird needs wind.
Bird needs that. I actually don't know. I have no idea. This shouldn't be this hard,
but I'm playing checkers when you need to play. I'm playing chess when you need to play
like hopscotch, like it's not even hard. I'm saying cheese, cheese, Dorito, cheese, cheese,
cheese, Dorito, Dorito. Illuminati symbol. Tornado. Tornado. Tornado needs a weather.
It's bad weather. It's I'm playing Pictionary again. Like the one of these has to be down here
or here. What am I missing? What's happening to me? Dorito sugar. Yeah. Stinky cheese. No sloth.
I feel like I've done every single combination you could possibly do. Um, I don't do puzzles.
I do pick Russ and that's it. I just know how to run wicked fast for like five seconds.
And like, I like, I, I, I don't know. I don't get it. How many combinations can it possibly
be that I haven't done umbrellas, dress, and bird. And I did this four months ago.
A person is watching the video of me saying the same shit right now. Pull it up. I'm doing,
I'm saying the exact same. You know what? How about we just pull the video up when I'm doing it?
And I'll say, I'll just ask myself, I will talk to myself. I don't even know where it is. That's
a, that's like a whole, that's a whole can of worms. I don't even know what timestamp it is.
What's the timestamp on the, on the VOD in a mod link, the VOD with timestamp. I need to open the,
uh, I need to have mod chat open. Yeah. Okay. I got it. I got it open now. Wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on.
Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. We just don't know. You don't know. Let me ask,
let me ask you, uh, me from like four months ago. Did someone find it? I don't think so.
It's like, it's like three streams, but I just, I just don't get it. Like, and I,
it's going to be so obvious, but I just don't care. Do you know what I mean? I would just throw
a grenade at this wall. I would, you know what? I would just call somebody. I would be like,
Hey Wesker, what's up? Hey, what's up, dude? I'm sitting at a wall. Look, I'm the guy that
runs fast. And like, you know, you keep me around because I tell jokes and I, you know, I'm a writer
I'd be dead in a minute, by the way. Oh, oh, you're, oh, you're a writer. You tell you write
jokes. Yeah. I don't fucking need you at all. Actually. Let me, I don't need a writer.
Uh, what do you want? All right. So I'm looking at this thing right now, Wesker.
Uh, there's a bird and there's a cutoff symbol. There's a cutoff bird. There's a fan at the top
and that's orange. The bird and the fan are both orange and this fan has a square on it. Okay.
Okay. Are you with me here? So far? On the right, there is a, a dress in a hexagon shape.
Dress. What kind of dress is it? It's, it's got one of those poofy dresses from like the
1400s or something. A poofy 1400s dress. Yes. That, that's exactly it. The ones that like,
they have like big cage in them. Yes, yes, yes, yes, yes. The big ones. Okay. I got that down.
Okay. Then the bottom, this, remember it's two umbrellas. So there's a second umbrella at the
bottom of the hexagon as well. Regular umbrella. It's just like one of those umbrellas. It's got
like frills on it. Frilly umbrella. Also from the 1400s. Yes. Actually, yes. Okay. So let me think
here. So what I think is, and there's four slots. They have four slots. Uh, let them out. I don't
care. Just let them out. Just tell me what to do. I don't care. I don't care. Just tell me what it
is. We can do it together. It's fun that way. We're doing it together. We're going to do it
together. Yeah. See chat. We're hanging out. We're doing it together. Rotate them. What do you mean
rotate them? Okay. Listen, you have to understand. I thought that was telling me that I could move
them. I, the Q and the E were, were not rotate in my brain. Wow. Shit. Oh, that's on the internet
now. Do you know what I mean? Like that's not, that's on, that's like on the, that's on the
internet now forever. I'm sitting kind of far away from the screen. I it's like, it's a different
setup. I, to me, the, the rotate was not there. Oh my God. That's yeah. I can't believe it.
I had to remember. I'm not pretending at all at all. Zero pretending absolute zero.
I was just so lasered it. I don't even know how I was so lazy. That's the worst moment ever.
You don't have the attention span for directions. I, that, that's probably the worst, uh, the worst
ever, ever in 15 years of doing this. I just had to go like this. And I don't, I don't have an
excuse for you. I really don't. My only excuse is I can see it now is just ADHD. That's the only
excuse. That's it. I can't tell you another reason why I genuinely could not tell you another reason
why, because I, my brain, the Q and the E were not on the screen. They were just not on screen.
They were gone. They weren't there until you brought that up. That's crazy. What a fucking
case study. That's an unbelievable case study for ADHD because wow. We, you just watched it.
Did I do it in the last one too? We've got the timestamp for the last one. Did I do it in the
last one? Glasses in the cutscene. Yeah, they really are just ruining everything. All right.
This is the maze part, isn't it? My name is May. You can tell what game I was playing
six months ago. Oh my fucking God. I can't believe I didn't see it. How I do it again. I do it again.
I do it again. It happens. It happens back here too. I don't rotate it guys. We're talking about
this as consistency. It's consistency. It is absolute consistency. I'm just, I'm not, I haven't
spun them once. I think I'm, am I missing one? Let's just listen to them for a little while.
Oh wait, you can flip them. Oops. Took them a lot quicker. Hey, I'm retired now. It's all right.
Okay. Well it's been, sure been fun. All right. So this goes here. This goes here and
this needs to be a square. Where is the, where is that? I don't have a, I can't,
I can't tell you what just happened there. The first ingredient should be in this room.
The only thing I can attribute it to is being sitting in this new room and being like this.
That's it. Oh well. Oh well. Hey, hey, hey, the mod chat. How could you let me fucking do it?
You should have said rotate the fucking cubes, man. You should have, I should have looked over
and it should have been like, hey, rotate the fucking cubes already. You should have gave me,
you should have given me some extra fucking direction. Wait, did they? No, they didn't.
No, they didn't. Okay. Let's go touch it. Ooh, I get to do the shooting thing. Is that in this?
You're sitting too far away. That actually might be what happened. And I know, you know,
streamer dumb. I know. I know. But I think that's probably why I didn't see it. I was moving them
too quickly and I, you know, I'm not going to give excuses anymore. That was really stupid.
Oh well. Okay. Watch your eyes. He's too, he's too comfortable. Uh, I think my brain
saw them as like A and D to like move them, not rotate. Okay. I mean, let me stop giving excuses
to why that just happened and play the game. So where is it? Red ink or blue ink or something?
Where is it? Okay. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Get shooting. So shoot the shields. Who has a shield? Okay. So
what's the order? 1, 2, 3, 4, 1, 2, 3, 4. That not correct. All right. Wait, wait, hold on. Zoom
it in. Let me get close. Let me go. Let me get close. One is, so wait, it's what is it? It's 1,
1. Hold on. 1, 2, 3. Is that right? 1, 2, 3. No, it's the way that they're on the wall.
So where the fuck is this one? Look around. Oh Jesus. Okay. There's other ones. Okay. So that
was, this is it here. So that's the right one over here. And then it's one. Where is this?
That's okay. That's like an elk, elk, elk, lady, little lady. All right. So where's the,
where's the elk? I mean, bro, what does that even matter? Or you just shoot it in the right
direction? 1, 2, 3, like this. Am I playing chess again? I don't know. Hold on. Did I have it right
when I spun it? 1, 2. Yeah. Okay. Spin it. 1, 2, 3, 4. Is that not right? There's no way. Well,
I, I flipped it though, right? You're playing battleship on a chessboard. I'm laughing so hard
right now. Okay. Well that's the correct one. 1, 2, 3. 1, 2. I gotta do it upside down. 1, 2, 3.
Why is he flipping it? I must be fucking tired. Am I like sleepy? Holy shit. I am like 40. Okay.
1, 1, 2, 3. Shit. Jesus. I gotta get my fucking eyes examined. Holy shit.
Oh my God. I'm like, I'm like too comfortable. Jesus. That was 15 minutes. Dude. Is it,
is there carbon monoxide going into your room? Jeez, man. That was fucking ridiculous.
Change the outfit? I can't. I have to keep it like this. It's too good.
Right. How about we continue this discussion another time? See you around. He looks like
Jerry Seinfeld. Okay. Let's go. Do I have any of the fun hats for Leon? Okay. So,
there is another thing down here. The gate and gong have the same sense.
Seems simple enough. All right. Snakes. This is a snake right here, right?
Does it just shoot snake twice? Is there another snake? There is. You should bedazzle the recliner.
No, not this shit. Turn and run? What the fuck? Open the door. Um, oh, you need to wear your
glasses. I think it's a combination of visual distance and ADHD object permanence. Like in
my brain right now, I can say, hey, that's an elk right there. And when I turn around,
it's an elephant. It's gone. It's carbon monoxide. It's it's no, I have a detector.
You're making me think for a second. You're like, oh, I'm like, oh shit. Being high doesn't help.
Yeah, that's true. Okay. Now for the second ingredient. Give me these jewels. I want it.
Looks like something goes here. Okay. Oh shit. It's one of these guys. Holy shit. That was cool.
I probably have to pick that up again. I'm imagining more stuff. Okay. No key. What?
I think I know what's coming. Yeah. Okay. Gold bottle. Oh my goodness. Okay. Oh boy.
Whoa. What just hit me? Almost out of bullets. Oh, you piece of shit. Leave me alone.
Come here. Come here. Come here. Oh my God. You little shits over there. Leave me alone.
Holy. Holy. Now I get a minute. Let me this, this, this jewels in here. Okay. So I have both
the bottles. Do I want to do anything else in this room or no? I don't think so. Do I have a
favorite gem? Um, probably birthstone. That's the easy answer. Stone of birth. What? Uh, should I go
back and check for that treasure? I feel like I should, but I think it's a key. I think it's a
key. I don't think I have a key to open it. I need the gold bottle. I need to keep the gold
bottle. So I'm not leaving that. There are blue medallions here. Okay. Out there. There's no
inputs on these. I guess not. All right. I want, what do I want to do here?
Starting to get good luck to you. There you are. I'll keep a lookout for items.
Okay. Hmm. Is there, is there another knife that I find later? I can do the whole DLC tonight.
Probably. Yeah, probably. There's only a few more chapters. There's only two more chapters.
Yeah. It's a lock drawer. All right. The last one is over way up here.
So I'm going to go through the courtyard. I want that, whatever that is. Okay. Louise,
that's two. Last one should be in a room accessible from the castle wall. And here's
some more info I've recovered about that old rock. Sending it now. Okay. Reload everything.
And where are the medallions? Can I jump this? I don't need to jump it. It's just right here.
Okay. That was easy. All right. Let's go medallion hunting. Oh wait, there are fishes in there,
aren't there? Does that work? Oh, it does. Probably. This is just health, right? Take the
free health. Wait a minute. Something over here. I think that's it. Yep. Turn on your real face
scan. You don't like my, my made up one. It's like a weird mustache. There's only actually
one treasure in here. Sting. Now, where are the others? Oh, God damn it. You wouldn't just let
me through, could you? Don't kill him. Oh, he fell. I didn't have to do anything. Shut up.
Can I throw a grenade in there? I think I got him. I got some. Oh my goodness. Run. Okay. You
are dead. Thank goodness. Yes. This thing does not do a whole lot of damage without any upgrades.
I want that. So you better believe I'm going to go get it. How do I get? It's over here.
Oh, hold on. Is it a chest? It is. I think I have enough to upgrade to. Oh, not good. Not good. Not
good. Not good. Not good. Damn. I got a million health. Okay. That was ridiculous. Bro, you are
fucking gaming. I am. Okay. So one up here, one over here. I don't think there's any more treasure.
Uh, hold on. Let me go up here. I could just go over there. Where's this one? It's in the building.
I like the stash. I get, uh, I don't know how long it's going to be here for. It will only be
here as long as it'll be here for enough time. Enough time. All right. Where is this thing?
It's like in that building. Is it in the building? How do I get in this building? No, no, no. There
we go. Okay. It's in here, right? No, it's not. Where is it? Where is it? Did I run by like three
times? Ah, okay. There it is. Last one is in the corner. Is it just right up here? You look like
one of the weasels from Roger Rabbit. Oh, that's awesome. I'm so glad you just said that. That's,
that's who I am. That's legitimately who I am as a person. All of them combined. I feel like I embody
every single one of those characters together as one, as one unit. All right. So I can turn,
I'll turn it in later. Now I'm going to go through here. Can I get there from this one?
Egg? Oh, it's a leaf. All right. Reload this. Reload this thing. What an egomaniac. Um,
they all died. They all die at the end of the movie, by the way. I just want to make sure
you're aware of that. Like they all die. What do you mean, bro? What? What do you mean? What?
Spoiled? Spoilers? Did I not say spoilers? It's the movie's 40 years old and I'm making that up
too. They don't all die. I thought that was required reading for the stream already. Oh,
I thought we already all seen it already a million times. Sorry about that. It's like a,
it's like one part of the movie. Don't worry. That was summer homework. Well,
that was summer homework in like 2019. I thought we'd all seen it already. I think we all have
some, maybe some of you haven't. I don't know. It's a great movie. I love that movie. I think
most of you've already seen it. I'd say majority probably. All right. One's in chat. If you have
not seen Roger Rabbit, I feel like you, there's no way that many of you haven't seen it. No way.
Really? Oh, well go watch it. What are you doing? Like one of the best movies ever.
No treasures. What? I did not mean to press that. That's right. I still have some unfinished
business to take care of. Did I not kill the thing? I thought I did. Nothing there. Okay.
Grab this. Somebody's on the phone.
Sorry. Nothing yet, but my little helper is creating quite the commotion. I have a little
helper? Everything will work out just fine. Oh, Louis. Louis. Leon. Yeah, Louis. Was that guy's
name again? Louis? Jesus. Leon. Changed your mind yet? Yeah. Assuming you haven't. I've got a tip
for you. Seems like something big is about to go down in the throne room. Babysitting's tough, huh?
Hey, it's me Wesker again. You know that anybody can go on a channel and hear anything
across a fucking walkie talkie. I just want to make sure you understood that. Wesker out.
Okay. I am going to go this way. Wait. I'm going to go this way actually, because I want to go.
Should I get this treasure? Yes. Thanks for answering my question. It's down even further.
What are your tips on growing a mustache? I cannot give you any because I grow a terrible mustache.
I've heard you have to just stick with it, but even if I stick with it for a month or two,
it looks like a bird shit on the top of my lip. I don't know if I have any tips for you.
All right. Let's check in up here. I will check below, but not yet. Now I'll go below.
All right. So this one will open if I do that again. Where are you going? It's not going to
happen. You would fit in well in an American civil war teledrama. It's an evil mustache.
It is kind of evil. That's all right. Okay. So that is closed. We need to open. Wait,
anything else back here? Was there another sun or anything? I'll just open it again.
Actually, wait. I want to go down here because I feel like I missed something in here. No,
it's the next room. Okay. All right. So if I go up here, I think I just get back up. I don't really
need to do that again, do I? Go back up. Nothing else? You're like a hamster running around.
Yeah. Yeah. Wait, did I not? Wait a minute. I didn't go over here. A yellow diamond. Nice.
This must be the collection room. Blue butterfly.
Blue butterfly. The collection master is a tacky and lousy boss. He leaves all the dissections
for me to do, even if he does not bother to come here. All he does is up at his three favorite
specimens in a particular order before leaving. There's nothing special about them in any way.
Well, only look at those three specimens. Mr. Wonderful. When we pay attention, don't act like
a fucking joker. It's a puzzle. Pay attention. All right. Order. Okay. So the butterflies have
to be in a certain order. We're on emote only. Yeah. I don't think that will happen again,
if I will be honest with you. Good to know. Okay. So sort of put their hands on this thing.
Skulls. Oh, bugs. Bugs and geodes. This is like my favorite room. Anything else I can interact
with? The shoes, right? So what did you do? You touched a beetle. Then you touched this head.
And I think that's it. You also went over here and you touched salamander, whatever that is.
No matter what order. All right. What are the options? It's butterfly, head, beetle, alligator,
beetle, snake, butterfly, head, beetle. All right. There's two different beetles.
You put your hands all over this thing. What kind of beetle is it? It's a beetle that's going like
this. Okay. Does it matter the order? Probably. Would you eat any of the bugs? No, of course not.
Well, I guess where do they start? Started here. You went beetle, beetle, skull, beetle, skull,
salamander. Okay. There it is. There you go. Okay. Good. Give me that butterfly.
You got everything you need, but exactly what you want. Well, that's not good. The parasite
is reacting to the ember. So that's the ember. That looks like something Wesker would want.
Give me a case. This will knock out the parasite, but only for a time. You ready?
Kind of looks like a grimace shape. Just remember, it's not a cure. We still need
to find a way to get that thing out of you. This guy again. I don't understand. It should
be working by now. Take the ember and go. Once the parasite is sedated, you can give me back
that damn stone. I can't leave you here. Not like this. Spare me. I'll be fine. You got another
promise to keep. Right. But you come find me as soon as you're done here. Okay. Well, round three.
Do I have any ammo? Oh, no. I'm just going. Okay. She's cured. I should have peed. I have to pee.
I'm just rocking around. Okay. I'm going to pee. I'll be right back. Maybe this might be
one more break after this. We'll see. I'm just going to go. Be right back. I have returned.
He must be going through some shit in there. Yeah, I was going through some shit in the bathroom.
Uh, wait, where's my headphones? Why are you pouring tea in the toilet? That is a good question
because I got a good answer for you. When I, I used to talk about tea all the time. I used to
drink tea all the time. I still do sometimes, but that's a, it's like a 2017, 2016, uh, lore.
And also people used to say that they could hear me peeing into the toilet every time I went to
the bathroom. So kind of a combination of a few things. All right, let's get back to it. Are we
ready? Chapter five. Yeah. Loud pee. Yeah, that's what it was. Okay. Make sure you get the stuff.
No stuff. Louise's footprints must've gone this way. It's handprints. All right. So I get it.
So that's a, what is it? A moon? So here's a sun. Okay. Moons are open. Is that? Oh,
it's just a locked door. Okay. Okay. Moons are open. Let me check over here. Wait,
sun needs to be opened. Chronicles of pursuit. Okay. Continue with my current method to change
nothing, but instead widen my search. My microphone needs to be closer. Okay. What
color is each subject? We know green is always science, but what's red, blue, et cetera.
Hmm. To me, red is math, right? Just like, Oh man, it's math. What about like social studies
is still social studies is blue. I think math is blue. Hmm. Yeah. No red. Now red is math.
Science is green. Yeah, for sure. Making sure I don't miss it. This is open now. Okay. So now I
can open this and go down English. You know, math might actually be yellow and English might be blue.
That's tough. You're demented for that. I it's tough though, because I don't know. It's a good
question. Okay. So, uh, I need this to be a moon. It's not a moon. I can't go anywhere else. Hmm.
Okay. Wait, there's nothing else I can do up here. Right? Yeah. This is a, this is a, this is a moon
that I haven't read the first time. Fight chat fight. Um, green might not always be science.
Science might be blue because of like, I don't know, water like, Ooh, like Marine life. Does
that make sense? If a green could also be now. Yeah, you're right. Green is always science. No
matter what. I think that's a given. Okay. Hold on. I got, I got to play the video again. I just
walked up and down the same set of stairs three times. Okay. Okay. Hmm. Can I shoot it up there?
I can't. So this has to be a sun. So I have to jump across and just, okay. So hold on.
Can I go across, but that's not, wait, hold on. I want to, I want to screw this up.
Do I have it? I have it right now. I think I do. Cause then I pull it one more time and then
down here, I'll pull it and it'll be back to normal. I think, right. You guys still fight
to both the subjects. Uh, okay. French is what color is math? Red. A lot of people said radio
math is white. Blue is math because it's cold and logical. Green is science because plants and
chlorophyll. Hold on. Let me, I got to read this. Oh, hold on. I got deleted. Yeah. Green is always
science about orange. What would be red besides math? I'm going to leave that up for now. Social
studies is orange. Yeah. That's that. That does seem pretty, that seems pretty accurate. I'd kind
of have to look at it. I would need to have the colors in the notebooks. Red is health. White
could be health too. So could red. Red could be health or blood. Down we go. Green is health. Oh,
I don't know. I think green is always science. What is this? I'll leave some signs to point you
in the right direction. Okay. He really knows his way around this place. Treasure over here.
Red is good for electives. Yeah. I'm thinking white would be, I think English is blue.
English is blue. Health is white or red. Math is red or orange. Science is green.
What about gym? Well, Jim, you don't like, you don't like study in gym in a notebook.
Jim, hope it's not a sign of things to come. Oh, not these fucking things. Okay. I'll get it there.
Move. What about wizard class? Uh, what about purple? I feel like purple is too
cool of a color to be a subject. Does that make any sense? It's too hip, I think, to be a subject.
It won't open. Not swimming in that. Math is purple. Let's keep doing this. Purple's for the
dark arts. Shit. Okay. Hold on. What's on the other door? Splish splash. Yeah. We're doing this.
Maybe not. Can I not go in there? You died very quickly. Purple is for purple alien. That's right.
You catch sight of the giant shadow moving through the water. Looks like
Gregorio's waterway has a lord reigning over its murky channels. Find out what it is and catch it
for me. Lord of the waterway. That sounds fun. In the water? That scared the shit out of me. Oh my
God. Why? I thought it was, I thought it grabbed me. I thought it was still alive and grabbed my
leg or something. Waterway. Cool. Okay. Seven. You've proven yourself reliable. Got some rare
things on sale, stranger. He's killing me. Why is this small key two and this small key six?
What's up with this scam here? That's kind of a scam. I think one of the cheap ones.
Wise choice. I know green herbs, red herbs. I mean, this thing's cool.
You can't go wrong with that. That'd be all pleasant. Oh my God. This is a mess.
Ooh, I got three blues. Go. Hey, I need all two purples. Hey, two math glasses.
And then I need blue, purple and gray. I can buy them. Can I welcome came into some other bits
in Bob's two names. Good instinct. Stranger. This ain't a charity. Why is he screaming at me? I'll
keep a lookout. I mean that it's, I could, I could do it. Although I don't, I should do every color.
That's for a hundred K. Yeah. I'll sell the other ones or wait. I got purple, green,
red. Hold on a second. Purple, red, green, blue, yellow. Ah, and I can say I'll save these.
Actually, you know what? I don't need to have to be double make the money. Only two chapters left.
As we'll just do it. I have a lot of money now for items that welcome burger King Barry
140,000. I got a lot of money now. This is an insane amount of money.
Thank you. So what now? I power. Ooh, stingray. What is that? A rifle? You'll get some bang for
your buck. I T a well-tuned increased power by one and a half times. Oh shit.
We're starting to get an idea of yours. You've exhausted our normal range of services. This
thing is unbeatable now. If you're interested in something, okay. 60,000. You catch my drift.
Should I just go for it? Your weapons. I need to do. I need a ticket. I think I need to see.
Oh, let us know when you've made some room. Okay. I have, what are you? What is happening?
What the hell are you doing? Docking up while you come back. Just make it all. Just make a ton
of machine gun ammo. Okay. That's pretty good. What do I got now? I don't eat the fish who heals
a bunch of ammo. Well, I've got something new for you. Ruby's all rubbish. She makes no difference.
I don't want to do that. Wait, is this an outfit charm? Oh, I thought that was an,
a new ADA outfit. I was like, Oh wait, this is a new outfit. Then we can talk.
You don't need to take it. Yeah. I don't want to be just completely broke though.
Got something new for you, but whatever you do, it won't do you much good. A deal. Well struck.
The thing is disgusting. It's a veritable work of art. Will that be all then? I think that's all
I want to do. Yes. Thank you. Do check out 70 shots. So we read the charm description. Well,
came into some other bits and bobs to rip shields away from certain enemies using the grapple gun.
That's great. He's killing me next time. Okay. Well this is what I need. So I'm good. All right.
Now let's fight the giant monster in the water. Imagine it's just, it's just right here. Let's
kill this thing. Can I get down there? No. Okay. Let's go. So where is progress now down? You know
what? I'm going to open that. I have a key. You know, pop it open every time it explodes. I think
it grabs me. You dick. You die in the water. Shit. What chair does he have? Probably some CEO chair,
like Herman Miller or something. This is a breastfeeding chair. This is it. This is a
nursing chair. And I wish I I'm not making that up. This is a nursing chair, but it was perfect.
And I had to have it. It was fucking perfect. It's just like, this thing is great. It's,
it works well. It can be a regular chair. It's just a chair. Who cares? Congrats.
Ooh, wait, I can fight the thing. I got a gold bar. I want to fight the thing.
Okay. Wait, you have new stuff. What do you mean?
Got some rare things on sale, stranger. A deal well struck.
Oh, you already had this. You had this.
What can I do you for? Don't get yourself killed.
Oh, chat. Is chat taking it too far? Is chat taking it too far? Settle down. It's a chair.
It's a funny little thing, but relax. Don't have to take it too far.
I agree, but we can all agree. It's a, it's a slightly humorous thing. Don't be weird about it.
Or you're going to get fucking zapped. Okay. My God. Is that him? Right? Is it,
this is the, is this the big guy? Oh shit. Where's the big guy? Wait, where's this diamond?
I don't see it. That's gross. Don't make me regret saying that. It's funny, but come on guys,
relax. Don't make it weird. Don't make it weird. What made you choose this chair over the others?
Okay. Here's the next part of this, which is why it's funny. It's one of the only chairs
at target. There are two chairs at target. This is one of them. They may be more,
there may be one to three chairs in your target. It's the target chair. I love target. Yeah.
Uh, it's also temporary. So, uh, I think I said at the beginning of the stream that
that's a big one right there. Yep. Uh, I'm getting a different chair to be here.
This is very temporary. Uh, and I'm just going to use it as a regular chair after
the other chair is just not here. It will be soon. You're going to betray this recliner.
It's actually, believe it or not, this is actually pretty comfortable.
I like it. It's just like, it doesn't, it just rocks. Uh, I want to turn that in.
What should I get now?
I think, I think I just saved my money. Is the charm of the charms worth it?
Actually it, yeah, it definitely is. Yeah. It's only five. Hard to find a nice desk chair these
days. And those gaming chairs are actually the most uncomfortable. This nursing, whatever,
like baby chair, whatever this actually is. Uh, it's just a great chair and use it for whatever
you want. Like me, you, it's, it actually is crazy. Let's get, let's get real for a second.
Finding furniture that I did when you just want like a small thing to sit in,
just like a little thing. It's kind of hard to find something like this. This kind of stuff
doesn't really exist. It's either like a giant fucking huge thing or it's part of a big couch
or it's a curved up here. It's made out of materially. It's just, it's just uncomfortable.
And it's, it's, somebody just said it's really expensive. So I, this is exactly what I wanted
it for. Everything is huge now. Yeah. And now is it like the best chair in the world? No. I mean,
I want to say this was, I mean, it wasn't cheap, cheap, cheap. I mean, it was still,
it was like, I think a couple hundred bucks, a hundred something bucks, I think.
But you get a chair that's like a nice chair like this. You might have to spend 500 to a thousand
dollars, which is, I just, I got one coming. That's going to be a little bit better, but
yeah. Some of these chairs are like over five plus a hundred thousand, 100, 100, not 100,000,
5,000 to like, I've seen chairs that are 5,000. You know, those big, they almost look like,
okay. You know, the chairs look like cigars. They look like gigantic cigars. It's all like
the only way I can describe it. The cigar chair. It's like this high off the ground and this wide.
And it looks like a cigar. Those things are more than one to $2,000 at least.
Yeah. The Mr. Green's chair. Exactly.
I think I don't need to, is there any more? There's an upgrade.
I'll do it later. Okay. So I can pull shields away now, but yeah, I want to say I'll be in
this chair for the next few streams, maybe the next two or three streams, but I did,
there is another one that I want, that I want to get. That's a little more elaborate.
That will help with my legs, but this is going to just kind of sit in the corner over here and
just be a chair. So this whole setup is temporary. You'll see some changes in the next few weeks.
I'm excited for it. Auto can sleep in it. Yeah. This would, this would be like a nice
little auto chair probably. Although it'd be hard for him to get up on top of it.
It'd be hard for him to get in and lie down on it. I'd have to pick him up and he might be able
to sit with me in the other one. That'd be kind of cute. Is he doing all right? Yeah, he's doing
great. He's doing wonderful. Oh, you bet. You better believe there'll be, I'll be hanging out
here with him sitting either right on my lap or right because the other chair I'm getting is a
lot bigger. They'd be right in the face. It's not quite a cigar chair, but it's a little bit wider
than this one. Well, I got the treasure I wanted. Where is it? Oh, it's hanging. Alrighty. We need
to go down there. Wait, I could climb up. Yeah. Wait a minute. Is it worth getting down and is
that open? I need a red robe. I actually thought about streaming with a robot and that'd be fun.
Shit. I can't open this. Okay. I gotta, I gotta lock in here. How did I even get back up here?
I'm just kind of talking. All right. I want to go this way. Yeah. You look like Hugh Hefner.
Please do one grapple melee. Yeah. I don't know. If it's just melee from a distance,
it doesn't seem to be working unless it's a different button combination that I'm not doing.
Where are you? You're gonna make me eat my egg or my fish or whatever it is.
You need to be far away and then hit it. I'll try it again, but I feel like I've been
too far away almost. Can I sneak in here? Remember guys, if there's not a button on the screen,
he can't see it and he won't know. Well, that's not true because even if there is a button on the
screen that says rotate with Q and E, I apparently won't see that either. So I'm kind of just lost
regardless. So I don't know if I can be helped. Oh, I'm so concerned about that person.
Holy shit. That was cool. That dude over there. That wasn't that far. That wasn't far away.
This person over here is, how are they still confused? Why are they not breaking out?
Oh, thank God. He took like two. Yeah. Why did he die so quickly? He died incredibly fast.
Was it the flashbang? The gun is just so upgraded. Then I'm start using it more often.
Did I get everything? Maybe. Make some more ammo. I think I can do it. Yeah. He just melted when I
shot him with this like two times. That was awesome. I think it's filthy. Use the charm for
extra SMG ammo. I think I have it on. Isn't it on? I think that's it right there. Cool chair.
It is a cool chair. It doesn't matter where it's from. It's a cool chair. 35,000. All right. What
do I want to do here? I want that. So I'm going to sell. Oh, well, there you go.
A deal well struck. Fool stranger. Melee crit. That sounds good. Now going for some mayhem,
eh? What if it is from target? Yeah, it doesn't matter. Chair is a chair. And if it's a decent
chair, it's a decent chair. Honestly, even when the new chair, when I get the new one,
who knows? I might sit in the new one and go, put me back in the other one.
It's what if it's not the same? What if I really just like this one?
Here's the second. We possibly save it again. Current one looks comfy. It is. It just does
exactly what I want it to do. Be a chair that can swivel. It can rock. It's fairly comfortable.
I will. Okay. I will say the material, this material is a little grainy. It's a little
rough, but it's not bad. It's fine. It's comfortable. No foot rest. No.
What is a man without his baby chair? True. It's a real man-sized chair. Let's kill this
guy once and for all. Definitely got him. What? The thing crashed from the ceiling,
landed right on his head. It didn't kill him? That would have killed any man or living being
or thing. Oh God. Oh, let go. Let go. Let go. Oh, not yet. Okay. Now I take it. Oh, that hurts.
This gun is so unbelievable. I could make the difficulty harder if I wanted to.
Holy shit. This thing is maxed out. Well, I'm still going to use it. Give me all the
stuff first before I lose access to all of it. You got to shoot it in the, in the orange goo.
Ouch. I think I got all the stuff. Oh, okay. This would be it. Almost out of bullets. One more time
maybe. Yeah, that's it. I thought I got, oh, that cure does not work currently. Don't tell me I'm
not good at a game when I did. Look what I just did. That's like one, two, three. Like, holy shit,
dude. Yeah. I mean, I'm seeing like a lot of people saying like, holy shit. I actually like,
I had it wrong. He's like really fucking good. I, sometimes I like to prove people wrong.
I like this area. The amber Louise, where is it? He's weird. Mushrooms.
Ada does not give a, Ada does not give a heck. Yeah, I know. It's part of her character.
Close one. Yeah. Thanks for that. You guys keeping me honest for it. I don't want to say
right. I don't want to say that.
Yeah. No, I'm just, I didn't say anything. Mom, are you reading chat Leon? There's only time to
say this once. They said it was a joke. If you hurry. Wait, if my mom was watching, wouldn't
she see the face cam? She would see the face cam. Sorry, ma. Okay. Uh, one or what? Two chapters
left. Okay. The last chapter is probably a runaway from the big, scary monster. So there's
probably one real chapter remaining, but it's all good. I'm ready to go. Let's do it. I would,
that was really lazy. I just needed to walk two more steps. That was okay. Storm trooper aim. I
got it in two hits. All right. Wait a minute. Trying to do the grapple hook thing. End up
running at them and not far enough. Really? How do you stagger from that far away? Okay. Well,
I have to get down there fast. Can I grapple hook down there? I'm just gonna wait for them to get
up here. Let's kill them. Then go grapple gun, melee attack type. Why is this showing me a
controller? But it's an F already bound to cause I changed the controls to have. Okay. So here's
what's happening. So I rebound my melee to thumb button. I thought it was telling me just to hit
the melee button, not F like, Oh, Hey, hit F, but also hit thumb button because that's what you
haven't found to because sometimes it like changes. Yeah. Okay. Well it's a, I thought they were the
same button. Okay. Let's go now. Turn it again. I collected the money. Yeah. For some reason I
thought it was just melee from far away. And even though I did see F, F to me was the same
binding of the same key, which is thumb button. So that's on me. I don't even need it.
What do I do with my money now?
I think I was going to buy gunpowder because come on, I'll buy gunpowder.
And soon. Well, it's good work. If I do say so myself, I can do that too.
A deal. Well struck. Uh, attack speed by one and a half times for the knife tuned weapon can make
up for a lack of skill friend dazzled. I like durability more. Our craftsmanship demands.
Ruby's all rubbish. It makes no difference. The price is going to be for generators.
So I'm going to keep the scope. There's some things money. An interesting choice.
I'll keep a lookout as well. All right. Welcome stranger. What can I do you for a deal? Well,
Hey, there you are. Hey, older Billy on the knife. Thank you. Equip your charm.
Didn't I? I think I had it right. Do check out my welcome. Life needs care every once in a while.
It's not on there. Welcome. Isn't that it right there? Where's that screen to equip stuff?
Like, how do I get to that menu screen? Oh, it's typewriter beat three novice star doors,
giant insects. I'll try. Yeah, that's on Nova star doors. It was a really bad dry. I'll say,
okay. This way. And then treasure. And then down that way. Don't be spotted. I upgraded the knife.
Might as well use it. Saved ammo. All right, let's try it. How do I do it? Got it. Treasure
is straight through here. Cool. Backflip flip. Cool. Flip. You suck. Oh shit. I ain't dealing
with that. Treasure up there. I'm going to play Starfield. I couldn't really get into it. I was
never a big Bethesda game player. Didn't really get into it. All right, we're down. And then,
okay, let's do this first. Although to be fair though, I never really loved games where
it's just a lot of dialogue options and dialogue options that really just it's,
Hey, here's like four things. You can just talk to this person. I never was a big fan of it.
It always kind of just leads to the same thing. Now Baldur's Gate has dialogue options, but
I feel like I'm invested in my character a little more somehow. I feel like it actually means
things. And somebody just said sorcery too, but a lot of stuff you do in sorcery, like has immediate
consequences. I feel like a lot of times in the games where you pick a lot of dialogue options,
it's just like, Hey, you can kind of talk to this person however you want. It doesn't really
necessarily matter too much, but like you can just have a conversation in the way that you would want
to. Like that's cool, but never really did it for me. Except one randomly will insult them. Yeah.
All right. I am going to get crushed by one of these and I'm not careful. I didn't get the
treasure. Did I miss my opportunity to get it? I don't think I can get back up. Oh, there it is.
Dialogue actually matters in Baldur's Gate 3. Oh yeah, it really does. Baldur's Gate,
the consequences are like sorcery. And obviously my attention span is pretty low already. So if
there's not immediate stakes on something, I kind of lose interest, which is like, Hey, talk to this
person. You need to go figure this out. It's like, Oh, okay, cool. And it's like, Oh, by the way,
you're gonna, you can sit here for a while and just talk. It doesn't really mean anything,
but you can do it. I always just skip it completely. You piece of shit. Where is it?
Oh, it's right there. I thought I was not even close guys. I thought I was naughty. I thought
I was in a perfect safe zone. Holy shit. I may have dumped my pants a little. I think I may have
dumped the chair. Okay. What the hell? Now I got to go all the way around. He's having another
brownout. Just don't, don't use any of these for thumbnails. I know you want to. Don't use
something else. Use me going like this. Okay. Try it again. Yeah, it sucks. It's a long run,
isn't it? Yeah. I feel, I can hear you're out of breath. Don't have the strength to attack,
do you? I was going to give you a minute. It's a long ass run. Now go back the way we came.
I can actually go up here, can't I? Let's not make the same mistake twice. I made the same
mistake twice. If those of you keeping score at home on your scoreboard, we're good. Who shot that?
Do it. And you missed completely. And now you got your leg hit. What was that all about? I got a
lot of herbs. I don't actually stop using my, um, my rifle because of the generators. How do I pull
it off? It looked like I had it. There we go. You're alive. I thought you were dead. Okay. Now
what? Into the ancient Chantry. I hear, I hear Laurel, to be honest. Do not shoot that. Grapple
melee doesn't make any sense. Why wouldn't they just come towards the player? Kind of like a
scorpion. Yeah. Well, I think, yeah. Unless they weigh a thousand pounds. It's just so unrealistic.
I'm surprised we're still in chapter five. I figured we would've got out of it by now.
Somebody told Leon that that hat gives him like plus 20% speed. And they were just lying to him.
That's the only reason why he's got it on. And Mr. Kennedy, why do you have that stupid hat on?
I don't think it's stupid, but it's stupid for the occasion. You're an idiot. It gives me plus
5% damage. Krauser has possession of the Amber. Don't ever do that voice again. Keep the client
happy. Sorry. Oh, do you? Okay. There's a show that is a scorn like, have you guys ever seen
Ballmasters Adult Swim? They do the scorn randomly throughout that show. You just hear
Ballmasters. They'll be in the middle of a game and it's like, Oh, big play happens. Ballmasters.
It's they do scorn. I was like, Holy shit. That's awesome. They actually,
it's actually a scorn. Like I've been waiting for somebody to do that for years. And I guess
somebody did it. That's a crazy show, by the way. That show is very alive. There's a lot happening
in that show. You didn't even play scorn. You smoking crack? Stop it. This is a great setup.
A motorcycle. It's a boat, dude. I need to eat a fucking jar of peanut butter after this. I thought
he took off on a motorcycle. God. I just hear like, Oh dude, cool. I want to see what like
fucking sick variety he's got. Looking for something? Chapter complete. Why peanut butter?
It's got protein and good fats and all that stuff. Peanut butter or hummus. Eat them both.
Not at the same time, but the hat flies off and he's just like, Oh shit. You look like you've got
something to say. I have something to ask you, but I don't think I'll get a straight answer.
Fucking stinks in that hat. Just telling you. Raccoon City. He's been wearing it for like six
days. The world changed. You try to save one person, a hundred others die. I guess I changed
too. You? Leon S. Kennedy. You haven't changed. You just think you have. So here's my question.
Have you changed Ada or are you just trying to use me again? What do you think? We're here.
Don't think too hard, handsome. See you later. Story of my life. All right. See you later,
Leon. Look at the improv show. You're about to go act in. Good one. Yes. Yes. That was a good
one. I think it was too. That one stinks. What's your opinion? I don't even have this rifle.
Whose blood are you here for this time? Mine or Sadler's? That all depends on you.
That's a sick weapon too. I don't even have it. Change of plans. Of course.
I wish I could put them all in that fucking hat. Friend's going to be enough. Interesting.
Okay. I'll do it. But cost you extra. Wise decision. Send you the new coordinates.
And remember, I do not like waiting. I know. I was going to say dialogue options.
So just get right to the point. God damn it. I've got a ways to go.
Head for the comms facility. Okay. So this is the island, right? Yeah. Okay. Treasures. Nice.
That just opened. Okay. You don't have to fight. Oh, Leon fights him, right? Crystal ore.
Stab him. Stab him. Stab him. Stab him. Why are you reloading the guns? Too close. We're good.
You're going to S plus all characters on perks? Uh, no, I did S plus on a few places and a few
people. Um, I wouldn't do that tonight though. I'm going to get to the end of the game and probably
call it. And then I think Monday is the next time I'm going to be streaming. Monday I might be in a
new setup. Well, an upgraded version of the one you see right now. I want to play party animals
again. I think stir wants to play it too. I also asked Vinny if he wanted to play as well. So we'll
probably get a crew together, play a little bit of party animals. That's fun. Well, okay. Did I
get everything from this room? No, there is a treasure hanging right here. Oh, I missed the
amp. Oh, whatever. Be just up ahead, but getting through won't be Ada and Wesker were added to
marks. Ooh, Wesker was fun. Wesker was a Magnum, right? Welcome came into some other bits and bobs
too. Why not try your hand running speed? That's kind of cold. All right. Do I, I think I want
flash grenades. Flash grenades are the best from what I remember, especially in the end, or should
I do? I don't know. Or do I just upgrade the hell out of the knife tuned weapon can make up for a
lack of skill. Why not try that on? That's about 40,000 for one and a half times attack speed.
I've never done that before. So maybe I could try it. Ruby's all rubbish. It makes no difference.
The price. Well, that's our choice to make. There's some things money. I'm going to hold
on to everything else. Anything else I can help you with 40,000. It's okay for now.
Check out my wares again. Great rifles. Probably the best at this point. Yeah. I mean,
there's a whole, I got one more chapter for this. So I want some max health, but it's sell those.
I'm not going to use them. These are so expensive.
A deal. Well, pleasant. And maybe I will just buy the rocket launcher
have like a super explosive thing at the end. All right. Handgun ammo is starting to get a
little low. You're going to regret that bolt action with the regenerators. That's why I'm
holding on to the rifle because, Oh my goodness. Bebop. No rock steady. I forget which one
hit me right in the forehead. Oh, kill him. Please. Another one. Where is he?
Oh, he's right behind me. He's not. Oh my God. Oh, that was all explosive bolts.
He just unloaded an entire magazine of rusty bolts. Hey, somebody said I looked rusty.
So I said, rusty bolts while I was saying explosive bolts, I saved it, right? Did I
write that? Did I screw that up? Yeah, we're good. Okay. Well that was kind of crazy.
Try it again. I think it's so good. All right. I got to go this way now. All right. I'm going
to blow you up when you land. All right. Where is he? Oh shit. Okay. You're dead. Collect everything.
Okay. This bunch of money over there. He's actually playing. I thought he just talks.
Well, we know what happens when I just talk. I, uh, I don't know that. I don't know Q and E rotate
a puzzle. And I turned my head upside down to see the thing right side up. Oh, look at how,
look at how pretty this is. This is like a, it's like Christmas. Somebody did all this.
Look at that. Is it for me? All the decorations. That's so cute. Thanks for me. Wait, treasure.
I should start using the knife more often. I think that's it. And yes.
Wait, why doesn't Ash, why doesn't Ashley have different clothes on?
If he's dressed like such an idiot. Wouldn't I have had her dressed in some
outfit too? I think she had sunglasses on.
Here comes the regenerators. Worst thing ever. Okay. I need to make sure I use that very well.
So we're going to the left. No we're not.
Sell two ornate beetles. There's one hidden in dissection in facility one.
And somebody stole the other.
Oh, just realized how much shit he has in his pockets.
All right. How much is the rocket launcher? 80. I'm going to hold. Hold my money.
Doing that for the regenerators only. What has he got in his pockets?
It's kinds of stuff. I need to get to the comms facility. It needs some power though.
What does he, what's in his pockets? I'm available. All right. Regenerators. I'm ready.
Don't have an automatic door. Yeah. The parasites watch out. They regenerate in.
Definitely. But it's okay. I'm hiding. Holy shit. Oh, a beetle. I'm not messing around.
Treasure in here? Where is it? Above? Hmm. No, nevermind. Okay. I am ready.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa. They run. They run. They run. It's running at me.
The book was way better. Is that back? It is. She played Venga bus, but really faded.
Like she's hearing Leon listen to it in the other room. I feel like that's the thing for post.
That's funny though. I'll give you, I'm going to give you a plus two for that one.
All right. Fine. That's fun. I'm doing it. Venga boys. You guys hear something?
Ow. Coming from the wall. It sounds like that's coming from below my feet.
This just sounds like it's coming out of her air pods. I just want to do this for a second.
Like, dude, he's fucking somebody. He's sleeping. Somebody wake him up.
Oh my God, man. I'm playing Resident Evil all fucking day. I'm tired, man,
but I got a playlist going. I sorry. I just wanted to make sure that
you had to deal with the muted audio in the VOD as well. Okay. Where are we going?
No, I got to go into the freezer. There is. That was bound to happen.
What the fuck? Oh goodness. I want that beetle. Jeez. Okay. I want that other beetle.
Hmm. Blood. What was this thing? Oh, there it is. Okay. I got both beetles.
Okay. Very cool. Now I got to get back down here. Science, math, English, reading,
arithmetic. He's in here somewhere. I don't know where though. Rotisserie chickens.
Why is there a rotisserie chicken down here in the, wait, okay. This is like the kitchen, I guess.
Wait, holy shit. Damn it. It just sounds like when Otto is sleeping.
I hit him. I didn't hit him in one parasite. What the fuck are you talking about? What the hell?
Why can I not hit this one? This one's been so finicky. That was very creepy.
Oh, you can't come through here. Would you guys rather fight one regenerator
with a grenade or fight two 100 duck-sized horses?
Oh, you motherfucker. Where are you? I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't know. I don't
know. I don't know. I don't know. I mean, I don't know. How big is the grenade? First of all,
and do the duck-sized horses, do they, um, are they angry? Or that's a hard question.
Where is he now? That's the sound I would imagine that a big duck-sized horse would
make. So if they're going to make sounds like that, then boy, oh boy, I would want to be really
prepared for them because that's, that's tricky because they might get really loud in your ears
and die already. You're going to fall back in the recliner. Yeah. Like that'd be kind of funny
one day if I just threw back till I have like my both my feet be in the air. All right. Well,
that is why I did that. So I'm good now. It's getting late. Do I, um, is chapter seven really
just kind of an epilogue like fight the boss chapter or is it long? Pretty short. Yeah. Yeah.
We'll finish it. I imagine I'm getting close to the end of this chapter soon. I need to craft
some shit. Okay. Unlocked. That's the, where the power is. I got to put, oh wait, power.
They turn the beetles in, gets things done. Got a selection of good things on sale.
Stranger, your valuables won't do you much. Well,
10 spinals. Damn. All right. So what can I do now? We're getting kind of close to the end.
I can do this. I got pressures that I have on. Ooh, this would be good. Triple.
Thank you. Welcome. What can I interest you in? I'll buy it at a high price.
All right. One and a half times the tax speed. I feel like, is that really that big of a deal
to suit your specific needs? I'm not sure. I really want to spend the money on that.
Yeah. Striker charm. I could buy the rocket launcher and just store it.
Yeah, that's what I'm doing. All yours, stranger. Got a selection. Now.
Just hold on to it. Welcome. Can I buy rockets? Please have this in stock, stranger.
Um, I should probably just do some upgrades to this. Just a handgun. It's a one-time use. All
right. Maybe I just hold the money. Work. If I do say so myself. I want this information. Yeah.
Ruby's all rubbish. She makes no difference. Didn't I get a bunch of those arrows?
Blast arrows? That's our choice. Did I already sell them? I'll hold the money. Thank you.
Do check out my wares again soon. Get a TV dinner table. I actually think I'm probably
going to have one. Well, let's do it. I'm going to put it in. There are four people
fighting in the chat right now. Don't tell them stop. There should be able to get out now.
I'm going to have to pee one more time for the finale. So I will do that after this.
Not exactly covert, but it'll have to do.
Highly sensitive antenna array on the Island is finally complete.
Browser. Real bastard, isn't it?
Ow, excuse me. Good one. Well, this isn't good.
You suck at the gun. Run it back for a second. I don't think I missed one shot that whole ride.
My favorite carnival. Oh, let's just go ahead and take care of that right now.
Giant insects. I can't just destroy them or something. Hello.
I'm going to make a bunch of handgun ammo.
And I'm going to upgrade the handgun. I'm going to get the Punisher and I'm going to upgrade it.
You'll get some bang for your buck. I guarantee it. That's a good idea. The red nine is cool,
but I want to be able to go fast. I did the red nine in the last playthrough. Let's do Punisher.
Let's go like this. This kind of work is about finesse,
straight little bit goes a long way. You see anything pleasant travels.
Where is it? Is it equipped? What am I doing wrong here? Oh, OK. I was like, wait,
I want rate of fire now. Let's go. This is going to be fun. A radio tower. That's where I need to
go. Ada, you can see it from here. Why did you need to put the glasses on? Although a few hours
ago everyone was sitting there going, how the fuck does he not see this? How can he not see
that? He can like, you know, the shields and shit. Ada, actually, you know what? I take that back.
I take it back. I get it. I take it back. I didn't see it either. All right. Why are you running so
slow? I'm still alive. What the fuck? I wanted the money. I wanted the money so bad. A radio tower.
I thought I was in reach. I probably turn them off and can just come back out here.
Really? Really? Aim. He's got two. Was he double fisting Molotov cocktails?
OK, just take. What did I say? Is he like holding both in two fists like this?
All right. There's a big, scary guy over here. All right. I'm not doing that.
I'm glad I turned around. Holy shit. Oh, my God. Turn this shit off. I'm not going to blow
these up yet. It's probably a big guy that comes out. It's a full baseball swing. One of three
bug buster. Oh, OK. Am I at max help? I think so. All right. There's two more to turn off,
so I'm going to go over here. Can I go through this hole? No. All right. So you can turn it
out of the way. Yeah. No. Turn it, turn it, turn it, turn it, turn it. Quick, quick, quick,
quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick. Come on, come on, come on. Go, go, go, go,
go, go, go, go. Oh, you got to be fucking kidding me. We're good. Standing with a very large
backpack on what it's like running. I got to conserve my ammo in the machine gun. All right.
Now, how does that help me? Oh, shit. Thanks. More across the bridge. All right. Can I get
get these up I'm being very lazy right now and it's stupid but whatever okay
okay let me reload the other weapons it's not quite safe to go out there I
could have killed somebody wait a minute did I did I not killed the gunman not
over there I fuck it up I think I'm gonna screw this up
spring me all the way back here and I've is lasers are aiming at me take the
other bunker but I jumped down that didn't I don't think I can I get back
over there without getting killed by the lasers hold on let me go over here okay
alright there we go that does it now the question is wait can I go across here I
definitely can but let me go get all the items free stuff only 600 that's all
that was over there two gunpowders and 600 bucks to disable both machine guns
no it's got to be like a secret in here yeah gold bar a large gold bar thank you
I'm gonna say okay if I can I go across this I'm right dead
fuck it I'm going that's all of them yay yay why would they keep those barrels
in there or fuel what do you think they get the fuel Ada you are strong holy
smokes my god this is ridiculous there's more the worst things I've ever seen in
my entire life yeah cut cut cut Larry the booms in the fucking shot again cut
except get back to one on man I was like I was a good take don't ever eat a bag
of potato chips before you put in a fucking secret code alright guys I'm
just imagining this it was somebody being like yeah coming in yep I had a
bunch of like fried chicken for dinner research okay
there's that he's funny tonight it's been a wide range of emotions tonight I
will say I just break this the effects of the amber are greater than anything
I could have imagined Martin Nico was once a fragile uncontrollable test
subject impervious to conventional weapons now for the bad news it may be
stronger but it's a mental capacity has not improved at all right so I can't
hurt whatever this is with regular weapons this treasures in here wait a
minute I'm just gonna blow through this ceiling or what okay let's go oh you
can't hurt with regular weapons I gotta go I think I've put steam on him what
the heck just don't even look just go right above me oh my goodness oh my
goodness
Darth Vader's gonna come down this hallway and start swinging his fucking
axe made out of stiff energy red stiff crystal weaponry oh my god no no no no
no cancel cancel cancel how do I remove it I don't remove it I'm really glad
that the monsters are sitting behind me like yeah but this doesn't open oh okay
we should be working together of course not though oh yeah that's gonna be worth
millions okay hey sadly came to me it's gonna be a long night okay this is where
it's gonna get I imagine this is probably a cutscene boss because I
can't hurt it with my guns so it's probably a cutscene boss nothing else to
do let's just go I was trying to get it to kill me anyways he's playing on the
difficulty that you can't fail this is it how to connect the device that was
really easy I just pressed three buttons I just picked random ones I'm really
glad cuz there's 6,000 buttons here I'm glad that the combination of six that I
put in a row were to disable the entire security system what a terrible dogshit
system that is by the way I feel like you could accidentally turn off all
security including the president's daughter won't that make things harder
for you there's no room for half measures the weak exist to serve the
strong no have to make bring me the amber no after I've arranged a way for
you to get back to the island copy that on it now Louise what was it that you
said again you should have known by now whisker I don't always play by your
rules okay I'm done here thank God they got
Windows Defender prevent all that all right where's the monster let's go he's
got jokes tonight they're just coming out one two three four five turn the
lasers on mm-hmm I'm gonna laugh my ass off imagine he did acrobatic dives and
shit through this working Jesus crazy it looks like we're doing it together see
I can proceed see see there's a CEO P oh sorry what's the next one
uh it's it's shit shit hey I don't have a fucking computer I don't have a
keyboard I don't have a keyboard oh no that was yeah that was pretty good now
Sadler they don't go that fast if she's not out of a cannon it wasn't even on a
jet ski imagine turn it on a jet ski and just
pressing the gas and you're just out of a cannon all right let's do it
thanks for staying up late look quite a few people here just chillin
you go pee uh yeah I will after this cutscene how much longer will the stream
be I'm about to beat the game so when that ends the stream ends
I'll meet him there okay just going wait stop no imagine this probably the
final time I'll see you so let's just upgrade everything by everything okay I
can do three but two and oh wait I think I actually can buy it can I I actually
purchase it damn it oh well do I have I'm at the end of the game it doesn't
really matter who cares I was gonna sell everything oh yeah I'll be right
back be and then we'll finish the game oh no I have returned guys ready to
finish this up let's finish this up so might as well just buy everything I can
stocking up while you can this is maxed out I'm gonna shoot the rocket launcher
anyways I just give her to all this stuff right why not much scope and
everything right okay I have the rocket launcher yeah I do it'll be a 60 year
old that collects knives that's a good one that's a good one all right time to
end the game holy shit that looks awful Wow maybe I will see him again I'm still
getting money wait what the fuck how's your hair like that as that because it
is oh do not know you reload I don't very much health I'll hold it for now
yeah he's still alive all right they've been doing all right yeah somebody asked
earlier they said it this is seven hours this is abnormal the last six months or
so it's part of the reason to be in this chair so much better now the frequency of
the streams is gonna stay the same right but I mean that this is not me telling you that
oh every stream is gonna be like seven to ten hours now that no no no it's just I'm
just much more comfortable than I was before and it's gonna improve it's gonna get better
I thought there was a stake when it first showed up on the screen but yeah my intention
is still you know slow it down and everything but I wanted to make sure this last kind of
arc you want to call it that was a lot more comfortable because I can sit here for whenever
I feel like it exactly what I'm doing right now it's like 12 15 at night just kind of here
oh I am out of everything what is going on why am I playing like Call of Duty world at war what
happened oh I sold the fucking scope wait treasure but it doesn't really matter we're done but I just
see the thing on the map and I want to go look at it and get it I'm glad I did it's a big one what
is it staff of royalty okay end of career voice hey I'm here right now I plan on staying here
instead of much reduced capacity like we talked about before but we don't have to we don't have
to talk about that we're playing Resident Evil with we don't have to talk about that hey remember
when I couldn't flip the fucking puzzle bring that up okay I hear it where is it use the rocket
launcher right now I have one shot in this I don't want to just use it on a regular guy that
just opens the door up I don't know the door could have been made of I don't know why I'm
doing this why am I doing why am I conducting an orchestra hat that's what happened control come
in I have the package this is gonna be hard to explain that customs well done
evacuate immediately understood he dies instantly he didn't get to say his fucking line restart now
no I know he's still alive why that was not the end he's still alive yeah he comes back and he's
like it's me and I yeah cuz we're up here I remember this I definitely should not have used
the rocket launcher there for whatever oh that was funny I don't even know what that boss fights
like should I just actually play it yeah that's all that matters is I won this right I wish I
had a second round obtain a powerful weapon okay I got the shiny thing on the ground first all
right let's go you're doing great down there Leon ooh a rocket launcher I wish I had one of those
oh shit I do have to hurry just go go go what what am I doing just run no no what is that what
is that what is that what is it that was a crazy explosion what are you doing shoot it oh my god
dude what are you doing I thought that was a red barrel ain't gonna shoot me a blank oh
that's right so in this playthrough then who is a to shoot or does Leon shoot it it's Leon
definitely they wouldn't retcon the whole game okay it's a it's a it's a big one not in my
inventory it's just it's it's a cutscene I get it what are these bugs even doing here still
surprise it oh Ashley oh yeah no don't throw a grenade over there you got two minutes with
seconds to spare I feel like that would explode wouldn't it just blow up
nothing personally on the reason I had an arrangement don't worry I'll take good care
of it right here it is just so calm this collective is where we go our separate ways
look at the end of this she gets back I see goes into her house her apartment whoever grabs
the pillow holds it here and just fucking screams hello it's Wesker it's my stuff where's
my kyber crystal my lightsaber it's a yellow one my favorite patch me through yellow means
that you're intelligent and not evil and smart I've obtained the amber it's what all the nerds
want is their lightsabers that are purple just one question what are you planning to do with
this do not pay you to ask questions I wanted a yellow lightsaber no is a new dawn is breaking
self-report a hundred will give their lives so that just one may live expediting that change
so we're talking millions of casualties billions how ambitious we're changing course now Wesker
why like wrong okay that's good it's really fun but it was at seven hours and a half that
well that's you know take a like hour and 45 minutes away from the puzzles that are good
but it's total game time five hours five now that was good you're gonna play city skylines
too oh yeah absolutely I'll say for sure post credits did you play Mortal Kombat just for a
little bit I tried it out for a few hours I'm just not very good at fighting games fighting
games are really fun to watch but they're not really fun to play for me fighting games are
kind of like puzzle games in my brain a series of very specific actions have to happen in a very
specific order or you lose real-time puzzle games yeah isn't that every video game um well very
specific actions in the context of you know what I mean when I say that you have to do a very
specific set of actions to be able to do these moves and to be able to predict what your opponent
will do this is every video game I saw a lot of trues though you guys know what I mean we're gonna
read between the lines here real okay so in a puzzle game well you can play a lot of games in
different ways like I can I can press W and then let go and I'll be fine right like if I just walk
forward in a fighting game and stop moving it's over I'm gonna get comboed and I'm gonna get
together I'm dead you have to string together a very specific set of actions in a row it's
there's no time for you to stop you can't just stop playing you can't just oh I'm gonna go in
my inventory for a minute nope if you're not doing it down forward slash B walk jump down
forward B jump back down forward slash B it's like a rhythm game it's like a puzzle rhythm game you
have to really be paying attention every single millisecond of the time in action everything in a
row and I don't know I kind of like to be able to blink a few times and not worry about it oh
I thought this is the post-credits for like six hours I spent an hour and 25 minutes doing
nothing I love watching fighting games I like watching people play them but the series of very
specific actions in a row I can't do did he see that wait he got to see that that rating how long
it took for me to play the game he's watching my stream right now ah he's fucking terrible B six
hours of game time too I would have figured out that puzzle really quickly he's just watching
he's just chatting in my chat right now being mean to me when I had a fucking gas leak in my
room I don't know why I was so bad at that no oh yeah defiance changes nothing besides we have
all we continue as planned soon son was set on the age of man I feel like if Wesker just took a
bath he would kind of not give a shit about this anymore a big bubble bath with an iPad I feel like
you'd be like you know what actually I'm gonna settle down I'm just gonna relax now don't ever
underestimate what can be solved in a bath okay serious I will try somebody said just even open
it I'm not gonna try or play but I'll just hop in and check it out the mercenaries I got my points
costume unlocked lots of costumes my goodness what is by the helicopter guy he's in he's in
the movie for five minutes oh no no okay it's a model I should wait I want to go back where do I
do the what do I do the outfits out campaign only okay okay we're gonna go with a rank or above as
Ada I think I can get that pretty quickly green needle I just want to see Wesker because I'm
probably not gonna play this again anytime soon really maybe I played in my kind of off time but
what do I need for a let's get to a and I oh no it's already over that's not what is mayhem a
motor just like good aiming or just when it kills it when it headshot kills it's like instant reloads
kind of like Leon's seems pretty good seems pretty good I don't lose the combo all right
incoming where is he where are you it is good it is really fun to play that's a molotov don't lose
the combo I'm just gonna let the timer now I'll have a oh where is he whoa still alive no he's
right oh no bad I'm gonna get out of the way oh shit don't throw that shit at me right now all
right I definitely have a I am in trouble but I should be oh I gotta heal uh I'll keep it going
might as well oh I guess oh shit careful here I need to get the fuck out of the way all right
326 wow wow wow oh no I got stuck on that guy the guy in front of me was just kind of weirdly
in the way I think that's a yeah I'll take a nice that's fine all right Wesker and new stage oh
there's docs all right let's play Wesker so what does he got he's got the Magnum he's got the
seven okay that's that's goofy don't can I turn into a monster or something what about the other
gun yeah it's one of these let me see he actually probably is the most fun to play because the
Magnum all right will you stop that's cool come on through guns kind of slow but it's still fun
all right mayhem mode what is it oh yeah he does melee attacks all right that's awesome where's
yeah okay that might be it Jesus let's flip that guy off holy shit I just got a lot of people there
these bugs are flying around okay I get a better vantage point in this the melee is amazing you
shithead whoa oh I'm stuck on something in the tunnel oh god I just kicked this guy's ass he
dead I don't think he I think he's still alive oh no get out get out get out I'm stuck in here
oh bad bad bad very bad very bad very bad I'm dead okay I need help oh I'm freezing up any
help oh too bad okay that was fun he's cool that's still an ass all right everybody it is late thanks
for watching thanks for hanging out I'll see you guys on Monday for party animals with stir and
maybe Vinny and then maybe one or two others maybe we'll cycle some people in and out thanks
for watching uh somebody said to give a rating to separate ways I kind of think it's just part of
Resident Evil 4 which is a 9.5 to me it's just another few chapters extended onto the game
Resident Evil 4 is a great game it's just a remake of that it was a little different though I don't
remember a lot of those encounters in separate ways did I even I don't know if I played second
boys maybe I did do you like puzzles well the problem is I get like in a feedback loop where I
get stuck on something and then I try to go as fast I can to fix it and then it makes it even
worse but I was fine it was fine I can just be kind of a dummy sometimes but it's okay we have
our weaknesses and one of my weaknesses is shooting at shields on a ball in the correct
order lies if he is my favorite souls like that isn't from software damn saw X was really good
too damn okay I'm getting some pretty good recommendations right now of things I thought
I might want to do but yeah I'll see you guys Monday thanks for watching it's the first almost
eight hour stream in a long time it's not gonna be the norm but it is possible see you guys on
Monday take care all your mother you know what to do see you soon