Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a fistful of frags gameplay commentary.
It's been a while since you've seen fistful of frags on this channel, and there's no real
reason in particular for that. Sometimes you put a game away and you come back to it months later.
Sometimes you put a game away for potentially years, which I did with TF2. I stopped playing
TF2 back in like 2008 for like 12 months. You take breaks, point is, you take breaks,
you come back to games, and you go, well, you know, I forgot about this game. This game's
fucking sick. Yeah, well, that's what happened. I'm playing Fistful of Frags again. Here's a new
map, I believe. It's one of the new maps that's currently in circulation. It's a train. This is
all about the trains in Fistful of Frags, apparently. A lot of these maps, the newer
ones seem to have trains on them, but that's regardless of the point. You probably saw the
title and you're wondering what the hell this title means. Were you writing a book now? You
wanted to make a game company first. Now you want to write a book and then what you would do. Next
thing I'm going to want to be like an astronaut. I'm going to be like, gosh, hey, you know what?
Today's video, we're going to talk about how I want to be a fucking astronaut. And I'm going
to go up in the airplane. We're going to go flying up into outer space and I'm going to meet some
Martians and I'm going to start a family up there on Mars. No, but this is something I'm actually
doing right now. I'm in the process of doing, I'm writing a book. Yes, I'm writing a book. I'm an
ebook. Let's make that really clear. This is not going to be a published book by anybody.
You're not going to see this on store shelves at Barnes and Noble. There's not going to be an image
of me on the cover in a three-piece suit with my arm resting on a desk, smiling a giant white toothy
smile. And it's saying like, how to manage your finances with German nine eight five. It's just,
it's going to be something I'm doing for fun. And it's a choose your own adventure book.
I got really inspired recently by playing that game sorcery. That was a choose your own adventure
book. I'm sure a lot of you guys remember me talking how into what I was and how cool it was,
how I wished more people would be porting over game books. And then Inkle, the company that made
that game sorcery. Oh, well, they ported that game sorcery over to iOS and Android and shit.
They came up with this engine. There is an engine that they came up with for you to write your own
choose your own adventure books. So I saw that and I said, holy shit, are you kidding me? This is
awesome. I got to give this a try. I've got to at least try to do this. And yes, I know that there
are other resources and other places where you can write, choose your own adventure novels and
stuff. But this, I just knew the company Inkle. I played all their games and it looked really easy
to use. There's a, the tutorial was very, very simple. And I just started, I started writing
and I already have like probably like at least a few hundred words written so far. I don't know
what the timeframe will be on this. I can't just be telling you, oh yeah, well guys in three months,
I'm going to be having 5,000 pages done. I don't know the length. I don't even know the subject
matter. All I know is it's going to be an absurd adventure where you can go branching in a million
different directions. I'm going to make all kinds of just strange references to things and I'm not
going to take it that seriously. So if you're expecting out of this whole Germans writing a
book thing that you're going to get like George RR Martin presents like a song of ice and fire.
No, this is going to be just me writing my thoughts down and having some crazy adventure game
that you can just go on and mess around with and have a couple of laughs at maybe.
With that being said though, I do want it to be a coherent experience. I don't want to just write
like a third grader just like once upon a time, the princess was rescued from the alligator.
No, it's going to be a coherent story and I'm pulling trigger on it. So in the somewhat near
future, you might get a glimpse into some type of adventure free ebook that I'm going to write
and talking about free, talking about charging money for it and stuff. I don't know. I don't
think so. The only reason why I would ever charge money for this thing is if I literally like legit
put like 5,000 hours into writing it and it was like a really big fleshed out whole thing and
we'll just see how that goes. I have no idea what I'm doing. I have no clue what's going on,
which is why this is not a get rich quick scheme for me. I'm not just going to say,
Hey, wow, you know, I could just write a shit book that nobody's going to like.
And I'll just put like a $30 price tag on it. It's just an experiment that I'm doing.
And that's all I really have to say. I just wanted to mention that that's something I'm
working on right now. On top of all the other things that I'm doing in my life,
it's just kind of a life update. What are you doing video? And that's going to wrap it up. So
thanks everybody so much for watching. Really appreciate it. And I want to close this out by
saying this, right? If you want to try something like, look, I don't think I'm a writer. I don't
think so at all. I'm not one of those people that like I didn't go to school for it. I didn't learn.
I don't, I'm not a good like writer. Who gives a shit, right? Just, just try it. Just do it.
Even if you look at something and you go, you know, I can't do it. I would suck at that.
Try it. Just see, see if you do. Cause guess what? You might do it and go, holy shit, I'm the next
Edgar Allan Poe. And it would have said wandering weak and weary as a carpeting on my own
rainbow chamber door. You could be like really good at it is what I'm saying. And you never know.
Just try it. Even if it's anything, whatever it is, I would say, just go for it. You know me,
just fucking go for it and just bang. You know what I'm saying? Boom. And with that,
that's going to wrap it up. I'll see you all next time. Thank you all so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it and goodbye everybody. Take care and have a wonderful evening. Have a
wonderful night. Have a wonderful morning when you wake up. I hope you get a delicious breakfast.