I've been training all day. I don't know how to get clothes though.
You have no Drip? You have no Roblox Drip?
He's got the default character face.
I don't have any V-Bucks.
Get some V-Bucks, or Robux.
Why would I give Roblox money?
Because they're-
Just so they can enslave our youth.
True.
Give me one second. I've got a whole fucking thing behind me. Hold on.
Give me like two minutes.
Hi everybody. Welcome to the stream.
It's a very special stream today.
Because today, today is somebody's birthday.
I don't know whose birthday it is, but it's probably yours.
I made a promise a week ago.
And we're gonna do it.
So we got a couple people here.
We got Oak and Ster.
Oak is going to guide Ster and I through the world of Roblox.
Because that's exactly what we're playing.
So I'm just gonna show this because this is kind of a pain in the ass setup, but whatever.
Oh, let me ask this question.
Hey, before I show everybody the screen, does it matter if they can see my username?
I mean, they're gonna see it anyways, right?
Yeah, it does.
Ain't a lot of nos and yeses.
I was muted. Oops.
You want to go to your profile and go to security or privacy?
And make it so only friends can join you.
Okay, cool. Yeah, I think I already have that setup.
Alright, cool.
Cool, cool. Alright, I'm gonna show this because people are waiting for it.
Happy birthday. Happy birthday.
Happy Roblox birthday to whoever that was a week ago.
I actually don't remember who it is.
Are you kidding me?
Yeah, Poke, it's somebody's birthday.
That's the reason why I'm playing Roblox today.
Well, happy birthday, somebody.
Yeah, happy birthday.
Is it a real person?
I think so, yeah.
I actually think it's somebody's birthday. Who is it?
It's my birthday.
Is it really? Happy birthday, dude.
Yeah, you didn't get me anything, but this will suffice.
Tell me I haven't been hitting you up daily to play Roblox.
Yeah, you can have some of that giant cookie over there if you want.
Save it. I'll be there.
I didn't get a fucking cake.
I've kind of been sick for four days.
Well, then it's not really a party.
Oh, there's a delay on the camera. Oops.
Hold on, I'll fix it.
No, there isn't. You're a liar.
Oh, they're lying. Okay.
Alright, are we ready?
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
What? What?
Okay, so this is Roblox, right? It's a kid's game.
Kind of.
On the main menu, how come I've already got Survive Michael Jackson?
It's a kid's game.
Hold on, there is a delay.
I fixed the delay.
Wait.
What?
Alright, Poke.
We got to...
Poke, you've got to help us.
I'm trying really hard.
I tried to make a list.
I have five things.
That works.
We can jump into random stuff.
I want to do Survive Michael Jackson in the kid's game.
Why don't we just do that right now?
First thing.
I don't want to play Survive Michael Jackson.
Why not?
Wait, it's my birthday and I don't even get to pick the game.
Alright, do we have to make a party or do we just all join that one?
I think you could join or we could join off you and friends.
Okay, I think I can just join it.
Yeah.
Okay, so let's go.
Wait, no.
Is the server going to fill with people if we say what we're doing?
Probably.
Oh, shit.
But there should be a lot of people playing it regardless.
There are so many of these.
Which one?
How many?
Area 51?
Yeah.
Survive Michael Jackson in Area 51 Kill Killers.
Oh, my God.
4.2 million people have played this.
Alright, I'm just going in.
Are we just going in?
Yep.
We just click the play button.
We just join off you and friends.
How loud is this game, by the way?
Should I turn it down or something or does that not matter?
It might be loud.
Okay, hold on.
Oh, my God, dude.
Did you see my character?
I'm joining you right now.
I have a rocket launcher?
I just saw you fall in the hole.
Oh, wait.
There's in-game voice.
Oh, you have to put your ID for that.
So if you're not verified, you won't hear voice.
Okay, I thought I heard something.
I got spooked.
Rocket launcher.
Buy.
No!
Did I just buy it?
Oh, cancel.
How much Roblox?
Do you have any Roblox?
I have like $100 in Roblox or something.
199 Roblox is like $1.
It's like five cents.
Alright, let's go.
Let's play this game.
I'm the guy behind you.
Oh, where are you?
Oh, wow.
What was that?
Who's doing that?
You're doing that in voice?
No, that's Michael Jackson.
What?
Wipe him.
Wait, he's right here.
Oh, my ears.
I can't hear.
I just ran away from you.
I think I'm dead.
I just saw you die.
What?
Okay, this is very strange.
I'm going to turn the audio down just a little.
I can't hear anything.
You can't hear that?
Let me turn this down.
Hold on.
Wait, Michael Jackson's right there.
Should I turn chat off too?
Or do you keep that on?
I usually hide it.
Or maybe put your camera...
Alright, where's the audio?
There it is.
Oh, my...
Why would they do that?
Why would they have that be the thing that plays when you go down on the volume?
I don't even hear anything when I go down.
It's using the wrong...
What was it?
It was an extremely loud sound effect when I pressed the down button on the volume.
That's not even fucking cool.
What?
Jesus.
Okay.
Are we all right?
Yeah.
I'm turning this shit all the way fucking down.
Alright, let's go.
I'm so sorry about that.
Alright.
No, I got to turn that off too.
How are you guys enjoying Survive God?
I'm trying to get my sound to even work at all.
You guys want to try a different map?
Yeah, I'm just doing my settings.
Hold on.
We're just getting through this.
Oh, it's a private map, I think.
What's the...
How do I make it so people can't talk in the chat room?
Do I have to do that in my profile?
I don't even know how to turn it off.
I think...
Alright, I'll try it one more time.
What just happened?
Why are there two different Michael Jacksons chasing this one person?
Oh, now they're chasing me.
I just aggroed.
They cloned them in Area 51.
How do you sprint?
Is there no sprint?
Oh, you can press the chat button.
Hide it.
Top left.
What is going on?
I wish I was a map that I could see where you guys were.
Okay, I think I got it.
The first sound I heard was...
I thought that was one of you guys doing that in the call.
I think we're doing pretty good.
How do you win surviving Michael Jackson?
There might not be a win condition here.
I feel like he just gets everyone eventually.
Alright, that was a good warm-up.
Pog, let's jump to one of the maps.
I'm getting us a nice obstacle course map.
Why did we let Ster pick the first game?
What were we thinking?
I feel like it's a prerequisite to be able to play anything else.
You need to be able to survive Michael Jackson, then you're free to go around the play lane.
Ster, do I have you?
I don't know.
I added you.
I don't know what I'm doing.
Oh, I got you.
Okay, go to your friends list and join off me.
Alright, so what's the easiest way to get out of this without closing the whole application?
You could just close it and then...
Oh, okay.
You have the website open, right?
Yeah, the app is what is being captured, right?
So is this going to kick me out of the app?
Oh, no.
You exit the experience and it's got me back on the, like, I don't know.
You're on the website?
I got the desktop mode.
Well, I'll use these as a website and then click on the website.
Oh, back home.
I see, back home.
Okay, so I'm going to hide my screen so we can make sure we get in somewhere before everybody else does.
So we'll see.
Are you in a game right now, Pog?
Yeah.
Can I just join off you somehow?
Yeah, I should be on friends.
See me?
I see you on friends.
I could go to view profile.
Is there join?
On your profile, I can unfriend you.
I don't want to do that.
Okay, hold on.
See all.
Oh, friend activity.
Here it is.
Okay, I see.
Is it this one?
Yeah, that's the one you're in.
All right, going in.
Yeah.
Oh, I see you.
I don't see that you're in one.
Really?
Yeah, I don't see either of you are in a game.
Refresh it.
You just joined one.
Yeah, you got to refresh it.
Well, I saw yours before I saw him.
You don't know what you're talking about.
What do you mean?
You're an amateur at this.
What are we doing?
I've never this first time we've you and I have ever opened this whole game.
We're doing this obstacle course stage one out of 50.
The popular one right now amongst children.
Okay.
So are we just going for it?
I went for stir.
Is he here?
Oh, they're like move my mouse.
You're going to turn your sensitivity way down.
Okay.
You're fire guy, right?
You're the phantom fireman.
I'm fire guy.
Box is way too big.
I'm default guy.
Okay.
Yeah, I see you right here.
And then there's the weird robot with the chain.
All right.
Are we going?
Yeah.
Okay.
Here we go.
All right.
Let's go.
Let's race.
Wee.
Oh, there's a jump.
Oh, okay.
Cool.
Is there any sound on this map?
Yeah, I don't know why it's so quiet.
It's just like footprints.
I don't even hear footprints.
Usually there's like fun music.
Okay.
Be careful when I'm holding right click and that's kind of probably a bad idea.
Right?
Because when I turn the camera, I think you press shift once and it goes like into a different
lock.
Oh, all right.
Not bad.
There's no music.
Oh, you can climb too.
Cool.
Oh, shit.
All right.
Be careful.
I think we're doing pretty good.
Yeah.
Dude, you're a 37 year old man.
Whatever.
Do you have any idea what fucking today is?
Honestly, if the kids are into it, you need to stop being such a boomer and acclimate.
Like if you don't get it, that's on you.
It's going to take like two or three hours.
Everyone else gets it.
It's going to take me all day to clean up.
I think you guys are like an hour ahead of me.
Did you fall down?
On stage seven.
You can skip.
You can pay money to skip the stage.
You can pay money.
Yeah.
Wait, why is this?
How come the floor is gone?
Yeah.
I'm just going to pay the money.
I'll see you guys at the end.
What is happening?
How much is it to skip?
Wait, there's like weapons.
I'm going to delete this.
You have to wait.
You have to buy.
What?
You stand over it and it's like, hey, use your Robux to get the gravity coil.
How much is this?
800 Robux?
That's how they get you.
It's 50% off, dude.
Are you going to pass up that dude?
What the fuck is going on?
Why can I not do this one?
All right.
No, wait, go, go, go, go.
I made it.
Is there really no music for you?
Like there's no music, right?
No.
I'm playing my own.
Okay.
No.
There's only like, there's only sound effects.
I don't know why it's so quiet.
How does it even happen?
It defaulted audio for me to my VR headset that's not plugged in.
So I think it might have done that again.
I'm so glad I turned it down.
Oh, I need the magic carpet.
Wait, you're going to spend money on the magic carpet, but not on like a cool outfit?
No, I'm not.
I'm a free to play Robloxer.
Whenever you guys are ready for the next map.
I got one.
I want to see that.
I want to see how far I can get with this.
Cool.
Yeah.
I saw you playing a game like this earlier today, poke.
So you're all, you're all practice.
Is this person hacking poke?
This person is flying around.
No, you probably paid money.
Okay.
This stage was hard.
So, but all right.
I have a question.
If you bought the magic carpet to fly around, what's the point of the whole game?
Isn't the whole point like to jump around and jump on the platforms that you just like
fly to the end?
Yeah.
But instant gratification, you can just, you can just do it.
They offer the versus took my fucking hair.
What just happened?
Oh, wait.
I got it.
I don't know what's happening at like any moment.
I see you over there, poke.
I see you going pretty far at a defaulted Roblox to my headset, my VR again.
Don't people make wild, wild shit in this game?
Yeah.
They're a whole like Call of Duty games, right?
And I don't know.
Oh, yeah.
I'll show you that one.
Pretty crazy.
I made some progress.
Oh, dude.
Where are you?
I'm on stage 18 out of 50.
You're a little bit ahead of me.
I am.
Yeah.
This person is like, what is this person doing?
It's person out of here.
Get away from me.
What the fuck is this person doing?
Get the fuck away from me.
Get out of here.
I have to win so I can hold on.
Wow.
As someone who didn't get into the fall guys craze, this is probably the best version of
jumping around on colorful blocks that exists.
It actually is kind of fun.
It kills you.
That's pretty sick.
I'm missing music.
He loves the Roblox.
I don't like how quiet it is.
This might be my new main game.
Roblox is great.
I think it's.
I'm just gonna say it.
What?
I think it's better than Minecraft.
Ooh.
Yeah.
People are gonna hate me for that one.
Oh, you've been doing Minecraft speedruns, haven't you?
Yeah.
It's fun.
Why is there an ad right here for this?
Wait, this is an ad?
When you see it.
When you see it, you'll laugh.
I'm like enjoying.
I'm having a good time right now.
I'm actually enjoying this.
That makes sense to me.
These are like, this is the pace of game you typically enjoy.
Wait, the ad disappeared.
Get out of here.
I didn't see the ad.
Wait, I saw an ad.
You didn't see it.
What the heck?
Sir, did you um.
Did you beat the last boss of Sekiro?
What the, why did I fall?
You know that I didn't baby sensory stream. Okay, cool. Yeah, I don't see an ad or anything
You got like an actual little yeah an ad on the side for the new Mario movie
Random of this fracking me. All right, I'm at 29. I'm at 30. I'm at 34. I'm popping off right now
Okay, not bad. Here are you zonked right now. What does that mean? People think I like
Smoked weed before I did this no
This is a birthday party that big cookie over there is gonna be shared by all of us. Is that why I'm invited I
Don't do this. Of course not thirty three. Where are you sir? I'm gonna wait for you
I'm I'm having a grand old time. Is that you all the way over there with the big I got wings
Is they you can fly with the wings? Are you the elephant? No. Oh, I have the golden wings
I'm on 38 out of 50. Oh, it's way better in first. Let's see right there. You have these cool-ass wings
Yeah, is it cheating to go well with it? It's cheating to do first person. Oh, whatever. Yeah, it's cheating
I heard that you get banned if you do it
Are you supposed to know which color kills you? No, you just pay money probably
Oh, are you at the thing where it's blue and red and yeah
Yeah, so when you touch don't it's very confusing when you touch the red you die. No, but on some of them
Opposite yeah, it's called it's a hard game and you get a get good at playing it
You're the last person I would expect to complain about a game being like a little difficult
Well, I should be higher up on your list because apparently I hate literally every game
What?
You know what now I'll give it to you. This is insane. This is really hard
I think anyone who can complete this stage without the magic carpet. Oh, you're almost done. Are you I'm at 44?
Yeah, I'm at 41. Wait, when did I get ahead of you? What I'm on 44. I'm right behind poke
What they're getting clowned on right now. I'm speedrunning. I'm gonna catch you but there's no way cuz there's like not even any turns
Yeah, but what if one of you falls off that could happen. How are you supposed to know which one of those is gonna fall?
Hey, it's a hard game man. You gotta buy the glasses on the left side. I got it
How many dollars like what's the dollar to roblox?
Robox looks I can answer that pretty quickly. It was $20 or I believe
17 or 1800 roll up dollars, whatever it is. That's what I bought. I made it to 50. Where are my big hands?
How come they got taken away?
Look at him not making it here. That's kind of embarrassing. I'm getting there. I'm at 47. Oh my god
This is a cute
Roblox girl. That's the default girl. Oh, dude. Oh, dude. You somebody said you bought it
I don't think you don't buy roblox. You just play it a hacker guy. Come on. Stop. Hey hacker guy
All right. This is it. This is the last part. We're all waiting for you. Wait, you only get three minutes to left to do this
Yeah, I think you're the last person. I was the last person to finish it. Yeah, it started the timer
I would do my animation that I bought it was like five dollars. All right, that was fun. Let's keep it rolling
I put a link. Ooh, that one looks actually really cool. This one. I love this one really cool
What you act like that? What am I ironic? I can't say that looks cool
It was like the germa hashtag ad stream voice shut out really cool. Shut up looks like this looks sick
I fucking hate your guts. We're both here. Did we both beat you again? Yeah, I'm trying to turn my chat off
I'm coming in. All right, so oh, would you we get to ride it together?
Yeah
No, you guys are riding without me. No, we're waiting for just waiting for you. Where are you standing?
He's just standing in top of us. Where are you?
Where are you join what Germans in a different? Oh, he joined his own server. What? Oh, hold on. I'll fix it
Am I in there now?
I'm joining off of you. It's friend activity and then it just puts me in my own game. All right, because the servers private
I think it's Oh, okay. Okay. Okay. Sorry. Okay. All right coming in. All right. Sorry about that
I'm I take me a little extra time. All right, so well, let's do it
All right, you spawn a cart and you just see how far you can go. Okay
So if you want to officially race art game pass here, no, no, no, I know a dangerous bomb
I don't do that right here. This is gonna be so sick. I can't wait. All right, right the one over here in the front
We'll send the back. Oh, we all want to get the same one. Okay. Oh
You riding on top of huh? All right. Yeah, get in the front stir. I'm turning it on
This is fucked up looking by the way, it's all it should be it should be on I think stir
I think you have to I think you have to steer is it me in the back. It might too big
Yeah, what do we have too much weight on this? It's your hands. I'm just gonna say it is this drive towards
How do I emote? Oh
There you go. Oh
All right, I'm in
Oh
Let's try this one you try to try to not break it get on it. All right, let's go
All right, I'm in
We all in turning it on
All right, go go. Oh
Turned off
All right, I got it I got it if you go too fast we might fall don't go too fast. Yeah, we might fall dude
Well, I didn't know I thought we were just I thought it was like a fucking Disney ride
I didn't know we had to control it
This was out of order
Maybe I shouldn't control it. Maybe somebody with some skills. How did you control it? How did you drive?
Just W's W. I had to turn it on. That's why the back
Fuck I love your character. Thank you. I don't even get a fair try
Why are there police coming?
I don't know
Shit now we're gonna wait for the maintenance guy to show up and fix this ride
I paid money for so I could fly in this like I'll fix it
All right, we're good though, we got to get through this at least once we got to get through one time
All right. Here you go. Who's driving it? I I will try it one more time. I'm down the track already
All right, we'll pick you up. Yeah
You got to go real slow man, you go slow on the turn slow on the turn is there what is break just s
All right, let's go I get in careful you could push us
Let's go. Oh
This is gonna be impossible. Are you kidding me?
Hey, why is there something in front look at this? What what is that push that he's pushing me
Why is there a car?
That was weird. Yeah, it was weird. How come it says I'm suffering underneath my name
I'm starting to suffer. What is suffering?
They're starting to suffer suffered and suffering. Yeah
I'm definitely starting to suffer
That was tight. I
Keep thinking that something I'm hitting something when you do that. Why is there a gun? Oh whoops
Oh
Come on. I got ice
When you press a or d you shoot a little cannon. All right, this is straight coming up here. Whoa
I didn't what just happened
You you didn't see little bumps. What do it? I?
Didn't know there was gonna be little bumps. How like can we fix it? I
Press space again. Maybe I can get poke. Did you fix it?
Oh
Are you holding a cotton candy what is in your hand?
It's a flight potion. Oh, I thought you were just like enjoying the carnival eating a cotton candy. I
Can't fix this. Oh, there's a big loop to loop too. Oh
How do we ride the loop to loop? I want to ride the loop to loop
There's no there's no way
We can't go into like a slight curve
Where even let me see if I can even see where you guys are
Also paid I also paid for this right here the fast car
Wait, he's got cotton candy. Oh
Wait, oh, okay. Cool. Cool. Cool. They took it away from me
They took it away. What?
My DLC right now a season pass
extra large carts, oh
All right, all the boys. All right poke whip look you should ride again. Oh sir. You want to go?
All right, sir. Drive. I'm going
It turns out it's still somehow way too loud even at like zero sound I can't go
It's W. I'm holding W and it's screeching at me
All right. Oh because it's not on. Oh
No, it is
I'm I can't fit in. All right. There we go. Like dude. There are there are four empty seats
Why do I have to sit in the one right behind you? Like I don't
Follow the back here
Whoa, all right, can you make it?
Stir you got to get us to the loop to loop. I don't even know if this connects to that
One of those cars just crashed
Scary tunnel. How do we get to the scary tunnel entrance? That sounds fun castle loop to loop
Stir you you got to use all of your gamer skills here and do this
We have to go
That's that one's over
Okay, no
All right. Here I go. It's the best car
Car fast car. Let's go. Can you drive it? Oh, how much uh, how much money do you have?
I got some robots. Are you are you a roblox millionaire?
Maybe I think it's asking me to buy it to even sit in it. Yeah, wait to send it. Yeah. Oh, no
No, I oh wait. I can I have I got money
You want to buy it I got 259
Roblox after this bike. Press this button. Is it gonna like what just happened? I reset it for us
This is just doesn't just give me access to it
Or is it gonna like open up like credit card information when I press this button? No, it won't
Go. All right. So I have access to it now stir. Do you have 60 roblox sense?
Yeah for anyone who has kids and you're wondering like how your kid spent like a thousand dollars in roblox. This is how
No, there's there's way worse ones. This is all right. It's your car sir
We gotta get her should I I'm kind of scared to drive this. Oh, no, there's no room. Oh, there's no room for you
I'll be behind you guys. Yeah, be careful. We gotta get to the loop to loop. We're dead first
whoa
Brakes are pretty good brakes are clean
This fucking Jojo character drive in the car very important wall. Please don't shoot. I beg you. This is so important
You won't believe how important it is. Oh
It bounced off
Interesting, okay
Excuse me. Hurry up, please
Yeah, we're riding way too slow
Watch that bump. You're the one driving. Watch it. This is one handle better too feels like it does
It's just us. Oh
There's so many bumps for this was I don't know
40 cents
40 cents too much
The cars coming behind us
That default stock explosion sound is like my favorite part so far
All right poke. It's time for you to get us to the loop to loop
This is not gonna happen between me and sir. Okay, it's not gonna happen. I
Know away, you know away. I know yeah get on
Turn the engine on in the back. Does it use this fall damage? All right. All right, sir
You're gonna turn the engine on I think I did
I'm doing it. There you go
That works stir. You're probably gonna get really sick
I'm holding it together
You just get over here
Yes, you did a fire
Remains seated. What why would you why would dehumidifier? This is the suffering process to get the
suffering
hot
So we have you put have we've been dehumidified yet?
It's not gonna explode in here
This would be the scariest fucking ride
No child should ride this
No human should ever ride this. This is scary
You are now less humid
Okay, we get up here. All right
Here you go. Use this one here. Oh my god poke you legendary legendary
Legendary gamer some reason
Alright, there you go. Now you guys at the loop. We said we could never get loop. Yeah
Sorry, look gentlemen, hold on to something stir. We're gonna go fast. You gotta put your hands up. I don't know how to do that
Hands up. Oh
Holy wait, why is it end like this? What?
What it just kills you you supposed to press the button right at the end
All right, let's write a new map person, let's write this one more time in first person
Okay, it's like a big one so we can all do it. Okay, cool. I
Have definitely proposed games to you that you've played for less time than this, but let's go. Yeah turn it on
This is different man. All right, let's go
You make sure you're gonna press the button
It's after the loop
Thank you, there's nothing else
You stink I'll do it. I switched the thing
Now it's all right, oh it's fun go backwards if you got stuck
That'd be great that'd be great tip-tock
Joke right there. Oh man
That was cool. All right, let's do another one. You want to do a see what we got you want to do like a
A shooter one or like a scary one. Oh, either one of those sound awesome. Whatever what do you think?
Okay. Oh wait, let's do the shooter one with the cool graphics for a second. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah
This is a good map. I like this one
Think you just join me and then a from friends. I join our friends. Yep. All right, where we going? Let's see
Okay, wait, this is in this is in of roblox
Yeah
What? Oh shit's about to get intense. I think okay spawn loadout
How do you even make this in?
How is this possible to make this in this game? This looks insane
What I think I have to go into like the actual source and lower the volume so loud
All right, that's a lot better
What?
Is that crazy? Yeah, I'm in queue. I can't see it
Holy shit experience is full. That doesn't look like a roblox guy. That looks like it like I'm joining. Oh
How is this possible? Oh mean stirring a game. I think I'm in a different game. I'm in a different game
Yeah
It said friend activity and I joined friend activity
Maybe a hard to play together on this one. Oh
Maybe because of the teams you're trash at this game. Yeah, whatever
Have okay, I'm not impressed with the graphics. I'm impressed that they have
My sensitivity is fuck. Oh, I think the graphics are insane. Yeah, how are you not impressed by the graphics?
I'm more I'm just saying I'm more impressed that there's a kill cam
That's that's a lot more complicated than making things look pretty. I'm sure someone dedicated to the blocks
blocks together
Turn up your graphics. Yeah, I think they're there's not even a graphics slider or setting in the game. Is there that's what you think
Your grenades definitely
Shit, I do so bad with hold instead of toggle
Anybody any okay you two is aim down sights for you hard to do with him. It's hold or are you a toggle?
It depends on the game really I think I'm a holder
I'm always toggle. Yeah, I'm a holder
I like toggle for some games. I'm gonna let me get I'm gonna try to get in your guys game
All right friend activity as you're in it. Yeah, I'm older. I'm lines. It's just friends. Can't you okay?
I think it's because it's full. You know, oh, it's full. Your your game is full. Did you leave I?
Leave I was never in your guys game. Oh
People are saying we should do a scary one called doors and it's like
Telling me to do doors. Yeah, it's like the best roblox game. I think in terms of like where are
Yeah, where's the like, how do I spend my roblox in here to fly?
Yeah, we have in this where's like the paper the magic carpet you can like customize your whole gun
It look at my sensitivity guys like I
This is so fucked up. All right, it's okay. Everything feels so wrong
Yeah, roblox has a lot of fun shooters. They're really fun ones because it's really easy because you're just shooting
different iPads
This is ironically incredibly impressive. This is actually
Blowing my mind how actually cool. This is first kill ever got it. Finally first kill
Mr. German 95 your game is running at automatic graphics. Your computer is probably not good enough. Wait. Oh, wait, it's had zero
Oh shit. This looks really good now. Yeah, Jeremy. You can play this on your iPad by the way
Yeah, there's plenty of very fun games on the iPad. There's plenty of great experiences to enjoy on a mobile device
This is one of them. Yeah, we definitely should do some horror games too because you know, everybody loves those
Am I in a game alone right now? I
think I think it's hard to get in the game together because
It's just because the game just get full. I want to play with my friends. Okay, I'm only a
Shooting game where you just get like a random gun all the time
Team kill right?
The one we just
Jackson one I
Feel like the people that I'm playing against are better than like top 500 overwatch
Yeah
That was really cool. I enjoyed that. We should play squid game. People are saying should we play squid game?
I know you die if you do that
Only one of us would get to live
I'm ready to hop in on
You should be able to join me off friends list
People make this joke and I know you were making this joke earlier
But just being able to jump from experience to experience really is kind of that's my cup of tea
You just can just play what I just jump in it
Who cares you play for five minutes fucking leave right like it or an hour doesn't matter. Yep
That's your steam library. Yeah. All right
Should uh, you got a private one or are we just turning off you? I just joined a
Almost full of him in all caps in chat
What I don't I don't know you look at this are we in the same game poke I
Don't think so. I'll try joining you
This one's very different voting assault Lodge works or Mountain Village
What do you think is good? Um, oh, yeah, your server is really full. Yo, I'm ready to game
I'm ready to I'm ready to game for like a solid three minutes and then we could just hop into a brand new experience
Let's deploy
something about these characters
like I don't know something about these characters holding like
guns is
My brain is having hold on
Sensitivity, I'll never get it right hearing every time we get in a game. I have to get it off my VR
What the fuck was that? Oh this guy's headshot
Single person. Oh, is he cheating? I don't know. It's hard to tell
I know I'm having trouble finding the right
Middle ground. I don't even know where you change just go to the sense of type 0.3. This is fun, too
Yeah, this one this game is really fun arsenal
These games are just addicting like just time waster. I actually really like them. Oh, I got a new gun shit
He's be even lower. I feel like the sensitivity is changing from game to game, too
Yeah, that's how it is. We said they love roblox. Oh, yeah, this is great. Did when are we gonna fucking play?
Stir is seething right now because like I'm having fun playing this like fucking goofy like
Pick any game grab bag experience when he's like desperately trying to get me to play path of eggs off like five years
I I just unmute it to my stream and was saying exactly that like 30 seconds before you started saying it
What is this weapon?
This thing is amazing. Oh
It's also like I'm max on volume. It's really quiet. I'm having the opposite problem. Oh
How's he not dead?
Whoa, there is a little quiet. I will turn you up
How's that? How do I sound? Oh probably better
Fuck just happened. Why did you do that? What the hell? What did happen? What honestly what happened?
What was that what happened?
What actually what did you what happened was that in the game? Yeah, I was in the game
Join you game. Did you do that you piece of shit? Did you actually do that? Yes?
Yes, you did. No, I swear. I if I yes you do it. I would do it. You just did that
Wasn't me. Yes, it was
Why do you why I don't know?
You did that somehow
Am I actually blaming you for that
Wait it was an admin so is me
What the fuck dude? Come on
Why I?
Am so glad I have this turned way the fuck down
I have this turned down to like 0.2 and it still was bad my initial reaction
Instantly when it showed up was laughing because I just knew you were gonna get freaked out. It didn't even scare me
It's just like oh god. This is cold. It was great
I have roblox at like 20% and it's turned down over here, too
Why do you think the oldest squeeber of the internet?
Well, cuz people are saying dude stir is quiet stir is quiet so I turn you up
No, you don't understand so I like I go over to discord and I'm like, oh stirs quiet
I thought that you had this you muted cuz you said you were muted. You were like, oh, yeah
Sorry, I was muted for a minute. I just said that so you were muted and I'm like, all right
So he was just fucking muted. So then hey, hey Jerma stir is quiet
Like I thought you guys were conspiring into your chat to make me turn you up in discord
So I go over I turn you up in discord and the next thing that happens is oh
Holy shit. I really thought that was you. I'm sorry. Maybe it was are we still in here. We're going it we're
I think we're ready for the scary game. No, I think you're all like warmed up. I just heard a laughing
Laugh. All right, dude. I don't trust any developer anymore
This game is running at like point five percent volume for the next for the remainder of the stream. All right, let's do a scary game
Okay
Why is it trying to get me to buy shit? I didn't oh
Spend hopefully that wasn't too bad cuz that was fucking awful. I'm really sorry. I gave us a code
I never played this one though, by the way, I'm scared. So doors
Super hard mode super hard has 80k players
80k right now see that. Oh, all right. Let's go. This is what it's all about
This is what I showed up for. All right, the dev is not gonna like put a fucking jump scare
Oh, there are jump scares. Okay, I'm scared
Flashing lights loud noises and jump scares. Okay. Wait, why did I take away all my cool stuff?
Way too big. He said I was too big focus your hands. I love your fucking character, dude
It's I love it. Thank you. It's awesome. All right. How do you go into first person?
I don't think you can in this one. All right, super. Oh, it's super hard. I'm ready. All right, let's go
Which one do we want to do first? See we just go in the elevator. All right go stir. Hey watch out
It's gonna it's gonna get you turn up your volume. I refuse not after that. I can't I would go giggle loud
I'll turn it up a little just enough as high as it's gone. Okay
So we oh it is in first person all right your headphones going in
Okay, hold on. I can't look down. I can't look down like that because okay
Okay, we're not
We're not in on it. We got to go indoors. I think here
There's a sprint. All right, here's zero zero zero one and we need a key
There's a there's a key over here. Grab the key. Nice. Wow, we beat we beat level one already. I found loot your hand is
I'm yeah, it's kind of it's kind of large. All right, we got the first key. It's all I can see. Oh
You have to hide from the monster. I get it. Wait, why I get it. Why there's so many it's a tutorial
I presume okay. Okay. Okay. Nice and warm. Here's a look alike. I heard something. Well, there's fucking nothing in here
There's nothing in there turn it up. All right, actually shotgun. It actually might be like loud
So just seriously be careful turn your fucking volume down, but Jesus
That was pretty sauce of you that was kind of delayed from my end, too
I just I'm so on edge after that fucking gun game. We played it. I can't believe that happened
Do something in here, but I can't touch it. Never mind. We're gone gold on table. What do you use the money for?
I wonder more doors. Oh
I lied and you accept my roblox friend request. It's my birthday. Um, I mean we're just
It's just everybody's birthday today. So happy birthday something's gonna happen. This is the room where it flips it on you go first open it
I didn't open that somebody else did. Oh, dude. Go you gotta go. I got your back nothing in here
What was that? I don't know mighty. I heard someone knock. Wait, did I just kick you out? No, okay
This would be way scarier if we didn't all look like dickheads
You know, I to me this is not scary anymore because stir your character looks like this it's no longer scary
I mean your hands you're the scariest dude here. It has so much detail in veins
Do they really I didn't even yeah, they do they're very weird it looks so fucked up if I look down by the way
It honestly just this painting is titled temple. Ooh
interesting cool
That's a welcome to
What
Bad I
Didn't see anything we just saw your character go what?
There was a spider inside of the thing and I was like, oh a spider then it jumps on my face. Oh
No, I'm not opening anything. There was such an overreaction to holy shit. That's the thumbnail for the YouTube video
Don't do that again. Oh, it's Jesus Christ, but roblox
Tidal the last pizza party. Oh
My goodness if only God knew what we were doing down here we've lost our way
I'm not no I am NOT touching that you are they must kind of scary. So this is door 12. I'm not opening this
It's good. Oh, dude
door number
Careful that means I got something. What's that? Which means it goes here?
Pits good thinking that doesn't fit. They're stupid. You're stupid. Oh
Door 13, dude. Oh, why am I opening these? How many doors are there worse? It's a good question. Oh
What's that? Wow, don't mock me. Did it not happen at the same time? Oh shit run
Jesus oh
Hide there was only one you come I didn't see it coming. I bear I saw I did for a second
Hey, I look behind it. Just it was so fast. All right, let's do it again. That's fun
That's fun. So I think it was the lights flickering and then we could you could hear of like a
Sound effect too. Yeah. Yeah, that was fun. Yeah, that was fun
Yeah, so I put I put a bunch of filler words in oh you buy stuff
I have no money. Yeah, I don't either
All right, then there's zero one. I feel like my game got twice as quiet
I turned up a little but not that high. I'm maxed everywhere. I can be maxed. I
Can't hurt anything anymore. You guys want you guys want to just try to get back to 12 the 13th?
That's yeah, let's go. Oh my god those
Nothing hold on. Oh, I think if you guys went too far forward, I took damage and it teleported me to you. Oh
If poke you you're like sneaking and leaning it looks great
All right, that one's kind of messed up. Um, is this door gonna have like a mouth or something to open and eat us?
It looks like teeth right here, it's gonna be like a mimic. Is it a mimic door?
I'm just going to 13. Yeah
What was that? I don't know. I'm going in yet. I don't know is that I don't know is it safe to come on
They were fine. Hey, we're stir. I'm here. I'm behind you. I'm not stealth. Oh, what a rogue class at the beginning of this
Oh, all right, there's 11. Wait, it's get it like, oh, I need one. Yeah
We're good. He just ran by is it safe
Wait, why is my character?
Yeah, my screen is flickering. I'm tripping out get out. I don't get out. It says get out. All right, I got out
I got out. I got out. I got out 13. It's very dark. I think we all make it
Yeah, I'm dying though. If I get spooked one more time, I'm done. Um, I'm done, dude
Can't take much books my last spook 14. I got one good spook left in me here fire. It's this room
Oh, it's rain. I know that's that's the one. Yeah, it was frying a chicken. This is oh, I got a lighter it has a fuel though
He's right here. Oh nice
Everyone get one if a monster comes out as you stab him right in the eye. Oh, oh my god
This is fun. I'm just going in we good
Something is whacking the books off the shelf and stuff. Yeah, I was present evil save
Oh, okay, this lighter here you guys played the remake at all present before. Yeah. No, it's very good
Don't spoil it. Yes, you play the brain game. We're playing doors. We're opening doors
Okay, there's a brain game in a spooker coming. I don't know about it. There's a lot of these
Kid that we have to get out now, right still dark your lighter. Oh, I do have a lighter. It's a very dark
Oh, oh my god. I died. Oh, oh my god. You did that's kind of sus. What's the right door?
This way you have a lighter. Oh, this is all mine. None of this is yours
What we got a hide trust me hide yeah, there's like this. Oh
There's like that cold air coming. Is that poke responding a monster cost 30 bucks when I'm here
You've paid to come back. That's awesome. Yeah, my mom said I could come play again. Nice. Oh shit. That's a spider
Yeah, it's awful scared me it's so bad. Thanks mrs. Laws
Why don't we just crawl out of the chimney? Good luck
We don't know how tall this building is so you out of your mind this building could be like 50 stories stir
And then you oh, yeah, go up there. You once you get halfway you get exhausted. Then what are you gonna do?
I like how you have hair on your avatar. This is like under that I do you have hair
Yeah, you kind of got like mutton chops. I've under fire. Oh
Cuz it's a mask right yeah, I think technically I feel like something's gonna happen. Oh, I have nothing. I'm dead you dead
The card I'm gonna be quick. Just put your credit card in again. I'm not scared. I'm rich
Why would you be scared? What? All right. I'm also a fuel in this thing. Oh you just skipped a 30. There's 229
Oh
You guys see what happened or no, I saw it scream at you and push you down stir. Where are you not quite?
I'm behind. I'm what I'm coming. Did you go to holy crap? Did you go 31? No, I went
We're behind you. Oh, okay. I just kept running. It's I'm single. I'm super jumpy today too already
Yeah, but just for no reason I apologize that I'm being like making like a hilarious YouTube video right now
There's an eye right there. I don't like
I think it's like an Enderman you have to say I have this I got this so
Yeah, I don't know dude. I
Just I just fucking swallowed like five gallons of spit right there. So don't look at it. I don't know
I don't have a credit card. I'm scared
Alright, this is getting kind of fucked up. So I don't I'm gonna hide think we're fine. Are we okay?
I think it's got a flicker. I don't there's an eye flickering everywhere
Yeah, I don't know if we look or don't oh, what's going on? I don't know lots of flickers
I feel like my graphics card is overheating
Nice there's a gold on table and rift and go back. Oh, excuse me. That scared me. What happened? It's a cutscene. Oh
Who is it going after oh, it's like a run section all right, I won't write okay right is right
I went straight away. Oh
We made it. Oh, we did it. It's gone gosh
Is it what oh you're lying pretty good nice job guys, I paid not to see it so watch out
You just don't see anything scary
nice
45 Wow, we're kind of pro with this now
Story are you the only one with a lighter? Yeah. Yeah, I'll make it make the time count. He has a phasmo
Yeah, a little bit. I haven't you said there's like a new game kind of like it. Yeah, I tried it yesterday
It's really it's really good demon knowledges or something like that. I'm
What the fuck I'm running out of light guys. Oh
Down no, okay. Okay guys, I feel like we're gonna see something
There was the switch I did the switch yeah, but we didn't collect the three gems
There's a green gem or red gem and a blue gem
You have to put them all to the red gem into the eye of the statue
The blue gem has to go into one's a fish and one's a bird and one's a snake. Yeah
It's coming hide the lights are gone, let's go no dilly-dallying guys, we're at 50 almost 48
I read a review that says no one ever gets to 50. Really? Shut the fuck up
This fake doors, I didn't know
All over this is red. Like you just died. Can I spectate you guys you could
What happened I don't know I open the door and I got glitched. Oh, wait a minute. This is scary man
Revive yourself put money in how do I do it the top the top come on? Oh, yeah, let's go
30 bucks easy. There's a philosophy. I heard a velociraptor
They just spawns and dies for you. Where am I? This next room? There's a velociraptor
Is the boss fight at 450? I think it is uh, we have to actually fight it doesn't even know where we are
This thing's an idiot. We're right at us. I think we just avoid a sneak. Yeah
Right side
Your hands just come out the door
I panicked your thumb just comes out. It looks kind of weird
Where is it the middle? I think we can get to the door. Yep. I made it to the terminal
It's a big lock. It needs a code. Do you guys any idea what the code is? No, dude
Yes, try your birthday. There's too many digits. We have to find the code in this room. I found it really
Yeah, it's in this table on the right. Holy shit
It has something going on it. I have to get to it. It's coming over. It's going over. Okay, I think it's going to you
Yeah. Oh, no, he's not you see it over here sir straight ahead. Okay, so we're gonna go down who's going who's gonna be brave?
I don't got a credit card. He's coming. Oh, never mind. Okay, but I'll just damn beat him
Yeah, he doesn't get it. He doesn't understand. Wait, maybe he does
Wait, he gets it. I wonder if he can hear us. Yeah, Bob beat him again
I'm gonna make a break for it to get the hey, hey dumb head over here. Oh
I'm going I'm going is he you are EQ or E. Can you get though QE?
Get out of there Jerma. I'm fine. I think I'm alright. I think I did the QTE. Whatever. Oh, I found it
It's a it's like a puzzle. I don't I can't understand this
I
Think he's coming after me, but I don't know what happened. He looks like really stuck
Use the opportunity and you get the code
Q it's I don't get it. I'm doing a minigame. Oh my god. He's right up. Okay. He got me. He got me
I've got my credit card. I'll be there in a minute. He's distracted with me. I got my credit card. Oh
Never mind. I can't
You can't pick it up. No, it's in your hand
You imagine being in this scenario being stuck. Yeah, he killed me
I think it got stuck in the in the closet that I was in. Do you see this?
Yeah, I fucked his ass up you have me didn't see what happened on my screen
I fucking knocked three of his teeth out. I took a candlestick and I fucking whacked him in the head
I pushed a bookcase over I broke his leg. I did that this shit. I got the book. I got you guys
Seven in it
You guys need glasses so bad. Holy shit, even without the monster here. I don't think we're getting past this
Like we're not smart you get out. Oh, that was a bad voice crack. I found another book
Square is zero. I think I get it
Triangle equals what? Oh gosh
But I can't look at the books again. Oh, it's on the bottom left of my screen. He just needs to pick up books
I love this. This is so funny X equals six. I got it weird crayon scribblings that you guys have to read
Okay poke to be nine
Seven nine seven six and then five. This is so funny
Oh, man, imagine a monster is behind killed your friend
Your friend just died by a monster the monster stuck like fucking the Wicked Witch of the West under a fucking bookcase
You're sitting there like um, I you know, I can't really tell where how do we get out of here? What's the code?
I think I found it. Oh, it's so funny zero. So what is it in order again?
979 six eight five zero. That's too many. There's only five switcheroo's. Okay, it should be nine nine six
Wait, actually no nine six. No eight nine seven six eight zero
This is the art this is when you're shit-faced and you're trying to read a fucking like thing on your phone
You got you are holding that you have closing one. I like wait, what's that? That's a two. Can you read?
No, I'm dead dead. Oh
You go. I'm scared. All right little bro get behind me. Yeah, I'm just back there. Don't trust them. It's pretty cool
Oh, there's a little shop. That's cool. Revive him here. Yeah, you can only it says you can only revive here once
Unless you guys can bring me back. Yeah, it says you can only revive in a run once unfortunately
I'm enjoying this though. Go for it as far as you can
I just took pills because I saw people do it in a rap video once. Oh, I think it's like a speed boost
A bottle of pills. What are you doing? What is that? What did you take like something? You weren't what was that?
I took pills and they were like a speed. No, no, no, we're supposed to look at the eyes
Oh look at the eyes and I looked at the eyes cuz I was so fast
I thought you ate something you weren't like supposed to eat
That was fucking fun how you guys fit you want to do you know, I'm not I got another one another map. Hell, yeah
next box or
Brain games another one people were saying. Yeah, what is that brain game brain game? Are we trivia? I imagine
Game but like if you don't know the answer you can give them five bucks this baseball too. Wow, cool
All right. Here you go. Here's brain game. Wow a map made by shovelware brain game
Do you want me just link in your chest so they could join? Um, yeah
Wherever you want. Yeah, where do you want it? I'm just a link in your chat one time. I got banned but there you go
Yeah, you can't do links
Okay, one of the mods though. Oh shit. I don't have my mod chat open. Hopefully they're not like screaming at me
There's already people here. He hates us. Oh, sorry
All right, they're in already. We're good
Alright, so how does this work? Oh nice. I got my costume back. It's starting 10 seconds. These all viewers. These people Wow, that's cool
We have to go up with help I'm stuck. Okay, I did run in the join game thing. Did you get it sir?
Yeah, who is this person over?
Oh
I don't remember what I wanted the mods to do. It's all right mods ban everyone
Ladies and jerkies in terms. He's watching. Oh
Shout out to the germs. I just tried I pogged and it hurt I hurt myself
Too fast. Okay first category. It's lit
Oh
Who's picking the category? I think it's not us because you invited people
It's leaf lock lift lock. That's what I said
I know this shit we answered easy. I did it wrong
I had to guess wait you got it wrong stir. Yeah, have you ever seen this piece of yeah?
Yeah, no, I know. I know past the order the flow of time as well
I was panicked because I wasn't sure if I could even click or not like or if there was a time
What is the name of the type of cable railway system involving two counterbalanced carriages on a steep slope
I think that's pretty easy. That's pretty easy everyone knows
Do you guys put stair lift too? Yeah, I think we all did I don't like that
Okay, various. It's phobia is the fear of what that guy is fucked up looking I gotta change that I
Think I just won did you maybe?
Oh, yes, okay, um science rules really. Yeah
Science into the air and didn't come back down
You just kind of hung there midair in this instance, which of Newton's laws did you break?
No, wait, it's that easy. This is of the one dollar question and who wants to be a millionaire
Whatever you get it wrong and everyone laughs at you. I
Really don't want to say this but I am currently freaking dominating right now. You have host advantage
Does it matter how quickly you answer are we getting like different points? I think it does. Oh, don't mind me
What you gonna pick eyes on the prizes? Yep
Good choice. Oh
This one's actually dude. You're gonna get a gun. This one really really
Oh
My god
You can ride our world famous attractions like shrunken school 4d and super slime spin you later
It's in the game behind the curtain and see how the magic happens on our iconic VIP. Oh my gosh
Including a stop by our newest soundstage where you can have a chance to participate in a live taping of shovel
Where's brain game? What damn wait a second. That's a lot of value
Yes, please
Oh
You remember that wacky cat Garfunkel from the Sunday Funnies, right? What is the name of his owner?
What there's no way you don't know this
Garfunkel I
Mean, that's valid. It's not his name isn't Garfunkel. He's a Garfunkel. What? Yeah, I think it was bait
Oh, how'd I get it wrong? I didn't even answer I could garfunkel. That's not Garfield. It was Garfield
Right. It's John. It's John Arbuckle. No, and it's got its Garfunkel. That's not Garfunkel. Who's Garfunkel? Oh
Why did you just say that cuz now
Can use them to communicate across distances up to six miles. What is the name of this kind of sound?
The rumbling I
Actually don't know this I should like die panicked I freaked up. I don't I don't I don't know I picked the weird one
Holy shit
Yeah, I'm getting I'm getting the trend that a lot of times. It's the weird one. I think so. I'm still winning. Oh
Is that Peter Griffin? You look like Peter Griffin to me. He does look like Peter Griffin
Whoa, come on, dude
That's cute. Are we gonna pick shapes and such if we all get this wrong, we should just delete our twitch channels
What shape has three points if you saw a three-dimensional object that looked like a perfect circle from all sides
It's a circle. I thought I got it wrong. I was gonna go. Oh shit. I guess
You guessed
I don't know what a sphere is. That's that's fair
Okay, God oink oink zoop out you said that and it just fucked up my whole day by the way, sorry
He's alright
You got the Canada advantage I
guessed
Shit, I put Albert. Oh, yeah, I did too. I did Albert
Just seen the most probable like Albert
14th and 15th century Europe was defined by a lengthy war between France and England
Dubbed by historians as the hundred years war this struggle for the respective countries thrones led to the longest recorded
conflict in European history
How many years did this war?
Actually last I
Don't even how would you even get this? Um, cuz you paid attention. I give up in history class
What is it? Well under 16 you guessed I?
Once I saw the number I was like that looks right and you know what it was right. All right
I don't I don't like that. I don't like that. That's that shit. I don't like I
I don't like characters whose shoes point up in fiction
Which type of character is often depicted with pointy-toed shoes in various pieces of media?
What's an alphacus? I wasn't I wasn't I didn't listen to the question
What's an alphacus?
I had to reread it. It's all right. It's the only zoo pals zoo pals
Shit y'all gonna hate me for this one
Flags of the world. Oh, no. Yeah, it's gonna be bad
How many stripes are there on the flag of the United States of America?
I'm gonna get all the points. I answered immediately nice job stirred, but I answered about two seconds faster than you
I've been 48
I'm trying to think of the stripes, right?
What is missing from these steps of the scientific methods
Observation research blank test analyze report
Yes, I was faster than you. I'm so happy about that because you have the better computer
Why did I only get five points for that I answered first
What's like you might not have answered first then pal, maybe it's cuz I chose the category
I don't know. I like how I'm completely covered by him. Even my answer was covered
He's standing just right
Hey
Kick that guy out of the building get that guy out of here so cool
I'm actually taking this seriously now cuz I don't want to start a win. Remember when I beat you a geoguessor every day
Cheating because he has a bigger chat Black Hills is known as the six
Grandfathers to the Native American tribe that used to live there and is considered sacred ground
What is the name of that tribe? I see it. I'll probably know
Shit, I literally just like read about this too. I think I actually don't I didn't even click them
I was gonna click it. I didn't I you saw the one I was hovering over
Throwing no, I'm good. It is in the shapes one
Yeah, this guy knows what shapes are
Every angle of any triangle what some will you get every time or got it wrong? I know it
How like I had a brain moment. Oh, I'm so dumb. I thought you I thought he overthought it. I
Always overthink those and go wait a minute. I wanted to click it quick
But then I realized if I did I was my games bugged and it's picking the wrong answer. I don't know what's happening
Oh
No, did you get something like what did you get a little bit of liquid or water on your iPad and you like kind
Of you can't press anybody. Yeah, I know that sucks, dude. I'm in rice right now. I'm trying to fix it
It's not his shape and it's not his smell though that is offensive in its own right
Oh, I know what it is. It's his color that particular shade of yellow is just weird
Mean
Yo, he got w'd
Damn it. If I had that I would have been back
Yeah poke. I've done it like five times and I'll just didn't answer a question
I don't know. This is boy. I got this. This can't be hard
Literature. Oh, it's literature, ma'am
This ancient sports ball was discovered recently by the archaeological team
We've chased away so that we could build our new studio on their dig site. It's even official size
I
Have a fence that needs painting, but I can't be bothered to do it myself
Which character from classic American literature could I go to for advice on how to scam others into doing it for me? I
Don't know I think that's accurate. Sure. Whatever. Yep. Thank God
Yeah, I don't know why the whole time he was reading it
I was like, dude, that's Huckleberry Finn and then I saw Tom Sawyer and I was like, no, it's Tom Sawyer
But then I felt like I was lying to myself. That's the only one that made sense to me. I just recognized Tom Sawyer. Yeah
true
Like I admitted I was wrong if I chose the right answer. How many rounds are there? I think
What is the most common word used in the English language easy, hey, I just used it in that sentence. Oh
I just messed up. I think it's his Oh
Oh
Yeah, I know you pressed what right?
I'm so dumb. Oh balls in my court. I thought that is was gonna though is gonna be come back
I come back here though
Fuck are you asking me what I don't know. I think that's wrong
He's covering my answer. I don't even know if I got it right power of music music. What is that from?
I'm mad. I would eat this banana
Your banana enjoyer right stir
Yeah, I've got a full bundle right in my kitchen I'm ready to go. Oh, what's your favorite fruit?
Did you just get it you just gonna void it
Hmm. Did he answer? Yeah. Oh, that's
He said a watermelon. Oh
Yes a watermelon
That was gone. That was fun. I was gonna say cute and fun together
That was cool for roblox is pretty cool
Um, I think I won you did win. Well, that was fun. Oh look at these are all of our fans
That was fun. We'll try an item thingy where you just get random items and chew each other. Yeah
I've linked it. Thanks for playing. All right. It's a fun game. Will you shoot you just get random over-the-top?
allowed items cool
Epic is this a private or is this a
Don't we just link in your chat? Oh, I just like the one that you linked. Is that the right one? Yeah
It says I'm not old enough to play this yeah, I'm also not old enough to play wait really
Yeah, so your account is not old enough to do this
Yeah, I think it's maybe our accounts are too new
Yeah, that's what not old enough means is our accounts are too new
Interesting, okay. Okay. Never mind
What what constitutes a not new account like a week? We're too young. I'm on you shake your job
Next we got should you next bots or you just run away from?
Gary
Yeah
I'm down for anything. This is fun. Wait, what are we doing? There was there's the squid game people wanted to see. Oh, that's right
We could do that. Oh, we could do that too. Let's do this one first. Yeah, I'll link
I'll get that one ready for us. Okay
Waiting for an available server. It's loading for me. Oh, it's in now. Are you all going in sir? Yeah, I'm in
Oh, yeah, I'm in. Oh, man
Put in oh shoot. I'm in
Just oh my all right. There you are. Oh man. I'm in
Yo, yeah
Oh
Am I am I my outfit or my man? Yeah, I know you those shoes look great. You're looking sick
Oh, thanks guys run hide team up do whatever it takes to survive. So we just have to run away from the monster
All right, I guess falling Easter
Is there actually there is be hopping
You'll see why okay, where are we running from what are we evading maybe it hasn't started yet
Maybe we gotta start it. Oh
Somebody's dead. Oh something's coming out of the ground. Okay, it's a lobster
Doing what is carried? Oh
Somebody's to revive me
Somebody save me for 15 real robux. I just respawned myself. I I don't know what's going on. Oh wait
Like somebody in the other room
Screaming. Oh, come on
Yeah, can somebody revive me? I'll try. I don't think you can where'd you where'd you die?
Yeah, okay, I'll try
Dude why'd you fucking kill me dude, I don't know cuz it was my birthday man
Is that me screaming? Can somebody please tell me it's a giant picture of you. Yes chasing people. That's me screaming
Yeah
You are the thing killing people. When have I ever made this fucking sound? I've never made these noises
I don't settle do this. Do I do this? What have I made that sound effect ever?
Yeah, he does that you bet you didn't see it no, I saw I saw like the
Picture, but I heard the I heard the sound
So are we oh sure I shouldn't exit them
No, did you exit? No. Oh, that was perfect. Who's got the uh, who's got the snoring thing?
Huh, you don't hear the
Whoa someone's playing music says dancing
All right
Now that I know my at like
2017 haunting images is actually haunting me now in a game. I'm prepared
Yeah, you it's doing the mini century sound how many children have died to you?
Think about how many how many children children have I haunt
Years when they grow up a bit and they see you walking towards them on the floor
Even if they don't grow up, they just actually see you in public like walking towards them and you're probably like mumbling to yourself
As you do
All right. Are we ready real life? Oh, we're good to go
Yeah, we're in it, right? I don't know how it starts. I think it's that I had to cook leaderboards then exit
Yes. Oh, yeah, you do. Yeah, you're actually just standing there. Yeah, I was gonna say I had the same problem
I'm not I don't I that's how I died last time. Oh
shit
Have you never seen that video of the guys singing
God, oh they're coming over here. I need a resume near the fire pit you died at before. Oh, it's right behind me
Right here. Oh, I got you. It's coming
I
Feel like I'm I feel like I'm inside of a tick-tock video. Do you know what I mean?
I feel like I'm inside of one. I'm downed you have to see that video
future
Our image that oh no
That was so weird. I think there's a bunch of random monster images and the fact that we got you first is like
Perfect. Oh, no, help us. Help us. No, I think this person goes throw me into the pit
I think that's what's going on here. Are you gonna throw me into the pit? Oh, okay. You were saving me. Thank you
Oh, oh, that was it. My gosh. I would let's do one more of these
How do we do new map menu press M and go menu? I think we could vote a new map or something
I think so. Oh, never mind
Other modes is it you have this equipment what I don't think I have anything should we vote for something else or just go play
Special round. What does that say? Are you guys still in that same game? Yeah, are you not I just joined it again
Yeah, it said it was nearly invisible. Oh
God again, it's Squidward
Which is dying in this
That's what you want even get back here. He's really big. Oh, it's the little cat. Ah
Get away shit first or help. Oh, that wasn't you
What just happened to this person what they just like Mortal Kombat died in front of me. What was that?
I think I'm the best at this in the world
What do you hide? He's too big. Yes. Thank you. Oh
What does that mean? I think we're good over here. I'm out here evading so pester. Okay
What are you near for find me? Watch out Squidward play adopt and raise a cute baby, please. Oh
God. Oh, I
Jump into that. Oh god. Oh
Our one friend that was here to help us. Oh
Oh
The cat Elgato no
Should we play squid game sure Kevin link it's a spit game right now
Happy birthday linked it. I liked it. It's still a fresh cookie back there that I haven't eaten. Can we get a bite?
Yeah, I'll save it. No, I mean, could you get it? Can you bite? Oh, you want me to take a bite?
Um after we play squid game, okay, I'll take a bite of the birthday cookie
Random all right squid game
Yeah, you can link it wherever should we do classic random or endless I did a random I clicked random as well
I love how they they let you
There you're in like the green jumpsuit, but they let you keep all your goofy accessories still the robot
What is going on with this person? It's three people. I'm so
Ready, this is such a weird avatar. It's why is it three people do we have to do teams?
We're all all right. It's it's it's uh, thanks for playing PewDiePie
Welcome to the block jacksepticeye. It's so many people
They're all gonna die. It's red light green light first, right?
The other will the wheelchair where we're good. We're good a VIP server owner gets to decide everything
Oh wait, you get assigned. Okay, there's a five percent chance to be a guard
I think I said, what did you guys get anything? I got a player. I became a guard. I'm on the ground
He's already dead. Oh
Okay, I heard the gunshot. Oh, no, it's the all right. This person's pushing me and that that's it. That's illegal. It doesn't count
Who is shooting people, yeah
Did anybody die check out this up skirt? Did somebody die? I don't think I don't think anybody died
Why am I in the ground welcome to tag avoid the person who's the tagger with this tag is there sound effects
I just hear a gun just read and bull it all the time. Who's it cool guy 43?
Oh shit, that's not you can get tags and then you read tags
So I think if you end while you're how do I play then they bring you into the the death chamber am I?
Don't get tagged. I can't hit people with the tag awesome cool guy. Come here. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. Something just happened
Okay, do I not want the stick guys give the stick to somebody you don't want the stick you don't want it
Okay, stick is bad. Okay. All right. I got it. I got it. I got it
That's what make sure I want to make sure I make it all the way
What I like this strat? Everyone's at the top. How do you push? I'm gonna make it
I think I got it. All right, so I haven't paying I have not been paying any attention besides what I was just doing
So we lives it's I have no idea what's going on. It's time to rest
Forge Alliance with other players wait, can we kill each other? Okay. Oh at night you fight they said they remove
Everybody is fucking walking over to me
What what what what they said they removed the age limit for item asylum so that we could play it, okay
We'll do it after I don't all right. I'm gonna forge an alliance with them. I don't know
This person's trying to kill me. Someone's gotta die, right? I'm dead. Come on, man. Oh shit who killed you
What was his name? I don't hit a big head on I forget what his name was. I saw I'm sorry
I'm like no, I'm dead revive. Oh, it's pay $5. Do it. Can I I did it? I just did it. Yes
That guy works at roblox credit card Andy. Yeah. Well, I didn't I didn't have a credit card
So I'm dead
You remember that that famous scene in a squid game where the guy fucking he falls through the glass pane lands on the ground
Spoilers don't talk spoilers. What are you doing? And then he pays with his credit card and he's fine. Wait, I never watched it
You've never seen squid game. Yeah. Oh
You said that like it's not like a year or two old. Wait, what? Wait, wait, you've never seen the classic the classic
Netflix original squid game. I know it's crazy. Oh this one. All right, I'm safe. What did you what did you get?
I'm a guard so I don't do anything. Oh you're a lot of people who made it through this
Oh, this is the guy that killed me by the way. His name is like boys boys something
He's gonna he's gonna he's got a red head big red head on he came out with a baseball bat
Why did I just do that? I you will never be the first two or three people. I just like freaked out and went I got
Okay. All right. All right. All right. Sorry. I got my credit card out. Never mind
Started to make it all the way through being a guard sucks
Yeah was watch you just watch and shoot people yeah, and I paid for it too
Oh, you paid to be a guard to be a guard and all I do is watch you guys have fun. What's the point?
You get to watch there is there's the guy that attacked me right there. All right, that's fun
Oh fun. Do you poke? Do you want to do one with you get to actually be a player? Oh, I don't care
We can do the item map if you guys want. Yeah, I was that one. Okay. I was completely zoned out almost that whole game
All right. Yeah, I was it was a it was something squid game was really popular for ages
Ten and under they'll do an item asylum, right? Yeah, so they removed the the age thing
Or whatever it was it making us uh, you can't yeah
And then apparently they came over here to say that because I actually read my chap. Okay
Oh this different link, okay. Oh shit. I'm Lincoln your Chester. It rolled what?
Huh? All right. Where are we going? Yeah, they're doing fast
Map Oh a consuming ten bodies with smile grants the ability to merge you see your weapons in the bottom. Ooh, okay
Why is it team fortress sound effect because I'm swinging the spy
Huh? I'm already dead
What do I even do with a spoon?
Fire
Oh
I'm fucking rolling everybody right now
That was like ten kills in a row
Built different scrumptious beverage. Why am I hearing Seinfeld music?
Plan. Oh, wait a minute. I'm going stealth mode. Yeah
Shit, is there a leaderboard? I have a crazy combo
Oh
This is not even a fucking player get the fuck out of here. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no shit. Oh
You went down my build shit, what's the fuck silly guitar shit?
Somebody has a dollhouse
avatar
Huh? Huh? Oh that you have spawn protection, right? I can't even throw wait. No, I'm friend request. What I was clicking the top
I
Keep thinking these are people in voice chat. It's a YouTube poop video
Shit, I just it's like a speedrun to figure out what you're what you're even doing
I'm good. What is this? That scared the fucking living shit out of me
This would pipes I just took a med kit
Oh
It's pie said I what is his name? No, I'm gonna get you my combo
Come here, Jerma
I thought that was a giant thumb. Oh
Yeah, all right. All right. Well, that was fun. Oh, yeah new game
They actually was fun. All right. What one more one more minute. All right, let's think of the last one
What's literally one more minute?
What is the good last game to show them? Well, yeah, what's it? What's it good? What's a good one to go out on?
Oh, what's up? What do you like? You want to like a drip contest where you just look at their drip? Yeah, that sounds awesome
Okay, that sounds so good
Do natural disaster try joining you on that?
Try joining you on that
Friends
That was a good one. It's kind of like like crack, but it was cool. Yeah, that's fun
All right. So this is a drip contest or no, you're just uh, just come look fast
Fashion show. Okay, if you get in the map guys go in the back go in the back
So we don't don't try not to look at anybody, right? Yeah, just me and you come here. Just look away
Okay, if you guys get in follow me
Contendants, okay. What's the word? Oh, this is like a very long time. This is your map. Okay, cool. Oh, this is fun
Yeah, if you were made it for me, it's really cool. Well, I want to see anybody's drip. No, I want to see you drip
I don't want to see it. I want to see it. Yeah, the spoiler. Oh, these are Goku's pants, by the way
All right, sir. Come in and sit. I'm poke. I'm XTC guys
If you're not guys go in the back here to come out one by one and show off your outfit to us
Yeah, if you're not behaving you're gonna get kicked. You're gonna get banned
You're gonna get banned from all of roblox. All of your robux are gonna go back into your parents bank account. This is real
I'm just looking at empty space. You can come in you can come in go on the green door. Yeah
Alright, so we're gonna take a seat in the in the middle of the judge table in the middle of the judge table
You'll see it. I'm trying not to see anybody fashion check-in. I'm trying. I'm not looking at anybody. Okay, here we go
Is it inappropriate that someone in the default roblox outfit is judging people? Yeah, it's kind of fucked up
But it's fine. All right. Okay. Well you what is what is that?
I don't know what that is
Do you see this guy? Yeah, okay
You gotta get your name called. I line up in the back. Let's go work. Oh my god. They're all
All right. I'm looking at the chair. How are you ignoring it? I don't know. I have attention problems
All right, so who how are we gonna do this?
How do you talk when they have like this speech above their head?
I think you just like press slash or something. So we're gonna give these a scale of one to ten or one to five or
How does it work? I guess you just rate them. Okay, I'm trying to they're all scattered here sitting down
Okay. All right. We'll start from earth to guppy. You just got your seat and then you just
Go and then next guy goes come on line up guys line up from here on this line. Yeah, do it properly
Yes, sir. They're doing it. They're doing it line up back of there
You know, I'll tell you I probably would have given you an A
But I'm just saying you you gotta get name called you just lost a letter grid. He was the first guy actually. Oh, okay
Um, I like get a sexy part of my face like in these poses. Okay, I'm gonna just like VR chat
But I'm not about to get banned. Yeah, it's safe
Next next up we got grim guys. All right, I'm gonna I'm gonna get I'll give you an egg
Oh, wait, we were grading. I think so. Yeah. All right. Yep. Is that is that Wakanda? You're about to get banned
I can't see through your fucking kick the next guy norpers good. Get out of here. I can't do this guy
Oh, I like this one was this one small zombie. That was good. That was a solid a hell. Yeah, that was an a
Just like hit the microphone. All right, what we got? Oh, that's an a
Hmm everything poke I'm in the back trying to organize. Oh, you're organizing right? Right?
Uh, I'll get I'll give you a solid B on this one. What why do you lose the letter grade?
It's I just don't know Pokemon
Oh
Not because like it doesn't match in any way whatsoever and there's a different color scheme on every part of his body
I just don't know Pokemon. Okay, it's good. It really is good. It's very good. So like that's still a B. Okay, cool
Okay, next one. I like it. I like dance. Yes. Oh, it's this one
Distracting me. I
you get a
You can fly that's at least worth a B plus that's an a that's a B plus for me
That's what I didn't overdo it, you know, nice fashionable didn't go too crazy, you know restraint restraints important. Very good. Yeah, that's an a
Oh, look at this person. Oh, I'd let them milk me. You know what I'm saying. What are you talking?
What are you doing? I'm coming out here bus and look at that dance. What are you doing?
You fucking so weird. Okay. All right
This I like the head like the headphones rate it rate it I have to look
I like the necklace the detail the details incredible. I'm gonna give this one up. I'm gonna give this and
Let's be stir the server server wrong with this fucking guy. He's got I'm downgrading to a B. He's got one move
Oh that well actually hold on a minute. You have to pay for those. So I'm not taking points off
That's a better be excellent. Keep it going guys moving on. Yeah, we gotta keep going
Wilson number one go and then Titanfall
There's a thousand people in this
If you guys saw this back line it's insane
It's kind of weird but man, it looks like you've been in the gym
Like you've really been working on yourself like you've been through some hard place. This is an a this is a straight a for me
Mmm, I would have I would have preferred an original art piece for the Wario on the chest
I'm gonna give this an a- by the way
I hope you're all ready to be here for about 16 to 17 hours because that's how long it's gonna take to go through
Seven or eight thousand people
Okay, turn the phone next listen you guys get when you get up there you get about like 10 seconds
I want to say finish rating you just move on and
Make this capacity. Oh my god. Is that Kratos? Okay, that looks really like authentic
What is the pic? I don't know who's on the shirt was in the shirt
We thought I can't tell I it's a guy. It's like I'm warped. He's got bees on he's got bees on his uh on his
Elbows, so I'm gonna go with a bee
It's stretched
Well, it doesn't say what does it say on your sleeve say F on your sleeve
I don't want to give you an F, but you got it on your sleeve
I'm gonna give you I'm gonna give you a B minus yo red up come up come sort the line in the back
I'm gonna start judging. I'm done. I'm done that close and give my seat. I
That's an F. We've seen that hat already
The other guy had that hat, but this is I feel like I feel like it's greatly diminished
I don't like to see repeats step a little closer, please. I want to see the dog. That's a B plus
No, that's that's an A as a B plus as a dog man. I like the spider so I give it a B
Yeah, but no drones in here next person someone needs to be the asshole
Someone needs to be the Simon XD. That's an A
The Disney XD
Diamond chain, that's an A. I want to I want to give it an A but the chain is pretty nice
Yeah, I'm giving you an A for the chain. Yeah, you got an A. You got an A minus. All right, who's next?
All right now come out
200 at a time. Yeah, just just line up out here guys. Everybody's gonna line up here. Does everybody come out?
All of you come out
Bored
Would we have ever done this that's that's an A but you know, it's amazing though, they all lined up perfectly Wow
They were all they were all organized and they're being great. Yo shout out to all these snipers. You guys did amazing
No, great work. All right. I'm gonna let's just real quick
I like the better call Saul. I don't know what goes into a king and avatar. So I don't know the
How do you you can make your character that big
It's funny. He's a monkey. All right, I'm gonna give I gotta give up my one and only s and I know exactly where it's going
I can't believe this is forty thousand people the person with the angry bird's face step forward over here
Please person with the angry bird's face. Where are you? Where's the person that they with the angry bird's face?
Oh, he's punching me. All right. Where's the angry bird's person? I don't know if they got an s
I don't know where they are. You know what you got an s2. I love it. I love the the screw about it
You can't just be handing out s's like that
You get an a you get an a because I mean when you that funny thing happened in one of the maps before
Oh this part you get an s ways. That's not a person poke
How many people can fit in one server? This is kind of crazy. I think like 100
It's not really lagging either. It's a kind of remarkable blocks is really good that stuff pretty cool
I'm I'm blocks. I'm out here. That's really cool. So I guess you guys you guys feel like you're done
Um, how do you how do you feel? I'm robloxed out your roblox time. No, that was fucking hilarious. That was awesome
Oh, there they are action-packed evening. Remember the cart game the trains. That's fun. No, that was a blast
That was actually a fucking fantastic time with doors. It's a great great time. Yeah
You talking about that
Basmophobia kind of game. Yeah, do you guys want to do that? I'll be so down we could play it whenever I mean what?
How are you guys feeling or you know, what's your what's your schedule like? What's your what's going on? My schedule is bad
So you can't play? Yeah, my schedule is bad
Why it's a party schedules bad? Oh, I have to take a bite of the cookie. Hold on. Let me get the cookie
I won't be able to hear you guys talk, but I'm gonna go
Examine some of the items I have on this desk over here. All right, I'm gonna wear pants, right?
I guess we're done. So then
But that's a yes birthday cookie. You didn't see plates. You didn't see plates. Look, I thought that was spongebob
Do you like your party? Did you like your birthday party? How was it? What do you say bro? What thing?
I'm not doing
All right, here it is. Here's a cookie. Uh, here you go. He's this that is stale. Okay. Sorry. I'm not taking another
There was a good there was like a cracker where he spoke you used to her we're just we're still go did he leave
Oh, I don't know. Am I oh, I'm muted talking myself. Hey, that was a ton of fun, dude
Thanks for helping out with that. I asked the XTC to play the scary the ghost game
No, really like right now. Yeah, I'm sure you'd be there right now
Oh, unless you're are you done if you're done, you're done. No, I mean, I'm still here for a little bit
I think I think this game is really funny. What is it called?
demonologist
Demonologist like I said, let me go pee too. Let me take a quick break. I'll get it and everything also if um
If I mean we can do it some of the time too. So if we if we can't do it today
I'm down. I'm down for rap. Literally. I'm I'm probably gonna keep streaming anyway, so
But we can do it whenever I'll be right back. I give me a sec. I'm gonna go refill my drink and
Wait, is Sturgis leave where the fuck did he go? I don't know. He's a fucking weird guy
Everybody's calling him the stirvert
He I'm going yeah. He's an absolute goddamn stirvert
I don't know. He kind of he kind of he kind of has a tendency to go over the line
And I do not condone him going over the line. I don't you were playing a kid's game. I
Actually really that was actually very fun. That was so fucking cool. You do not condone
Yeah, when I look over at him and he's like talks about you know, I'm not gonna say it
Yeah, I don't even just say anything. All right, I'll see you in a minute. Oh, I just said I don't condone me
You know what I can't even say it I don't say it you I don't want to yeah
Get out of here get out here you I you left I looked over at you
You told me that you said a weird thing about me. You know what? I mean, it can't I'm not repeating it
I'm out of here. I was just fucking with you. Are we talking? Yeah, okay
No, no, no, listen. Listen, it started with an M and it and then and then it was four letters and I'm I now
I'm leaving I'll see you later
All right, get out of here. Well, I'm still I'm still playing. I'm still screaming
Oh, they can't even hear you. Oh shit. Sorry. No, I was wondering I okay
Oh my god, they literally can't even hear you. Yeah, we've been talking. That's funny. All right
Well, okay, everybody thought it was a hot mic. No, I'm talking on
Poke stream too. No, I know poke stopped streaming
Oh my stream then I rated poke and poke was already gone and then people were in my chat like drama is dissing you
He's doing a diss track right now
I was like what what's going on? And then I saw that you're gonna go pee and I don't know
I I don't know man. Oh, so I wouldn't be RV on mine and it looked like this was a hot mic scenario
That's funny. And and this is all because I said something about 2% milk in that category
Sturi if you apparently owe the mods hazard pay hazard
All right, all right, I have to go pee wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
I just want to say you know what I'm getting diss track
I just want to say me and Jerma planned a whole bunch of games to play together and we were gonna do some fun stuff
And then one guy in his chat says oh
Okay, it's my birthday on
Wednesday, can we do a roblox birthday? Oh, yeah, fuck everything. I was planning with stir
We're doing roblox for your birthday. You're gonna deny the birthday party. How dare you so if I have to say something about milking someone one time
I'm owed that I
Felt tension. I
I'm not even streaming. I spit water all over my desk. My whole monitor is covered
I have never done like an actual spit take in real life. That was so much water
Fuck stir. Can you say happy birthday, please?
I don't know who I don't know who it is. Neither do I
All right, I actually have to go BRB, okay, but what are you doing you come back? I don't know focus um
We still hasn't pissed. Yeah, I have to go pee. Okay. Okay, but what's the plan?
Are we um, are we gonna keep playing or something or are we saying I'll go for whatever?
Uh, I don't think he uh, I think he but I don't know if he's playing but I'm not a play three of us
If you guys want yeah, I mean if I could I gotta go. Well, yeah, well the other time no late nights
You guys are late night. We are late night Andy's I can't I gotta go put the kid to bed. I'll see you guys
Yeah, no, thanks for playing stir. Well, he has a kid. No, I
Have no idea
All right, I'll be uh, yeah
we can set something up I can just pivot to like I was gonna play Breath of the Wild or something if
If there's something else you want to play we could just play something right now if you wanted to I mean if not
I could play BOTW
Okay, hold on since we don't have a crew for the scary game we should save save it for another time
Yeah, and you enjoy Breath of the Wild. That sounds awesome. Hey, I had a lot of fun. No poke that honestly that was fucking awesome
Thanks, dude. Thanks for like helping do that because I had no idea what the hell I was doing. So it was a lot of fun
Thanks, dude. I had a lot of fun man. See you bro. Good to see you. Bye. Bye. All right time to go pee now
I'll be right back. See you in two minutes