Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with some Smite.
This is supposed to be the Ares breakdown video, but the reason why it's not here right now is because Ares just got a major change in the most recent patch for Smite.
And all the footage I had recorded was before the massive change.
So before I, of course, do a breakdown video on Ares and all of his moves and how I play him,
it would probably be better to record some new footage with the big changes.
So that's why you're not going to see that. It'll probably be there next week, next Sunday.
But in the meantime, I'm going to bring you a live commentary.
This is just going to be some stupid goofy highlights of me and Spoonerism playing the game.
And I'll let it speak for itself. Hopefully you enjoy the clips I've thrown together here, guys.
And I'll see you all next time. And of course, take care, everybody.
F3. Oh, I'm low on health.
Once I get this ultimate. Oh, Neath is shooting me with her freaking ultimate.
Ah, what the fuck? Oh, it interrupted my ultimate.
Are you OK? Neath shot an ulti over here. Is that why I died?
Yeah, she shot. Did she shoot me or you? I think she shot you. I think she shot me. Yeah, I think she shot you.
Go ahead. Where are they? Use it right now. Get this Q open. Bang. Oh, I'm crippled. Good. Good, good, good.
Damn it. I didn't have enough mana. Oh, this Kali is chasing you. This Kali is going nuts.
Shit, no. You'll be OK. Oh, I missed. Ah, shit. I didn't buy Aegis. Oh, man. I just got ultied by Neath in the mid.
Oh, Neath, bitch. Oh, what? Neath. Yeah, if I didn't miss that too, I probably would have killed that Kali as well.
But then I got ultied by freaking Neath. If I had mana, I would have killed Kali.
Ah, sorry. We're good. Yeah, she's a bitch. No, no, I didn't want to say that.
God damn it. I have to like right cancel. Yeah. Me and my like fat fingers.
All right. Look at this. Neath has like two traps over here. Oh, what a fucking jerk. Do you see that on the ground?
Yeah. I thought I got him. Careful. Fall back. Oh, no, I almost got Kali. Come on, Kali, I'm almost dead.
Oh, I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. Fuck. All right, we're killing this Cupid right now.
I don't have any mana. Yeah. Yeah, get him. You're not getting away, Cupid. Not this time. Not this time. This time.
You are getting away this time. Go, you.
I have no mana. I gotta get out of here. Come on. I gotta get these call. He's all healed up now.
Oh, put a friggin stick in my eye. Oh, shit. Shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit, shit.
We're going to donate it over here. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
We're doing so bad. Cupid. Cupid. You're dead. Oh, now I'm dead. Oh, no. Die.
No Neath fuck you Neath. Oh wow they got our other tower
This Neath keeps shooting me with her ultimate. I have to go back again
Neath is such a piece of crap. We have no towers
There's no more safe zone
This is so funny. Two man gank mid. Where is he?
All right, you ready? Use your ultimate. Let's get her
Oh yeah
That's what we're gonna have to do this like all day
Actually, let's try get this tower. Oh keep it. Keep it behind. Keep it behind. Oh they're both here. Oh
Lord, come here you. Oh, I didn't use my ultimate. Now you're dead
Shit, I gotta get out of here. I have no mana. Oh
Bitch and happening get me out of here. Now. You pissed me off when you pissed me off people die
Hmm fuck we have no towers. I know damn it
No run
Don't die man. Get out of here
Get the Washington get the Washington monument shoved in your face
Good alt good alt. Mute. Oh, he's going for a pull. Oh boy. Oh, I can't believe it
Shit no, this is cottage. Oh, he hit him. He got him with the ult. Oh
They're all so low. Let's get this tower. Damn it. Oh going in for it. I'm you know
Sorry, I got it. No, I didn't
Yeah, I use fucking ages. That was a good attempt. That was a good attempt. Let's go get the buffs
Okay, doesn't matter who gets them. You should get speed. Okay, will you get it? Yeah, my god
They're all right here
You're dead fuck oh
goodness, ah
I thought I was gonna get one person with that. Oh, it sucks. I'm sorry. Yeah, use it right now. Oh
Cupid no. No, see you later
Sprint. Oh
Where are you going? Sobeck?
Where are you going? Sobeck? Oh
No, you get away. He's not getting away. No, he's not I'm gonna hit him right. Yeah
Nice I got two assists nice job. You want to go nice? You want to go money?
You're outnumbered bitch. Oh
She's against the thing you can get this tower right now get her. Oh, you are so dead neat. Oh
Nice
Beautiful. That's it. They're all done. They're all down. Yeah that that lever really screwed him right here. This is a good game
You're still recording. Oh, yeah
Good. It's so funny. Like this is gonna be an interesting video cuz I like rage stopped recording
It's just like oh, never mind. All right. Do you best goat impression?
So this has been going on for so long that we have regressed to doing goat screams
Yeah, is that really what's happening right now? Yep
He's going in for a pull get ready to do a bunch of moves. Oh
Here we go. Nice butt cross with a double cheeseburger. Look at that
We just need no we just got to whack this thing a couple times. You know, just go in
I'm gonna take it with Aegis get rid of this friggin thing. Oh
I have no mana
There we got it. This is the end of the game right here. This is the end of the game
Just kill the minotaur do everything Neith if you hit me with that ultimate, I swear
It's alright. Sorry. It's gonna be game over here in a second
ultimate him
Yes
I don't care if I die. Yes
Where's my camera?
Holy shit, holy shit
That was a good game
I thought we were gonna lose that
Yeah, well, they did have they did have a lever there. So but regardless
We did it