Hey, what is going on guys? Jerma here again with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
This time we're on CP Junction, a map that not one person plays and oh my god a pyro!
He's dead. I got him. Don't worry. So anyways, this is on Junction with the demo night setup
using the Persian Persuader, the Splendid Screen, and the Alibaba's Wii booties.
I love saying that, by the way. That's my favorite item in the game to say.
Anyways, if you are unfamiliar with this particular game type, A and B are open to capture.
Red Team has to stop us from capturing these points. The only way for us to win the game is
if we capture A and B. That's the only time that C is going to open. So watch right here,
B is going to get captured and I'm going to club this guy in his mouth. So we cut B, A is now open.
Notice how C is still locked. You have to capture A and B before C even opens. Junction is also a
very close quarters map. All the action happens pretty much in these connecting hallways. It's
pretty chaotic. It can get really ridiculous, especially when more than five or six people
on each team are fighting in these hallways. Regardless of all of this, though, this is still
a very, very fun map. One that I highly recommend that you try at least once, maybe twice if you
have the wherewithal. But unfortunately, you're not going to find it in any server browser or any
popular server because nobody really plays this map on a rotation. So try and find it, though.
It's fun. Anyways, watch what happens here. I turn around, this scout is trying to kill me.
I'm doing some dodging and weaving and so is he, so it's very, very difficult, especially playing
Demo Knight. Second scout comes behind me, get out of my way, buddy. I get shot right in the face.
But that's what you want to do as a Demo Knight. Don't run yourself into trouble. If you noticed,
I was going into that room, trying to get a little bit of shielding there from the walls in the room,
coming out, trying to go to the side that he's not on, waiting for my charge and recharge.
Because remember, you can only melee somebody when you have this set on, so it's very difficult
to do anything. Once you have your charge depleted, you're a sitting duck and you have to hide or you
have to try and outmaneuver people to get a kill. Charging out here into nowhere, just trying to
find someone to kill, and this soldier blows himself up on me. I always think that's funny
when that happens because the shield blocks you from blast damage, it blocks you from pyro damage,
pyro damage, it blocks you from fire. What the hell am I talking about? So anyways,
get a couple of kills right there. I get on the point. Demo Man is securing this place
like a, not a boss, something else, something else that's not as cliche, like a porcupine.
So A is now captured, almost to completion. We have pretty much the entire team on it.
This is where stuff gets real. This is where it hits the fan for our team, I guess you could say.
You'll see what happens. They get a couple of sentry guns up on C, and as you know, as a demo
knight, there's nothing I can do about that, and the entire team just gets suppressed. You'll see,
we come around the corner over here, get the kill on the soldier, and then, okay, there's some
sentries over there, and then watch this. It really is just like the entire cavalry just came
around that side. So anyways, I get myself killed right here. I get shot by another scout,
which is pretty much the bane of the demo knight is a scout. A good scout will always kill you,
in my opinion. They can just cover so much more ground than you can, the movement speed increase
and all that. They are just very, very difficult to deal with. I've killed a few scouts in this
gameplay, and I'm about to kill another one, but the point still stands that they are very,
very hard to deal with as a demo knight. I jump down here, you'll see I get him. He's not really
paying attention to me, so that's kind of why I get the kill. He got a little too close trying
to run around me. I end up turning at the right time and getting the kill, and this is now the
point where we are totally screwed, and it's very evident that we can't do a damn thing.
Sentry right here on this side, and there's a sentry pointed down at this side too. So as a
demo knight, I'm kind of sitting here going, okay, there's nothing I can do. I can't do anything.
The only thing I can do is protect this area and spy check or protect the medics or something.
There's really nothing I can do, and as you see here, I don't really do a good job protecting
anybody. So when you get in a situation like this, it's a good idea to change loadouts or
just change your class completely, because there's really nothing you can do at this point,
especially on a map like this when there's a lot of sentries. Sentries, you can't do anything
against a sentry. If you're a demo knight, you might as well just go make a sandwich and eat it
or something, because you're not going to kill a sentry as a demo knight. Uber Pyro comes up here,
and I'm going to be okay, because like I said before, the shield protects you. I think it's
30 or 40% fire damage reduction, so I knew I was going to be okay from that, but that heavy medic
Pyro got not so much of a good outcome as I did. So at this point, I'm really considering,
okay, it's time to do something. I'm just going to kill myself. So I just run down here, try to
get one more kill, get myself killed. Time to change loadouts. I equipped the sticky launcher,
and the beauty of doing this, guys, is you still have the wee booties and the sword equipped. Now,
you don't get the benefits of being able to charge at people, and you don't really become
a melee-oriented class anymore, but the wee booties give you plus 25 extra health, so now
I'm at 200 health, and the Persian Persuader allows you to collect health as ammo, so if I
run over ammo, I'm going to heal myself. So you're pretty much a more stocky demo man,
and the only real thing you're losing is the grenade launcher. Most of your kills, most of
the damage, most of your buildings destroyed, they're going to be with the sticky launcher.
Now, some people are ridiculously good with the lock and load or with the regular grenade launcher,
but most of your kills as a demo man are going to happen with the sticky launcher.
Left side is now secure, as you saw. I killed every single building that was there in about
two seconds. Coming out here around the corner, I get ubered, and that second century is now
toast as well, and I kill about four people along with it. So here we go, bang, bang, bang.
Everyone's now going to come to the point. Medic goes down, pull out the sword just for funs and
giggles. Everybody now gets on the point. This scout does not pose much of a threat at all,
because I have a medic with me and I'm a demo man. So anyways, here comes the entire team.
Everyone's on the point. We win the game. Top fragging, probably because I just killed
six or seven buildings in 15 seconds. So thanks, everybody, so much for watching.
I really do appreciate it. Take care, everyone, and I'll see you all next time.