Alright, now you can hear me and the audio sucks and it's always gonna suck on German985's YouTube channel
And his twitch channel because he's too much of a fucking idiot to purchase a boom mic that could just hang down here
Off camera instead. He brought his goddamn desktop microphone all the fucking way all the way over here
But it's probably better than was last time if it's not then
Look at me because I can't fucking do anything about it
You all right, I can't like test this
Okay, you know, I'm like in like Looney Tunes
When like Bugs Bunny plays fucking tennis with himself. That's what I feel like I'm doing right now
Like I'm like, hey, can you hear me?
Blurry what I guess not blurry I can see it over there blurry what
No, I just made it darker it shouldn't be blurry
It's low resolution. What?
Am I streaming this in the wrong resolution?
No, it shouldn't be
What the fuck? What is this up wrong? It's a goddamn camera
What the fuck is it doing?
Computers. Computers suck. Don't even buy one
Wait, why is this? It's like broken
Like can you even see?
What the fuck is going on right now?
Come on. Hey
Can you hear me? My OBS just crashed
Hi, my name's German985
I just spent two hours
Trying to figure out what the fuck was wrong with my computer
He was crying
I uh
I have no idea what's going on
That's the honest to God truth
It looks like a deep thing
It looks like PS3 graphics
Let me just
Hey, you got something on your face
Any better? I just like wiped it
I wiped it off
Can you see?
Alright, here's the thing that makes no fucking sense
I'm going to level with me here
This is the same camera
This is the same computer
This is the same place
Less than 24 hours ago
What the fuck happened?
It doesn't make any sense
If it looks that weird
Give me one second
We're going to troubleshoot this together
Because I got news for you
I paid for this fucking spot
And I'm going to use it
What if I do this?
Oh fuck my leg
Hit the camera
You can see the refresh rate
Dude, 60 hertz
60 hertz refresh rate
What the fuck is this?
Can you see that?
That don't make no fucking sense
I'm looking at the preview
Right now
I'm looking at the preview in OBS
It's perfect
This shit is perfect on OBS
What the heck is happening here?
It's perfect on OBS
Dude, 30 fps
Does anyone remember
Those of you that were here the last time we did this
I streamed it in 60
To make sure we'd get the fast fucking movements
Right?
I didn't stream it in 30 last time
I shouldn't have to do that
I did 30, it was 30
What do you mean it was 30?
It was 30?
Don't fuck with me here
Wait, hold on
Hold on a second
Are you serious?
I gotta get to my computer
Wait
How is he blurry
Alright
Here's what I'm gonna do
We'll try this
I feel like I'm getting
Deja vu right now
Did I do this exact same thing
And go, oh this looks like shit
And then we did it in 1080 in 30
This is crazy?
This happened the last time
Is that what you're telling me?
It's in a twilight zone
I'll be right back