Okay, how you doing? Um, so I got it open here. Oh, there's no BRB music, shit. That's my bad.
Well, there will be BRB music in a second. Not my BRB music, but whatever BRB music you're about
to hear. Um, alright, I need to change the title, don't I? Where's Daffy? Um, what should I title?
I don't know anything about Miku. What do I title the game? Because I mean, it won by a fucking
landslide, so. Keep Where's Daffy? Where's Miku? Why would Daffy Duck be in this game? I'm gonna
be honest. I'm gonna put an honest title here, I think. I've never played a Miku game in my life.
How about I've never played a Miku game in my life. The VR one, that was not a Miku game,
that was um, Space Channel 5. That wasn't a Miku game. What is the name? What's the title of this?
Hatsune Miku. Colorful Stage. Project Diva Megamix. Megamix Plus. Project Diva Future Tone DX.
Project Diva Arcade Future Tone. What game do I have? Project Diva Megamix Plus. I think that's
the one, right? Okay, I've never played a Miku game in my life. We're about to find out how this
goes. Uh, let's, let's go for it. Should I use a controller or a mouse? I feel like controller,
probably. Is it a rhythm game? It's controller, okay. Um, I need to recapture this window. Okay,
can I put this in a, can I put this in a display full screen with frame? What does with frame mean?
Oh Jesus, that's not what I wanted to do, but whatever. Um, hold on, I need to re-add this.
Where is it? What do you mean, looking for game to capture? It's here. It's right there.
Oh my God. Okay, there we go. All right, what is, what is it? Full screen with frame? No frame.
What's that mean? I'm just going to do 1080. That was weird. All right, let's go. We're looking,
hold on, I'm trying to move this thing. Clean your camera lens. There's nothing on it. There's
nothing on it. It's fine. There's nothing on it. Okay, time for Miku, everybody. You ready? Put it
in the dishwasher. Put, put it in the dishwasher. Okay, let's go. Is this a good enough volume? You
want me to turn it up? This is really loud for me. All right, so what do I do? What do we want
me to do? What do I do? Rhythm game? Custom gallery online store options rhythm game, right?
So what do I, how do I play? Let the tutorial begin. Hold down the pause button. What? Wait,
what? What was that? I, I, what do I have to do? Here comes the B icon. Press the corresponding
button or key. What? Why is, what's with the left and right thing? Here comes the A icon.
That was perfect. Shut up. Left or right? That's, left is R. That's weird. I don't like that. That's
weird. That's freaking me out. Second. Are there any lyrics? Same time.
You know, God bless the bassist. He's got to be up there all night. Left and both right. Okay,
I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it.
When you see hold under a target, hold the button or key down to increase your score. Okay, you got
it. One, two, three, four. How long do I hold it for? As long as I want? Oh, all right.
This band, they're waiting for me to start the song and I'm just on stage like,
yeah, who's ready? It's like, geez, fucking hurry up, man. Like, let's go. When the rainbow icon
shows up, that's your chance to spice up the music video. It's like a midi version of this song.
Quack, quack, quack. What the fuck?
This is what? Am I going to get in trouble from streaming this audio?
This is literally just like songs. What? How is this wrong? It's B. What are you talking about?
Look. It's not wrong. What's happening? What's going on? What's going on? Look,
I don't understand what's fucking happening. It's wrong? What are you talking about? You
ignored the tutorial? No, I fucking didn't. The layout is set to the wrong controller.
What? It thinks B is A. It thinks A is B. What? I just did the tutorial with it set to the right
thing. What the fuck is it talking about? It's set to a Nintendo controller. What?
No, I don't want to customize Miku. I want to customize my fucking controller.
It was there? Where? What is all this? Y is Y. X is X. B is A.
What the fuck was this all about? I literally just did the tutorial with these settings.
I don't care. Okay, left is left. Right is left. No, right is right. Oh my god, dude.
Shut up. Shut this fucking music up. I don't, what's going on?
What? Multi press up plus left. What's happening? I'm so confused right now. Multi press up and left
is Y and X. Um, huh. Unbind these. Up plus down, Y, A. This wasn't in the goddamn tutorial, dude.
Can I leave now? I don't like that song anymore. Blackjack. Blackjack. Okay, let me see if I can
actually play the game. Here we go. That's a pretty good hand. I think the tambourine sound is fucking
with my head. I feel like I'm ruining the song. All this for one hand of Blackjack. There's like
three or four people at this table smoking cigarettes just like,
so did you, did you bust or what? I'm sick of this. Oh, dealer had 20. You all lose.
Try again. All right, how do I turn off the tambourine? How do I turn the tambourine off?
Button effects? Bell? Oh, okay. Woodblock? Let's try woodblock. Slide C. Wind chimes. Laser.
What's wrong? All right. Okay. All right. It's like too much stimulation. I have to get out of this.
Cat food. Butterfly? I never heard this fucking song before in my life.
How am I supposed to keep the rhythm if I never heard it? What the fuck?
Okay. Okay. Okay. All right. I didn't clear it, but like, I don't know the, I don't know how the song
goes the first time I've ever heard it. I can't sing the lyrics to something I've never heard.
Hey, dude, you got to keep the rhythm. You know how the song goes.
Like, I don't fuck. Oh, I've never heard it. What? Oh, thank you. Turn off the fucking tambourine.
Dude, I'm like in a front fucking row. Go Miku. All right, you're coming with us. Row it up. All
right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All
right. Stop. I'm going to try that again. I can't have two headphones in. I can hear this in my
sleep. One more time. One more time. All right. All right. No, turn off the... Go back to the song
list. Turn off... It's too hard. Get me out of here. No, I don't want to hear... How do I turn the song
off right now? I don't want to hear like... I just want to change the fucking button configs.
Miku, I'm such a big fan. I'm a fucking footpecker. How do I turn it off? How do I turn it off?
Options, not customization. Like that? All right, let's go. This is a bit too much for you,
don't you think? What the fuck? Here it comes. Here comes the chorus. Next game,
80% of you said to play this. You're going to have to fucking deal with the people in the chat that
made me play this. And by the way, it's stellar. You're almost 40. Play the banana song. First,
I need to fucking fix this. I feel like I've been stuck in a dream for the last 25 spray minutes.
Okay. Do you... No. How do I save this fucking changes? Oh my God. Thank goodness. Here we go.
Please play the banana one. Whoa, hold on a minute. All right. All right. All right. Let's go. All
right. That's so much better. I would go to a Miku concert. Do they serve alcohol at a Miku concert?
Like I would just get drunk and just like sit there and nod. Can you drink? Can you serve alcohol?
They don't? I feel like I'm talking over a vacuum cleaner. It's loud for me. Hopefully it's not this
loud for you. I would be pissed off because I would definitely have like a few too many, right? And be
pissed because I can't get up and dance. So I'd be just sitting there in the corner like this, just
like, I want to get up and dance so bad. This is a long song, isn't it? Somebody's leaning in now.
Dude, you good? You good? Yeah. Yep. Man, you get up and dance. No, no, no. No, I'm all right right here.
I'm cool. I'm cool right here. Dude, come on. Let's go. Let's go dance. Yeah. No, just you go.
I'll be there in a minute. You go. All right. How about dermatology?
Oh, that's cool. Do all the songs have their own kind of backgrounds? That's actually pretty cool.
I like this. All right. You guys know, I thought Miku was a real person until like a year and a
half ago. I thought it was a gorilla scenario. Here we go. I think I'm ready for hard. One more
time. One more time. Let's go. Important notice. Hatsune Miku. Alcohol consumption is prohibited
both inside the live venue and the exhibition hall. All right. Well, then all right. All right.
I don't need to. What's another good one? Let's do hard. That's a lot of songs. All right. Okay.
It's all right. Seven and a half difficulty, man. Are you serious? Oh, by the way, should I put,
this is like flashing lights in this. Should I put a warning? Probably should. I'll put a warning in.
Title. Warning. Flashing lights. Yeah, there's like really bright flashing colors and stuff.
All right. Hold on. I wasn't ready for that. Am I ready for hard? Do you think I can do hard?
Turn the difficulty down. Oh, shit. Too late. All right. Is this everybody's favorite song
of the whole game? Let's go. Let's get perfect. Oh, shit. The animal just hit. The animal just hit.
Oh, my God. That was fucking impossible. Lower difficulty. Maybe a little bit lower of difficult.
No, shit. All right. Hold on. I probably do it with one eye.
Oh, they turned it up. They like dialed it up. They turned it up. It was like,
I wasn't ready for it. Dude, your mic sucks. I know, man. This one sounds pretty good.
I can't fucking do those. Fuck you. Let's go. Did I win? It's really hard. It's really hard.
What's mega mix? What's the difference? I feel like this is going to be impossible. Start music
video. How do I do? I'm going to do the music video. All right, let's go. Oh, my eyelid. How
do I play? I'll do my own. I'll do my own rhythm game. Get me out of here. Where's the one that
goes... Where's that one? Holy shit. I just want to know. I'm just curious. An auctioneer.
I'm going to do a hundred bucks. I don't know if that's what you were saying. I don't know
what to do there. That's all of them. This is from Clayfighter. This is the Clayfighter solo.
The theme from Clayfighter. Oh, it's a good spastic controller. Settle down. No, I don't
want to retry it. This microphone keeps breaking my sound. What does it sound like? Can I hear?
Clip that. I want to see what that sounds like. The mic blew out. Why does the mic keep blowing
out, man? I want to see what it sounds like. The edible really did hit, huh? It was right at the
end of the song too. That clip is not available anymore. Did I get fucking shut down? It sounds
so fucked up. It's like, that's so funny. It sounds like such shit. It's very sudden, loud
movements. It just goes, no. Okay, let's keep going. That's actually kind of a good thing,
though, because when I scream like a little shithead, it cuts it off so you can't hear it.
It protects you from hearing me sound like a little shit. Okay, let's go back to the song list.
Okay, World is Mine and Po-Pi-Po. All right, World is Mine and Po-Pi-Po. There are 178 songs.
Po-Pi-Po? Oh, that's not it. Where's P? This one? Po-Pi-Po, Po-Pi-Po, Po-Pi-Po, Po-Pi-Po, Po-Pi-Po, Po-Pi-Po.
Wee. Wee. I'm gonna fucking lose.
Did I win? Oh my god. All right, the next one is, what was it called? Something? I keep getting,
I keep failing. 58%. The World is Mine, okay. World's End and Black Rock Shooter. I have to
at least get 60% on one of these on hard. You know what it is? I'm too good for normal and not
good enough for hard. Every rhythm game that has the button presses like this, it's always tricky for me.
Okay.
Hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it, hold it.
Hold it.
what the fuck did i fail again 54 fucking percent man oh i'm too good for normal too bad for
hard this should be an intermediate intermediate all right what's the name of that song that
goes where is it it's not here it's not an l where is it that's with an i where is it i need the dlc
it's not in the base game what that was the tutorial all right what's another one oh what
was it i did normal but whatever this is too easy see this is too easy but hard is too hard for me
be careful up there i wish i could watch the music video with you i'm too busy playing
cool oh shit this okay listen when they're on the i can't talk because there's a fucking song playing
okay when it says the buttons you need to press and they're like i my eyes have to go frog eyes
to see the button palms when the this what buttons do you press press these buttons together it's
like i have to go like this because they're on the very edges of the screen all right so are
they different songs oh there are different songs we got glow sticks now by the way rolling girl we
got glow sticks you want to use them go for it why do i feel like this is like what caffeine sounds
like in your bloodstream let's crank it let's crank it let's crank it whoa oh my god that just
punches she's going nuts she's punching shit she's punching the wall what was that she just smashed
her bare hand on a music stand that would hurt that would fucking hurt
it's so funny i i get i can half pay attention to the music video we're in a different location
fucking cross-eyed where are we now is it the kingdom hearts stairs
look at the kingdom hearts stairs that was pretty good i almost failed but that was a fun one
i like that one all right how about like how about five more
and then we're gonna do pac-man ten more all right we'll do ten more this is one
yeah
i'm so sweaty what are you saying it sounds like the tomodachi life voice oops
oh that 12 000 extra points 12 000 extra points that was interesting
how much don't you like i got rank did i get more songs do i unlock more stuff new all right nine
more that's it you melt down out there's melt is the right one it was the one you were just on
holy shit this one's fucking crazy all right i'm doing this one this one sounds like mice
are talking to each other
my eyes hurt i think i blew a blood vessel in my eye is it okay does it look all right no get
it away from me you get away that song was so intense all right what am i looking for
this one started over shut up this is not miku who is this is it all right this one's a little
more chill bonus pretty good combo i unplugged the mic for a second it's okay that was cool i
like that song i like the chorus that's a good course all right seven more and that's it and
we're gonna play pac-man please play magnet all right magnet kokoro new magnet then kokoro
we're gonna do it on hot we're gonna do magnet on hot see if i can even last
so
six more six more for this or five more for this one let's go
let's go oh i like the way this one starts i like the way this one starts
this uh this starts really good i thought i just fucked that up
fuck you oh it was mad that i did it wrong x and b is impossible to do it with one hand
i thought that was credits i was like did i beat the game what is it saying i have no idea what it
said i can't read it weekend girl love is war or weekend girl all right weekend girl alien alien
for fuck's sake all right alien alien and then weekend girl no weekend girl first a streamer's
choice sorry we're doing streamers choice it's this one i'm sorry i'm talking really loud it's
really i'm talking over it so loudly streamer's choice
did i win i'm running out of gas holy shit i just barely beat it i'm running out of gas on that one
all right what was the other one no not retry go back uh weekend weekend girl all right
this extra extreme how would you even do that that sounds impossible oh all right alien alien
am i gonna be able to do this one on hard this one's probably really hard i'll try
i did it that was intense quality commentary here by you dude um i'm sorry i'm sorry man
i can't talk when i'm getting laser beamed in the eyes by like a thousand inputs a second
i'm going to talk about my dunkin donas drive-through story while i'm fucking inhaling
5 000 inputs a second what do you want me to do i i got no funny story to tell you what i'm in
the middle of inhaling this shit oh right up all right well we have four more pick some good ones
because we're getting the end and we're gonna do pac-man the disappearance disappearance of
i just want to see what i'm just curious what extreme looks like i'm just curious
this failed failed failed yeah what about your youtube search history i don't i'm not doing
that right now what do you want me to do world end do triple baka triple baka disappearance right
extra extreme the disappearance is it in t it's not in the game here it is
cool
she's in my head she's inside my fucking head this is fucked this is fucked that's fucked
oh my god that's fucked all right give me another one what is it on normal i'm gonna do this on
normal because holy smokes oh super mario oh no i'm shitfaced at the concert no this is the
finale man you can't sleep during this this is the kind of this kind of this to me everybody in
the audience is just going like this just like shaking the fucking around like everybody just
fucking shaking nobody's even dancing to this a crowd of like a thousand people just shaking
here we go no there it comes everybody get ready to start shaking around start shaking
all right all right let's go
it's too much stimulation today i've had way too much stimulation today
yeah so is uh is your mom picking us up or are we gonna take an uber or something
i'm not putting glasses on the mmo wait even the finger all right the mmo rpg
addicts theme i'm doing the mmo rpg addicts theme ah fucking keyboard turning i'm failing this
i didn't get it i didn't get it fuck close could you do senbon all right three more
what's going on senbon do triple baka triple baka i don't see triple baka it's not here
six singers isn't gonna be hard stargaze stargazer okay
foreign
i figured the bathroom sadistic factory music all right two more let's go one more after this
you guys gonna make a count i have to build meter in the early game
go go go go go go go holy shit she's gonna come out she's gonna come out of the machine
fuck fuck that end that just i've barely screwed me up that end was so just screwed up it's it's
like one two one three one two one three one three one three one two one three one two one three one
three one three one two one three it's like i can see why people play these this is cool all right
last one where we going all right you know we're gonna do streamers choice i'm gonna find the one
i think is the best sounding which one just do random not a chance okay what do you want
luca luca i don't see luca luca oh let's do it this game's fun yeah all right one more
last one i wanted to see what this all right actually last one last one
one okay this one seems fun
get ready to puke the new take i need a breath i need a second that's so fucking much it's it's
like i feel like i'm gonna fucking throw up three two one oh i had it i got this one i lost it i lost
at the fucking very end i it's just like so many like i had it i shouldn't have paused the fucking
game never mind no i'm done never mind i'm done never mind i'm done i'm done i'm done all right
give me one more to go out on love is what freely tomorrow yeah i'm trying to find the one you're
talking about sand planet it's not here love is war all right this is the last one even if i lose
if i fail it don't matter we're going to pack pack man after this this one's not that bad
it's fun this feels like i'm watching germa sensory videos this is cool all right you know what
this is cool i will tell you i never played a vehicle game before but there's a lot here
this is cool i mean i don't really know any of the songs but you know what this seems like a lot of
content i had fun do customization oh shit that's right whoa yes i got 15 000 bucks all right which
one do i want to do wait there's more um uh pirate pirate and sonic the hedgehog different hairstyles
um punk hair
how do i put it on how do i wear it modules
oh change parts what change parts i don't get it oh yeah that's fun was the one that i said
sounded like hamster's talking what what's going on do rinse i don't get it what do you want me to
do what do you want me to do what do you want me to do it's the name of the song oh i i don't care
whatever i'm doing this on extreme what's the craziest song on here like i mean crazy
what's the craziest song sort by difficulty
this one
one
i'm done that's cool we're gonna move on to pac-man pac-man museum for like an hour or so
to wind down the screen hour or two i i think i'm all uh burnt out from flashing lights on the
screen this was cool though i don't know if i'll ever go back to it but it's fun i'll be right back
i'm gonna pee we're gonna do uh pac-man stuff see you in a minute brb i'll actually get music on
this time i promise