Hey. Sorry. Hi guys. What a great way to start. Make a lot of fucking gross noises. But hello.
Sorry, I was doing something that required my attention, but still started on time with that
2 p.m. Right before 2 1 58 exactly. I think it was. Don't have to stream for 24 hours,
because as you see, if you type in the new the new emote, I told you that when the stream started
today, if there wasn't that emote there, that I would have to do a 24 hour stream. But thankfully,
look at that. It's there. By the way, I don't know what to title this stream,
because what the hell else do you title this? We're gonna play Darkwood. It's October. There's
been a lot of requests to play this game. I don't know why. And this is scary. Is it weird? Is it
intense? I don't know. I have no idea. But what am I right? Just is Darkwood. Should I just
title the game the name MonkaS? No, that's so it's too easy. Hold on. Yeah, if you have any
horror game suggestions that I have not played, throw it in the recommended channel. I'll take
a look at them because it is October. So I mean, right. It's Darkwood. I was gonna write like into
the into the dark wood, but that's too easy to that's simple. Sometimes just has to be what
you're doing. Dead Rising. All right, let me make a tweet. I'll be back in like 40 minutes.
Just making a tweet. I see a lot of Yes, yes, this game is so good. Yes, this game is so good. Is
it really? Is it good? Am I okay? Am I gonna like this game? Or is this gonna be one of those
scenarios where I'm just like, I don't I don't fucking get it. I don't find that's just fucking
stupid. It's stupid. That fucking dumb game. I don't fucking like this. Find out. But yeah,
let's go. Enjoy the new emote. There's a couple of scenarios where you should be using it, by the
way. Really, I think only one or two scenarios where that emote makes any sense. One is,
if I taste or smell something gross on stream, or if you if you hear this sound,
this is pretty much the only reason why I would be on. You can't even hear this.
So if you hear a vacuum cleaner on stream, if it's in a game, what a perfect opportunity.
Or if I'm like, that's it. Don't use it anywhere else, or I'll get rid of it. All right, let's go.
Let's do Darkwood. Funny thing about this game, I actually downloaded this game a long time ago,
apparently, and have seven minutes of playtime in this game. I don't know how I don't know when
or why. Did I open it and go now? I mean, that's, that's as long as it is to do the
options in your video settings. Derma, don't do this. Turn on face cam. All right, if you're good.
Not a blind stream. Well, the menu is maybe not blind. Turn on cam. If you're good. All right,
play. What if I imagine I hit play, and I didn't know that you guys could see that there was a
save game that has like seven hours of playtime, and I've just been fucking lying that I never
played it. Thank God. That was close. There's like four different save slots, all with like
20 hours of game time. Face cam. You'll get if you go if you'll get a face cam if you're good.
Difficulty normal. The forgiving mode. When dying, you drop part of your equipment. No.
The unforgiving mode. You have a limited number of lives. After that, it's game over. No.
The ultimate thrill. Death is permanent. No. Oh, there's no easy. Indiegogo content. This option
enables additional cool but immersion breaking content. I don't want that. Does that mean like
Thomas the Tank Engine is going to be in the game and like draw like a like a mod or something? I
don't want that. Skip the prologue. No, don't skip the prologue. Normal difficulty. I don't want to
break my immersion. I'm going to get super locked into this. All right, you ready? You'll get this
if you're good. Why is it glitching out? All right, you'll get this if you're good. Is he wearing
Aquaman? Yep. All right, I gotta put I'm not putting both headphones in. You're playing a
challenging and unforgiving game. You will not be led by the hand. Respect the woods. Be patient
and focus. Okay, so backseating is allowed in this stream. Those of you that backseating is okay.
I'm going to give you a phrase. If I use this phrase, that means tell me the answer. Okay,
I'm going to look into the chat and I'm going to say please tell me the answer.
And that's all that needs to happen. Backseating is completely allowed. Like,
I encourage it actually. You're not going to read a challenging unforgiving game like that.
And then I don't know. I'm going to focus but I want the answers. I'm going to get them.
I don't even know what's on this coffee cup. Prologue. Quiet.
You've been good enough. You'll get the face cam for five minutes then it's going off.
I see hatred and fear in their eyes. As if I was responsible for spreading for the spreading
disease. Okay, there's an illness. There's a disease. There's a disease. As if I were
the source of all the misery plaguing this land. All right. I have nowhere to hide from them,
nowhere to run. The woods have closed us off from the outside world. Give me the solution to the
first puzzle. I want pre-backseat gaming. We are all doomed. So we just wrote go left.
Alcohol distiller. This is like Hotline Miami. Table. Search. Pill. You can have 30 pills.
Is this my inventory? Notepad. My old notepad. Examine it. Nothing interesting apparently
happening. Nothing on here. There's no secrets. There's no clues on here. Okay. Chair. Drag the
chair. All right. I'm going to block the door in case anybody comes in. All right. Alcohol distiller.
A homemade device for producing moonshine. The audio is too low. Is the audio too low?
Hold on. Let me help you out here. That's probably better. How's that? Better? I think so.
A homemade device for producing moonshine. Okay. I don't have any moonshine. That's my health bar
and my stamina bar. Do it louder than this. Yeah, but it's a scary game. I don't want it to be that
loud. No, I know where it is. Apply these. Yeah. Hold on. Hold on. Everybody wants it to be loud
when like the monster jumps through the fucking window. I get it. There you go. There's your
immersion. It's going to be loud and scary. Okay. That's good. Somebody think of a title,
by the way, while I do this. Better? Wooden door open. Is there a sprint? There is. It takes,
what is that? It takes stamina. Barricaded window. Dismantling this now would be suicide.
All right. Okay. So this is a post-apocalyptic zombie world.
Potatoes. The only edible thing growing on this land. I still have some left.
What am I doing? What am I doing? What am I doing? What am I doing? Why am I tying my shoes?
Oh God. This generator is almost out of juice. I need to find a full gasoline can. I saw a broken
tractor to the east. Maybe I could find some gasoline there. Go left. Thanks for the tip.
Appreciate that. Nothing in the cages. This time they're empty. Nothing in the cage.
No, I just have some pills. Chair. What the fuck? My old zenith camera. Can I spin it around or
something? Can I take it with me? My old useless medical bag. It's a bag. It's not useless. Photo.
Oh, I see. There's like a, there's a ghost in this photo. 1985. All right. So did I take these
photos? I took this photo. All right. What about over here? I would rather not open it. I spent
too much time to lock him in there. I mean, lock who in there? But this guy I don't care about,
by the way. The guy in here. Container. The lock is jammed a long time ago. Never mind. I used to
keep useless junk in there anyways. Why do you have so much useless stuff? What's with all the
donuts? I don't know how to do that. How to do what? Him. Him. All right. Well, where's it gonna go?
I need to find a can of gasoline to the east. Locked. I think I left the key in the wardrobe.
Oh, come on. Where's the wardrobe? My tools. They haven't been sterilized for years. The
local patients can't be helped anyways. All right. So I can't use them. Where's the wardrobe?
This is not a wardrobe right here. Isn't this a wardrobe? How do I leave my house?
How do I leave the house? Locked. I think I left the key in the wardrobe. Oh, there's another room
here. You can only select and interact with objects within your reach. The interaction
range is indicated by the color-changing cursor. Color-changing cursor. Oh, okay. All right. Let's
look at the bed. Just woke up. Radio Unitra. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Look
more than an ass. Oh, the radio has been silent for years. Although sometimes I think it can
hear voices through the static. I guess. I don't know. Wardrobe. There we go. All right. I know
these notes by heart. I don't want to... What did it say? Quickly produced moonshine. Barely filtered.
So what does this do? Board. Matchstick. Rag. Key. Where'd it go? What? My medical book. I thought
that was a picture of... I thought that was a picture of me for a second. I don't know why I
thought it for one second. Okay. So this is some kind of illness that's been spreading.
Okay. Anything else in the book? All right. Hold on. Board. Matchstick. Can I like use the
board as a weapon? All right. I have the board selected so I can just like cross somebody in
the head with this, right? All right. Well, I got the key. Locked. I think I left the key in
the wardrobe. I have the key on me. How do I get in my inventory? The cursor has a plus icon next
to it. You can hold left mouse button to open the selected object's action menu. Got it. All right.
I'm ready. This is a dog. What do I do? Wait. Hammer. Can I use the hammer? Destroyed well.
Rope. This is a survival game. I don't have to survive in this game.
My 125p. It used to be a luxury, but since all the access roads have been devoured by the woods,
it became a useless pile of trash. The People's Tribune. Daily newspaper of the Polish People's
Republic. Okay. To Edward Geirich. Oh, this is not English. Something about the United States
right here. Anybody read Polish? I don't know what that says. Deduced. My dog. I don't think
he's going to make it. I should end his suffering. No! No, not the dog. Immediately you're going to
throw the dog at me. I don't know what to do. How? Wooden doll. A large humanoid dog with a carved
out face. Okay. That was like loud. I don't like this. Barricaded window. So what's the point?
What's over here? Do I actually have to walk through the dark woods? Is that the whole point?
I don't know what to do about the dog. I really don't know what to do. For a space to vault over
obstacles like fences or windows. It's the title. You said the title. Can I like alcohol? No. Like
I can't. I don't know what to do. Oh, it's actually you actually have to vault. Okay.
I got to put both headphones in for this because people are going to scream at me.
All right. Go east. Do I have a compass? I got an axe. All right. Axe. A formidable weapon. Oh,
sick. Okay. So you hold right, you hold right trigger and you get a cursor and you just
overhead swing into things. Do I cut down trees? I don't think so. All right. Go east. This is
south. Although I don't know which way I'm facing. So it could be, it could be anything.
Dog, dog, dog, dog. Oh, I don't want to do this though. Oh, I'm sorry. Be at peace.
I missed. I'm sorry. Be at peace. Oh my God. I can't even do it. I'm sorry. Be at peace.
I'm not doing a very good job. This is fucking embarrassing. My dog. I don't think he's gonna
make it. I should end his suffering. I don't know how to do that. What do you mean you don't know
how to do that? I left click dog. My dog. Middle mouse. I don't know how to do that. Right click.
He won't swing. No, this is not an all right scenario. This is a horrible scenario.
Uh, Freddie Dredd just gave 10,000 bits. Here's some bits for your boy. Thank you for streaming.
Then left click. I don't like this game. All right. So I don't like this game. I'm gonna do
the coloring book instead. Uh, but thank you, Freddie Dredd for the 10,000 bits. Really appreciate
it. So it's not hold and let go. It's hold and then left click. And then Clown Daddy just gave
five community subs. Thank you for the five community subs. Appreciate it. With a weapon
selected in your hot. I just had to walk five feet. Uh, with a weapon in your hot bar,
hold right mouse button to take aim, then press left while aiming to attack. Okay. Sure. Right.
Tree. Knock down the tree. Loud. Too loud. I don't like how loud this is. All right. These trees are
growing too fast. Soon. I won't be able to cut them down fast enough. Bear trap. Pick it up.
Okay. Dead cow cow bone. Uh, all right. I got a cow bone. Does the weapons have, weapons have
durability. Look at that. It's already like almost done. What about up here? Left shift. What does
that say? Left shift? What left shift? Run location found path. What are you talking about? Location
found. All right. Where's East? I'm going East, right? I can hear shit behind me. What does that
mean? Is this the radio on silent hill? When you start to hear like the weird echoey music,
it means that there's something like a monster or something, right? I'm going to get ready.
To access the map, press M. This is like an, this is like a stomach and intestinal track.
This is where I am. Your position on the map is not marked. When you discover a new location,
it will be added to your map. The location you are currently in is indicated in red. In order not to
get lost, you need to learn how to determine your position relative to the discovered locations and
landmarks. All right, so I'm here. I got to go down. Oh, this is gonna be, I'm so glad I have
you guys here. I'm so happy you guys are here. You guys can help me. The woods have been, have
devoured all the roads that connected us to the outside world. No one is able to pass through this
thicket. Unless they had an axe, of course. I'm gonna, I've, I've drank like two cups of coffee
today. So I'm already really jumpy. Just to make sure everybody's aware of that. I'm so glad I have
a limiter on my mic now because like I'm gonna scream at some point probably. It's gonna be so
loud, but I have a limiter. What's this? Burns campfire. To immediately transfer items between
inventories, hold left control or left shift when clicking. Okay. Can I have, can I have more than
one rag? How many boards can I have? Seven. How many matches can I have? 21. How many rags can I
have in one stack? Five. What do I do with these though? Should I go up? Wait, where am I? Okay,
I'm here. There's an up, wait, check down here. What's that? Oh, there's light over there. Happy
Halloween, by the way, guys. Do a tuber voice. Why would I do a tuber voice right now? These parts
of the woods are dark. I should craft a torch. Tab is your, this wasn't here before. Uh, crafting
torch. You have seven boards. You need one, one, one. It's okay. Craft a torch. How many should I
make? Should I make one in one? What's a super torch? Oh, this is a gasoline torch. Okay.
All right. So I have, okay. So did, okay. I can, all right. You can swing this. Oh, for the love
of God. I have to switch weapons. Can I kill people with the torch? I hope so. Where am I?
I don't know. Up. I have to go up. Abandoned house. Where is the house? Where's the, oh,
it's right here. There's a wall here. All right. I got to be ready. I got ready to burn a motherfucker.
No, don't barricade this door. Go in. Should I be going, should I go in here?
Chair. Wardrobe. Oh shit. There's rags in here. Nice. Bread. I'm out of space.
Rag. Should I make, I'm going to make some more torches. I think that's what I'm going to do.
Right? Yeah. How long does this last? Matchstick torch. Torch. Can I stack them?
I can't stack the torches. What about bone? They last for 20 minutes. All right. What about the
pills? What about the board? Turn the lights on. This is post-apocalyptic world. There's no lights.
I kind of want to take this stuff though. Rag. Bread. I need to take this bread. Why am I saying
so fucking strangely? Bread. Bread. Bread. Rope torch. Should I just eat the bread? I'm dying
right now. Why do I have health? How do I eat it? Your lungs are more efficient because you ate
bread. What? Did I inhale it? How do you save the game? Is there a save? Okay. There's somebody
like out here. Hit the X. I get the fuck out of here. All right. I'm out. I got, I ate the bread.
That means I'm not hungry anymore. Is there a save? There's no save. All right. Where the fuck
am I? All right. There's the house. I got to go right. Can I vault? Can I climb this? I don't
think I can climb that. Can I go through here? You can only save at a cooking station. All right. Up
maybe. Over here. Because I came from this way though. I'm already lost in the woods. I have no
idea where I'm going. All right. This thing's going to get up. In a few days it will be completely
absorbed. Absorbed into what? Clothes. Fucking rags. I don't, I don't know. I don't want it to,
I don't know what to do with the rags. Clothes. Searched. Yep. More rags. There's a deer over here
or an elk or a moose. I don't know. Whatever this is supposed to be. Ah, I hate it. Clothes. Rags. I
don't need rags. My medical bag? It's useless. So it's worth, but it's worth a hundred bucks.
I don't understand. Why is it worth so much money? Who do you sell stuff to in this game?
All right. Made it through this. I haven't been in here though. Doorway. Repair. Search these clothes.
More rags. I don't, I wish there would be more than five stacks. A bottle? An empty glass bottle?
I don't think I need this stuff. More rags. What am I going to do with these rags? They're coming.
Who's coming? No one's coming. Don't say that. Don't say they're coming. So I gotta go up.
All right. Slow down. I can't run that. All right. Guy. Guy over here. Do I have to put this, put this
guy at peace too? I probably, I'm walking over with an axe, but still. I think this one is still
breathing. Be at peace. Can I talk? Big metal key. If there is an exit out of these woods, this key
will surely open it. Number 21. He's unconscious. I've never seen him around here before. It's me.
It's gonna be me. He's only carrying a key and some journal. Since he managed to sneak in here,
he must know how to get out. Of course he won't help me voluntarily. So wrench. That is of no
importance. I need to get out of this accursed forest. You hear me? Rat! Where's the rat? Show
me how and I will let you go. I sometimes hear her voice. She's calling me. Calling me to return
home. Where is the exit? Am I interrogating this person? Where's the exit? Show me where. I don't
even know if, for all I know this could be just some person that just like went wandering in the
woods. Hey! I'll kill you like a dog if I have to. So I'm the bad, I'm the bad guy. What if you don't
kill the dog? I'm the, I knew I was the bad guy and now I'm this guy. Yep. And now I gotta kill me
who was me in the tutorial. You got it. That fucker stole my key. And enter into a small cell and
maybe the pantry. Let's get in. Use the lockpick. I have lockpick. Search. I couldn't open it with a
lockpick. I could open it with a lockpick. Okay. Crafting. I can make a lockpick. How do I make a
lockpick? One lockpick is two lockpicks. What? Why would two lockpicks make one lockpick?
Needs two, oh, it's like wire. Oh, that's not what it, okay. All right. Hey, uh, hey, my stomach
hurts. I'm gonna puke in here, man. Fucking best way to do it. All right. Let's see what else we got.
The barricade's too strong. All right. Easy. Let's make that lockpick and get out of here.
Neat. Okay. Lockpick. I can always make gauze. Heals wounds. All right. Let's use that. Nice
tutorial. Teach me how to use gauze. Okay. So use gauze. You, okay. Use. Using it. All right.
Lockpick. Let's do it. Unlocked. What's in the container? A shovel. It's heavy, but it has good
reach and a flashlight. All right. So I got to bash this guy's head in with the shovel.
It's too strong to dismantle. So just smash it down. All right. Does he hear that?
The item is no longer usable. Okay. I'm out. Wait, he was right in front of me. He was literally
right there. Okay. It took me so long to register that he was standing there. Holy shit. My, like,
pee brain. That's supposed to scare you immediately. And it took me, syringe. Fuck. Can I hit him with
the flashlight? I better not leave the house at night. It's safer here. Is this just a series of
taking the house from the person who squatted in the house before you?
What the fuck is this guy? Lamp. Turn the lamp on. Turn it on. How many batteries are in this
flashlight? Oh, there's a code. Please let me out. What? There's other people in here. All right.
Hold on. What is that? Is it a bomb? I think it's a bomb. All right. Don't touch this. It's a bomb.
That's a bomb. That's a bomb. Right? Stuff doesn't blink red unless it's a bomb.
Dismantle the bomb. Turn. All right. It's not a bomb. It's a radio. No, it's a bomb. Right?
Why is it connected over here? How do I get the fucking thing open? What about over here? This is
connected to this. Lamp on. Search the... What's going on? Can I punch? This is the... The radio
needs to be dialed to like a certain frequency, right? And then the frequency will open the door.
Oh, that was fucking easy. All right. Watch out. Somebody in here? Somebody in there? There's like
a torture device in here. All right. Generator. Don't turn it on yet. That's going to activate
everything. Meal table. A meal table with leather belt strapped on. Metal table. A meal... A meal
table. What's in here? Why did everything turn off? This is going to be somebody in here. He's
going to be in this box. Okay. No, there's nobody in the box. It's just gasoline. Table leg. Use it
as a weapon. You got it. Uh, I'm going to keep the shovel though, just in case I need it. Fuck
out of here. I need the code. How do I get the code to let the other person out? Generator on.
Let's go. To refill the generator, click the gasoline tank. Cover your mouse over the generator.
Hold right mouse button, followed by the left mouse button to pour the gasoline. All right.
I'm going to smash this guy's head in. How much do I have to refill it? I have to refill it that
much. Incoming joke alert. Incoming joke alert. Oh man. I've been playing wow for like fucking
six hours. When am I going to get to 60? Everybody fucking laugh immediately at that hilarious
fucking wow reference. Yes. All right. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Actually pay attention.
Not funny. Didn't laugh. Yes, you fucking did. I saw it. I told you it was a bomb. The corpse
has two dials instead of eyes. His mouth is wide open and I can hear a distorted voice.
Barely distinguishable from the radio static. Turn on the generator. Turn on the generator.
Wait, it's not on. All right. He's going to get up. Right. I'm ready. I'm ready. Right. When he
comes up, this is going right in his head. The corpse has two dials. His mouth. I can hear it.
Barely just come from radio static. 4892. 4892. Okay. 4892. Got it. Who the fuck's in here?
Door seems stuck. I need to apply some force to it. Help me. You don't say come closer if you need
help. That's like what the witches and the fucking bad guys from Disney movies tell you.
I knew it. You fucking Disney witch. I didn't even know there was a corner there really. I just saw
it. Plastic chick. It's a bomb. This is a bomb. Oh, who's laughing? Right. And how do you will
want to get out now? You think you can man age all by yourself? Dot, dot, dot, dot, dot.
Hear it. Next motherfucker that comes near me is getting blocked in the fucking head. Who's in the
house? Somebody coming in the house right now. All right. I got to get out of the house, I think.
Did I lose? Or is that script? That's script. That was fucking terrifying. I hate fucking two
headphones. Now this is too loud. I have to drop this. It's too much. I was stretching the hand.
Leave the volume. No, it's too loud for me. It's too loud for you guys. Chapter one.
Don't do it or I'll leave. What? Don't turn the volume down a little bit so you'll leave?
Is this me again? All right. I have no stuff. Bandages with alcohol. Good for heavy wounds.
A pleasant worth is emanating from the oven. I can sense a strange yet familiar scent.
It's the smell of the protective substance, which gives me relative safety after dark.
The vapors rising from the huge cauldron are distributed all over the house via long pipes.
As long as I remain inside my hideout, I have a chance of surviving the night.
Examine the oven. Look at the weird bottle. Let's examine that. When I arrived here a couple days
ago, the oven was basically prepared. I just needed to light it up to ensure my safety at night.
This cottage must have been one of our hideouts. One of our hideouts. The inhabitants of these
woods don't need to inhale this revolting gas. Well, it's a weird bottle. The label on the bottle
says staying out of the reach of the protective substance after nightfall results in immediate
death in 99 out of 100 cases. It's advised to evenly spread the gas inside the sleeping area.
Okay, so you have to be in the gas. Warning! Even a properly prepared substance does not guarantee
100% safety. Remain vigilant. It is recommended to stay in well-lit indoor areas in order to
minimize the risk. So we need to have set up a stove that has gas coming out of it.
A small empty cast iron pot. I haven't used it yet. I haven't felt any hunger or thirst
since the accident a few days ago. I can't stop thinking about one thing. These mushrooms,
these red pulsating mushrooms, they look so tasty. Maybe this pot will prove useful after all.
Oven efficiency one. You just make a giant mushroom syringe? Holy shit. Okay, well, I don't
have anything. This is essence. Dose one. That's, oh, that's what you meant when you said cooking
saved the game. I see. All right, let's go. Turn the lamp on. I can't even turn anything. Wardrobe.
Nothing in there except there's a nail. Use that as a weapon. I don't think I can. Rag. And photo of
road. The road home. Wooden door. I think this is fairly safe in here, but I've been wrong. It's
okay. And cranky dog shit. Yesterday I barricaded one of the windows. If I want to stay for some
time, I should do the same with the other windows. Okay, done. Workbench. Repair. I know, man, this
is gonna get, this is gonna get nasty for me. Hotbar upgrade. So I get more slots. I need one
blanket and one wire. Board with nails. Antidote cures poison. Gas bottle. Okay. Upgrade workshop.
I need six boards. I need, okay. All right. Okay. Okay. Okay. Let's just hold on. I can't
board these up. Large mushrooms. Harvest them. Got it. Odd looking mushroom. Cookable. Okay.
All right. Y'all are gonna think I'm insane for doing this, but I'm gonna bind sprint to
one of my mouse buttons. I mean, I know y'all are gonna think I'm insane for doing that,
but I have to. Okay. Sprint. Run. Left shift. No. It's gonna be mouse button five.
That's a thousand times better. So now if I want to go left and sprint, I don't have to hit A and
then shift with my pinky. Much better. Got it. All right. Is this a streamer that sprints with his
mouse? Yes. All right. So we've got mushroom. Oh, wait. What'd I just do? Is this like to level
up your health or something? Yeah. It's, uh, you, you collect mushrooms and you put it in there and
you level it up. Yeah. Right here. Check this out. Harvest these and then I can, I fill it up with
syringe and then syringe myself in the neck and I'll get another bar of HP. Got it. So they've
wrought over time though, which is trying to figure out what that means, how long that takes.
I'll look for a couple more of these things. What's that? Night. You are in the hideout
under the influence of the protective substance. It will help you survive. Okay.
Build a well. I don't want to build a fucking well. Saw. Use a saw. Convert wood logs to planks.
Okay. I can make planks. Do I have to like fall out for this house? Is that what's going on here?
I want another mushroom. They're going to map too. All right. Underground entrance.
That's the X. That's where I got to go. Right? What's the mission? What's the goal of the whole
game? I don't know. Let me put that mushroom back in here. All right. They're worth 10 each.
Escape the forest. All right. Sounds easy enough. I need to barricade this though. Look at how
fucked up this is. Wait, what's in here? This generator is half empty. It contains enough
gasoline for one more night. I should find a full can in the house above the underground entrance.
Oh shit. You have some stuff on you. Got a torch on you. Thanks, man.
Native weapons have secondary attack. Try it by pressing mouse four.
Okay. It's an overhead swing. All right. Now I need to get the gas that's under the
underground entrance. Say that again one more time. I have enough for one more night.
That's not good. Okay. I can't sprint around everywhere. Don't waste the torch. Oh, sorry.
So how do I get over there? There's an underground entrance.
There's a full can of gas over here. Where? Full can of gas? There's a dog. Is it a
is it a poisoned dog? Or is it a regular? Sounds like a regular dog.
Okay. Dog. Is it a regular dog or is it an infected dog? Is there a difference in this game?
Is that an affected dog? Is this dog affected? You don't sound infected.
Get out of here.
God damn it. Where's the underground entrance? I need to find the full can of gasoline or I'm
not going to be able to survive another night. Oh, that's where I am. I have to go up into the left.
Loot the dog. The dog is still alive. I can't loot the dog.
Is there a beetle? There are more than one dog now.
I need to get the gasoline or I can't do this. Gasoline. All right. I'm going this way.
There's always a bigger dog. Just don't go near the dogs. I don't know what the fuck they are.
They're just like hanging out. They're just in random spots. Okay. I need to go this way.
Underground entrance. Get me up there. I'm just going to run away from the dogs if I see them.
Is it nighttime? This is the sun's out. Is the sun out right? All right. There's a dog.
Why did they just... Okay. I'm here. Underground entrance. Where is it? Underground entrance. I'm
here. Where's the underground entrance? Found it right there. Don't step on the bear trap
and give it to me. Okay. Is this it? Am I in like a zone I'm not supposed to be in?
Bear trap. If I climb through this window, I'll get... I'll step in it and I don't want to step
in that. Why can I... I cannot punch. This is the house. I'll find the entrance to the underground
here and I'm not bleeding so I'll be okay for a little while. I gotta get more mushrooms.
Watch it for this shit. I'm going to step in this. The cyclops are currently supposed to eat.
Eat. I don't have anything. Oh, I can make another bandage. Not as well. Bed. Backpack.
Ooh, nice. Okay. Bread. Pills. What do the pills do?
Medium caliber. But there's guns in this game? And a battery? Wait, there's guns.
Ooh, shit. All right. Lockpick. Nail. A couple of rags. There it is. Full gasoline. Pack of...
I thought that was... It's a pack of cigarettes. Looks like an apple. Oh, that's why it looks
like that. Okay. I guess it's just an interesting thing to find. All right. I got the... Do I have
a weapon? I have a weapon, right? Do I have a weapon? I don't have any weapon. Make a torch
and a bandage. Fuck. Okay, move this. Am I stuck here? No, not anymore.
Oh, it's these mushrooms. Nice. Okay, good. You used... Wait, what are you talking about? What?
I used the gasoline? Why did I use the gasoline? I dumped it on the torch? Why would I do that?
Wow. I thought it was a person. I thought there was a specific gasoline torch. It's a red one. I
don't have a red one in my inventory. See? Like gasoline torch. Look. Oh, I made that one. Well,
fuck. Is that going to be the mistake that ends this whole thing and I have to restart the whole
game? Tell me now. Okay, I'm going to examine it. The entrance to the underground tunnels.
I don't have any stuff. Why am I... How am I going to do anything down here? At least the game saved.
I have a mushroom. I don't want to... I can't... I don't know. What am I looking for down here?
I don't even know what I'm trying to do down here. What's the point of down here?
I need a torch. I have a... Wait a minute. You're telling me that the torch with the gasoline on it...
Oh, it's alcohol, technically. Rubble. The tunnel walls were crushed by enormous roots. Dig.
I don't have a shovel. Shit. Nothing over here. Let's keep going. Go home. Go home. Go home. Go
home. Should I go home? A light bulb dimly lits the wet walls of the underground passage. The
further part is shrouded in complete darkness. I need a light source to continue. Keep going. Go.
Go home. The thick wooded posts barely hold the soap brown and the tangled roots. The construction
seems on the verge of collapse. I'm going home. I'm going... I'm at her. I'm going home. Okay.
I have mushrooms to deposit into my mushroom syringe bank. Okay, now I gotta go this way.
There's a dog. Where the fuck are these dogs? Out here into the right... Wait, what's up here?
I'm so glad I have this stereo audio so that I can hear where they're coming from.
All right, I'm just gonna go. I gotta deposit that mushroom and then I'm gonna make a... I need to
make a weapon or something. I have to barricade boards and windows and... This way. What... What
day is it? What time is it? Do I even have that knowledge right now? Oh, you motherfucker. Where
are you? Is there any way I can see what time it is? All right. So, generator. Gasoline. Fill it up.
Okay, here we go. Right? This is what I'm supposed to be doing. Right? I'm going for it. And I'm going
to assume that the bar is a day. One of those bars is one day worth of fuel. Right? Okay. So,
I have two days, two and a half days worth of fuel. Now, climb over here. There's probably like a
creeper in the house now because I haven't barricaded any windows. The bear trap under the window is
still open. Looks like this night was exceptionally uneventful. I didn't put that there, did I?
Okay. Oh, fuck. There's stuff in here. Okay. Rope. Two pieces of alcohol, two pieces of bottle,
and a mushroom book. The title reads, The Use of Mushrooms in the Household. That's what it was.
People are doing shrooms and giving themselves this like post-apocalyptic disease. All right.
We're almost there. Two more. Game is saved. Now, I need to craft some stuff. Bandages with alcohol.
Battery. Do I have a stash or anything? Can I stash? I can stash this stuff in here.
Right? I can just put it in here. All right. Well, I don't need half of this stuff. I can
put the pills in here. Scrap metal. Is there a way I can just control and do it? Yeah. Okay.
I'm going to keep the lockpick. Keep the alcohol. I'll keep one alcohol, one rag.
Keep the bread. I don't need the rope. Do I need these things? I don't know if I need these things.
Or not. I have no idea. Nails? What do they do? I don't know. Check your journal. Items. Keys.
Journal. Me. Skills. You. Skills. Okay. So I need. I don't have any planks though.
Varricade. Varricade. I need three planks. I don't have any planks. Let's look at planks.
All right. I think I'm. I need a weapon. There's a sandwich outside. There's not a sandwich outside.
I guarantee it. What do I have to do with this stuff? Lock all the doors with furniture.
That's what I was thinking. Wait. Otherwise people can get in here. See what I mean? Like,
people can get in that. Planks. I'm going to go on a plank mission. Can I move the bed?
I cannot drag the bed. All right. I got. Let me consolidate. So empty bottle. I'm getting
rid of this. Back to my stash. Turn. Turn on the generator. Turn the generator on. Why?
What are you talking about? I'll fucking have to. No. Leave that. Generator. Generator. Generator.
Generator. I'm going. What? Everybody just relax. Look. Hey. There we go. How I. I mean,
it's kind of annoying. Should I save energy? Does it burn? I don't want to just leave my lights on
and leave the house. Doesn't that sound bad? Keep them on. All right. Don't leave during the night.
What the fuck? Don't leave during the night. What the fuck? So what do I just hang out? How
do I? Can I sleep at night? How do you sleep? So I just have to hang out here. Stay safe until
daytime comes. What was my watch? I don't even know what time it is. You wait, fucker. Oh my
goodness. This is because I'm looking over here. I'm looking over at you guys and everyone's like,
just hang out in the house. Hang out in the house. Don't step on the fucking bear trap.
You knew it was going to happen like once, right? Like it was going to happen one time.
It might as well happen once. I thought somebody threw an axe through the window. I really thought
somebody threw an object at me. All right. Stop. Am I bleeding? How do you tell if you're bleeding?
Go near the light, please. I just stepped in a fucking bear trap. There's no more bears.
I'm not setting traps. I'm not setting bear traps. Go to the light. All right. All right.
All right. I'm next to the light. I'm fine. And now I'm going to heal. There. There's nobody in
the house, right? There's nobody in here. Did that say possible mushroom? Poisonous mushrooms.
Why is it coming out of the ground? What? That was possible mushrooms. I was right. Okay. Mushrooms.
What's that sound? What's that sound? What's that? Stand next to the light. Next to the light.
Just put a ton of light over here. I hear somebody sprinting. Get the fuck away from me. Do I need
the torch? No, I have this. I'm just going to drag it around with me. Be quiet. I'm standing in a
gigantic halogen light bulb. It's too dangerous to cook during the night. Close the door. I can't.
Okay. I can. Close the door. That one is barricaded. Is there something going to come in here?
I don't have any barricades. No. I don't even know what that means. Wait. Somebody said the
first night's not bad. What? Is this like Five Nights at Freddy's? Is by like night four there's
going to be random fucking animatronics running around this house? Great. How many days? How many
days until like somebody else has to take the shift? Look outside. I'm not looking outside.
Someone's going to grab me through the window. No. How do I know it's daytime? Look around the
corner. All right. I'm going to bring my fucking light source with me so I don't get in trouble.
Is this like holy water? Is this going to burn them or something? Why isn't music doing this?
I did it. I survived today. All right. Now turn the generator off. I don't need this light anymore.
Look at how fucking much that's too much. I need gasoline. Okay. All it needs is to have to just go.
Okay. Quickly. Quickly. Wood legs. Nothing in there. I need to go now. Clock. Time freeze. Why?
We need time freeze. Why is time frozen? I have like a time. I get a setup phase. There's an NPC
in here. What? Where? Who the fuck is this? Wolfman. Even from afar, I can smell your
futured stench. Be glad I don't have an appetite for carcasses, meat. The figure hides its face
under the hood. It smells of wet soil and fur. He's got like a machine gun. I know what you're
after. I can help you reclaim what you've lost. If you help me attend a certain matter, what do you
say, comrade? As he leans toward me, I can hear him giggling under the hood. I knew what would
interest you. Before we make a deal, we need to prove that you can do the job. I have no time for
weaklings meat. Do you follow? Show me what you're made of. Get through to the silent forest.
You think it's so easy. If I were you, I would prepare myself well before setting out.
When you get there, you will find me in this spot. Remember it. The wolf grabs you by the fucking
shirt and rips you towards his face. The likes of you always crawl back to me. The wolf grabs
some of that and scribbles something on it. Show item. Does he even trade? Oh, beautiful item.
Perfect for a church fair. So, you want it? Wolf road. What's that you got there? The wolf snatches
the photograph from my hand and studies it carefully. Finally, he snorts. His thick yellow spit landing
on the photo. Aha! This road doesn't exist anymore. Overgrown with trees like all the other ones.
Wolf throws the photo to the ground. Before, better forget about the road home meat. Around
here all the roads lead to nowhere. Trade. Oh, he's got a watch. How much money do I have?
Where's my money? How much money do I have? All right, I have three empty bottles. Is that enough
for a gun? Handgun frame. Reputation is money. Tape. Is that free? Value? No. Chain. I buy weapons
and ammo. All right. I need this. 150. I need a weapon. I need something. He has gasoline. 60.
I don't have enough. Here, take a bottle. I don't want that shit. Um, I need to buy gasoline.
Alcohol? Wait, I have other stuff. Wait, hold on. Tell me the story. I'd avoid getting in trouble
if I were you, Meat. Or at least until you get a decent weapon. If you wish to spend some more
quality time basking in the striking yet natural beauty of my features before you head off to the
silent forest, you will find me in my camp. And oh, he's leaving. I want to hold on. Before you
head off to the silent forest, you will find me in my camp in the dry meadow. Points to a location
on my map. He's not gone, right? All right. You're still here. All right. Give me a second. Just stay
there. Where's my wardrobe? All right. I got a bunch of, I got batteries. I got fucking pills.
I got bullets and shit. What did I just do? Okay. Where is it? Okay. I got metal. I got nails.
Let's sell the battery. I need that gasoline. I just don't know what this does. Don't sell the
nails. Okay. What about the bullet? 20. All right. That'll give me 50. That'll give me 60, 70 enough
for gasoline. That's one bullet. It's, I'm not gonna be able to do shit. That's fine. All right.
Give me that. And I want a gasoline, please. 50 minus 40. All right. Okay. The bullet is for you.
What do you mean? Sell the bullet. Buy gasoline. Thanks a lot. Appreciate the business. Now I'm
going to fill this shit up to all the way. I think. I don't know. Yeah. Should I? Halfway?
Should I do this halfway? Halfway? Get it to half. All right. That's it half. And then I've got other
stuff to put gas on. Dump gasoline on ground to make fire. That's not, that's not a bad idea.
Thanks for the tip. What else can I do? All right. Go over to this. Yeah. This thing over here.
Saw. Use. There's the gasoline over there. That's the EXP bubbles down there. I'm gonna fill this up
to. I was supposed to do that? I don't know. Was that, was that supposed to happen? I don't know if
I was supposed to. Convert wood logs to planks. Convert wood logs. Aren't there wood logs over here?
Wood logs. How do you not have wood logs in a pile of wood logs? It's empty, but it's wood logs.
There's wood logs there. Why would there not be wood logs on a pile of wood logs? What the fuck is
this game talking about? In the pile of wood logs, there are no wood logs. This should be at least
one. I gotta find wood logs. All right. I'm gonna find some wood logs. There's the wolf's camp.
Wolf's camp. Silent forest. There's like the portal. All right. I'm gonna go to find wood logs.
How do you get wood logs? Do I have to cut down trees? I don't have an axe. Are they just lying
around? They're locked. Good thing I got a lock pick. Get it open. Ooh. Full container of gasoline.
That hurt a dog. This is my only weapon. I have to save it. Wait, can I hit people with a bottle?
I think I can. But what about a broken glass? Broken glass. Um, what are these pills? Oh, I could.
All right. I can't get the... If I step on the glass, it's gonna hurt me.
This game seems pretty realistic. Wait, I need logs. Wait, I gotta go back. More gasoline. Okay,
so gasoline is gonna go into... I'm gonna get rid of it. Do you eat glass? I know. I'm gonna fill...
I'm gonna go just gasoline. I can like fill it up the whole way. All right. Let's do that.
Right? That's probably not a bad idea. Gasoline here. Let's get it filled. At least enough for
I'm comfortable with it. Because that guy... I'll have plenty of gas. I'm filling the whole thing
up. Full tank. Full. Is it nighttime? What have I fucking done all day? What time is it? What time
is it? Workshop. Oh, this is a huge inventory. Okay, just put everything in here. Um, chain trap.
No, I don't... Repair item. No. Okay, I need to put the syringe thing in here. Odd looking mushroom.
20 essence. 30, 40, 50. I got it. It's done. What the hell is this? Staying in dark areas at night
can be dangerous to me. Okay, all right. I can see far... This is a level up system. This is how you
level up. Okay, I can see further. Once a day I'll be able to heal myself by standing next to an
electric light source. Once a day I'll be able to learn my current location on the map. That's pretty...
That's... I'll be able to heal myself by eating mushrooms. Any electric light source could be
anything. I kind of like the first one. So I could just stay next to anything. Seeing further is
important. I don't know. Either one of these two sounds really, really good. I would... If it was
me, and because I'm stupid, I would pick this one if I was playing off stream. Because I don't have
a fucking chat of 15,000 people to help me. So I don't even need this. Like, we can pretend
that I already clicked this because I have you guys. So I'm gonna just go where it takes me.
It's done. I need to choose a negative perk. What do you mean a negative perk? What the fuck you...
What do you mean a negative perk? I have to pick this one. What? Staying in dark areas at night
can be dangerous to me. I like being able to see... But I could heal. It's over. I did it.
See further. What's that mean? Does it mean like physically actually seeing over here or like the
light goes further? Oh, that's not good. That's actually kind of bad. That's not good at all. This
is terrible. What's the point of this? It's useless. Shouldn't have got it. I should have got the moth.
Too late. Got to sleep in your bed that you make. All right. What time is it? I don't know. Let's
go with... I got some bread. I got some bandages. I got... Okay, let's go scavenge. This game's fun.
I like this game. All right. Time to scavenge. What time is it? I don't know. He's coping.
Actually, that's not bad because I can see pretty damn far. All right. Scavenge.
Is it nighttime? Dogs over here. All right. Easy. Burned house. Burned house. All right. I can
scavenge in this burned house. I don't know. Those dogs are in there. Dogs are there, but they can't
get in the house. They don't have hands. What? It's an open door. Oh, fuck. How many fucking dogs are
there? Oh, there's a tractor over here. There's a log. All right. Hold on. Oh, gasoline and a tire.
Nice. Dogs. Don't touch dog. Just... That's not a light, right? Logs? There's debris over there.
There's like a big wooden log over there. There's a pig too. There's nobody here. I'm fine.
Okay. I got a log. Oh, what does he got? An ear? I don't know. Get the... Don't do that.
Shut up. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up. Shut up. I got it. I'm out of here. I got to leave. I'm out.
Time to go. I got a log. Okay. I got a log. Where am I? Burned house. Okay. I got to make... I got
to get like a weapon. What happened to me? What was that? What happened? Why am I sick? Why am
my character sick? Why is my character sick? Why is he sick? What happened? What's his ween?
You're poisoned. How do I get rid of poison? Bandage? All right. I'm back home. I got to turn
the lights on. Okay. I've got... Is it time for the lights? No, not yet. What do I got? I got a couple
of planks. All right. Workbench. Board with nails. Got it. I got a weapon now. Okay. What does the
ear do? Throwable can be used as bait for carnivores. Okay. I stole some gasoline. I'm
going to put it into the tank. Bottle. Let's store the tire because I don't know what the hell this
is for. I'm going to... I'm going to put on the board, I think. I guess. Yeah. Good. Oh, now I
feel like I'm ready. I need more bandages. Bandage with alcohol. Yeah. Fuck it. Let's do it.
Fuck it. Let's get it. I'm going to eat this food. Does that do anything? Was that a stupid
mistake? This is not like Minecraft. No, this doesn't heal you. Okay. That was dumb. I just
have more stamina. Well, oh well. All right. Hotbar upgrade. I need to board up some...
I only have two boards. All right. I got a weapon. I'm fine. I'm just going to stand next to the...
Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. Oh, fuck. I have to turn the light on. Turn on the lights now, please.
Right? Turn on the light. Turn the light on. Turn on the light. That's like... There's something
happening. Oh, it's rain. It's raining. All right. It's raining. What does that mean?
I didn't mean to swing that. I thought it was like something zoning in. Like the sides of your
screen are flickering. It is an animal or a bad... Like a monster or something. I'm just going to
stand here until it's... Is that lightning or is that... Okay. That's lightning. I can't get
struck by lightning, right? There's a roof here. You're doing a great overreacting to everything
joke. I drank three coffees today. I can't help it. This is four. Should I just stay in here?
I need to use my daytime. But what's the... What's the actual... You know what else it is, too?
I have to talk louder because I'm blocking both my ears. So I'm... It's like somebody has a vacuum
cleaner on right now. Thank you. Nice work. You guys nailed it. No, for those of you that are new,
if I block both my ears, I've like literally become useless. You know how like Superman has
kryptonite and he's like the most powerful entity on earth, right? But if you like hold a kryptonite
crystal up to him, he just like... That's what happens to me. Like I could be like the fucking
strongest person on earth. If you just covered both my ears, I'd be like... I'd be useless.
You're not Superman. Ego maniac. That's my weakness. You're like a shark. What?
All right. Is it nighttime? But the question I was going to ask is how do you tell when...
How much time is it for a day cycle in the game? An hour? 30 minutes? 20 minutes? What's... How do
I know? You can tell from your light, okay? You find the watch. I could have bought a watch.
When the light gets orange, that's when it's getting dark. Thank you so much for your incredible
contribution. When grass is green as day, grass orange dusk. No color is night, okay? Sorry,
I'm still good to go. I knew it was going to happen too. And now this is where it gets fucking
loud. And I've got the kryptonite on too. Is there a mushroom down here? Apparently there's
a mushroom down here somewhere. Orange, orange, orange. Time to go. I forget where the house is.
Oh no. Where's the house? I'm going to be honest. I'm too afraid to do anything.
I'm too afraid to fucking do anything. I'm just going to wait till it's orange. I thought that
around here. I thought it was orange. Barricade. I don't have any planks.
It's a very quick cue. You have right to be antsy. Get wood to barricade.
There's a storm outside. That's not smart. But where do you get wood?
It's not just from the simply like the trees, right? You just have to find it. This adult is
scared of thunder. No, this adult is scared of loud ass noises that go in both ears at the same
time while he's doing kryptonite to himself. Guys, I don't even listen to music in the car.
I need my ears to see. Somebody, there's a scientific reason for it. I don't know what
it's called. I swear to God, this is not a joke. I need my ears to be aware of where I am and shit.
I swear to God. What is it called? Ecto, echolocation. I really think I have that.
Because when my ears are blocked, it's hard for me to pay attention and see and stuff.
I think I use echolocation like a bat. It's weird because when I scream really loud,
I can see better. It's weird. It's dark out now. All right, I gotta turn it on, right? I'm done.
I don't fucking know, guys. Orange means almost night, right? I'm just trying to learn. Orange
means it's almost nighttime. So when it's orange, that's when it's like get the fuck inside.
Get inside now, please. And then once this, this is a, it's like a green light, yellow light,
and then red light. Now I know. Just needed to learn. You wasted an entire day. Congrats.
Every single day it gets harder. You might need to restart. Wait, what do you mean every,
every day it gets harder? Did I just really waste a whole, what did I do today? I don't know.
Whatever. Does it really just get harder every day? I'm just waiting to turn on the generator.
What was that sound? Is what I want to know. Don't let the chat backseat you. That's okay,
though, because I have no idea what I'm doing. And this is a game that doesn't hold your hand.
I'm just trying to see just, okay, so this is how long it takes. All right, turn on the generator.
Not yet. Turn it on. Not yet, but it's still orange. Actually, it's becoming not orange.
Okay, I'm gonna turn it on now. Okay, now I'll turn it on because it's becoming faded.
Where's the light? Was that light? Okay, just stand next to this all day. What a waste of time.
So if I just lock myself in the corner with the light facing out, I'm safe. Close the doors. The
doors are closed. Close the doors. I don't know where they are. Which door is open? I'm terrified
to go over here. Oven. Is that a person? I'm closing that. Just stand over here. This should
be fine. This is how you die. This is not fine. How do you escape now? I'm not trying to escape
right now. I'm trying to... Guys, I didn't even have a weapon until 15 minutes ago. I was being
attacked by dogs and shit. Turn off the lamp. You won't ever tell me I won't do something.
Five seconds. One, two, three, four, five. Turn off the lamp in 10 seconds.
No. Something's coming. No. Something's over here. Don't move. Is there a crouch? There's something
out here. Walking around. What does that mean? Does that mean they're near here? Oh god. This is
not good. Something is lurking in the shadow. I should stay close to the light. I'm... I'm standing
right next to the light. Oh, they're in the house now. They're in the house. The ghosts are in the
house. Hey, hey, hey, hey. Why is it not? What happened? Why did that happen? What is that?
What happened? A man roughly my size is standing before me. I can barely make out his disturbingly
familiar features through the mat visor of his helmet. The massive helmet is covered with an
old sack and seems to be an integral part of the unnaturally pale body. I remember him. He's the
one who rescued me from the doctor's house. The man reaches out to me with his black hand.
It's covered in charcoal. There's something written on his worn woolen glove. We need to stick
together, brother. His lips are moving, but all the sounds are drowned inside the helmet.
He shrugs and takes the huge sack off his back and drops it on the ground, revealing its contents.
Go to the road. He wipes his left glove on his pants, takes out the charcoal from his pocket,
and starts scribbling. When he finishes, he lifts his dirty hand. All roads lead deeper into the
woods. He's got a lot of boards. What are you guys linking? What is this? He stole the gun.
It looks... I mean, it looks like... No, guys, this is... I'm telling you. Let me tell you something.
I'll show you. This is the kind of internal reaction you have when you realize
that the movie you're watching with your parents, you get to the scene that has the
pornography in it. This is what you're thinking internally, and my face game is what you're
actually presenting to everybody in the family that's sitting there watching.
That looks fucking like 100 years old. I gotta stop moving my skin, because
when I sit here like this, I could be 20. Anytime I make any emotion, I turn 40.
Thanks for that, by the way. All right, let me keep going. So this is me. I just died, right? So
this is me with the... I got, like, oven mitts on or something. I got a bolt handle. Hold still so
they don't see your age. Yeah, it's a weird superpower. Then when I stand still, I de-age
by like 10 years. I could be 20. What an eagle maniac. I'm fine. All right, I still have...
What happens here? So I have no money. I guess... Whatever. I can't do anything.
All right, now I'm gonna prepare completely, because now I understand the game. I still have
my board. Gonna get boards. What's in here? I've got gasoline. How much gasoline do I have?
I gotta go find boards. I got a plank. I can hit stuff. I'm ready. How much gas do I have? Plenty.
Just totally plenty. All right, let's go. The lighting's weird in your room. If you fix it,
you might look younger. I gotta turn off the generator. All right, it's daytime. We're good.
Now I understand how the day and night cycle works. I'm gonna bring a little bit of food. I'm
gonna bring just some bandages. I'm gonna go scavenging to get boards to put all over the
place. All right, store this shit. I can... I'm gonna take this. I'm gonna bring out...
Fuck, I don't know. Heal? Is this a pill? I'm always afraid to make mistakes in these games.
I need a bandage. I need two rags. Prioritize the bedroom. I will try. All right, I'm just gonna...
I'm gonna go. I'm gonna go. I'm going for it. Let's go. I have to just get stuff. Prioritize the...
What's the bedroom? All these rooms are all fucked up. Which one is the bedroom? I have no idea.
That one? Okay, let's go. The one with the bed. Okay, I'm going for it. Let's go. I got a plank.
I've got... I'm ready to defend myself. What do we got? I'm gonna check out this burned house.
There we go. All right. Broken glass. Let's get it. I don't... Maybe I can use it for something.
It's a trap. All right, nice. Okay, cool, cool, cool, cool, cool. Let's go.
Got plenty of daylight. Burned house. I got my plank. I can hit the random things that attack me.
All right, like that. Like right now. I'm ready. Two dogs. Four dogs. Is that too many?
There might be six. There's a six dog. There's a camp over here. I have to do this. Uh-oh. What
the fuck was that? It's the... I didn't... Okay, that's what it looks like. God damn it. I didn't...
I couldn't even fucking tell. I need to check in here. Can they see me?
Oh no, I'm gonna die again. There's like seven of them. Get out of here. Wait.
Wait. No, no, no. Give me the meat, meat, meat, meat, meat. Hurry up. Get in your fucking
inventory. Hurry up. Ah! How do I throw it down? How do I give them the meat? How do I give them
the meat? Okay, no. I have the meat. That's why they're coming over here. Oh my God. It's not
gonna work out. Throw the meat. I was trying to. Does it hold right? How do you throw this shit on
the ground? What the hell am I doing? You have to hold it for like two or three seconds.
To put it in your fucking hand, you have to go... All right, I don't know what the hell I'm
supposed to be doing here. Trying to find wood, but apparently this is the dogpocalypse.
It's all dogs. It's only dogs. The animals took over.
I gotta go a different way. Don't step on these poisonous mushrooms.
No weapon. I got a weapon. I need to heal though. I need logs. You would think that logs would be
the easiest thing in the whole game to find. There's trees everywhere. Why is it like finding
ammo in Resident Evil? How come I've not seen any logs? Can I get a log? Okay, there's a tree.
A fallen tree. Its bark looks chewed up. Hit it. That's not doing anything. Okay, I'm gonna...
That's not a log. This is like a chest. There's treasure chests lying around, but no logs. Did I
get like a shitty seed? There's more bear traps than logs. Oh my God, finally. Wooden logs.
That's it? Thank God, finally. Stumps. Stone too. All right, so I got... Getting there.
Okay, how many logs do I need to make enough planks to survive? I have six. Did I miss a pile?
There we go. All right, I'm fucking off. I'm out of here. I'm over here at the log pile.
Over at the hideout. Let's go. Trap. I missed... What do you mean the biggest pile? I missed a pile?
How did I do that? This one right here? That's not... Oh, I thought... I didn't think this was...
I thought they had to be the little like rabbit pellets. Okay, I'm good. Wait, chest. I need to...
Okay, let's get me out of here. There's a lot of these random crates. So now I board up with the
windows and then make sure that I have light in the bedroom. More piles. Thank God. This is just a
wood. This is just... We're getting as much wood as I can carry. I got no more room. I gotta go.
What is this? Yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm fine. I'm fine. I'm fine. I hear a dog somewhere. I know. I gotta
kill it. I gotta kill this dog. I'm gonna kill the dog. There's only one dog, right? Kill it.
There's only one dog. Kill it, I guess. Don't... I had one here. I fucking missed.
All right, I'll give it here. Give me the dog's ear. What happened to it? I had to do that. There's
nothing else I could do. Where the hell am I? I don't... I think I'm going the wrong way. Okay,
up, up, up from here. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Not right now. All right, we're here.
All right, so now get in here. Thank God. I have nothing to cook, right? No mushrooms. Turn the logs
into planks. So, wood logs to planks. 25 fuel. How many should I do? Is that a good idea? All of
them. I... Okay, I have 16 planks. Okay, now windows first, right? Which windows? Bedroom windows
first. Window. Bingo. Barricade. I need... Let's go. This one, too. And then this one.
Good. What's that? All right, let's just throw up in my mouth. I don't know why I told you that.
Should I very... No. Corner of the bedroom. I don't know, there's a backpack back here.
Can you honk in this game? That'd be awesome if you could. Okay, so this is fine.
Now I need to do that. What about over here? Is this okay? Is that blocking that? Push the furniture
in front of the door. All right, barricaded window. That's barricaded. So, this has to stay here,
though, because look, I mean, is that blocking this? Can I get confirmed? Am I now safe? Okay,
so they can't get in now. Door. Close the doors. Lock up. The only way you can get in is from here,
but should I... I'm just gonna barricade this door. Put the stool in front of the door. Yeah,
so that's blocking that door. I don't think I have any more furniture. Can I make furniture?
Okay. Drop your traps. Do I have traps on me? Oh, okay. Trap. Broken glass. Where should I put it?
In front of... In front of a window? In front of one of the doors?
Should I put it, like, over here? Right in front of the front door.
What? Outside the front door. It's, like, here. Like... Wait, am I gonna step on this? Oh, shit,
the well. I need... Oh, shit. Um, I need gasoline. Where's my gas? Give me my gas. I can remake this.
Okay, give me the gas on this hot bar here. Make some more wood. Here we go. Okay. What does the
well do for me? Give me fresh water? Okay, so... Oh, nice. Okay, so I can heal.
Is this infinite? Okay, I can hold... I can keep these in here. Now let's put the glass down
once per day. That's useful. Okay, so, um, I'm gonna close it. Put it here and then close the door.
No, they can't get in. It's orange. All right. Did I do it... Did I do this right?
Oh, wait, wait. I have to... I have to turn the, uh... I have to turn the generator on right now.
I didn't turn the generator on. Where's the light? Where's the lamp? Does it... Okay,
this is... Turn it on. Okay, there's plenty of gas. We're fine. Did you just write GTA 2 is lame?
What does that have to do with anything? Okay, this is blocked. I think I'm safe now. I'm safe,
I think. I should be. I gotta take my plank out just in case somebody gets in here.
And the torch. All right, I'm ready for a fight. Bring the other light in. What do you mean the
other light? There's another light? Put two lamps in the bedroom. Um, okay, here we go. It's
happening. It's happening right now. So I gotta put all the lights in the bedroom. So I'm going.
I'm going. I'm going. I'm moving. I'm moving. I'm moving. All right, everything's barricaded. I've
got two lamps. I've got the generator running and I have my... I've got traps outside the front door.
I've got everything boarded up. One guy. You don't have a roof. There's no roofs in this game.
Close the door. All right, they can't get in any other way, right? Let's board it up.
It's all boarded up. All right, I'm ready. Barricade the door now.
Yeah. Should I not have that? I'm just locking myself in the bedroom completely. Now I'm trapped.
Put the lamp on the door. It's... I can dismantle it. It's okay. All right. Um, should be fine.
What? Now what do I have to do? I still need to go over to like the secret silent forest.
Okay, I can do it. Don't stand near the windows. I can hear something skittering around.
What if I don't don't stand at the door either? I'm good. I'm good. They can't get over here.
They don't even know I'm in here. It's all barricaded up. Well, what's that thing? Why is
there a demon in here? Why is there a demon in here? What do I do? What do I do about that? What
do I do? Touch it? I picked it up. What does it do? Eat it. Um, okay. I ate it. I gave it a heal,
apparently. Why somebody just said eat it and I just reflect it. I just don't know what to look
at in the chat. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Here come the ghosts. Are they going to turn
off both lamps? I got to move the lamp. I have to move the lamp out of the room. Yep. They turned
up that lamp. It's okay. They can't get in here though, right? Ghosts can move through walls.
Ghosts can move through walls. How do I combat a ghost moving through a fucking wall? How do I?
I'm good. They can't move through the walls. Things you can't kill are afraid of the light
usually. I made it. Correct. Turn both lamps off. Okay. I almost just died from this.
Day four? I thought it was day two. I thought it was day two. Is it day four? When did it become
day four? Let's turn the generator off. I have to get out of the room. Um, where's my bed? It's
right here. All right. I got some time here. Uh, trader is back. I got a hundred trader reputation
gold. I noticed a smile on his face through the mat visor of his helmet. The man nods in greeting.
Show item. Okay. Trade. Wish I had whatever the hell that demon dropped. That'd be nice.
Axe blade. I don't have any money. I got, I stopped biting your lip. That's bad habit. Um,
I could get gas. Save it for the watch. Yeah, that is useful. Shotgun. I feel like the,
maybe later on when you survive one night, so you get more money or something, but
I can barely walk around with a stick with nails on it. Get some wires. I think I have some wires,
don't I? I gotta move this though so I can turn off the generator. Better off finding stuff. Yeah,
I got plenty of gas. All right. Move this back. Maybe too far. You're right here.
All right. Up and work bench board with nails torch. I still have a little bit of torch left.
All right. What the hell? Just dump all this in here. Okay. Lock pick. I do need the wire.
No, that's no, that's a different kind of like curly squiggly thing. That's rope and that's
wire. I need to wire the nails in there too. Upgrade the work bench. Oh shit. I'll be able
to craft more items and fit more upgrades into weapons when I upgrade my work bench.
Oh, let's do it. Okay. Ooh, I need a barrel. Lantern. How long does it last?
Waiting to see the final time on the speed run. Probably 16 hours and 42 minutes.
Should I just buy these? I think I'm going to buy two of them, but I need,
I'll go look for them. I mean, I'm going to, I've got, I'm going to go explore.
I'm going to bring some meat with me. I think I have a couple of pieces, right? Yeah.
Bring this. I have a bandage. I have, I don't think I can think of pills too, don't I?
Rag and alcohol. Can I make, how do I make a rag to go off? Right. I'm just going to go.
I'm going to go, I need to go like down here. Or no, I, the underground, it's been like two
and a half hours. I was supposed to go this way. Underground entrance. What am I, I have to go in
the underground entrance. I forgot that was part of the, all right, let's go. All right. Here we go.
Underground entrance. This loud rain. I, sorry, I can't hear you. Already there's a dog.
I want nothing to do with this dog. I could buy a shotgun. I can only shoot it one time, which I
will miss. I won't hit the thing I'm aiming at and it'll be a waste of money. There's that hole.
It's in here. Wait, how do I get in here? Climb the window, right? Get in the underground lair.
I hear mushroom noises. Here we go. I actually do not remember what I was supposed to do down
here, but I'm just going to go down here. I guess this is go through the underground passage. This
is the blood more. This is the fine, the den of evil of this game. And I've just barely doing it
now. Motorcycle magazine, automotive magazine. Okay. Maybe I can sell it. I needed another torch.
It's all right. There's no map down here either. What was that? Is it a dog? Of course it is.
Dogs everywhere. What is that? There's like a light over here. Mushroom. This part of the
passage is blocked by overgrown roots. Smash it. There's going to be like a sacrificial
fucking circle over here. It's my only way out. I won't be able to open it without my key.
Look at the handle. Press your ear against the keyhole. The hatch handle is covered in a thick
layer of dust. It hasn't been open for at least two weeks. I can hear a faint voice throughout
the howling wind. It sounds familiar. It seems to be coming through the keyhole. Someone's calling
me. The hatch handle is covered in a thick layer of dust. It hasn't been open for at least two
weeks. Look through the keyhole. I don't have a key. Is this the way I leave the game? This
is how you actually win. Interesting. Okay. Well, I'm on my way back, which means that I'm going to
I knew it. I knew it. I'm just going to run. I think I'm going to run. I think I'm just going to run.
Ah, I was down and then left. There's going to be a monster here or something. I don't know. I only
have a little bit more of my torch. Oh god. They are so powerful. Run. Just run, run, run, run, run,
run, run, run. Jesus. Oh, it's getting dark. It's getting dark outside. It's night. It's
nighttime now. I think it's nighttime right now. Is it nighttime right now? Oh, I do have mushrooms
to deposit. Oh god. What is this little dog? All right. I'm good. I'm good. A minute, a minute. Nice.
Okay. Let's put these mushrooms in. I don't even know what I need. Let's see. 10 essence, 10, 10.
Okay. Not bad. So I can't actually go down there yet, but I can make another board with nails.
What a repair item is what? It's four. Okay. It's one and five. To make a new one, it's two and ten.
So you just want to keep this repaired. I don't think I need to do that yet though.
Okay. I've got a battery, some more planks, some meat in there. All right. Looks good.
I just want to let you know that you're doing great. Hey, thanks. Appreciate that.
Can I make another lamp? This is a, somebody said this is a useless emote, the new one. I know.
I think the only reason why that's serious is because I didn't want to do a 24-hour stream.
It's last night I said, last night, sorry, what I meant to say was three days ago.
I said if I didn't have that here by the next stream, then I would have to do a 24-hour stream.
So I only did it so I didn't have to do that. All right. Now what? I think now I just have to
chill. The generator is not on. It's not dying time at all. You have time? Okay. Yeah. It's just
the rain. All right. I'm going to go down to the lower right just for a little bit and see if I
can grab any new supplies. Find a new place. What's this? A farm? Farmland? A wedding?
Wedding. It's just like a maze. Don't fucking be an idiot here.
What is over here? Oh shit, there's a place. Okay. Oh fuck.
Is it just one dog? Oh, it's a dog. Okay. That dog can't hurt me.
There's going to be gas in here, right? No gas or anything on the car? Nothing here? No way.
I have to do this quick. I have...
I had... I had to. I'm sorry. I had to do that. Otherwise it would kill me.
What's on the table? What is that? Nothing? What is going on in here? The torch... an old wagon
decorated with coked ribs and flowers made of white tissue paper. All right. I gotta go.
Chair. No. Come on. Like a box or something in here. Anything.
Food. Anything. A box. Stop. What do you mean stop? Stop, stop, stop, stop. I have to leave.
I have to leave. I have to get out of here now. Oh my god. Oh my god. What's happening?
What the fuck is that? It's orange, right? I gotta go. I'll come back here another time.
It's not orange yet. I wish I had a torch. Something's banging. Combo to get in there.
What is with this placement of barrels? I'm gonna get stuck in here and it's gonna be really bad.
Yeah. I'm like getting stuck in here. I can't get stuck in this shit right now.
I'm stuck in here now. Fantastic. I don't even know how I got in here.
Destroyed well. Good. I got one piece of rope. Awesome. Excellent. I'm surprised there's nothing
else in here. I can't. There's no... I need a combination to get over there.
I need a combination to get over here or in light. What the fuck was that? I just can't see
anything. Can you tell me there's nothing in the dog house? Wait. No. More of these random logs
in the way. Is there a faster way to get out of this? Put me down here. I'm just gonna go up
to the right. No. Do I actually... I have to go through this again. How do I get out? I do not
I do not remember how I got in here. I think it was from up. Oh no. This way. Oh you motherfucker.
All right. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. I'm fine. Top left. Just move this way. A bunch of dogs.
Turn on the generator. Stamina. Get it back. Come on. Thank you for clapping for me. I'm here.
All right. I'm good. I didn't learn anything new. I didn't get anything new. I guess just survive
again and run this way tomorrow. I guess. I got rope. That's not gonna do shit for me.
How do I get back in my fucking house? Wait. Mushroom remains. Somebody's in your room.
You mean in the video game room or in like the actual room? Because I'm too scared to turn around.
I have to turn on the generator. Not quite yet though. It's still all right. All right.
Everything's still barricaded. I'm gonna. I'm gonna repair this.
Just so it's. Why is it red now? Okay. This is fine. This is fine. I can drink from the well tomorrow.
Uh doorway. Repair the doorway. Wait. Somebody got in here? That's not good. Was it always broken?
Oh. I think I'm all right then. All right. We're getting to be close to night time here.
Is there anything else I can do? All right. So the goal. Goal for tomorrow is to go down here.
Try to make at least somewhat of progress going down this way.
Right. I need lock picks too but I can't find any wiring. Turn off the lights and play in the dark.
It's 4 30 in the afternoon in Las Vegas. I can. It's. That's not going to work.
You're gonna have to wait another couple hours. I have no more gas either.
I actually really don't like this. What's happening right now because I don't have
any more gas. Close my blinds. They're. They're closed already. The sun is huge out here.
You're way close to the sun. To those who don't know Las Vegas is in the mountains.
So it's like 4 000 feet elevated closer to the sun. That's why it looks bigger.
That's why it's harder. Nothing else. Not one of these mazes. Something small I can just grab right
there. No. It's too risky. It's amazing that literally nothing I just said was correct.
Whatever. There is glass there. All right. I think it's time just to sit and just exist in here and
then I'll have enough money tomorrow. All right. Let's do it. Just turn it on.
So I should be able to buy some decent stuff tomorrow. It's in there, right? Yeah. Okay.
Live another day. Why are you doing Han Solo? What the hell do you guys know? All right. Bring
it on. Let's go. I have to pee too. I have to. I'm gonna take a break after this. He'll pee.
And then grab. I'm so sick of this happening. Again. We're only talking truth on this stream.
Only truth. I've showed this before but like seriously. We're only going to speak truth.
Okay. This is a razor death adder. I've used this mouse for years. I don't. I don't understand.
I need to. I needs to be explained. So why this. Why do you have this sticky thing over here that
can come off? Do you see what you see? What's that? I did. This is that's part of the mouse.
This thing is sticky. It's like glued on and it's the grip for the mouse. Why on earth is this
possible? Because now I can't put it back on. Why is this? Why is this like this? Yeah. I've tried
to put this back on like three or four times. You're supposed to buy a new one. This mouse is
less than six months old. It's like six or seven months old. Glue it back on but that's the problem.
It's never gonna fit the same way because it was like stuffed in and glued in there. I'm not sure
you can see this. It's this thing is bigger than this slot is. It was like stuffed in and glued
inside. Why is there even a grip on this mouse? What's the what does this grip do?
What's this grip? What's it here for? I did to grip my mouse? All that happens is you just get this
disgusting brown shit in there. That's it. Just collect it. It's a brown gamer shit collector.
I don't understand. And you can't just take it off and now I can't grab this because it's sticky.
Actually maybe that's the point. So now it's a super grip because now I stick to this when I hold
it. Am I alive? I'm still fine, right? I've owned the Death Adder. Different versions of it for like
15 years. Never have I seen the glued on weird grip thing on the edge. All right, I gotta pay
attention. I'm just gonna get an Amazon... Who opened that? Did I do that? I did. Did I do that?
Why did this open? Put the lamp on the door. Good call. Okay, I feel better now. I've used
a generic Microsoft mouse for eight years and I'm just fine. Yeah, I'm just gonna get the $4
Amazon mouse. Fake gamer. I use an Amazon keyboard. That thing is fine. It was $8.95.
It wasn't $300. Cheap gamer. My... Guys, we all have the same buttons. I have WASD on my keyboard.
So do you. I press W and I go up. You press W you go up too. You don't get extra keys. Maybe
some of them do. All the mouse has to do is left and right click with maybe a function button or
two like a mini scroll wheel. You don't have any optical buttons. Gamer keys. And when have you
ever used your gamer keys on your special keyboard? Because every time I've had a special keyboard,
they go untouched. In fact, I try to find ways to turn them off because I've never... I don't touch
them. Dust actually collected on some of my F keys on some of those like super function keys
because I've never touched them once. That's like having the help button on your Dell
keyboard and you would accidentally press it and you'd get the help screen would come up and you'd
be screaming at your monitor. Show us your keyboard. I've seen it before. It's an Amazon Basics.
Thing is cheap. But the buttons press and I move. Now if I really wanted to splurge,
you go for that like $29.99. The one that has the thing that stick... It lies down on two little
sticks and goes up at an angle. They didn't even come near me. I'm fine. My gamer keyboard. I want
to go home. Who's this? After you survive night, you gain reputation with the trader. All right,
cool. Who is this? Oops. What the fuck? Why did you do that? It's a... It's a vision. Not even real.
It's just a vision. All right. I have 200 bucks. I need to buy gasoline. I'm sorry, guys. Everyone's
going to be very upset about this, but I have to. I could get a metal pipe and make a gun.
Don't bite your lip. Omega low. Omega low. Why? How much is a watch? 200? 300. I can't. I don't
have enough. I need to live like another day or two. In the meantime... I need a torch. I have to do
one. I need a torch. I'm going to go anywhere. I already have a board with nails. Make torch
and explore that wedding chapel. That's what I was thinking of doing. Sell some stuff. I feel like
I need this stuff, though. Tire's not worth anything. Metal scrap I'll probably need. I'll
probably need some of this at some point. At least I think I do. Sell your useless stuff. I don't know
what's useless. Scrap metal. You can't go to the wedding. It's a waste of time. Okay. Well,
that's good to know. Hold on to my... Yeah, I'm going to hold on to this stuff. I'm going to go
explore the place I want to explore. I need healing, though. What can I get? I need two
pieces of cloth. That shouldn't be that hard to find, honestly. I really do need gasoline,
too. Hopefully I can find it. I can dodge by pressing control. Oh, that's really... Okay,
that's good to know. General. I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I have like one more night in
this thing. This is going to be bad, isn't it? All right, I'm going to go down this way. Down.
Over and down. I have my torch, right? Get it on the bar. Poison. Don't touch it.
Just metal that trap. Get scrap metal. Perfect. Okay. Down. I'm trying to find a way through here.
Silent forest. There we go. Logs. Do I need these anymore, though? I feel like I don't even need
these. Do I need this shit? Important message. That was very important. I'm glad everybody just
told me. Very important stuff you guys are putting in the chat. I appreciate it. I just hit the
Windows button. Another key that should never exist anymore. There's no reason for that button
to exist. I have this theory that Microsoft... I have this theory, right? Pause the game. I have
theory that the reason why there's a Windows key on every single keyboard is because it's just free
advertisement for Windows. If it's on every single keyboard... Oh, that's the Windows key.
Every single company that makes a keyboard has it there. I'm surprised it's not on Mac keyboards.
Do they have to pay money to license that, by the way? If I want to make a keyboard and I'm going
to make the German 985 keyboard and there's a Windows key on it, do I have to pay Microsoft
fifteen cents a sale to do that? I'm actually serious. I'm actually asking this as a real
question. I'm not kidding around. Yes, I do. Do I? So why do most companies put it on there? Why
not just have a bigger control and a bigger alt? It's copyrighted. Who copyrighted the keyboard?
That's an important function. No, it's not. There's no keyboard copyright. You don't have to pay
anybody. Is there somebody that invented the keyboard like 40 years ago? And now you have to...
two-year Pepe dance. What? All right, I gotta go. Silent Forest looks like it's this way, but
I'm gonna move over here. This looks like the entrance to the Silent Forest if I was an entrance
to a forest that was supposed to be the entrance to this. There it is. All right, we got some
potential room here. There's a spot over here. Window? No. Fucking demons here or anything.
Stop singing. What are we doing? I need a... All right. Generator. Switch it on.
What is in there? How much gas is in this? Last one just for the visual.
Who is saying huh? Really? Every door has a lock? What is that? Hole. This place is infected with
something toxic. I need to find a way to get rid of it. I don't know. Burn? Burn it.
Burn it. Molotov cocktail. Okay, I gotta get this right. I only have one. Can I do it? Okay.
What about over here? I guess I can still take this stuff. Oven. Nothing in the oven?
All right, there's somebody in here. I heard him. Oh, come on. There's another one. How do I make a
Molotov cocktail? Wait. Are you serious? That's annoying. Okay. Further in? There's a guy in here.
I heard him. It's a bathtub. What's that? Egg. Something is floating inside. The skin looks to
be quite thin. Maybe I could puncture it or pierce it with something. An embryo. Get rid of something.
Get rid of something. Get rid of something. Get rid of something. What do I get rid of? I don't
know what to get rid of. I can't make the stone. And I'm gonna make a bandage. You fucking idiot.
You imbecile. Two bandages. Uh, no. Um, the rag? The meat. Give me that egg. I got it. Okay.
What? Bathtub. Search the bathtub. All right. I'm getting into uncharted territory here. There's
somebody. I heard the noise of somebody gurgling and stuff. Nothing else over here. Don't die in
here. Who's gonna be in this bedroom? Why is it so dark over here? What's that? There's a guy. Yeah,
there's somebody right there. The person. I just like had to press the number one and I just panicked
to a point where I could hit three times. Oh god damn it. I didn't even know what it was. I thought
it was going to be just a regular person. It was one of those guys with the giant spear halberds
and you have to hit them like seven times for them to die. I tried to press one, but I pressed the
tilde key, which by the way, why is that on a keyboard? I'm going to make a new, I'm going to
make a keyboard where all this useless shit is not on here. You know what I'm saying? I'm getting rid
of the tilde key. I'm getting rid of the windows key. I'm getting rid of whatever this is. What is
this? What is this like filing cabinet down here? Do you see this? What's the filing cabinet button
next to the alt key? What is that? What is this? What's that for? Page up, page down, you're out.
Scroll lock, pause, break. The music button. They're all gone. All of them. There's a music
button on here. I want a, I want a minimal keyboard with just the shit that you know you use.
Why can't I, why does it exist? The filing cabinet button opens the right click menu.
Why do I have a mouse? I want it to right click menu. Tiny, it's going to be a tiny little keyboard.
No, it'll just be all the QWERTY, all the numbers, all the function keys are gone, by the way.
No windows key. Tab can stay because it's useful. Caps lock can stay. All this like home, end,
insert. Just, I just need one, the delete key needs can be this big and sit right there. And
you know what else I don't like? The FN key is like a double function key. Nobody uses that many
keys. I can't think of any person I've ever come across my, hold on, I'm burning daylight here.
I can't think of one person I've ever come across in my entire life. And I mean my whole life
that has ever pressed the FN and a function key in my entire life. Even IT people. FN function,
for what? What do you use it for? What's it for? I want to see at least two or three different
scenarios where it's useful. For your volume. I want you to just, volume. So you, hold on,
so you need, you need, you need 24 function keys to raise and lower the volume of your computer.
I can understand. All right. If the tail of the key doesn't exist, that guy's dead.
And now I lost the, the fucking, I lost the egg. No, I didn't. Game's actually pretty fun. Never
mind. I was at, I bet, pretend that whole thing didn't happen. FN is for music control. Turn on
the radio. All right. Anyways, they've been making computers, they've been making keyboards
the same fucking way since like 1994. And nobody's decided to, the machines in the factory are set up
to always do it like this. So they're just like, I don't want to change that. I don't want to get
rid of that. It's important for no one. It's, it's for grandma to accidentally press and like
turn her brightness up. All right. I'm done with that. A little bit of an angry. I'm supposed to
pee. Brightness. No, if your screen's too bright, just go to the power options and just drag the bar.
I'm making a keyboard and I'm going to make trillion dollars. It's going to be the trillion
dollar keyboard. All right. I'll be right back. I gotta piss. Seriously, possibly imagine if you
were playing like God of War 2 on your Xbox and you accidentally press the filing cabinet button.
What, what's his image? What are you linking? I look like a skeleton. Okay. If you pause at
three seconds, I look like a skeleton. I'm talking about the video, not the stream,
the video that just got linked. All right. I'm ready. I'm ready. Oh, I hate losing.
What a super villain thing to say. I hate to lose.
Okay. Do the thing where some, the cartoon where somebody pulls your tongue out high
bar and lets it go. Wait, what are you talking about? I don't even know what that means. All
right. Let's go. Okay. What was I doing? I had this egg. I'm going to store the egg. I don't know
what it's for. I'm going to store this, store this, all of it. I guess if I killed that thing,
it would have been good. I need lost inventory. Wait, I can go get my inventory. What was that?
Show him the germ. Show it to him. What do you mean? What do you got? Something here?
What? I saw that. Yeah. I saw it. Yeah. It was me being funny. It was me doing that on purpose.
I was doing like a funny face. You know, I want to like, all right, somebody said cook egg.
Are you for real? Does that work? Should I cook egg? Draw my perfect keyboard. I can't
make it. Oh, that's all right. Okay. Cook egg. Oh, 40 essence. Nice. Okay. That's worth a lot.
Now this is a hard game. This is a very hard game. It takes a lot of patience. I
imagine playing this game on nightmare or whatever the hell it is. It's going to rain again.
Should have hatched it. Can you do that? That's weird. All right. I'm going to go.
Oh, where am I going to go? I've been here. I this this wolf's camp I can go up to,
but I'm not like I'm not good enough to go up yet. I need a I need to not panic when I see it's
just that I feel the same way when I ever came across the butcher in Diablo one. I had the same
reaction. Same exact perspective. Same exact scenario. It was around a corner. And he would
just it was terrifying. I couldn't do it. It was scary because you couldn't see. All right.
I don't know what exactly time it is. And I don't have any gasoline. This is the last day
that I can do this without needing to forcibly. I need to get gasoline. This is the last night
I can do this. Try try to go get my inventory. I think I'm gonna try to get it. I know that
guy's in there. I just have to dodge and hit him. I'm going for it.
Is my hand slippery and fucking in rain? What is going on? Now, instead of being go find logs
for an hour. Now go find rags for an hour. At least there are plenty of those. That's true.
That is correct. You're right. Although this thing's almost broken and it's I need that watch.
I would literally sell everything in my inventory tomorrow to get that watch.
I hate not knowing how much time I have. It's killing me. I need to repair this weapon. Don't
step on that glass. Just do it. I need another torch. I wish there was a mode in this game where
there was just a big box that had 10 of every single one of these in them. Just to get you going.
It's getting late. Yeah. But I can't turn the thing on yet. Right when I feel like I'm getting
going, I have to hide in this house and be terrified. I guess that's the point, right?
I need, I'm going to make like four torches or five torches or something. I need alcohol, matches,
planks, and rags. Is this going to be enough if I turn it on now? I see a booger. No, you don't.
I hope this is enough. Otherwise, I'm dead. Where? What? What are you talking about? Stop.
All right. Pray that this is enough because then I'll have enough money to hopefully buy some stuff.
This is why I can't have face cam. I've told you this a thousand times. B omega booger.
There's a booger on the door behind you. Imagine if I moved out of the way and there was just this
six or seven month long booger wall. When I was, it's nighttime, so we had to talk about some of
these things. When I was like, maybe seven or eight years old in my bedroom, you know what's
coming. The wall next to my bedroom, because my bed was right up against the wall, right up against
the wall. But I was, when I was eight, maybe like seven or eight years old, every, every single night
it would go. And I thought I was being so sneaky. We know what it is. I'm not going to say it. I don't
need to, but there would be a collection hidden. And anytime we would rearrange the room,
if my mother wanted to rearrange the beds or, Hey, we're going to change this. So we're going
to change some stuff. What is this? I was like seven. I was, I was a literal child. Okay.
This didn't happen two weeks ago. Seven's too old to be, you puked in your mom's bed two weeks ago,
more like nine years ago. I threw up in my bed. Yeah, but that was like, that was like a decade
old. More than that. That was 10 years ago. You were 25. Yeah. I had to fuck. I puked. I had to
throw up. I was sick. I didn't feel well. What? You've never thrown up before unexpectedly.
This is like red light coming through here right now. How did you get in here? How did he get in
here? How did he get in here? Well, I need this stuff. How did he get in here? Oh, the door.
I'm going to sneeze. Oh, come on, please close the door. I need to go outside.
Light will do it. I need to like, look out the window. Come on. Really? You're not going to let
me do this stupid joke that I want to do? Mother nature. Why? I was going to get up and sneeze
into the wall right here. And well, not anymore, apparently. Quick, do a windows key. No, I got,
I got seven monitors here. They're all bright. You know, I was trying to think of what I would
do with like five, six, seven monitors. People have that. I'm trying to think of, okay, if I had
stream labs, OBS, web browser, game or whatever right here. Chat. What, what, what could you do
with four monitors? More than four. Look at the five monitors. For what? What would you put on them?
Put stocks on one. I guess that's true. All right. Well, I did it. Another day. Trade. What do I got?
300 and I'm going to get the watch. I'm going for it. No, but I need a gasoline.
Was it 48 watch or gasoline necessity or vanity? No, I don't sell it back to him for 150. Put it
back over here. All right. I need gas though. So let's sell some of these. I'll sell you a,
hold on. I need 48 time. Eight, eight AM. Now I have that forever, right? And this can't break.
All right. Does he buy logs? No, I need those logs. He'll buy pills though. Whatever. I don't
need these for anything. I'm not going to do drugs. That's 30. Maybe some scrap metal. Sell the watch
stones. Battery. I'm going to sell both drugs. Sell the meat. I got, I don't have any more meat.
At least I do. Okay. I don't think I need it. So let's go pills. That's 35.
I actually don't have to sell these pills. Grab the gasoline. I'll take it. All right. We're fine.
Okay. Refill. And I have a watch. So it's eight AM permanently until I leave.
I need to fill this. Looks good. It's almost empty. Night starts at 20. Good to know. Tank is empty.
Let's go turn it off. I now have enough for at least one or two nights. There's nothing else in
here. Put the pills back. Have the watch. Put everything back. Bring a rag with me.
And why is this? The only two rope can fit on one. All right. Bottle. No. All right. I need
torch. I need, I need like an alcohol or something to put to, I don't have any. I have nothing.
I have nothing. I'm going to get this to, I have to make this full. I have to. Okay. I've got my
watch. I've got my board. I'm going down here to get my inventory. It's just one person down there.
I've got my watch. I'm ready to go. Let's go. Good luck for your law degree. Thanks. I'm trying.
Don't mess this up. I need to find mushrooms too. Okay. Perfect. I need to just kill the
dude that's in here. I don't want to take any unnecessary stuff in my inventory.
So essentially it's one minute a second kind of, sort of. All right. Here we go. Into the woods.
Is that guy just out of the house now? Or is he going to be standing somewhere in particular?
This is going to, okay. Don't panic. Don't accidentally press one of the 17 useless
keys on the keyboard that you have. He's going to be right here somewhere. How did I get down
there before? Through the other side? Okay. What's that? What is that? Is it a bug? What's that?
Dead bug. Bug. Shell. Where the hell is he? Fucking butcher. Hold on. There's no gas in here.
Not shift. You motherfucker. Where are you? Okay. All right. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on out. One, two, three, go. That's it, right? Nobody else. Okay. Alcohol. Note.
The door code is three, three, three, three. It can't get any easier. Remember it. I'm not opening
that door after dark anymore. I went to get some gasoline from the pig shed. I'll be back after
dark. Gas from the pig shed. What is that? Shiny stone for the 130 bucks. All right. I need to
use bandage. Is my inventory down here somewhere? Where's my inventory? Where is it? Is it not here?
Corpse. Chair. Wardrobe. Take all that stuff. Lamp. Oh, backpack. All right. I'm leaving.
I know the code and I know that there's gasoline in the pig shed. I'm out. What time is it? 11.
That's enough time to get out of here. Code two. All right. Get me out. I'm panicking right now.
I'm just so fucking nervous. What's that noise? Why is there a noise? The thing's about to be out.
Three, three, three, three. Sleeper. Sleeper. Who's sleeping? Shotgun and a map of the forest.
Is the guy sleeping? What do I do? Should I kill him? He's going to get up and he's going to attack
me. Right? I have to leave. Hey there, friend. Hey there. Hi. Hi. Hi. Hi. Yes. In the last hideout,
look for an exit beneath the floor. He's going to fuck. He's a friend. He's going to get up and
run up just like that. Like I told you. He called you friend. That doesn't matter. I have to leave
now. I'm not going this way. Anybody that's alive is going to stand up and sprint at you. That's how
these games work. I can't let that happen. Not with this much stuff in my inventory and no torches,
by the way. So, okay. I have to leave now. I have to leave right now. Get out of here now.
Please get me out. I don't know how to get out of here. Okay. There it is. I'm sorry. If an NPC
has a dialogue option that's like trade, gossip, talk. We're good. If you're rolling around on the
ground and I don't know who you are and there is no dialogue options. He's a friend. There are no
such thing as friends. Not in a post-apocalyptic world. I made it though. I don't have enough
gasoline. All right. I can't look at chat anymore. Sorry. No more chatting. And so why am I just doing
that? All right. I'm here. No. Now I'm in the wrong spot. So, 3-3. That's how you get down
here. And then this is the silent forest hideout. I'm assuming I eventually have to end up up here
somewhere. Here we go. Let's fill this up with the gas that we have. No. Which I should have. I got
plenty. What is this? A piece of wood? A staff made of wooden unknown origin. And I have shotgun
shells too. This is pretty good. Okay. Let's fill this up. Not bad. Now this is a weapon. Let me go
back. Let me go to my weapon crafting bench. Let's see if I have anything new to do. Upgrade
workshop. I need, I don't know, is that toolbox? Shell, rag, alcohol. Okay. Let me make some more.
Shiny stone. That's worth a lot. All right. Let's take out the bandages. I have three bandages.
An image link is here. It's all right. Torch. I can make one. So make one. I need board. I can.
All right. I can make three torches. I need to turn on the thing out here. Let's do that.
Is it a bear or something? What was that? 25 fuel. Shit. Shouldn't have used it all, huh?
What happened to my watch? Oh, it's in the workshop. Never take that watch off. Ever. That's
fine. Alcohol. I have three bandages. One torch. Board with nails. Upgrades. Hardened. More nails
and light. And flex more. Yeah. All right. Prepare it. I need boards and uh-oh. Should I have done
that booger eating stance? Everyone's focusing on boogers and pee. That sounds about right. I need
more fuel, which means I have to live tonight and then buy fuel tomorrow. Yeah. That's the play.
I got enough. Let me see. Let me just lock some doors here. I need some supplies. Right there.
I actually think I want to bring this into the other room. That was a nice reference. Somebody
else said it on me. These are all still good. I can't cook anything. Oven efficiency one. How
do I make my oven better? This is still good. All this is still fine. The other hideouts. Oh, okay.
I see. I feel you. All right. So we got to get ready.
Pull this back. What do I think about the game so far? The visibility thing seems frustrating,
but cool. Oh, I think it's, I think it's good. I think I'm slowly starting to understand what
I'm even supposed to be doing, but uh, I think it's good. I think it's fun. He hates it. Well,
I mean, I'll probably uninstall it after this stream today, but I'm kidding. It's a joke. All
right. At least you're honest. We'll see how far I get. Torch. Free bandages. I need to repair this
before it becomes too late. Although while there's still some time left,
I'm going to go see if I can find some nails. Where have I not gone? I haven't gone like over
here. I'm just going to check it out really quick. Is it a survival game? Yeah, kind of.
It's a top down, it's a top down horror survival esque game. So yeah, it is. Okay.
Dry meadow. I'm up here now somewhere around 19 or so. I got to turn around. Nothing over here.
You know, like random logs or anything. Oh, if you have any of the horror games that I have not
played on stream, at least, or in a while toss them in the recommended for the discord because
I would play a bunch of horror games this month because obviously it makes sense. Right.
This is not, I'm not going to find anything over here. No, it's not worth it.
I just need to live one more day. Yeah, it's not worth it. Let's get me out of here.
Do PT. Didn't I do PT on stream? I don't remember. I know I played PT, but did I play on stream? I
don't know. Probably not. All right. I have to get the hell out of here. I must return to my hideup
before night. I know that's what I'm doing. Let's hide. So it was a good game.
I have heard it's a good game. How long is Soma? Move the bookcase like eight hours.
That's not bad. That's good. Check the door doors. Oh, okay. Good, good, good, good, good.
All right. Close this one. Lock it up. It's like two to three average German streams, but one
playthrough of Soma. Everybody's saying that I'm not going to be capable of beating it in like eight
hours. I think it's going to take me like 20 plus hours to beat it. What did you say? It might take
me 20 hours to beat that game. Is that some kind of challenge? It's around 16 hours. Well, that's
double what the last person said. The number would be good too. We'll check them out. All right. I
got to pay attention because this is an important day because then after this, we're going down to
the silent forest hideout. Every time I talk about something random during this, nothing happens.
I need another topic to go off on. Oh, my stream title is terrible. That's really bad. When your
stream title is the name of the game category and there's no difference. When somebody's browsing
through Twitch, it just says Darkwood Darkwood. And they think that there's something wrong with
their browser. And then they don't come to the stream. I should put Darkwood. I should put this
in brackets. Yeah, that's not a bad idea. So it's like the title is Darkwood Brackets one.
Yeah, that's not a bad idea. Okay. So now if you go out to the Twitch browser,
it'll say like Darkwood Darkwood one and you'll wait. They named it twice, but that's weird.
Looks a bit weird. Don't refresh. Well, yeah, I wouldn't refresh because you'll get an ad.
Somebody here. How are they in here? Are they in here? He's fighting the dogs outside. That was
really close. That was right outside the door. He's not going to like shoot a gun in here, right?
They don't sophisticated. Do they? I'm going to assume morning is like five, like 530.
Are they people or are they zombies? I really don't know. I think they're infected people.
Can you sleep? You cannot sleep. You have to just weather the storm. They can't get in.
This is a good strategy. I like this. Two lamps in front of the door, both barricaded.
Do I think that hot lava is worth buying? Um, it depends on how much you'd like to jump
and grab stuff. Who did it? Answer it. Did we get him? Did we get the streamer?
Close the door. He's throwing. Oh no, don't die in here. Oh, please. Why did you open it? I was
closing it. Oh no. How did he get in? Did he actually get in? He got in and it's one of these
guys. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm blocked. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead here. Just don't. What
do I do? Come on, Foxy's right in front of me. Duckies to my right. I can hear Freddy. I can
hear him through this ear. I need to do something about that. I can't continue like that. Gasoline's
the easy answer to be able to get planks. I'm going to bring the dresser. Yeah, that's not a
bad idea. Weapon parts. I have something for you actually. I have something for you. Should I sell
the jewel? Whatever it is. Cause I have some stuff that's worth some money. I got pills. I got the
shells. It's worth 130 bucks. Shiny stone. I don't think I'm ever gonna have a shotgun.
At least not now. I'm just gonna do it. Whatever. If it's a bad idea, it's a bad idea. It's okay
though. I need stuff now, not stuff later. 200. I'll have a lot. Which then can get me
fabric. I need this. I still need gas too though. Handgun, bolt handle, long barrel.
What about the axe, blade, shovel? There's too many things to do.
I don't know. There's too many diff. I don't know. I don't know.
Wire. It's done. Whatever it is, it's done. Gasoline too. Bucket. Like I need it. Okay.
Front door. Front door. Front door. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait. Wait.
All right. The front door. Now I need something better than that. All right. Now I need to fill
this up a little bit. Okay. Turn this generator off. Sour Jupiter. Really? Nice job. All right.
Now I can make... What the hell happened? Lockpick. At least I have a lockpick now.
I need to repair this, which means I have to go... Wait. Did I turn it off?
I did, right? Yeah. Why do I have loud P? That's an old reference that I have not seen in a very long
time. It's been a while. All right. Planks. Need them. Planks. Need them. Planks. Need them. Plenty
now. Repair this. It now does more damage, which is good. And then I need to move some stuff.
Oh, shit. I need nails. What was that? You guys heard that, right? All right. Can I buy nails?
I can. Just give me 10. I heard that if somebody was walking around. All right. Now this thing is
good. How many torches do I have? Zero. I want at least two. Seems good to me. I need whatever that
is. I am going to board this shuttle, because what's the point of leaving out this front door?
There is none. I always go out the back door anyways. I need more nails. I need two more nails.
Don't do that. Why not? No, I'm doing it. That's how they keep getting in. Dermot, you answer the
door when it knocks at night. Should I really be doing that? Okay. Give me the other gasoline.
I'll take it. All right. I'm done. Lockpick. Get rid of the boards. Keep two torches. One in the...
here. Get rid of the bottle. Get rid of the stone. Keep the bandages. Keep the lockpick.
It's time to explore. I'm ready. I'm going for it. I've got a good weapon now. I'm going...
I don't know. Burn down house. Or the... I mean, this is where I need to go.
I can go up. Okay. I'm gonna go up. Up. I have heels, right? I have three bandages.
Let's go. I'm gonna go straight up into the air. Go that way. Ah, this is a high-level zone.
I went into the high-level zone. Where are you going? Where are you going?
Where's it going? Why'd it do that? I got a shiny stone. I got it. Why is there a rooster? All right.
Why did they run away? Is this dog dead? This dog doesn't look dead.
Where am I? Where the hell am I? Oh, this is the burnt house. I can do this now.
I can do this shit now. All right. Stuff. Stuff. Anything. Search the sack. Alcohol.
Bedding. Nobody in the bed. Wardrobe. Oh, there's a flare in here and there's pills in here, too.
A note from the burnt house. I know they're there. I can hear them laughing. They're behind the wall
of trees. I can't get through by myself. The trees go... grow back too fast. Double mushroom.
Oh, this is perfect. Mushrooms. Just behind the trees. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Sofa.
Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yep. Yep. Yep. All right. I might be a little up.
I'm pretty close to leveling up, I think. Without a doubt. All right. Easy. Come on over here.
There's a red log. Come here. Come on. What's a red log? There's a pig. Right? The pig. What?
The pig door? The pig door, right? Something was just on my leg. I'm not kidding. What was it?
I don't know. I felt something. I promise. Didn't the guy say that there was a pig?
Red seesaw. What's the significance of the red seesaw? I have a lot of mushrooms now.
Nothing in here. What? I swear there was a pig door. No. All right. Well, I got the burnt down
house now. Check the sofa lol. Sofa lol. All right. Okay. White dress. A white child-sized press.
And the thing that's $450. Do not die. Get this back so I can- that's a lot of money.
Let me see. Right there. All right. I'm up. Why am I- people are asking why I'm killing the dogs.
Because they're trying to kill me and I'm just trying to live. I've got a $450
piece of fabric in my back. I am not going to lose that one. Bingo. Nice. All right.
Every time. I swear. Hot bar upgrade. Inventory upgrade. Okay. I wanted the slots. Only two slots.
Antidote. No, no. I want to level up. Speaking of that. 120 out of 150. I need three more mushrooms
and I get to level up. Almost new powers. Yeah, I just need three more mushrooms. Oh, that's cool.
All right. Nice. So the burnt house is pretty much completed. The wedding though. I don't have the
key code to get in. I should be making some traps. All right. So let's go with chain trap
and then I'm going to go with bear trap and then I'm going to go chain trap again. Bear trap.
Now let's take a look. Repair item. Get that completed. I still have a lot of time so I'm
not going to do this yet. I have a lot of junk in my inventory. I can do this again?
No, only once. All right. I'm going to take this time here to try and find a chest to open,
which I think there was a couple over here. I still have about four hours or so.
There was a chest over here somewhere. Like legitimately right here. Pretty good. Yeah,
I think that deserves a few peepo dances. Nothing else? Oh, I got a couple of these now.
I'm going to be making some money now dog. Excuse me. By the way, you can always tell when I look
at chat when I go like this is that you guys are right there. All right. Now this is the underground
passage place, which I can't do anything here. This is the end game. That's how you leave. That's
how you win. I'm trying to find mushrooms though in the few hours I have. Win, win, win, win, win.
I can't win. Not yet. I'm going to head. I'm going back down towards wedding, but I need to find a
couple more mushroom. I've already done this. And the anime is lame. All right. I, why are you
saying that? Where did that come from? Wire, alcohol, magazine. Is it GQ or better homes and
gardens? Just farming those minus twos. Don't mind me. Minus two for every dog that you kill.
It's not fair. I can't. It's too far away. All right. I've got to get back.
My face came too dark. Oh, I'll fix it later. Where the hell am I? Oh, wait a minute.
Is this back at the? Yep. All right. This is back at the scrap yard. Yeah. All right. Let's go.
Ooh, that's a corpse area. I missed no room and inventory.
Shit. I need those nails. Uh, what was that? I don't, nevermind. Let's get me out of here.
All right. What should I eat? What do you guys think? What do you think is the number one thing
I should eat? Oh, nevermind. I can't eat anything. That's you guys would suggest.
Right. I'm on like, I'm on a, nevermind. I have to eat the stuff that's in the fridge.
Dammit. That sucks. I can't eat like loaded potato skins. Like somebody just said, I have to eat
lettuce, like plain meat. I have to do a FODMAP diet for like a week or two.
But should you guys know how hard it is to do a FODMAP diet? A FODMAP diet is you cannot have
any form of garlic or onion or fructose, essentially. It's a carbohydrate thing.
And weirdly enough, garlic and onion is in every single goddamn food in this entire country of the
United States of America. Garlic powder, onion salt, onion powder. It's in everything. It's
in every single food in the whole country. So I can't really go out to eat until I figure that
out. Oh, and I love onions. I love, okay, hold on. I love onions. I love garlic. It's one of my
favorite things on earth, but I cannot eat it for a while. That's the unfortunate thing. I don't
know. I got a lot of gas, so I'm going to go sell this magazine. No, I think I can, let's just turn
it on. Let's just, I got plenty of gas, but now I need to block this door. I ain't dying. Okay. It's
in here. The window is boarded up. This one is this one is they're all are. All right, hurry up.
We're good. I think right, that's good. Right. What did you do? I don't have time to change this.
Oh, no, that's not good. I don't have time to change. You want to. I don't have time change it.
I don't have time to change it. I have time to change. I don't have time to do it all. I
have time to do it. I have time to do it and has to say I was gonna stand right here change it.
Oh, I think I just got it. Okay. There's the door, right? The door is right there,
right traps you need traps traps traps bear trap should put it down like right
here what should i do try just put it up here
in front of the windows can they get in the windows they can't get in the
windows right yes top window
my phone just turned on because somebody texted me
this is the safe room right here oh they're right here what's that why is it
blinking almost done i have a lot of stuff to
sell too i'm very shiny shit all right we're good
this is the strategy just keep this load this room up with complete and total
traps big bureau in the way nobody's gonna
get in here i should have enough money to do some
stuff too but how do i get out well i don't have to
get out till tomorrow morning so i'll be fine
no i just kind of ruined that sorry 8 a.m
day eight cool i have something to show you
no i don't i thought i got a like a dress or something
all right let's get rid of this i have something to
stash too i ate the dress did i i don't think so shiny stone i got two
shiny stones get rid of the meat let's do
shine yeah i'm gonna make a ton of money right here
couldn't i that could have been in the game i don't know 275
and i could get an axe blade that's the play
what are you doing that's the play axe blade
do i need an axe handle yes shovel blade shovel axe blade
what do you think stupid what do you think stupid
i'm getting it all right press one in the chat if it's if it's axe blade press
two in the chat if it's shovel go somebody's hitting forward 20 done
regardless of that's the outcome that's gonna play out here i'm also gonna get
more wire you only have one wire what are you stupid
what do you think stupid so all right let's get this shit in here
gasoline gasoline how much gasoline do i have is there a sort inventory
by type or something another battery three batteries
alcohol rag matchsticks yes your mouse okay sort it yourself
all right okay scrap metal scrap metal yeah i could die
in in in blizzard games i just press a button and it does it
please omega lard those traps would be fine for a while
make another lock so this i got two of these right no i only have one of these
what this game is not even good i have one lock pick
not even remotely fun all right um what do you mean i set off chat what are
you talking about everybody relax i want to show you why
don't you see how easy it is for me to control my chat room
so how do i make this upgrade item repair item
can i hold on can i do i have to just hold this thing like a big lollipop
and hit people with the head does that work
you need a workbench upgrade i'll be able to craft more items and
fit more upgrades into weapons when i upgrade my workbench and i need
a toolbox the generator is still on god crap it's all right what do i need to
get upgrade workbench i need like a i don't
where do i get the tool thing i don't know
i still have everything that i need from four
i'll be all right all right store this i got my toothpick
let's go repair the yeah yeah i guess i'll do it i need more
knives knives i've been to the wolf camp no that's probably a good idea what did
i do this for oh this yeah i got those knives
lockpick watch torches board with extra nails
i'm going up this way to the wolf's camp but does that mean there's actually
bulbs here let's try this i wish i could save scum
this game i would do it every time i'd be such a scumbag all right here we
go up here just to check it out
exploring everything antlers will sell for 150 dollars
really holy why did you say it like that okay let's go this way over to the left
that'd be easy here wolf's camp weird shadow i got all day i got the board
i'm looking for mushroom i need to do the mushroom shit i can smell your stench
from far away meat isn't this a guy that i didn't this guy come to my house
is this a bite will he eat it out of my hand
yes meat gossip if i were you i wouldn't venture too far from here unless you get
bored of your lousy life meat only a few returned from the dense
woods and those who made it back were not
able to share their happy stories he he he what do you got he's got a
chain you also have a watch you got wires too i don't know i can't
really show item beautiful item wouldn't recommend
don't wander on wait what do you have you had a
toolbox what does he like i'm not trading watch for
toolbox he likes meat ed do you have any of the stuff here
your meat he likes biscuits he likes weapons and ammo okay
so if i have any weapons or ammo i'm gonna bring it back to this guy and then
get the toolbox well thanks that was fun uh i'm gonna go
this way now should i bury this should i just bury
this in the back this head and take it no this this isn't daisy
well hey man i just want to say hello here like you're uh
yeah you want to be our team up and have friends
happens every time oh shit nice anytime there's two people that come up to you
in those games they're always going to kill you because
they're in a chat together hanging out they're in a separate skype call and
you're not in that call you're dead i'm just using skype as a
reference point discord fine and no that's not incorrect because
daisy is not popular anymore it was really popular when skype was really
really popular too so that does i don't need to retract that statement
150 dollars 150 dollars somebody said it here
meat i keep saying it weirdly though holy shit he's he fights
he and he's very very powerful why didn't you tell me to do this
i was under the assumption no i ain't gonna kill this fucking thing you're
kidding me i'm chasing after an elf with a board
with nails in it you think i'm gonna win
he's a trap hold on lure him into the trap lure him into the trap
hit him hit hit him hit him please god my voice just cracked four times
i just seen there they are they weren't kidding
150 the liar i pressed too hard down on the horn you know when you squeeze a
horn really instead of going like it goes like that's what i just did
or i got an elk by the way that's that's what happens anytime somebody's voices
crack they're pushing too hard on their stomach horn
i have to i didn't get a heal the tree is a goo
i don't know who was over here oh broken down tractor i don't mind if i
loot it
battery oh no what do i do how do i do what do i do with this
um what's useless here i'm just gonna make some stuff hold on
i got a fucking battery dude lock pick and uh another bandage battery mate nice
i don't know what it's for but nice what do i do with that
does dog like batteries broken tractor i'm here
maybe i can sell the battery to the dog well it's not a weapon but you know
you understand uh and i think i i think that's enough
face cam for a night okay i'm going back i'm kidding jesus
people people are giving subs uh raddest raccoon gave five community subs and
then the great canadian fk club gave five community subs as well thank you
both of you back to back thanks a lot appreciate that thanks for
the subs and congratulations those who got those subs
use the new emote well as you know this is germa985 where he has
probably 17 or 18 open emote slots but you get one every four months it's a
drip feed all right hold on here i still want
mushrooms there's a new emote yeah it's germa
vacuum cleaner i got so much gas it's too much actually
thrown in the trash what do i got
antlers storm look at all this gas all right i can
you guys thought i was gonna have a problem with gasoline i'm gonna do some
inventory management right now gas is going down to the bottom
i'm gonna do it by fill quantity what happened what's
whoa they're all okay never right so i'm gonna
all right um wood we'll go above gasoline anything made out of wood
antlers are technically wood okay so bottle why do i even have these
pills no stones why do i have these stones
electronics is going to go next anything that could be electronic
metal things that have made out of metal okay drugs and alcohol is next
okay um things that cause a fire not bad things that have made out of
wood and then rubber this is just kind of
miscellaneous up here all right scrap metal goes down here
nail goes down here things these things that have made out of metal alcohol
battery this is electronic or things that have made out of metal
drugs i don't want anyone to tell me that i'm fucking insane because that
you heard that somebody was just walking around
clip the last 30 seconds the last 10 seconds there's somebody here
okay i got that's fine organic material and go here this is like organic
material why is it so quiet okay uh arcanite
reaper thanks for the five community subs appreciate it
15 subs one two three back to back to back thanks a lot guys
i need to open some chests i gotta repair this
we're good nice and repaired what do i want to do tomorrow
i need to live through today car battery i'm gonna go take this
let me take the gas first before this gets too late
what do i got here generator and switch it on no
uh you the vilemi just gave five thousand bits
thank you for the five thousand bits from vilemi and they say germa psycho
well thanks for the huge amount of money there's also an emote came in there was
a mega cheer and now there's an emote i got an emote
what is it is only visible to me what is it
what's a mega cheer i don't know whatever it is thanks should i do it
show us i don't know what it was i don't know what it was
um show i don't know what it was it was like a treasure chest
what's it called uh i've i don't know what it's called
germa no what's it called secret emote treasure treasure chest
i don't know if they could treasure chest check your rare emote stash
that's not a thing is it yeah there it is there it is there how do you do that
rpg empty did it work no i did i spell it wrong whatever
thanks for the emote hey thanks for the emote wrong capitalization
was it really i really am just like shiny right now
it's a scary game my blood pressure is going on
all right let me think about what i'm gonna do here i have traps set up
everything's good to go i have my fighting stick close this door
push this back to where it was that's good all right i didn't turn on
the generator you think antlers are wood and you wonder why we call you an idiot
i love how one of these is can you eat deer antlers why would you do that
i just i typed in what's the material for antlers
it's not bone it's not cartilage it's a it's not made out of bone or
uh kerosene whatever the hell the thing was it's cartilage it's a cartilage
material that's wood like that's what it said said it's a cartilage material
that is wood-esque wood dash e s q u e although not wood it is a wood-esque
substance that comes from cartilage not bone not kerosene yes i'm
intentionally saying the word kerosene intentionally for all of you here where
are you over here there you are for all you hear that think i'm doing
this on purpose i am okay i said kerosene instead of keratin
okay there all of you oh fuck i have to leave
i blocked myself out of the room oh the generator i forgot about the generator
get it on safe thanks guys you you really saved me there you really got me
saved there thanks a lot guys that one first j why
would i press j why do you want to press j is there something i need to do should
i what does it do i'm begging you don't cool
thanks guys into the damn savages everything should go smoothly
i don't remember anything since the attack on our camp somehow i'm wearing a
coat so i must have changed my clothes on
my way here i don't recognize myself anymore
i can barely hold this pencil has my body changed i no longer feel
hunger or thirst what is happening to me i remember his face the face of the man
who saved me then held me captive i don't know how i
managed to escape his hut ended up here what i do know is that the
insane fucker took my key my only chance to
get out of the woods he also took out all the pages from my
journal i doubt that he was able to learn the location of the
underground passage though i should check if the door is still
locked just to be sure i must find him i don't think he
still lives in the same place where he held me makes no difference
as i have no idea how to get back to that vile place
this the time's not going forward i thought that was going to be burning
time and now my hands are tingly because i've
leaned back that was a yawn that that was almost a yawn
but don't yawn on stream because then people think you're bored or tired
don't yawn on stream that's a good tip for you
if you're gonna if you're gonna be a streamer don't yawn on stream
it makes people think that you're fucking tired and bored and not unsatisfied
take it from me yeah they come you can always tell when someone's trying to
hold a yawn because they look like a lizard that just
ate a bug they go if you didn't know speaking of
lizards did i tell you guys that i was thinking
about getting a couple of like frogs or like a bearded dragon did i tell
you guys this i'm thinking about getting a bearded
dragon and they like so they're cool or like two
like a couple of tree frogs they're real chill yeah i've heard that
awesome get a crested gecko day that was on that was one of them too
i think i'm not being attacked right baby tree frogs
you'd be an awesome frog dad
which door no they're in the house now okay
thank you i was just being too loud and my like roommate banged on the wall
fuck what do i do about this what do i do about this
do i just have to let him come in and then step in the trap and then kill
i'm ready no he's not coming in no okay this is plenty of hp on it
i'm not i don't think he'll get through it today he'll be back tomorrow
the other doors are they i'm kidding that wasn't real
i just made so many people yawn for a second i didn't recognize the germa
sour emote i thought it was a germa yawn emote they could both be the same thing
that's the start of a yawn or jeremy just ate a bug and he's a lizard
that has endless possibilities i think
why are there bugs in here come on hurry up and turn to dawn
before he gets in no day number nine day nine gain reputation 100
now is when i go get the box 104 i want the toolbox should i get a
couple of these though i don't want any of these get the box
get the box get the box okay hold on time is frozen right
now in the house yeah i know i don't what do i want to sell
the antlers don't sell the antlers sell the wood
sure sell the animals i mean that's 100 right 150
that'll give me 200 now there's a reputation with this trader
is that the same thing with the the dog guy so if i have 200 now i have to sell
it to the dog guy so sell antlers to dog guy and then
find a gun all right i need to i need to fix the uh the walls there
how many do i need let's get a gasoline can here and you know what
i just we're talking abundance i've got so much
money you know what i mean like i i've got so much money i'm just gonna dump
the whole thing in here i got so much gas i've got too much
money let's just let's do it except don't do that because there's no
reason to do that because why would i do that
i'm gonna put the rest in here what difficulty am i on this is on the
second highest i believe it's called nightmare
or whatever it is like uh extra hard okay that's fine what's that
that was just one of those fake guns that when you pull the thing it makes
that rotator thing spin in the back and it goes like
you guys know what i'm talking about they're the toys
i need to hear that again when you pull the trigger you actually put pressure
and you makes a mechanism spin around and it clicks
you'll hear it and then you want to be able to unhear it no not a taser
okay i need to fix what does it take to fix it
this is fine this is the one i have to fix down here don't step in it
dismantle it
barricade oh no i need i need six more needles
you got those don't you one two three four five six
i put why to do seven back on here
um i need a handle all right um all right really no no no all right
very i have to go turn on the this way i'm gonna make some more
planks out of the wood i think there's wood in
here too yeah there's wood in here load it up
plenty show this guy the plastic duck didn't i already do that
that wood goes down here
plastic i did this already didn't you can you can only show the photo the road
all right looking good hot settle into the next hideout soon
down here all right so but does do my my work i have to take all my tools and
stuff with me right does do my work is it like diablo
where the stash down there is the same stash that's not how this works
oh shit i have to start to bring it down there then
are you serious there's a guy that does it for me okay
all right well for the meantime i need to get
that well i gotta go to wolf's camp i gotta bring him shit that he wants
um antlers bring the meat with me am i gonna find some more stuff i have
to sell him something that he's gonna want it's 200 adventure time
no no not the show not the show the game i'm sorry i probably scared a few
people let's go in the meantime i let me hear like
somebody screaming all those are dogs okay there are a couple
of chests down here that i probably can find
two lockpicks let's go for it i remember this one
shut up shut up shut up don't don't even where are you
what what why who is going like
those chests right there dude
that don't even need a lockpick oh hell yeah
i can do another upgrade now nice backpack too
oh it's like 10 feet away from my house anything else over here look up at
chests and then we have to go up to the wolf
slow down it's only 9 a.m that's plenty of time
there's an amazing chest ahead ahead where
what does that mean just i thought there was another one
hey fellas vaude here germ was about to die lol
i want to make sure i've uh tackled this one
head on no i am not about to die it doesn't happen
don't listen to random people in chat that say incorrect stuff
wish you were here by the way right we're at the camp but this has got to be
something else over here right something secret no oh here i am
here i brought something for you i have antlers for you i need a hundred
more dollars 90 more actually well just take that
meat too what about drugs do you do drugs
i'll find something i'll be back stay there i'll be back
i'm thinking over here there'll be a uh chest
i'm gonna be here before i don't break this it's my only means of protection
that would be bad well i don't even you don't get experience but you know
it happens and it scares the shit out of me every time every single time
no i need to sell i just need that toolbox so i can get out of here
i need to go down to that silent forest get me out of here i'm just going for it
now no not enough time there's plenty of time
i'm going for it right now let's go i got tools
catch your breath down to this hideout and that's how we find
chest not that cool actually kind of kind of shitty not really that cool
down here is the forest i'm not going to stop i'm just going to
go into the new hideout which is down what does it go all the
way this no people don't spawn in here right
right i'm taking out the light three three three three
three wait didn't i already did three three three three three three three
didn't i it's boy three three three is the
password for every single door that's not secure what's going on
that's a shortcut i see all right let's do it
let's go all right down to the silent forest hideout straight down
uh-oh why am i looking at you guys for like help
i'm gonna walk them into the into the into the bubbles
heal what's my visibility okay hold on a second
wait uh okay i don't like the noises um what do the drugs do just take them
should i just take the drugs i'm gonna take the drugs what do they do
somebody help me what do they do alcohol another staff
they fuck you up bottle okay free bottles staff of the shovel what is that
real wait i already have a stick i have a stick
already this i have a stick in my inventory
already taking another stick i have to make a decision now i'm
spending wasting so much time match sticks
or take the drugs or the one wire make a lockpick i only have one wire
put drugs on the stick eat the pills okay that's that was worth it
where the stick go i have no idea what the stick is and i kind of don't care
i have to this thing's gonna break i have to start using this it's gonna
break i don't want to break that thing yet i'll
kill you with the two guys here that's a thrower god damn it
ah where is he i have two superheroes i guess okay easy i have so much there's
gonna be so much shit right here all right i think this won't break
an idiot get to the hideout which one which one
oh fuck this stuff um uh just come back just come back come back
come back just come back come back come back okay all right all right all right
okay hideouts hide down here right just
hide out is right here wait wait wait wait wait wait
hurry up just go to the first one i have time do i okay i'm going to first one
stop hitting tab it's right there but i i don't have any um i gotta go to the
old one because i don't have anything boarded up
i have to go back i have nothing boarded up
that whole place is always open i could kill i'm good all right
i've got and i got a gun now you have plenty of time no i don't i don't do i
don't no no no no no i don't i don't i'm not gonna do it i'm not gonna risk
it's right here i'll be fine what's this so much time i don't know no no i don't
i have four hours that's not it's barely any time at all
straight up here you're out of time no i didn't
no no way not to be not to build up all the board i don't even i don't know what
the place looks like there could be seven windows i'm going
here in the morning yeah i don't know they could have a giant bay window out
the back how am i supposed to know look i'm safe
they got french doors yeah i don't know get the toolbox now but just i need to
make sure that i'm gonna be safe first not yet i i'm gonna do it i gotta
do it this way i have to okay inventory upgrade yeah yes
or should i do the hot bar i'm going for the inventory good
okay now i have a gun let's store this in my new category which we're just
going to start now that category is weapons weapons and clips
i've got gasoline i'd like to fill those two together
i've got a full row of gasoline now battery
pills goes in the drug category which is down here stop buying so many
would i buy did i buy something i love how the watch never goes away
okay what about torches i'll just do double torch put it away
put the torch away i need to repair my stick good and then
i have a stick right stick and staff go together
upgrade item no i would upgrade the workshop
i need the thing i need it's also gonna happen tomorrow okay i have to do this
now i have to do this now i gotta be ready uh i
didn't get anything to cook right i need to turn on the generator and
i need to fill the generator with gas there it was see the thing the try me
at the at walmart the thing where you go like it's like
it's like a toy shelf you know i'm talking about the try me
thing not a taser no like at the toy section in the toy store
no don't drink coffee at fucking what time is it 7 30
what's it called a toy gun the demo mode for a toy gun
german just do your fucking job i'm i got an hour i'm fine
you know that thing that's at the toy store it's like it's a fake gun that you
pull the thing in the lever and it makes that sound when it goes around the
circle you don't have talking about guys wait i did this right yeah that's fine
right i did i did that i repaired it no i didn't did i
barricade no it's barricaded you didn't close the door
they're not gonna get in this if they do i'll bash them
the generator door what do i care about the generator door
they'll turn it off what that's not real no i don't believe you
that's fine you know when you go to the or and
on the toy there's all kinds of fake when you pick up
and you it makes this derma you forgot you put your diaper on outside
shit sorry about that all right i have to pay attention because i have to deal
with this for like the next six hours keep the lamps far away from the
windows because of the light i don't push that
up out of don't move that out of the way put in
like the corner am i making noise am i making too much
noise can we get a diaper check yeah oh boy you don't
jesus it's because i have two headphones in
i i can't i can't like comprehend it something i sure shouldn't say is in my
one of these are my ears where is this guy get open back
headphones just did i i've tried them on in the store
before who's he hitting is it orc outside
lifting weights answer the door right somebody i i want
a unanimous opinion to go answer the door answer the door are you sure
yes should i answer the door what door is the one i'm supposed to be answering
i'm not i i can't answer the door the hell are you selling right now
no i'm not doing it answer it no not right now maybe another day
yeah i have to yeah was it too late why is there a helicopter all right
no the timer just started what am i doing out here
where's the trader oh come on did i seriously just
come on man actually pissed off about this truly angry about this
uh i'm gonna bring two uh gas cans with me
i'm gonna bring the shovel i'm gonna bring the guns
the ammo and the wood i'm also gonna bring the
alcohol and i'm also gonna bring the tire why would i bring the tire
the stick i'm gonna sell uh this is why i came not capable of
games like this sell the the medium caliber magazine to
the wolf get the toolbox uh that's what i'm doing i just i have
to do this and just get this over with store the gun frame you can't build it
yet but i'm gonna bring it down to the new hideout
game scary yeah it is pretty scary it's good though it's fun
you need to get the sunglasses with speakers in them what the hell are you
talking about they make those i think that's inside of like the
sky mall magazine those things definitely don't work
broken tree what about it oh oh all right cool i can't take the wire but
i'll i'll be back i'll be back over here there's a dog all right trade let's sell
you medium caliber magazine and then i'm
gonna buy the toolbox yes accept it
toolbox i've received i need a few people to tell me
if in the new hideout do i have to upgrade everything again
let's go i'm on my way to the new hideout
down here new hideout time to board windows new spot
that link what do i mean that link but just like
the you right clicked on the google image search instead of actually going to
show the source is that what you're talking about
and it's like and it's like the side of like a cheese's box
amount of text bread cheese and salt what are all those
ingredients let's be real here it's like ice cream
milk sugar done why is why are there some foods that have the amount of
it's cereals like this too why is it like the back of a clorox bottle
the ingredients like this fucking long clorox
only has one ingredient hey hey i heard a werewolf all right got plenty of
time poo okay hideout is right here there
might be somebody in here though this place would make a good hideout
yeah if it wasn't already occupied by three demons let's find out what's in
here all right i'm ready do i have to activate
this do i have to like lie in the bed oh fuck this all right
okay um cooking stove oven oh light the oven yeah
the oven is lit again i don't have any mushrooms
silent screaming is what i'm i knew there was somebody here
you asshole
ah fan belt gasoline all right this is a generator
now this is saw where's the generator all right this is where we dump the gas in
here the whole thing turn off do it again fill
this up too we're gonna be in this place for a while
that's why i brought the gas cans i'm gonna need them
stop okay fan belt all right now what on earth
okay i've got to start getting this place ready the room
all right where's my why was that so loud that was really strange bike bell
hold on a second let me just get this in here
what was that there's something else in here bathtub
oh no hold on um hold on i need to ring the bike bell i'm not going to do
ah there's something in here there's an animal i'm doing really good job not
screaming though what was that what was that
what was that what the hell was that okay um
uh i have to go out here
no no no no run run run run run run run don't die here please
close the door close the door close the door close this door i don't have any
doors where is he are you all right i don't have
time for this shit i don't have time for this shit wait
uh what is that i have a trap i need to make it i need to get trapped
we're gonna get a trap in the kitchen oh you motherfucker
a rusty bell someone has attached a note to it liquor tasting
and transport services fast and efficient call now
something is happening bike man hey there boss
i'll be honest here boss i'm really thirsty you see
if you could share a refreshing beverage with a weary traveler i'd make it worth
your while boss ashes to ashes dust to dust when life's a bitch
booze is a must ah good vintage bottle a day keeps the
monsters way to your health boss if you want boss i can bring you junk from
the other hideout which hideout should i take the junk from
boss from dry meadows on like a nun in a
cucumber field i don't know what that's supposed to mean
i don't know what that is um okay so where is my
what does he come back i need a trap i need
tools i need to board windows i need to put
stuff in boxes and there's a giant dog that's in here that's going to kill me
so let's i need to prepare the doorway i need up don't have anything actually
don't have i have nothing literally nothing uh it's not going to
work i have to leave i have to kill the dog but i have an
hour how do i board the windows i'm gonna die i
need needles i need needles to do this i'm
not ready for this why did i bring all my stuff here
run back but all my stuff is being brought over here
where is he does he come back when does he come back cook
didn't already do this oh somebody gave 5 000 bits
thanks for the 50 bucks remember the guy knocking on the door in the first
hideout will give you access to the wedding house please don't miss it
also fortify the generator roman's second hideout and bring all the
furniture and lamps in there all right all right thank you uh spoons
for self-defense with a 50 dollars 5 000 bits appreciate it that's a lot
of money what do i do here moth was that a mistake
why is it dark why am i here what's going on
shiny stone uh this is a dream is this a bunch of free stuff
press your ear against the keyhole i've already done this i can hear a faint
voice through the howling wind it sounds familiar
seems to be coming through the keyhole someone's calling me look through the
keyhole and what is in there is it like a face okay
come to me it opened all the shiny stones i got a lot of these
i hope i get to keep them i feel i'm uncomfortable at the moment
dude do i got full stacks almost turn on the lamp are they gonna get up
uh yeah and it's a person lying down should i turn it off
okay more shiny stones active skill menu moth it's i okay i just slept for like
four minutes interesting there's still an animal here
where's the guy that brings the stuff i have to wait a day
i'm gonna die here i need nails i'm dead i have to i have to literally run back
backpack where oh i have time i'm almost out of time almost out of time
uh did i have any nails oh that's all messed up now
nails barricade that shit i don't have any nails
i can't use bottles as traps i have i okay i need to oh this is bad this is
bad what do i do i have to block all doors i have to do
what i have to do everything is stored right okay um
shiny stone is uh i can put over here come here get in the bathroom good idea
where's the bathroom right here all right put the tub over here
i need a lamp in here i need a light i need a light source
hurry up where's the light lamp right here okay block this with the bathtub
i'm going i'm going i'm going i'm going i'm not i'm not gonna panic good to go
okay bring the close this bring the dresser over here
this is just like when you actually move a piece of furniture get it in long ways
start turning it i could turn the generator on uh hold on move this
i'm like looking over here constantly for like reassurance
that's good spot all right let's turn the generator on no
forget it turn it on i'm fine okay and then you got it i got this i got this i
got this i do okay i've got this get back in the window and then
the bathroom is good i'm gonna sit here and just be quiet
pull this in here and then block this door hey you know those things just stand
here what if the light goes out it won't hide it get yourself in the
corner this is this is a corner this is the
corner stay in the center should i corner like this corner i don't know
what corner you guys want me standing get get in the tub why am i crying
that's scary man all right as long i need to pay attention because i would
have just seen where they were coming in from
oh my god he opened it with ease he just pushed it with his face
they can break the bathtubs guys what an excellent choice of
barricade it was it's made out of ceramic it can be broken you can break a
bathtub by putting a boot on it i'm not gonna move all of you say in
bottom right corner you're the real real gameplay
aficionados if i was standing in that top left corner
don't come back in here what's that mean what's that mean what's that mean
what's that mean what's that mean what's that mean
what's that mean what's that mean oh my god they've breached
how many were there that was like a hundred people i almost had them all
there was like 30 or 40 people in that room i got really greasy i got really
all right we're never going to forgive you don't
look at the crow oh that's a crow that looked like a
scary witch person uh okay it's been six hours i think that's
time to drag to to drain it down we'll continue tomorrow yeah we'll
continue this tomorrow never gonna finish it i've only got
like two extra i'm probably not gonna i'll try
go eat your no onion diet you freak hey i'm talking about my health here all
right yeah we'll we'll continue tomorrow i think like this six hours is a good
stopping point i'm all greasy games like this just
stress me the fuck out like this cortisol levels are just probably
so high right now but before i go here's the this is me faint reflection in the
semi-transparent visor of his helmet suddenly he starts to move quicker as
of looking for something i mean i died here and i just unlocked this place so
that's not even a problem there's no out of here he shows me what
he's written and then he wipes it with a sleeve and continues scribbling we're
stuck here with each other uh i have to make sure i've also read
the second sentence what was that just like a you weren't
paying attention the man takes out a full tank of gasoline from his sack he
places on the floor thanks appreciate the full tank uh i'd
need to where is it you said you put a full
tank of gas down here a little lie it's right here all right ah
upgrade workbench i'll do this first because i mean i'm just here
let's go bingo level three now i can make a gun
i just need tape the mushroom is rotting in my inventory
oh okay where the hell is it 480 shovel yeah i'm yep yep yep yep yep i'm
just i tell you before tomorrow before tomorrow's stream
i'm gonna eat like a nice like fodmap fucking piece of fish
i'm gonna be ready tomorrow i was ready today too but you know i'm gonna be i'm
gonna eat brain power food tomorrow with no garlic no none that was 50
essence holy what has it been worth more if i
it's okay all right i ration stamps is this a code all right um
already did this make sure i look at i have to turn off the generator
new emote tomorrow or riot what are you guys gonna just keep
bullying me into putting new emotes on this train
all right is the game saved the game is saved i think
no no no new emote tomorrow i gotta i gotta eat food and be ready
but that's it i'll see you guys tomorrow we're gonna do the uh outro here
dark wood's fun we'll see how far we get tomorrow probably the same time
somewhere around like one or two see you guys tomorrow for more dark wood
no new emote tomorrow did it work did it work did it work come on
i don't understand this thing i don't get this thing
why is it keeping this for what i even tried to reset it and change it
gifts 100 subs every stream wow why can i not get this to work
because this is a different session what happens if i just do it again
okay like well how about this um how about uh all-time top sub gifter
okay that works session top sub gift this this is this is the session by the
way a thousand subs right i forgot about that
so why is this not working monthly top sub gifter it's me
30 weekly top sub gifter it's clown daddy so why why session top sub gift
are not working i don't get it that's odd but i'll see
you guys tomorrow thanks for uh thanks for being a little
less messy inside of the theater just make it weekly i guess i have to
figure out why it's doing that hope the stream is a better title tomorrow
i wish i could pick the game as dark wood 1 and then make the title of the
stream dark wood 2 in fact dark wood no but i can't do
dark wood too because people think it was a sequel
dark wood one dash copy of dark wood that's funny okay that's that's what it
will be
dark wood one dash shortcut i like the dark wood one
dash copy of dark wood no this is a lot of fun though
i am happy playing it again we'll see how far we get to go
so let's do the bits because this is still something i can't seem to figure
up anyways let's get to it thank you earlier
what happened to the bitcoin donation that doesn't exist anymore
i had an ethereum address that was down there and i think
four or five dollars went through it over a year and a half
i don't have that down there anymore it's all good though
but thank you too oh wait a second this is the wrong music
this is saved i think right should be are you sure you want to quit you will
lose any unsaid progress time since last save five minutes 22 seconds yeah that's
fine that's okay that's what i was looking
for thank you to gibbler for the thousand bits
way way way way back hey germany chance you could make your face cam full screen
and put the game in the corner i don't like scary games
i don't really do well with scary games either but you know
i remember somebody saying well you really are like overreacting today
now that i just i drank two coffees and i played a horror game that's kind of
what happens super overactor today rate my fridge
out of 10 my current fridge is like probably like seven like six
but thank you gibbler appreciate it thank you frido man for the 1500 bits
finally caught a live stream been watching the stream archive for
the past two weeks while grinding mmos after work
and it's been a blast it's a small token of appreciation also play
indivisible it just got released i actually saw that
i seem pretty mixed things about it though people seem to really like that
game or really not like that game seems interesting though it's like an
rpg right turn base we'll see it is currently on steam now
but thank you for the recommendation thanks for the 1500 bits
dub ski dude thank you for the 250 bits appreciate it
this game is concrete proof that you are in fact an on-demand streamer
been waiting to say that for months thanks for playing this game by the way
dark wood is fantastic on demand streamer what do you mean
so is gifting yourself subs a way to avoid taxes
uh no no actually you can turn the content
on demand the truth comes out uh no that's not how it works
the money look the money gets taxed twice funny you say that
anyway thank you dub ski appreciate it lewis thank you for the 400 bits they
say wow wow that's it appreciate it lewis
uh tony thank you tony for the five community subs earlier
tony villanto villante thank you green 501 gave 300
bits earlier they say hello germ bimbo or germ bimbo bimba thank you
thank you green 501 101 dominations thank you for the 250 bits
hey germa like a ton of people here i've been a fan of you for a while
whatever you play you always manage to get a chuckle out of me and turning on
your stream when i wake up is like opening a door and seeing a
friend in the doorway thank you thanks for what you do and
greetings from the uh expat community of south korea
thank you so much thank you for the 200 bits
i appreciate anybody that decides to watch this channel for more
than 20 minutes you know if you've been here for a year you've been here for
a week you've been here for 20 minutes i hope you like it
maybe we'll see you again thank you for anybody that watches this channel
thank you 101 dominations thank you sad vega for the 250 bits they have a dog
here the dog emote i used my gamer keyboard
last week i created a g key function in vanilla wow
to buy a rear pattern before anyone else could
it did multiple macro functions at once within the period of a few seconds
making my life easier i also have a key that i pressed that
says germa's short in twitch chat while i play a game
um i don't think you should have sent that in a message
i don't think that's legal it's legal is it legal
i remember okay this i think there's a video of this happening
if you spun around in world of warcraft fast enough the game would disconnect you
from the client me mlc stealth inside there
was another there was like two or three other people there
but there was a video of this of mlc stealth spinning around at five
thousand miles per hour and he just gets booted and we just
kept getting booted from the game you had to it was a joke though it was
not oh let me just spin around with my mouse
you had to turn your dpi up to like 10 000
and then just have your character go like a blender in a circle
and you get you got like kicked out there's a video from like
seven or eight years ago longer than that probably
now sensitivity 999 million is it this let's see uh yes yes this is the video
yes this is it you found it let's like let's go adventure or are you going to
like disconnect again
this is it what was our names i can't believe that like
disconnects you i'm going as fast as i can
why isn't it working my name is tornado
like tornado hold on a second tornado let me just put a browser in here
you know what i need to get i need to figure out as a live streamer
i need a good like extension that is just a web browser that's just you put
something in here in his plays the video does that work how do i do that
let's see still his name is hot pocket because he used to eat them every day
get vlc okay hold on why is this not working
this is mildly irritating get on there what is this doing fucking computers
okay browser source go ahead i know you want to get on here
why is this taking so long no not browser source two
no not browser source two what am i looking at here
this is about to play like okay i don't know why this is playing
i didn't play this the whole bottle holy shit
did you get the clip that clip it somebody
on fucking monday that's the worst clip on my whole channel
it's homer okay here we go you're signed out membership
are you still here yeah i'm still here oh no okay he's back
he wiggles yes i got it i understand so hot pocket aka mlc stealth
yeah let's go let's like let's go adventure or you're gonna like disconnect
again
yeah this is strange love i can't believe that like
i remember i wonder how she's doing it's been a while
i'm going as fast as i can why isn't it working
it's like he's having a seizure
there i go two dollar mike this is like it's
eight years ago i can't believe that actually works okay so you're just
wiggling the mouse around yeah hold right i want to see if this
really works you know i'm like being a troll and
pretending to do it as fast as you can
why is this a video
you just have like a realization you're like wait we like recorded this
it's like three minutes of just like we disconnect oh i think we all
recorded this classic 2010 youtube yeah you recorded
everything you don't you didn't want to miss
anything what is this
why do i have two ads double ad
i've never seen a double ad oh don't worry we can do it
what does that look like
i'm not watching this video i'm not watching this
i'm not gonna watch this video
nothing has changed yes it has oldham is full of treasures my friend
treasure i like that i'm done i'm not watching this video anymore
you can watch it on your own time i'm not watching that video ever again
guys listen to me all right i have something i i made a thousand videos
thousand of them okay so i don't i where are how i don't know you know where
are we got over here i don't remember that we're here get the
janitor up here please and that's the cam that cam is on
would have been embarrassing i wasn't ready for you
all right let's keep going i forgot that was the cam button
all right so we also had uh oh it was the person that said they had a
macro for a while right okay my face is the same color as
this shirt what are you talking about i don't have it
orange it's not orange it's just like it's like a little tint of red
i've been it's hot in here do you know where i live
like it's cold thank you too uh sad vega though appreciate uh they say uh
germa i work in it and i can tell you the fn key is very useful for fixing
people who accidentally turn off their wi-fi
exactly why it doesn't need to fucking exist
why would you have a function key to turn off your wi-fi
just click in the bottom right of your screen and disconnect
uh and alter their screen when they accidentally press the fn key and
another key in a combo yeah i don't get it
you could make every single key 10 larger
if they was half these keys didn't exist there's so much more key real
estate your enter key could be bigger your
spacebar could be longer and larger your alt your control could be
bigger key you don't need bigger keys sometimes you do
it's an apple key on on an ipad or whatever whatever
but thank you uh sad vega appreciate the insight
door cube thanks for the 250 hey germa thanks for looking at my dumb
photoshop yesterday and saying wtf honestly it made my day i maybe i did
i don't remember yesterday i wasn't here yesterday
where was i uh thank you gnarly for the 250
appreciate it i'm having fun with the new germa sour emote
would it be awesome to have some community bt tv emotes enabled too what's
the point of chatting if i can't use germa wild
i'm not going to make another 24 hour promise here
but uh i can't you only have five better tv emotes enabled at once
do i have to do something else to enable more than 10 of them or 20 of them or
something how do i do that you can enable your own you can have
like 20 000 it's five dollars oh okay yeah i'll i'll take a look
into that particular thing that you talking about
thank you thank you narcoleptic bear for the thousand bits
uh appreciate the ten dollars there for when you have to wait out the night
you should move the lamps away from the windows as the light seeping through
will attract monsters this is essential for surviving nights later in the game i
have to now that i'm in a new space tomorrow
we're gonna really start to move around and we need some french rearrangement
here people why are people so strange uh
anyways thank you narcoleptic bear appreciate thank you dino pulse
zeta for the 500 bits do you think you could eat as much garlic as wario and
be able to fart as much as him if you wanted to
i'll tell you wario is way healthier than mario
wario eats garlic mario eats flowers that burn down his esophagus
wario only and mushrooms mushrooms and hot sauce
wario eats garlic and he's got some weight on him so you know that he's
probably eating some beef wario is 100 muscle shrooms and hot
sauce yeah that's not a great diet and sometimes cake he gets eats a ton of
candy and sweets too what else does mario eat mario
eats spicy food like just hot stuff like hot
sauce mushrooms but does he eat the mushrooms
or does it they just like disintegrate into his body
he eats like bird feathers cherries bird feathers
that's mario doesn't even even eat food wario at least eats food
his candy is not really technically it is technically a food
it's just like sugar but that's like a food group i mean no maybe it's not
it's not really food is it it's a carbohydrate what is food would
you break it down to an absolute zero it's just energy sugar is just energy
so it is you can't get energy out of a bird feather
luigi doesn't can't eat luigi eats the same stuff as mario
heat is food yes when you eat something it just gets converted into heat in your
body and energy and then you burn it then you have to fill
it again it's just like a bit you're just a gas tank
i mean that's true yes i mean that but that that's just basic
basic just raw science i could go into more of that
everything has energy idiot oh yeah so if i ate uh if i ate the like
the glass here that i could i would turn that into energy
i would not i would i would not if i sucked on this piece of plastic
red air i'm not gonna get any energy from that i can't turn that into heat
kelvin that's not your name that's the temperature that you use
prove it yeah kelvin hawkeye of mine thanks for the 800 bits germa you just
shit in my pants going outside like that that's that's like three or four strange
messages in a row but thank you appreciate it we also had
uh mason karki thanks for the 250 bits did you remember like a year ago when
you were building the birdhouse and put a chain around your neck like a choker
i haven't been able to get over it dude it was like so hot okay okay couldn't
believe it that's four that's four in a row
it's a full moon tonight but thank you appreciate it
also an anonymous cheer gave a thousand bits
anonymous sleeve is anonymous cheer no message or anything
thank you uh cn live gave a thousand bits as well right after that's
no message either bala koala gave 25 dollars
twice and the full moon is out so obviously they wrote peepee and then
they wrote poopoo with germa sour before each one of them 25 dollars each
thank you bala koala for the 5 000 bits total
and your full moon comment uh thank you your
ear zephyr zephyr for the thousand bits germa's reactions make scary games seem
like comedic rumps also funny scream uh but let me just
give 5 000 bits right now they say germa can you wear a collar on stream no
reason no i'm not going to wear the collar on
stream that's not gonna happen ever so just you have to accept that
that's not gonna happen the closest you're gonna get is when i
put that thing or that little choker thing around
that's it that's the only image you're gonna ever have
what are these messages i'm telling you i don't know
is the we have like a red moon or something we have like a green moon
tonight but thank you for the thousand bits
appreciate it gnarly thanks for the 250
by the way i saw people suggesting you play sc6 after you showed my characters
on stream i just want to warn you the character
creator is really restrictive and not really worth it when compared to wwe games
plus i'd have to play soul caliber which i don't want to do i don't have
anything against soul caliber i'm just saying i don't
i don't really want to play soul caliber you don't just make those characters
and then just don't do anything you have to play soul caliber
i'd get frustrated you know what would happen i don't even need to tell you
what would happen i would get shit on twice in a row and
i would it would piss me off more than anything and i would quit the game
and it would just be one of those streams or it was like oh he got like
angry like once every two or three years it'd be that stream
do cpu versus cpu no i'd still get angry because my guy didn't win
but yeah uh i didn't really have a plan but
your uh characters were fucking awesome so
thank you for those hey crispin thank you crispin three day for the 300 bits
and they just say pogchamp pogchamp pogchamp
sorry about that and let's get the credits on screen
they're right here i should be ready to do it i'm ready to go
are you are you ready for this to go see you tomorrow see you tomorrow right
more of this they should pop up there they are
thank you for supporting the stream anybody that subbed all the community
subs everybody it means a lot thank you again have a
great night we'll see you tomorrow we had a few more bits that came in
right here though we had white fox with 500 bits hey man just thought i'd
chime in i'm not sure if this helps but i spent three years not eating onions or
garlic for health reasons it is annoying for sure if you ever try
and eat out but some pro tips sushi and home cooking use lots of
your favorite produce to make up for it like avocado tomato uh really fresh
tasting stuff hope it all works out i was able to
tolerate onions again after a few years off of them by the way yeah
my doctor's not sure of what if that's what it is
but i have to do this diet for like a while i was supposed to start doing it a
while ago but going to do the carnival and then twitch
con you kind of can't it was just it was
gonna be too hard to start so i'm doing it now the diet is a low
fod map diet what's wrong with me no there's nothing wrong with me i'm okay
um yeah thanks for the tips i was making a joke that if i got a bearded dragon
that i'd have to eat a bunch more of good salad because they eat a shitload
of greens and healthy food so i was trying to
really sell this to kim by the way hey let's get a bearded dragon
and she's like uh i don't know are you sure about that i'm like yeah well we're
gonna eat more salad because we're gonna buy a bunch of
salad stuff to feed to the bearded dragon and then
we have to eat that salad too it's making us healthier did it work
i'm not sure yet but i want i want one either that or a couple of frogs either
that or like a like a little gecko or something
that's that's just fun they're cute plus for the frogs
there's another thing that i told kim i was like kim you want maybe i'll get a
couple of tree frogs and she's like oh really what's what do you and i said
don't worry it's on brand i will see you guys tomorrow wait hold
on fickle pickle just came in with five dollars 500 bits i saw you out but i was
too afraid to talk to you because you were watching the lizards get sprayed
but you were at this pet store that i happened to like stumble across
i literally saw you looking at the lizards
no you didn't no way this no way holy shit hey those lizards pretty cool
he spotted out in the wild at like the lizard store
that's fucking crazy you didn't even know why didn't you say something
you should have been like hey those lizards are real cool huh
hi drama and i would have been like hi how are you
that's fucking crazy you need to have a secret code
phrase for fans well uh i actually if you are curious i've been doing my
research and i have been trying to find places in
like the vegas area that has lizards and uh amphibians
so i've been to quite a few places interestingly enough
kim and i actually went to one yesterday and the day before
i don't think anyone would call you germa in public except for fans that's
what i'm saying lizard store meetup why would i ever do
that that would be so that would be so strange
but there actually are a couple places believe it or not
like three or four of them you kind of have to go
a ways but there are some great stores that have great
great great great selections can i bring my dragon
no what guys we're not doing a lizard meetup okay
the secret phrase is pee pants no just say hi
germa so i'll immediately know that what's going on every if anybody
sees me in public and it's it's happened a few times
it's it's all right you can go home say hi just be like hey what's up man
germa right and i'll be like yeah what's up how are you
it's happened a few times it's you don't have to you don't have to hide from me
you'll have to prove it's you now i'm trying to figure out like
who you were you know what i mean now i'm trying to figure out
who were you there you know what i'm saying i'm just like hold on and wait a
minute i'm scanning my memory like where were
they which was somebody did somebody look at me
did somebody look at me and like i made eye contact did it may have
happened once i don't know i'm trapped that's so weird
that's i that's so that's so interesting
say hi next time look i'm going all around to all the lizard stores
is it weird that knowing that lost people recognize you and don't show it
i mean i not really i mean i'll be honest with you
if if i was to go out and somebody was to say something like hey what's up it's
it's just like i would say hello to anybody anyways it's like oh hey how are
you good to see you how's school how's life how are you
doing how's your job and then you're like all right awesome
i'm doing good and tell you a few things about me and
all right i'll see you later like i'll see you later
it's not like it's odd you know people have conversations with each other all
the time guys i have conversations with people
like the coffee shops you know what i mean like somebody will say a sentence
you're just like yeah yeah yeah but ever do yeah but ever do and they're like
yeah but ever do you're like yeah but ever do
and then you just move on with your day right it happens all the time
all right see you tomorrow take care guys
i'll see you tomorrow we actually can go like this now
because it is the end of the stream take care everybody
much love to you have a fantastic rest of your evening
maybe i'll end up with a lizard i missed bits by crunchy pickles
what about a pet snake um four dollars by the way 400 bits
i here's the thing about snakes snakes are really really really cool
they're really really interesting and they're so
cute like a those ball pythons are just adorable i cannot feed a snake a mouse
i can't couldn't do it that's the bit that's the wall
and i know that you can get them frozen right but that's just i don't know i
can't this is too much for me i could feed a bearded dragon bugs
and k not kale uh like greens and stuff whatever they eat i have to you know
obviously still do some research if i'm gonna do it or not i could eat a i could
feed a bearded dragon bugs but not a rat or something no
i would get attached to the mouse but none of this is set in stone this is all
just i've been sort of looking at a handful
of stores in the area like in the vegas area so i've kind of been hopping
around like do they sell things do they sell things do they sell things do they
sell things let's get in the car let's go
so none of this is really set in stone i'm just doing research i don't know
i'm obviously trying to ask the right questions you're attached to a frozen
mouse no you you know what i'm saying though it's not
that simple if you do it you have to get a lizard cam
don't be it can't be the dragons just hang out and just sit on your shoulder
aren't they just super chill but they'll poop on you
that's all right whatever yeah there's a humidity control i've been
doing a lot of research they just sit around and act dumb i
don't know it's it's up there in the brain i'm gonna have to this is this is
a multi-month decision process by the way like i'm not
gonna turn the stream on tomorrow and there's gonna be a bearded dragon on
stream like no this is like a multi it's gonna take like months to figure
this out but see you guys tomorrow for more dark
wood take care see you soon have a great rest of
your night goodbye