It's time to move in. Why is everybody standing completely still? What is going on?
Let's go everybody. Welcome to your new home, the rumble house. You can go in.
They all immediately want to go to the gigantic stereo. Oh, they're turning it
off and turning it on. What the fuck are they doing? Why is everybody pulling on a
changer and turning it off and turning it on again? We'll see what happens. We got
Germa. We've got glue man. Grandpa. That was really weird. Why? Why are you doing
this glue man? Why is glue man doing sit-ups? Hmm. Okay. You're all supposed to be dicks.
You're all supposed to hate each other. Stop getting along. This is the rumble
house. This is not the like let's talk and have fun and be friends house. This
guy's in a fucking hot dog suit. Doesn't that piss you off? All right. How do I
control that? Okay. I'm gonna go to star. All right. Star, you're gonna start
all the trouble. You're gonna start trouble with glue man who is on like
drugs. Insult. Fuck you. Your underwear is gross. He agrees apparently. It's so
stupid. Everyone's having such a good time. I really just don't even know who's
gonna start the first fight. Eventually people are gonna start to get real
tired and somebody's gonna throw a punch. Nope. We're doing more sit-ups. All right. Turn
off the fucking stereo. Come here burger boy. Get over here. Turn the stereo off.
Turn it off. This party is over. Grandpa is just. Oh there we go. Here we go.
Grandpa's got like flaming drinks. Yeah. All right. Where do they put them? What?
Oh they're on the table. These drinks are on fire. What are you doing? What are you
doing? Where do you go? Did I tell him to do this? I like don't even remember
clicking on to for him to jog but apparently he's gonna do it anyways.
Wait. That's it. That was it. That's the whole jog. I really think he's coming
back. Did you seriously just. Okay. Wow. Holy shit. You didn't even go past the
property line and you're coming back and you're very uncomfortable. Well I wonder
why. Get back in the house please. Just go like start a fire in the fireplace.
Travel with. Well they all like hate each other. Where do we just go? Who did I?
Who did I not take? I don't know. Okay. So I guess we left behind. Let's see. One,
two, three, four, five. Who did I leave behind? And why does he got all his weight
back? Dude. Here we go. Oh here we go. Here's
something getting a little riled up here. Got an old rivalry with this one.
Glue man and Jerma. They hate all and they both drink at the same time. They're
both just pissed. Don't even tell me. Don't even tell me. That wasn't even the
right drink. That was. Where did I get that drink? I picked up like a bowl of
fruit punch and threw it in his face. All right. Well we're gonna. Uh-oh. Wait a
minute. Wait a minute. What? Oh you screwed that up. He's gonna piss his pants.
Yeah you gotta. We gotta make some friends. Everybody go over there quick.
Call her over. So say hello. We need to make some friends. We're all such
shitheads. It's like we need to like make a friend. I don't think she heard you. No
I really don't think she heard. No she's gone. You see that was a great job. You
did a great job making a friend. Well let's go check on the other. Let's go
check on the other crew. Who's this random lady that they got to do push-ups?
What is going on with this group? Why is this person over here doing
sit-ups? Well it looks like they made some friends. At least glue man did. Glue
man made a lot of friends. This entire bar and club like loves him. He's like
the coolest guy in town. Where's grandpa? Where'd he go? He's sleeping on a bench.
Good for you grandpa. He only had like ten gin and tonics. Okay. My like stomach
just kind of hurt from that. Somebody's gonna come in here and turn. Somebody's gonna come in
here and turn on the radio. I guarantee it. I bet you a thousand dollars somebody
comes in here and turns the fucking radio on and they're gonna wake up the
whole house. They're asleep. You can't. They're not listening to you. I can't.
Alright. Star's gonna pull a cereal. When is somebody going to pull out the remote
control? Turn on the stereo and wake up everybody else that's sleeping in the house.
We're still missing King Bia. Who knows if he made it out alive? Because he might have
on the way back. There it is. There it is. Who did it? I don't even think anybody did it.
Everybody just went like. Why are you all so stupid? Takes us one asshole. No one will ever
sleep in this house. Because somebody always goes I want to dance. I want to like to dance
now please. I swear to God if I come back again to somebody else doing fucking sit-ups that has
nothing like I am I don't even know what I'm gonna do. Why? And they're gone. Disappeared.
Look look look look. I think it's the same lady every time.