Oh, everybody's expecting her was expecting me to do a big VR rant.
Yeah, like I do every time. Everyone's expecting it. You're like, oh, wait, wait,
here it comes. Here it comes. Oh, here it is. Yeah, here it is. Here it comes.
I'm not gonna give it to you today. I was gonna go. Let me tell you though. Fuck.
Nevermind. I was gonna say fuck VR. Yesterday. All right. Everybody relax.
Yesterday. I set everything up. Everything was ready to go. And this, why does this
continue to happen? I don't know. I set everything up. Everything's ready to go.
It's a beautiful VR space with all this cool stuff. Right. I get up this morning.
And I couldn't, you couldn't download Hitman 3 on Steam. They waited till the
last second to even put a Steam store page up. So like, I don't don't get mad.
So I literally like three hours ago, you could finally go to the Steam page for
this game. And I got it. And I got it ready. And I open up the VR segment. And
the shit is just mirrored, just flipped. Everything is just mirrored. I was
reading everything backwards. Everything works fine. Is the only program I was
using that was flipped horizontally. Steam VR was fine. My other games were
fine. My headsets fine. Why was the game flipped horizontally? Dude, I restarted
the game like 15 to 20 times. And it's not flipped anymore. I, I don't what
happened? What the fuck happened? All right. I'm not gonna go any further. I'm
just gonna tell you that Hitman VR is not good. I haven't even played it yet.
Everyone just relax for a minute. I need to sleep. Let me just let me just chill.
Let me chill. He's gonna cry on stream. What's wrong with your voice? I'm like
talking in a weird place. I'm talking I have I'm using the VR headset mic like
it did last time. So I'm talking in a weird place. I don't know. Maybe I sound
weird. I don't know. Seething. No, I have that like seething voice. Do you guys
know exactly what I'm talking about? I like you can tell by the sound of my
voice. I'm like seething by the words trail off like it's a little more airy.
You know what I mean? Like that's exactly what it is. I've been sitting for three
hours every and this happens every time. VR is a $1,000 paperweight. I take that
back. I don't mean that. I do. Anyways, I don't mean that. It's actually really
fun. I'm so fucking mad. I'm going back and forth with VR Josh like, dude, what's
going on? Why is my game flipped? He's like, really trying to help me and stuff.
But actually, he had some good tips. So okay. VR is a piece of crap. I hate it. I
can't wait to play Hitman VR. Are you guys excited? Don't turn off. Please don't
turn off. I don't know. It took me so long to get to this stage. Don't do the beat.
Do not turn the fuck off. It took me forever. I downloaded three different
programs to get the chat window to show up. Because Hitman VR, don't say it. I'm
just drinking coffee. Just chilling out. We're just gonna chill out and drink
some coffee. Okay. We're gonna hang out. We're gonna chill. We're gonna drink
some coffee. We're gonna hang out. Hi, everybody. The Hitman VR flipped. It's
not. For an illusion again. The room's not big. It's a full room. All right. Are
you guys ready? Coffee's not good for you. Actually, there was a study that was
done. Medicine magazine. Coffee is actually good for your brain. It's
actually good for your liver. And then I don't don't drink don't drink like the
fucking extra cream extra sugar bullshit. This is what I'm talking about. Don't
dump it. It's a black coffee. Just black. That cup is huge. Pretty normal to me. I
didn't get my I got my ring light setup. Even more footage at the boomer brace on
I'm ready to go for like two to three hours. What brand coffee is that? Of
course. Turbo 985. Brinks Illy coffee. I'm gonna get in. I believe the audio is
on. I don't know. All right. What mission should I do? Because I have access to
everything. What do you guys think? Make sure I get in this thing. Well, I see
you. Hey, there you are. It works. Do the first level. The clown one. Dude Dubai
Dubai. I mean I have access to all of them. Also, can I do some scream tests to
make sure that he's not gonna hurt your guys ears? Would you guys allow me to do
that? Press A to play. All right, dude. Press A to play. What's going on here?
Can I do a few scream tests? All right. What's going on? Don't even fucking tell
me. Don't work. Oh shit. My fucking pants. It doesn't work. Can you hear it? All
right. I'm good. All right. Let me put I gotta put the straps on and I'm ready to
VR. There's one. This is a little loud. I will say. At least for me. Not for you. I'll
make sure to turn you guys up but I'm gonna turn me down. Welcome to hell.
Welcome to streaming VR where four people need to be in the room for it to
work out the way that you want it to. I'm going on another rant. Is that loud? How
loud is that? Is it bad? What just happened? Your camera's tilted. Uh, I don't
think it is. I think it's an optical illusion, dude. Because that's...
No, my camera's not tilted. It's an optical illusion. Is it loud? All right. I
gotta get in this. I gotta get into this fucking game right now before I have a
meltdown. I gotta turn the audio down for me. Better? All right. Here we go.
You guys ready? Here we go. Here we go. How's it look? Let's go. Let's go. All
right. Hitman VR. Hitman. Virtual reality. Where should I go? All right. So
where am I going? What destination? What do you think? We can go to Miami? That's
Hitman 2, right? I'm not doing the concrete level first. You're out of your
mind. That is not happening. Concrete. Concrete. Concrete. Dude, Dubai. All right.
You know what? Let's just do Miami because this is like one of the first
levels of the second game. I'm very curious how this is gonna be. How
is there hair in my nose? I just blew up to get the nose out of, like,
the hair out of my nose and I just fogged up the glasses. I don't want to
scream because I think it's loud. Okay. Spoiler alert. Doesn't matter. They're
all fogged up now. Oh, fuck you, VR. Are you kidding me? I put, like, that fucking
gas up there. All right. I don't even care. Yeah. I feel like, I feel like in
VR, it's like that I'm, like, getting fitted for a wedding dress. That's how
many people need to be in this room to help me. Like, I'm going like this. There's
a person with, like, a thing going around my neck and around my, like, my waistline
Does this look good? I need five people in here. Help me. All right.
Difficulty. Not casual, right? Or should I do? I mean, it's VR. Isn't this gonna be,
like, impossible? Let's find out. All right. Here we go. Do I need to play
anything? I don't think so. Let's go. Please, God, do casual. Well, it's a little too
late now. My shit's all fogged up. All right. Make sure this is tight. We already
know this shit. Nice t-shirt. Hey, thanks. We already know this. There's a
driver. There's, all right. Okay. Okay. The finish lines. This is actually, okay,
this is cool. Can I have a sip? Can I have a sip of that? I feel like, I feel like I'm playing,
remember when the Sims did their first-person update? I feel like that's
what I'm doing. What's wrong with my body? Am I gonna get in trouble? Why is there a
UFO? I didn't even punch him. I just, like, cocked my arm back. What? Listen to me.
Okay. This is too real in VR. It's too real. I don't, I can't play it, like, it's
too real. What's wrong with my hands? Why am I phasing out? How come nobody cares?
Can I get in the picture? Where'd he go? I missed. I'm just a psycho. I'm sorry. No, I don't mean,
I don't, all right. You can arrest me. I don't know. I, this is weird. Everybody
looking at me. Stop, don't look at me. Stop looking at me. Stop looking at me. I
gotta get out of here! What happened? What happened? What happened? What happened? What's going on? What happened? I punched a guy. I punched a guy. It was me. I punched a guy. This is fucking chaos.
All right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right, all right. What are you
doing? Okay, that was too much. That was way too much. Wait, what? Replay. Restart. All right, restart.
This is too much. We can't hear anything. Huh? I'll turn it up. I'll turn it up. I got it. I got it. I got it.
Where's the audio? There it is. How's that? All right, we're back. That better? Good. Now it's too
loud. Your mic is peaking. I know, man. How bad is the mic peaking? Let me fix it. I got it. I got it. I got it. Check this out. Oh shit. Let me test.
Oh, that's better. Okay. Are we in? We're in, right? Yep. Okay. That was too much. That was like a little too much for me. All right, let's get in there.
How is anybody reliably supposed to do this? Okay, don't be an idiot. Just be a tourist. That sounds easy. How do I take a picture? How do you take a picture? Just on drugs.
Hey, man. Do you know how to work this thing, man? I don't know. Do you know how to work it? There's no batteries in that thing. Oh, man. Sorry.
All right. So what do I got to do? Targets up there. Eliminate Sir Knox. Eliminate Robert Knox. All right. I know he's up there. And you're over there. All right. Why do my arms keep doing this? Hello, I'll take that. What is that? View Intel? How do I? What was it? How do I view Intel? Can I have one of those? Oh, wait, I can hold on. Hold up on the left touchpad. Oh, shit. Okay. I was gonna say, where's the map?
Intel. All right. Globally Innovation. I can't speak. All right. Well, let's go. Am I gonna get in trouble if I go through here? Yes, sir. I don't think I have a weapon. Do I have a weapon? Thank you. Okay. Let's go, sir. All right. You're welcome. There's so many people to load. Kill that guy.
All right. Where are you guys? Oh, there you are. Let me go. No, no, no, no, no, no. Excuse me. Okay, let's go. Don't hurt anybody. What? Free photo shoot. Oh, soda. Why does your aluminum cans explode? You don't think that's a little dangerous? Why would an aluminum can explode? That's weird, right? All of us can agree that that's really fucking weird. Like, honestly.
I guess nobody else thinks that that's odd. Oh, you Intel. Get out of the way. Get out of the way. Move out of the way. It was the Intel. I feel like I'm just I don't I when you have the other view, you can see what you're doing. I'm just lost at a convention. I hate this. I hate being like get away from me.
Hold down the left pad. What are you saying? Go to the viewing area and pretend to be one. This is making me sick. I mean, it is VR. I'll try to reduce my movements. All right. What can I what can I just go down here? Oh, food. All right. Can I get fries? Hey, damn me. You damn me to do it. It's a catcher. Everyone's looking at me like I'm a boy. I'm a boy. I'm a boy. I'm a boy. I'm a boy. I'm a boy.
Weirdo. I don't like being this close. Oh, parking garage is down here. The only thing we're calling is a bartender. Okay. Doesn't the guy come down here? Somebody comes down here. All right. Saving. POV. You're bald. Do the tutorial. I mean, I know I know how it works. This camera up there. Watch out. Okay, I got to dress as this guy. Jesus.
I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding with you. No, you. You didn't see anything. What? Oh, shit. What the fuck?
That's like a monster. Security. No, come here. You need to deal with this guy right away.
I'm trying to strangle him. This is a restraint. What? Nobody dicks with me. Give me the gun. What happened to the antelope? Whatever he was. How do I reload a gun? Yep. Okay.
Okay. Oh, what? Where did the mascot go? Where's the mascot? I strangled him. What? Hold on. Oh, this is so I don't like this. This is scary. Oh, my God. This is so fucked up. I don't.
I could use some assistance. Oh, my God. What happened? What happened? How do I reload this? How do I reload this gun? All right, please. Nobody come in here.
How do I stand up? Does anybody know how to? B, A? No, that's camera. How do I get up? How do I get up? C, right stick. Okay. All right. All right. Where is he?
The thing is, I don't even know. There's no mini map. So I don't know where the hell anybody's coming over here. This is hard mode. All right. I got to stuff him in here.
Do you know what I mean? I can't. There's no mini map. Sorry, man. Okay. All right. We're good. I just got to get the hell out of here. I don't want any weapons or anything on me though, right? No weapons. Don't take any weapons.
Okay. Now that I'm disguised, that's okay. Just leave it open. Who cares? What about all the bodies? I don't know, man. Like, I'm going to have to leave them. What keeps happening to my arms? What's wrong with my body?
Oh, it's because I'm moving away from myself. Oh, this is weird. Why am I doing this? Okay. So now let's look at the Intel. Oh, okay. So I'm on this one right now. Key Intel was lost. Oh, nevermind.
How about a perfect machine? That sounds good. So where is that Intel? They're up there. All right. I'm going to go back up. I think I can actually go back up the whole way, right? Re-center your position with left stick. Oh, shit. Okay, nice.
All right. So now I'm the mascot. So now I can walk around freely. I don't even care if I could see. All right. We're going to go this way. What's this? Oh, this is cool. Okay. Oh, I made it just in time for it to end. Oh, come on.
Can you give me the spark notes? What did I miss? What year was that built? Come on. Just what year was that thing built? Just tell me, please. Fine. Fighting. All right. Can I go in there? Oh, Intel. I don't have anything on me.
I'm here for the meeting. How are we? Yep. I'm the mascot. I'm here to meet with the guy upstairs. Okay. That's all right. I give the finger. It's a VR game. Okay, over there. This is a just completely different game. It's a whole other experience. Didn't I say this sucks?
Didn't I say this sucks? I said this sucks, right? Like it before I even played it. I would say the game. I would say the game. A journalist prayed my response protocols have not been set up properly for an interview at this time. Please enjoy. Tap up. There we go. Okay, good.
The race is entering its final lap. 47. You don't understand. You don't understand. None of you understand. We can't let this stand. We can't let this stand. Are you kidding me? Robots like that? They're gonna they're gonna take over. No, no, we can't let this stand. We can't let this stand.
Hey, don't worry. It's all right. It's attached. It's cemented. It's screwed in. I'm just the weird guy that everybody looks at. Every time I try to do a little routine here. Hey, hey, knock on wood, right? That they're not going to kill us all.
I understood from the briefing earlier that we're just supposed to grab him if something happens to it. No poking around the engine. What? I can push people? This is the art. This particular car is the first production. What the fuck? Stop.
That's crazy. Yeah, that's weird. I'm just going around fucking tapping people. Dude, you know, weirdo. Alright, where's my Intel? I'm so distracted. I'm sorry. I just am.
Imagine a guy dressed like this running up and doing like a power move, right? Like an inch away from your face. How am I still allowed in here? I'm clearly on like fucking crack. I'm afraid not. We've had a few incidents with people getting a little
two hands. All right. Where's my restrict access to the car? Did I lose the Intel? Yes, of course. What was it? Okay. Oh, Robert Knox has a prototype of his RK mark three racing car on display in the Cronstadt Bayside Center. He's so concerned about it that he has ordered the engineers in the Expo building to get him immediately. Should anything happen to the car, it's likely he will come rushing down to fix it himself. Okay, we're gonna fuck up. We're gonna fuck up the car. You got it. Get out of the way. I didn't want to.
Talk to you. Okay, so I got to miss the car. Our engineers are working. Do not enter. What am I getting in trouble with this? Save it. He's gone. Hi. Hi, I'm back. Okay. What the fuck? What? What? What's wrong? No, I'm not. I mean, I'm just trying to get an Instagram video. I'm just trying to get an Instagram video for like my followers. I thought I could get a picture in there.
What happened? Oh, I have to be an engineer. Sorry. Very good, sir. Just keep walking. All right, we're good. I'm sorry. It's fine. Are you an engineer? Strangle them. I'm trying to strangle them. Give me that gun, motherfucker. I covered my hands with butter before I came here. You're never gonna get me. I was trying to how do you choke people? I'm sitting there trying to choke the guy. I can't choke him. Why not?
Your hands need to what? Can't you? Can't you go over like this and didn't strangle people? Your hands will enter choke. Oh, VR just tried to help me. You need to enter choke mode. So you tell me if I put my hands around this guy's neck like this and I hold
me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me, me
coins i don't i need to find like okay i gotta distract you i gotta get you over
there and i'm gonna strangle you expo staff only i am expo staff are you
serious i'm the guy in the big outfit what's this oh coins no put it away what
is this oh it's a soda okay okay all right all right now i can distract him
all right save the game here what whoa wait
i'm just looking i thought that was the bathroom sorry
i thought that was the bathroom all right save the game here
i'm gonna save the game you dummy okay here we go
look at me to choke somebody it's going so fast i can't read it
please soil the car your hands will flex before you when you're okay
i think i got it okay that's not what i wanted to do
i didn't want to do that you can keep that one
how do i throw this what the fuck how do i throw things
this is pissing me off oh wait i remember all right leave me alone
please leave me alone please damn what's happened over there man
something happened go see what that was what where am i it's too dark it's so
dark in here all right dude it was so fucking dark in
there i go didn't you know where i was i don't i get it now i get it i get it i
get it so you tell me that my hands are gonna do a choking motion
so when i just punch oh i can i can just punch him that's right what am i
thinking all right can you guys see me i have so
much room over here i'm gonna utilize it okay so give me the coin
the hell is this where are my coins where are my coins i just had them what
happened
what the fuck weren't my coins
why do they look weird what's going on here
i mean look they're right here select rg what the hell
okay fuck you
wait this is so hard to don't look at me i think you dropped i think you dropped
this i think you dropped this all right get out of the way what
okay oh shit did i break something did i break something
i think i might have broken something
didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't didn't
didn't didn't didn't this is so hard in vr i just i have no map
all right i'm gonna leave i'm gonna forget this guy forget that guy
yeah i know so you hold you hold left trigger you make a throwing motion and
then you let go right that's what that's what the
tutorial said i did the tutorial that guy so i need to
mess with this car i need like an engineer outfit
is that weird play this tutorial you don't actually throw it
okay i get i'm getting out of here i'm getting out of here the exhibit sucks
it's not even worth it yeah we all paid 50 dollars on groupon
to fucking come here look at that that's all that's in here
they make you watch a two and a half hour video in the next room
50 dollars by the way all right where do i go
i thought that was a person never mind i was like there's an engineer
who uses groupon i don't i don't know i don't think very many people
first of all okay i like this i can sneak in here
this definitely okay let me look at the map because like holy shit this is hard
without the map okay the aquarium's right here i'm going
to go through the aquarium let's see if it helps
i gotta get this stupid bird costume off i look like an idiot and i can't i'm not
even allowed here and of course right of course the cool
thing with the fish this whole area is unbelievable look at
all this knowledge look at all this all these cool facts about fishes and
shit nobody's in here this was probably 10
bucks of course right no let's go see the robots they're
gonna fucking kill us all and stuff no not the fish though cool
i'll be adult where's my shit you want to come over for clara's birthday
it should be six you don't have to answer that
that didn't work you can't see me there's no way
all right i went into the wall they can't see me this is a restricted area
what it's a fucking aquarium bro what do you mean restricted area all right
okay sorry sorry i went to the aquarium yeah okay
yeah i'm in trouble aren't i i'm well i'm leaving right now
i told you to complete what the i'm fucking leaving right now
impatient i tend to shoot people i'm sorry my body is fucked up
i'm leaving right now i sense you weren't any trouble
very good sir just this fucking game come here come here
i don't want to put put the gun down where's the other guard
where's the other guard i gotta go kill the other guard i have to like knock him
out all right get up get up get up where's he
there he is what no you can see from my disguise
we're good okay i got a gun where's my gun
put that away let me recenter all right now i have i gotta save the game not
right now this is bad i don't now i can actually probably go
over there and sit down right put that guy in the tank what do you
mean put him in the tank what do you mean put him in the tank
what why did it go black i think i gotta do it to the other guy too i
think it was too scary there's mini map and
settings it will appear what is it really is mini map in the
settings yeah yeah there's something on your shirt
mini map and settings really where is it wrong settings go back
okay where gameplay hud vital info objective objective vr auto
global hints challenges challenge hud npc icons
weapon hud vr difficulty hud auto save hud
am i am i blind reload hud i it's like i have to
i'm it do you understand how hard it is mission story guidance objectives
where is it what do you mean go back vr comfort
vr blinders toggle the blinder zone vr turn mode head bob collision
guys it's so it's so much more different when you're in the headset
like i i'm looking at a gigantic mural in front of me
mini map all right there it is mini map vr holy shit thank god
where is it all right that kind of blocks you guys though this is not as
good as i thought that was going to be okay
all right well whatever let's go you bet your ass i'm gonna fucking take a
hammer are you kidding me all right i now have i'm a security guard
not bad okay i'm gonna go back in here i'm i'm technically an employee now
right i went around i just turned around this
way so now i should be able to like go back behind there throw a coin
snap the guy's neck yeah okay i got it dump the body
i don't need to dump the body i'm fine i'm coming for you
okay so what if i sit in it now what happens can i sit in the car
as a security guard are they gonna get mad
get out get out get out get out get out get up oh my god really
we can't just have a little bit of fun all right
why we can't just have a small amount of fun
we're like guarding this thing well i'm not gonna break anything
there's more than one engineer but it's so hard to find them
i don't know what i gotta look for this name tag can i see what that looks like
okay i i gotta find a cron stat engineer but they could be anywhere this is the
worst game of the year i don't think so all right i can go in
here this is employees only let me in here
i'm just a guy like you what's in here engineer
i'm hitting this guy with a fucking hammer what's what's this guy made out of
what are you you can't be serious you can't be serious hit the guy 10 times
the hammer i think i 10 times with a hammer
you understand that wasn't my fist that was i punch a guy in the face once and
he goes down i hit him in the head with a hammer 15 times he's not going to go
down hold the trigger when you bash
did you guys hear that like this game was not made for vr
no but it's kind of fun to do it anyways all right get me out of here
oh wait we didn't we didn't dump them it does it gets rid
oh that's unfortunate you get through the whole cut scene okay
i am now go get the hammer there's the hammer
so you're saying hold the trigger when i hit that's what you want to do
i'm just testing to see if it hurts me okay i got it
all right can i not fuck this up a third time please
your back diaper looks full that's again i've been told not to say diaper and i
just did it's because i have a lot of pressure
right here all right that's enough out of you
let's try this again okay that was that was a little better
i gotta get rid of you in here okay you're in there
good to go what direction am i facing in the room
okay what's that screwdriver oh shit make it up there wait there's no
engineers back here why would there not be an engineer
oh no i'm on camera engineer come on there's all kinds of wires and shit back
here look at all the wires there's so much
stuff back here so much engineer stuff back here
is there is anybody here somebody right here that's an engineer right there
engineer engineer engineer get up oh jeez please help me what he's i hit him
in the head with the he's alive come on like a little gremlin get over
here hey okay all right it's not what it looks
like man it ain't what it looks like it's not what it looks like it's not
what it looks like why is he still on me it's not what it
looks like you fucking piece of shit
wait wait wait wait you don't want to
hey i didn't i forgot that's where everybody was
i didn't do anything i didn't do anything we're fine everything's fine
nothing no problem at all no problem we can relax
i'm an engineer it's like everybody else here all right
i'm not compromised i don't think so are we good
we're good no cops right i don't think so
i think i'm good all right all right all right here we go i'm an engineer
i'm allowed in here what am i what am i doing here
uh what do i do click the switches smash it you need to what go back back out
back at the oh okay okay right here sabotage
where's the screwdriver i threw it in that guy's head back here i think it's
it's in his head can i get it out of his head it's like
right here hold on what's this oh shit all right it's right here
somewhere right screwdriver there it is okay all right
we're good i got a screwdriver now oh fuck what's wrong with that guy
wait that guy can see through all right here we go
now what oh okay there he is i see him now what oh fuck you
what's connected to me what happened where's this person
all right fine get over here i'm gonna kill this guy right now
oh my god oh my fucking jesus christ jesus christ oh my god
this is impossible in vr my body's cool like
like that's all that's happening that's the whole game
like look at like what the what's why am i detached from my body
i don't think you're supposed to stand up and play this like for any reason
this is not a room scale game was it a wait was it a bad guy
i gotta get out of this fucking place this is a standing
only game yeah but i mean if even if you're standing only it's like you're
gonna move oh i'm supposed to go like this am i
hunted right now i am in the storage room no sign of the target
anyone have visual on the target he's got a fucking machine gun
hold on stay there time out time out for a sec i'm like
my first day of paintball they say lmao what did he say
okay i'm gonna go back because this is not happening
i gotta go back to when i first sabotaged the car put it on casual
difficulty that's probably a good idea can i change
it right here peter griffin you don't need to be an
engineer just get the screwdriver and sabotage it really
what the hell i thought i had to be an engineer to do that
you should try aiming i mean i'll tell you it's kind of it's difficult to aim
when your hands inside the palms are wet all right do i have the
screwdriver where was that screwdriver it was over
here wasn't it somewhere you should wear gloves you should sit
up i can't sit on i'll throw up if i sit down and play vr i will throw
up in 10 minutes i have to stand if i don't move around
in vr guaranteed i'm gonna get banned on from twitch
because i'll puke it'll take less than five minutes
you have a shit stain don't say that don't say that dude come on hey remember
this funny thing with this guy i remember this guy oh never mind all
right let me let me practice this because somebody what what happened
bingo okay so when my hands do that like curl
like you who are you why they're not doing it
you are i don't understand it well he wouldn't do it okay
screwdrivers right here somewhere don't do the concrete level
i'm not gonna no i'm gonna do the i'm only gonna do like five levels
this don't fit okay whatever okay so now you're telling me
just go and sabotage it don't worry about anything else don't hurt anybody
don't punch anybody don't kill anybody don't do anything dumb just sabotage
i'm gonna save it right here you should do something dumb
i feel like it's been the last like 45 straight minutes
we need to talk to the boss man about these uniforms again it's polyester
sticking to my i know i feel the same way everything's
sticking to me right now too okay so sabotage the engine
now be a security guard until he shows up
why's the engine off let's just try to get this started again
done good better call nox why am i sitting here like
i didn't do anything bad i'm just people listen the mark three's making some well
noises yep yeah i'll be here all right so here he comes
now what you're not done sabotaging it how
save the game can you not be the sus guy that's too late
you need to find the car blueprints go back
wait i'm going to read the intel i've never done this mission before
okay this is it right here yeah okay so anything happened car
he will come rushing down to fix it himself so i'd have to put like a like a
bomb or something there kind of find the car blueprints near the
tar you need the blueprints yes you have i know you have
your shirt is that him who is that what whoa
what the fuck i'm a security guard i'm a security you bumped into me
i need you to get in the car don't touch anything until i tell you
is that me you want me to get sir do you want me to get in the car
do you want me to get in the car just regular
get down get down get down oh my god the save that game doesn't auto save i
forgot it's our emirate so i'm not okay wait
wait wait wait so i need to get like somebody said i need to get like
something to put it to sabotage it so that i gotta find like something to
dump in there there's something in the garage you need
the octane booster all right octane booster
it's out is in the garage all right so i've all right
so i got i can sabotage get the octane booster wherever that is
i'm assuming garage is this way right poop in the gas tank
that's a classic engineer joke whoa what is that stuff anyway
i think some of the teams are using it to increase car speed
heard a few cron step mechanics talking about it the other day
something about nox not wanting to use it because she wants to win on her own
imagine that okay is it that illegal i don't know
nox ordered them to put it here so they asked me to put it here
so i just did that not touching it again sounds like a good idea nice all right
boosters down here hey bro was that uh there's an octane shit you're talking
about where's that octane shit right here oh
that there's a bottle of cronstance patented octane booster mixture
somewhere in the loading bay okay that's somewhere in here this is
gonna be such a pain in the ass to find this
over here octane where's it at blind this vr man it's like a completely
different world in here that's not it that's a whiskey chug the
octane it's marked for you it's not though over
here is that it right there no is this it vr andy find the octane
tank near the oh my god it was so fast it's upstairs
no not there as a fire axe you know i'm gonna take that right
oh my okay all right like holy shit you can't give me the fire axe right now
octane is it an energy drink is it like one of these
i can't take this that's a bad idea i'll take these though for sure
um pick it up god put it away where's this shit where's the octane
i don't see it anywhere it's on the shelf shelf shelf shelf
let's see in the all the way it's all the way in the corner you can't say
blind it's literally a tiny bottle of tylenol
sitting in the very corner of the map don't drop this
okay here we go save it all right i'm gonna get this right now
i'm at least gonna complete one of these missions in vr
now i can go take care of this this is gonna be cool i'm actually this is
actually exciting to me i'm actually very excited right now
reset calibration okay all right there's the car
don't do anything weird just be a normal person don't do anything weird
sorry that was that was awful i was like sticking my tongue out at him
i'm sorry okay so sabotage the car and then put the octane in
okay i'm ready just a second there security guy
what what did you just do hey what are you doing with that
what stop right there hands in the air i guess it makes sense
i guess it makes sense it you know what it does make sense
you distracted me do not press that button
okay so i can't nobody can look at me i get it
take the axe and just go crazy no let me at least get to the end of one of
these missions before i do anything insane so i gotta wait till this guy
looks away wait till you leave i get it i understand it don't worry
all right now i need you to get out of the way
say what yo go check it out check that out will you
how do i get him to get out of here leave yes we don't need two security
guards looking at the exact same place you can leave yes
and i don't appreciate being a photograph without my permission
thank you very much all right i'm good i'm good i'm good we're good
why's the engine off let's just try to get this started again
now he's gonna call the guy doesn't sound good better call nox
call him get him down here he needs to fix that
mr nox yeah it's smith from down at the expo
listen the mark three's making some well just odd noises
uh can you come great all right yeah yeah i'll be here
i feel so devilish i really do i don't know something about being in the vr
mode is like i'm so i'm so devilish save it right now all right where's he
at he's over there you're gonna take a long
time to get over here aren't you you need to hit the yonky splonky all
right i swear to god if someone's been
tampered i'm a security guard too you need to get in the car don't touch
anything is he smoking i don't think he should be smoking
do you think he should be smoking stop smoking he's talking to me
you want me to do this yeah is it me you want me to do this you want me to do
this am i doing this you seem hey you
trespassers he told me to get in the car you told me to get in the car
you will need to follow me i he said get in the fucking car
he said get in the car everybody heard it i'm trying one more time
you said to get in the car yeah keep walking oh my god it's taking me very
strong to not punch you
so i have okay fine i'm a security guard
oh my fucking god what are you waiting for he told me to get in the car
he told me to get in the car that's so unfair
hey you there go get in that car and press the gas what i tell you
oh get out of the car man what the fuck it's oh come on
was he even was he even talking to me all right we have to wait for him again
this was on the phone you're out of frame
oh i'll fix that you need to bring the octane to the car
but after putting it in you need to so now i have to be an engineer
i get you i get it i swear to god if someone's been tampering with the heads
will roll i gotta be an engineer anything until i tell you
no because i know what happened last time not doing that which one of you
which one of you two motherfuckers am i gonna take
he's taunting me hey what happened oh no what the fuck happened hurt i'm all
right i don't think something's wrong with him though what happened to him
is he okay it's i can't even see it's so dark
open this shit there's nobody even in here right not really wait there's an
engineer down here are you alone there's two of you wait i can get you
give me the fucking screwdriver oh my god please it's like it's so sloppy
i want to like cement my feet to the ground what just fucking happened
what happened what was that what happened
huh what happened what happened out there
who did that which way you did that that was fucked up whoever did that
hunting for what what did i do wrong i'm so confused did it kill him
the car just exploded nobody even got hurt good day to you sir
okay what happened i'm so confused i honestly don't even know what happened
can anybody explain why that happened did i take too long
okay here we go here we go here we go here we go no more fucking around kill
the guy the screwdriver take his disguise
and just run in there and stern the gas on what okay
anyone i need some help
fucking crazy i'm not sure he's out cold or dead
i'll look into it that's understood no please
somebody got in and turned the car on i have to get this guy
this is so much easier in third person you just throw a coin over there and the
guy is gonna go over there getting a coin
out of here is like i feel like i have a thousand things in my pocket
okay coin got coin throw coin that way both of you go over there and look at it
is this illegal for me to take that okay all right all right all right all right
all right all right stop stop stop stop this is perfect oh fuck you game
at least he's gone wait save it save it right now
okay game saved i'm now an engineer i'm ready to go
what the no no i was coming i was right here he's still alive
how are you still alive sir sir it's a it's miracle that you're still alive
it's remarkable god damn it i have to run as fast as i can from this point
here we go all right center center center center get centered
center center center center center run i gotta be the one that blows it up
ready three two one action
you knew who was doing that who was doing that
why did he turn it on you guys have fucking idiots
why is he here why did you do that what's wrong with you
hey how about you show some respect this oh that's right
you're right you're getting now you're right you're right you're right i gotta
be faster than that you're too far gone i am i can get there
do they do a smaller level i can get it i just i'm gonna see if i gotta go
faster i went the wrong way i gotta go the other way
i legit have to run to the left side and push that other engineer out of the way
i have to save that guy all right come on where am i fuck oh my they do it faster
every time you're slower every time all right not
this time motherfucker i'm gonna go go go here we go i gotta do this fast
wait throw a coin at the wall that's actually brilliant hold on let me just
do this quick i don't care can anyone please help me
i need help i'm here i'm here i made it i made it i made it i'm here to turn the
car on i'm gonna try that tactic to throw the
code at the wall why do i have to turn around every time
by the way like i'm not gonna fuck around coins coming out i can i can
freeze the game that's so brilliant by the way freeze coin
against the wall right here
it didn't it didn't work a guy fell from the rafters he was naked up there
i don't know what he was doing up there but dude come on
yeah i need to do an even earlier save than that fuck
okay all right so here's the plan i'm gonna
whip a coin over and then i'm gonna get this guy
oh my goodness gracious okay give me the coin
i'm gonna distract these guys with the coin out here you know just like fucking
who cares just throw it over there okay they're distracted they're
distracted they're distracted
where am i i'm trying to walk forward he's walking backwards oh my god this
game get up get up what i
distract i distracted him with the coin and it
didn't even matter i will get this i can assure you okay coin
i got an idea here's the idea ready oh my god what the hell
why i did it hold throw oh my god hey you think you left this behind
perfect pick is check it out
blow it up blow it up blow it up blow it up i'm here i'm ready
all right how do i blow it up what do i do step on the gas quick
step on the gas tip of the gas step on the gas how do i step on the gas
how do you step on the gas how do you step on the gas
how do you step on the gas what what the fuck what i pressed b
start engine i just did it start engine b it's b on it's b on the
on my left hand not on my right hand it's the other b
why does it why is it not b1 and b2 a1 and a2
you gotta be fucking kidding me give me the coin quick
why is it not b1 and b2 i don't understand okay
i gotta get this right can't do it anymore
why is it so finicky it's such a piece of shit
i will get it i've what if i shoot the gun
go check it out oh i did it i got i got i got i'm good i'm good good all right
let's just turn the key and see wait wait wait let me do it sir don't
touch it
i'm only doing this one more time this is my last attempt at this
and then i'm gonna go to a different level okay i need to go out there and
like distract them don't let them do anything yet all right
give me the coin now i'll be waiting for a written invitation
what if i just do it what if i just do it and turn it on right now
am i gonna get in trouble what if i just do it right now just turn the car
hey you you can't be here who do you think you are
you need to follow me right now no questions
you have to be an engineer to turn the car on like this hey you have to be an
engineer oh my god damn it okay all right
all right all right i give up one more try all right fine
i actually give up we're doing something we'll do another level after
this just stab them in the head and run i'm going to stab them in the head and
run if i can't get it i need to distract with
the coin immediately as soon as it levels load up okay get the coin
i give up i'm done i'm done with this i'm done with this fucking piece of
shit i'm done i give up i didn't want to throw
it at you you know what i've had enough of this
level i've had enough of this i've had enough of this did i tell you
wrong save well i still have to get the engineer costume from the other guy
i okay i only get like an extra five to six seconds on the other save
and i have to get that guy's disguise i have another idea i promise this is the
final attempt i'm gonna shoot my gun just at the wall
and then drop it that will distract everybody but see
okay all right all right all right we're good okay
all right when everybody relaxes when everybody relaxes we can start this
again talking walks down he's gonna come back
watch this he's gonna come back there he is right there
25 meters 23 meters they eventually they're gonna the lockdown is gonna be
over and we're gonna be fine here he comes
he's coming back up okay he's turning the corner
he's walking a little bit further away they'll be back
right now we're on searching when that's off of searching
in like another 30 seconds 10 seconds they're coming back right
still searching where is he all right what is he doing
he's right here okay okay get a grip okay here we go wake up and get a grip
we're good your car is waiting okay your car is waiting for you sir
i know there's a little bit of chaos earlier here but we're uh
we're back on schedule to get the car uh for you to check the car out
don't forget about that forget about that naked guy not a problem
all right so again i i heard this weird rattling in the engine i couldn't
didn't really know what was going on so let me see if i can get in there
baby no no no let me do it let me please step back people let the
pros do their thing okay i'm here now i'm so disappointed here
over my disappointment is so it's so high right now i i thought he was
gonna go to the back of the car and do his little routine again
oh man i didn't even save it either i i know well i thought it was just in the
bag all right we know it works i'm gonna go for it again and then we
can just chill and then i'm gonna take a break
shoot the gun real quick i'm gonna go and sit in the car
and wait for this asshole to come back i promise this is the final attempt this
is the last time we're gonna do this i promise
i promise okay now just go sit in the car so he can't do it
okay save the game just go sit in the car
no one's gonna care this one right here okay okay we're good now
jeez i am ready or please i need to know
i don't know whatever that was been here five minutes and he's already
fucked up twice please get some help where is he going he
goes all the way over there he goes down he comes up here
he walks he walks over there and then they don't care
sit in the car i'm waiting for this dickhead
save again win or lose i'm taking a pee break
is another mike mike mike mike huh mike what's what's good we good mike is
all right but how come i can't turn it on now
mike is fine okay good so it's b oh it does say right b doesn't it okay
it's left b to turn the car on good all right here we go
moving on save it again right here right there okay
remember your other controller is on an xbox layout
where are they i'm just waiting around for these guys where are they
okay here he comes get in this is it right now i'm in the car you can't do
shit here we go come on go look in the back and make
sure it's all good all right i would take a look yeah finally
okay go take a look at the engine what are you waiting for
go look at the engine is he in range well i found something
why they met me what that is concuss him he's not even dead sir
where's my gun get out get out get out get out get out
get out get out i'm good oh it's sunlight okay
now i just have to no clear i'm in the clear
it's all clear save the game do not load the game save the game i don't know what
how did i not kill him i can't save it i'm in combat
where are they nobody's around me right now okay i gotta get that guy's costume
no i think i can leave this way i think right
where the hell am i now where am i going where am i
can i save thank god okay all right i gotta pee i'm gonna get some water
i'll be right back jeez where even am i that was
oh go downstairs go go on he's to eat oh man
okay i have one more person to get yeah this is this is insane
this is this is equal parts like horrible to play and equal parts like
the funnest thing i've done in like a year
it's weird i don't know how i feel about it how's the is the audio fine too
how's the audio now that i can come out of here for a second and take a look
is good okay well i'm starting to get used to it though
um i've reattached my boomer brace i'm fine
you should do dubai yeah all right if i get caught one more time if i get kind of
messed up i'll um because i don't want to just only
be on one level for the whole time i'm playing right
go to i'll go to dubai how's my back it's okay
i have not taken this off so it's been good fun oh no it has absolutely
i have to i just every time i start a vr stream i'm always like in the worst
mood of like the week because it never works i'm just kidding
i'm doing fine i'm having fun did you take your vitamins
actually i did i've been taking b vitamins
i have taken my vitamins thank you very much i think i'm ready to go back in
now i'm having a good i'm having a grand old time this is a lot of fun
i will try and then we'll go to dubai let me get this back on
so you can see me okay the mic is better
sounds fine okay coming back i'm not doing the concrete level no thank you
that's not happening i do i keep like this
because this camera is is only 1080 so it just it's only this wide i can't like
have it fill out the rest there's not much more to see over
there though not that big the room's not that big
all right going in where am i there they are
i kind of went into the ground here didn't i can you guys see
scream title title what's wrong with the title
you can reset the menu position too it's a title
doesn't it say being 47 what's the why is it so funny
okay settle down being four seven all right i'll give you that one
you get to have that one that's the only one you get though ready to go
i am ready to go i believe oh no i have to do this oops
uh it might be hard to look at for just a sec
apologize okay we're good being 47 it's 47 he's an iconic he's a
all right who's more iconic in 2021 pac-man or 47 what do you think
who's more iconic in 2021 pac-man or 47 yeah it's probably if it's definitely
it's definitely uh sir you can't be here this doesn't
work and you can't strangle people in this game
should i make it look like he got hit by the vacuum who's that somebody coming
where can i put this guy i need wait okay i need an intel mission right
is there any intel in here anybody intel i thought that was shit robot i
might need that later screwdriver i just got all these tools
sick okay this one too sick and thank you i'll
bring it back oh it wasn't me where am i going i need
some intel all right intel global innovation knocks the
mechanic i did that one i did that one mission stories here we go
a perfect machine and uh intravenous the munchies i can't do any of these i
guess i can do this one i think i did this one already all right
so where do i go for this one mission story where do i go it's a
medic area searching all right just get me out of here
i'm dressed as this guy all right the medic area
okay i guess i'm gonna leave out here and i'm gonna go to the medical
area the med bay it's on the ground level where the road is
okay where the road is and i'm just like wandering in a random direction right
now aren't i doctor doctor doctor be a car guy kill
that guy over side of the other side of the track
okay i got it yeah can you open this gate
don't bump i'm trying not to bump them great race
this is a good race today yeah sure all right i gotta go that way
underground i feel like i'm playing this with tank
controls because 47 can only move like forwards
all right there we go let's go why are you so tiny i'm a small person
i'm five i'm five foot eight i'm a small person i'm a kind of a small person
okay that's why i play games like this maybe look big and tall
do i hear an auto do i hear auto i did the pre-race oh here we go
well let's just say she's got a bad case of intermittent explosive disorder
poor dr sorenson first he almost loses a patient to a seemingly harmless case of
dehydration now he has to deal with this guy
suffering from urinary retention not his day i think we did this when i
played this a few years ago screw up the revitalization procedure on miss nox
i know it's just a simple injection but given his track record these past few
days well at least i know who's buying his
beer tonight follow the story mission so it seems cierra nox has jumped on the
revitalization bandwagon and is scheduled for an injection of
sure the doctor who is supposed to help her with the procedure
is preoccupied with a patient who is unable to you
all right here we go here we go here we go it's in here i gotta get in here
i have my just take a seat we're very busy right now hi did dr sorenson manage
to get seer and just looking to see the doctor
i heard him arguing with that kronstadt lawyer earlier
no didn't have any luck once he's done with that other driver he'll just have
to use the intercom and call her over the pa system instead
she should be able to hear it just fine all right as long as it's in hand
yes what's up dude hey do you know anything about clash clans
fucking stuck on this one i can't good thing that didn't happen
i'm so glad that didn't happen because i didn't save it for a long time
that would have been really bad thank god
dude hey dude you gotta watch it you gotta watch this fucking tiktok cringe
compilation dude it's so funny come on what do i do i just want to say
that this is a damn fine race i'm coming in
that was a joke i'm not going in oh
wait the doctor i gotta be a doctor i gotta be a doctor
i gotta be a doctor i gotta go over there how do i get over there
where's auto auto what are you doing over here
no don't lie down auto he's just lying on the ground
i don't what are you doing over here i don't want to step on you what happened
to the game what happened to the game what's going on
uh did did auto unplug something i think auto may have unplugged their
cord the game crashed auto um
mission complete there's something i might have unplugged
hold on oh yeah hitman's gone it's hitman's not even here anymore
what happened okay i actually the game actually crashed all right hold on let
me fix this give me one sec uh it's running
i'm not joking what is it i'm not joking there's a wasp in here
it's not a wasp in here so here's the real problem
opening opening hitman is a disaster i when i finally got the game to run
i couldn't leave it so this is going to be a nightmare
uh let me see if this works because the game specifically says
do not open the game if steam vr is open see what happens it's such a mess
all right hold on play whatever you want i mean i kind of want to keep playing
this yeah i gotta exit steam vr hold on i have
to restart steam all right i'm back here's the real
question i think i lost chat we're about to find out
because this was the biggest problem that i had with this setting this up was
every time i opened up the thing that captures chat hitman would like run at
two fps and crash let's see find out let us find out
i'm back in vr there's not there's no wasp in here
all right there we go i should be good let me see if it's still on there can i
see you guys okay steam is opening vr
oh my god that's loud shit i lost chat oh please
you guys can't even see it this is the exact same problem i had last time
i'm probably have to change games because this took like two hours to set
up uh and now i physically can't even get
what the fuck man fucking phd to play hitman 3 in vr
can i see it come on please load load please
do it i think i lost the chat i can't play with chat
if i'm gonna play hitman wait let me try this technically it's
running shit yeah i can't see chat anymore
and it's gonna be a huge pain in the ass to get it back or maybe it's not hold on
give me one more second where are my hands oh come on uh
oh this is gonna take like an hour to fix play squid game
next game i'm gonna change games i may have lost the chat for the rest of the
stream by the way because that was a monumental pain in
the ass to get that to work especially with hitman it's like a
fucking nightmare to try to get it to work with this on index for some reason
let me try one more thing why does everything that launches on day one not
fucking ever work the way that's supposed to because i
have like access to this i don't know why i can't open it
and it technically should be hold on a sec come on come on come on come on
come on come on come on let me see it fuck i have to
why do i have to redo the whole thing in this overlay
all right if this takes more than one full minute
i want everyone to scream it's been one minute from now
if it's been one minute scream all right chat is back
hold on come on dude come on man no no oh it's such a pain in the fucking
ass it really is i had it and i just lost it
again where the fuck did it go yeah getting chat on your wrist
um is like an unbearable process sometimes it's so fucking annoying
i don't i don't know what's going on it's crashed again
it's been one minute all right i'm moving on but i still have to set the
chat up though so it doesn't even matter all right i actually have to go brb
before i scream into this microphone as loud as i can i bring back
all right i have restarted a couple times i think i got it
i believe we're good i could be wrong i hope i'm not wrong we'll find out
very shortly can you see and guess what oink chats back i just needed to take a
breather and just not like scream i told you like i was gonna scream
and again like i told you you need like four people in the room with you to get
this to work and i know i've seen those other goggles
right the other the other like vr goggles
they're like fucking 200p like it's not it's not gonna happen
give me another 30 years and maybe you'll have fun in this
all right here we go destinations i was doing this let's load it
and i load it from here load game all right let's move
where was it right here bingo all right everybody relax
we're fine i muted i screamed a bunch of obscenities
my voice my voice is a little harsh now because i screamed so many swears
all right but hey sorry i dropped my crowbar that was in my pocket
thank you appreciate it young man never know what you're gonna need one of those
all right i gotta go find the doctor that's a glass door
doctor is this way i bet you i can just fucking walk through this now because
they're not paying any attention we're gonna go for it in one two three
go save it quick your voice is always so harsh
all right where's this guy don't move come here come here
all right i got a secret to tell you oh fuck off bastards
where's that guy it's coming around oh shit is he gonna go all the way
wait a minute
you all right are you okay you okay somebody just hit you with it somebody
hits with the crowbar dude get over here all right where do i dump
them i'll just put them right here and then save it
all right we got it bingo all right let's go
doctor's over there i am a doctor he's in there
doctor what why am i in here poisons poison uh what's this syringe
oh shit okay how does this work how does this work i'm curious
sierra nox should be on her way to the emergency area
what i forgot you were in here sir okay i know how it works you just have to
stick it into their head you just have to stick it into their
head oh look at me get rid of the patient paging a doctor
your vitamin and rehydration session has been delayed more information will
all right i gotta get in there's a patient in here and i have to get rid of
them oh let me recalibrate sick
mr doran i'm gonna ask you to get a move on half sierra nox coming in next for a
post-race iv vitamin boost i don't want to keep her waiting
i'm too my best hair doc surely you must be able to squeeze out a few
drops i'm supposed to get rid of you you've inhaled around a gallon of water
by now oh shit poison the iv pressuring me it'll never happen all
right overflow the sink you can't do that in
this game it's not impossible you can't do it i just want to
uh um um uh get over here wait is he alive dude what kind of
control scheme are you fucking playing with here
now what disguise show disguises this guy
now what do i do i have to kill that guy no i don't
i have to kill this guy are you serious i don't think that did anything
uh i don't like this i don't want to do that now what
oh wait i can page the uh i can page i can page to say that we're ready
for the next patient i have arrived paging miss nox
paging is nox your treatment is ready for you
sierra nox should be on her way to the emergency area
okay i forget your name sorry doctor severs okay she's coming this way right
so now i can save the game and i'm going to syringe her in the face
remember you have a vitamin deficiency i okay doc
i can poison the drip all right it's poisoned here she comes
here she comes holy shit okay i'm gonna i'm actually gonna do it
i'm sierra nox you page me i have an appointment miss nox if you can just take a seat please
oh great oh she's here oh she's here why is she not coming
give me the hammer oh she's right we're ready she can come
on in ah miss nox welcome are you ready for your
treatment come on in you're not the wrong person
miss nox i'm ready for you let's do this hello hey don't strangle her now
hey i you want me to test it i would test it first hey yo fucking i would
test it don't fucking get in there i would test it first if i were you
hey i would test it miss nox we're ready for you all right doc
where do you want me miss nox come on in have a seat and relax
sit right there what's on the menu something that'll take care of this
vitamin c pain in my neck vitamin b i promise
once i'm done you won't so what's in this thing anyway vitamin d3
floral extracts hemlock it's designed to be fast and efficient
doctor fast and efficient i like that doctor
wait bella donna isn't that poisonous yes should i be concerned doctor just
relax wait did i say there was poison in it
hope you're having a good time i am you're gonna be having a good time too
real soon
what are you still alive when isn't the poison gonna kill her
the poison should have worked by now let me try that brew
i did it why is everything locked i punched a bald spot into his head
what are you i punched him so bad he went bald in the place that i hit him
are you serious no fucking way what all right i'm out i'm out of here
hooray i completed a mission in hitman vr it actually happened
very cool do the concrete dance party next all right i'll do that one for like
five minutes 52 minutes like three hours i don't want to do what we're doing next
up no no no no no menu what's the concrete level called where is it
berlin right oh wait i can actually go to the dance party you can slap people
oh wait turn it on casual yeah right i'm gonna pick my nose i don't care
on vr you have to play on casual it's impossible i keep biting my lip
you're the worst gamer that's fine oh that's right i forgot about this mission
you have to meet uh that lady right biting your lip is worse than picking
your nose i bite my lip all the time i can't help it
i should really put some chapstick on though yeah i shouldn't you back here
i can't have a goat hello yes where are you i know you're here somewhere where
are you there you are all right stop biting your lip enough
stop it enough what happened here no no she what happened this is her car she
must have gone down this way she had to have oh no my god this
actually is kind of cool in vr this part it's kind of like i'm playing our game
all right here we go save the game right here i'm not doing that again
do you copy bingo i'm with a knife this is like looking for a needle in a haystack
just keep trying agent montgomery all right let's go to the party
agent 47 this guy's serious threat you can't underestimate them
no i never do joe we'll find them we're all in position good report back to me
if there's anything considering how much you love this series
is the vr version fun to play that depends uh wait wait like two weeks
because it is a fucking mess to get this to run like i told you the first like
hour or two that i tried to play this game
in my headset it was flipped horizontally and i was reading everything
backwards for no reason i've restarted the game
like 20 times and it fixed it wait a couple weeks that being said
this it's it's awesome like it's really fun to actually do this in vr
the controls are kind of sloppy uh i would wait to make sure the game
actually can run on a lot of platforms because i mean i had a it was a huge
pain in the ass i'll be honest with you all right let's get in line hey remember
this joke i don't wait in line for anybody
i'm gonna go ahead of all of you where am i going
i don't have to wait in line i'm gonna cut everybody
remember that joke what i did that a couple years ago
all right let me in you already know get the hell out
get out stay safe sir i'm ready no weapons i said what i said
i gotta hide this stuff excuse me sir seems like you're not clear to come
through here sorry i'm not it's not my turn yet
oh maybe this guy this is the drugs guy excuse me
i was wondering if you could help me find my bike no
i have lost my allergy pills no don't care
i can get you in for free no i don't care shut up
what else do i have i can bring a camera in there all right i'm ready
just kill the bouncer all right am i am i even in frame
kind of you can pat me down i've got nothing on me
man i'm ready to party hey love the suit classic cut
thank you but this is a restricted area sorry
what do you mean i second that emotion means get out of here
can you believe this sherry i'm with him him and i are we're together we're
coming in right you and i are hanging together
hanging out with friends so we're just gonna be let in and
together we'll go in there and i'll buy you know i'm really i'll buy you out
like a bunch of jobs like all the drinks you can drink tonight
i'm loaded whatever fuck you hey uh about that bike i forgot i'll help
you where is it you're looking for your bike i
can help you how do i help him kill someone please i'm let me get
inside i'm trying to help this guy find his bike where is the bike
it's over here isn't it what where's the oh there it is
hey i got the pills i think it is oh what's oh my god is it a knife
but a gun happened to find my bike with with my allergy pills i can't believe
what's going on in the world at that at this point
is this legal i found them you are a lifesaver
thank you hey look if you want to get into the club
now i could get you in for free you know you look like a man who needs to
let off a little steam let me in oh you are a little stiff
you really need to come inside but i promise you
my allergy pills can remove some of that tension
don't take some follow me where are they i'll take them
i mean it's probably dusty in there i don't blame you for taking those
hey i should be on the list the name is hellfreed ziegler
and this gentleman is my remember me yeah you look cool
come inside yeah remember me yeah said free drinks all night
he's gonna get in somehow didn't want to fucking help me
you have to put this sticker on your phone
no photos allowed even when you're on the guest list
if you want to pass you need to comply to a frisk sir
go for it just a quick pat down sir nothing to worry about
no i often i was gonna pay for that guy's drinks all night
two of them at least two don't touch me i was gonna buy that guy two drinks
this place is fantastic it's hard to get here but it's the best
party anywhere oh trash what's in there anything good
first there is a chill out area where you can scan
oh don't forget the juice bar the juice is
juice bar okay cool makes all your allergies go away
you have a lot of allergies you know they have shots that you can take
you have to take them like for six months it's a pain in the ass but you
should feel better it gets your body used to like the built
up i get the uh inflammatory response that your body has
all right let's go come on give me that one how much plus two
okay this feels like weird being in first person
oh shit i always throw this guy off and i'm doing it in vr you better believe it
i throw that guy over every time have you had the juice yet because i had a
lot you have to press a oh i thought i
could just like shove them it's so loud i can't even hear anything
else all right let's do it it's chris redfield
i didn't even touch him i didn't even touch him
i think you were standing right next to me i didn't even touch him i didn't even
touch i just jumped off i didn't i actually
didn't even touch him he just like fucking like dolphined
over okay no more fucking around i'm going to
the dance floor i'm sorry i won't do it again i promise i
won't do it again i'm so sorry jeez i promise i won't do that again i have to
get it on myself somebody's standing at an edge like that
i did they have to go over you know it i know it
i wanted to see how far i could get okay not doing that again promise i'm out i'm
out i'm done done i'm done can i get some juice all right
i feel like i'm in the metaverse right now
you know what i mean i like this is what it's gonna be like
like just as fucking weird and awkward as it is in real life
oh cool hey what's up i don't like this i don't want to do this
what how's everybody doing stop looking at me everybody don't point at me
oh oh gross cinnamon sticks how much are the cinnamon sticks dude
can i get some of that juice i'll take one juice please
what what you came into my space bro really
really you know there's a line right you know there's a fucking line
you know there's a fucking line you know there's a fucking line bro
back up come up here and shove me he came up and started pushing me
no that's fucked up that's fucked up you know what i mean
he comes up pushing up on me telling me to get out of his space he literally put
his hands on me he punched me in the back of the head
i want to try this juice i heard it's good he really did
who is he talking to i'm like rp-ing as like the
the drunk asshole it who was it i where was the guy that pushed me it was
this guy no it wasn't oh must resist the urge
push him must resist the urge to push him over the head
um i didn't know i could not be over here all right where the fuck can i go
i'm drinking soda all right i actually probably would
what what i what i'm just drinking a fucking energy drink bro
what bro what
what happened oh i completely forgot that the actual video game was playing
i'm just sitting here rp-ing as a weird like a guy at a bar
those guys are actually contracted to kill me i completely forgot about that
you have to avoid those guys right i completely forgot about the people that
are hunting you right okay that's gonna be so hard
like who brought dad yeah just shat burning
oh it's the best part it's the best part best part
hey dj play play that song that we all like
hey dude excuse me i have something really important to say
excuse me excuse me excuse me watch out just excuse me i gotta get up the front
excuse me yeah i'm wicked sorry i'm looking sorry
i'm really sorry no it's all right bro so i'm looking sorry
i'm looking sorry yeah no no it's all right sorry
hey hey can you play too rude sandstorm i that's my favorite song can you hear
me do you think hey do you have any hey if we all yell
at the same time no bro bro bro if we all yell at the same
time then he then he'll play it no what's it no
if we all yell at the same time he'll play the song we should say darude
sandstorm is what account three down to three darude sandstorm you
guys ready yell it at the same i can't fucking hear
you yell it at the same time hey dude can you play darude
oh big foul oh i'm gonna get thrown out now i'm gonna get kicked out
no just don't just cover me i didn't do that
hey if we all yell at the same time we say darude sandstorm at the same time
he'll play it what this sucks i don't want to be in
this environment ever this guy fucking hates me oh these guys
these two guys are pissed
those guys are on drugs these people are on something really hard
my god what did you take what did you guys take
because you're just standing there and not even moving
what did they take stay away from that stuff man
oh i'm sorry dude i'm all right i'm all right now i'm not gonna puke
is that water hey we all yell at the same time
all right let me get out of here i gotta get out of here i gotta just get in the
bathroom bro hey bro do you know where the
bathroom is bro where's the bathroom man seriously
i'm i need it i don't know where it is but i i feel
i'm gonna fucking hurl oh bro hey bro i think this i think this
guy was just trying to kill me what is your idea this this guy over
there's trying to kill me what do i do about it i'll be back oh
dude yo bro bro hey yo bro
what what happened who did that i didn't do that what i was trying to
anytime you go to like the club and you meet the guy that you were like
saw in the beginning and you haven't seen him in like four hours it's always
dude oh no way hi i'm gonna dump it all right have fun rp'ing it's time to
actually play it ask to play the among us remix i want to
do the dj thing you said you're only gonna be here for five
minutes i did i honestly did not know what that was
gonna do i don't know why did why would i push him
push him for what why would i do that oh let me get back into you
i'm absolutely i'm not gonna beat this one at all when i'm not playing this one
more than five more minutes i want to get to the dj station
bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum bum that's how you get
punched in the face what's happening to my character geez
so loud in there so too loud they need to turn that
shit down it's not fun don't your ears hurt it sucks
hey get light nerd what's going on in here
i have to use the bathroom what get out of my i have to use the bath
i have to have to have to use the toilet so all of a sudden
why are you all partying in here get out of here everybody get out of here
this is a bathroom it's a bathroom is any of these open
somebody in there i'm gonna save it down here
i feel you are violating my personal space
this thing's weird that mirrors don't reflect
what what should i do about this what is it can i not do anything in
here can i actually can you just move out
of the way i wonder can i even go in are they all
locked just what none of you care
did i close the door nobody cares okay uh oh staff key what
all right i got a staff key now what are i staff i thought i was staff
hey dude can you play the rude sandstorm at your next head
could you play that i just have it's my favorite song and i can't believe i
caught you when i wear the way at least i did
i'm gonna get out of here but just play the rude sandstorm for the next set
people are gonna go fucking wild i promise i promise people gonna go wild
i'm leaving shut the fuck up i'm just trying to talk to them
i'm leaving i'm leaving i'm just trying to talk to them look there's more than
one of you what i don't have any coins i gotta be a
tech person what about just running worst joke that
took more than five no it wasn't i'm gonna save it and run
yeah i'm gonna just save it and run that's the best play shit fuck shit
fuck shit fuck fuck shoot oh shoot okay i made it
whoa ah hey hey i need you to follow me i'm going i'm leaving
all right i gotta i can't i gotta get a disguise first
what dude this game is seriously like i just it's like a
fucking sloppy wet sock no i'm reloading it's like this game
this vr game handles like a wet sock all right i need a tech outfit no i can't
use that right now i'm going the other side is this open
shit what about here all right this is better
where is anybody there's one person right here all right close it get it
and go this way turn on the case all right hold on save it here
yeah definitely save it right here see if i can pull somebody and then take the
disguise somebody coming here are my butthole
when is germacraft coming back it's not somebody coming down all right
who's investigating it shit this camera i need a i need a weapon
the strangle never works oh my god it's the dj
strangle them strangle them get the fuck over here oh my god
oh there's a spot over there these controls are gonna make me puke
into my own mouth no i need the fucking disguise
invisible andy oh i'm so sorry i'm so sorry
i had no idea where you were for a second you're right there
sausage poison the poison the missing poison
hey man really working on my new set go rude go rude yeah just working on my
new set go rude i heard it's a good one hey you
gotta tag out you ready hey hey get the fuck off my set
what the fuck dude get out of here why do you keep doing this i'm in the way
get off get your hands off that that's my fucking mouse get your hands off that
stop touching that we'll be right back after this commercial break dare
interrupt my set
it actually works all right i'm going to another level
what's another level are you want to see before i stop go to dubai maybe two more
all right i'll go to dubai look close how's my back it's i'm okay i feel okay
47 look closer to boy i'm having fun though this is a good time
i do need to reset my face welcome to dubai
today is the inauguration of the sector and the ceremony is well underway
you will find marcus stuyvesant near the building's signature art installation
oh this is the one that's oh yeah this one
47 and 47 do you copy i'm here are you in position i'm heading towards the
point of entry can't jump get back to me when you're there
wow what the heck are you serious what what the heck is going on this is
crazy
oh 47 use your camera and scan oh right i can use my camera i think i can
override the windows controls from here how do i do that
um okay that's a huge kind of pain in the ass
i'm in position 47 the inauguration is taking place close by
once you've infiltrated it get your bearings i'm sure there must be floor
plans somewhere understood we need absolute focus on this
it's 7 30 how long have i been playing for alerted to our presence we may lose
them for good how long have i been playing we are so
close 47 i've been playing like three or four hours
they're not going anywhere oh my god the skies okay hello i have arrived
i'm here so good to see you
oh my god
oh quite the introduction thank you sir
but the introduction wow this is actually really pretty
oh or derbs can i have one oh shoot that excuse me thanks a lot buddy
thanks a lot buddy you you gotta call somebody about that
what'd the other win thank you beautiful architecture
thank you i'm proud to yet again immortalize our great family name
what's most important this access granted oh nice
you're trespassing oh i almost made it to the chocolate or derbs dude
oh that's a long ways away isn't it minus two
yeah of course i'm gonna walk up again you want something funny when i first
played this uh well i think i did i don't remember
when i first played this didn't i get stuck here and i like punched this guy
in the face like 10 times where am i oh thank god bro now they
can't stop the windmill i was just going like i partied too hard
oh hey i'll take that i just going like this i was just
walking like this i didn't hurt any what what is it talking about what are you
talking about i don't i can you see this turn on look
over here non-target kill bro are you serious
i don't it's fucking crazy it didn't do that
i literally went like this walking forward
i didn't kill anybody i didn't kill anybody i literally was walking forward
going like this where's uh there no it's not where is it
you killed them i did not now this is not did i not even save the game
shit you're right i didn't all right you know i wanted what's that neighborhood
level i want to go there the one where it's like
the people are doing the backyard barbecues and stuff
what level is that hitman to vermont colorado
this hitman one miami where is it i want to do this one i just want to
walk around gentlemen let's gentlemen there you are
do you have the beach level ah that's a good question vermont
yeah this is this is the one i just want to go to the barbecue
i've marked your map with several points of interest we're running this
mission with very little upfront intel but these locations could provide clues
to help you obtain the information we need good luck hopefully you just hear
that i think you can i just like burped really loud in the
headset okay so he's in there he's over there hello neighbor
am i yelling i feel like it's loud in my head so i'm like i'm talking and
yelling louder than normal i think am i yeah fuck i'm talking way louder
than usual because it's so loud in my head
very cool barbecue birthday party got intel right here
oh geez darling i'm so hungry have you seen those beautiful patties
back there and mr wilson keeps standing behind the
grill even though there's clearly no more gas on it
i know it's weird why doesn't he go grab a new canister
i'm telling you these new folks are strange
did you see that cassidy guy snooping around here
he's been looking at the party three times already
why not just go inside it's open to everyone
yeah it's strange all right let's go oh maybe the wilson's are throwing a
barbecue and everyone's invited it sounds like nolan cassidy has some
interest in the party as well but for some reason
yep i don't trust a man i'd be the grill master of the grill
all right neighbor oh my god i would be like the weird guy
i'm sorry my shirt's ripping is it all right that i get that's the guy with the
grill i was playing the guitar did it come
through in the eyes unlock the door it's right here
really well shit all right i need the key probably in the house
i'm sure he'd be delighted to lend you something what is that
you got a key how are you i'm doing you know what
you know what people don't fucking ask that anymore
like how are you doing right i guess scary
why are you a horror movie character why are you full silhouette i don't get it
what i can't take more than one i don't want to come back up here for five
three or four times that's that burger's way too big all
right hey boss how can i help you yeah sorry i'm talking very loud still
i need a key it's definitely it's in the house all right
it's it has to be in the house where is it it's definitely in there
it's in the house next lot
key key it's definitely over here if an ice cream machine
oh it's just beer oh fuck that's that would have been so much
better if it was like soft serving machine
oh suits you sir thank you uh look at her
look at her key look at her key they are some strange religious cult
how do you keep that much marinara this clean either you're crazy or a manic
depressive and i don't think it's the latter giant
ostriches you wait until tonight if one of them he said orange is wrong
in here where is this key this gotta be the key is definitely something in the
house somewhere right have i lost my mind oh i'll take that
key there's a wasp in the room there's no wasp in the room
guys it's january in las vegas there are no wasps right now it it's like
it's like 40 degrees outside like 30 degrees
can i go back here hmm how do i get the key to get over there
maybe all the way around you must be warm in that suit
it actually kind of goes all the way around
okay all the way around if i go can i go in this person's yard
can all right good there we go trespassing
that's okay i should go like this
oh fuck off honest to god how do i get i i just punch through it
have you seen that janice's oddball nurse has added to camp
no i don't care i'm the grill master i think he comes early
how could as everybody's got their doors unlocked everybody has it locked doors
you can vault the fence no you can't jeez
oh yeah okay well that wasted like 10 straight minutes for no reason
all right okay over here where the hell is this
over here oh shit i'm not supposed to be here
work um
wait a minute yeah i didn't see how did you see me you didn't see me
i need some help here sir i will have to ask you to stop
the right way okay duck duck duck
all right keep your hands where i can see them what they can't see
they can't see me i can't get out of my i didn't save the game either whatever
i i didn't even save the game anywhere shit
okay well at least i know what to do just go hop the fence
and then go i thought i could i didn't know they could see through the bush
there's ants in your room that's all right they help me
all right i'm i'm i gotta stop my body hurts
47 stopping in 10 minutes of interest we're running this is too much fun
though i'm having too much fun but these locations could provide
clues to help you obtain the information we need
good luck yeah the ants help i've trained them
these ants like they they brush my teeth they go around the toothbrush like at
five thousand of them they pick it up they come all the way up my leg all the
way up to my chin i go i open my mouth like this
and they all right climb let's do this shit again
oh shit wait hold on
very important no no no no no no wait wait wait
why would just i can't hit it whatever wait this one right here
hey wait um excuse me sir i think you dropped that
yeah i dropped a golf club relax it's a party
hey stop this ridiculous behavior at once
nice i got it you say what have something
oh here's the grill bastard no i can't i can't do it i can't do it i can't do it
i'm gonna do it
i didn't save it all right i'm done i'm exhausted
i'm exhausted
i'm too tired all right one last just i'm just gonna one last dick head run and
i'm done i pro this is the last just shit head
run and i'm i'm done i wish my body was just such a piece of
shit i would keep playing whittleton creek okay all right i just wanted 47 so
this way marked your map with several points of interest
we're running this mission with very little upfront intel
but these locations could provide clues to help you obtain the information we
need good luck
blake is he that guy who tried to ban maple syrup lollipops
oh hello there how are you
i'm sure there was a very good reason i'm running for a seat in the next election
running for office this year i know you would be extremely appreciate
47 agent 47 i don't much care for politics
not only i like to ban the maple syrup lollipops between you and you tried to
cancel how i don't care about politics either
15 rules to the local town plan in an effort to try to make everything look
do you want to hang
i'm trying to shake his hand no i a friendly piece of advice fella
your boss blake the third he's probably the most unpopular guy in all of the
county in the 10 years he's been chairman he's
bound the municipality in so much red tape we can't even see city hall i like
your honesty if we vote him into higher office between you and me
yep i don't care about politics either neither do i
a better world what are there good luck pal you'll need it
no i'm not gonna punch you appreciates your support
what do you stand for on the issues easy man
what do you stand for on the issues here's a flyer for you mr blake has many
important initiatives to share what is that oh i thought that was like a
thing on his phone that's his fingers coming through
here's your chance to change the world i just kind of like walking around it's
fun
hey you guys haven't been poking around the frog habitat behind the house
have you no oh okay great it's it's just that
well i i saw one of those security people from mr janice's house and
i'm pretty i gotta get this right sure he was burying
who should uh gardener or what who hey man why are you dragging that person
around fuck i need help i didn't even see these
well how come they didn't see that happen
i'm i'm toast i see i'm toast i'm toast adult attention deficit disorder
hey whoa okay i mean that's true you've obviously been watching the
stream well that's not the best way to get a woman's attention you know
hey what in god's name do you think you're doing
i'm gonna punch you now because that's let me see your hands
hands behind your head big boy what are you waiting for
i'm too tired i don't think i can go on
add oh man i'm having too much fun but i got i gotta call it
so how i'm gonna do these vr streams is so the next stream is gonna be
probably on uh on saturday or sunday so you don't have
to wait like five days for another stream so
probably on sunday we'll come back in a couple days
i'm not gonna play um hitman vr maybe i will but i have this i have a
shitload of games that i want to play i did not think i was gonna be doing this
for three and a half hours but that was a lot of fun um i will see
you guys on probably sunday i will see you guys uh oh that's right
yeah uh if you guys want to watch i'm gonna
host it anyways but i'm gonna i'll take a mess if i talk about it
um so stirs myriad uh i'm gonna be on it on saturday so if you want to watch
whatever i'm doing on that on saturday i recommend you go check it out
i'm not playing in myriad i'm simply participating
in a in a way uh that's gonna be saturday
i don't know the exact time i would go check stirs channel
i'm gonna be hosting it anyways so i'm gonna be doing that and then
maybe maybe on sunday yeah we'll come back on sunday
or maybe maybe i'll just do it right after i don't know just keep an eye on
the stuff it's gonna be the next two days
you want myriad is uh stirs dnd-esque kind of campaign it'll be a lot of fun
also keep an eye on the channel on february 1st that's the big stream don't
miss it well you can if you if you need to but
don't but you can all right you're an npc
what well you don't know anything you don't know what i am or not in the game
i could be uh all right i'll do a hair check
uh and then i'm gonna take off sorry there was so much like technical
bullshit especially halfway through and i was supposed to start
way before four o'clock but i'm spent i knew these were only going to be a
couple hours each but i'll see you guys on sunday for more
vr not necessarily hitman by the way i really
want to keep playing but i just can't it sucks i really want to stay
it's all right uh i last time i did vr and i did this in streams more than three
or four plus hours five hours it was a big mistake so i'll take it
easy and i'll be back on sunday thanks for
watching everybody we will see you soon if you're back with us again you're
gonna do among us vr it'll probably be a lot better if they
patch it yeah that's what some people said do you recommend
the game i mean yes but probably not now if you're buying hitman for vr right now
if you just like i want it on steam for psv i'm not for uh
for index or vi whatever give them a few weeks maybe
let them patch it because they probably will there's a shitload of things that
are kind of weird and wonky with it and i'm gonna go drink some water and
get some food i had a lot of fun that was a ton of
fun as it always is vr sucks i'll see you sunday oh i'll see you
saturday if you're gonna watch the myriad so
we need a hair check fine i'll give you i'll give you a disgusting image
after the credits
there's a lot more too i have way more vr games
because six months ago when i did this last time or seven months ago
it was a lot of stuff that we didn't play that i still have
so there's a lot to do yeah mark february 1st on your calendar
it's gonna be a wild one special guests and what what is the stream
i don't know you're gonna have to find out you're gonna have to watch it
all right good night guys see you later take care of yourselves
i'll see you sunday or saturday at 4 p.m pacific
on sunday oh right yeah yeah yeah i'll give you a good big image of this
see how bad is it it's not that bad it's actually not even that bad
howard all right i'll see you guys later have a good night