So now I'm going to... I'm still alright. Let's um... I don't know, am I, is my brain capable of even
playing Breath of the Wild? What is on Switch right now that I can just get? That's just simple.
I feel like it's become very evident on this stream that I am not completely screwed in.
I feel like I'm playing in somebody else's body, you know what I mean? Like I feel like I'm controlling
me, like looking down as a spirit. What's like simple? Play Animal Crossing? There's a new
Monster Rancher. Wait, there is, isn't there? Hold on, I need to investigate this. Let me investigate
this. Is there really? Let's take a look. What's the first thing that pops up on the uh like the
featured page, I wonder? It's only on Switch. I'm afraid to play a Monster Rancher game because I
said that I was gonna get guaranteed, no matter what, a monster to S-rank in Monster Rancher 1
or 2 and I just didn't do it. I got to like A and just quit. What have we got? It's gotta be something
that's just like just completely just basic that I could just do. Oh, Vinny Raid, what's up? Welcome
everybody. Thanks Vinny. Thanks for playing. Uh, maybe we didn't have the best Splatoon gameplay,
but we hung on. We had a good time. That's what matters. Uh, welcome. All right, so what can I
just do? Maybe I will just open up Breath of the Wild and just kind of do a shrine or something.
Yeah, let's just do that. That's easy. Let's just do that. Do the SNES online thing. Eh,
it's this one, right? Oh, I don't have to do this anymore. I can actually, I can really hear the game.
You can explore. Yeah, that sounds like a good idea. Thanks for hanging out everybody, seriously.
I know that I'm kind of a little fucked up. I have COVID if you don't know. I'm gonna just say
that because that is what's going on. We have to be nice. He's sick. No, I actually am fine. I just
feel a little weird. All right, the last thing that I did. All right, we need to change the title of
this stream so it's not like I'm shitting my pants or something. How about, I don't know. All right,
mods, you have complete creative control as long as there's no swear words. You don't talk about
like how, what I, how I look like, what my face looks like today, which by the way, I'm surprised
nobody has said anything about like the way that my, I guess maybe it's not coming up that well,
but maybe I have to be bigger on the cam. No one's said anything about this today,
which is fucking shocking. Do you see like my facial hair? I think people might have just been
being nice. I literally shaved this part and left everything else. I thought it was hilarious,
by the way. I was talking to Holly and I thought it was the funniest thing ever. I was like, oh my
God, like I'm going to shave like this part. The real reason why it's not just for like a stupid
comedic purpose is because I haven't, I've been, I've felt sick obviously. So I haven't really
shaved in four or five days. So it got really, really itchy and annoying. And it's, I don't know,
I hate having itchy, annoying hair up here under my nose and above my lip. So I just got rid of it.
And that's the actual reason. And then I just like, I kind of didn't care how to do the rest.
I was tired. All right. Let's, what are we doing? I just upgraded my tablet. Let's go.
I have access to, I don't think I want to do the big shrine right now. I don't know how much more
gas I have. Rank two is over here. Let's go ahead and deny that one. Okay. Oh, actually,
that's a good idea. I need to turn that off. I had to turn it on. Hold on. How do I do this?
Oh, here it is. Okay. What do you mean, deface? I mean, that was a little mean. Again, that was
a little mean. But I, what do you want me to say? All right. I'm not going to turn this off. Okay.
There we go. Why are you defacing me? Yeah. There's this, which is the area with the big divine beast,
right? Not ready for that one. What I am ready for is I think maybe a little bit of exploration
to the left here. Does that make sense? I'm going to go to the left here. I want to check it out.
You want it to be your friend. I don't, but I, when are you going to do a full playthrough?
Rest of the Wild is a fun game just to, just play it every now and again for a few hours.
It's a great game just to be like, all right, what else am I doing today? This, I'll do this.
All right. So I'm looking for shrines because I'm a shrine Andy. So I need to go, I'm going to go
over here and what's that shrine just ahead? There's one there. It's the only one I can see.
All right. We're going to go straight ahead here. I should probably mark it.
Oh wait. I can use the zoom in thing. There we go. How do you zoom in? Oops.
I saved it. It's over here somewhere. This is interesting. What's going on here?
That was with a pixel to spare, to not die. Yeah. Again, I wanted to be live today too,
so I could warn everybody that tomorrow is the sus guy stream where the entire channel is going
to be rebranded. You are not going to even recognize this place tomorrow. So the sus
guy is finally going to play among us and I'm fucking leaning into it as hard as I can.
All right. So I upgraded the stasis, didn't I? So what does this, what's the upgraded stasis do?
What does it let me do now? Probably something, right? Put this on. This thing's damaged already.
I didn't even fucking do anything. It can freeze enemies now. Let's try it. Ooh. So this will do
all the damage. All right. That's pretty huge. That's awesome. I've never actually done that
before. All right. Trying. I'm going to have to get rid of this weapon. It's going to be damaged.
Where was it? It's like this way, right? Am I going the right way? What time is the sus guy stream?
Now that is a good question. Is it right here? I already did that one. To the left? Why do I
have to fall off? What time? I don't know. Just, just look for it. You're not going to be able to
miss it. I'm telling you. But it's going to be, it's going to be like a hundred billion people
watching that stream. You understand? You're not, you'll be able to find it. Now this is so funny
to me because if that stream is like wicked shit viewership, it's going to be even funnier.
So I'm prepared either way for this to be a win no matter what. Because that's funny. Like if like
nobody shows up to that stream tomorrow and I do all this rebranding and I do this big, oh, I'm
like selling out for the sus guy joke. That's funny. I just got a fairy? What? That's a revive?
Okay. I need to go this way. Is the horse anywhere near me? No. You can eat. No, you can't. Can you?
You can get more. That's pretty cool. I didn't even know they existed. The shrine is between the
tower and the distance here. Is it this far away? If I could have glided and not fallen down.
I have the shrine thing set to on, right? Cut the grass. They, wait, they're in the grass. That's
cool. Oh, watch out. Ganon. There it is. Ooh, that was, this one's weird. It's like a dragon head.
Do you guys see? Oh, wait, this is the, oh, okay. So, I get the horse back here. Let me take an
inventory here. I have a lot of shit. Maybe do some cooking. Eh, I got plenty of apples.
Greetings, traveler. How about a song? That, there are, I thought he was singing.
I'm sorry. It's nothing. I don't mean to pry. Pry about what? Are you, have you never met a
rito before? Odd. My name is Kas. As a bard, I spend my days traveling this land in search
of ancient songs. Have you heard of the ancient songs? No. Ancient songs, songs that sing the
praises of a hero who beat back the calamity in an age past. One of the more famous among them
recounts the events of 10,000 years ago. I happen to know a song about the ancient hero is passed
down to me. Do you want to hear it? Yes. Please do. How is it? Here we go. Should I sing this part?
A dog. I don't feel well enough to do this. Hope survives in Hyrule. I don't care. I,
he's supposed to be singing, not me. It's supposed to be his song. Just read it.
Somebody said, dude, you have an iron deficiency. No, I have COVID right now.
I don't have an iron deficiency. He's lazy. No, I'm not. I have, my iron's fine. Kingdom of Hyrule
was once, I don't know the beat. I can't even hear the music. Ganon lurked beneath the surface,
strengthening its jaws. So the ancient people of Hyrule said to help cause. This is not even a song.
Their efforts bore fruit in an automated force to help avert calamity by sealing it at its
source. For giant behemoths for which the power never ceased. Each of these titans was called
a divine beast. It's not a Disney movie.
Well, how do you know that? There's no lyrics here. You sound like Steve from American Dad.
That voice actor is an incredibly talented singer, by the way, if you didn't know.
And when I'm, I don't know. I took too much fucking cold medicine for this one.
So this is the original game for the regular Nintendo. Wait, that wasn't 10 years ago. This is
what? Twilight Princess? No, you're a fake fan. I don't play Zelda games. Yeah, that's correct.
I think I heard this music and it just made me think, oh, that's old Zelda stuff. Thanks for
listening. Please come back and hear it again sometime. Hold on. I got to replace this. Give me
one sec. It is the original game. Yes. Well, I think you, I think you're one of the only people
that said that, but I appreciate it though. Hold on. Let me plug this in. I'm plugging in different
headphones. It's not a song. It's more like an old proverb. All right. But if he said he was going to
sing, he has an accordion. Ouch. Ow. You ever put too much weight down on your elbow? Weird, like
weirdly enough, you put, you put your elbow down to brace yourself or something and you put a little
just somehow too much weight and it's just, just this insane pain. Just whoa. But other times you
put the exact same spot, it won't hurt at all. Okay. Well, that's cool. Pretty cool lore. Trying
time. I'll show you how it's done. I missed every single swing and I didn't do that on purpose.
Is this a combat shrine or a puzzle shrine? Let's find out. Time for a chat mute. Yeah,
go ahead and do it. All right. It is shields from water. Okay. Shields from water. I'm going to
assume this is, we're going to have to do this. Freezing here. Do I die in this water? No. Okay.
I got to stop the flow of water. Actually, this is, this is a current here. I don't even know how
you even do that. Like, oh, you know what? It's all right. Sprint being X and jump being B.
Kind of weird. All right. Does this do anything? Walk with water. Wait a minute. I can't. Ah,
look at that. Didn't take me any time at all. Really? Is this not high enough? Oh, okay. Watch
out. Laser. Okay. Let's try this. No, not stop time. I can pull it out, right? Ah, all right.
So, the chest chest over there. Oh, I know. I already got it. You don't even need to help me.
If I need help, you know how I'm going to ask for it. You better believe it. What's in here?
Ancient core. Pretty good. Sorry, I already got it. This one doesn't seem very hard. This one seems
just pretty good. You know what I mean? Ancient screw. I just got that for free. All right. Hold
on. Let me, I need, I don't want to use these arrows. Where did I get 41 ice arrows? Are you
serious? Okay. Well, I'm going to use it and let's just use the knight's bow. Okay. Should I play the
Sims 4? Like just get all the expansions and just play it? What the fuck? Get up. Stop. How do I get
on? I thought I was going to miss it. Whatever. That's fine. Like I dragged over. At least I
could see what I need to do. I'm going to have to block it, right? Whoa. That was cool. Okay.
I definitely have to block it from going over. How do I get that one? No. Wait, I know what to do,
right? Yeah. Knight's broadsword. I'm going to run into one of the wood ones. Okay. So what happens
over here? No, no, no, no, no, no. Get it. Grab it. Grab it. Grab it. I'm dead. The current is going
to pull you. All right. So I just have to get to the raft. Now this is where I'm going to have a
little bit of trouble, I think. So I have to get rid of all this. Can I move this with the... No,
this is made of wood. All right. I turned it into a fucking McRib. It's fine. Oh my God. Wait,
wait, wait. Don't. That's okay. I'm dead. I have to get on top of this. That just spawned and I
wasn't even ready. Is another one going to come? So I have to block it right at the end here.
Oh shit. Easy. Got it. Spirit orb. Why are you on? What are your pajamas on? This is a Marvel shirt.
This is not. I have four now. I can do another upgrade. Explain the McRib joke. It looked like
a McRib when it was upside down. This is not what I explained it. How? You're a nerd. Go back and
look. It looked like a McRib sandwich. All right. I got four orbs. Let me get the horse back.
And from here. All right. I got a... Oh, it's a bridge right here. All right. I'm going to
go to the bridge and go left. That's the plan. I like exploring. Is this on Switch or PC?
Rank two. This is it on Switch. You can't get in for anything else.
All right. Rank two. How am I doing on it? I think I'm doing okay on food, right?
I've got a lot of food that I never ate. I spent like 45 minutes cooking all this stuff before
and then like turn the stream off. Wait, I have those truffles. I don't think I need them yet.
Let's keep exploring. Buy arrows. Oh, thank you. Where is... Where's the guy with the big
sack on his back? He's inside. Okay. Look at this dog. Cool. All right. I want to buy.
Yeah, but should I play The Sims 4? You know what? After VR, after like the two or three days in VR,
we're just doing a fucking brand new Sims 4 insanity day. Oh, I need to give me all these.
This is so cheap. Wait a minute. Am I getting scammed? Buy them in bulk, right? 6, 12, 18, 20...
6, 12, 18, 24, 32. You save a little bit of money, but I'm going to buy 20 of these.
What is this? Oh, hot-footed frog. Max stamina. Should I just get buy everything? These are only
10 cents. These are cheap. I'll take them. Are these worth it? I mean, if I got money, I'll take them.
I'll take them all. No. Okay. It's... No, no, no, no. They're easy to go catch. Okay. Go catch them.
They're free. Oh, I thought it was the dog for a second. I was like, wait. I know. No, I don't want
to hear that song again. It was a good song, but I don't... We don't need to hear it again.
All right. Let's go. I'm for exploring. What was the thing that people said that it just...
The horse automatically goes on the road if I press something? What is it? All right. How do
we save this person? You press Z, L, L. Okay. Are you okay? Look who's here. The guy that stood around
and watched me get beat up. A little help next time. Okay. That's what I just did, isn't it?
All right. Let's put that... No, I'll keep this one on. So if I get closer to the Calamity Ganon
castle, is it some bagging happen? Just don't press anything. Okay. What does that mean?
What is... I don't... I'm not going to the castle. Let's go over to that tower this way. All right.
There's a lot of towers over here. Should I fight this thing? Oh my God. There's like
more than one. Can't do it when I'm on a horse, can you? Oh shit. Multiple people
shooting sniper rifles at me. Is he okay? What happened? Oh my God. Why is this like
level 100 zone? What is going on? Why am I still alive? What's happening? Excuse me?
Help. Help. Why am I stuck? Get up. Yeah. Fuck you. Climb a tree. Climb a tree. Climb a tree.
Climb a tree. Climb a tree. Quick. Just like a fucking animal.
It's raining, you stupid game. What if they... Can they shoot each other?
I just have to get over there, dude. Come on. What keeps refilling my health? I just... Oh,
that was fairies. Oh, I didn't know I can't go over there. There's like a... All right. I didn't know
what was going on over there. So I didn't know I was going to go into like the part of the game
where I'm not allowed to be. And I'm going to get warnings on my screen. Like, you're leaving the
game area. Warning. You're leaving the game area. Okay. Well, we... I can't... I'm not going this way
again. I'm going somewhere else. Where should I go? It's not possible? All right. Well, then I'm
going to go... I'm going somewhere else. Go south, then west. Like down here? You need to learn how
to parry. You're just too low level right now. I'll go this way. You guys also have to remember
that I haven't played this game in like two or three weeks. I don't know where I'm supposed to
be going. All right. I'm going to say if this is like too high and too hard. Did you say rip?
I'm going to go this way. Let's just bang a left. It's cold here, but that's all right. I have cold
gear, don't I? No, that's swim speed. I don't have any cold gear. I have fire gear. What about the
divine beast? I feel like I was right about to do it. The one in the mountain. Yeah, I'm going to
go there. I feel like I was about to start doing that. Yeah, I'll do that instead. That was up here,
right? I remember there was a mine cart. How come I need to get a tower here? It's just a green tea.
Get the tower first. Yeah, I'm going to just find the tower first. All right. I just wanted to get
over here and see. This is definitely not the right place to be. Oh, my shit's burning.
You know what? I don't fucking want it anyways. Okay, so that is a tower that way, which I think
this is closer to the tower. Why did you throw the good sword? It was about to break. That sword
actually was about to break. This is where the mine cart is. All right, hold on. Let me try to
remember something from a month ago. I'm going to go high, right, and look over here because I can
actually see what the fuck I'm looking at. You use first person? I will. All right, let's take a good
look. So I need to look over here. There is the tower right there. Stamp it. That's not A.
God damn it. Is there anything else here, too? No, that's definitely where I want to be.
All right, can I just float over there? We're going for it. You got that shirt at Walmart.
You don't need to concern yourself where I get my t-shirts, okay? You don't need to concern yourself
where I get my t-shirts. It doesn't matter. Did I get it from Target, Walmart? Did I get it from...
Am I dying? Why am I dying? I'm getting hurt. It's not that much. Well, I can just climb. It's not
raining. I can get up here. Oh my god. Why is it raining? It's not even raining on the weather
forecast. It just rained in one spot for one second. All right, we're good. Come on, come on,
come on, come on. Please, please, please. People are gonna make fun of me. Oh, nice. Good. Okay,
this will do it. Yeah, there it is. I'm good. Broad sword. Let's get it. This is pretty. Thank
God Frank too is okay. Yeah, he took a explosive sniper rifle bullet right to his side. A shield?
What is this? Do I have to match that thing? I have to match this. Okay, so it's... Put this
down. Let me go look at this. It's like a Tetris piece. So it's one on the top. So it's one, two,
three, four. One, two, three. One, two, three. One, two. One, two, three, four. One, two, three, one.
I forgot. One, two, three. One, two, three, four. One, two, three. One, two, three, two. One, two,
three, four. This is not right. I have to do this. Okay, I had it in reverse. It's like this.
Everybody talks shit about me when I couldn't do this the last time and it's probably a different
puzzle. I probably don't have to match these. Or do I? One piece just sticks out in the back.
Just put it in. It wouldn't fit in. I mean like right here. I don't think I can do that. I can't
believe this because everybody fucking said last time too. Am I supposed to be matching it? Is that
what I'm actually supposed to be doing? There's two sticking out on this side, one on this side,
one on this side, and then three on the back. So it's got to go over here. I don't know if... I
thought people may have been fucking with me. How did that take 24 minutes? It took like three.
And that person for an hour. Oh, it's in my eye. Oh, this is like steamy. Okay,
should I just go up the front door here where the path is? This seems like the right idea.
Are the chocobos hostile or no? They don't look it. God damn it. Overshot it.
Fucking piece of shit. You thought you were gonna get me with that? Nope. Sorry. I'm gonna watch my
health. Who is doing that by the way? The chest. Oh my god, there's a chest here. What is going?
Why did I climb up a fucking mountain? I'm so angry. Hold on. I tried to turn around.
Nice. I need to eat something before I die. Just something tasty. Something that's not
gonna do anything crazy, right? How about this? How about just a few apples? I don't
need... Whatever. I don't want to waste food. Are you guarding something? All right, let's move.
You motherfucker.
Trying, really? What's this? Oh, goodness. I'm eating something better than that. Yeah,
let's just go with a fried wild greens. Let's go. Give me more health. Don't go chasing. He's dead.
What are you guys guarding over here? What's this? I'm gonna blow this shit up. I'll take them.
That's good. What is that? Crab? Is there anything even in that? Roasted bass. This is food,
so this is good. Okay, more food. I'll take it. Pick up the boxes and drop them to break them.
I'll remember that for next time. Very cool. All right, almost there. It's right up here,
right? Is this a shrine? That's my favorite. What was that? Are they on fire? Okay.
Still have COVID? Yes, I do. I do. It's pretty mild, but still sucks. It's sort of right in the
middle of it right now. Did I get this one? No. Let me go up a little higher. Yeah, I have my
sense of taste, my sense of smell. It's all there. I'm just really raspy and congested,
and it kind of just feels like I like get my face punched. I just feel like kind of sloppy.
Okay, can I jump? I think I can jump over this, right? Can I not? Elden Tower. I think I can make
it. Just got COVID myself. Definitely not a fun experience. I just hope it goes away soon. They
know that COVID has a tendency to linger, which not looking forward to that if that's the case.
I am fortunate enough where I have a very mild case of it so far. I obviously don't want to,
you know, knock on wood, but it's pretty mild. Cool. All right. Let's actually see what we're
doing here. Don't push yourself. No, I'm good. I wouldn't be live right now if I
didn't think I could be for at least a few hours or so. I mean, I might be a little sloppy today,
but is that any, let's be honest, is that really any different? Your voice sounds better than
last stream? Probably. Although I have been taking this high little cold kind of whatever,
maximum cold strength. Cool. Okay. Well, now I can actually see what I'm doing. So important.
This is, where's the, the beast is up here. Let me go to, actually, let me go here.
Destroy Ganon, the hero sword, free divine beast. Okay. This is the one.
Ludo, thank you for helping Unobo after taking the painkillers. Ludo was about to go challenge
divine beast Varudania, but then his back started hurting again. No one will be, well, no one will
be challenging the divine beast today, it seems. Okay. Meet him there to let me, okay. This is where
we need to go. This is what we were doing before and it's right here. Cool. Let's go. Yeah. I've
been doing, I've been taking Nyquil to it in the evening hours because the thing about taking
Nyquil is it just, it makes you just feel like you're on another planet sometimes, especially if
you do it a couple of days in a row. I always try to space out stuff like Nyquil. You got to be
careful with drugs like Nyquil. It works, right? Stuff like Nyquil is, oh man, it works, but you
just got to be careful with that shit. All right. So let's do it. What's this gem? Am I ready to do
this? I mean, if there's ever a time to do it, I'm ready. Here we go. Jesus. You think I'm ready
for divine beast too? Let's find out. Help me. Oh, it's not even a cut scene. Yeah, but taste
your own medicine. Fire. Really? Swing. All right. I am out of just basic shit weapons. What should
I use? I'm afraid to use anything. This is a whole, this is all collectibles. I don't want to take my
collectibles out of the Saran wrap. You know what I mean? I don't want to take them out of the plastic.
What should I use? Just use them. I know, but they'll be ruined if I use them. I don't want
to take them out of the plastic. I'm going to use, um, the, the Lionel sword. The Trident can't be
replaced. All right. Oh, thank God. A shit weapon that I can take out of the plastic.
I just took this thing out of the box, took the plastic off and freaked out and tried to put the
plastic back on. All right. You good? Use ice arrows. What are you, a dope? Really? I tried to
press the other B button. Yeah. The other B button. Wow. You're crazy strong. Goro, you saved me.
Are we going to do the divine beast together? Hey, you guys understand? I just put fingerprints
on that sword and just reduced its value by like 50%. It's true. Not coming, but why? His back hurts.
Okay. If boss can't help, there's nothing else we can do. I suppose I'll just head back now.
Please replace all the Goro's with Goku. That's right. Oh, you're not going back, but why, Goku?
What? I'm going to try to board the divine beast. Why do you think you, you know, what do you think
you are, Lord Durek? It's dangerous in there. How do I do it? Nope. I forgot how to do it.
Goku. I forgot. I actually don't remember how to do it. Okay. Why risk it?
Problem is good old boss raised the bridge of Eldin to make sure that that mean divine
beast couldn't get over here. You lost his touch. Yeah. I won't. I'm, I'm don't feel well. Use the
cannon. You can't use the cannon if boss won't come down here. That means we're out of luck.
Oh, it occurs to me that you know how to use the cannons. I do. Okay. Just shoot the cannons at
it. I'm going to be the cannon ball and you'll launch me. I've got Daruk's protection Goro.
My ancestors help can't possibly fail me. It means I can smash into anything and I won't hurt one bit.
Okay. Okay. Let's, let's shoot you out of a cannon. Oh, did I shoot him at the bridge?
Is this lined up right? Shoot him into the lava. I'm looking forward to this Sims. I think that's
going to be a lot of fun. You good? We did it. Time to do the divine beast. Let's get a move on
across that bridge. Sims, let's go. It should be fun. All right. Let's get ready to move.
Bridge of Eldin. It's pretty cool looking. I need to talk to you. Divine beast Varudania is out
causing trouble again. Let's go stop him. I wonder how we get in. Definitely in his mouth.
He's going to go like, we have to run in. Or in his legs. Okay. Take out the
drone things. What's this? Yikes. Sentry is always a nuisance no matter where it is or how many of
them there are. When finds you, Varudania will go nuts, which will cause Death Mountain to erupt
Goro. I always get spotted and magma bombs come raining down one after another. If Boss were here,
he'd swap those magma bombs away like they would nothing force his way up. I don't think you'd be
able to do that. I don't want to cause any trouble. Maybe the best idea is to give me a signal to let
me know when I should stop and when. Wait, what? Wink? How are you going to see that whistle? When
I hear you whistle, at least stop in my tracks or start moving forward. I like it. Even though
it's kind of like calling a horse. Okay. I'm counting on you. So I got to tell him when to stop
and when to go. We just play red light, green light. All right, we'll go. Go do it. Yeah. All
right. You're ready. All right. You're ready. Just testing. I don't understand. I don't get it.
We have to scale this whole mountain together, but isn't he just going to walk behind me?
Why don't we just stay on the edge here? What are you doing? I don't get what's happening here.
Isn't he going to stop if I stop? I'm not telling him to do anything.
Just don't go in the circle. Okay. So stay here. Don't move. How fast can you go? This is bait,
but I'm going to take it anyways. Can I shoot these down? Wait, can I move this?
Okay. We need to move these rocks out of the way. Stop. Don't go anywhere.
Jump. Why is this here? This is in a weird spot. Isn't this in a weird spot?
This doesn't seem so bad. All right. I'm going to get in here and I'm going to shoot you to...
Where am I going to shoot you to? Why would I do this? I don't want him to go that way.
Why would I do this? This feels weird that I shouldn't be doing it like this, but whatever.
Let's try it. Was I not supposed to alert this creature? Did you do it wrong? We did it. Oh,
okay. We just have to keep doing it like this. All right. Sounds good. All right. We got these two
drones here. How far did they go? I'm doing it pretty good, I think. How far back did they come?
This one stops there. This is going to be hell on earth. I already know it.
All right. This is as far as it goes. Let me take a quick... I need to take a look
because I'm going to screw this up. Is there any safe place? I have to keep moving the whole time.
So I have to take a picture. You stay here. I don't want you to get in trouble. I need to look.
All right. There is a safe place right there. Ready to move? Let's go. Get in here. Stay right
there. All right. Then I go now, which would get me to... I don't know. Where am I trying to get to?
I got to go alone. There is a safe spot right in the middle. Is that accurate? Is it safe right
here? I think it's a safe spot right here. Oh! It is. Okay. Get over here. Let's go. Turn around.
Oh! Fuck. Where do we go? What? Go, go, go, go, go... Turn around. Turn around, turn around,
turn around... Turn, turn, come back here. Back, stop, stop, stop, stop! I don't get it.
what it does it stops how do you can you hold the umbrella up for me too fuck you
buddy I don't get it do I have to climb excuse me I'm getting up there I don't
give a shit if you come with me stay there don't move you are you safe right
there he's not gonna get caught right are you gonna get caught no you just get
over here come over here right now you have an invincibility shield you can
move dude what it doesn't matter I think we can still make it we can still make
it no shield get over here get over here move your ass right now okay we're fine
so how do we get by this one I think wait a minute I think I know I wasn't
even gonna do it like that it's dead by accident over here okay almost there
what is that okay can you fight what don't let him activate any of this shit
need a bow we'll show you for a bow I don't want to equip anything all right
you good you good good good who cares about that I don't need it all right
another cannon to shoot from here go one more I'm assuming it's probably the
hardest stretcher I don't know why I couldn't get through the first part to
work I hope I have little save points every now and again here that would be
horrible if I didn't in fact you know what I'm I don't trust myself at all I'm
eating as many fucking apples fishes and potatoes as I have in my inventory
didn't I get like roasted bass I did doesn't really heal that much all right
how far does it go odd no you stay here don't move I think I know what I need to
do but I don't know so let's find out if I know what I'm doing I don't know what
I'm doing I know what I'm doing this is the wrong one I'm all right I'm okay
what are you doing all right so why did I what was the why did I what was the
point of that what was the point of that break all that to fly up for no
reason have to put something there oh I know what to do it's got free a lizard
come on really nothing it way too hard way too hard just to come back with it
spawn again I think I do have to die you know what let's go fuck it let's go just
walk just walk you can make it trust me you can make it go you can make it just
trust me you just go now actually perfect timing I think come on come on
come on come on don't walk into the metal I eat it you idiot okay all right
do not I did it way too hard I thought the thing was so heavy I just really it
was like a fucking okay stay here oh it's another one all right can I how am I
gonna move this I need to kick it hit it yeah but it's wedged against this
rock this way I'm gonna shoot it this way out and whatever let's see what
happens that's it that's it that's enough right one more one more two more
I quit actually this is safe hey if you're above the clouds you can't get hit
I need to get down please I need to get down please are you doing over oh my god
I'm gonna fucking he's gonna hit it again all right I swear to God I don't
I was gonna take it I can't buy for me on the ground so he's running back oh my
god he's running back right in the face I actually should die I should die
because I need to respond the rock that I'm doing wrong I need to get the rock
to go up and hit the thing or whatever just started over at the checkpoint
which is right here if he wasn't running back he could have kept going
the dog there is no dog okay get over here wait how far away is this no okay
perfect okay okay okay where's the rock where's the rock there's no rock anymore
the rock is gone it's permanently gone no it's up there so am I do I have this
idea right do I have to break these first well I push it down there and it
gets sucked up and hits it and breaks it that's wrong it's wrong what if I need
to magnetize I can't magnetize it I can stop these from moving magnetize the
soccer ball magnetize the soccer ball why and then kapow wait hold on wait a
minute wait a minute you mean I can fly and then kapow let me try that all right
why the pile that's why I went way all the way over here to do this but I was
curious so Kapow can I do this I mean I did it but I didn't I get hit by the
blades and saw me I don't think you can do that world Kapow boulder Kapow I
don't get it like do I have to shoot the boulder at it to hit and break it I feel
like that's wrong minecraft how missile Kapow Kapow no missile missile Kapow
missile creeper minecraft creeper bomb creeper oh I'm gonna I think that's what
you guys are trying to tell me I'm gonna try it I probably just aimed it wrong
last time is that what I just have to aim it this way and get it like correct
how many swings is it wait a minute why these rocks here why these boulders
lined up like this why is this boulder here to all right in my brain this is
like hey let's set up a little puzzle here we got this big boulder that you
could move and it's like it's really in frame and it's something you have to
look at and walk by and yeah maybe roll it down the hill so it gets sucked up
and then gets kids to think why are these here that's just bait it's just a
bait puzzle because honestly I could have just done this the whole time just do
this oh thank goodness I didn't get spotted
maybe better view where is it where is it that's how like it was a hundred years
like years away wait well I didn't know I could do that what am I doing okay why
did I press the button a second time what did you do that because of monkey
with tools I'm a fucking ape I'm a monkey I like you I how did I get that
wrong I don't even understand how I did that wrong I I just I don't understand I
thought it was you never seen I'm gonna get a double in this game before there's
no reason me to press the button a second time I just but I'm I don't know
my mind was just like is it close enough try stop don't talk to me fuck you and
your shield why can't I I did why can't I have one of those okay we're gonna do
this now the correct way everyone's saying fly and then drop the bomb I'm
gonna fly and I'm gonna drop the bomb okay just don't drop it into the wind
right don't do it in the wind fly over whoa look at that oh explosive okay fuck
fine no stupid idiot stop these are like a super
crates I pick these up and smash them hey heads up heads up heads up down
there what should I do wait I should probably use this I'm gonna need these
later I'm taking them with me I think all these with me what up can I have
one can I please have one why did it let go Frank just come over Frank whatever
your name is you just come over here it's safe it's safe now you can walk
this way it is completely safe I'm promising you there's no monsters and
there is absolutely no drones that are gonna be shoot now oh I don't even know
how it's impossible to drop all three of them in the lava I don't even it's not
it's not what's happening watch out don't get hit please all right we made
it I did it I actually I made it something shaggy okay this is it I made
it I'm finally here I got it now I understand that was hard to watch you
know I have something that I think is pretty funny about the Breath of the
Wild playthrough so far people act like I'm playing a horror game you know I
watched that with like one eye open leaning back in my chair dude that was
so hard to watch I was like barely looking at it I couldn't even stand
looking at it it was so horrible is he all right oh my god that looked so
horrid what's wrong with his face stream is a horror movie bro they're just
cringe I appreciate that thank you you did fine it was fun I mean whatever hey
I'm having a good time
oh as in they're cringing out the info from the guidance stone over there now
okay so I have access now to this second spirit thing really dark in here do I
need a torch or something dragon bone vocal club okay I figured it out okay
there is just a torch here now all right let me throw this away I get rid of the
sword now I'm afraid to throw that away I feel like I can't get one of those
ever again right throw it is everybody gonna freak out if I throw the limo sword
into the wall and explodes is that yes throw it into the wall or no yes you
need to yes keep it yeah that is gonna freak out if I throw I'm gonna let go
and I'm in five seconds oh I don't have mod chat even open they might be
freaking out is it somebody's drinking milk oh hi Jerma hi we're good all right
so if I let go of right burger people gonna be mad everyone's typing people are
always mad it's funny over all right torch see if we can't see anything in
here here we go all right creepy cool anything else over here oh that kind of
sucks it it goes out um shit all right I need I gotta just there's probably like
five ten of these I'm just gonna look around for those first before I fight
anything huh I can't see anything I need to put a bow on I'm just put it on
this whatever this royal bow it doesn't matter I'm gonna die okay okay I shot
good I'll use that okay let me just check this perimeter a little bit yeah
two chests hmm well I had a good thing I bought a lot of these can I actually
turn the lights on here am I just being an idiot and doing this completely wrong
this turn lights on I know I'm on ooh all right so just like the other one the
controls have been enabled you're gonna have to help me out with this one nice
job getting the map of the divine beast the terminals that control Rudania are
noted by the glowing points on your map to take back Rudania you'll need to
activate all of the terminals you got this little guy okay yes finally I can
see I'm gonna being able to see camera was a little high on the camera all
right so here we are I need to activate all these things this should be fun this
is a beast it's a giant shrine it's like my favorite part of the whole game so
what can I do I can I can move this up or down put it back put it back put it
back put that back put it back put it back put it back out um okay I need to
turn that back let's go back the other way am I going the other way I think I'm
fucking this whole thing up all right I'm on my he's almost back no this is
correct no this is the right way this wasn't here before all right let's just
try going this way first this is out we're kind of where I came in right I
wonder if that out was in my mouth okay a ball has to go into here when do I get
the ball just checking out all the rooms relax well you've died I think this thing
is all right so I have to touch that I wonder if I can just jump to this I'm
gonna try it that works got one there are four terminals remaining that's the
way okay well now that I'm up here oh all right no I'm so pissed an idiot I
didn't mean to do that um well I'm down here now so whatever I have to turn it
again what's happening okay I'm gonna turn it this way again whoa all right okay all
right all right wait wait wait wait wait oh how do I get that I have to turn it
but I'm not gonna fuck around right now maybe a minute link what the hell are you
doing whoa come on I can't like that I'm getting turned around here all right let
me what what is it what is going on here get rid of that there's one up on his
spine up there feel like I can get that one right now I'm gonna get that one
right now check this out let's go hold on if I spin him I can walk along his
spines that sounds correct there's also something over here too this might be
stupid but whatever um I don't know let's try it wrong way I'm on the wrong
side wrong side wrong side wrong side I'm going to the lava
damn it what's this oh I found one oh I can't do this one I wonder if I can
actually just brute force it and get up there I think I probably can but that's
not the way I'm gonna try to do this so let's go up this way what's this eyeball
all right I'm gonna do this right I feel like this is correct this seems like a
right way to do this one I do you I jump through it how do I jump through that
the one spot that I couldn't land on is where I landed I'm gonna try that again
I feel like I can get it this way I do I need the blue flame to do that I think
it's I need blue flame okay well where's the blue flame can I grab one easily
from here through window or something not really well let me just go I think I
can get this one now right this is one on the spine oh please
I'll take it really really where I was wondering if it was on that side of the
other side there are three terminals remaining I love these these are so I
would I love I would have an entire game that was just this stuff just give me
like 20 divine beasts and that's just that's the entire video game all right I
need to light that blue flame where the hell was that I don't know we're here
somewhere I want can I I'm just gonna spin it okay let's go
so if I go around here ah there's one right there hmm oops that's not how you
do it I think I got it don't hands in your head me I got it now I do ha ha ha
get away from me the other ones over here right cuz I flip it and then yeah
I gotta get up here watch this so I could I flip it and it's gonna be this
way and then I can like this one right I thought I don't flip this shit and I
could come on there another one somewhere but that was the one all right
there's another one though I swear there's another one maybe there's not
I lost it or is there another one well let's try to do this ball one then no
okay well I guess I'm wrong all right I need to go down to where the ball may
have dropped where did the ball go nice is that better than what I have on for
anything I guess I could get rid of this bow right where did the ball go I dropped
that ball down but I don't know where it is we're gonna drop down it was like a
tube shaft or something and where is it I don't know where it is it's gonna go
down and look oh wait a minute what's this why is this in the way what did
that do I get it I get it I think I get it all comes down here and my wrong so I
moved this out of the way turn it well it's frozen right and wait make any
sense that makes sense to me and I'm gonna see if it does anything
enough yeah one more after this more after this is what I meant all right so
the other ones ones in the tail ones on the other side of his leg flip them
again all right this one's got all this grass shit all over it what does this
mean can this be a lady but I don't have to do with this I think I'm stupid I
know what exactly what to do with this it's oh yeah that was easy
that was simple it's the easiest one of the whole night get out of the fucking way okay
just one terminal remain last one is in the tail wonder how hard this is gonna
be I think it's probably underneath them I gotta make them flip right something
to do with this shit it's definitely something to do with that they go
outside and look I break this whoa hello let's open it all right cool I
think I'm almost done with this I see probably a boss at the end right I pick
up an object wait wait what am I doing when I fuck with anything in this room
I pull this can't pull it off and burn that wait I can burn this that scared
the shit out of me oh wait I know to do okay ready watch this it's stupid or is
this correct find out why is that not working oh I'm overthinking it just a
little bit here all right let's go do I have enough like health to do this and
weapons and shit and start up the main control unit which is up on his back
there should be a new glowing mark on your map you're gonna need to make your
way over to that stay focused all right so this is probably heat so I'm gonna I
gotta be ready I do have a lot of food although not really I have to be careful
let's get back up there which I use as a weapon probably I don't know like the
I'm gonna use like the ancient battle axe just giving this fucking thing
I have arrows I got a lot of ice arrows I think I'm good this shouldn't be too
bad whatever it is go second divine beast about to be destroyed well actually
we're not trying to destroy them activated I like data I know how to deal
with you I shout out watch yourself now that ugly pain in the crack is Dan in
handiwork thing got the best picture I will crazy looking good all right that's
a good picture okay I keep the islands fine get out I swear to God man a X is
B and B is a and a is Y and B is X just kill me honestly I'm gonna do fire
resistance no defense boost back up back up back it up what's happening all right
fire resist high behind something I don't do I think I have to hide all that
for a little ball like that man that thing is tiny Wow that fool be careful
that big scary and that is nothing that was terrible
alright so what am I how do I like reflected whoa he sucks it up I freaked
out I don't know I got it goodbye that wasn't too bad the last boss I think was
harder because the water and I think my internet was freaking out too there we
go second divine beast you are no good at this game oh you said you are
so good at this game I'm sorry I read that wrong our container I'll take it oh
I also do I need to upgrade um I have four spirit orbs so I can upgrade very
nice once you activate the main control you will not be there really I got
everything didn't I I think I got everything inside most of it I love the
divine beast am I the weirdo that thinks the shrines are the best part of this
whole game I know I've asked this before but I they're the most fun I like the
little weird puzzles and little combat things I have already beat that game
though years and years and years ago I would play it again they did a remaster
of it didn't they I feel like I should apologize doing all I could to protect
Hyrule when that thing got the best of me sorry that me resting with the rubble
cause such a mess the good news is Rutani is now back under our control
that means that our century-old Ganon beatdown plan can finally go into effect
I'm gonna take this down the mountain I'll have a better shot at Ganon there
and then once you've made your way into Hyrule Castle we're gonna light that
thing up feel like this guy's still talking from like a thousand feet away
give you something it's a special power of mine called Daruk's protection it's
no good to me now that I'm a spirit but it might be useful for you new power so
I'm going to assume that you can just run to Ganon at the very first ten
minutes of the game and try to beat it in an hour that accurate you don't have
to do all this that's cool from this moment for the power of protection yeah
my soul now lives inside you good luck little guy a lot of people did give my
regards to the princess that would actually be kind of sad if on your first
playthrough you'd be in the first you've been waiting for this game let's say for
like five years and you just go I'm gonna go investigate the castle and it's
the end of the game and you just like beat the whole game and you just oh fuck
oops didn't mean to do that this is huge map and you just don't explore any of it
you see the credits that did happen you'll have three hearts though yeah you
can beat the game with a stick damn
well that ought to do it we're set here now we just gotta wait for the perfect shot once Link is in the
castle Brutania will unleash an epic blast Ganon won't know what hit him
looks pretty good from up here even after a hundred years the old rolling
ground sure are a sight for sore eyes I wonder how the warrants fared after the
great calamity I sure hope everyone down there is still going strong after every
hey look at that still going strong indeed oh by the way son pass down our
family power to somebody else it's not you link has it he does have it oh never
mind okay so protective power containing the perfect defense of the champion
Daruk it will automatically protect you from all manner of attacks as long as
you're holding the ZL really oh fuck don't do that how long does it last so
it's generally just if it's a you take three hits for free that's pretty
helpful three blocks then it recharges it's very useful though cool cool cool
cool cool very cool alright I'm gonna complete this mission and I need a
spirit orb thing because I want to I should just probably stamina thanks so
much I don't exactly know what you were doing in Rudania but well it seems to
have calmed down you know while I was up there I could have sworn I saw Lord
Daruk standing on top of Rudania I wonder was that his ghost I don't know
how to explain it but somehow I feel a lot braver now oh that's right I talked
to boss about you and he said to bring you to him an order from brass can't be
refused move it on those like fun okay I need us one of those shrines this one
here somewhere right he said earlier you would play a game full of only divine
beasts that's basically every other Zelda game yeah somehow different is that
true uh I need where's a there shrine here it's right in every town right was
the boss have to say side side on the main dude's house okay you really are
something I can't believe you conquered Rudania telling me impressed but good
graves you have to do it just when my back pain went away I was already in
go now you may look like I was just vivid about my back pain oh and I'm also
happy to see you know Bo finally got his act together yeah I know that's you're
doing as well but enough back padding and other such nonsense take a look at
this calm down it's returned to his peaceful ways now we can get back to
digging for ore around Death Mountain all right still gonna thank you wait why
did I did I do I get an item there's some treasure in my house actually get
stuff all right it's a sharp blade yep weapon over as a Hylian you probably
already know apparently a hundred years ago the Hylian champion had a legendary
blade the sword that seals what would they say the sword sleeps in a forest I
already saw it I have already found it 13 hearts right what's my treasure
boulder breaker that thing's huge nice boulder breaker very cool all right let
me not use that the next like 12 hours of gameplay you know I think I you know
I thought about this joke and I'm not gonna do it because I think it would
really piss everybody off I've been really thinking contemplating this if I
should do this or not but I'm not gonna do it so you can just laugh at it now
all these weapons that I've been hoarding for the longest time and I'm
just never gonna use them I was thinking of when I get to Ganon at the end of the
game just all throw every single one of them at him and break them all just like
one two three and just see what people do I but I know I feel like I could
break I feel like I could fuck up the whole game I'm actually concerned to do
that but just know if you see me do that that's like the like the laugh out loud
thing that I was planning because I'm never gonna use these that's like you
know you always hold on to your shit the Resident Evil bullshit where you get the
rocket launcher half way through the game you don't shoot it once you have
like eight rounds for it and then you just shoot the fucking tyrant eight
times with the rocket launcher and then watch the credits roll all right so look
at the shrine over here there is all right should I do hearts or stamina what
do I have one two three ten hearts I could get to ten hearts yeah that's
probably safe almost at a second row right it's ten and ten and ten if you're
wearing pants which is unlikely can we have an outfit tour I got pants on I'm
not gonna give you an outfit tour okay cool so that's that and that's where I'm
probably gonna end the stream I'm gonna go take another dose of medicine relax
I'm glad I was able to stream today though cuz I don't I feel like I've been
like away from my personal broadcast for a little while and I really did not when
I got COVID a few days ago it was just like fuck I hadn't streamed like a week
before that I took a long break in October so I really want to participate
but yeah he's radioactive no I'm fine we get an outfit tour here's your outfit
tour there but yeah tomorrow the plan is now again I have to make sure that I if
I wake up and I'm really screwed up VR is gonna have to move a day but the plan
is sus guy rebrand tomorrow and we're gonna play among us VR I think I've
already talked to a few people obviously Vinny was interested I think Charlie was
interested too in playing and his group there that we might say hello to them
for a little bit I might just bounce around whoever's playing it right I might
just like I don't want to be annoying though because that scream is good is
essentially one just huge joke to me right cuz I mean the whole you'll see
tomorrow but wherever I can bounce around as the fucking sus guy scream
that's where I'm gonna go we'll see yeah I'm sure there's a lot of people that
are gonna be playing it this thing with among us you need like you need like 30
people right you need like 20 people to play it so I have to I'm gonna have to
just jump in a random lobbies or play it with like a group like um like like I
said like Charlie and some of those were interested so but I need to be
better and if I'm gonna be in VR I need to take the time now to go just chill
and just put my head down keep an eye on the sauce if for some reason it's all
fucked up for some reason I'm do you understand the core gameplay of among
us I have no idea here's what I know I know that you have to pretend to do jobs
and if you're well you have to do jobs but if you're the imposter you have to
pretend to do them too and kill people while you're pretending to do stuff I've
never played among us before I don't even understand how it works all I know
is that oh man I saw this guy in admin that's the only thing I said emergency
meeting I don't even know what that means I don't know what that means it
just means like hey call in a meeting to determine who killed who I'm just gonna
the first lobby I'm in dude I'm pressing the button fucking immediately
and then I'm gonna turn and like run and cartoon break through my fucking drywall
Bugs Bunny style and then uninstall the game this should I should have a big
button I got there I have a COVID and I got one day to prepare this so I don't
know I don't think so I don't think I can even have a huge button in the
middle of my room when I'm playing it that would be so funny though if there's
just a huge red button and I have to go to press it I don't even know where it
is we'll see what I can come up with in the next 12 hours my eight-year-old
brother saw you on my screen and said oh my god that's the sus guy by the way
I'm gonna tell you right now tomorrow is gonna be an incredibly like G rated
stream I'm not gonna say any swears and I'm the sus guy you know I mean it's a
we're going we're going to break number records tomorrow tomorrow is you better
be prepared I'm trying to break every record on the channel tomorrow it's all
gonna be like freaking it's gonna be like whoa like yikes you know I mean I
gotta be very careful what time tomorrow I have no idea at some point
tomorrow afternoon I would imagine people are gonna be so pissed but not
really but I don't know I think it's funny so I'm doing it but you'll just
see this is gonna be shit all over the screen it's gonna be fucking unbearable
I'll probably turn it off like halfway through I don't know we'll see it's
gonna be unbearable there's gonna be like I don't know you'll see it's gonna
be it's gonna be annoying but it should be fun it's gonna be your worst dream
ever tomorrow it depends on what you determine that to be if I'm honest you
really gonna think it's the worst dream I've ever done or you're gonna think
it's your favorite stream of the whole year it depends stream roblox after it
it's gonna suck delay it to Saturday I mean I gotta play it at the launch if
I'm gonna do this it's has to happen tomorrow among us VR launch everyone's
so hyped about it this is if there's one day to do it it's tomorrow so I'm gonna
get VR set up troubleshoot it cuz you know it's gonna take like six hours get
some day quill in me tomorrow stream I'm gonna I don't know what to expect
tomorrow because having kovat and playing VR might be a recipe for disaster
but this joke has to happen so I'm streaming for at least an hour you know
what I mean I'm streaming for at least like a couple of games so I'll see you
tomorrow take care of yourselves thanks everybody for watching thanks for the
raid Vinnie and thanks Vinnie for playing too he's a good support today
because I wanted I also wanted to talk about the stream tomorrow and I wanted
to hang out too we were just in the middle of a conversation I was like hey
um what are you doing right now he's like um nothing really I'm getting ready
to make some dinner though in a little bit Mike can you like play Splatoon
with me he was a good sport I appreciate it but yeah I'll see you
guys tomorrow we'll jump around probably a few different lobbies or whoever wants
to tolerate us right because I really don't know how to play and we'll go from
there so have a good night call your mother have a good rest of your evening
and I will see some take it easy everybody