I love this comment, what he said.
LOL, he's streaming the entirety of Columbo on his other channel.
Why do you know what Columbo is?
Why do you know what that is?
Do they still play Columbo on like TBS for like 8 hours a day?
Do they still do that?
I want to know what the royalties and kind of syndication rights that the Columbo producers have.
Because Columbo has been I think syndicated and on more networks than Seinfeld and Friends combined.
I think there's like a 20% chance that if you change through television channels, you'll land on Columbo.
It's still like that. I did not know that.
How are you? Good to see you.
Things are going well. Give me one sec.
Oh, I thought I muted the mic.
Holy shit, why did the mic not mute?
That button doesn't work.
I just like moved my microphone to be closer to my face and I thought I muted it.
I usually do. I usually catch that.
But this button doesn't work.
I'm really sorry. That should not have happened.
I'm doing pretty good. I'm doing good.
Let me just make a tweet.
Ailee streamer?
He said, well, why are you 6 hours late?
Well, here's the thing.
Yesterday, I was supposed to stream at what?
Four o'clock yesterday?
But what happened was I ended up playing.
I delayed the stream by like three or four hours and then played with Ludwig, Charlie and Connor.
And then the stream that was supposed to happen yesterday is happening just today.
I mean, whatever. Oops, wrong Discord.
Whatever.
I'm tweeting. I'm tweeting. I'm tweeting. Just wait.
I'm tweeting.
Oops, wrong Discord.
I got the ID wrong.
It's whatever.
Was that even that bad?
OK, the joke wasn't bad. It was the execution.
That was the problem.
I had great joke writers yesterday.
It's just I, as the actor, screwed it up.
Right?
I'm also the writer too, so don't get mad.
That was a good one.
It was so bad. It was embarrassing.
Was it really though? I don't think so.
Pre-written stream.
I told you guys this, but I have on my third monitor over here.
You notice how sometimes I kind of look over and I'm not looking over at you guys?
Like the chat room. I'm looking at the other monitor.
I have about six to seven thousand jokes that I have written out as one sentence.
Kind of like little references from when I was a kid or whatever.
Just here.
And I just look over and I pick one.
And I just say it.
It's a really, really good tip if you're trying to stream to an audience.
It's like I have six or seven thousand, kind of one sentence.
Like when aliens show up.
That kind of shit, right?
That's like a sentence here.
If I hit control F, find D, and I type Duncan.
It's two or three hundred of these lines here.
It's like Duncan, Duncan, Duncan, Duncan, Duncan, Duncan, Duncan, Duncan, Duncan.
So it's like pretty much any scenario.
I can just do it.
It's kind of like an encyclopedia.
You guys ready to play MS-DOS?
All these cutaway gags.
You should do a naked joke.
Well, a naked joke turns into a banned joke.
I just turn on the full face cam.
And just, I just am naked and I just point at the camera and go.
Got ya!
And then like the not like this image shows up.
And my stream's just gone.
How is that a joke?
Oh ha, that would be funny.
It's with you guys.
Alright, so we're gonna play MS-DOS.
It's returning.
It's been a long time since I've played it.
The last MS-DOS stream I believe was probably like two years ago.
It's been a very long time.
It's been like at least a year or two.
I used to do this once a week.
Because there are probably a thousand plus MS-DOS pieces of software.
So we're gonna play.
This is how we're gonna do it.
The first one is gonna be a big fan favorite I think.
One of the most requested DOS games that I've received since saying I was gonna go back to this.
No, not Wolfenstein.
Nope.
No, we're talking about Jump Start Kindergarten.
That's the one that's been requested a lot.
I was told that the music in this game is the only reason to play it.
But we're gonna find out what that means.
Finally, a game fitting for chat.
I wonder how excited...
Okay, this is...
If you guys resident sleeper this game, I'm gonna be real pissed.
I'm gonna be very unhappy if this is like,
Ah dude, next, hurry up.
Everybody pretend Pogs until the thing that they pretend Pogging actually shows up.
I've learned this over the years.
I, you know, I get Pog-lit all the time.
You guys are just Pog-lighting me a lot.
Oh my god, you didn't...
No, dude, you gotta do Pog.
Pogchamp, oh my god, Pog.
He's gonna do it.
And then I do it.
This fucking sucks, dude.
Fucking do something else.
I would rather you play Picross, dude.
Get the fuck out of here.
Fucking turn your stream off.
Alright, here we go.
Jump Start Kindergarten number one is the first one we're gonna do.
Let's do it.
You guys ready?
Are you?
I know.
Alright, it's so far so good.
That we're at school.
This is the song.
This is the song here?
This is crazy.
I love the tuba.
What about the garden?
Can I go to the garden?
Everything is clickable.
This was huge back in the fucking forties.
Everything was clickable.
Yup, you didn't...
Oh, Gerber, you can't click on the tree and have oranges spawn.
What are you, fucking dumb?
Whoa!
I need to do these streams more often.
This is really easy content.
Do you guys see?
Oh, they're on a swing.
Oh, and he's not getting pog-lighted.
No, I'm not this time.
Alright, let's go.
Let's get it.
There's a note.
What does the note say?
Type each letter of your name on the keyboard.
Click on the doorknob when you're done.
That's great.
I bet you it's the same person that did every single voice in the whole game.
You want to talk about, like, compassionate game devs?
This is the programmer.
This is the voice actor.
This is the guy that made all the puzzles.
One man show, truly.
Um, Anthony.
Good afternoon.
Hey.
I'm Mr. Hopsalot, your teacher.
What?
Click on anything you see or click on my ears for a surprise.
The teacher?
Click on my ears for a surprise.
Ready?
Let's try a puzzle.
What?
No.
I don't want to.
Let's learn about letter sounds.
Um.
Find the object that starts with the sound of W.
Iron.
Dirty.
Wrench.
Square.
Nail.
Xylophone.
Rectangle.
I.
It's wrench.
Wrench.
Find the object that starts with the sound of K.
Those pants are way too big, by the way.
Oh, screw.
Screw.
Kite.
Leaf.
Volleyball.
Brick.
Kite.
Find the object that starts with the sound of S.
Skate.
Find the object that starts with the sound of B.
I think it's a dolphin, guys.
Remember, guys, B is.
Bat.
Find the object that starts with the sound of R.
Rooster.
Find the object that starts with the sound of X.
X-ray.
This is worse than baby sensory videos?
Don't pog-light me.
Starts with the sound of Q.
Q.
Car.
Quarter.
Find the object that starts with the sound of O.
This is not a surprise.
This is just like work.
Owl.
Find the object that starts with the sound of Z.
Z.
Zipper.
There it is.
All right.
If he pulls this off, I'm going to lose it.
Great job.
Click on the puzzle.
Who is that?
Again.
No, I don't want to play again.
I want to do something else.
Let's learn about letters.
No, I want to get out of here.
I don't want to be here.
Find the box that has the letter H.
What?
No.
How do I leave?
Find the box that has the letter H.
How do I get out of here?
Click on the type of puzzle that you want to try.
Oh, I want to get out.
Arrow in the corner?
Okay.
Let's go.
Find the box that-
I don't want to do that.
I want to do this other stuff.
What does this thing do?
Is this a drawing game?
I hope it's a drawing game.
Listen carefully to the sentence I'm about to say.
Then choose the pictures on the chalkboard that go with the sentence.
Click on me to repeat the sentence.
Okay.
I don't know who is the teacher.
How am I supposed to know who the teacher is?
My teacher.
Couldn't these all be a teacher?
Say it again.
Okay.
My-
Who is the teacher?
The one with the glasses?
Was it played?
Well, this is stepping on a bug.
Who is the teacher?
The one with the glasses?
Was it played?
Well, this is stepping on a bug.
Is this it?
An ugly?
Who's ugly?
They're kind of all ugly.
It's going to be like the witch, right?
Is this a sheep?
Alright that was fun.
He hates this.
The music is fucking awesome.
hates this I like the light the music is fucking awesome next game not no you don't by the way
people that are coming in here and not following the rules by the way the rules are we have to
spend at least 20 to 30 minutes in each one of these games you you can't you can't just come
in here and break the rules that's not how it works purple table purple table i'm hold on i'm
the game what's in here popcorn popcorn yarn basket vase telephone
why why is there popcorn in the closet here all right people saying purple table is where the
game starts all right let's see oh yeah you have to find the piece that doesn't belong
before you can color the picture okay what piece doesn't belong glasses wow you did it
change the picture by clicking on any piece when you like the picture select a color is there a
blender filling it in okay let's i definitely want okay let me get let me get let me set the scene
here i don't like that one i like that i like that no it's got to be it makes sense it's got
to be the lobster yep okay i like this now what i didn't want to fucking do that the piece that
doesn't belong before you can color the picture what doesn't belong the dog fantastic all right i
want to color the picture change the picture by clicking on any piece when you like the picture
select a color and start filling it in that was like somebody that was like a someone put got
their hand in a mouse trap and they held it up to the camera screaming and their eyes were like
looking directly into the camera all right how about uh dark green about green cool dark blue
okay turtles are green like dark green
god damn it don't do it please don't do it don't do it it's gonna get clipped forever
dark blue yellow i don't know this is fun pink there's a log over there brown brown
turtle shell is like this turtle shell but how does the turtle shell look like
i'm gonna throw up why it's like brown right yeah
bruh
so
what do you do for a living uh i'd rather not say orange stingray stingray dark green dark blue
it's make it make clean water that's gonna be kind of oh that's kind of cool
stingrays are like aren't they kind of like uh what color is the stingray blue dark blue
light green all right there we go this is pretty fog jam do you really want to erase the whole
picture do you want to save this picture no what else can i do what can we watch a tv show a for
apple doesn't do the whole alphabet b for b all right we have to guess which what each one of
these is going to be let's see how accurate i am c or carrot c for car fuck you all right that's
zero out of one d for dog d for dog got it that's that's one out of two e for elephant
e for egg oh why would you put egg that's so stupid egg no elephant what kid thinks oh yeah egg
okay f f for fish f for fish g g for oh g is tricky goose g for goose g for giraffe i should
know it's gonna be giraffe h is gonna be house no house h for heart oh god damn it okay whatever
i i for iguana for ice cream fuck j jump j or jump no that's like a verb these are
all gonna be nouns what would j be jump jump j for jack in the box
k is gonna be kite k is gonna be kite k for kite yes of course it is here we go
i have to get a passing grade on this otherwise i fail the fucking first grade l for lion l for
lobster what lobster a kid does no no kindergartener knows what a lobster is m for
moo m for moon and then i get half credit for that one n for nice something like little kid neat
nice n for nest nose yeah nose of okay o is gonna be something like octopus watch it be it's gonna
be like oboe oh for octopus got it p is gonna be play or play no it's not gonna be prey it might
be prey this is like nine this is like 1982 like two it might be prey prey p for pump none of you
got it right you guys are saying parrot penguin no q for quartz what kid would know anything
starting with the letter q quartz q for queen fuck r for rhino rhinoceros run rhinoceros r for rock
rock s for snake every time guaranteed for soap d for time t for tic-tac-toe that's three tic-tac-toe
u umbrella u for umbrella thank you i'll take it v for i mean i've got i got x is guaranteed by the
way guaranteed v is violin v for vampire w for water or whale it's probably whale w for woodpecker
these are all so messed up okay if x is not xylophone i will okay if x is not xylophone
i will literally get like a like a bubble blower and like blow bubbles into like the camera x for
x-ray that's easy whatever y yo yo for yo yo thank you and z for zebra and that's it z for zebra
of course how is it not xylophone that makes no sense how many did i get all right what what's
happening over here you're reading a book what is this thing is that the number i want to see
what the numbers are there are there are rats here three sounds like the caveman thing one two three
two one two three it's the caveman voice thing you're not going to count 17 times right two
13 15 16 they skipped 14 i'm not clicking not clicking it it's this one let's learn no no no
wait i want to learn about that let's learn about letters no sizes find the box find the
find the box 30 minutes time is up yeah hold on we're almost done let's learn about
numbers no sizes and i'm done find the box that matches the number three i can't do that it's
your you said 30 i know but just i want to see one i'm curious let's learn about letters click
on the type of puzzles that you want to try go okay let's learn about sizes here find the biggest
pig biggest pig
find the smallest log this one's easy though smallest log find the smallest sock this one
smallest sock i love that more than anything and they don't nobody does it anymore because it's
like it sounds jarring smallest bear i made this joke a thousand times but i'm gonna do it again
i love when there's audio files that are recorded independently and are pumped in
and it's only said one way so you'd end up with scenarios where you'd have play in like a baseball
game or like a football game or something back like a video game back in the day and they might
even still do it i haven't played one in a while but if you were to pick like the toronto blue jays
versus the toronto blue jays they would go the game we have coming up here is the toronto blue
jays versus the toronto blue jays and i thought it was the funniest fucking thing i've ever heard
i thought it was the funniest goddamn thing i loved it i would always just play the same team
so i could hear it how big is the smallest bear smallest bear find the smallest frog
smallest what is this is lava find the biggest dog biggest dog they definitely still do that
find the biggest hippo what is this image behind here what is the scene is leaves and like grapes
find the bigger pig bigger pig what are we looking at find the smaller ant smaller ant
what is this is it grapes fantastic why is it covered in leaves click on the puzzle to play
again all right 30 minutes is up that was uh wait is there anything else i can see that was jump
start kindergarten let me just check make sure there's nothing else like hold on you tell me
i'm not gonna blast tunes here and we're about to move on you kidding me
even the bug is dancing see here's the real sad part about this the kids think this is dancing
that's been dead on the windowsill for like a week the vibrations of the loud music are moving
that around and we're telling these children it's dancing all right do they can i change the
oh it's the different songs this is kind of dangerous
this is kind of dangerous all right what give me something else what's what is this thing
hands why is it hands okay what about this one
what do the animals do i'm not bringing my kids here ever again
no yeah i don't know i don't i don't like this just give my kid a worksheet and like a coloring
book i don't want i don't want like animals to show up and do like songs and stuff i don't know i
all right now i changed my mind holy shit what the fuck you got what this guy got in a car accident
who is this person just stop stop you're spraying him in the face turn that hose off
holy shit this is fucked up we're just spraying this this guy in the face
okay i'm this is freaking me out i'm fucking out of here
this is freaking me out this is really weird right like something's weird uh let's go let's
leave all right let's get out click on the basket to play the harvesting game whoa really click on
the watering can to play the watering game all right this is cool how many plants i need then
you click on a plant to put it in my basket roses and cabbage when you think you have a weird
number group of click on my basket flowers you'll have to hurry though that gopher loves to eat my
plants i need six heads of lettuce ready set go one two four seven eight nine got it oh that's
too many oh let's play again i need seven four four heads of lettuce ready set i need four carrots
onions i need four carrots i need four onions four carrots one one four carrots how many do i need
you did it that's just the number i need i need four i need carrots oops i did it wrong
how many how many do you say one two four five six seven eight nine ten three four five seven
eighteen nine oh no the gopher ate up my garden oh yeah they're in your bag stupid what's the
watering game i like to make patterns see if you can guess the pattern of plants in my garden
pattern what do you mean pattern yeah this is all this is this is a bad idea can you guess
your carrots your carrots are going to cannibalize the roots of your cabbage
monster what do you mean pattern oh i don't get it the gopher
i wait oh you just have to do all right i thought i was supposed to guess what his whatever
what's he doing it's dinner time i imagine making this song and listening to it back
what i planted here except you have to this is i love this you have somebody to compose this
all right the next thing that's coming up is going to be a fucking dandelion you guessed it
oh sunflowers two sunflowers all right all right bro can you guess what i planted here
uh yeah one of these you guessed it been 30 minutes oh my god this is boring oh it's don't
have it i'm having fun okay i'm having a good time is there anything else i can do outside
oh yeah this is fucking weird i have a camera no i want to do the picnic all right what we got
cookies watch out there's so many wild animals you're easily entertained that's it's from like
1980 it's fun all right we'll do it we're moving on it's been 40 minutes you're right
okay i've had a great time in this one but we're gonna move on okay fine you're really gonna be
not happy about the second one those who that were not happy about that first one you're really
gonna not be happy about the second one in a similar way i will not spend 40 minutes in
this one i promise i promise dinosaur adventure rate them out of 10 okay what do i do so what
what do i do click here to read a dinosaur storybook play the name of sorus game play
the read a sorus game explore the world of dinosaurs or click to see movies about dinosaurs
i think we're gonna see the movies where the fuck is this footage from this is from a theme park
or something this is weird that's it this would scare the shit out of me when i was a kid because
this is real where is this from animatronic animals especially animatronic dinosaurs are
terrifying even to this day to this day going on that was that that like jurassic park ride with
the t-rex where you go down and the t-rex's huge animatronic head is just right there
that's something so unsettling about that even in my 30s i just i don't like it i do not like it
i'm very curious where this footage is from is that what a dinosaur sounds like
they're anisora i'll repeat we've already seen it all right what are the other activities
these are not animatronics what the hell are they then what are you talking about all right
how about a read a dinosaur storybook long long ago animals called dinosaurs lived on the earth
there were big ones small dry ones some flew in the sky
this is like this is like somebody's backyard this looks like pine trees back here this is
somebody's backyard that these were these these wouldn't exist they're like a regular ass pine
tree exists like a hundred million years ago grass didn't exist no but i mean like a like a regular
like backyard pine tree i did they with i don't think they existed it was like weird alien stuff
it was big like tropical plants but did they exist weren't they they have like the huge leaves
all the jurassic plants were like gigantic lettuce leaves i don't think they were just
like maple trees hanging out where did they go well we don't know but some people think comets
like sad quite a way to end the uh presentation all right namosaurus find the brontosaurus
easy brontosaurus long neck keep looking this is the brachiosaurus
that's bullshit because you can't see the whole body tyrannosaurus is this one
keep looking this is the this is t-rex that one you're right way too dank i'll turn it down
i don't want to find any of these anymore all right hold on what about this one oh shit okay
that hurts my head hold on a second so this one we have to we can go away pretty much anywhere we
want 2 000 wait all right let's see if there's any pine trees 100 million years ago brachiosaurus
what was like a million years ago i'm a genius million bc what about like do they have like
what do we know was here 2000 1922 to 1925 and we'll do a hundred million miles or something
100 miles oh pine tree lore yeah we gotta find out what the first pine tree was planted
there you go 100 million bc is that a but that's not a pine is it a pine tree pine trees some of
the earliest versions of trees pine trees came before but doesn't that seem odd though i can't
imagine like a tyrannosaurus rex just walking around a bunch of pine trees that feels weird
doesn't it don't you like imagine just like a like a baseball diamond near them too
like at some old like town park like this feels like a weird image like this is just oh yeah
they're just flying around like back there american education pine trees were the first types of no
it's not it's not na education it's na education and then 20 years to forget everything it's na
education and then on top of that whoa 20 years have gone by so i don't know that a pine tree
existed what was the first bug is what i want to know what was the first bug holy shit life how did
it happen okay in this illustration you can follow what might be the history of life on earth in the
sky you see the development of galaxies similar to the milky way there are the comets planets and
moons that formed in the solar system and the rays of our star the sun send us the energy that
life depends on in the ocean at the far left the molecules that were the original building blocks
of life are forming as you look to the right you can see the bacteria that were the first cells
of life followed by more sophisticated sea life amphibians were able to how they know this how do
you how do you fucking know any of this is real how do they know any of this you weren't there 150
billion years ago how do you know this this is the story about how what what fossils show us
how do you know that what's oxygen huh what's oxygen what is it what is oxygen what is it
oh it's molecules what's a molecule see got him somebody said bro i was there i know that is not
a okay i'm who is this oh it's charles darwin i've been playing way too many from software games
this just like looks like all the statues and all the games uh yeah like
200 250 years ago the first from software statue glint stone i'm just fucking around oh my god
guys i i know i i get it i'm not telling you i've been saying how do you know think about it wait
can we hear darwin talk i'm a genius uh soy darwin sir charles darwin the all-knowing all right let's
go to the next one i'm done all right coming up next is the uh 100 000 pyramid game show hopefully
it's not too loud because these tend to be horrible sounding yeah it is horrible sounding dude okay
hello this is your host welcome to 100 000 pyramid you have so much space down here press
any key to start play okay one player contest are you a beginner or an expert um i'm a beginner
into your name me you ready oh up in smoke around things associated with tobacco it are when ready
to guess the best clues for these words things associated with tobacco okay uh pipe what what's
going on um smoke what um cigarette i don't have a cigarette things associated with tobacco
oh plant who did they who did they survey for this um leaf it says nicotine that's not what
i'm supposed to write what else is associated with tobacco trade lungs what the fuck cigar
chew um that's what's it called dip spit gum chew um what's it called it's called tobacco it's
called something it's called something what's it called baseball yeah it's called dip right
cha chewing tobacco yeah this game is this isn't how this works chew um enter clue and hit return
what the fuck mouth spit chew gums eat teeth what does this have to do with tobacco
an auction uh bidding this has nothing to do with tobacco a pouch um change uh coins uh kangaroo
scent nose smell this is okay i virginia uh state plant tobacco uh weed a um um plant a uh garden
tree flower this what a dumb game uh dirt i didn't even press enter what are you doing
dirt guys i need help grow i did it okay how about uh lend me okay i get the game now lend me your
ears thunder lightning disco ball dance easy siren um police sir water beach uh board an engine car
hyena dog animal conquered rape what's it conquered flight plane airplane okay between
three lines oh seven eleven i don't know what that means a will death um not lawyer family money
state yeah dying dead die funeral i don't understand document i have no idea i misspelled
lawyer doesn't matter away whoa encyclopedia i horoscope um planets signs oh an ad tv television
an ad radio newspaper that's a good one really magazine there we go nice contract
sign this is probably lawyer a manual an agenda um planner nice a will all right this is the last
one it's not a way i can't do spaces will i don't know plan testament testament i spelled it wrong
testament what okay i peed first i'm gonna get that hundred thousand testament brakes car mat uh
shower uh floor crack wood um floor again sidewalk good good one wall do things people
step on or walk on you don't step on a wall concrete ground street i have to come back to
this one file pavement road dude path foundation asphalt herb what the hell do you else do you walk
on you don't walk on anything else you don't walk on glass who's walking on like a glass
floor what are you talking about patio ice cement the mound pitcher linoleum um flooring
platform step stand uh stand no stair stage platform oh um podium not gonna be mario mario
was not alive yet mario was not even born yet train station station actually might be it what
is this deck board i think this is over wood balcony this is the last one there's nothing else
shoes what oh that's right treadmill walk all right we only got two more two more that's it
things at a gas station okay mechanic um are my camp but that is a thing at a gas station a mechanic
yes a fix repair empty tank or shit gas gas tank give me a break pump how is it fuel meter
what else was empty at a gas station and wallet bottle red empty register no dude that's not it
tire gas bladder bathroom things at a gas station it's got to be like empty tank
empty fuel tank empty fuel can gas can fuel canister canister oil uh canister car yeah car
propane is there a propane tank in your car calories empty wallet empty fill oh my goodness
a gallon gas a gallon of liquid a gallon of um a gallon milk a gallon of uh tank a gallon
jug it's a service gallon gasoline measure there we go all right a battery power electricity
charge it was no electric cars back in the day here no there's no charging electric
battery for your car dead jump jumper cables jump uh replace start they're getting they're
getting trickier spark plug ocean wait why are you saying ocean cables oil those oil no a battery
charge a battery you use a battery you replace a battery replace acid voltage
what a crock is shit hood engine uh fluid um windshield wiper fluid under check check under
the hood repair drunk and the hood like boom pop like pop the hood um open oh shit we got it a
spare tire charge battery and knock this out right now things you sit on throne king fence bird uh
squirrel cat did i spell squirrel wrong squirrel how do you spell squirrel it's such a weird
fucking thing to write why is squirrel just not spelled like s like k w e r l just like squirrel
actually that would be weirder wouldn't it i'm honestly like a squirrel what the fuck is this
it should be squirrel like this squirrel it's a squirrel not a squeal it's a squirrel okay what's
on the fence it's a bird uh rabbit post you sit on fence what who sits on a fence mailbox
cat a politician you know okay squirrel it's not right yeah cat i garden pick it okay there it is
a tuffet what is a tuffet a tuffet is like boomer talk for some kind of chair or something right
what is it tuffet lap um i don't know uh sit on like santa a cat dad a kid i i don't know children
santa sit on somebody's lap grandma grandpa what is going on dog um like it's not gonna be dance
it's not gonna be dance blanket that's not why you don't sit on that santa i tried santa
oh fuck um i don't like uh i don't know i who the kids sit on like grandma's lap or something
who baby i don't what is this it's not gonna be dance pillow christmas
oh no no hurry race track cushion chair a parent mom what the fuck is this
oh yeah i tried race already what what is this what was the answer oh i can play them i can play
it what was the answer all right i can play for 25 grand things in uh what the actors the script
play a play a play a show a show a play a film what the hell is going on the script the movie the
storyline this four letters it's not movie plot show i did show book try just try movie movie
there's four spots not five let's just be clear these things are sprouts wild animals alive
freeze these things are nature okay don't believe the lies of the how many slots there are
it could be anything things in uh things in a food can't a cannibal meat vegetables chicken things
in a soup things in a recipe things in a meal things in a kitchen things in the things at uh
in a in a dinner things that are things in a bowl things on a plate things in a plate
cannibal's meal what is cannibals restaurant fridge what i can't delete this pantry a cannibal's
meal what does that mean diet food things in a pot what is cannibals hearts of the heart
these things are bugs uh animals shit oh well that was a hundred thousand dollar pyramid
up next is a game called uh ceo this is a full motion video game uh it has lots of
full motion cutscenes i have no idea what to expect all i know is it exists i think you have
to like buy and sell companies see how do you find these old games there are a ton a ton
of these on archive.org it's like thousands of them okay uh it's just loading give me one
sec no one said that some live action if any cutscenes are in them oh yeah almost ready
just loading up the good ones are on gog the bad ones are on archive.org oh we've seen some really
good ones on archive.org need to lower the timer to get more more to get through more of these ah
i don't really have a time load i'm just messing around all right this one's big damn this one's
like 400 megabytes games that big back then when did this come out 400 megabytes 1995
that seems huge for 1995 that's massive 3d movie maker came out in 1995 and i don't think that was
more than that was a big one too i think that was like 100 megabytes maybe less diablo 2 was
one gig it really was all right here we go what's my laundry routine i filled the bathtub with water
let's throw all the dirty clothes in there and just take a gigantic spoon and just like
and then i take it all out and put it outside and lay it on the ground in individual pieces
and it dries in like a day or so will you walk can i unask that question no you can't damn this
is a big game that's poorly optimized 92 how's my day it's going good you look really germa-esque
today didn't somebody say my nose was like a pickle yesterday i guess see it all right here
we go you ready let's go okay this looks uh in partnership with cnn oh no wait wait wait wait i
gotta turn it up it's in partnership with cnn i gotta we gotta get this right okay name me me
uh me uh me okay mr mr me host has accepted your log on aiv group access corporate
mandate simulation video messages waiting to wait imagine how fucking annoying this would be
okay play messages beginning transmission in three two one you have one new voicemail
cnn on the line all right cnn left me a voicemail i'm catherine sparks at the cnn center in atlanta
welcome to cnn online a plane crash near serievo may have killed dwight owen barn what the hard
driving ceo of the a4 group stock markets in paris london new york and tokyo reacted to the
news by driving down the value of a4 stock trading of a4 shares was halted in london and
this is my company as prices declined 18 percent in a matter of hours transacting printer on a
worldwide scale a4 has risen classified documents tokyo paris berlin rome london dominating such
diverse fields as silicon chip manufacturing telecommunications and agro technology our
latest i don't think you want to put those on your desktop the phone from betola hello steve
in 1974 marotta the japanese president of the a4 group disappeared from his private yacht in the
seas off bermuda this evening his successor dwight owen barnes is still missing his plane made its
last contact with the toronto control tower at about eight o'clock last night while flying over
the town of totovo 50 kilometers from the serbian border the scotchi government says it has no
information about the disappearance of the businessman's jet and has sent several rescue
teams to the area the extreme tension in the balkans together with the bad weather conditions
which have hit this mountain area for the last week is making the search extremely difficult
i wonder i want to see what's in like these classified files at first light okay nearly
25 years ago dwight owen barnes grasped control of the then modest 10 billion dollar a4 group
turn it into today's 100 billion dollar multinational conglomerate what do we do barnes
disappearance creates a vacuum in the executive ranks of one of the world's largest and most
visible what do we sell three former ceos have also departed in an equally abrupt and mysterious
fashion perhaps even more uncommon is the fact that within a short period a new ceo has been
named to head a four a complete unknown from outside the organization or from just watching
the news corporate entity for that matter then a4 usually follows a series of management reversals
resulting in international market shifts of global proportions out of which the company
cnn will monitor world financial markets and provide updates as more information becomes
why do i have access to this guy's computer via cnn online
video message is waiting there is still one here it comes starts playing cartoon network
it just goes like teen titans i'm gonna get another call another video so you would like
to sit in the chair of power well i'm going to give you that chance it's fucking like the jimmy
world has learned of my absence and may soon learn of my successor it amuses me to hear the
pundits speculating about the circumstances of our succession policy it gets some better lighting
your fucking office sucks at a4 we trust in the element of surprise imagine any other company
stepping outside their cozy network of corporate sycophants and placing a rank amateur at the top
so your plane didn't pay for his dividend from such timid corporate myopia is the factor of
complete predictability you see by the time our competitors clones root their way to the front
of the trough we can anticipate their every move we know every corporate report they've ever
published every guru they've ever quoted and everyone they've ever you see we got my son's
math homework book and we're gonna try to find out what how to do long division today
that's like a little that's like a fucking eighth grade notebook with fresh rot an individual who
possesses genetic instinct and vision to shock the competition that's how we stay on the cutting
edge so what am i supposed to do 25 years ago i was that individual he set this camera up he's
sitting here alone even i may have become too predictable so we've devised how many takes do
you think it took you who have taken the i'm just waiting for the fuck to address our initiative
fuck the following simulation three two one world of the a4 simulation he's probably fucked up a
thousand times you're ready to sit in this chair i will hand you the reins with my blessing as for
my mysterious disappearance a classic red herring and a bit of coincidental timing i find myself in
a position where's he gonna go i must drive down the value of a4 so one of our best hackers
recently uncovered a shark in the water in the form of the head of our agro genetics operation
he and his confederates have been this laptop into offshore holding companies to cloak the
fact that they've been amassing shares of a4 in preparations for an unfriendly takeover
that laptop is built into the deal with the euro bank group using these shares as collateral to
fund a final blitz which would do i'm getting up and getting a coffee in the middle of this
this is i can only two days to go the answer a poison pill i disappear the stock plummets
euro sleaze calls in the loan our raiders are seriously deluded in deep or misappropriations
owing an insurmountable debt to euro bank i can fast forward they realize it they'll be i don't
have access to a mouse on just two owns all of those offshore operations scorched earth
preemptive creative fatal would you have thought of it this was just one of the easier ones
welcome to the game all right what do i have to do okay entering simulation please wait okay
no i'm waiting for like either he didn't press the end recording button he's sitting there burping
and he's gonna be sitting there like welcome to the game okay that was a good one
the like i'm burping but i don't want anyone to know i'm burping they're like
i fucking hate that by the way all right new game where do you where do we want to go
how about right how about seattle what am i supposed to do no not excuse this interruption
have you seen today's paper no what is it what's in it no i haven't seen the paper what do you
want who will replace dwight owen barnes a question on everybody's mind it's gonna be me
our office is open at nine a.m. okay all right what about uh what about the bank our office is
open at nine what time is it right now i have 83 million dollars in debt how am i supposed
to do anything bro this game is fucked up turn the megahertz up all right stock market
we're going all in okay i want this game is not happy with this setup so wait i want to buy
big building nintendo goodbye nintendo okay how much does this cost i'm just gonna buy
i'm gonna buy 83 million dollars in nintendo it's based on my clicks by the way is how the
game is running okay wait what's happening what was what's going on why was it doing that oh all
right i want i want 10 million okay i want over again this is i can only do 99,000 shares
we're only being offered 1700 shares i want 99,000 what what the fuck all right buy this one then
fortunately this stock is no longer available for purchase okay how about a cola soda fortunately
this stock is no longer available why can i only buy like 2000 shares all right i'm out of here
i'm out i'm fucking out of here i don't even know how to leave how do i get out of here get
compact it's a long-term investment all right i'm bailing i'm bailing i'm bailing i'm bailing
as you see as i faked my own death so i could play porn music at you while you've bought
a thousand shares of these companies that don't exist like what the fuck was that
okay how about here's the next one i think this is gonna be popular
this is gonna be a popular one are you ready oh just i didn't i just microwaved my brain with
that sound all right all right all right all right turn it down all right tony and friends
in kellogg's land all right can i name all these people tony the tiger toucan sam the smack'em's
frog um poco who's this who's this i thought these two were aren't these competing brands
they did they have the same cereal i don't know who that is all right tony and friends in kellogg's
land these are still list and how do you start the game three games only three free games okay
oh shit let's go this is explaining the controls anybody know german how do i what does it say
read it out loud
on
whatever just walk and collect delicious crunchies sweetened cornflakes wow i got a hidden block
you were just speaking simlish oh there's vitamin b1 there are kaizo blocks how far does that go
can i jump on this thing's head whatever this is is there a sprint this is actually kind of fun
so what are the what are the bad guys in this game what is like a bad what is it like anti-cereal
bugs bugs love cereal don't they is that i wonder what the bosses are i don't know how much health
do i have all right i'm good they don't pay for the cereal vitamin a and those are vitamins right
they have to be i go to the house come on i can do it i can die i'm known for this uh you can't go
in the house do i play as the other characters vitamin bb oh i just got something over that was
this is actually pretty fun nice how do i leave enter control alt alt mario walk so the tiger
could run all right i got uh vitamins i want to know what the big alligator is it's like dragons
and shit in this game do i play only as tony hold on a minute i'll try give me one sec one second
i'm gonna try as hard as i can okay just give me one second see if i can let's see if i can pull
this off there they're great there and everyone knows that a healthy breakfast lets you play
soccer in every commercial they're great that was pretty good that was good he's in my room
ah yeah that was that was good what's wrong with that one i'm available percule the tiger
uh they're great okay is that spiked i landed on that spike you the giddy and off-near thing
but the cereal mascots did i just get hurt by the milk oh i'm invincible hold on i'm tony the tiger
the all-knowing do you have a clone of you that does all the multi wait a minute that person what
are you asking do you have a clone of you that does all the multiplayer streams you alone versus
you with other streamers is like dr jackal and mr hide i don't know okay let me ask you a question
when you like go over your friend's house do you how do you act so when like your friend's
mother or father comes up and is like oh hey son hey good to see you again if you're known to like
sing if you're a singer are you going to greet your friend's dad by being like hello mr stevenson
how are you today you'd be like what are you doing why would that happen i act differently
in different like groups because you know i you know i can be a weirdo in my own house but not
in other people's houses first analogy but i understand no you get it though right like
if i'm gonna if i'm like a weirdo in my own house if i like repeat like the thanos lines
over and over again that's my house i'm not gonna go repeat the thanos lines at like my friend's
house new character by the way can you jump higher the difference is your friends know you're
weird if i don't just like take over somebody's stream do you want to do you know how annoying i
would be am i dead if i fall this is water i don't know i sometimes i let it i looked up i act a
little weird but i don't want to sit there and like play a trumpet while we're like playing with
four or five people eventually someone's like hey can somebody shut the fucking trumpet off
because it's all i hear how do i get up there wait i'm in the wrong discord yeah yeah oh yeah
mm-hmm you want me to do that you want to do more of that okay it's thrown out
oh vitamin c you did push the discord joe pretty hard yeah i know oh fuck is tony immune to spikes
i don't understand you almost got thrown out last night i can't be the other two why not okay tony
is not immune to spikes i don't get it i can't be the other two no one's immune to the spikes how
do i do this you have to use tony's um i don't understand i'm kind of stuck down here he loses
i might i think i have to jump over it
okay
all right i want to i'm uh one more get out of here milk is invincibility right go go go go go go go
go hurry hurry hurry i'm invincible right now do i have to walk across while i'm invincible
no no way i don't think this is possible this guy sucks at this dog shit game sorry
all right from here i think i have to go up and around that's the only way this confirms you're
a furry what are you talking about man these are serial characters are serial characters furries
yeah right a serial character is a furry fuck i just whatever i can just damage boost it yes
they're talking animals don't we're not gonna have the argument again about like what is a
furry and what is a furry a werewolf is not a furry but we already went over that and i
will defend it i will defend it forever where no it is not a werewolf is not a furry no it's not
no it's not it's not animals okay standing on two animals that have human characteristics
is a furry okay snackum snackum sam whatever this guy's name is wearing a baseball cap and
eating standing upright and talks that's a furry a werewolf that like doesn't have fucking college
class that is like just a snarling beast that turns into this and is on all fours that is not
a furry that's a werewolf it's not a furry it's not furry adjacent no it's not it's an animal it's
a beast no it's not a furry it's a beast it's a beast not a furry like if you okay if my werewolf
character were to stand up on two feet and have glasses and like a school notebook and going like
this all right now i'm a furry but if i'm on all fours with like and i'm an animal and this i don't
have like a like a suit on i'm an beast i'm not a furry i wonder which way i gotta go oh maybe this
way oh okay there's a key over there that's not a weak argument no it's not if if i look outside
and there's a moon out there and i am a human and it's like oh not the no the moon and i go off
camera and i come up and i've got claws and i'm like snarling that's not like i'm not first this
is a tony the tiger omega coin by the way okay let's go over one more time one final time and
that's it on all fours snarling beast upright with a cigarette furry you get it okay good
that sounds like furry justification to me who cares someone said i do i got a question for you
two very important questions this is tricky is tom from tom and jerry a furry or a cat good luck
with that one okay all right is the dog that talks like this in all those cartoons the one
that's always looking after jerry is that a furry or is that a dog that can talk is this
spongebob a furry i don't know man i don't know not enough human characteristics okay
so garfield's not a furry garfield tom jerry excuse me that means hold on does that mean that
toucan sam is not a furry which one of these is a furry because this is just a this is a bird this
is a toucan this is a frog with a baseball hat on right i'm this is interesting they're standing
upright toucans stand upright interesting and he's not wearing clothes but he is he's not wearing
clothes he is is the levels are getting harder by the way tony's wearing a scarf how do we unlock
the other two characters this is bullshit oh my god no tony's not a furry he's a nudist he's an
animal oh look at that i don't know why i'm so into this one it's just like kind of easy and basic
and fun i want to see a boss though whoa okay you bounce on the clouds this game sucks eggs
you bounce on the clouds oh shit what the fuck is going on here next game yeah next game that's
stupid next game i'm done i'm done next game that's it that's it next one okay this one's
called strawberry magic what are you saying dude your niece is watching my niece is not watching
i'm not playing lego star wars this one's 400 megabytes what maybe i love this in the background
would play something else how come you're not playing lego star wars um i don't know all right
how about jeopardy jeopardy is a good one right oh this one's running out of batteries
would you like a new character um no what intestine two is jody because the three is dan
get ready to play jeopardy choose a category famous person plants christmas tradition furniture
family tree u.s. residents all right how about plants for 100 the underground part of the plant
that supports and holds it in its soil roots what the fuck are you talking about why i don't get to
guess what are the roots what the fuck that's bullshit i have to buzz in that's stupid a baby
sits in this during mealtime a crib no what are they sitting what is what was who is what is a
baby sits at a high chair what is a high chair all right jody let's go all right plants for 200
hard exterior covering found on trees bark what is bark smart i think i know i know a 32
all right uh plants for 300 plants grow in this direction when exposed to light
grow in this direction towards sunlight who is sunlight who was sunlight plants grow in this
direction to be exposed to light who is sunlight where who is where sunlight up what is who what
uh is upward what's it you lose all your points in jeopardy what the fuck what nobody else fucking
knows this no one else knows this towards the light as a when sands are when sands plants
when plants are exposed to sunlight they go towards sunlight the fuck are you talking about
okay uh christmas tradition or 400 oh what's happening a traditional christmas beverage made
of eggs milk and sugar that's eggnog what is going on what is eggnog what's happening
all the other games started playing shit hold on the other games are playing how do i mute this
oh god damn it hold on wait wait wait wait wait wait another game opened what the fuck
hit control m i i'm trying is there okay can we just you know when i figured out when i
learned hello boys and girls my name is strawberry magic you ask why easy magic because i was born in
magic land and strawberry well i really don't know why not everyone has a name that fits him
what you're probably asking what i'm doing here well in magic land where all the magic in the
world is made we work very hard making magic is not at all a simple task you know that and so
from time to time when i get tired i sneak out to the secret tunnel and come here for a rest
okay well what can do i tire so easily
me
strawberry was she confused that her robbery magic was she confused that her name was strawberry she's
like oh sometimes your name doesn't make any sense you're a strawberry it makes perfect sense
i can't explain why they call me strawberry oh that was a joke and while lazy strawberry fell
into a deep sleep under the tree a group of children sat in their classroom working on their
end of the year school party oh goodness and now i'll assign you your tasks bill you'll be the clown
oh that's fucking rude rude you'll be the dancer great you'll sing i just love to sing and anthony
you're the butcher you'll be a magician she doesn't want to be a magician was the only
one who was disappointed with the party was so sad this is fucking weird i would
he's a muggle i'm sorry i didn't meet himself oh my god what's the connection
between your being sad and the raindrops falling out of your eyes when children are sad tears
fall from their eyes and i'm sad because i have to put on a magician's show at the class party
and i don't know even one magic trick i'm strawberry magic i'm from magic land but
everybody works hard this gets elucidating through my secret tunnel so that i can citizens of magic
land in it maybe i can turn you into an exact copy to set your foreign turn him into like a
different like a banana or like a fucking kiwi or something magic magic one two three
make this creature same as me that's a very insecure password by the way that's the magic
magic to make him an exact copy of me he looks like a strawberry oh well i suppose i really do
look like a strawberry oh what happens if they can't tell the difference between us
this is under a rock in magic land everyone is a hard-working magician you will probably
have to work too okay oh i almost forgot take the suitcase with you this is where you'll put the
items you will collect what the fuck any problems you can call on me for help okay remember in
order to make magic you will have to collect three items if you want to return home close the
suitcase by clicking on the top part of the screen in the meantime i'll rest here good luck
wait when you rest here so where this is magic land magic land looks identical to real land
something's in the distance some i don't know what that is i don't know that could be like a
missile all right i don't know that was fucking scary it was like this thing like with like fire
behind it where should i go google maps put over here don't get run over oh wait is this magic land
what did you do to the vegetable there are two kinds of fruits and vegetables in magic land
one kind is for eating and the other kind is for magic the fruit for eating is grown in the natural
way but the magic fruit and vegetables growing abra the great magician's garden and they are
alive and intelligent creatures just like me do you think it was a bad idea to make it so the
things that we eat look identical to the magic creatures you think we would it would be make
the make the peanuts the magic things right but what did you do to the vegetable vendor
that was a food vegetable i scared the basket heads a little so the vendor had to stop selling
strawberries for menace you it's you again how dare you come near my stand but i have a surprising
what's magical about this i know strawberries on my stand where you can hide and frighten the
customers hey mr vegetable vendor i just brought a new shipment of fresh fruits and vegetables
come here and get them all you have to do is fill the customers orders and give them exactly what
they asked for hey man i got some fresh fruits and vegetables for you in fucking magic land
yeah hurry up i got a few more deliveries i got two deliveries in the bronx i got
fucking i gotta go i get a boston magic land is way out of my fucking way by the way
what is this please give me heads of lettuce five is it ashtray okay five heads of lettuce
those have not wanted melons no put them back what that's an apple that's green
where's the lettuce dude heads of garlic oh you're out of your mind folks excuse me ladies and
gentlemen folks you want five in the ashtray all right we'll put it over there four five
okay goodbye thank you very much i'm going why is he so heavy oh he's back please give me
cherries seven seven cherries where are they oh my god they all seven i get out of here thank
you very much i'm going so heavy they are but these aren't magic this is food i'm so confused
how many times i have to do this please give me peppers six this game is giving me brain
up where's peppers i don't want no no cucumbers fuck off peppers ears of what the fuck is an
aubergine aubergine where's pepper is it i don't have peppers that's a tomato this is carrot
i don't have peppers that's not a pepper what the fuck how many do you want
how many do you say you wanted how many uh peppers six all right get out now you can go
thank you very much i'm going it has to be it give me my like banjo kazooie puzzle piece
i see you've made some very nice sales i must have made a lot of money today what is what
where's the money do you mean to tell me that you sold the vegetables and didn't ask for money
i'm sorry sir you said to give the basket heads exactly what they asked for
and that's exactly what i did they came up every time and said give me so i gave them
now you listen to me a shrimp even when i begin to believe that strawberries can change
the sad truth blows up in my face what a fool i was to depend on a strawberry i won't talk to
the strawberries again until you give me back the money i gotta get money for this guy well
do you have money for me how much money how much does it cost let's go help let you take anything
after the closing down sir we arranged for him i think this is the funniest thing in the world
but seriously he's just having to like you it's a good idea for you to give him back the money
she's happy that we're fucking with this guy he won't let you take anything after the closing
down sir we arranged all right so i gotta get money i think this is the funniest thing in the
world but seriously i don't know how much money it was to like you it's a good idea for you to give
him back the money all right let's go i'll be back and give it back to the vendor it's three
dollars should i turn this up or is it already too loud and annoying for you looks like i need to
turn it up a little maybe a little bit right there should be good right there should be good
they drive cars here all right what about inside this house good day sir how can i help you
i don't know are you a banker they still haven't discovered who let the air out of the tires on
their police bikes it was you it was her are you prepared to help me of course it's a policeman's
job to help everyone who asks for our help look while i can't say that you're an outstanding
magician you're not like those in there have you lost something strawberry well i think i'm
i did Ernie Ernie voice you've always been a funny one how could you have lost the magic silly
how can you lose something you don't have this thing not even close it's not even close that's
true but i am looking for the magic i could only get my wish through this magic very good
what are they talking about right track you know you need the magic to have all your wishes come
true not like the prisoners there inside who don't think you need magic in order to get your
wishes they steal wishes that have come true from other magicians they're locked up in those cells
to make sure they don't harm anyone else but they're causing me to suffer i have to guard them and
i'm pretty tired of it i'd really like to get out for a break could you guard them oh you know why
i guard the prisoners this motherfucker right here just talked about how dangerous these prisoners
all right oh four-year-old i wouldn't it be good if i took a break while you watched a couple of
dangerous criminals that will probably fucking kill you why would i why would i want to do this
don't you help the poor fellow a little let him go out for a short break how do i do that
all right well go take a break i'll tell i got it i got this
a string of i wonder who it belongs to okay how do i say go ahead and take a break yes i'll help
strawberry please meet junior cop the student policeman he's new here and isn't familiar with
his job yet why are they leaving us alone look strawberry there is a prisoner in each cell
although they are being punished we don't want them to be sad so we allow them to meet visitors
whenever a yellow light goes on over a cell this means that visitors have arrived and you have to
open the cell door send junior cop there and press the button to open the door if you don't open the
cell door a red light will go on and a short time later it will start blinking if by then you don't
open the door the prisoner will burst out crying and refuse to come out what when the visit is
over a red light goes on over the door of the visitor's room and you must quickly
if you do not do this quickly the prisoners will escape and disappear as fast as you can bat an eye
why you can look at a clock to see how much more time you have left until the end of the mission
i missed all of that um so oh my god what do i do yellow light means junior cop go
let this open this guy's cell open it quick open it all right what happened
to do my job right during this shift i'll go back to the desk don't worry strawberry
i've already caught the escaped prisoner he's being led back to his cell at this very moment
be careful next time strawberry you just helped larry to strangle him if so go to the cell block
and by the way he always talks about strangling strawberries so be careful try harder next time
i don't understand what's going on here yes so what do i have to do explain it again yellow
light goes on over a cell this means that visitors have arrived and you have to open the door
send junior cop there and press the button to open the door
okay if you don't open the cell door a red light will go on and a short time later it
will start blinking if by then you don't open the door so what happened will burst out crying
and refuse to come out when the visit is over a red light goes on over the door of the visitor's
room and you must quickly send junior cop if you do not do this quickly the prisoners will escape
and disappear as fast as you can you need to escort them to the electric chair look at a
clock to see how much more time you have left until the end of the mission junior cop get over
there junior cop what are you doing junior okay now what the fuck do i do i don't get it what's
happening all right i got him that it the shift passed with no problem i got it no prisoners
cried or escaped i'll go back to the desk oh my god what the fuck strawberry very good you have
been a very good policeman want to see the magic here the magicless strawberry turns into a brave
policeman i now appoint you a policeman in magic land and here are your missions one the string of
pearls that belongs to a bretta the magician's daughter has been found take it back to her two
our brother magician's hat has been stolen we have an identikit picture of the thief
go to the school for beginner magicians and try to find him using this identikit picture
okay that's a crime sketch citizen all right what's on the crime sketch
don't agree to being a policeman you leave magic land everyone will think that i'm you
have to work hard like that poor policeman strawberry i have no choice i must go on
looking for the magician school that's exactly where i have to go anybody looking for this kid
yet right i mean hello strawberry there are no prisoners in the cells and my workday is just
one long break imagine being arrested by a preschooler the suspect is not here
i will open the identikit magician school what the fuck i want to see what it looks like
okay well we did this let's go okay so i think we probably go left or right here
we can go right can't go left let's go right it really is google street just a little guy
okay hi i'm as happy as happy can be i love a bretta and a bretta loves me
oh dear he's in love with her too uh so what do i know what i'm as happy as happy can be
i love a bretta and a bretta loves me a bretta oh dear he's in love with her too okay well i
i don't know the guy looks like he belongs in like a you got a strike in bowling and that
thing shows up like pushes the pins down or something that was weird uh all right this
game is pretty elaborate let's keep going straight ahead from a no what is this tunnel
where does it lead and what are you doing here are you hiding too because you don't want to work
back what's really strawberry not everyone is like you have you forgotten behind this door
there is a deep dark pit beyond that pit lives the beautiful firefly fairy did you know that
the firefly fairy can show you the magic within the magic well i transport everyone who wishes
to reach her if you want to fly on my back to the firefly fairy you must bring me a barrel of juicy
nectar of flowers i'm so hungry all right whatever i don't know you look i want to look at this i
feel like this is this guy here the door will open up if you insert the magic disc in here
okay all right we're gonna bring this guy uh nectar it looks like i can't get past the pit
how awful it's not i mean just bring the guy a bottle of nectar we can go we can leave
stop people on the street down here we got somebody going on here ronnie this is the place i hate most
of all they work very hard here did you know that everyone who didn't want to learn the secret of
the magic works here but strawberry i know that i must look for the magic i'll do anything even
hard work if i have to strawberry i knew you'd get here sooner or later after all all those who
didn't want to learn the secret of the magic ended up here and had to do very hard work why are we
having why i came here for exactly the opposite reason i want to find the magic and i'm ready to
work come into the construction area and wait for instructions you know what guys i don't think
magic exists i think they're full of shit oh no i don't have to do anything because i am magic
that art magic needs to do all the work what do you what what can you do for magic by the way
strawberry lounge in a chair and turn other people into strawberries how does that help us
it's other people roots get back to work stop questioning me what oh i what why are we doing
this what do i have to go useless magic and to talk about useless magic oh our magical abilities
turn people into people that we look like and they might get eaten by mistake please operate
that crane what the fuck are you talking about if you keep this up and refuse to work you won't get
very far what does he want me to do what did he say i was too busy being upset go back into the
construction area and see to it that the wall is painted properly where's the construction is only
partly painted or is not properly painted is washed clean and you have to start all over again
where is that though is this the that's a construction yard right here isn't it
that's what i'm trying to do wall that's not painted where is it if you keep this up and
refuse to work you won't get very far i have to go left oh left not down
on
strawberry go back into the construction area and see to it that the wall is painted properly
any wall that is only partly painted or is not properly painted is washed clean and you have to
start all over again i know okay go left instead of left what the hell is this what an interesting
place i wonder what kind of work they do here your attention please box boys get ready to paint
and form a line box boys you must jump into the pool of paint and fill up with the right color
after that march to the wall and splash the paint on the bricks strawberry you will have to change
the color in the pool so that the box boy that will jump into it will be filled with the right
color and splash it in the right order but box boys jump why are we doing this to these people
what color do they want what color do i need it to be what color do i need it to be red what color
does this have to be i don't understand what's happening red or i don't understand what's going
on you have to do red purple blue red does this make any sense yellow i don't get it what's
happening red i don't know i don't know what they're asking for does it matter they already
ruined it green now but is it just yellow green blue it's not like a pattern it's just solid now
we'll do blue i thought it was i had some kind of pattern or something you fucking idiot yeah
okay so it's it's i get it i get it i get it i get it i get it so that means i need two more
and then we gotta go purple after this one goes in
purple yeah purple purple purple purple purple purple purple one more purple and then red
okay so i i hopefully i can correct this new radiohead album is sick
saying this is the new radiohead album so then it's like i gotta change to yellow i'll get it
i'm incredibly invested in this game by the way we're not going anywhere for a little while
okay red red now back to yellow yep okay and then oh my god this is gonna take fucking forever
here is really hard we haven't painted the wall properly i'll come back here later
shit i'm here go do it do it strawberry go back into the construction area and see to it that
the wall is any wall that is only partly painted or is not properly painted is washed clean and
you have to start all over again okay i'll get it i'll get it right i'll go and continue painting
the wall please do all right red i must finish painting the wall i can't torture it you're fine
real live call the box boys oh the box boys box boys jump all right we got it this time
just turn your volume down for like 10 minutes it's one two three four five so five uh red paints
and then yellow so that's i need one more red and yellow bingo
okay now blue
let's go you're making sleeper agents wake up with this song
it's not a big deal it's just a background song okay one two three four one two and one more
and we're going purple dunk in there this game sucks excuse me you're talking about strawberry
magic being a bad game that's kind of uh that's you yeah you've just annoyed me here's what you've
done all right wait one two one more and then green and then that's it all right we're almost
out are you still playing this i'm invested are you not curious about this
i'll turn it down if it's too annoying i'm very curious yeah okay that's it that's it
that's it stop painting that's it that's it strawberry do you think that this wall
looks like it's painted properly eight rows of bricks are painted the right colors
i swear to god this guy gives me like three dollars oh yeah there you go here's your three
dollars okay so that's it very you managed the wall painting job very well the painting crew
was happy to work with you i must say you have made some real progress here is a barrel of
nectar from the finest flowers it's yours this is your pay for your work today oh thank you mr
foreman and good thanks for the thanks to what amounts to a a individual bag of gushers i got
the nectar though that's for the bird yeah so we we all right we know we gotta go that way but let's
go left we haven't gone over here yet i think this is the magic school hey where are you going
you can't go any further this is the school for magicians and only people who have magic wands
are allowed in if you have a wand show me if not don't bother me pity i could learn some magic at
this school i'll try and get a wand nice walk in be able to enter the school for magicians
without the god's permission all right well it looks like we're gonna take the nectar
all right let's go i could learn some magic at this school i'll try and get the next game for
the love of not we're almost done you understand like we're i'm beating this one we're so close
we have to go to the magic school then we have to go i'm playing this still so this is how it's
working i have an exam but this is more important uh your schooling is more important i'll be here
okay here you go here's the nectar here's the barrel of nectar have some and then we'll fly
over the deep dark pit the barrel of nectar is closed with a lid i can't get to the nectar
here huh you give me a botched barrel of nectar it looks like i can't get past the pit
how awful that's a lot of nectar by the way i thought it was small
the thing's huge that actually might be worth like that might actually be worth like 100 bucks
is it nectar or is it lsd all right there's another way we can go all right we go we went
yeah we gotta go straight here this game is very expansive this game is a big game
let's go over here all right i'm thinking just right here the gate is closed and the breeder
bird is guarding the garden reader bird what i'm sorry i can't come over and open the gate for you
i have to mine the eggs until they hatch in pairs are those people who's hatching
the little sweetheart sleeping so peacefully inside the eggs they'll soon become adorable little
chicks off-key piano is scary do not disturb quiet please look strawberry inside my eggs
he like grabbed that nose and switched it like this i really tried hard to plan things so that
there will be two of each color i tried to peek inside the eggs but shelly who guards the eggs
won't let me disturb them that's right she always comes looking and disturbs them the chicks need
their rest she opens the egg and immediately forgets the chicks color what does a matching game i really
do want to know if every chick has a partner when you do find a pair their shells would get colored
in the same color that way i won't be worried it's a matching game this music this person's
fucking going crazy on piano okay red green blue dark blue blue okay here we go yellow
no red red okay blue yellow and yellow is this one right no it's this one
okay here he goes okay green okay wonderful i have exactly one pair of every kind
now i'm ready to open the gate this game was probably the elden ring of its time
i'm not so sure about that all right so what's in here wait i'll be right there to open the gate
but i want to like i want a detailed animated scene of her nose
wrapping around like all broken and shit and turning the handle with her nose
oh my god it actually did it oh fuck this is that a magician excuse me excuse me strawberry
just a moment are you going into the garden by any chance yes planning on it hey who are you
i finally met someone among all these strange creatures who talk like one thing and look like
something else who's a magician a real magician creatures who look like one thing and talk like
those are clothes of strawberry but you don't look exactly like you sound
i know i look so funny only because i had to find the magic what is happening what's so funny
about looking like me you look like that because you are looking for the magic i'll let you in on
a secret you and your friends in this weird place really do need first-rate magic so it's not to
look the way you look you're a magician aren't you that's right i'm a magician that's my profession
i learned hundreds of tricks and illusions and when i appear on the stage with my rabbit
everyone thinks that everything is real but between you and me everything is an illusion you know the
hand is quicker than the eye but i'm telling this only to you because you belong to this world and
you'll never get to my world and you won't be able to reveal this secret to my audiences
you mean you don't have any real magic at all that's right it's all illusions look time is
passing quickly and i have to appear in the circus in a little while my rabbit decided that he
doesn't want to appear with me anymore and be part of my act with its false magic tricks no magic he
ran away to this place he says that the real magic is only here i have to find him and get
how is everybody getting here if i see a rabbit i'll catch it and bring it back to you how did
he get here how did this guy get here we had to get shrunken down into a fruit and then go under
a weird rock how did you get here i have no idea strawberry don't forget if you see my rabbit tell
him to come back to me if i see a rabbit i'll catch it and bring it back to you this guy just
appeared and dropped a lore bomb this is the rabbit's restaurant the rabbits come here to
eat carrots if you wait here you might be able to catch the rabbit the restaurant for rabbits
the magician's rabbit is very fussy about what he eats he's used to eating well and only eats in
five star restaurants what if you want him to come here you must provide the best service to your
rabbit customers when a rabbit comes in you must serve him his carrots immediately that way your
restaurant will be awarded more stars and the magicians rabbit will appear when he gets here
serve him some carrots and grab him remember you can take only up to three carrots on your tray
each time diner dash now okay there's a rabbit i gotta serve very quickly what table are you going
to here i think hurry the fuck up why are you going so slow to work they're leaving bad reviews
oh they're doing this for us i hate that voice hurry up and get over here all right i got four
stars now the magician's rabbit only comes to five star restaurants oh you love the bad review
i'm coming i'm coming i'm coming jesus come on man i gotta piss so bad all right where's the
magician's rabbit which one is the magician's rabbit is there a way to tell dick hurry up
where's the how do i know which is the yeah i don't know what to do
are they all the magicians rabbit how do you tell who's who god dude
i don't know wait she's trying to say something there he is there he is there he is all right
we gotta grab this guy cute little rabbit someone is desperately looking for you
he misses you where's the magician i miss him too and i want to go home come along little bit
with the magician all right now maybe i'll get some money strawberry don't forget if you see
my rabbit tell him to come back to me that sounds like somebody this guy sound like rabbit strawberry
i'm so grateful to you for finding my rabbit listen i have to ask another small favor
is this while i was looking for my rabbit i scattered lots of candy along the paths
i wanted the rabbit to find him and understand that i was looking for the warden from super
drill fortunately someone gobbled them all up he got stiff from eating so much so please
take this medicine powder and sprinkle it on him so that he can move again medicine powder
oh here you are i'm so happy i'll never run away again let's go home
i didn't know the rabbit was that big all right sprinkle the medicine powder
who's that for medicine powder such girls are coming out of there
whoo it's a wonderful smell look at how many cakes are all right is this
hello strawberry hungry hey poor little rascal when will you understand that you have to help out a
little you simply can't just walk around snatching things from here and there you'd really like some
cake wouldn't you well you'll give me some help and i'll give you a very good cake oh a very good cake
do what he asks his cakes are delicious all right i gotta pee cake that was ordered especially for
the chickpeas they will break out of the eggs today now this is their first birthday i must
prepare a cake in their honor exactly according to the frame drawing can you help me bring the
layers of cake having the right shape and color that cake is dog shit you don't have no frosting
no decorations it's just three cake tops the cake sucks i gotta pay i'll be back
okay i am back as long as it take you to pee um well i didn't just pee i gotta i refilled my
water slash green tea slash matcha slash drink i refilled my green water that's right he took a
bong hit no no cbd i'm not i haven't been high on stream for almost a year and a half
ever since the analog clock incident i have been like no not i can't do that anymore i was just
like i can't do it i cannot stream and be high i can't i was walking in circles and stuff and
i couldn't read analog clocks no that's that can't happen okay let's get back to it uh we're
continuing strawberry magic i feel like we're we're getting probably close to the conclusion
if i were to take a wild guess i'd say we're getting close this is a 60 hour game i i highly
doubt that 60 hour games could not exist on the dos here we are that's a good volume let's bring
it back all right what we need to make the cake right so it's just one of these that's not what
i have you're talking about oh what a nice cake layers of cake exactly according to the drawing
it's up there already on the table fucking bozo it's right there this is the drawing of the cake
that was ordered that so who handed in strawberry layers of cake exactly according to the drawing
what do you want it's right in front of this guy huh that's wrong what how is that wrong
are you shitting me oh god damn it what the hell is going on here i have to reset how i gotta reset
strawberry i thought you wanted some cake what is it what is it
i talk about high that what the fuck finish putting the cake together
how do i get rid of this am i actually soft-locked how do i get rid of this
this is the cake that was it with the curtain shit how do i restart how do i start to make one next
to it i can't i can't make it no layers of cake exactly according to the drawing and put them on
the table or i get off i have to look i can't try putting the top layer back i don't need this part
of the cake thank you to that person in chat i don't need this part of the cake all right so
get rid of this i don't need this part all right so what is this what the hell does this even look
like like this that is strawberry please bring me layers of cake exactly according to the drawing
and put them on the table there are sauces in the top left this part of the cake smaller
pick it up just grab it and put it back put it strawberry cake strawberry put it back
this part of the cake it's the smallest one i don't need this part of the cake
i mean like this one here and then the teeny little one that doesn't look right that looks
wrong doesn't it very good strawberry this is exactly the cake that was ordered
go into the decoration room and decorate them exactly according to the drawing when you're
finished you'll get some cake okay r1 r1 r1 r1 r1 r1 r1 hey oh strawberry so okay that's what
how it's going to be then that's what we're going to do fighting you must decorate the cake
exactly according to the picture kind of botched it but that's kind of what it sounds like inside
the boxes i'm very pleased that you're helping me fight you have lots of work to do pulls out great
sword yeah it's like r1 i would hey no what are you strawberry all right then it's time to have a
battle i just decorated the exact same way you got it what was that is it a baby the cake exactly
according to the picture i'll show it to the baker we've managed to make a wonderful cake
for the chickpeas i can't wait for them to break out of their shells here take the cake i promised
you enjoy every bite i got it i got some items please end this oh we're at the final three or
four areas this is like the final three spots i have no idea where this is but i hope they want
a cake and packages packages and boxes scurry scurry scurry i deliver in a hurry hello sir
what are you doing strawberry strawberry you really are something else you're so innocent
all of a sudden hello sir what are you doing what are you doing here have you forgotten that my last
delivery is being held up on account of you you rummaged around in all the packages so please go
somewhere else if you show up here again i'll put you in our box and i'll send you to the farthest
i know the farthest place he knows of is that warehouse over there all day long all he does
is work put you in a box strawberry honestly be a little more serious you promised that if i came
here you would help me discover the secret of the magic in the meantime all i do is work instead of
you and you sit there laughing at every yeah what's up with this not laughing i just don't
understand i've always been nice to everyone and i always wanted to play he did not dedicate to the
rhyming everywhere and you you've just arrived and everybody loves you that's right it's because i
help everyone not like you oh mr potter sir i like that like misbehaved yesterday but today
i've come to help to help what happened today that made you decide that i decided to look for
the magic and i'm ready to do anything to find it go socks now you're talking like a resident of
magic land so listen very carefully the cost of shipping these packages is very high
so we have to stuff as many of them into crates as we can without leaving any empty space the
packages coming off the conveyor belt are of different sizes so it is possible to fit every
box into an empty space until the crate is completely full you can start now
now okay fill the box with our stuff these packages have been sorted and are ready to be
shipped later on don't touch them airline find out this is just bald to emphasize her i think it's
fine oh oh oh oh oh this fucking game is fucking stupid what is the moment where i was a moment ago
dad you fucking uh what was it it's games with fucking kids i don't give a fuck i'm playing a
fucking kids game and you guys are talking shit in the fucking chat yeah okay pickle nose pickle
nose fucking say that pickle nose the fuck up what do i actually have to do i didn't pay any
attention to this i didn't pay any attention go to the next game no i i've what did i think what
do you want me to do try and we still have lots of packages to pack pack up packages
this is where the packages for shipment come out okay so when where do they these packages
have been sorted and are ready to be shipped later on don't touch them where what do i have to do
oh whoa this is where the packages for shipment come out so how does it start a shipment let's go
this is where the packages for shipment come out the left package
where this this one looks like i can touch it right packages have been sorted and are ready
to be shipped later on the box near the shipping window over here these packages have been sorted
and are ready to be oh it's so low poly i couldn't even see it i see it oh god this is heavy i'm doing
this right it how many packages do i have to put in here what the hell this is not worse than the
day dallas encounter get out of here no way not even remotely close no fucking way no way oh my
god how dare you no you know how i know that because when i was playing the dallas encounter
i looked over a chat which i was trying to i was ignoring chat for a lot of that stream
because when i looked over it was a sea a sea of people begging me begging me to stop playing it
it was like begging like dude fucking stop please please do anything else man just do
like tier list or something it was seriously every single comment every single one and i
ignored it oh it was it was ridiculous this is so awful i don't want to hopefully i'm doing this
right i don't want to do this again oh my god it was so bad this minigame is bad i will give you
that oh my god can we please thank you the crate is full and ready for shipment worst
dream ever day dallas encounter real magician strawberry here take this coin and buy something
tasty for yourself you really i don't know what the worst dream i've ever done is i could probably
give my opinion i think that's money we can bring to the fruit vendor i think the worst dream that
i actually really have ever done is that card one goodbye but like unlock card like dungeon one
that was unbelievably bad unbelievable that was the worst thing i've ever done the my camera was
too low quality you couldn't even read the cards you physically couldn't even see what was going
on i thought that was gonna be way more fun fortnight tournament was not fortnight was fun
that was like fun because like the group we were having a good time yeah i didn't play very well
but i mean that was a fun stream for me this funny house is the artist's home he copies pictures all
day long okay so this is the painting you tried it was just fun strawberry this artist doesn't
look very busy at all that's what you think ronnie this whole town looks like it's asleep but you'll
soon see that this guy's a little freaked out that we walked in his house without asking
oh mr clover hello strawberry walking around doing nothing as usual huh oh no sir what are you
painting two days from now we are going to open an exhibition of the paintings of the greatest
artists in the world there's one picture that i could not get for the exhibition so i have to
make an exact copy of it i've already drawn it but my eyes are tired and i am not sure that the copy
is exactly like the original i have to copy his copy look and see if i've forgotten some
all right i'll copy your copy maybe i can help you you i find that how to believe
since when do you want to do anything oh no you're doing okay
okay
oh you really did a pretty botched job on this one clovey look at the pictures in front of you
the frame picture is the original the bone on the easel is the copy do you see any details in the
original that don't appear in the copy a lot of things actually there are differences you're
fucked up you're fucked up why are you helping this guy make forgeries
i'm so happy that you helped me with this picture because it might have been very
embarrassing if someone discovered that my copy was not perfect now you're invited into my secret
library you already know that not everyone is allowed in what um i don't know if i want
to go into the secret library face lots of books in the library i'm looking for the book with the
secret maybe if i find it i'll be able to do some magic magic's not real the guy just told you that
wow this artist really hides a lot of books here i have always asked to be allowed to come in here
and look at mr clovey's books and he never let me do it you're really lucky to be in there
okay so we have to find the book if i want to find the secret book i need to get the library
oh my god the art of copying pictures i need to get the code if i want to find the secret book
i need to get the library code will he give it to me but sir you have a very impressive
collection of books he's still playing this yeah to be among the fortunate people who have visited
your library what um you guys don't have on here i have way too many items to stop now
don't die dallas encounter me on this one all right i need the code to get in there
there's only two or three locations i haven't been to i have not been here and i haven't been in one
spot over there i kind of want to see how the place out i do we do a um i want to see if i
come back to the real world as a magician oh dear this is an order for red painted furniture
all the pieces must be painted in red and i've run out of paint excuse me mr carpenter sir
i remember watching two swedish dudes play this i'm prepared to stop working and talk only to
someone who will bring me red paint for the furniture oh yeah i remember these two swedish
dudes played this before that's fucking awesome if you have red paint give it to him if not leave
here what i don't how do i get red paint this is where the carpenter soars his boards
well okay i i know i have the money to do go to the fruit vendor i'm doing that and yes
i'm gonna complete again painted with blood that's not funny painted with blood okay like just gross
and uncalled for disgusting not funny not funny apologize to me right now all right here's a coin
do you have money for me i do do you have red paint thank you very much that will really be
of help to me here take a cherry what do i think you will do with the cherry well i have a contest
to see what you're sweeter oh god damn it you with a hyuck hyuck guy and i got it wrong
so can i is this can i make this red paint who wants a cherry there's one place i didn't go
i need to go to the magic school where's the magic school bro bro where's the magic school
no more of this bro i'm not getting died alice encountered here not happening all right so it's
not this way it's to the right and straight it's still at least an hour left i'm not going anywhere
i don't why people think i'm just gonna leave after this game's done i've only been streaming
for like three hours i'm not gonna be like all right strawberry magic was cool i'll see you guys
say i see you guys next time no i'm still here there is gobble goodies he gobbled too much candy
and that's why he can't move and you almost missed you almost missed the gobble goodie
you almost missed the gobble goodie okay medicine powder
i must have been standing like that for years hey i'm hungry i'm so hungry
can i get a cake a cake here this cake is really great i prepared it myself
oh tasty very tasty oops the dice cube got loose from what where the dice cube
i've been looking for it for a long time it's special because it can open places
that have been closed by magic unbelievable it's been inside gobble goodie's tummy all along
you eat everything that moves stands still all eyes down everything i can open magical
doors with the magical cube magic dice cube thanks okay so let's keep going thank you um
whatever your name was i don't remember uh nothing else i can do here i go left or right
it's an s tier item yeah let's go right oh here we go oh there's so much i love this all right
let's go to the hot dog stand what money these two funny guys know the magic of how to make the best
sugar coating in the world the recipe is a very carefully guarded secret and that's why it was
divided up between the two of them each of you could enable pvp invasions in the game if you
give them a piece of fruit they'll sugar coat it for you with their own special magic coating
i have a cherry right here fresh here of a cherry and really would like you to
coat it with your world renowned ha ha ha elden ring i'm gonna sneeze strawberry do you remember
that we ordered strawberries from the vegetable vendor we ordered strawberries from the vegetable
vendor and you hid inside the box you hid inside the box and then when we poured the strawberries
into the pot yeah the pot when you were inside you gobbled everything up and didn't leave anything
for anyone else not even a drop that sounds like joey joey and louie let me be careful those two
never reveal to anyone what they put in the pot in order to make the sugar coating i don't believe
them they won't tell you listen to me they will tell you what ingredient is needed but not where
it is they will even confuse you on purpose do the exact opposite of what they ask
the big magic wand magic wand you can be sure you have been shown the secret of the coating
will never be known one two three eight nine ten now you have to start again what you said the big
magic wand that is outside the cupboard into the pot small magic wand right here right now we fooled
him we fooled him what are you talking about they said didn't they say that they it's the opposite
now you have to start just shove them over and just take the fucking pot which is under the table
put the big magic wand which is under the table i thought you supposed to do the opposite
so the big magic wand that's on top of the table so it's the small magic wand that's on top of the
table it's the opposite this is marvelous ronnie we didn't let those two showoffs get the better
of us put the big jar of honey that is on the table into the pot big jar of honey that's on
the table into the pot big jar of small jar of honey under the table into the pot wait what
is this not it powdered flowers you're losing viewers i'm not i went up like 5k in the last
five minutes to you it's not even the item what that wasn't honey one two three eight nine ten
now you have to start again put the big container of powdered flowers that is under the table
into the pot what for him he's discovered the secret i got it put the big jar of honey that
is outside the cupboard into the pot so the big jar of honey that's inside the cupboard
a small i need a small jar that's inside the cupboard no no i don't want this is a honey jar
that that's a honey jar in every single video game this is not a honey jar
no it's not that's not a honey jar in every no
he's discovered the secret it's the sugar cube that is outside the cupboard into the pot
what the what the fuck was the last thing you just said but the sugar that was outside
the cupboard into the pot the sugar inside the cupboard
it's correct right oh dear how did he find the right ingredient
the big magic wand which is under the table into the pot i'm not going anywhere
you've discovered here the secret of the great magic that we have tried so hard to keep
well good for you we're happy to know that you're not as stupid as we thought you were
what the fuck they're so mean
the cherry for you you can come whenever you want and eat as much sugar coating as you want
it's really tasty isn't it who wants this i won't tell anyone of the secret
i think it's fun i'm having a good time what is this it's all so stupid that i don't know what
to think they say that i've discovered a secret what do they think that i have to appear on the
cooking show or something i have to present a magic trick at a party real magic
who wanted this i hope that now you understand me
i almost choke laughing when i think of how you'll stand on the stage and tell the children how to
make sugar coating that's it i'm tired i'm going to sleep all right i will make a deal with chat
if in the next 15 minutes i am not at the end game of this game then i'll move on everybody was
so pogchamp on strawberry magic until until i actually want to play strawberry magic everybody's
all pog until i play it was all pogs it was all pogs until i start doing puzzles all right how do
i get out of here it was all pogs until i actually play the game all right you got 15 minutes 15
minutes and if it's not i'm finishing it yeah you can't go permission from abra oh wait a minute
i was born here it's a big deal i'm streaming for like another three or four hours don't worry
this is the home of the one and only abba the great magician he knows all there is to know about
magic and no one can match him in making magic everyone in magic land is afraid of him and no
one would dare go against his commands run a poll to see who wants to see you finish it all right
fine do it all right mods run a poll to see if people want me to finish this i guarantee you a
lot of you a lot of you guys that say no you're gonna be very surprised i think i think you're
gonna be very surprised okay we can't i can't go in there what is it that is it just a choo-choo
train it's a landslide it's a landslide hold on i need to see i need to what a fucking landslide
what a landslide landslide oh no no no that's a what an absolute fucking landslide whoa i actually
was surprised oh my god holy shit if i did that during die dallas would be 90% no i've succeeded
in creating parts of an engine like none that i've ever been seen in magic land that's interesting
i think that when the engine is built according to this model it will be the fastest ever made
but let's go this is the train station what a huge and beautiful train is standing there in the
distance i wonder what that professor is doing he's concentrating so hard that's the train designer
he built the wonderful train that you'll soon see from up 15% of you just like bit your tongue
to design a train too and like smashed your desk away from him did he get 85 oh god
are you gonna leave them they're very important i don't want you to hello strawberry today you
haven't made me angry i'm the happiest train designer in the world i've just finished
designing the parts of the model for which don't leave it's we're just having fun man a marvel of
train engineering to tell you the truth though when you're around i do get a little worried
i'm sure that you've stolen some part of the model no sir all the parts are on the table
oh dear i'm less than 25 voter turnout there all the parts of the train model are here you had an
opportunity you were there you could have said yes or no i can't tell you to vote sure that all
the parts are there don't worry to all the strawberry magic haters out there let's i'm
gonna level with you what i'm gonna be done really soon okay i'm gonna be done very soon we don't
don't worry about it we'll be all right trying to put all the parts together yourself well let's
just see whether you have the talent to be a real designer magician we're now designer magicians
okay what does it look like great this is fitting together perfectly
what does it look like this is oh shit all right all right i gotta go pink this is fitting together
perfectly and then that's the two brains up here that doesn't belong there it does oh i need the
blue the brain is rotting just i have some vitamins or something i wonder a real wonder
this is fitting together perfectly just go eat like a banana come back you're not you're not
you when you're hungry okay no strawberry did you really think that it was so easy to design a
train a new cosplay as a strawberry magic character i wonder a real wonder i got like a strawberry
costume that doesn't belong there what is this right on the front this is a picture of the train
model i wonder i did it a real wonder stop playing this game you just missed the 85
percent poll it was 85 want to be just stay just stay 85 said to stay to stay you had an
opportunity to vote and you missed it now what do we do this is a picture of the train now what
now what there's one piece left where there's one more what the fuck picture of the train
model where is this piece oh my god i thought that was strawberry's head a real wonder i am
going to stay strawberry although i did get angry at you when you stole the parts from here i'm
pleased now it looks like you did learn something after all from playing with the parts i designed
good for you you can ride on my train anytime you want
okay thank you now what you're not going to give me an item or anything this is a picture of the
train model so can i ride can i actually go on a train or is that it this is great i can ride
the train now what does this take us we have some visitors strawberry what are you doing here
here i wrote up a designer's wonderful train and arrived here how are you as usual strawberry
i make use of the secrets known only to me to give help to anyone who wants it nice
i'm ready to help anyone who needs my very special talent to a recount okay if you need help
i can help you let's do another poll if you want me to stay and play strawberry magic
and if there are not at least 10 000 votes it'll be pissed let it watch it be higher
i'm ready to help anyone who needs my very special talents if you need help i can help you
so help i want to help help me then magic dice cube that's not what i have to give now
what do i have to give that's not what i have to give now strange that's not what i have to give
now okay i don't think i can do this yet all right that's all it's on the train i'm just taking a
walk more people vote well i gotta see it let's see it only three only four thousand votes let's go
what's going on here i i can imagine how mad the strawberry magic haters are right now it's
probably like livid it's like i i'm so mad it needs to go on longer all right we got a kind
of a weirdo here oh strawberry what's the workers where are you headed first of workers what does
that mean what do they do here you do ask silly questions ronnie how do you do here they work
like horses that's what they do here what the fuck this is so fucked up strawberry don't look
so innocent you know very well what we do here the problem is that you never like to come here and
help us are you planning to bother us today too no i don't intend bothering you at all i'm searching
for the magic i really need a lot of beans from the most unexpected direction what is this so
a hundred pepper worker seeds but i can't find the house where the seeds are
i'll help you which house are you what is this boat what's this pole i'm looking for the house
which is under the blue house and behind the blue house under the blue house and behind the blue
house got it right this is the house now i'll be able to grow pepper workers from the seeds
thank you bro pepper workers that you've changed now what what does that do what does that do for
us we just get like a bad ending i don't know i don't get it you in strawberry you got up early
still trying to get out of doing any work huh get out of work oh no what made you think that's the
opposite i'm interested in working today i've already worked for the pepper and he even sends
you his regards do you need any help send you his regards unbelievable i wondered what happened to
the strawberries well if you're such a good workforce it might not be a bad idea grow more
out of you here i received an order for a hundred corn workers for next month a hundred more corn
force workers after so a hundred corn workers seeds which are in one of those houses but
i don't know which one someone has mixed up the houses i found a strange note here and i don't
know who left it what does it say written in such a vague way i'll help you which house are you
looking for i'm looking for the house that is behind the house that is under the red flower
the corn asks easy questions that have very hard answers okay shut up shut the
fuck down and shut up what what was it it's under the house behind the house
wonderful that's the house now i can sow the corn seeds goodbye and give my warmest regards
to mr cucumber what she's causing so much trouble in this town every single person i've
met every single one is like oh strawberry you're here to like fuck up my business
every single person all right this is probably one more what what do you mean what am i talking
about we we've been watching this strawberry magic person over here now wait what what happened
no go back go back go back go back did i miss a puzzle i didn't get anything for doing this
is there another one what do you want me to do i didn't get an item for this
but i've gone left again i went left for the corner i didn't think i could go left again
guys help what's the name of that song i've been trying to figure it out for a long time and i
cannot for the life of me find it the one that goes do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do
using like a shitload of youtuber videos what was it called it's called oh my fucking god hello
i want to disturb you but i'm looking for the magic can you help me course i can help you do
you know the magic that will help me find the house that i'm looking for i have to sew cucumber
worker seats right away but i can't find them show me the house where the seeds are hidden
okay i'll do it i've been looking for this song for a long time yeah the purple house
above the rock oh i wonder where that is look for the purple house above the rock like
turn your head wonderful you have found my seeds real magic i rushing off to work
give my regards to miss red pepper so long that did good can we have a reward
sure what was the reward i didn't get anything understand ask about them that asks me to help
him even when i answer from them i hope you're right strawberry and that i could find some magic
here to show at the party it's a child's game yeah well i mean where are we going apple this
has got to be the end no mrs red pepper you strawberry how did you get here you know that
you are very near to the clearing in the forest and only those who are good at magic are allowed
in this part of the forest oh tell me you naughty boy did you find some secret detour around harry
the corn and mr green the cucumber no not at all i took the main road and helped each of them
it's been 15 minutes add another time i'm really surprised what happened strawberry that you
decided to help have you decided to become a magician yes i've been looking for the magical
somebody was very bad i'm sorry help me of course i can here magic land needs a large workforce
my friends cucumber pepper and corn are already busy with preparations
they also sell worker seeds i have the job of preparing a workforce for emergencies
abra put the seeds in one of the houses do this in real life to his description
i'm having trouble finding the right one strawberry come on wake up are you sure
strawberry's been asleep in this place i'm sure i told you keep on looking you have no choice if
someone asks for your help you have to help them and that's that there's no such thing as magic
she just found this innocent kid all right i said oh hey come and do all my work and chores for me
looking for the red house above the red flower it's real magic strawberry i'm rushing off to
sow my seeds bye give my regards to eggplants don't forget now no i somebody just give me an
item so i can leave you see strawberry mrs red pepper is just like all the rest she only wants
me to help her and didn't give me even a clue as to where to find the magic listen to me ronnie
aubergine lives in a very important part of the forest it's the most carefully guarded place
before the clearing in the forest hey his magic is very special interesting all right
we're gonna get a spell i think we're gonna get a spell i think hey you other me again today
you're the last one i want to see here go away what is it is it a hot dog or what is it a plant
what did you do to aubergine that is so angry at you and is chasing me away
uh you see uh yesterday i was very hungry and i thought all day about the wonderful
apples that aubergine grows i asked him for one but of course aubergine does not give apples to
anyone who doesn't help him so i offered to help him pick the apples and i really did pick them
you have hit rock bottom after they were already in my bag i really didn't feel like
why is so many people have such a vicious reaction to strawberry magic
i'm having fun with strawberry magic wherever i go as soon as i get there i have to suffer because
of the mischief you have gotten yourself into nobody likes me here and it's all your fault
you wanted to come here so don't complain go back to mr aubergine he really isn't as bad as he looks
just what house do you want me to do so then i can go to the magical forest and get the magic
fucking comet azure
this ain't worst dream 2022 fan anybody that says that because it's fake it's not real
i'm having a blast no way no way all right no way i won't be as stupid as yesterday
today you won't leave here until you do get the magic right ready tell me what i have to do
i'm looking for the blue house which has a blue house above it and a blue house in front of it
what this one that's marvelous strawberry i'm sure that the apples you ate from my tree had a
wonderful effect on you if you're going to the clearing in the forest give my regards to the
goodbye okay so now give my regards to the forest let me into the magic forest so i can get the
magical spell to be able to music allows the bod to play magical tunes for sale rhythm a bicycle
in good condition a service cart huh excuse me sir doesn't look around
just a minute don't disturb me for sale an electric range a pair of chairs
excuse me sir strawberry i'm tired of your pranks this time i won't give in this time
you have to reveal to me how you managed to sneak into the forest every time without anyone's
noticing you this is the most carefully guarded place in magic land and you're not allowed to
run around here why what are you guarding here all i see here are lots and lots of furrows nothing
else bridge to read us according to legend the great book of magic is buried here really was
hidden hundreds of years ago oh my god nobody knows for certain where it was buried because
the enchanted compass rose which points to where it is has been lost and to this day no one has
found it but abra the great magician is willing to give anything to anyone who can give him the
book which has all the lost secrets in the library behind the clove guy and whoever has the compass
rose in his possession can find the ancient book of course but the compass rose itself is not enough
we also have to find the ball that will fly us high above the clearing in the forest
and move in the directions that the compass rose shows us okay all right i don't have that
strawberry you have nothing to do here all right i don't have that i don't have that i don't have
that i don't have your usual lazy self somewhere else hey hey when you have both items you need to
find the book we'll look for it together goodbye strawberry harsh all right get me out of here
i'll come back all right i'm giving it 10 minutes that was a growl no it wasn't
strawberry all right all right all right all right i'm almost there i'm almost there i promise i'm
almost there promise i'm almost there everyone relax give me something to say in the low voice
i'll do it i'll make everybody happy give me something to say in it again give me something
to say i'll say it in the low voice berries strawberry avocado did i tell you that i was
laughing my ass off like the other day because i just kept thinking of the voldemort homer simpson
comment and that video that like oh oh just was the video was playing in my head over and over
again i was fucking dying all right what what do i need to do i need to go to the magic school
i didn't want a magic wand nothing has come in oh i might move on i might give in because i don't
know what to do now does this does that magic does this count as a magic wand i don't know what to do
i'm stuck i feel like i'm so close i'm so close i need to something to open the nectar lid i need
will the dice open the magician door i need the red paint need yeah i need red paint i don't know
the fuck anything even is here man i don't think i went down this way did i know this is where the
bridge is what's across the bridge all right i can't i need to open that nectar but i don't think i
can i need another item just the construction i already did i got this already i don't know
try the dice what would the dice work on that magic building hold on but just the lollipop
count is a magic wand i feel like it's a kid's game might just sugar-coated cherry
ice on the nectar that's a pity you kidding me i could learn some magic at this school
that's right people are commenting on a walkthrough on youtube
god you have about three hours left to finish this what magic dice you can't open the barrel
why come on what do we do magic dice that won't help you open the door we can open any door
i don't want to get stuck here it looks like i can't get past the pit
i have a legit question why you still playing because i'm invested and i want to know what
happens there dev painter for paint all right ice on magic school i can't get in there with all the
wand all right all right all right all right all right hello strawberry there are prisoners in the
cells and my work day is just one long break all right all right all right all right that's it all
right that's it cake all right there are two let's plays of this that exist all right but i
want to know i want to finish it what do i wish i go i have this picture i need to get into magic
school i have this necklace for somebody who's the necklace for i don't know all right painter
all right store is closed today what open it up magic dice cube all right all right that's it
all right magic dice cube you can't go in there without permission from abra
what a shame i was born here magic dice cube
i think i'm stuck i might have to give up here in a second i really think i have to give up
we've lost about 10 percent by the way 10 have shifted over to the move on side that's a full 10
percent starting to lose more people more all right people were like yeah let's go
fuck the strawberry magic haters 10 you changed your mind the last 20 minutes
like yeah you know what actually fuck this game we should do something else paint all right i'm
gonna get the red paint i'm not kidding if i am not at the end of this game in exactly 15 minutes
i'll quit i promise so you're back you probably want to go into the library i'm pleased to invite
you to go you worked hard and you deserve it i need red paint this is the color red take it you'll
find it useful oh no hi sir touch oh oh what all right red paint now we have to go to that
construction place which i forget where that is help me please help me over here construction
red paint get an item we're good we're going for it i'll be there in 15 minutes well have you
brought a can of red paint go back oh where did you get the red paint i placed the order for it
a long time ago and never got it i must produce all this furniture in this color for a second
i'd like to ask you if you know the secret of the magic the secret of the there is no secret
why you always ran away from the magic and liked resting better but if you're looking for it again
here look a shape has been drawn on this board this lever will move the saw in any direction
either what's a lever lever if you saw the board according to the drawing i'll make you something
which can help you okay let's do it this is gonna take forever
i'm trying to like turn it now
what the fuck that's better
i need to go down again see any line here fuck you uh better i think i crashed the game strawberry
if you don't help me saw the board i won't have time to prepare the item you need in order to get
closer to finding the magic go over to the board which is on the table this is making my brain
itchy i got it okay get to work strawberry perform the magic why is this magic it's a saw
this actually sucks okay i have an idea
i don't see any line here i have to put the saw up there first strawberry you know what have fun in
your lounge chair that's better this is gonna be fucking impossible don't see any line here
oh my god oh my god that's better not in the right direction
i'm not on it okay you are on it when the
there's one pixel block on the white no that's wrong you are on it when there's yeah
what the fuck is happening right now excuse me what how do i get this correct
not in the right direction i can only go so far that's better
who cares strawberry you managed to saw this complicated shape very well in just a moment
i'll paint it red but in the meantime take this very useful screwdriver this is just great the
board is painted red and i have a little time so let's go prepare something for you that will
bring you a lot closer to the magic i'm making a magic wand i can open up the nectar now when you
have it you must show it to everyone and then they will know that you honestly want to become a real
magician i'll fit the guiding star onto the top of the wand oh the guiding star will prove that
you have already been to a place from which the secret of the magic can be seen do you have the
guiding star if you do give it to me and i'll finish making you your magic wand
that's not what i have to give now why walk all the way over there
you little shit all right go get out i don't have the guiding star i'll try and get one
all right i'll wait for you here nectar good luck the star is gonna be down there magical school
find who stole the thing we're getting close it's been 15 minutes no it hasn't okay i need to go to
the door open the lid have the guy fly me to the magical kingdom i gotta remember where that is
okay where the fuck is the magical thing where is it i don't know where it is up and right
fuck the haters there's no hate people just messing around i mean there's probably okay
there are 17 000 people here i imagine at least 100 of them i probably unfollowing the channel
at this point they probably hate me now because they hate this game i'm sorry i'm actually i'm
sorry i wish i could say something to you i'm sorry i like just but i have to finish i have
to get over i have to do it sorry a screwdriver all right let's go this will help me open the
barrel toilet what's going on with his eyes this nectar is delicious i'm ready to fly
but the door is closed i think i've got a fucking magical cube that won't help you open the door
shut up this guy was lying the whole time the door is closed it can't be opened without the
magic disc the magic i need a magic disc i just gave this guy drugs and that's all that happened
looks like i can't get past the pit now what how awful now what i don't understand
what happens now i need a magic disc the lid no it's not it's not the lid it looks like i
can't get past the pit awful shit dip the lollipop in the nectar shit stuck again
give the candy to the weird dude i don't know that what are you saying weird guy
give a lollipop to the monster wait the the gobble guy will he actually eat this
do another poll yeah do do another poll i'm curious to see how much if people are losing
patience every like 15 minutes i'm waiting for it to swing the other direction and the majority
say no it's actually funny i like this okay here to tell me that you are going to feed this cement
mixer again yes god damn it i can't i can't feed it to him all right i this is bad where i'm
actually i'm stuck the guy at the bridge the guy at the bridge i don't i don't think he's gonna
want it the bridge guy or the warehouse necklace to the that's right all right what we got for
percentage percentage what is it 73 percent losing it was 77 before uh-oh 73 percent still
majority it is string that's not what i have to give now god damn it do you want this candy or
something that's not what i have to give now i need the library key scroll from the painter
go to the library library key scroll where do i get that 70 is enough okay every 10 minutes
we're gonna do the poll if it drops below 65 i will leave so you're back you probably want to
go into the library i'm pleased to invite you to go you worked hard and you deserve it we need
to stay strong guys uh i'm just saying if that draws drop those 65 i'm out of here the dice in
here i still haven't found the secret hidden in the book try again or the train ice cube a sugar
fuck if i want to find the secret book i need to get the library code
it's the library code scroll there's a scroll under the easel help me help me help me
i thought that was what the easel was on i thought there was a piece of wood
one of the books in my library contains a great secret the code with which you will
find the book that has this secret is on the scroll my fucking god with you
i thought that was a piece of wood holding the easel up all right strawberry friends
we're getting closer i haven't found the secret hidden in the book i'll try again from time to
time another book will be lit up on the scroll you must find its place in the library and click
on it exactly i will oh no next time you guys i'm telling you under 65 percent i'm and i'm
alt f1 good you clicked on the right book good you clicked on the right book run it exactly
that's the book good you clicked on the right book strawberry friends and strawberry haters
who's gonna win 101 ways to skive work that's my kind of book 101 ways to skive work that's my
kind of book look ronnie is rising by itself it's opening up to a certain page what's drawn
there did you notice the ball that fell out when the book opened up straw boring can i get a ball
it looks like a compass rose it says here that if i reach the clearing in the forest the compass
rose will direct me to where the lost book of magic is hidden oh okay bring this to the forest
the great magic all the tricks in the world are in that book legend has it that it was written
by the father of all magicians thousands of years ago but everyone thinks that it has been lost
take the compass have any six percent we're good use it to help find the ancient book
they'll love you in magic land maybe i'll find a small and easy magic trick in the book
i'll take the compass rose hurry up and take it this is a very strange ball it doesn't bounce
like a regular ball i'll take it with me okay so i've got this is the thing that i put on top of
the magic one right very much sir very impressive collection of books and i'm from the fortunate
people who have visited your library no that's for the clearing in the forest all right i got
the compass rose i'm gonna go to the forest go to the dorito farmer okay that's the artist
and i found a match compass rose in the secret book i've already wasted a lot of time i'm here
for dos games not straw ass strawberry do you think i'll be able to find one here straw ass
is a dos game so you are here for this will continue just the way i told you to thinking
don't tell me you're too tired to go on working because you have a lot of work in front of you
just keep trying and let me rest all right strawberry friends berry bros i'm going to
give you guys a little bit harder for a task this is for all this is for the marvels here when i
do the poll again you got to keep that over 75 and think you can handle it it'll be hard
and you see how strong that community is all right i gotta go to the forest which is
where do i get to the forest i don't remember at all 75 can you do it where's the the forest
okay run it that's way too high let's find out if you got what it takes all right let's do it
keep the strawberry magic alive this rose my blue hat that's it that's the rose where did you find
it this will be abra the great magician's happiest day of his life doesn't like rick we're so close
to finding the book what else do you need strawberry we have to find the floating ball
and start out immediately i got it in search of the book what's going on here what's going on here
okay we're at 80 all right berry bros you get to live another day wonderful now we have both the
ball and the compass rose and we can start our search 75 to the ball and i'll kick you upwards
when you're up there you'll be able to see the furrows was compass rose will guide you
pay attention you must begin from the blue dot that's my hat that way you'll know where i am
all right he just kicked me
oh my god what the hell is this it's your stream i know this is fun stars will float in the sky
and you'll be able to catch one and fall to earth with it now listen very carefully you must look
at the blue dot that's me and move in the direction i tell you you must move only one
dot at a time the enchanted compass rose will guide us and we'll reach the place where the
book has been hidden move one dot to the upper left okay how do i do that how do i do that
well that's not the proper direction it's an upper left dude wonderful oh move one dot to the left
great we're on the right track move one dot downward yes i can't go down there very good
move one dot to the right that's it that's the correct dot move one dot to the right
we just did a circle great we're on the right track move one dot to the upper right
right everybody all you fucking assholes that's how many clicks star why have you come down
you almost found the most important book in the world strawberry i just don't understand you
send me back up strawberry i'll go so you're back want to try and look for the book again
send me back up there you go back on the ball again yes i want to try i must get that book
this has been unbearable i'm having a great time one dot to the left 80 percent of the people here
watching disagree with you move one dot to the right wonderful move one berry bros are very
strong right now great we're on the right track move one dot upward wonderful move one dot to
this fucking sucks very good when i finish i'll be the only person
in the last 10 years to play this game and beat it great we're on the right track
move one dot to the upper right we're at the end game now great we're on the right track i promise
i'll go back to jeopardy i will move one dot to the upper left move one dot to the right
it very good move one dot upward i'm gonna get the magic book strawberry i see something
interesting on the ground catch a star right away and come down on it yep yep yep yep yep
where we have to dig yep roger got it got it got it got it coming down see the gas and do 80
i'm so excited we found the great book of magic everyone thought the book was lost forever i
would love to see a look on abra the great magician's face when he gets the book back
i got it i got the book i got the book i have the book that i beat it it's over
i have the magic book the great book of magic i can get the magic wand this is it this is it
take the star to the magic wand get the magic wand made take that to the school bring that
finish the school bring that book to abracadabra and then see the final cut scene and it's over
and we went this is it you need to do ranny's ending who was the person that made the
it's a construction place this way right i'll speed it up don't worry and then we go to the
academy do you have the guiding star if you do give it to me and i'll finish making you
your magic the lord of the frenzied berry ending very good here is the wand now everyone will know
that you are serious and intend discovering the secret of the magic is so close strawberry
from today on you are a citizen with equal rights of magic land and you are no longer
considered lazy now that you know what you want to be i hope you find the magic all right
hey chaos take the world all right school time i'm feel i feel it we're almost there
the school was back this way and then to the right i think where was the school we're always so close
man i'm telling you we're so close it's this way right and then up across the bridge i get a poll
up there 80 come on come on berry bros 80 i need those you guys that have been hanging out watching
enjoying the strawberry magic stream i need you right now i need you right now those of you that
have been watching just chilling and you're logged in right now and you can click that button we need
you to be over 80 80 you've come so far magic wand is seriously interested in learning how to
become a magician so if you pass the entrance examination you'll be allowed to go in i'll soon
test to see if you have the talent to become a magician i'll show you one card then i'll turn
it back with the fast movement of all great magicians i will then replace the cards then
you will have to tell me where the card you first saw is those that game 80 come on this is your
card follow it this is your card now you can enter the school it was so easy that was unbelievably
fucking easy here i'll be able to find the one who stole abra's hat i must look at the
identikit picture and find the suspect all right i gotta find the suspect this is a picture of the
suspect who's ernie i have to find which of the students here looks exactly the same got you got
you 84 holy shit okay you know what i'm gonna ask next time you know what i'm gonna ask next time
all right i'm sorry here's the hat take it i got the hat okay now i take the hat
through that magical house and right where's that magical house wait should i give the magic hat to
this guy or to the police officer oh strawberry there are no prisoners in the cells and my work
i just got i got a huge craving right there this hat belongs to abra i can't give it away
i don't know why no i got a huge craving right there for um just like risk it i don't know why
where do i go i thought that guy couldn't fly unless he all right i gotta find this um this
place where is it it's like where's the magic's uh abracadabra's house i don't remember where it is
back to the right this way no no no no no still playing this i'm almost done back to the right
it's a hamburger helper guys run it again 85 i need everybody to fucking really focus
focus 85 and that will be the victor that will be the absolute victory and i'm not going to ask for
another one you want to see this continue to be played and finish get to 85 right now permission
from abra what a shame i was born here how do i the magic what do i do about this the great book
of magic i can't get in here yet do i need to go to the train station bring the magic book to the
uh person at the end of the train i'm gonna try that bring the doorbell on the house come on are
you shitting me your train is reading more be even better oh oh oh oh oh what's happening
we're at 84 right now guys yeah this is it kill the magic or the magic lives on
poll ends in literally 10 seconds 84 you gotta get in there get it you gotta get in there now
you gotta get in there right now you gotta get in there right now get it to 85 right now if you
haven't clicked on it if you haven't voted this is your last five seconds your last opportunity
berry bros you're about to lose it berry bros that's it this is a picture of the train
model okay all right all right all right all right all right all right i have an idea i'm keeping
that in a different window i'm gonna finish it before the stream ends can i get back into this
what was this one i need to mute this i can't mute it shit how do i mute an individual window
in the mixer i can only uh they're all on uh firefox volume mixer i can't i got individual tabs
i there's only one firefox tab right click how do i do it you can mute it via the dust box window
yeah i can't it says click for a sound is off click for sound that doesn't work
right click mute tab mute the tab i'm i i dragged it in its own window it's in its own window right
now i can't mute this window right click the tab yeah it's out of a tab it's out of a tab
shit how do i put it back in the tabs i need to put it back into the tabs here how do i do that
oh we got it we're good let's go hell yeah hell yeah all right we're good everything's fine
back to jeopardy i'll take uh take plants for uh for 100 invented the light bulb and the record
player that's thomas edison who is thomas edison who was thomas edison got it what now you're
complaining no all of a sudden oh the magic is dead kill the magic strawberry magic let's die
die die and i move on to jeopardy and all of a sudden it's like really yeah get rid of that
get rid of that i want you to do something else i'm playing jeopardy now look what you've done
first woman to appear on a cereal box um i don't know who is first person to appear in a cereal box
84 percent the magic we want the magic back it was uh nancy nancy kerrigan i don't know i don't
i don't know this famous olympic athlete was the strawberry magic oh my god who was it dan tell us
who is mary lou retton give give us a poll to see if 85 percent want jeopardy all right if even if
if even 20 percent of you want jeopardy i'm staying the green matter found in plants which
is what all right how about somebody please ratio this game this 16th century monarch sucked what
was their name what did it say oh had six wives henry the eighth that's okay xmas tradition 500
here we go people who walk from house to house carolers christmas carolers carol caroling what
is what are carol how do i spell carola carolers christmas caroling i don't i don't know how to
days three days what do you have to eat something fucking blew me up this game doesn't have any
magic in it i mean it kind of does this thing is camping me no no you don't need a pole you
don't need a pole you don't need a pole because we're going to move on to another licensed one
we're going to move on to uh scoobies haunted kitchen you don't need a pole you're fine we're
fine use your mouse to catch the ghostly ingredients for your major shaggy sandwich place the floating
food on shaggy's bun but watch out scoobies hungry too where are the sneaky ghosts we have
to make a sandwich this is taking a long time to load oh this runs like shit too all right cheese
fun cheese bacon salami lettuce why is scooby dead why is scooby have dives head gone
cheese what is this implying tomato bacon fun i got it this game sucks okay how about uh let's
keep going about taco bell promotional game but he misses strawberry magic 84 of you all right
this is a taco bell uh fps game your viewers are plummeting i didn't say we were done with it i just
said that it was not happening right now breakfast what do you mean breakfast 84 is not enough for
you i said i wanted 85 all right here we go after this uh i'll figure out a plan of what we're going
to do after this come on open it won't open end of the stream voice i didn't say that
pod watchers skipped to i didn't say that i didn't say the stream was ending what are you talking
about it froze hold on okay taco bell temple there are only 16 percent of the people here
are watching enjoying this this one crashed uh what the fuck what the fuck that one crashed
all right what about popeye wrestle crazy let's try that one number player is one okay let's go
this one he threw something how do you do a move he didn't beat me already right so he threw a
bomb in the ring what the fuck that was insane what are the controls all right stop throwing
grenades into the ring that would be great who is that one more try i'm pressing every button
on the keyboard nothing does anything i crashed my computer let's go the magic is back the magic
returns i got the magic book that's not what i have to give now that's not what i have to
give now so what do i have to give this person magic never left he was skyrocketing what oh
my god i was at like 17k and that 80 000 viewers now the word must have gotten out that the magic
has returned word must have gotten out i'm ready to help anyone who needs my very special talents
if you need help i can help you is it the necklace i don't think so that's not what i have to give
now this one piece of the puzzle i'm missing here i'm just taking a walk goodbye remember the cnn
part oh yeah guy like walking around grabbing his chair i know that i've pretended to die
i forgot that was the same stream that was fucking hilarious by the way so where do i go
i not the forest go to abra's house i think there was nothing i could do here though
best scream 2022 i don't know about that i'm having fun but you know oh here we go let's go
let's go let's go let's go time for the ending cinematic who is that who's bothering me now
maybe someone has found the great book of magic huh runny it's me runny
runny he doesn't know who ronnie is this is no time to mix things up you are really me
you're strawberry now it's me strawberry strawberry i'm warning you if you don't
stop ringing my doorbell and running away i'll punish you brisket why don't you stop fooling
around and help me find the great book of magic got it right here was lost hundreds of years ago
and now there is great danger that the magic will be lost i must find it you've brought the
great book of magic back to me that's the best thing that's happened in magic land for hundreds
of years i'm so happy come in please come into my house and i got his hat too so this is perfect
i've met you and have seen what you're able to do i think differently about the strawberry workers
you have never shown any interest in the secret of magic you spent your time on childish pranks
and silly jokes and didn't learn anything and now wonder of wonders it was you of all who has
brought me back the book where all the best kept secrets of magic are written tell me strawberry
what happened to change you so
just listen to the old grump who always kicked me out
just listen to how sweet he sounds now because you're helping you're not just sitting on a lounge
chair i know but i've changed now and i really would like to learn the secret of magic
what magic would you like to learn i get to pick you must learn the magic of the three items
i want to learn how to
you listen to this motherfucker
the magic of the three items that's the most difficult magic of all
it takes a lot of hard work to get hold of the three magic items strawberry you've taken a very
serious task upon yourself and i'm ready to help you remember if you bring me the three magic items
that's what we have which no one except me has succeeded in getting
i'll teach you the secret magic lollipop the magic dice with the magic hat of master of master
magicians what do you need what are the three magic items that i won't tell you i can only
say that i don't have them once i found them too and that's how i became the best magician in the
world if you bring me the three magic items i promise you i will teach you the secret of magic
and you will be called the best magician did you know i'm the only magician that can get out of a
locked box watch i'll jump into the box you'll lock it and in half a jiffy i'll be out this is
no oxygen in there this guy's gonna die uh are we gonna is this guy gonna die in here
oh don't do that
this guy was just trashed what do you want me to do
strawberry i still can't get out of here strawberry quick get me out of here leave them in here
i'm choking strawberry quick get me out of here i'm choking strawberry quick get me out of here
i'm choking why did you go in magic dice cube did he go in strawberry i still can't get out
how do i open it well what do you want of course i'm laughing this is ridiculous the guy's like ah
i will come and bring me three magical items i don't know what they are but go find them
oh by the way i'm gonna trap myself in a box that i can't get out of and die from suffocation
excuse me what do you want to do here strawberry quick get me out of here i'm choking i need a
puzzle piece this dude's dead go into abra's kitchen without his permission
honey don't make the magician angry you have to get his permission to go into these rooms
help what is that i don't know what this i don't know what this is
goodness i can't get hope he doesn't suffocate in there
strawberry you should be ashamed of yourself don't bother me now did anyone give you permission
to come in yes i got the hat to prove it what the fuck am i supposed to do about this
honestly what am i supposed to do about this i need a i need a thing to help him
there i don't know puzzle on the boat wait it was on the casket of the puzzle in the
front of the box but i'm missing a piece it's not a casket it's a box why am i saying casket
who said i didn't say casket i i swear to god i didn't say somebody in chat did that's why
i said it strawberry i still can't get out of here strawberry i still can't get out of here
i can't click these oh i got it strawberry you amaze me more with every passing second
i'm beginning to believe that the little red sweet strawberries have magic talents still
undeveloped of course but still worthy of admiration oh i'm so hungry i was in the box for such a long
time the let's play open if you get something to eat oh how about a magical lollipop we
strawberries are red and sweet try to eat sir i i only eat special dishes very special even
exceptional is that salmon or a hamburger or what do you eat what do you want in my wall
it's four different colors and then i will eat the hamburger that pops out of the fridge
this is the pantry go in there okay wait he eats strawberries this is a big plan for me to get
beaten what the hell is that jesus yeah sheesh sheesh the heck was that strawberry all of the dishes
here look very ordinary and the magician wants the most exceptional food here help me there are four
kinds of food on each shelf one of them does not belong to the group and is therefore exceptional
okay so i have to find it out of there and put it on the top shelf that wants a weird dish he
wants okay so what doesn't belong here you want a cake um that's right cake is the exception
since it is a baked product not like grapes the pear and the apple which are fruit
it's why i picked it thanks for the input all right this is chocolate loaf of bread candy and
it's a loaf of bread doesn't belong it's not candy that's right bread is the exception since
it is a baked product not like ice cream chocolate and candy which are sweets make me a cake sandwich
i don't know what is this milk a donut that's right donut is the exception since it is a bakery
product and not like yogurt milk and cheese which are milk products okay so we have carrot
see these all look like it's a bit of banana because it's a fruit that's right banana is
the exception because it is a fruit and the tomato the carrot and the cucumber are all
vegetables this guy's deficient in a lot of stuff okay so i did it cake is not the exception since
it is a baked product like bread what the fuck are you talking about that's right the banana
is the exception since it is a fruit and all the others are bakery products i don't believe this
all he wanted to eat was a banana why didn't he just tell us he wanted a banana oh i like this guy
i know
right all these banana haters bring me the exceptional dish here this is just what i
wanted to eat you know now that i've calmed down a little i can tell you the magic didn't work
perhaps because whenever i do something really big and important i have to put on my great
magician's hat got it unfortunately that has disappeared someone who wanted to be as great
as i stole it from me i'm sure that it was one of the pupils in the magician's school oh well
never mind the police are taking care of the matter and i forgot there are police in the universe
listen strawberry take this note and bring me some vegetables from the magic vegetable garden
why when the gardener sees the note he'll let you in you know what if you bring me vegetables
from the garden and help me find my hat maybe i'll be able to help you get a little closer to the
three items of magic need vegetables by the way why don't you go up the steps and meet my beautiful
daughter abretta i'll go for a little walk outside i have your hat oh okay
you in here i've been mad at you for a long time and if you think you can get away with
putting beetles in my bed i'm warning you my father will make jam out of you
you i'm sorry i promise i won't do it again honest i really do want us to be friends again
ronnie why are you being so nice to that show off all she does is look at herself in the mirror all
day there's no mirror in here beautiful she is stop it strawberry because of you this sweet girl
doesn't like me either never get into so much trouble with everyone here
now i'm in trouble too on account of you it was so funny watching how scared she was of the beetles
i put in her bed just you wait and what's wrong with you driving you crazy over her clothes
what's wrong with you what a menace
i want to be your friend eat a sugar coated cherry got it bring me one and then we'll see
we were prepared coming into this we were ready for that one
could have been a little longer than half a second ronnie ronnie listen i have to confess something
she can't be your girlfriend i'm in love with abretta and i've tried so hard to make a good
impression on her and i've never succeeded every time instead of falling in love with me
she threw me out you put bugs in her bed you fucking idiot so easily why doesn't she like
me i'm putting beetles in her bed but now let's talk about really important things let's talk
about clothes there she goes again with all her silly interests i'm going to get some sleep
you know strawberry i never have anything to wear but i see lots of clothes here
no there aren't no there aren't i never have the clothes for what i need i'll tell you what i need
it for and then let's see if you can find the right piece of clothing all right climb onto the table
and we'll see what you can offer me all right here we go it's time to pick the clothing piece
of clothing what what's the right piece of clothing i've been invited to the animal party
what should i wear all right party find an elegant enough dress for the occasion
in the dress when you're finished and if found one let me know are we thinking a long dress
are we thinking i what are we thinking here how about this one here how's that one no um i don't
know dress okay how's that uh i have this one a party gun i think i like that okay what else
that's it what's that party hat no headphones diving goggles i don't think that works for a party
uh these shoes are just fine okay now what party this looks like a party hat um
what else do you want what else do you want to wear decorative perfect you've managed to find
these old rags the secret understand it it claims that all i do all day is look into it and that
makes the mirror angry this is weak drip back at me come to the next room and see what it weak drip
hey we'll see how the mirror starts behaving badly towards me go away enough is enough
hardly a minute goes by when she changes what she's wearing and then she comes and looks at me
don't you think this is a little too much you don't well this time i won't let you look into me
then we smash the mirror with a hammer oh this is great what a fabulous mirror just my style
why should it work all day no drip i really like this you see well
very but the mirror will change how i look you must force it to show me exactly how i look
and the minute you see that it's right the mirror is scared to death of hammers
and it will not change the way i look again what's going on
stop i'm trying to lower the other arm okay that's correct right he's picking up the hammer
i'd better stay put and don't make anyone angry oh pretty look at pretty things you know what
i'm so confused you from now you too can look at pretty things here have my picture
okay thank you very much i'm lost you you know where i can find the matters i can help you a lot
but before i do that you have to bring back the string of pearls that was lost yes i have those
oh here is the string we're enacting you here i have it in one magic item that you have certainly
earned take good care of it what is it it will help you find the magic thank you it's uh it's
um i don't know what that is all right we're gonna get that picture to the guy at the bridge
and then we're gonna go we're going all right yeah go to the garden
just standing here okay i have your hat strawberry you promised me you'd bring me a basket of
vegetables and that you'd help me look for my hat i'm still waiting don't disappoint me okay do not
disappoint me
wonderful i don't even want to know who stole it from me the main thing is that i have it
now i can use the best vegetable magic there is and with no mistakes just a minute where are
the vegetables that's weird all right let me in let me in here mission to enter the garden here
here's my permission to enter the garden voice crack please enter the garden it was
voice crack listen strawberry i'd never have let you into the garden i don't understand how
abra gave you permission well anyway you have to bring him the basket of vegetables i tell you to
take but there aren't any vegetables here at all i'll just sprinkle this magic powder and the
vegetables will just pop out okay a lot of the biggest vegetable into the basket
this one's the biggest one right there all the right vegetables are in the basket
there's only one in there take the basket and bring it to abra quickly i only wanted one vegetable
you could have thrown that into his window like a nerf football
why did i have to come over and put it in a basket one here you go here's your one eggplant
basket here's the basket of vegetables abra take it strawberry i'm so happy i'm three times happy
first because i found my hat second because i can work the vegetable magic without mistakes
and third because you proved to me that you are not a mistake you are great and a magician of
wonderful talent thanks take this pink turnip inside it is one of the magic items
i'm leaving now don't forget to come back to me once you have the three items how do i open i how
do i open the door i need a disc thank you very much abra but just a minute i get the magic item
out of the turnip really strawberry come here abra may think you're a great magician
but i know it's not so easy to get your hands on a magic item if you don't study to become a
magician the best thing you could do is go to the forest sorceress she'll help you to get the item
out of the turnip okay well i think we're completed up here i need to give that picture
to the person of the bridge why did they make this game um let's be very very honest
very honest in 1986 this would have been pretty pog i'm sorry this would have been awesome
this would have been huge all right where's the guy the bridge is over here this would have been
amazing if i was 12 11 10 and i had this game would be like holy shit this is incredible
it's huge yeah it's a photograph a picture of a bretta the magician's daughter oh strawberry
i am so happy here take this disc i worked hard finally finally that it will open any heart
it didn't work for me maybe it will work for you finally red strawberry come here
i care what the fuck was that weird all right i got the disc there's definitely going to be a
magic piece down in that dungeon whatever it is and but first of all i'm going to go get this done
i'm going to go turn this in oh wow man feels good to complete the game one string
let's go get the uh the fruit this came out one year before mario 64 93 when was mario 64 95
96 the designer is enjoying the beauty of the model want to stab him now 96 i can be not in
the strawberry magic category this is i don't know it's like so many people playing this
it's like tons of people playing it so i did a couple other things too it's like just like a
really saturated category what's it have right now let me see 650k 650 000 watching yeah i mean i was
doing other retro games so i don't want to like it you know forest sorceress i need your help
very much i've brought the magic pink turnip with me and i need to release the magic item inside it
show me the magic pink turnip and i'll be glad to help you here you go give me a magical crystal
that was weird so pink and juicy i'll put it down here the magic to release an item
it's very difficult and you'll have to help me oh come on what do you what do i need to do now
strawberry even the most talented magicians in the world sometimes need help from less talented
magicians but on a different subject less talented i'll let you in on a big secret
abra does not know the magic of the pink turnip and my specialty is in the magic of release
so it's a good thing you've come to me all the items in this room can put together the magic
to release an item however in order to know what items are needed for the pink turnip
i have to close my eyes and dream the items will soon appear in my dream
you can help me by looking into my dream and try to remember the items that appeared in it
then bring them to me from the cubby holes on the wall this must be the dream i've been sitting on
my balls for a long time and i just realized it if you get that if you figure that out
like i've been sitting on my balls and like i just figured it out right now
figure it out right now what was it i i wasn't paying any attention
i didn't get a single piece of it i didn't pay attention at all dude what what you what
it was rope is that rope dragon's tail it's a dragon's tail was the wheel there
the hat was there too i just didn't even look a magician's hat and the wheel the wheel
you got it one more window that's it so what the hell now that we have created the magic
we have to make it work on the turnip here strawberry the trick has succeeded the magic
item is coming out thank you very much it looks kind of rotten in the middle aren't you supposed
to be an elden ring streamer sometimes we break it up with a little bit of variety he's so scary
why i would what did i do what do you mean he's so scary i didn't do i didn't do anything since
you got here i just sit here playing the strawberry game and i was like oh my my balls hurt that's it
that's the only thing that happened it's a little weird it's a little odd that i said that but i
mean i'm it's like 10 30 at night but this guy craves brisket i wish i wish i'd imagine like
stop telling it's gross all right fine i'm just i just in case you see me go like
you're gonna be like what's wrong what happened what's wrong with them nobody be like oh i'm my
thing i hit my finger on the i have my finger hurts that'd make me a liar where is this fucking
place it's the bridge yep yep yep yeah where are you going up dude i'm trying we will know if you
lie how many royalties do i get from the joker i mean that would be pretty fucking awesome real
all right it's a mature audience stream you had to click the thing
we might be playing a game for seven-year-olds but it's uh it's a mature stream all right put
the disc in let's go work is magic and magic's work too this is well known to me and to you
hmm the door has opened let's go hmm i'll just finish end game and we'll fly over the deep dark pit
is this a cvd stream no i don't i don't look i have i stopped taking tbd teach to you on stream
in like a year and a half now i've said that like a bunch of times i'm just gonna lie but it's not
okay the door to the cave is closed i'll go and take a closer look nice this is it
this is it this is the end here this is the end firefly fairy lives in the dark she doesn't like
the light only special magic will open the cave what do you think i got in my pocket right here
ice bingo
are you guys ready we're gonna see the end of the game and discover the fairy's secret
how many days have gone by since i've been here my parents have to be looking for me
the fairy doesn't like the light and doesn't like visitors that's why she hides but when a
visitor does come she comes out disguised as a firefly and she always has some real
fireflies around her to light up the cave the secret is that the fairy's light is not
steady and as soon as she comes out it blinks for a few seconds pay careful attention ronnie
when the group of fireflies come out you have to direct your attention to the one whose light
blinks you must then follow her and catch her if you succeed
slave radigan's theme that one's blinking here she is appearing before my very eyes
how beautiful regal she is oh god oh brave ronnie i'm so pleased that you tried so hard to meet me
you are a very special boy and you have a brilliant future ahead of you
hello to you too firefly fairy you you know that that i'm ronnie of course i've been waiting for
your visit for quite some time as a matter of fact ever since you arrived in magic land
i wanted to make sure that even when you saw some glittering magic you would know how to
tell which is the real magic you have done that and you have earned this magic item here it is
yours what am i gonna be weren't we doing like a little thing at school items i have to go to
avra quickly but who cares like what you couldn't have just learned a coin trick on youtube oh you're
the dancer you're the chef you're the magician ha ha why did i have i could have just learned
a card trick or something let's go fly bird we're taking off this is it i have all the great runes
oh yeah we're coming we're getting i'm not gonna say it never mind you know i whatever thank you
very much fly bird it was wonderful flying with you you guys can say it i'm everyone hates when i
say i've enjoyed your flight if you have please tell all your friends and relatives about our
wonderful service always available to you thank you for flying birdish airways
this is where we wake up and we're coming whatever i don't i'm not gonna say it everyone hates it i'm
not gonna say it everybody hates it everybody hates it no we're going to abracadabra's house
and we're ending the game nobody knows what you're saying the other do i said we're gonna
at the end of the game it's like oh you were like in this weird limbo area and you're gonna
come out of the birth canal that's what every game right that's that's what every game is yes
the birth canal every game with a complicated ending is always like oh you're gonna wake up
you can open your eyes you're gonna be coming out of the birth canal why is he so weird it's not
i'm just i an elden ring oh at the end of the game yeah you're gonna wake up it's gonna be
gonna be you're gonna get out of like limbo you're gonna like be reborn right that's the
that's the joke i'm not speaking to that joke anymore he's high he's high as fuck i'm not
everybody's relaxed right now or i'll end stream where am i going dude have i done that like three
times tonight i feel like i have one of these days i'm gonna play a game i'm telling you it's
gonna be an elaborate big elaborate ending and it's gonna be being like reborn or something
you've never done the birth canal yes i have oh my god you're out of your mind i do it every
other game your will to find the magic was strong enough to let you succeed in the difficult tasks
you were given i can reveal to you the real secret of magic
listen to me ronnie and i can tell you that i know you are runny yes you did find magic but
that is just a magic trick it is an illusion where the audience thinks that you have performed magic
when really you have only been quick with your hands this is what rabbit owner the magician did
but what he does is not real magic the secret of real magic is in this book
and i will reveal it to you strawberry you had better listen to although i think that
you already understand most of the secret as you have already seen work and commitments are the
magic when we want something very very much we sometimes think that what we want is magic
but if we work hard and keep at it we will always reach the magic
magic land is for this you saw for yourselves you have seen that you cannot be a good magician
without studying in school to gain the knowledge that will allow you to invent things
magic is just reading books like the train designer does every kind of work has its own
special magic you've seen that with the artist the carpenter the porter and the vegetables
vegetables and magic i agree i actually agree with that it's weird
you put this little tiny little seed in the ground and it fucking expands in the ground
into an edible thing that you cannot that someone else gave you it's a fact only she could get the
magic out of the turnip you brought her you most certainly learned that you cannot steal knowledge
and use it like the student in the magician school tried to do seeing that every goal we hope to
reach is magic that requires hard work you even have to work hard to gain love that's right isn't
it strawberry but you're just using magic as to win my daughter's love i am happy that magic land
was able to teach you what we already know that's just a made-up word understand how to get magic and
use it correctly even if you are faced with several kinds of magic that your will wants
to achieve be able to choose the best magic among them for you this every noun the firefly fairy
have to be afraid even if you think that a deep dark pit separates you from your magic when you
went to the carpenter and he performed magic with the hammer hitting the nail when you went to the
chef and he performed his magic making the food that's not how it works
and get it as the vegetables did and succeeded in getting their own magic remember this too
even when things get tough you must never take the easy and short path of stealing magic like
exactly what you're doing the easy path of explaining to a child with me that everything is magic all
magic come back home even if it is hard for you we understand make no mistake we love you and
will help you will be so different going back to magic land now that everybody loves me
i want i also want to find my real goal i find the magic but just a moment i want to say goodbye
to ronnie wait he knows but they always knew that you were not me and yet they helped us
i'm going back i'm going back energy my task is to find my magic and become the best magician in
the world i'm sure you'll succeed thank you for all your help i'll miss you strawberry oh
and fortunately for you ronnie that was a real spell you're not going anywhere
you're permanently a tomato i'm not going anywhere oh here we go with the talent show this is it
what what the fuck wait they were like living carrots in the real world isn't that kind of
weird no one's asking a question of like where did all these like weird like mutated fruits and
vegetables come from this is his heart the whole time oh shit he took too much the crowd was amazed
and we're all wondering where did ronnie learn such wonderful magic but only ronnie and strawberry
knew the real magic they learned was not the one shown on stage what does that say i'm not back at
the school i i'm not at the school i didn't go back home i'm in magic world still i never went
back home that's swedish that was i liked that a lot that was cute the real magic was magic was
just replaced as a verb or what a noun for hard work but then i actually like floated a thing and
they made a magical explosion and it floated up i would try got turned into a strawberry magic was
real how would i become a strawberry i'm telling you we just need to wait a few more minutes here
and then the birth canal ending happens you're gonna come on press enter i don't think that
did anything yeah it doesn't do anything now that's it i got to the end of the disk
there's a sequel is there actually a sequel no there's not really strawberry magic there is
a sequel oh i'm definitely gonna play that at some point uh i think that's probably a good time to
end it there's an episode two of strawberry magic i'm definitely gonna play the sequel it was 11
o'clock i think this is a good place to probably stop for now i actually liked that a lot that was
really fun some of these old games are just so weird they just need to be experienced when are
we gonna come out of them what about yeah tonka construction i did not realize it's not dos game
there's a windows 3.1 game i need a virtual machine to play it so i'm gonna need to get that set up
i think i could probably install windows 3.1 on dos box and get that to work
but it's that's not technically a dos game yeah that's it that we can end here so uh the next
stream we were live yesterday today well nothing tomorrow i'll be back on tuesday seems like a good
time to go tuesday the 19th uh there's a lot of stuff that i can do there's more dos i got like
another probably 15 to 20 games and more uh this is the casino sim casino what is it called sim
casino not casino inc it's a different one it's a new one let me see i got a list here let me see
let me take a look at it any of these doing it for you what do you guys think uh we've got
blood fresh supply that's a dos game but it's a shooter so it could be pretty cool there's also
there's this car that car game that mon uh bazao mon bazow sim casino a lot of people want me to
play wobble dogs i keep seeing that pop up and recommended is it any good i'm seeing a lot of
yeses okay yeah we could maybe we'll check out a couple to uh not tomorrow on tuesday a lot of
people saying blood all right we got like three options on tuesday we'll pick one and at some
point i really do want to i'll talk to blood wig i want to see if we can set up a that elden ring
pvp night with like the kind of community trial by combat with the you know each streamer picks
like three or four champions that might take a little longer to set up but at the very least
tuesday we'll do one of those three games i just said any updates on the baseball stream it is
going to be in july the date is locked down it is confirmed i have a hard date but i want to make
sure i'll announce the hard date on tuesday i do have a hard date for the baseball stream i want
to be completely accurate with it though i don't want to give you false information
but it will be in july guaranteed confirmed it is already booked so it isn't locked down well
no the date is locked down it's it's a hard lockdown date i just need to talk to community jake
this is a few things that i want to make sure exist before i announce it what is the baseball
stream you'll see you'll see it's a big event stream you'll see yeah have an awesome night
thanks for watching i know that i've been starting later and going later recently but
i'm more i've been more active at night recently uh yeah i'll see you guys um tuesday have a good
rest of your weekend here there's another day have a good sunday of course take care of yourselves
i'll see you tuesday good night guys see you later