Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight, gonna be playing as the Pyro with the loadout that is on the screen right now, as I've been doing in the last couple of these post-commentaries.
And this video is going to be in that series of what would I add to the game, and today's gonna be for the Pyro.
Now, I'm not going to particularly add something for the Pyro, but I had an idea for a change to all the flamethrowers across the board.
Now, some of you guys are gonna probably disagree with this idea, but it's something I've been thinking of since Team Fortress 2's inception, and a lot of us know there's a lot of controversy behind the Pyro class,
especially considering WM1 and, oh my god, why are you doing this, you suck! Or, no, it's in the game, it's an actual technique, you ambush people, you hold it on them.
That is a debate that's been going on since TF2 was released, so it's not a new debate, this is not a new argument to make, but I've never really made this video before.
I never really talked about the WM1 or the, is it worth it, should it be in the game, how could you combat it, what are some changes you could do.
I've never made that video, and it kind of seems fitting that when I want to talk about the thing I would add to the game, I would talk about it right now.
So what would I add for the Pyro that is not currently there?
Well, like I just said in the beginning, I'm not sure this could be a new item or if it could be something that's added to all the flamethrowers across the board.
But for the time being, we're going to pretend that this is a brand new item, we'll just say that.
So, imagine a world where a flamethrower could overheat.
The longer you held down the mouse button, the more a bar filled up, and when that bar filled up, your flamethrower kind of goes, and you cannot do any more flames.
And the way that you cool it off is with the compression blast.
And now that would sound like a very simple change, and it is, but sometimes the simplest of changes can make some of the most drastic effects.
And I feel like adding something like that to the game will encourage people to play Pyro a little bit differently,
and make them try to pop people in the air, and do different kinds of advanced techniques, and learn how the compression blast works, learn how to pop people around.
I feel like that would be a great addition.
Now, where this thing could probably go completely and totally wrong is with ammo consumption, because as we all know, a compression blast takes quite a bit of Pyro ammo.
And if you have to spam that all the time to bring your coolant down, to bring your flamethrower overheating down, that would really suck.
So maybe there was a way, if it was at full charge, if it was at fully overheated, it didn't cost anything, or maybe it costed a lot less, and it was a smaller compression blast.
I don't know the mechanics of the game, but I want it in the game.
So if this across the board were to be implemented to all the flamethrowers, the flog would just get deleted.
So sorry, floggestinator, unless you have a compression blast added to you, you're getting deleted from the game, but no, no, seriously.
If you have any thoughts on this, if you guys have any additions, or changes, or twerks, or tweak, twerks, isn't that like a dance?
If you have any tweaks to this mechanic, or you have your own changes you'd like to make to the Pyro class, or any additions, please put them in the comments section.
I love to read those.
And I guess we're going to move on from there to talk about a second topic in this video, and it's going to cover an actual item that I would add for the Pyro.
Because this whole conversation thus far has been about a mechanic change, not really an original item idea, and I'm going to give that to you guys right now.
So my original item idea for the Pyro is a grease gun.
Now this has been thrown around a little bit, I'm pretty sure I've heard a couple people say this idea, and I really think it's pretty cool.
So instead of a flamethrower, rather than shooting flames out of this, you know, you would shoot liquid.
It would be grease, kind of like the Demoman's sticky idea, where you drop down like a grease pit, and it stays there for an indetermined amount of time.
And you could light it on fire with your flare guns.
So you could have a trap set up over on the right, like on Nucleus, so you see like a guy coming down, and you know he's going to be there.
You have a trap, you have a grease trap set for him.
Shoot it with the flare gun, and it would do a bunch more damage than just a typical flame, like if I held the flames on you.
And if you didn't feel like doing that, you could also cover people in the grease as well.
It didn't just have to lay on the ground or on a wall somewhere.
You could cover somebody in the grease, and it would have the same type of Mad Milk or Jurati effect, where it was just dripping off their body.
So you could still find spies that way, and maybe it did like mini crits if you hit somebody with a flare gun after that to do a little bit more damage.
I'm not sure, but I think the grease effect is a different mechanic they can put in the game.
That's not like anything we've seen so far.
I guess you could say like the Scottish resistance, but a Scottish resistance that you can like put on people.
I picture a cool scenario where you're getting chased by somebody, let's say another Pyro or a Scout or a Demo, or whatever class happens to be chasing you.
And you drop like a Hansel and Gretel trail of grease behind you.
Then you can light the thing up with like a gasoline fire.
It like shoots down the hallway, hits them, and they go, oh my God, they have to think of a different technique because there's fire down the whole damn hallway.
You could just run around spraying walls as like a weirdo and just light it up.
It would just be fun. It would be fun to do.
And that's obviously the most important thing, having fun and being a weirdo.
Actually, those not necessarily in that order.
Yeah, the two most important things in life are having fun and being a weirdo.
Like, no, that's not really that true, but you know what I mean.
Maybe you don't. You probably don't. I'm just crazy.
But anyways, guys, that's going to wrap up this video.
Thank you all so much for watching. Really do appreciate it.
If you have any ideas, if you want to change some of these ideas to make them better, by all means, I'd love to hear what you guys have to say.
And that's going to wrap up the video.
So I'll see you guys all next time. And of course, take care, everybody.
Grease Fire!