Minecraft, Minecraft, Minecraft.
Oops, that was the wrong one, wasn't it?
Hey, what is going on everybody?
Jerma here with a new Minecraft series.
And a lot of people have been asking me.
They said, Jerma, what happened to JermaCraft?
I know you ended it at that 10 episodes,
but are we gonna get any more Minecraft?
And here's the answer.
Absolutely, my friend.
And on the screen right now,
I'll give you a couple of lowdown of the maps and who I'm playing with.
So the map is gonna be the Frozen Caverns,
is the name of this survival map.
And I'm not sure how far I'm gonna go with this.
I'm not sure how many episodes.
I don't think I'm gonna have like 55 million episodes.
But I'm gonna get enough where you guys can see some of the funny things,
some of the highlights, some of the interesting things that happened.
And the people in this video, this is with Lepter1,
who a lot of you know of, and Italics.
And both of those links, of course, will be in the description.
Go check them out.
Two cool dudes in my personal opinion.
So what do you say we get this started?
And before I go any further, I forgot to mention,
both of these two guys, they're gonna be doing videos of this series on their own channels.
So if you want to see it from somebody else's perspective
or from a different viewpoint, then definitely go check them out.
So let's get this started now.
Everybody, I hope you enjoy the video.
And I will see you all soon.
Take care, everybody.
Zombie up here.
Oh, don't worry, take care.
The zombie's got nothing.
Oh, God.
I just said something.
Something just exploded.
That would be me.
This guy is like whooping my butt.
It's okay, I'm just collecting a ton of snowballs
from which we will make a ton.
And I mean a ton.
We've got a tag team this guy.
There we go.
Okay, we were just like hammering on that guy and he didn't die.
All right, what do we have in here?
We have some leather and we have some fishing rods.
Fishing rods.
I will fish.
We can make food.
Yeah.
We can make armor with that, can't we?
We have an Enderman up there.
Yes.
All right.
I dare you to throw a snowball at the Enderman.
Dare you.
What?
He's gone.
I don't even know where he went.
Hold on.
Oh, there he is.
Oh, this is not going to end well.
You can't double dog dare me.
I'll always do it.
No, I'm running.
Lepter is using up the fishing rod on the Enderman.
Get out of here, you tall bastard.
Jerma, you can jump and do crit hits.
Yeah.
My food.
All right, so that was good.
I've already got six rotten flesh.
All right, so before taking on hard areas, prepare yourself.
That's over here.
Oh, skeleton.
Watch out, there's a skeleton on your left.
Jump and crit this guy.
Man, we are not even going to make it out of the starting.
He is freaking out.
OK.
All right, so is there anything else that we need to know about this place?
Maybe underneath.
I'm going ice fishing, baby.
Should we go down?
But the point is we're trying to find records, right?
Right, but we also have to find supplies to live off of.
Well, I'm sinking like a goddamn rock.
Oh, God.
All right, just use the charge attacks to push them back.
Wait, what do you mean charge attack?
If you double tap, you sprint, and then if you hit them while sprinting,
it pushes them back.
I got a bone.
What just happened?
Good job luring.
Jerma ran right in there.
I used my charge and dodge.
This was a nice ice cave until that fateful explosion.
There's a sign up here, guys.
I knew I saw something earlier.
Really?
Well, look at this hallway.
This looks eerie.
All right, I'm making some more snow.
I'll be back to check on that.
There's something else in there, guys.
We'll have to go back in a second.
We'll die.
Is there?
A lot.
So it's OK.
Junction one, no records.
What does that mean?
Oh.
Start.
I got it.
Start your zone one record.
Oh, no.
Bye, Lepter.
Did you guys just both fall off?
Yes.
How am I still up here?
I'm like the stupid one of the group.
There's a hole in the glass.
Oh, I'm looking through it right now.
I'm like right below the bridge.
Stay here.
Just take this stuff and keep it safe.
OK.
Just don't fall.
Hey, guys.
There's skeletons in that tower.
I know.
Watch out.
I'm going to get knocked down by them.
It's going to be gruesome.
It's going to be like the other recording, you and I.
Oh, we should not have thrown all those snowballs.
Yeah, I need them.
Dude, those archers are just aiming for you.
You're going to get like toasted.
I'm past them.
There's a chest all the way down there, though.
All right.
So I got over to here.
I'm going to fill in any blatant holes.
So we have at least like a two block.
Are they shooting at you?
No, I'm just like throwing snowballs at them.
We need to make the snowballs into snowballs.
Don't throw snowballs.
I didn't figure that out until it was too late.
All right.
Look over there in the corner with all those.
I got over here.
Should we follow you?
Well, you can.
I mean, don't fall.
Run.
Yeah.
No, don't run.
You don't need to run.
Oh, no, don't run.
You're out of their reach.
That's not a good idea.
And watch out for the holes in the ground.
Yeah.
Watch out.
I'm filling in a two wide.
How do you make those blocks?
Is it four snowballs?
Yeah, it's a four snowball thing.
All right.
So if you guys walk here, it's black ice caves.
I have one record.
Good thing we didn't make, you know, leather stuff.
I just fell in the lava.
Yeah.
Oh, you fell in the lava?
That was that was what the was.
Oh, that was what that noise was.
Yes.
That's what that was.
I'm about to run out of food.
I got I got 13 blocks.
There's a tree down there.
That's what we need.
All right.
I'm going to get that tree.
So I'm going to fall and I'm going to die.
No, you don't say that.
I can't believe I died.
I see more of those.
Take more of these blocks.
Take some more of that ice cream.
Is that all you have?
Yeah, that's all I have.
I thought we were saved for a second.
Jerma comes to the rescue.
No.
Oh, I know.
Wait, maybe, maybe we do because I have a bunch of clay.
All right.
I got down here.
Oh, we have mine carts and mine tracks, which are useless to us.
Here we have some.
I'm going to get this tree down.
Cut this tree down.
We need to save it for Christmas.
That is a Christmas tree.
If I ever saw one, it's it's nighttime.
It's nighttime, guys.
Just let you know.
So we got to build a shelter like ASAP.
It's about to get real nasty.
We missed what you missed the block of wood up there.
Oh, look down here, guys.
Oh, you guys.
OK.
Oh, my God.
I just.
I'm OK.
Lepter.
I'm not OK.
I died.
What happened?
I dropped down on a pressure plate.
Oh, there's just like pressure bomb plates all over the place.
Apparently.
I will not.
Oh, my God.
So should I eat this bread parkour over that zombie?
What?
How hungry are you?
How bad are you?
I'm not that hungry, but I'm going to die.
He's going to make it past the creeper.
Yes, he does.
If you are going to die, then go ahead and eat it.
All right.
I'm going to eat it.
Oh, God.
That was delicious.
What did what did you eat?
What was your bread selection?
It was a piece of old stale sourdough bread.
It's all in your mind, man.
That was probably like artisan bread.
You know, that was like like cheese bread.