Alrighty, alright. Let's change in the title and we can go.
Let's see if I can get to round 50.
How's my cam? Is the cam still fucked up?
I'm not just gonna go right into it. I'm not just gonna jump into it. I need practice.
This camera.
Practice.
I'm gonna go just- I'm gonna just go here and I'm gonna go.
I lost all my points believing in you.
You can't just go right into super hard. I need this- I need like a 10 to 20 minute
get my brain going again.
I forget what half these guys even do.
Alright, let's do it.
Three o'clock.
I just read a shitty comment in a sea of handsome streamers.
Not this fucking thing again.
Did I do it? Alright, I was gonna say what the hell.
Knock that up, right?
Fuck it up!
Change the weird baby sound effect.
I can't change- It's the sounds of the game, man.
Alright, I'm feeling- I'm getting warmed up. I'm feeling the juices flow.
The baby color.
Oh, you're talking about that like frog noise.
That's actually-
That's it, right?
I don't understand that one.
How- Do you have to just keep doing it?
It has to be consistent speed.
Base cam is delayed.
Yeah, I- I could try to fix it in a minute. Hold on.
Alright, canister, juice, hat, backpack.
Canister, juice, hat, backpack.
Something in my throat.
I need a canister.
Shit, alright.
I need a hat and a back- hat and mug.
I definitely can fix it by doing something here.
Oh, shit. No, no, no. Put this back.
Okay, it's a canister.
The cockroach just keeps freaking me out.
Get that fucking cockroach out of here. It's annoying.
Baby noise is giving us suffering.
You're gonna be fine.
Oh, that's a lot.
150.
Hold on a sec.
I had- I had way more time than I thought I did.
What time is it?
Move over!
I thought I had like-
I thought I had more- I thought I didn't have enough time to do that.
I couldn't move the damn thing.
Alright, I'm good.
Got it.
That- What is-
That's one of the dwarves from the Hobbit movie.
Get it.
Baby noise is funny.
I'm not even hearing it.
My lip gloss is-
Ooh, that was close.
My game's not muted.
I know, it's like-
Okay. I don't like that one. That one sucks.
I might get to 50 on this one.
You just gotta get one of those.
Nice bitrate.
I am streaming.
I'm streaming at the maximum bitrate that Twitch allows.
Okay.
Mug, mug.
864p.
864p is the resolution, not the bitrate.
Oh, I thought we had some smart people here.
Alright, what do we got?
Red.
Oh!
Man, man.
Why don't we have 4K stream?
Because if I streamed in 4K with a 6000 bitrate,
it would look like I threw up all over your screen.
Guys, 1080p at 60fps with 6000 bitrate does not look good.
I would need-
This-
Get the fuck out of here.
Okay, it was blue, blue.
Okay, blue, blue.
1080p 30, you can-
It might-
You could do okay with.
I don't know.
I think a 1080p video at 60fps, you need like a 10,000 bitrate for that to look okay.
Don't you have 3090?
That does not really-
It's just about what Twitch has for their limitations.
I could stream Nvenc with my 3090, and I can't get out.
I can't leave.
It's still the limitation of 6000 bitrate.
I could run at slowest as possible in coding, but that doesn't really do anything.
The actual CPU preset and the Nvenc presets here-
Once you go past medium, there's really not a real discernible difference at all.
What fucking time is it?
You can go beyond 6K, you have to enable it in OBS.
I mean, I could physically do it, but it's against Twitch's guidelines.
If I strike a stream right now with like 20K bitrate,
and I would get Twitch to turn my channel off, I'd get in trouble.
What?
Can you stream with a 60fps camera?
Well, here's the thing.
I don't- The reason why my camera's not 60fps right now is because my fucking camera is-
Whatever.
You fucked me all up.
Listen, I can do it, but it's-
Look, watch what happens.
39, whatever, I don't care.
So I have to have my exposure up really high
because I don't use webcams that frequently.
I don't really care.
So my exposure has to go up, but when you let more light in,
when you pull more light into these webcams, you're opening up the iris.
So the frame rate just gets annihilated.
Ready? Watch this.
So I just turn it all off, and I have to restart the camera.
This is not going to go through here.
Here we go.
Watch this, ready?
Now the camera has to restart.
I have to restart the camera.
Well, you can blame-
So here's the thing, I've talked shit about this in the past.
I don't- I really don't know why every webcam-
Even like the UI for the webcams, like controls and stuff,
are stuck in like 2003.
Are we going to get like technology that's not based in like 2004, 2005, or webcam?
Why did they just stop developing better quality webcams?
Did they just think-
Did they realize that nobody really cares after 1080 or after like 720?
And that like an overexposed, like kind of sloppy, shitty exposure is-
I don't understand.
Why is it- Why are we stuck in 2006?
Use a DSLR?
I don't want to set up a gigantic DSLR,
and have a convoluted system to plug it into my-
So I could do a high quality camera on my stream.
I just want technology from like 2016.
Use your phone?
Look, I'm back in 60 FPS, or at least close to it.
Company has software for the camera.
Low quality camera adds to your charm.
No, I-
Look, I'm not going to set-
I'm not going to set up a setup like that.
What, for like the four times a year I turn my webcam on for more than 20 minutes?
No, I don't want to do this again.
I'm warmed up.
Don't you have the money for it?
Just because something is possible does not mean it should be done.
What, because I can like set up a DSLR over here,
and have like this elaborate-
I don't want that in my room.
No, I don't wa-
I don't want it.
I feel psycho.
I don't want you guys to see any of this shit above my face, whatever.
All right, we're going right into it.
Super hard.
All right.
Ooh, that little jump down there almost screwed it all up.
Patrick!
This guy sucks, Ernest!
Get in it!
How the fuck am I supposed to do that?
Holy shit, how did I get to 47 last night?
I have no idea.
How on earth did I do that?
Oh, Ashley's not in here.
Yeah.
Washed up from one day ago.
Part two.
NOOOOO-
I'm not warmed up at all.
I got to do one more site-
Okay.
That team sucked.
It was a bad team.
I'm not-
I was a bad team.
Now I got the good team.
I got the good team.
I'm ready to go.
Change the character noises.
I will, after like five more attempts, I promise.
Okay, I gotta lean back and relax.
I'm leaning back and relaxing.
Watch.
I had to go above.
Holy shit, Ernest, go off.
Oh, he's holding a paper airplane!
Oh, come on!
What?
Oh my fucking god, why?
Shit, some of these-
Some of these this fast are impossible.
Some of these minigames this fast are actually like not even possible with the 2D characters.
All right, we're going original.
All right, let's try this.
Are you getting better?
I gotta get-
I gotta warm up.
The ones where it's like rock the baby, they give you like a full one second.
I get like maybe a 10th of a second.
You gotta rock up like eight times.
That's the last car.
Oh my god, stop.
I'm not getting electrocuted.
I'm fine.
That's cheating?
How?
I didn't hear!
Oh yeah.
That's not fucking possible.
That's not possible.
Seriously, the time-
The wait for the beat?
Like, the fuck are you supposed to do that?
Oh, get the rhythm here.
Huh?
I want to see the clip where that hit me.
I'd like to see the hitbox.
Desync.
I'm not desynced.
It's a shitty-
Watch.
Desync.
You're a liar.
The desync is a shitty webcam that can't be in a room
that doesn't have a fucking gigantic ring light in your face.
All right, let me see, let me see.
What happened?
It's the webcam, it just sucks.
And this is not even an old webcam.
I actually don't-
I don't mind the guys going that way.
It looks pissed.
I'm pissed at webcam technology.
I have an opinion that they just made all the webcams they've ever made
10 years ago and just didn't make anymore.
Okay, the worst part about WarioWare for Switch
is because they've changed-
Because you have to be the 2D character,
it's like you move the character and like it's-
A lot of these minigames you need to take like a second to know where to move,
but like you have to move it so quickly within like a second.
That's like, how the fuck am I supposed to do that without-
Like all these minigames require you to control the 2D character jumping around.
But if you move even a small amount in that minigame,
you fucking ruin the whole thing.
Fucking GameCube one was better.
Listen to the prompt.
Okay, let me tell you something about the prompt.
You ready for the prompt?
If I screamed in your ear an action for you to do,
I scream in your ear and you have two tenths of a second to do that action.
You're gonna freak out.
You're gonna be like, what did he say?
What number?
And I'm gonna laugh at you when you get it wrong.
To like, you see what I mean?
Like, what the fuck, man?
It's like they're just moving the character around.
It's like moving the character physically across the plane.
Like, it's just like, it's-
What the fuck?
Like, I have to go up and around into the left-
Here we go.
God damn it, I tried to-
You see what I mean?
Like moving the characters around is so-
Fucking God, I hate it.
I got it.
It's this one.
Oh, needing to know like what side you have to move the character is so fucking painful.
It's like, okay, so right at the very beginning you gotta move quick,
either left or right with everybody.
So it's like, all right, what is the game?
What's going on?
And what direction do I have to hold the analog?
I had it.
Might fuck around and believe in Jerma.
Now's the time to do it.
Don't lose faith just yet.
I covered it with my face.
Yeah, I like, I'm trying just to press the button,
but moving the fuck around in this game sucks asshole.
This game's not tuned correctly to do the super hard.
The game's not tuned correctly.
With a 2D game, you gotta play with 2D characters.
The first full second is you trying to figure out what fucking character you are
and what direction you need to move and can that character even do the mini game?
This is not tuned for this.
They- This is a fucking extra mode they put on.
It was never tuned for it.
This is the one.
Hey, I'm just telling you right now, bet all your money on this next run.
Bet it all.
I'm telling you, I'm gonna get it.
Bet every cent you have.
It's so annoying.
I think some motherfuckers just go so much faster than others.
Like, do people have different fucking speeds?
Like, it's- For a game that takes one-
And that's cheating apparently.
Some people look faster than others.
This game's a six.
Let's see if it can build back and come back to like a 7.9.
Let's see if they can build it back to a 7.9 for me.
Let's find out.
He said go all in.
What's the point of having half of these characters in the game
if only three of them are any good?
Let's go.
All right, this is the team.
This is gonna be this-
This is the team.
This is the run.
Bet everything.
I- I would- Don't listen to me.
This is the one.
Bet everything on this one.
All right, this is the one.
Definitely bet on this one.
I- I- My controller got stuck.
Bet it all.
All of it.
Your whole bank account on this one.
You're supposed to do that with some characters.
Ah!
But we're lives in the ocean.
That one.
That defogged his face!
Super airplane.
Fuck it!
That character!
That character's like-
Why am I supposed to-
What are you-
What?
That character-
That character's like-
I was like-
It changed-
Okay.
Here's my complaint.
Some characters changed the actual level.
And in WarioWare,
memorizing a level is incredibly important.
And if you have a different character
and that motherfucker changes the whole level-
Oh, I don't think so!
Oh my god!
Forty fucking nine!
My god!
But he was-
Oh my goodness!
You've gotta be kidding me.
Oh my god!
It was forty nine.
You've gotta be kidding me.
The one that was like-
Oh, you're gonna shoot?
Hold on to the ring as it changes the fucking whole level.
Oh, I'm so disappointed.
Got there once, I'd get there again.
I'm going for it.
No.
Fuck the haters.
I'm going in with eighteen vote.
You're a three.
Relax.
Everybody relax.
Put every cent you own on this guy.
Why wouldn't he move his arms?
I-
Forty nine!
It's still in my brain.
Rent three.
Worst fucking character to do this with, really.
Fire you motherfucker!
What are you doing?
What?
What the hell?
Okay.
What the fuck?
You've gotta be fucking kidding me.
What?
Like, I'm pressing A and she's not firing.
Does this thing have a battery?
I've charged them overnight.
Okay, we're doing a fuckface team.
Don't care.
It's goddamn Switch controllers.
Right, it's the controllers.
Yeah, it is the controllers.
Focusing with every cent you own on this.
Every cent you have for channel friends.
Oh.
I just burped.
People are gonna get just like, pew.
Yeah, that's unfair.
Okay, what's the RNG?
What's the-
What's the fucking RNG on that one?
What's the RNG on that one?
You put Snake on top of the-
You can put Snake-
Whatever.
No, you fucking dumb donkey.
I'm just trying to move my character across the goddamn screen, dude.
I'm just trying to move the guy.
I don't-
Oh, man, hold on.
2D WarioWare.
Move guy.
Oops.
You just get stuck in this shit, like-
I-
Three, one-
I gotta start over.
It's not gonna work.
I got two more lives.
It's not gonna-
I'm not gonna do it.
Dude, I can't even fucking move.
I can't even-
Like, some of these minigames, you get like, stuck on a fucking pixel,
and then like, it's over.
You just lose.
Remember when you just had to go like this?
Or like this?
Or like that?
I know.
I can't believe I got to 49.
I'm so mad.
There was like a Satan sitting on my shoulder,
whispering in my ear, just going,
49.
You fucked it up, didn't you?
You could have just moved on.
Why can't I fucking touch-
What?!
Why wouldn't it flip up?
It flipped the other one up, but it wouldn't flip the middle one up?
I literally touched it with my head.
This is definitely not the one.
I'm not gonna be able to do it.
I can't do it.
I can't.
I can't do it, guys.
I can't do it.
Do not bet on this one.
I'm gonna lose this one for sure.
Guaranteed.
There's no way I do it.
No way.
Guaranteed to lose it.
Dude!
Dude, yes, it's so fucking annoying.
Like, you try to get over there,
and he's gonna get like-
Wrong way!
I can't even move the other way.
God, it's like the characters have made it a fucking grease.
They're gonna patch this game in like a fucking two or three weeks.
They're gonna realize this is-
Humans couldn't do this past level 50.
Is it gonna go-
Oh, shit, we need to add like an extra half second for you
to decide what way you have to run first.
I wouldn't even pay attention.
This guy's gonna get patched.
They're gonna patch this.
They're gonna realize like,
oh, why is super hard mode in this game?
It's not even fucking tuned correctly.
Okay, okay.
Yeah, it's gonna be like,
oh, we saw the streamer of this guy,
German985, twitch.tv slash German985.
We realized our absolute faults as developers.
Once he got to 47, 49,
I mean, he's like one of the greatest gamers on the platform.
It's just not possible for people to do it.
So, they'll probably patch the game,
and then they'll realize everything was incorrect.
That one's so impossible.
You can't do that one.
Just fucking why?
This game's not built to be able to play it this fast.
Oh, my God.
It's not built to be able to go this fast.
Some of these fucking characters require a full second to even do anything.
Wow, Jeremy, you kind of suck, lol.
They're baiting me.
Don't let them bait you.
But like, do you understand my problem?
Like, this shit.
It's not supposed to play in this mode.
All right, the whole game was like tuned accordingly.
This one is definitely not.
Without fucking question.
I can't believe I got 40 fucking 9.
New technique.
I'm coming.
What?
Jesus Christ, man.
Some of the characters are just not designed to play certain minigames in one full second.
So, a bunch of these characters are just not designed
to do half of these minigames in the time that Super Hard gives you.
You get my drift?
Believers crying.
Like, holy fucking moly, man.
That was going so well.
You have to have five people.
Like, why can't I just play it with one person?
Like, every other character on this list that's not a shooter flyer
requires a full second of your brain to even understand
which way you have to go to do their weird technique to complete the flip and minigame.
I almost said the F word.
That never happens on this channel.
I almost said it.
I'm really sorry.
That came really close.
But do you understand that that level in particular,
it takes a full second for all the characters to even move the water.
You go slower and you have to get like out of the fuck you have to like go around.
It's by the time you know what you're doing, it's fucking over.
How is it the characters suck?
Like, why would I put nine volt in here?
Let's put nine volt in here.
Watch.
Why would I ever use the shitty character?
There's no reason to.
You don't get extra gosh darn points for playing as nine volt.
What?
Okay.
Everyone.
Do you get it?
Do you understand why like some of these characters should never play with?
This should change the whole minigame.
Changes the entire minigame.
That's the thing about WarioWare.
It's got to be the same.
So you can fucking know what the fuck you got to do when you get it in your brain.
Like, why would you change the whole minigame?
That's the point?
I had 40 fucking nine.
Can you get past 35?
Whoa, we're going down.
You guys lost even more confidence.
Wait, hold on.
This one doesn't.
No, no, no, no.
This one doesn't count.
I'm noticing that we're going down to 35.
You guys have lost all confidence.
This is still going.
You don't have to delete this one.
We're just still going.
I had to reset that because I can't believe that I'm being taken down.
That way, I'm just going to stop that one.
Now I know what I have to go for.
It's so finicky.
It really is.
Yo, damn.
Get out of the fucking train, Wario.
God, it's like some of those are just so impossible to do in that small amount of time.
It's just needing to move these motherfuckers around like that
and like in awkward directions.
Fuck.
Make it 40.
Like having to like analog around and then touch this little area.
It's just like fuck, man.
Like this shit.
It's so finicky if you touch it.
It's like, wait.
That one's seriously that you can't fucking do that shit.
That's the stupidest one.
It takes way longer to even get over there.
That one's so dumb.
I've won.
I got it.
One, one, one, one, one.
What the fuck?
Why would they?
Dude, some of these are seriously stupid.
Like some of these are stupid.
Some of these are guaranteed losses.
I have to get it.
Do you understand how some of these are stupid and they don't make any fucking sense?
Some of them are so finicky.
What the fuck are you talking about?
Defog, defog.
What do you mean?
Like I just, what?
I swear to God, some of these mini games are just dog shit.
It's just glasses.
Morty.
Fuck that, man.
And how would you expect me?
I'm fine.
I did it.
It don't even understand what some of these want you to even do.
I feel like some of these are so strange.
It's like, what are you talking about?
Shimmy, what the fuck are you talking about?
You have a tenth of a second to figure out what the fuck to do.
Shimmy, what's that mean?
It doesn't mean punch person inside.
I'm throwing this one in the trash.
It's over.
When you have that few time to understand what's even going on, it can't be that like, what?
And the characters, oh, I am fucking furious right now.
It is on.
Some characters just, they, their movement doesn't even make any sense for the game at hand.
Some of them like move faster.
Some of them are slow.
This is the one.
Walk it in.
That one needs to be patched.
That one needs to be.
A poor carpenter blames his tools.
Yeah, a poor carpenter blames the tools.
If you give me like a rubber children's mallet toy to build a fucking house with.
My voice, it's changed.
Patch that one too.
Patch that shit too.
That one doesn't make no sense to me either.
Fill in it.
Put your fucking head over there.
Those ones are so stupid.
They're the worst.
No, I was trying to shoot the guy.
I was trying to.
Black.
Hang on.
Get over there, you fucking.
This carrot.
Why couldn't I fucking break it?
Why couldn't I break it?
You can't change the rules, Wario, where just you can't just change the rules like that.
A head bump breaks the fucking thing.
Don't change the rules on me.
I've only I didn't shoot like is the guy.
Oh, he only shoots this way.
Oh, yeah.
And I draw.
Whoops.
I didn't.
Oh, 47 again.
Oh, I keep coming so goddamn close.
Easy.
I love getting stuck on shit.
Great 2D character game in a Wario.
Fucking God.
Some of these are just impossible.
And I guess you have to live with that.
It's unfucking believable because you're going to end up getting.
Eventually, you're going to end up getting one of the mini games.
That's just like not possible with the character you're playing in the super hard mode.
You eventually going to get hit with a shitty scenario
where you can't even beat it with the guy.
I don't want to try the different characters because you like this game.
No, no, I hate it.
Actually, I think it's the worst one.
This is the worst game I played in the last 10 years, at least.
What a what a what a fucking flop.
Remember, guys, just call something a flop if you don't like it.
No, I do love this game.
I just think that it's.
I think it's fairly untuned for this particular game mode I'm trying to win.
Oh, what a fucking flop.
I'm telling you, it's going to sell fucking less than 10,000 copies.
All right, here we go.
Oh, what the fuck can't change the fucking rules.
You can't change the rules like I'm touching the what the fuck.
You can't change the fucking rules if I touch it.
Three, four.
Perfect fucking character for it.
Perfect character.
Let's go.
All right.
OK.
OK, got 73.
All right.
The game could jump back up to an 8.2.
It was six point.
It was six point two and that became an 8.2 again.
All right, good.
One more for the run.
One more for the road.
That's it.
I promise.
What a fucking flop.
Hey, beat man.
Thanks for giving me these up.
I can literally only bet 10 channel points.
Great.
Oh, I don't know what you did, man.
This is impossible.
Yeah, right.
No fucking way.
Throw that girl the trash.
I got 73 points and I have nothing to prove anymore.
I win.
That was a wicked bank some moment.
Sit in the chair.
What are you dumb?
Couldn't get 100.
It's all right.
All right.
Let's how I want to try.
What do you mean first place?
Oh, I want to try this one real raw.
This is my voice.
Holy shit.
I'm so glad I had cricket.
Cricket is the only reason why I'm still here.
Check the leaderboard.
Oh, that's probably a daily game.
You're right.
This game is really good.
What?
I don't change the rules again.
Game over.
I'm not going to get 100.
No fucking way.
I'm not putting that on me.
The title of this stream is 50.
I'm not doing 100.
These are very hard.
Although I have time, though.
Oh, I feel like I'm playing a comp.
I feel like I'm in slow motion.
I don't understand.
Now I do.
I feel like I'm talking in slow motion, too,
as I was going too fast before.
See what I mean?
Everything is too slow.
Oh, that's weird.
I've been on x10 speed for the last hour and a half.
Both of them don't fail.
Holy shit.
These are hard.
All right.
I'm going to try to get 20 on this one.
20, I'll be happy.
Then I'm going to spend a bunch of my money and leave.
I'll be happy with 20.
Holy shit.
Oh.
Oh, funny.
Got it.
That was tough.
I, this is the, this is why I don't like the game.
I don't like when they make you move and you have to.
Like, you have to move in every one of these mini games
and it's just like, fuck, I moved a little bit and I did that.
I ended it.
Last round.
Like, I start every one of these ready to go.
Grab it.
Now we're doing this one ASMR.
Okay.
Today, I'm replaying WarioWare for the Nintendo Switch.
And I'm going to be, relax you.
I'm going to be really relaxing for you.
Okay.
So what we're going to do here is I'm going to try to get these things.
And exactly what I'm going to do here is I'm going to get this thing here.
The pill has been unveiled.
It's impossible.
Literally not completable.
It's literally not completable.
I was going to scream, but I don't want to do that.
All right.
One more try.
What kind of ASMR do you listen to?
I don't.
Anyway, that, that looks good right now.
Is that avocado toast with an egg on it?
Scrumptious.
That sounds good to me.
Scrumdiddlyumptious.
What?
That's what you guys are upset about now?
Is me saying that avocado toast looks scrumdiddlyumptious?
That's, that's what you want to say is the thing you don't like?
It was awful.
I, no, it wasn't.
Holy shit.
I think it's pink.
Yeah, it's pink.
Are they calling me Ned Flanders?
Oh, how am I Ned Flanders?
Oh, they move across the screen.
Of course they do.
One more.
All right.
I'm done.
One more.
One more and then I'm going to feed my friends.
I would not be betting on this.
I have not had any experience with half these minigames.
Why would you be betting on this?
What?
I don't get it.
Last one.
Trap two.
Do I wait?
Do I have to trap two individual or trap them both at the same time?
Got to be more clear about that, please.
Stop betting.
What's wrong with you guys?
Oh, shit.
Holy moly.
That was hard.
One more.
This is actually the last one.
I swear to God.
I'm getting 20 on this one.
I would bet on this one if I were you.
I'm telling you, I would do it.
If I were in the chat right now, I would bet that I was going to get 20.
I'm just saying.
I look like my face at the end.
What?
Wouldn't that be the big one and the small one?
I'll do this one with no lips.
I'm going to be better.
Finish.
One kernel.
Oh, my God.
Empty.
Finish.
Seek shelter.
It's me.
Watch out.
Hence.
Great.
Yo.
Some of these.
Throw them in the trash.
Remove them.
Just get rid of them.
Wrong way.
Last one.
Some of those are stupid.
Just throw them away.
They don't even need to be in the game.
They're dumb.
You don't get to eat?
What's up with that?
I'm trying to make it to 20.
I don't have to make it to 20.
I don't care.
I really don't even care.
I don't even care.
Oh, my God.
These people think I care.
You think I care?
I was trying to...
Oh, I can jump up there.
These people in the chat think I care.
I don't even fucking care.
Holy shit, dude.
Like, I don't give a shit.
I don't care.
Oh, well, I'll be having pasta today.
End the stream if you don't care.
That's the thing.
That's the way you don't get.
I don't care enough about the stream,
and I don't care about not streaming for me to care.
Are you serious?
I don't care about not streaming.
I don't care about streaming either.
So what?
Balls in your court.
It's a big bunny.
Pink did not win.
Wait.
Oh, I think I got baited here.
Yeah.
No.
Perfect character for this.
One, two, three, four, five.
Oh, he didn't even care.
No, I don't even care.
Fucking frog.
I don't even care.
Oh, wait.
I'm so addicted.
I can't stop.
I know.
I'm having fun.
How am I supposed to tell the difference?
I talked a lot of shit today, but I'm not even serious.
I don't care.
Hold on.
I can do better than this.
Shut up.
I could have gone for so much longer.
I think people really actually hated that.
I could have gone for like another 30 to 40 full seconds.
I started seeing way more stop than way more cool, dude.
All right.
Let's go feed our friends.
So that was WarioWare.
That was really fun.
Ooh, legendary.
Come on.
I only got one legendary the whole time.
It's kind of horse shit.
Come on.
Legendary.
All right.
Wario.
Let's give you a present.
I'm going to assume that Wario probably likes the thing with the Wario truck.
Right?
He didn't like it.
Why wouldn't you like the truck with your face on it?
I know he likes meat and you have mission points, too.
Oh, shit.
That's right.
All right.
Let's go to...
Orbeeline.
What do you got?
What does Orbe...
The bowling pin, right?
Yeah.
I don't think Wario is capable of driving.
Okay.
Who wants the truck?
All right.
What about Mike?
Or for the guitar, right?
His favorite thing.
That's a lot of points.
I got a mission for that.
Music related.
Performance related.
I don't think anything else here.
We have a lot of sports stuff.
Baseball.
Take the baby off.
I will.
I'll take it off.
You get mission rewards at level 15 for everybody.
Oh, shit.
That's good to know.
Any more sports?
I don't think so.
Boxing, though?
All right.
What about you?
Wedding dress, right?
Yep.
Okay.
Yeah, well, I'm going to look at all this stuff.
Don't worry.
What about this red gem?
It's literally her favorite thing.
Nice.
Got it.
Okay.
What about birthday cake?
Yeah.
I got three of these.
Mood change from the beginning of the stream to now?
I mean, what?
I mean, I...
Oh, football.
Mike.
No, not Mike.
Jimmy.
What?
I didn't go on an absolute tirade and tell you guys that this is literally...
The game's awful and it was a 6 out of 10 and it was a flop.
It was going to flop.
It's just venting.
It doesn't mean anything.
I'm not actually saying that.
I like this game.
I think it's really good.
It's not a flop.
It's good.
What'd I say, though?
It's the worst game to come out in the last 10 years.
That's not...
I mean, you know that's not even accurate.
How could that be accurate?
All right.
What about video game-related stuff?
I don't know if he's going to like any of this.
Who's construction?
Trigor?
Give Ashley food?
I mean, Ashley and Wari were like red meat or something.
Okay.
What about...
I mean, what is this, like, sushi?
Ashley's favorite thing is sushi.
That's her favorite food.
I don't know.
Okay.
What about mushrooms?
Holy shit.
You like those, too.
All right.
Okay.
What about like an afternoon tea?
All right.
Yeah.
Scallion?
Boiled egg?
Don't like eggs.
Candy?
Yeah.
Grapes?
Love grapes.
Why do you look like that?
I don't know.
Ask my mother.
Is this kind of food?
Oh, tuna fish.
Are you kidding me?
Yep.
Little 15, right?
All right.
Almost there.
How about...
How about one of these?
Okay.
All right.
I'm done with Ashley.
Come on.
We're going to go through all these people.
Don't worry.
What about red?
Don't you just want to make the devil...
Don't you just want to make the devil mad?
Okay.
Wait.
Jimmy's close.
Obi-Wan is close.
All right.
Crygor is close.
How about...
I'm going to...
Okay.
I'm going to give him the crane.
I'm going to give Crygor the crane.
What about the...
You like these.
Helicopter?
No.
Painting.
Loves it.
All right.
We got him to 15.
Nine volt?
Likes the construction stuff?
All right.
Like, here's a helicopter.
He's a little kid.
That means you're going to like the truck, too, then, right?
Bicycle.
The toy truck.
The shoes.
The sunglasses, maybe.
Not a...
Probably not a cell phone.
Yeah.
Okay.
I'm not giving him the toilet.
I don't think that's accurate.
He loves bikes.
Definitely the high-tech shoes.
That's for sure.
Yeah.
All right.
Come on.
We...
I'm just going to give him the toilet.
He loves it.
All right.
I don't want to spend any more on him.
He's 15.
So who else likes the toilet that's not 15?
It's definitely Wario.
Has to be.
That's 14.
And we're just going to use...
Remember the boxing glove?
Wait.
I thought Wario liked to punch people.
Mustache catalog.
Yep.
I just got to get him to 15.
Wario 15.
Ah, just give him the other one, so he cares.
Okay.
So these remaining ones.
How about cricket?
How about deer scare?
This is soothing.
He didn't hate it, but he didn't love it.
Dumbbells?
Like training?
You're obsessed?
I mean, I'm just having fun, man.
Didn't like that one.
We'll just eat the apple core because nobody wants that.
What about the camera?
Oh, he doesn't like cameras at all.
He hates them.
All right.
Who would like a camera?
Mona?
All right.
Well, Mona, you're just literally getting all the rest of the items.
Because then I'm going to go get more money.
You like manhole covers?
Okay.
Ooh.
All right.
You like the glasses.
What about the cactus?
She seems to have liked everything so far.
She just likes everything.
Okay.
All right.
I need to go complete my quest so I get a shitload more money.
So I'm going to go back and complete my quest.
All right.
What have I got?
Oh my goodness.
Look at all this money.
I haven't come back to my quest rewards.
It's in like four hours of gameplay.
Unlock all games.
I haven't done this once.
Oh, hell yeah.
All right.
Score?
I have to have gotten something for doing 50.
Play high tech and story with the crew free earn at least 31.
Okay.
I'm going to score 46 or higher.
Play thrill ride with the crew five or at least 10 or higher.
I got to 50 in the other one.
Are you kidding me?
46 not 50.
Okay.
Well, whatever.
Clear it after spilling 30 pieces of food.
Okay.
Troll the credits.
I don't want to.
All right.
Here we go.
Ooh.
Make Wario head honcho.
Holy shit.
Oh boy.
Okay.
I mean, I've got 25,000 bucks.
I'm not.
No, no, no.
We're going to open 10 times.
Whereas do some legendaries.
I'll take it.
Come on.
Legendary.
Five stars.
What the fuck?
Yes.
I got a crown.
Five star golden crown.
That's going to be big money.
What a whale.
All right.
Let's do it.
I'm ready to level up again.
And now I'm going to level up other people to 15.
We're going to the cycle continues for at least another 10 minutes.
All right.
Who wants the golden crown?
Okay.
You need to get to 15.
Expensive vase.
Wario.
A real head turner.
Great for folks with a take charge attitude.
Well, I know you like.
No, you don't like this.
What do you like?
You like dumbbells.
It's going to be Wario.
Ashley.
Wario is already 15 though.
In the soccer ball.
Yeah.
He likes it.
What about the boxing glove?
Almost 15.
Afternoon tea.
No, isn't like it.
All right.
What about sushi?
No, what about high tech shoes?
Anything else?
I really want to get him to 15.
Football.
Golden egg.
He doesn't like sushi.
Ashley likes sushi.
Baseball.
Give him a vase.
I'll try the vase.
That was incorrect.
Worth a shot though.
All right.
What about the electric guitar?
That's all right.
We got our 2000.
All right.
What about Jimmy?
Headphones.
Crown.
Oh.
Well, there we go.
That was actually his favorite thing.
All right.
Now, what about some of these others?
We've got...
Orbulon is level seven.
Do I have anything?
I got some of their bowling pins, right?
Jimmy just clogged out of his mind.
Yep.
You like these?
No.
You like these.
How can I get you to 15?
Toilet.
I have two toilets.
Let's see.
I think I'm thinking the vase.
I'm going.
I'm going vase.
No, it's not worth it.
It's not worth it.
Camera.
Iggy bank.
No, that's Wario.
Golden egg.
Got it.
Oh, we're going to have even more money to spend.
I can't wait.
Okay.
15.
What about these guys?
Oh, Mona.
All right.
What about Mona?
Cabin crews.
Wedding dress.
Oh, yeah.
Do that again.
And the manhole cover.
That's right.
I'm not even going to need to use it.
Who else is close?
All right.
You're 15.
Anybody else have more than level one?
No.
All right.
Let's go with...
A penny.
What should I do?
Red.
Do you like...
Bases?
Do you like helicopters?
Maybe because helicopters fly?
All right.
Level nine.
And why don't you take the crane?
Why do you like construction material?
All right.
He likes vehicles.
Fine.
You just got him to a little 15.
Give me red meat.
And apple core.
He likes the apple core.
All right.
15.
Who else?
Penny?
Penny, do you like a toilet?
Yeah.
I just got to...
I'm going to feed Penny literally everything.
Even if she doesn't like it.
Because...
I need to get somebody else 15 so I give them money.
Come on.
You're going to like one of these, right?
I'm going to sleep for seven hours.
Holy shit.
This is abnormal.
Likes tea?
I'm not going to make it.
Come on.
Level 13.
One more level.
I'll get it.
Got it.
15.
How interesting.
Ha ha.
I'm just winding down, man.
I'm just like blinking like a hundred times when I say a sentence.
All right.
Let's go.
Where am I going?
Okay.
Here.
Money.
Give us more legendaries.
I want like...
Give me like four legendaries right now.
All right.
That's the last time I can do that.
I'm hungry.
Let's go eat.
Family guy whale.
Nice.
Come on.
Legendary.
All right.
Last chance.
It's all right.
I can't afford any of this.
Oh, there is actually one more thing I want to do.
All right.
So what do we got now?
We have Ashley likes one of these, right?
Yeah, the meat and the sushi.
Yeah.
I'm going to check out all the new art.
Curry sounds amazing right now.
Thank you.
I don't know.
Maybe not.
Orbulon.
Five volt.
Nine volt.
I can get up.
Nine volt loves this shit.
Give 18 volt the laptop.
Oh, yeah.
Do you like anything else?
No, he likes it.
Did you get gold in the Wario Cup?
Um, I didn't even...
I don't think I even really played it.
What's the point of raising the levels?
Um, to unlock new costumes for them and art.
Man, it's just kind of fun.
Gives you points in the Wario Cup mode.
Oh, that's kind of cool.
Change mic.
I'm going to...
Don't worry.
I'll give everybody their final costumes.
I'm just going to get rid of these.
Oh, that's too bad.
All right.
Let's see.
So we got Wario.
Look at Wario's gallery.
Cool.
Really creepy and weird.
Very cool.
Oh, look at all this.
They got all the different colors.
Phantom blue thanks to the five community subs.
Appreciate the community subs.
Kind of like, uh, shadowy Wario.
All right.
Cricket.
Cool.
Okay, now should I...
What do you...
Should I get you special or what?
I kind of like that.
No, no special.
All right.
Let's do main.
Color hair.
Green with a orange shirt and yellow pants.
Sure.
All right.
Mona, what about you?
Very cool.
Cool.
Come on, man.
I'm just winding down.
I expelled all my...
I expelled all my energy.
I'm screaming at the super hard mode.
All my energy is gone.
I beat no more heroes two hours ago.
Cool.
It is cool, but I'm just tired.
I'm relaxing.
Relax.
I like how this went from a nuclear meltdown to this.
There wasn't even...
That was not a nuclear meltdown.
It was not.
A nuclear meltdown.
That is not even close.
It was not even close to a nuclear meltdown.
Give me a break.
We did not go full nuclear.
No, we did not.
Oh, I like that.
Well, you're screaming at the game.
I wasn't screaming at the game.
When did I scream at the game?
Streamer dies playing WarioWare on a 10-day sub-a-thon challenge.
I need to listen to this.
Let's watch this.
Okay.
Get over there, you fucking...
How long is this clip?
It dies.
10-day sub-a-thon challenge.
Why couldn't I fucking break it?
Get over there, you fucking...
There is like a delay.
It's like a tenth of a second.
Get over there, you fucking...
It's because of the webcam lag.
Okay.
Well, whatever.
You got any more clips I can watch?
Sure.
Watch this one.
Okay.
I don't think this was a nuclear meltdown.
I really don't think so.
I think you guys got it wrong.
I don't consider this to be nuclear.
This was like...
This was slight irritation.
That character...
What?
That character is like...
I was like...
Some of this is clearly having a small amount of issue
with the fact that the video game was fucking poorly.
I didn't expect what was going to happen in front of me.
That's a very normal reaction to have
when there's something incredibly that you don't think is going to happen happens.
Three-year-old.
That's not a three-year-old.
I got...
I'm getting stuck because I was at level...
I was at literally episode 49,
trying to get to 50.
I couldn't do it.
That's a horrible, horrible scenario.
Here's another one.
All right.
I'm going to only watch like two more of these before I get the point.
I don't think it was nuclear.
I don't think it was.
It was like...
It was sizzling.
It was simmering.
It was simmering a little.
This shit was not nuclear.
All right.
What's this one?
That was fucking stupid.
Don't you get that?
What are you, motherfucker?
What are you doing?
What?
What the hell?
Okay.
What the fuck?
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
But watch what happens here.
She doesn't grab it.
She didn't grab it.
And she's supposed to be...
When you touch it, you put it goes on your character.
What the fuck are you, motherfucker?
What are you doing?
What?
What the hell?
Okay.
What the fuck?
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
The air blow.
All right.
Last one.
I'm not watching.
You'll see.
Watch the second channel.
You'll see this video soon.
Oh, fucking nuclear.
I don't know what this one is, but I'm gonna watch it.
This one's called the air blow psycho.
That one's kinda fucked up.
It's kinda fucked up.
Okay.
That one was like a fireball was just going towards me.
And that's the last thing I thought to do before I got liquefied.
Oh my goodness.
Holy shit, dude.
I'm at Thanksgiving dinner.
And we're sitting there as the family.
And the sun's not there or something.
It's like, oh, everyone's at the table except for like Sean.
And I'm mom.
And I spent all day doing this.
Setting up this table and everything.
And then finally, like we're in the middle of a conversation.
And like Sean comes down and fucking just in his underwear.
He goes into the fridge and starts drinking milk out of the carton.
And I just took a bite at a turkey.
That's the face that's like the holy shit, Sean.
What the fuck are you doing?
Why are you not down here?
Surrounded by family.
Uncles, aunts, cousins, relatives.
And now it's embarrassing for me now because I have to talk.
What am I going to do about this?
All right, I'm out of here.
I'm done.
Wait, let's look at the rest of these.
That wasn't even nuclear.
It was a little spicy, I will tell you.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
This is one more.
Fighting cat dog.
Fighting cat dog?
Like Nickelodeon cat dog?
I don't get it.
Did I make a Nickelodeon reference?
What's the Nickelodeon reference?
That one needs to be patched.
Are you talking about the rabbit from cat dog?
Cat dog?
You guys are in lots of trouble.
You think that you can come into my restaurant, cat dog?
Oh, fuck it is.
It's the rabbit.
It's like the bad guy.
That one needs to be patched.
That one needs to be...
It's the cat dog rabbit.
How would you even...
Oh my god.
We consider and watch these.
Maybe it was a little nuclear.
I don't think nuclear...
Look.
All right.
Well, look.
I think I've gone all year without a nuclear stream.
So whatever.
I don't even care.
I don't even care, you know?
I don't care.
All right.
Last one.
What is this?
I'm stuck on shit.
Great 2D character game in a Wario game.
It's fucking caught.
Some of these are just impossible.
And I guess you have to live with that.
What's wrong with that?
I'm stuck on shit.
Great 2D character game in a Wario game.
It's not...
All right.
I've won Batman.
This is actually the last one.
I'm...
Look.
Yeah.
I was pissed off.
I'm playing super hard nuclear mode.
All right.
If I'm going to play nuclear mode and try to get past 50 rounds on nuclear,
it's going to be a nuclear stream.
Don't you get it?
This is the last one.
And then we're going to go through the last of the artwork here.
And we're going to go from there.
What was this called?
You've won Batman?
Or I've won Batman?
I don't know.
One of those two.
Just a laugh.
Where's the one where I call it a flop?
I'm going to see that one.
All right.
Somebody link me the one where I call the game a flop.
That's the one I really want to see.
Jerry Seinfeld.
It's not that one.
He hates it.
That's probably it.
I am going to judge if this is a nuclear stream or not by this...
My interaction here.
Because I can tell that I was actually a little actually irritated during this part.
It's not that one.
Okay.
Let's find out.
You like this game?
No.
No, I hate it, actually.
I think this is the worst one.
This is the worst game I've played in the last 10 years.
At least.
What a...
What a fucking flop.
All right.
I concede it was nuclear.
I concede.
Let's get back to this.
Okay.
Oh!
Look at this artwork.
Dr...
Dr.
Chrygor.
Now, hold on.
You can't hear anything.
There we go.
All right.
We have...
Who do we have to-
He's coming to us.
We have a new wave of people who didn't kill themselvesake.
He just succeeded at his.
Why?
Alright.
Let's watch.
Oh no!
What?
That cover.
Okay.
Right away.
Oh no.
Fine.
not see oh great Ashley's art oh I'm gonna leave I'm out of here I mean don't you feel I feel like
Ashley has to be this one yeah oh Jimmy oh pretty cool cool wait this is just the same one with
Wario skip nine volt I'll go back I like the gold oh nine volt without hat was this worth the anger
um I mean the anger was not opening galleries and looking at the artwork it was to get past
level 50 in super hard that's the point of this whole second half of this stream I like that I
like that no I want I'm looking like a blue purple hair and then yeah I'm not we don't watch the
Seinfeld impression oh my god fine it's probably not even all right we're gonna watch the Seinfeld
impression when did I do it I didn't do a Seinfeld impression I did I do a Seinfeld impression
I this is the game I don't like when they make you move and you have to mmm funny this is the
game I'm a mom if you're watching I'm sorry I know my child I was gonna try to be able to keep my
energy levels in down right and enough all right who did I miss oh I said everyone freaking out
that to change Mike old Mike oh yeah sometimes it can be long it's seven hours it's fine guys
remember I'm a weekend Andy my streams are only like Friday and maybe Saturday or like Saturday
Saturday Saturday maybe Saturday Sunday I'm a bum of once or twice a week Andy now I'm I can go
for like seven hours it's fine oh wait a minute I want to see these that's my favorite because
there's my favorite character oh alright let's see I like that like that one I feel like kind
of not have you not be red who each you're almost like a different character now why can
red should is not red anymore you made an onion well whatever all right penny we got pretty cool
oh and I think I know the one I want penny to have the song oh yeah right the song
song okay hey I hate it all right so let me ruin this for you I'm gonna do it
what is it listen got her hair time in brains glasses perched up on her face
you got her hair tied up in braids oh my god oh my god yikes yeah okay there's like 10,000
people here imagine going up and singing like the national anthem of her like 10 to 20,000
people and you have an ultimate voice crack that was one of the worst voice cracks I've ever had
probably in my whole life I gotta delete the VOD I have to delete the VOD of this stream there
was that bad that was a career ending voice crack let's listen to the goddamn song I'm gonna sit
every minute and see you next week see you on Friday next week or Saturday keep an eye on the
sus thanks for watching as always it's been fun see you guys next weekend have a good week
oh yeah I'll see you next weekend have a good week guys let's turn to the wait hold on
there's anybody else I yeah give this game a rating I highly recommend both the games
you saw in today's friend there you go oh wait hold on I already did it I already did it speed
skater it's this week's Wario Cup okay all right I'll see you guys the next weekend probably
Friday or Saturday we'll do like Friday Saturday Saturday Sunday something like that you know how
that works at this point thanks for watching listen to the voice crack I kind of I don't even
know if I want to play that again on stream what are we gonna do next weekend that's a good question
I had the last two weeks the streams really kind of planned out so we'll see I'm not gonna I'm
gonna play it I need it I just want to personally hear it you got her hair tied up in braids holy
shit dude you got her hair tied up in braids got her hair tied up in braids it sounds like
somebody came behind me and just squeezed my stomach just wrap their arms around both sides
and just pushed in hard like I've been lifted out of the seat like they came and lifted me up out
of the seat and pulled and pushed into my stomach right at the end here wiggly Joe thanks for 20
community subs community subs this really was a meltdown stream well no it wasn't actually here's
my defense the first four hours of this stream was me just playing no more heroes than us hanging
out so it doesn't really qualify as a meltdown stream only the last hour or two was a true
meltdown anyways I'll see you guys next weekend take care of yourselves thanks for watching as
always good night goodbye and take care