No, this is weird. There's like four people. There's there's two two guys and two girls and they're standing inside of each other and it's really
That's weird. I guess it's because we're multiplayer so it can't animate that or something
Yeah, it's probably because it's spawning two of each thing, right? Yeah, this is freaky screw your lamp. Well, she's gonna rest
She's fighting back. Wait, you can arrest her arrest her
So how can you you got a green like police outfit on you stand out irish?
I kind of I kind of look like carl winslow from family matters
Oh urkel welcome to the police cops. We ride hard and we don't take no guff from fucking perps
Look at me standing with my ak on my fuck
Hi guys
What the fuck?
Who got this guy? Who's who's the new jack? I'm the new david sin
Stay out of your car up again. You bucked it all up. I'm god damn boston bastard. Where did we go?
I don't know how to do this
You look so dumb
The fact that you don't have a gun out too is just like
So, uh, I bought this job on ebay
All right
All right, so who who has like a I have one i'm gonna initiate, uh, i'm gonna initiate
I'll go get get to explain what we're doing to the audience. Okay, so this is a mod for grand theft auto
Before and uh, basically it means it makes it so you can be a cop and
You get like jobs as you can see. I have a call ready. We're going to it and we get our own cars and stuff
And it's awesome
All right. I I apologize that i'm in like the slowest car possible
What are you doing? I'm so god damn it. He chose vehicle transport
You could have chosen a swat car and it would have been faster than this
Okay, our sirens are doing nothing right now. Even the traffic does not respect our authority. It's all right
He's like hold on get the fuck out of the way i'm flipping my car for you guys
Uh, apparently it's down this way. Oh damn it. You missed a turn
Here i'll let you go. Go ahead. Go ahead. This thing handles like a dirty sock
gone
All right, let's go
All right. All right. We got this we got this
I'm falling informally. This is my bread and butter. Okay. It's my bread and butter. I've been on the force 16 years
I've been on this apparently the thing is just we're gonna be doing boston access
Yeah
I get a gerber for the last two hours. All right, you can call for additional backup by pressing f12. What do we need?
Oh my god
Um guys, oh shit, it's a shootout everybody get locked and loaded hold on do it. I got this
Eliminate the gang members. They're all over here. Hold on. Okay, it's auto
Nick what you got to do is is uh half press the trigger then it's freeing
Oh, we're gonna office down somebody office down. They are not moving very much. These gang bangers suck. Yeah. Yeah
I got this guy headshot here comes
It's playing it's playing music. Oh my god, this is loud. Yeah, we got him. Yeah
First ask questions. Oh, can we kick their dog? I wanted to kick their corpses. I wanted to fucking disrespect them
Where's our money? Oh, it's one over here. Good job boys. Good job. Oh, there's another one. I got another one
Yeah, I got it. I got it. I got a call. I got a call. That's a great work boy. Sorry
I hit you with my car. All right, so what's going on over here? I don't know. He he was up here
Really? Is there a guy that we need to apprehend? Is it possible he's underneath like in the subway or something?
No, no, he's in these alleyways. I think you got people
He's got a gun. Oh, you got a gun. What are you doing?
Wait
Is it this guy right here? He just fell down
I'm trying to arrest him. All right back up everybody back up
It's not arresting him. Well in that case then yeah, I was yeah
No, I don't think it works. You gotta do you gotta go do keyboard mouse for that shit
Whoa
Precinct 46 scumbag from precinct 46 class kills his own
I'm gonna use just keyboard mouse because I think the controller fucks up there like the events. Okay, fine
Yeah, listen, you gotta you gotta take him out that guy was a known criminal. All right
I was doing the world a favor by putting him out of his
fucking misery
From where I come from. This is standard issue bazooka. I don't think you know what you're saying
What i'm following you
Oh shit, i'm gonna follow you dick shit. I'm really drunk right now. So wherever you go, i'll just you don't follow you
We're both in the same boat there sucker
All right, where are we going? Where you got a call?
Oh 46 watch your ass. I told you i've been drinking i've been drinking drinking pepman schnapps all day
That you pour that in your coffee, yeah, I don't even drink coffee anymore. I just drink it out of the fucking bottle
Anybody got a call? I got a call. I got a call. Where's uh, where's uh, where's the shit? All right, I got a call
He followed me. It's down there. We're driving that car
You killer. Hey, she drove. Hey, get out the bike
You're holding up traffic. Hey
Can you fresco? I don't
The people are loading in properly
You're writing a dead guy a ticket. Yeah, right. Yeah obstructing traffic with the dead ass body
You just you really did just write him a ticket after after killing him. So if you go take a right here
Okay, and then take another right at the end of this road
Can you say it like a navigation system, please? Please take a right at this road
Please go five forgot the big bong, but whatever stop stop stop. Thank you. Stop stop stop
Please get out of your vehicle and apprehend the dickhead
Where is he? Where is he? I get an invite. He's apparently in the shop. Is he in this coffee shop thing?
I think he's in the coffee shop. Is he is he holding up the coffee shop?
Oh, it's this guy right here. No, wait, where is he? I think he is in the coffee shop. Is he holding the place up?
Yeah, he is. Oh, he's fucking up the the bartender. Damn
Hey, put your hands up. Try to this is your gig
Yeah, this guy's this guy's done
Don't kill him. Try to try to take him in come on contain the rage. Whoa, he just threw her down you come here
You're gonna fight back. I'm trying to arrest you. You have three seconds to comply three. I'm sure I shoot him in the foot
All right, you know what don't do with your shot. Oh god. I'm gonna give him a little nudge now hold this suspect
Let's see. I'm gonna frisk him. Come here. She's just sitting there taking it though
I'm gonna shoot him in his leg
Hey
Stop it. All right, uh to drive the suspect to the station. It's f9, which is my record button
Wow. All right, you know what?
You know what? Maybe we just maybe we just kill him. You know what?
I think that's probably he made his choice. He made his choice. Can you invite me back onto the squad, please?
Are you okay, honey? Let's just make sure yeah, we're not talking to you
No
What you got here
You found weapon. I found a weapon on the suspect. Whoa, okay
You can arrest her. Yeah, it was maybe it was her that was being like
Yeah, do you have the option to arrest her? I do
Arrest that bitch. So it wasn't even it was
All right. Here we go. What are you doing? Are you frisking her again?
I have to hit f9 to like it looks like you were frisking the fucking table