I'm gonna go to the official Fall Guys Twitter, and we'll see. We'll see. Okay, it is...
Stop, stop it! People are playing it. All right, let me, let me just open it. Let me see what happens.
There's other people streaming it right now. Oh shit, really? Okay, let's try.
And turn off, turn off like the fucking fantasy music. All right, I'm giving this a shot.
Got him again. I don't think you got me again. All right, pull it up. There it is.
All right, come on. Let's go. Come on.
All right, how do you play? Navigate the obstacles and race to the finish line.
Okay. Oh shit. Okay, navigate the obstacles and get to the finish line. Is there a jump? Which one am I?
Okay, there's a jump. There's a dive. These are all other players, right?
Oh, you all just got instantly eliminated by the fucking Mario thing from Bowser's Castle.
I've been playing games for 10, 100 years. Who's... I'm getting like notifications on my phone.
How do I do this? Is it a bouncy? Oh shit. All right, I'm in like, I'm in like 14th place.
What happened? This is the risky way. You gotta go the risky way. Good. I'm okay. What was that?
What was that? Is it like, is it like drifting behind somebody? Oh shit. Fall count one.
All right, what place did I make it in? I qualified. I came in 10th place.
People just can't get that thing on the ground. All right, I gotta change my,
I gotta change my title. I'm finally playing Fall Guys. Finally. Hunting for treasure chests.
Whatever. Did I make it? 32 remain. That's me. But Fall Guy 8300. What happens if you qualify?
Wait, you could be a soda can? How do you get these new things? Memorize the icons on the tiles.
When an icon is displayed on the screen. I didn't get that all of that. What does it say?
Match the icon on the screen to avoid the slime. Match the icons?
And nine. All right, so it's cherries and grapes. And so I've got to stand on whatever's on the
screen. Cherry, cherry, cherry, cherry. It's cherries. I don't get it. What? Oh, I have to
I thought I had to memorize them when it went to zero. Oh, I get it. It's that, okay. I get it now.
I get it now. What the hell? Now I can't do, am I done? Did I lose? Am I actually done, done?
Oh, shit. What's happening? Wait, did I get some points? I made it to round one. I got $85,
$43, and I'm almost level two. All right, I'm, I'm ready to go. I'm going to turn it up a little
low. Your one day game is over. See you tomorrow. Stop. I'm so glad I get to actually play. I
thought we weren't even going to see this at all today. 46 out of 60. That's it. Do people
not know it's back up? All right, now I understand. So is this randomized or is it the same one every
time? It's randomized. Okay, that's cool. Wait, I want to be the french fry guy. How do you unlock
costumes? I'm going right and I'm going to go straight and then I'm going to go right again.
I'm going left. Why do you go faster than other people?
Get up. That's just not even possible to do. I'll take fucking first place. I'll take first place.
Oh, I'll take first place. Thank you. I'll take it. First place. What did I say? I was looking for
10th. All right, now don't fuck up the rest of this. That's cool. How many rounds are there?
Struggle. When you're number one, you just sit back and just watch the rest of them. Just,
just try. Don't worry. I'll be down there next round. Who's next? Oh, you're not you. Who's left?
Oh, there's one person that didn't make it. Is it zooming in on me? How do I do a thing?
33 remain. Turn off the music. Um, there's a toucan outfit too. It seems like a lot of outfits.
Okay, this is important for me to stay in first place. Dodge the flying fruit
and race up the conveyor belt. So dodge the fruit, race up the belt. I'll be first place.
Shouldn't I be in the front of the first in the row like Mario Kart? What's this bullshit?
Shit. Right at the middle. That was right at me. That was right at me. You aimed it at me.
By the way, the bodies are hitting me. The bodies are just crumbling on me.
You know what you got to do? You got to hug one of the sides.
Shit. Come on. I got to qualify. I'm not going to qualify. 16, eight. What? How did I come in
first place and not even qualify in this one? I told you this one sucks. Oh, this is kind of
fun though is movement acceleration. Don't jump. Oh, that's good to know. I have coins to spend.
Well, let me do like four or five of them and then we'll figure it out.
Just don't jump. Keep to the sides and don't jump. When did we get in a full room of 60? Only like
30 to 50. Break through doors and race to the finish line. Some are real, some are fake. Oh,
wonderful. I like that song. That's the kind of shit that I sing in the bathtub. I like it.
Oh, right in the middle. I'm thinking one, two, three, four, five. Just count. Start at one.
Just go one, two, three, four, five. Start one, next one, two, next one, three. Watch.
One. Get out of the way. Are they all like this? I can't be in last place. There's a huge bottleneck
coming up. I kind of fell down. Good. All right. Yeah. Fuck that. I'm going. Get out of the way.
Just jump. Just do it like jump. Jive into the end zone. Get out of the way. It's because I walked
in the wrong one. I went right to the left side and it instantly put me in last place. Am I stuck
here? I walked right to the first wall. What the hell? Oh, I'm stuck. You were so bad that the lobby
broke. No, it didn't. No, it didn't. Yeah, we're good. All right. So you're saying I can buy
something. 500 kudos. Earn fame. Outfits. How do you buy outfits? Oh, wait. This is 500. Okay.
I have 12. All right. I can do ninja. I can do featured items. DLC store. Regular items.
There's be the egg. 7,000. I can't do that. You need crowns. I'm just going to get cucumber.
Oh, it's probably. I'm glad I do that. This is just green. This is a big cucumber. Have to
win at least once. You're a pickle of 2500 subs over two streams. Won't buy $7,000 worth of fake
currency. Hey, first of all, I just opened the game 20 minutes ago. He turned himself into a
pickle. Oh, I see what you're doing. Run and balance across rows of seesaws to reach the finish
line. I'm going to lose this one. So you have to balance. Jesus, the whole thing turns. Well,
we can't all go on the left side. You're going to dump me. Don't dump me. Balance it out first.
Shit. Oh no, they're going to dump us. No, no, no, no, no. It's okay. I got lucky too. I'm fine.
These people are just ruining this. I'm not going to wait around. These people,
these people are idiots. I'm going. Oh my God. I have to go this way.
Put it back up. Is there a punch? I'm okay. I'm still fine.
There is punching. All right, we've got to even this out so we can all get across.
No, somebody go on the right side, please. Oh my God. It almost didn't work. Wait, how do you do
that? Grab people. Well, how do you grab people? R2. That's kind of mean. This is the guy that was
doing it. Depending on your preference. Oh, okay. I don't think this guy even, this is just like
such a seasoned veteran. He just kind of walking around. The worst game is slime game. So many
people get knocked out. We'll see if we find it. You have to grab some ledges. How do you pull
yourself up? If I jump and hold R2, will I automatically do it or just hold up or do I
have to keep holding R2? Move between rotating rings to avoid falling into the slime. This is
what you were talking about. All right, come on. Let's go. Avoid the slime.
That's slime right there, isn't it? Can I touch the donuts? Where's this next slime? Oh,
shit. This is going to make me throw up. Okay. I'm good. This one's going wicked fast. Why?
Slime incoming. I just jumped into a slime. Slime over there. Go back.
Do they just keep going back? Get off me. Oh, I'm just trying to like kill a guy. Oh, shit.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit. How many more? Oh, you fucker. I deserved it. I know because I'm trying to push
people off the edge. I was trying to push people off the edge. I deserve it. Why didn't I do that?
I was right about to qualify for round three. I'm going to have trouble in this game because
I can't pay attention for more than one consecutive round. I will try as hard as
I can on two rounds in a row. Then by the third round, I'll start talking to you guys about an
animal I saw in the backyard yesterday. It'll be over. Here we go. All right. Let's get a full one.
Change your username to improve matchmaking. What do you mean? Obstacles. It's just obstacles. Watch
out. This one's kind of short. All right. That's going to be really hard up there. All right.
I'm ready. What animal was it? It was a chickadee. It was eating a bug. That one's spinning.
That was mean. No, don't get wedged in. Y'all can't go in at the same time.
Wait, all those people just got screwed. Are they done? Birds just pretend to be real.
What? Can we be spied on? Birds aren't real. They're just robots. Birds are spy cams. So what are
the eggs? You don't leave two Logitech cameras together and then come back in a few months and
there's six of them. I don't know how that works. Wait, use RT to grab a tail? I don't even know
what that said. I'm going to instantly eliminate. Make sure that your team has more tails than the
rest of the. What do you mean tail? We're on teams. We have to grab tails. Whose tail?
Our tails? Their tails? You got it. Got it. I don't understand. What do I get? Do I get a tail back?
Get his tail. Golden tails. Oh, you mean this guy right here. Oh, shit. I get it.
Who has one? Give me that. That's a good strategy. Just go by the mallet.
I need it. I didn't get it. We only have three tails in 30 seconds. Go get another one.
We got five. All right. I got to protect this guy. That's me. That's my guy. Give me that tail.
Oh, come on. No. No, it's us. It's us. Fuck. This game's so hard. No, that was my fucking teammate.
My fucking teammates couldn't do anything. They fucking weren't grabbing tails and everything.
I had a tail for like 10 seconds. None of my fucking teammates had a tail for more than
fucking one second, dude. Toxic. You immediately gave it. Yeah, but I didn't even know how the
game worked. You need to smash the PC in rage. I don't think this is a rage game. I think this
is a sit with your feet up on the couch with a bowl of pretzels on your crotch. Just eating
and just like kind of giggling every few minutes. I'm not sure this is a rage game,
though. We'll see. Are you watching a stoner comedy?
Kind of. No, there's too many people in the way. Good. I qualify right here.
In the middle. I have to get off of me. Go back to fucking Rugrats.
He's just trying to push people off of the edge. And that is what made your downfall.
Now I'm in first place. You put a one. Does that matter at all? By the way,
it doesn't matter at all as long as you qualify. Okay. So that's why people are standing at the
edge and just pushing every single sorry motherfucker that comes over here and just
pushing them off the edge because they just want to make sure they lose in the first round.
Okay, that sounds like fun. I want slurpy guy to make it. Oh, that's unfortunate. How many
rounds are there? Three? You get more points the better that you do. There are five. Oh boy.
I've got to do this. No, not this one. I hate this one. Wait. No, I like. Okay. This is I
fucked this one up last time. I'm not going to mess it up this time. The idea is to just memorize
where two of them are. So I'm only going to memorize where the cherries and the grapes are.
I have to look at it from the same angle. Okay. Two cherry cherry on here.
Two cherries in the corner. Bananas right there. Just I know where the cherries are.
I know where the cherries are. And I know this too, but I wait, this is the last one you see.
What does he want us to do? Jerry. I'm safe right here. I was an asshole and I'm about to pay for
it. I don't do that. I was kidding. Right. Looking for a watermelon. Don't touch me.
Okay. Grapes. Don't do it. Okay. I don't know. Okay. Watermelon grape. I know where the grapes
and I know the watermelons are. I don't know what anything else is. Oh no. Okay. I think it's over
here. Okay. It's cherries, apples and bananas. I mean blueberries. I don't know. Okay. I know
where the apples are. I don't know. I know the oranges are. Wait, is this an orange or an apple?
Yeah. Finally, I made it to the third round. First time I've ever been to the third round.
Eliminate very many people. There's still 30 people. Not this again. Oh wait. Jump and dive
through the hoops to score points for your team. I should be pretty good at this. I have to dive
through the hoops. All right. I'm going to do so well here. Watch this shit. Yellow team is about
to have like 10 to 15 points. I didn't know it did that. All right. Let's go. I'm going to go up
here. Huh? I didn't get that one. How? What? I'm staying over here. I'm going to get this one. I'm
going to get this one. I'm going to get this one. It's all right. I got it, buddy. Good. That's a
double. Don't even go for it. You're not going to. A lot over this way. I had that one. No, we're
fine. Hey, right here. I'm going to spawn right here. 37. They're coming back though. This is not
good. 38, 31, 20 seconds. Anything can happen in 20 seconds. No. Why is Brett so good?
Oh, they're not coming back. 38, 43, 38. There we go. Blue team going.
That was total zone control. Was it? Damn. Now we're down to 20. Okay. This is where it gets
interesting. Zoned. Work together to push your ball to the finish line before the other team.
Oh no. Okay. Okay. I get it. I'm on blue team. So I'm going to go on the right side.
Just be gentle. Honestly, this really should be like two people doing this.
I'm actually not doing that bad. All right. Somebody has to sacrifice themselves to get it
up here. Turn it. Turn it. Turn, turn, turn, turn, turn. Good. Keep going this way. Weave it. Weave
it. Weave it. Don't push it backwards. Weave it. It's not going to fit through there. Oh no. Oh no.
We're fighting each other. Just go. Oh no. We're going to lose.
We're going to go. Get it down the hill. What are you doing? Wait, it's these guys. They're
infiltrating us. Who's going to get eliminated? No, it's going to be red. Reds was stuck. Is that
what they kept on infiltrating? 13 remain. Is this the last event? Okay. I got to play well here.
What's the last event? Four pieces fall away when you stand on them. Keep moving and survive
longest to win the crown. What? So don't step on any pieces. Oh shit. But what about these ones?
I'm going to stay up all night. I got to, I have a plan. I got a plan. Just do it very slowly.
You can have your own spot. I don't care.
I saw him coming from my peripheral and it fucking freaked me out. He sprinted by. He was just being
an asshole. He was just trying to dump all the, I was, could have been up top still. Oh, I had it.
I was in fifth pillar. Oh, damn it. It's just these two. It's this guy. That's the guy that ran
across and just was cutting everybody off. He wins. The guy that's made it a brain matter.
Hey, good job fall guy. Three, eight, five, four. I think he's level two.
I got bubble gum. Sure. Put it on. You're doing really well. I thought I could stay up top. I
was one of two people up top and then I fell and my dumb idiot brain didn't realize that all the
other layers were going to be just ripped apart. I don't know why I was thinking, Oh, I'll be up
here for a little while. I fell through all, I fell through four layers. You got to be Pickle Rick.
No, I'm getting, I'm going, this is cotton candy. He's like, aren't these my colors?
Where's my chin? I'm more green, a little more green. Bad idea to go to the middle one. I told
you it could be a hot dog, all kinds of different food condiments and stuff. This is awesome.
That was bullshit. And I did a front flip too. Get in there. Get in there. No, no, no, no, no,
no, no, no, no, no. Oh no. Who's the last one? Oh, not you. Not you. 39. So what, what, what is
the most eliminated round one or like three? Fuck. I think this is the thing everybody hated
qualified one only. Okay. I was going to say only one fucking person qualifies.
I'm going to take this slow. Wait, good idea. Bad idea. Let's do the right way.
Wait, there's a secret over here. That's not
good. It's just like too many people that don't jump. Whoa. They bounce backwards.
I'm good. You had to jump at the exact same time. Didn't you? You had to do that. Why did we both
do it at the exact same time? The guy was just like standing there. Oh, I can be Patrick. Yeah,
I'm being Patrick. Your pretzels would be everywhere right now. No, no, no. I would make
sure that the integrity of the pretzels was completely and totally sound Patrick impression.
Okay. Uh, SpongeBob, what's that supposed to mean? I don't understand. That'll be a hundred
dollars. Please don't do that. Is this a PS4 exclusive? No, it is a PC. I'm down with the
losers. Great. Oh shit. There's a naked Patrick. I have to be, I have to be aware that I'm not
the naked Patrick. I'm regular Pant Patrick. Okay. I get hit by reverse upside down ball
Patrick. Sens Fortress. So yeah, it kind of is like Sens Fortress. Okay. Does the hot dog soup
cost like $7? You can earn it. Okay. That's cool. Is it going to choose wants to choose something?
I don't think it's might be locked out. Oh, okay. All right. Now I know what this is. I'm going to
be very, very, very serious. You know what that means? I'm going to go to the corner. I'm going
to put myself in the corner and back my tail into a, into the wall and no one will touch me
for the entire game. But I don't have a tail. Get away from him. You're not going to touch him.
We have four. Okay. I'm occupying one of their premium content players.
Can you get it? You little shit. Hey, come here. You little bastards.
Oh, who has one? Who has one? Who has one? How does red team has zero? All right. Give me a
fucking premium two cam. What? You didn't touch my back. You didn't touch my back.
You didn't touch my back. Oh, it doesn't matter. You just have to grab the person. Oh, I thought
you had to like grab their tail. I was going to say, I thought now I get why I couldn't cheese it.
Okay. I'm trying to grab their tails. I'm trying to grab them from behind.
They got carried. That's all right. Carried to first place. Grab eggs. Store them in your team's
nest. Okay. We have to get eggs and put them in our nest. Put the most eggs in your team's basket.
Oh, this is cool. I like this. I almost didn't get one. Hey, get out of here. Get the fuck out
of here. Get this guy. You're not taking any eggs. Come here. Oh, rabble rabble. Whatever.
Fuck it. I don't care. Wait, somebody do we need? Oh, he's just getting in here.
Get. Why can't I get out? Shit. Give me the golden egg. That golden egg's not getting out of here.
I will fight you to the death to keep that golden egg in here.
Don't let him get that golden egg. Stop him. Good job. Okay. Orange team has eight.
I'll let him take that golden egg out. What are they doing this? 23. Stop. They're just
pillaging us. Don't let them take them out. Get that back in here. All right. I'm going to,
I'm going to hold him. Little bastard. I'm not letting you get away with this one.
You lost quite a few there. So what was the deal with what they were? There was no more eggs on
the board. So they just desperately tried to invade our nest. It's not going to work.
All right. I remember this one. That's the point. I'm going for this one behind me.
Count is two. Oh, come on. Good. I'm going to stay right around here.
The side is kind of neglected. I told you the side was neglected. Shit. How come you're so good?
No, this red guy, the red guy. I'm standing up here. We're going to get his camera. Please
camera. Get, come on. Spawn up here. This get swollen up here. Spawn. I'm really, you're not
going to do the one spot that nobody is. Come on. I'm trying to help my 34, 35. I'm contributing
this game very much. So don't tell me I'm not carried. Yo, you mean I'm the one carrying.
I'm responsible for at least 10 points on this team, at least seven, but okay. Let's round that
up. I got to get down to the final 10. Again, here we are. Come on. This is it. I got to win
one of these. What's the final event? Ball mountain. Reach the top of the mountain in first
and use R T to grab the crown. Reach the top of the mountain. All right. I'm going straight
up the middle. Grab the crown. All right. Right at the middle or hard left going right side.
Holy shit. Nobody went right. It was a brilliant idea. Can I jump over this?
You're going to go, I'm going to get it. I'm going to get that crap.
Did that just hit me after the fact? That's okay. I'm still in it.
Oh, somebody fucking got it. Why did I get hit by the ball? The ball landed over me.
Okay. I got hit by the ball that landed like 10 feet behind me. That was a buck. Oh,
kind of like Patrick though. Wait. Oh, that was kind of cool. Watermelon. Now I'm going to be
watermelon. Watermelon Patrick. Lightning melon. Yeah. No. Purple is based. I want to do
watermelon. Wait. Watermelon's not this. What is a watermelon? That's watermelon, right? Yeah.
Do I have enough to do anything? 1300 featured items. It can be a hamburger. Get kudos. Boxer,
fish. Oh, I kind of want to be the baseball guy. Help him. Help him. Help him. Buy gems.
Baseball is top tier. You have $20,000. Spend five. I hold on. Let me. If I do this,
how much should I get? I get small kudos, large kudos. No, but I don't want to just buy a bunch
of shit. Small fall guys. Cool. Small kudos bundle. It's $10. Should I do it? All right.
I'm doing it. I do it. No. Well, everyone wanted me to do. Everyone said to do this.
Just earn the kudos. Yeah. I'm not buying anything. No. You know what? You guys almost
just got me to buy shit. All right. How do I? Is there a bigger menu? It's like a DLC store,
but where's the, I mean, regular items? Where's is this? Is this it? That's, is this how you get?
Or do you have to like buy it in the DLC store? Oh, it just rotates. Okay. Well, I need more
money. And this is a watermelon. Just refreshes. Oh, okay. What do you mean? No. I mean, the lines
are a little too dark, but it was by the DLC. I don't just to have like a hamburger. Did I get
helmet on? The outside of a watermelon is not red. Yeah. I, I know. Why am I the weird guy?
Because I'm talking about the outside of a watermelon. Watermelon. Okay. Yeah. I'm,
that's right. It's just a little too dark. Hold on. I gotta go. Um, it's just a little dark. It
needs to be green, like dark green. Just going to follow it. All right. I made up all the time. I
lost. It's not red on the outside. It's red on the inside. If you smashed me in the head with a
mallet, maybe I would open up and be red. Just follow it. Don't fight it. Just follow it.
See him had his hands out. He was like, I'm going to get you, you asshole. What happened? It was a
jump. I had to jump over that. Don't fall through the little butt crack there, please.
I can't get eliminated in the first round. You know what I mean? Like I can't.
I was too busy looking up watermelons. Whatever. I'm so, this game is so addicting because you,
I just want to win one, but it's probably never going to happen. That's how they keep you here.
You desperately want to just win one time, but it's probably not going to happen.
You'll come close, but you'll never win. I think that's just the BR marketing scheme.
Just make people come really, really close to winning every single time, but they never do.
So they keep you there. It's gambling. Yeah. It's just sitting at a slot machine. You,
you put in like 10 bucks, you lose five, you win 10, you lose four, you win two, you lose eight,
you win. It's just a slot machine. Don't get hit by the debris. All right. Which one? I'm going
in the middle. Nope. Nope. Oh shit. I didn't think it was going to be real. All right. Right.
That's fine. We just have to call desk qualify. Don't matter. It's 42 of us all in the same spot.
It's just who's lucky enough to walk by first.
It's black Friday. Oh, that's another watermelon. I have to win one of these.
Keep your balls in your area to earn points. Keep. So we have to keep our balls in
our area. So the goal, I'm going to be on offense. I just, just like a game of soccer,
I'm going to go on offense and I'm going to go like, I'm going to go drop, kick the goalie.
Okay. Here we go. Ready? I'm going to get red ball. It's red. They don't expect like three of
us to come get red. I didn't expect that. I got it. Just keep it over here. I'm going to go get a
blue ball or a red one. Blue. Nope. I'm going to, there's nobody over here at this red one writer.
I'm going for this one. There's only two people on red, two people on yellow. Let's go for it.
On the side, side, side, side. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. On the side.
Good. Keep it going. Excellent. Okay. They don't have any. I just feel like I'm playing rescue.
You play with three or four friends and one of them instantly just hates the whole game
and is destroyed. Like, yeah, dude, you picked Australia and I came over from Europe and fucking
just blacked you out. And now you have to watch us have to spend the next four hours trying to
fight each other. Although late game, having that Australia zone, that's two, that's two units
every run. That's a strategic location to have in risk. No one's even paying attention to me.
We're going to get it fucking eliminated. Hi. It's tight. I mean, over time. How did red get all
these? What happened? You were too busy talking. We're just running into each other. Last time I
checked guys, you don't play the game of chess by you smushing all of your pieces into all of my
pieces. And whoever has more pieces on the board in 30 seconds wins the game. That's how you play
chess. The guy that picked Australia won. It's actually like a really annoying place to have.
You put your troops on that, that little zone there. It's so impossible. You just put like 500
units right in the entrance. You just have Australia the whole time. Let me, I gotta get to like the top
10 again. Last game is so nerve wrecking. When are they going to have the DLC where I can just
pay to be in the final 10? You know, when are they going to invent the Disney fast pass
of this game? Right. It's like, Oh, 13 people have been eliminated and we've got one that just joined
the fall guy fast pass. You'd be hated when you, everyone would just gang up on you.
What's even possible to do this DNQ did not qualify in the first round.
Unless somebody does something real dumb. Like that guy, the guy that you just watched. Yeah,
like dude, you and me get it. We get it. Like we're the only two that aren't going to qualify.
We'll just be a fruit salad together. Is this guy disconnected? Oh, he's back. How is this still
possible? Why is it still going? Wait, I just have to beat the pineapple guy. You're throwing
for views. No, I got trapped in that windmill. I could have made it. I just was sitting there
talking to the pineapple guy and he freaked out. You know what probably happened? The guy was
probably sleeping in his chair with his pretzels on his crotch and he was just hanging out, just
stoned. And when I grabbed him, his controller vibrated and he freaked out. Whoa. Whoa. Oh,
shit. It's just drool is all over the side of his mouth. And embarrassingly he looks over and there's
a puddle of just wetness right next to his head and he just fucking puts a blanket on it. I don't
want anyone to see that. It's embarrassing. I am going to qualify this time. I'm going to just be
quiet. Quiet. No, we put too much weight on it. Why don't we just all keep it? There's a bunch
of people waiting for this to come down, but we just keep ruining it. We just keep making it too low.
No, I don't want to do it. Oh, not yet. Okay, go now. Are you trying to kill us? Only 10 people
have made it so far. It's penis music. I hate that I get it now. But you know what I'm saying?
I hate that I get it. Like how the hell do I get penis music? I'm not supposed to get that.
I'm trying to drag this guy over the finish line so he stops doing this. All right, man. You don't
have to build a farm all the way in the corner of the map. I already took your castle. Nobody
gets that shit? No, we played Warcraft 3 online back in 2002. I forgot. It's too old. I want the
soda can one. I hate this one. I mean, you could just ask the audience and just go to where most
people are standing, but sometimes the audience gets it wrong. This is boomer fruit, but eating
a banana is a boomer thing. Like eating. All right. I know what that man in the right hand
and the grapes right there. This is right, right? Come on, dude. Come on. Why push him off? Why push
him off? That was so, that wasn't even called for. That guy's probably so sad right now. He got it
right and he lost. Oranges, watermelons. Okay. Orange, watermelon, banana. I know what they are.
What's the, it's a, I didn't, there was a cherry.
I'm on the edge. I don't like being on the edge. Hey, all right. What is it?
Cherry, banana, orange, watermelon, cherry, banana, orange, watermelon, cherry,
banana, orange, watermelon, cherry. This is where the grapes. Holy shit. I don't think anybody lost.
Oh, that guy did. Oh yeah. That's the guy we would have all made it, but somebody pushed him
off the edge. And that motherfucker was on camera. You know, we saw it happen. All right.
This is the egg one. I don't like this one. It's too long. I'm going right for a gold egg though.
Golden egg. Get that golden egg, please. Good. Nice. Nice work. I'll take that egg from you.
Don't just defend. What? Holy shit. Another golden goose. Just block the game of football.
That's all this is. Don't let him get back you. Oh shit. That guy just had, he just gave them like
10 points. Get it in there. Nice work. Blue can take it. Blue has nothing. Okay. I'm all right
with this. Just defend. Get that D, get that D, the D, the D. They're going to try to get out
and just fucking stop them. Wow. Completely unguarded. This is a mistake. Defensive genius.
Defensive genius. What's up, sir? All right. We got two more, right? I gotta beat one of these.
You can throw eggs by diving, letting go. Yeah. Don't choke. Depends on what this is. Fruit shoot.
Dodge the flying fruit. Okay. You got to pick a side and just commit to dodging and not try to be
first. All right. I was already down. I had damage mitigation. Pretty good dodge right there. See
the little shimmy? No. Fucking plum. Yes. Spent right by him. That was the worst noise.
That was a car. I don't know. I'm ready to win. This is the last event. I got to win. All right.
Super mountain. I hate this shit. Someone's always better than you. The number one rule of BR is
somebody's always better than you. No matter what. There's always three people better than you in
every game. Watch out for those balls. There's one coming. They don't even look.
I'm never going to win. You can't win. There's no winning in this game.
You don't win. There's no winning. Somebody's always going to be in first place in front of
you. This is the carrot on a stick. They make sure the carrot's still there so you buy a bunch of
fucking kudos bars. Wait. I got a crown. Oh shit. I want it. What am I going to do with the crown?
Stealthy. Ooh. Boxer. I'm going to save my crown. I don't want. Yeah. I'm saving the crown.
Let's go put this on though. Okay. What do I get? Upper. Yes.
All right. I need to change to my favorite colors. The Boston Red Sox. All right. That's fine.
No pattern. I'm just going to be. Yeah. I'm going to be pink. Finally. I can stand out.
That's like Peter Griffin. I'm stopping doing that. Anytime you go like
that. That's Peter Griffin doing a funny song. I can't do that.
There are 10k people. Yeah. There are. Holy shit. There are 10k people here. Hey.
You think I'll be able to beat this new fall guys? Or do I have to come back and do this
tomorrow and try to win before I do anything else in my entire life? Like I have to win once.
They're keeping me in the casino. I have to win. Someone is as unique as me.
All right. Stop trying to go up down. I was waiting too. I was waiting and I didn't even
get it. I'm now I'm stuck forever. I'm actually not in a bad spot somehow. I just got destroyed.
All right. I'm not going up the middle. I have to be safe quickly. Quickly. I was just in the road.
Oh my fucking God. I'm so mad right now. We were all waiting at the bus stop. And for some reason,
I was waiting on the road and we were in the highway. I still did it. 36.
That guy right there. That that that chocolate mint sprinkles guy is probably so mad that he
didn't go over. He was making it his job to fuck everybody up. That dude just had both hands
over and over again. He's just smashing his fucking desk over and over again. Both hands
projecting. Whatever. Too many. Too many. Only 30 people can qualify. This is not good.
No. But we have to go to the how we do this. We just lose. Stop doing it. I'm going the other way.
I'm going the other way. You guys are stupid waiting for the bus.
The bus is always going to come on this side. Yeah. Yeah. Look at that. Everybody's like,
oh, wait, maybe we should do that too. Hey, what does that do? Why is this? Why am I? Why
have a cursor on me? Why am I selected? Somebody about to drop like a nuke on me was I don't
understand. What's this for? No. Excuse me. They all just spun on top of me. Oh, come on.
It's too slippery and we can't do it. That just saved me. Is this six of us?
Really liked getting telephragged by eight people that all respond in front of me.
Hand desk with both hands and fucking scream.
pretzels are everywhere. Oh, CBD. Nobody listened to that guy. Liar. And he's just trying to fucking
mess with me. And he's trying to defame me. First round is always not the worst.
Always the easiest. Why can't they all be like this?
Why did I fall? I was just running. I want to be dumb. Why are these people all getting thrown
over here? Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Funny. Yeah. Target the streamer. Yeah. That wicked funny.
Yeah. Of course. Right. Yup. Says German on a five up there. Yeah. Grab me. Target the streamer.
Nobody can even tell who is who. Right. Doesn't even say your name.
This might sound really weird. Don't you want to see these people?
This is the greatest compilation box of jelly bellies ever.
By the way, what happened to jelly? Jelly bellies could have really, really stepped a game up.
They decided just not to. It's been the same gross peanut butter flavor. No, no, no. Butter
flavored throw up smell induced vomit jelly beans forever. Buttered popcorn. Like if you eat that.
I'm sorry. I can't understand how they could have said like 14 words out of order.
You know what I mean though? Butter popcorn jelly bellies are just there. I feel like they're
only in there for people to make like jokes about. I don't, I don't like them. Don't all do the same
thing at once. All right. I'm safe for now. It's going faster. It's the worst thing to pick. Wait.
Oh boy. Oh boy. Oh boy. Oh boy. Oh boy. Oh boy. Oh boy. Oh boy. Oh boy.
Oh boy. Oh boy. Like jump on this one. Oh no, I shouldn't have done that. Okay. I'm good.
Like I really fucked up, but he's still alive. Why are we so good? We're all like the 11 year
olds that fall instantly. Come on. Are we all 30? Yeah, I think so. Probably fall off. Somebody
fall off. Somebody fall. There's only two more people need to fall. Fall.
Oh shit. All right. One more. We're good. Yes. It's kind of sad, but this game is
all like 30 year olds and we all think that everybody else is 10. I never thought about it
like that. Why can't we just have fun? Yeah. Why does it matter? That doesn't matter. Just
why can't we just have a good time? No, no fun. I don't like this one.
But all right. I got that off. I got that off you. Am I fucking this up? I think I'm
fucking this up. I might be messing this up for us. I'm like throwing them and they're bouncing back.
Get the golden egg. All right. We've got more blue over here. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good.
Get it in there. Good. Good. Okay. Back in the game. How much is a gold egg worth?
No. Are we going to be the team that everybody comes and just ruins?
No. I'll be defense. Fine. Get eggs in here. I'm defending this place with my fucking life guys.
Call me. Oh my God. We're so bad. This is awful. This is so bad. What do I do?
What am I supposed to do? We lose. It's over. We couldn't even get one egg to stay here.
I'll be the only guy that has one egg. What do you mean toxic? That wasn't toxic.
It was zero seconds left. Toxic. You could have won. We had two points. The people in second place
had 21. Am I going to play Minecraft today? No. Probably not going to play Minecraft for another
year. That's not true. FTK is happening in like two weeks. Sorry about that. Never mind.
Only three weeks or something. Oh, I want to make sure I say this. If you,
the reason why the DLC movie night was going to be the end of August is because when I,
I didn't really give anybody a cutoff date. I did that stream and then disappeared for two
and a half months. So now on the 23rd, that's the last time you can submit anything and please go
check out the rules. What? I got banned? No, I didn't. Am I in low priority queue? What happened?
I didn't get actually banned. Did I? No. Good. All right. I got to focus. I'm just going to put
on focus music. Uh, I, I got it. I'll do it after this. You got to go with the flow with these.
Okay. Sick. All right. Well, I'm going this way. Don't fire. Don't fire. Don't fire. Good.
Epic. Oh my God. This is so epic. Stop diving. I can't help it. I'm sorry.
That guy was just wanted to go. He didn't want anything to do with that.
You see looking at how, but what flavor would that guy be? That guy would be like this weird
raspberry cotton candy and shit. This would be like licorice, uh, mint, watermelon. They don't
have, they have all those flavors. What other flavors would you add? They have all these,
every single one of these could be a flavor. They have it in Jelly Belly.
I don't switch the subject. You're toxic. Yeah. You want to see toxic? I'll show you toxic.
Everyone just waiting with just clenched. Oh, what's he going to do? He's going to look wicked.
Fucked up. No, I don't give a shit. I'm just playing the game.
He like shook me off a little and I was, I was holding up on the
controller thinking he would go off. I'm fucking smashing my hand. Okay. I have to, I need focus
music. I don't even know what focus music is right now. I don't know. Like a dial tone.
Why can I not hear this? Why can't I hear that? I can't hear it. You can.
What's the first thing you think about when you want to focus? Um,
first thing that I want to focus on is the first thing. Um, energy, like body energy.
Not, uh, not anything too loud or. Oh, no, no, no. I just, just, just body energy, body heat.
That's what I think of when I think of like, well, how do you focus body heat?
Is there a song like, or the thing that, okay, body heat. How about Halloween farts three?
That's not a real song. And that's, I mean, maybe it is. Why is it Halloween? What's the
difference between a Halloween fart and a Christmas fart? I think I did the both the same thing.
Did you put one through an echo filter with like a pitch shift on it? He needs to center his chi.
All right. I hate this one. This one's too easy just to blow up and just lose.
Where do you think you're going? Back off.
All right. Now defense. Click the link coward. I'm in the middle of a,
of a battle Royale where every second counts. I can't click on the link right now.
Oh, and somebody just stole a golden goose from us. All right. I got,
there's two eggs over here. I got to start fighting. Just grab somebody.
Good. Don't be in last place. All right. That's good. Just defend. No one's paying attention.
Wrong guy. Oh no, they're all coming in. They're all coming in. They're all coming in our zone.
Hey, why is everybody standing around? 19 seconds. We're good. No, that's not. That's one of my
friends. Okay. All of blue team is in the red base. We did it. Toxic team kill. All right.
What do you want me to click? Why can I not hear this though? That's annoying.
Nobody just uploaded this. Somebody just uploaded this or they just titled something differently.
This is Halloween farts three. How is this? What does it mean to do with farting?
I don't understand. Wait, soccer. All right. All right. Let's go. I just fucked it up for
everybody. I just ruined everything. What? Pretty good shot. All right. Line it up. Bounce it over
here. I know that they did this. I know they did this in soccer. Watch this. Get it in there.
Now they're in trouble. Four to one. It's going to double. Get it in. Nice. I set that up.
I set that up big time. Good setup. This is bad. Blue is kind of getting destroyed.
Just whatever. No, no. Don't go chase it. We're up by six points.
Don't go chasing it. Where's the goalie? Oh, somebody's screaming right now.
I'm going to bounce back this way. Watch. I'm going to head it in there. Thank you.
Yes. Come on. Do it. Yes. No. We got to get to 10 points. Wow. That was an across the 11.
This is just sad. How come a bunch of them didn't leave like I did? Are they not children like I am?
Damn. There's only nine people. There's like an 11% chance that I just win just because I exist.
This is awesome. Okay. I'm going to let them bump their heads. Not mine.
I'm going to hit that toucan up there. Get hit. Hit him. Hit him. Hit him. Hit him. He's going to
miss. He's going to miss. Watch this. He's going to miss. He's not going to get it. He's going to
miss. I hate this game. Pigeon? Sure. Put it on. I'm the Toronto Blue Jays. Cool. I like it.
Why would I play the Halloween album again? I'm trying to find out where there are parts.
It's just every haunted house I've ever been to. There's nothing there. Wait. What? Wait.
Oh no. I've had wrong audio. I've had fucked up audio the whole stream.
Yep. My audio has been completely toast the entire stream. So I have a pair of headphones
that I have an extender for. That extender, for some reason, when I plug the headphones
into the extender, if it's not just right, it can really just screw up the entire audio.
We have muffled and shitty sounding and I feel like wiggle it around a little.
So it actually, I cannot hear what's going on there. I feel like wiggle the thing around.
Wait. Don't fall for that. Is that not true?
That really is a problem that I have and it looked like it wasn't plugged in all the way.
Oh, this is you guys are just fucking around. Oh, okay. So one of you just made this and
uploaded it. Oh, this video was uploaded in 2015. Let's see who comes in.
I'm going to try to ruin somebody's day. I'm going to try to be 41.
Is that toxic? Now I'm going to watch the guy just desperately coming and I'm going to just
walk over right when he gets right here. Is it toxic? Isn't that just part of like the
jelly bean game? That's what you, I can do this. It's toxic. I saw that right side over there.
There was like 10 people. So I'm like, no, I'm not. All right. This guy right here is doing it.
Let's see if he gets it. 37. No, where is he? Oh, I'll be a coward in that scenario. That's fine.
But on calming Fortnite music, I have to like turn the music off on this.
What is calming Fortnite music? Fortnite has a soundtrack. It does. It has a soundtrack.
But yeah, but is it something that people like actually listen to?
No. Why is this left one not going down ever again?
You saw that. What the hell was that? All right. I, that was stupid.
The thing stayed up with five rotations. All right. Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out.
I'll put on the Fortnite song. What is it? Where's the, where's the Fortnite song?
No, that's why my BRB. Preston. Fortnite music, the calm before the storm.
Is this going to work? Uh, go back. What am I doing? Okay. Let's
Relaxing gaming music, Fortnite OST. This is not haunted house music. This sounds like Halloween
music. I'm going to get a DMCA from Fortnite. What? Really? Okay. No music. Just only my breath.
That's all you're going to get. No, people are going to hate that. That's not funny.
That's just people. Like a thousand of you believe if I do that.
All right. I got to pay attention. I have to come in first. Why does this guy have the same clothes
on? That's always the worst thing in the world. You go to a Halloween party and you hope to God
that nobody else has the, I'm the adult, the adult doctor costume thing on the bag and two other
people at the party have the like nurse bag costume. What do you mean? Huh? You go to a
Halloween party and somebody's wearing the same costume that they got it out of the bag from the
like the party store. Like the costume is in a bag. Nobody understand what I'm saying.
When you go to a Halloween party and everyone's dressed up and a bunch of those people there got
their Halloween costume 40 minutes before the party and they got it out of a bag. It's just a
bag. It's got a hat, a little thing for a mask, a suit. Uh, it's just a bag costume. I know what
he said. Yeah. Wow. Why is this so bizarre? Have you guys ever been into a party store in your entire
life? You know how they have just the wall of just pre-made ready to go, just costumes in the bag.
I'm getting trolled here. What is a party store? This stuff still exists. This doesn't like something
from like the forties. This is a, the bag costume and it's Wolverine and the, the legs,
the pants are so short that they end up being like Capri's. You get like a shitty Wolverine
mask that covers half of the top part of your face. And for some reason, the arms are so baggy.
I've worn them before. It doesn't even come claws. I was in a good position until I got hit.
Okay. I'm just, what RNG is this? I'm getting hit by every single fucking one of these.
It's the music. I need music. What can I put on for music? That's not going to get my channel
fucking terminated. Am I going to have to make my own music to listen to on stream?
But on the Tekken 4 OST. All right. Now you're talking. I don't even know what this is.
Damn it. I want to play this one. Not fair. This one looks so cool. Tekken 4 full soundtrack.
This one looks fun. Have I ever seen that one? I had a shot at that honeycomb level and I really
blew it. I'm so sad. I'm going to get DMCA'd by Tekken. Not, that's not going to happen.
This is pretty perfect gaming music. Louder. It sounds like I just grabbed, this is right in the
middle of a drum solo. Oh, these sounds ruin it. No, you can't even hear it. I'll fix it.
Let's keep the momentum going. Everyone's going to be fine. Play Gex? I don't know what that is.
Shit. Shit. Shit. No, no, no, no. Don't. Please. I was the last motherfucker to cross
that finish line. All right. How do I put Gex? Please don't. Don't. That's actually going to get
me in trouble. Okay. This is just what happens when the DJ is setting up his shit. He hasn't
started doing anything yet. He doesn't start for another 15 minutes. Never play 100 Gex. It's awful.
I don't even know what that is. I don't know. I'll listen to it off screen. Oh, shit. Barely getting
these. Oh, dear. Oh, why? No, dude. It hit me with everything. It hit me every single time.
You hope I get banned. I lost. This song's kind of scary.
I feel like I have to be on drugs staring up at the ceiling for this song to make sense.
This is a main character just did drugs and is lying on bed staring at ceiling.
Way too loud. This one. Do this one. This one. I can't play things that are copyright claim.
You're going to get me in big trouble. This is hog. Fortnite. The end lobby music. I don't.
I don't want to listen. I don't care. I just, I just really, I'm just going to be honest with
you. I just, I don't, I don't care about Fortnite at all. Like I really just don't. I don't. I'm
just going to be completely honest with you. I have to be. Play this. It's not copyright.
I'm not putting that on. I don't know what that is. All right. We keep getting, I get
I lose this every time. I don't think I've won this once in the two times I've seen it.
Wait, I'm on blue team. I figured out what they are, but they're Pikmin by the way.
I can't even see the chat right now. As long as you're not in the last place, it doesn't matter.
All right. Can we seriously break this up? This is bullshit. No one's paying attention to this one.
Four. Keep it over here. Don't push it out. Don't push it out. Don't push it out.
Say, say, say, say, say, say, say, say, say, say, say, say, say, say, say, say, say, say, say, say, say, say.
Keep that in here. Get off of me. Play the, lay the spire soundtrack.
Hold on. Oh no, no. Don't get it in here. If big ball go over at the same time. Okay. Red
just, red is furious right now. Red was fine. They had four into the last two seconds.
Play this song. It's copyright free, copyright free. All right. What is it?
Tekken seven. Why, what's with Tekken? Tekken seven.
infinite azure round one this is not gonna do anything bad right
all right i'm good i made it i'm down to one of the last few have i even finished this course
why did i follow the masses what would i do that why did i do that why am i doing this
that guy just grabbed me that guy grabbed me he grabbed me right before i jumped on
and we lose what why even have a grab in the game it's just i'm gonna just fuck up your day you
i don't have no idea who you are but fuck you three people people are quitting the game
so many people left the game people like i'm gonna qualify there's only 10 people left no
oh no no no please oh no i i hate this level i was so i feel like i'd get the same i'd feel
like i'd get the same gameplay here if i just went out into my living room spun in a circle
and just sprinted in a direction i feel like i would have the same amount of fun
do it do it on stream do it and that's not to say that that's not fun right yeah you just need
to get like 10 people in the same room to do that i'm too afraid i would have stayed up wouldn't
it i thought it was gonna be everyone was so afraid to do it oh come on man 13 18 19 20 21
234 everybody just run in a circle and sprint in the direction that hit your head into a wall
all right what's next put on the put on pikmin oh you know that this host is awesome you're right
put on farting around by kevin mcleod i feel like i've heard that song before farting around i
actually haven't that's the first i've ever heard that all right can i seriously get to the last
event again i just want to get to the last event it's fun when you get there good then i mean is
is there a do good in fall guys are you sure we're all just not pieces of popcorn that are
gonna get grabbed and shoved into somebody's fucking mouth and just whoever didn't get grabbed
the last like five like burnt kernels that didn't get picked up they win the game
don't give it to them don't give it to them they want that that's what they want that's what they're
all just sitting there waiting for it i'm not gonna give it to you i'm gonna be very i'm mad
i'm not like i didn't do anything wrong get out of the way quick go in oh this is the one that
goes i've heard this before i'm not drinking on stream ever again oh great canadian fuck club
20 community subs i think other people have given shit too and i'm just stupid yeah we had 20 subs
from great canadian fuck club we had 10 from poshmeister five from unionize your workplace
five from ajax the mediocre we had the 50 dollars from weak cancels thank you then five from uh
mcnaster i don't well okay you just can't just don't fall off you don't have to come in first
you don't have to qualify it doesn't matter just make it to the top it doesn't matter i'm trying
to get ahead of people and it's just get to the top what's the point of even trying to do the
super secret jump bounce thing when it's just gonna kill you these people can all fight each other i
even care i'm just going to try to finish i don't do anything sneaky anything weird i just want to
win they all they all should have waited somebody got i have hit somebody's fucking crotch you can't
have this many people in the ball pit at the same time somebody said this level is the scrub killer
all right this is the farthest i've ever been i'm sorry dude all right easy easy there's nobody
around me get away from me don't touch me i'm okay i'm okay all right final round let's go
i need to win one please 12 remain 10 9 8 7 7 people that's it there is a 18 chance that i win
this game just because i exist all right i'm gonna win this one turn this fucking music off i don't
what is this music turn it off turn it off quiet i want complete silence the fucking button didn't
work you you all right fine fuck all of you i'm trying to make just a big trap in the middle so
what about me what about me i'm gonna get trapped oh no no i gotta go this way i'm out of stuff you
piece of shit this guy's all the way up here still come on no i tried so hard i got raspberry
cool this one is hyper why are you looking at me a playlist oh it's yakuza um all right whatever
so i i really thought i was gonna win that one when i saw that there was four people eliminated
and there's only two people left oh i really thought i was gonna be the one that i have more
space there were actually three left yeah shit i don't think it's i don't think you can win
it's like winning the lottery you always know somebody does but you don't put on cheers to you
no no no no that we are not at that drastic of a time period for that
this level the whole thing doesn't matter until right here 8302 that's me
8402 all right i'm just texting all right wisdom i played yakuza zero i've liked it but i that was
back when i was a jeremy streams one jeremy streams a game one time for two hours on splatoon cartoon
music fine i mean we're playing a cartoon game yeah i know i've heard this one a million times
i'll do it for one round and it wasn't gonna happen drop drop all right i focus i'm gonna lose
i'm not gonna qualify i'm not gonna qualify i qualified somehow always tv the best game and
it's my birthday sure happy birthday by the way this is the noid but wasn't this a pizza guy
what was a pizza hut what chain was the noid what did they get rid of him for
he used to bounce around in a pogo stick right i'll get rid of him
oh it's dominoes why they get rid of the noid what was wrong with him gotta get in the middle
okay all right cherry cherry cherry okay watermelon great great great
don't move nobody will get off my spot i do that guy almost just okay this is rugrats
this is just the rugrats theme song rugrats and seinfeld why is seinfeld the same thing
wait wait i don't know i wasn't paying attention which where where where the band i don't know i have
no idea i wasn't paying any attention at all i'm just gonna stand over here with all these people
okay orange apple orange grape apple orange grape apple orange grape i don't know what the
watermelon is just ask the audience wait why did the music just become okay come on i'm never gonna
win no sucker jump over the spinning beam and avoid falling into the slime oh i haven't done
this one yet this is a new one wait wait wait wait there's two of them there's two there's two
but there's two but there's two there's two there's two there's two oh does it go faster
i just don't want to be in the same space as everybody else oh my god i'm fine oh shit oh
shit oh shit oh shit no is it went already hold on let me just let me just go get a deck of cards
and just fucking fan it into the air and then just go find the ace am i am i doing enough like
metaphors for this game how many of them is that's like four i get them i there i'm gonna get the
fast pass this is a game made for babysitting maybe if you had 60 babies they were all playing in the
same lobby a baby land party quite a few people actually so what are we doing tomorrow what am i
streaming tomorrow i'm gonna give you some choices here i'm gonna give you a few choices the choices
are uh the chronicles of riddick uh the remake one the one that was on ps3 don't stream ever again
okay man i'm sorry okay dude i'm whatever i got to me that's that's getting to me i'm sorry dude um
shit i'm just kidding uh all right so this i got the riddick game i've got take a look in a second
super monkey ball i don't have that yet it's on the way it'll be here soon god damn it no it's i
can't even stand up oh my god i'm not gonna qualify i'm not gonna qualify it's over i don't
think i'm gonna qualify i gotta i gotta overtake a bunch of people right now or it's not happening
what the fuck happened to me no stop jumping on here no what is the song called into the ocean
by frank elbertson quick do something funny what all right fine can't quick hurry up do something
funny oh i'm sitting tied in a chair of tape job quick do something funny if your funny meter
drops below fucking 25 man i'm dead sorry dude hey hey i'm gonna win this one i'm gonna i i'm
gonna win this one i'm gonna do everything possible to win not that one though you never
get the song name that was called this was called wistful wild from pikmin 2 i know what your plan
is it's my plan too we all have the same plan i thought that was coming together i killed that
guy i just saw the propeller and then i saw blood come on hey this music is making me sad i gotta
get this sad music off you're gonna play cooking simulator oh hell yeah not right now but yeah i
will get it one's gonna spawn right here somewhere look at this empty spot come on do it do it do it
oh shit why are you guys standing around it's the whole team afk did i do it disconnect incoming
what do you mean you're very cute play this one well it's halo 2 grab the tail all right
there's not that many people right now this is a smaller group of grab the tail i have one
what's going on wait why is this me versus two people this is the final wait that's the i just
have to have a tail and i win is that you tell me that's how this is gonna play out
wait they're all coming for the tail fucking idiot hey i clearly grabbed that fucking guy
you got me here oh you just fell for the oldest trick in the book but then you fell i fell for
the oldest trick in the book yoink ah seven seconds five four three two one i win i won the
game i won i won the game i won the game i won the game i won the game i won i did it i don't feel
fulfilled at all i just i feel horrible actually i feel like that i don't feel fulfilled i need ten
more and maybe i'll it'll be close that one doesn't that one i don't feel fulfilled on that
one that one with like the servers died and like 30 people got booted wait but i got fiber internet
that means my internet outlasted them right that somebody said that that counts as a minigame i
didn't get any rewards either oh i didn't win it was a pretend win oh all right well i'm probably
gonna play ridic tomorrow that game looks insane i feel like i'm gonna have a ton of fun in ridic
it's a stealth game you gotta you gotta like break people's necks behind them and there's like a
shooter and stuff it's like a shooting game right like third person first person perfect game yeah
you should play fall guys it really sucks that the one that i'm potentially going out on
is the fake one that i didn't even really win that makes it even worse i feel horrible like
i wanted to win so bad and i didn't i i pretend one is just i don't i don't feel that i hate this
oh the service the servers are dead okay all right tomorrow that's gonna i'm that's it i'm
gonna call it here we will i'll probably do a longer one tomorrow i'm feeling probably like a
more than five or six hours stream probably tomorrow i really want to play ridic if you
log in again you'll have a crown let me is that true let me see the chronicles of ridic yeah
they made a couple of games actually they made one game then they remade it and added a dlc
campaign and just made it another game kind of a weird development story actually
and let me actually just see this do i get a crown when you start streaming five hours later
tomorrow i will probably start tomorrow around 11 to 12 pacific probably like 11 servers are still
dead damn okay all right well at least i got to play it i didn't know if i was going to get to
play this or not and i did technically win so you can take that away from me if you want you can
remove that from my gamer license that's fine but i did technically win a game all right yeah
i'll see you guys later i'll see you guys tomorrow i actually kind of like it i thought i think it's
fun i'll see you tomorrow somewhere around probably 11 o'clock pacific there's a shit
little people here and you know i'll be honest with you there's been a shit little people here
since i came back like seven to ten thousand viewers every stream now i can't even this it's
ridiculous these are numbers that i didn't think were fucking possible
so i i am shocked that this many people are still sticking around so happy you're here i hope that
you continue to enjoy it i hope we have fun because i'm shocked that there's this many people here
and i'll see you tomorrow let's run the credits i think i got this finally fixed if i didn't then
you're gonna hear me yell there was a hole i forgot about that there was an entire ai dungeon
segment of this stream i forgot it was like an hour all right here comes the credits hopefully
yeah all right but they're in the wrong spot it's okay they're spaced weirdly and they have an even
stranger font what is this font what is going on with your credits dude i don't know i'm trying
to make it work they're fucked up uh i star wars crawl no no there we go all right just pretend
that they're back there wait well then they're too small whatever yeah i i moved it down all
the way but i think but i think my layers are just screwed up oh i replaced oh i see okay i
replaced the layer that this is supposed to be behind with but like just images i don't know
what the i don't know no that was the last thing i'll see you guys tomorrow we'll play ridic if i
you know what i could just wake up tomorrow and be like now fuck that we're gonna do something else
that was fall guys ai dungeon in about 35 minutes of me being irritated that my ethernet port didn't
work hope to see it oro it was a fun stream i had fun oh ow ow ow raid oh man who's
you know you know who's streaming right now that you know i i hang out with them a lot
like in real life is orb he doesn't make an incredible orb he's a wicked good streamer
he hangs out with i see him a lot like at least once twice a year let's go go to and i'm streaming
early enough what's he doing among us what is among us i'll go say hello the game is a good game
all right you guys are all getting you guys are all getting dumped trucked on his stream
so like be nice i'll see you guys tomorrow have a good night oh mute sorry