Hey. Hey, friend. How you doing? What's going on? Give me... I'm just catching my breath. I just ran.
You guys have no idea what it's like behind the scenes. There's a lot of running. There's a lot of
running. There's a lot of... of... of... of... My drink is not ready. There's not enough ice in it.
It's crazy behind the scenes here. There's not enough ice in my drink. Shit's crazy here.
Anyways, how you doing? Jeremy, we're always on time. Not me. Let me make a tweet. We'll talk about
a bunch of stuff. Just give me a minute. BRB. Okay. Do you guys know what I'm talking about
when I say that? When you realize that you put ice in your drink and you look over at it,
there's three or four little pea-sized ice cubes and it just ruins the rest of your entire day.
It's like that and then you take a sip out of it and this shit's lukewarm. It's not even cold.
You almost get annoyed that you want to just fish those out because they're not doing anything.
I know. I'm just fucking around. Play papers, please. I've already played papers, please.
Are you guys like me? If you're like me, a drink... Correct me here if you need to.
A drink needs to be either very hot or very cold. Unless it's water. If we're talking about a glass
of water, that can be room temp. That's fine. Anything else that's not water, that shit better
be ice cold or piping hot. Yeah, room temperature water is the way that I like to drink water.
If you're not talking about what... Nobody wants to drink a lukewarm fruit punch.
Nobody wants to drink a barely kind of not really even room temp coffee or tea. No. Ice coffee? Yep.
Hot coffee? Yep. Cold fruit punch? Yep. Hot fruit punch? No. Lukewarm fruit punch? Absolutely not.
I would rather drink a hot fruit punch than a lukewarm room temperature one. Does that make me
weird? Does it? Okay. Well, whatever. Today, we were going to play... We were going to do DreadX today,
but like all things on this channel and all streams you've seen on this channel,
last second I pivoted to something else 25 minutes ago. And instead of doing that,
we're going to do that tomorrow, we're going to do something interesting.
No, I'm not going to play the Quarry. Guys, so many people have streamed that game that you
probably have memorized the entire script. I would be in the game and I would look over here and you
would just be writing dialogue as it was happening. I didn't play the last one either. I don't know.
I'd rather do DreadX than the Quarry. I have my resident sleepers on standby.
Well, you better put those away because what we're actually doing...
There is an event going on on Steam right now. It is the Steam Demo Day week. And what that means
is there are thousands, I think, or hundreds of demos on Steam. And I've got it open here.
And I'm going to scroll through and we're going to pick a random shit to play. And I'm going to
give you my real... I'm going to give you my real opinions on a scale of one to five. Five being the
best. One being decent. Kind of decent. We're not trying to discourage anybody here, okay?
One being decent. Five being great. There is... No, there is no scale. Why would I even rate them?
I'm not going to rate them. I just think it's a fun idea. We want click maps. We want click maps.
No, you're not getting click maps. It takes too long. I'll give you my honest... I'm not going
to give them a score of one through five. I'm going to give you my honest opinions of what I
thought about the demo, okay? Oh, there are a thousand of these. So we kind of have to go.
We're going to get started. I'm just going to pick out ones that I think look interesting.
I'm going to install them. We're going to go. I'm already seeing some pretty interesting looking
ones. Are you guys ready? How do you feel? You feel good? You feel good? Can I just test my noise
limiter here? It's not sound fine? Yeah, whatever. Okay. Some of these look good. Are these games
even out? No, they're coming soon. These games aren't even released yet, but there's demos for
them. This is kind of cool. What the hell's going on here? I'm actually... This is really cool. All
right, here we go. So as you see here... Hi, how are you? As you see here, we have quite the list
of games here. Each one of these has a demo, and I'm literally just going to scroll through and see
if one pops out that I think looks cool. I already got one I think that looks cool already. What's
this one? This one's a roguelike? What do you guys think? We're not going to start at one. There are
a thousand demos. We're not starting at one. I look like a fucking caveman today. I sometimes
look over here, and I catch what I look like on the preview, man. This one? This one looks kind
of cool. All right, I'm going to do this one. Wait, I can buy this? I thought it was not out.
Oh, pre-purchase. Okay. All right, so we're going to go for this one. I'm going to install it. You
guys ready? This shouldn't take too long. I've got fiber optic internet. It's taking a little
longer than I thought. It won't even launch the game. Is it ready to go? I'm killing my internet
by doing this too. Okay. What was this called? Cult of the Lamb? Where is it? Where is it? I just
downloaded it. Where the fuck is it? Steam is not down. Is steam down? Steam is not down for
maintenance. Do not say that. What the fuck? What? It's down for maintenance? It's Tuesday. Oh, come
on. The second that I turned the stream on is... Oh my god. I thought I only had one more day for
this. I did not plan this. Why is fucking maintenance day? When does it start? When
is maintenance over in like an hour? I'll play Dread X maybe. Tell us a story. It's back up?
How would it be down for maintenance and back up in fucking two minutes? God damn it. All right,
let me see. Let me see. Is it there? Wait. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Oh, tell us a story. What do
you want for a story? It's down. I still can't download anything. I did not plan this
I promise you. Restart steam. So do I need to restart steam? It's not down. It's back up for me.
When do they usually do this? Whatever. I just started. We're just gonna hang out. We're gonna
hang out. The downtime is only about five minutes. Yeah, then let's just hang out. Whatever. Guys,
it's not like World of Warcraft. They're not gonna bring steam down for like 12 hours every
day or every other day. Whatever it is. Every fucking horrible. Can you imagine if they did
maintenance every other day for 12 hours? This game actually looks kind of fun. The expansion
launch. It's every week. Yeah, it's every week. I don't know. What are you saying? Talk about.
Oh shit. That's right. This is insane. Can I just show you something? Well, I can't. I don't know
if I can show you, but this is absolutely insane. So somebody in the community and let me just be
very, very honest with you here. I've told you this a thousand times before. Nobody listens to me when
I say this, but, but there is something really cool here. Somebody in the community is a fucking
scientist and they found. Let me get, let me get it out here. I gotta get some images here. This
is fucking crazy. If you want to look into it, you can. So let me, let me read this here. So,
uh, I have something really cool to share. This is by somebody in the community.
Are they comfortable with you sharing their name? I don't want to share their name if they're not
comfortable. Uh, but anyways, they discovered a new way of isolating viruses that kill antibiotic
resistant bacteria. Somebody in this community. And the first one I discovered using this method,
I named after German. This is a fucking goddamn discovery. They have pictures of the, of the
Petri dishes and this apparently is real. And they named it like the German nine, eight, five, like
Eddie thing. I don't know what it is. Let me see if I can pull up an image here. Yeah. Let me just
show you the Petri dish. Cause we, we, we, we, we, we, we, this was shared with us. I was sitting
there going, Holy Oh my God. Take a look at this. No, it's not fake. This is real. It's the German
nine, eight, five. How do you pronounce that? So they're, they're okay with me sharing their name.
All right. Well, the name, the name, I'll give them, I'll give them the, the, the discord name.
The discord name is Jared da, Jared underscore dying discord. And they have some fucking
breakthrough medical research shit here. Like it's actually phenomenal. Uh, this is, it's
blowing me away. Take a look at this. Take a look at this. Take a look at this. Hey, take a look at
this. That this is apparently it fucking working against bacteria, uh, antibiotic,
bacteria resistant shit. This is real. No, this is not a kid in high school biology. All right.
Stop saying that. This is like a fucking doctor scientist, but no, this, uh, I'm flattered. I
really wish you'd put your name on it. I didn't do this. No, they're not pancakes guys. This is,
and I said this out loud. This community has got a shitload of doctors, a shitload of scientists,
a shitload of, uh, creative, uh, editing artists. Uh, this, there's so many people in this
community. You're all doctors and scientists and I, I, I, I'm proving it today. You need to infect
yourself with this. I just like drink this. I drink like a potion with like a bunch of,
these are not pancakes. Do you guys know anything about scientific medical research? You don't know
anything, do you? That's me in there. That's me taking care of that. I'm in there and I'm
getting all of those fucking molecules and I'm destroying them. Let me see this one.
Flooded second dilution set with the solution on it. Hold on. Is this, it's a plaque essay,
a pure, a purification. I'm not getting like gas lit, right? No, this is real. No, it actually is.
Steam's working. Well, I don't want to obviously put, I want to make sure this, uh, this person
doesn't get flooded, but I want to at least share a little bit of that because that's really cool.
Somebody found a way to target antibiotic resistant bacteria. Put your name on it,
though. It deserves to be you, not me. You guys ready? It's real. Yes, it is. You're coming. No,
it's not. It's not gas lighting. It's no, it's not. I swear to God, it's not this. I just don't want
to like blow up this. I don't want it to be like, oh my God, everybody go like that. You know what
I mean? Like it's a cool thing. I just want to share it. All right, let's go. I'm going to try
to do this again. Let's see if it works. I believe you. Okay. You ready? Call to the lamb,
install demo. There we go. There we are. Just kidding. It didn't work. Let me try a different
one. You should play smite. I actually need to get ready. I got to play smite. I got to prepare.
You don't know what I'm talking about. I'm going to potentially be in a, in a tournament for smite.
Ms. Skip is holding a smite tournament and I was very vocal about how badly I wanted to be in it.
So I got to like practice. All right, let me try a different one. And maybe it's just that one's
fucked up. Okay. How about now? Will this one work? It just takes me to the store page and then
I can't download it. All right. So when I go to this, when I click on install demo, it takes me
to the store page and then it says download and I can't download it. Same, same exact things happening
to us. Should I just open up dread X and just say, fuck it. Maybe I should restart steam. I'll try
restarting steam. This is, I like, this is cool. Just kind of hanging out, talking for a little bit.
Is it working fine now? There's music playing. It's, that's the trailer you're hearing.
The demos go away. The demos go until the 20th. So if you can't do it today, all right. Well,
I'm going to give this like five more minutes after I restart it. And if not, then we're just
going to do direct X like we were planning on doing anyways. So it's all good. It's all good.
Stretch the webcam out. It isn't kind of a weird spot, isn't it? No, I don't want to stretch it
out because it's going to screw up and I'm going to have to reset everything. I'm trying to get it
to work system. Okay. Come on. Anger foot install demo. No download. Nope. Let me try. Let me try
restarting steam again. Sunflower update. Haven't planted them. It was actually, here's the thing.
There's a lot going on in the next month or two that I was kind of scared that I wouldn't be able
to give them the attention that they deserved. So I was afraid to plant them. Oh, baseball,
baseball, baseball, baseball. We're going to talk about baseball. Yeah, whatever. I'm going to be
streaming all day today. So don't worry. I'm not going to leave in like three hours. So,
and you said it and now I'm thinking about it. I should have planted them. Yes. I have a custom
made cup of the sunflowers. Okay. Let me restart this baseball, baseball. Very important. Okay.
Listen, the baseball date has to change. It is no longer the 14th. It is not July 14th. The baseball
date is changing to July 20th. Only about six days. We had to do a lot of changes, a lot of stuff
with the venue and the, trust me, we didn't want to move it, but we had to. So only like six days
later, July 20th is a new date. I will let you know if anything else happens, if anything else
goes on behind the scenes, I'll let you know. You'll be first to know. We had no choice. And
when I say that, trust me, we had no choice. Had to do it. All right. With Steam. Open Steam, please.
I fucking hate computers. All right. Steam. God, I fucking hate computers. What the fuck is that?
All right. Come on. Does anybody confirm that it works? Otherwise I'm doing DreadEx.
What happened to this? This is five minutes. Steam maintenance. Download something on Steam
right now. I'm downloading something literally right now. It's up. I just restarted it. The
stream is going to be like seven or eight hours, guys. Don't worry. I can't believe they would have
maintenance during the big event. Can't believe it. Wait, does he really think that Steam is down?
So what's happening? What are you talking about? There's no maintenance. You guys have made it up.
No, you didn't. Why would this not be working? All right. I'm about to throw a towel in and just
play DreadEx. Okay. I'm going to give this until, so the stream has been on for 25 minutes. If by
minute number 30, we don't have some progress here, I'm going to DreadEx and I'm just saying,
fuck it, whatever. Steam has maintenance every Tuesday. But why don't they, why do maintenance?
I know that this is a North American Andy talking, right? Do maintenance at like two in the morning.
Why do maintenance at fucking four o'clock in the afternoon? One, 12 midnight maintenance or
1 a.m. maintenance means that that's what? Like seven a.m. EU, six or seven a.m. EU. That's like
eight in the morning EU. That's all right. You can wait till like eight a.m. to play. You want
them to come into the office at 2 a.m.? No, I want them to unplug the router. What do they even do?
Speaking like someone that has no idea how this system even works. To me, always, I would always
get so, all right, let's talk about this for a second while we have time. I would always get so
mad at the Warcraft, World of Warcraft maintenance because it was, I just, in my brain, it was,
they were turning on and turning off the servers. That's, that was what they needed to do. And that
was it. They just had to turn on, like, unplug and then turn it back on. But then it got me
thinking even more. What do you, what actually goes on during maintenance? Like what actually
is happening? Are they like clearing out a bunch of cash? What, what is maintenance? What is it?
What does that mean? Somebody can, can somebody enlighten me? What does that mean? When they say,
oh, every Tuesday, maintenance, what's that mean? What do they do? It's, it's, they're maintaining.
But what, what are they doing? Cash, backups, updating hardware, updating the system,
software updates, backups, hot fixes, hardware stuff. They're cleaning it with a toothbrush.
It's maintenance because in my brain, maintenance is always, oh, it's okay. What do you, what is
going on though? Are all these systems just barely functioning and every week we have to turn them
all off and it has to be a bunch of fucking crazy shit behind the scenes till they keep them on?
Oh yeah, guys, just a weekly maintenance, you know, just maintaining things, just making sure
everything works. Okay. Making sure that your stuff, your services are up. Not a big deal.
Just every, for a few hours every Tuesday, that's okay. But behind the scenes, it's like,
we are a sneeze away from everything turning off permanently. Every service we have is permanently
going to shut off. We're fucking hours away. Is that what it's, is that what it's like?
And I'm just sitting back here like, fucking turn on my game, idiot. And right now there is a guy
at like Steam, like Valve HQ, fucking running down a hallway with like a clipboard in his hand,
just like, okay, there's a fucking hundred fucking things I got to do. That system is in,
I see red. I see red. I got to go to that one now. I'm just sitting here waiting for them to
turn it on. And somebody is, is, is, is, there's a lot of drama going on behind the scenes.
Residence lever. Just relax. No, wake up. Don't relax even more. You'll fall asleep. Stay, wake
up. No, I don't want you to relax. I want you to like prep up a little. Is it working? It's been
30 minutes. Yeah, it has. All right. Does it work? Let's try. I'm going to try restarting. Come on.
Hey, hey, everyone that said the Steam is only going to be down for five minutes. It's been 30.
Okay. We're going to come on. Call to the lamb, install demo. Dude, come on. Try a different one.
I tried three already. Pick a different demo. All right. I'm going to try like a few of these.
It's all right. We're just hanging out. Don't worry. Okay. How about this one called potion permit.
Should I do this one? No, I'm clicking on install demo and it's just taking me to the store page.
Okay. So now there's a download demo and I click it and it just refreshes that game store page.
Exit Steam. I did. All right. I want to do this though. I so badly want to do this. This
will sound like a fun idea. Check your library. No, it's not there. Potion. Yeah, it's not even
here. I really wanted to do this. When I get on something, I have to do it. I can't just not do
it. Did you ban from Steam? No, I'm not. This dude's hallucinating. I am not hallucinating.
They're not even doing a demo thing. You made it up. All right. You know how I know that? No,
I did a test. I have one already installed. I did a test. I did a test. Okay. Let's go.
I downloaded one to test and we're just going to play it. Oh, fuck. Yeah. I'm excited. Let's do it.
Before the stream started, I wanted to make sure it worked. You know what? Sucks.
So before the stream started, I tested it. I got it set up. I'm going to have it like this,
check it, install. Okay. That works. I press the fucking goddamn stream button.
Steve is offline for an hour. Okay. No more resident sleepers. Are you going to make me
very upset? All right. The one that I downloaded to test, hopefully it's a good one. What should
be the best one of the night? Could be. Could be. This one's called Melatonin. We're going to try
it. Oh shit. I'm so glad I installed this one. All right. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. No more
fucking around. I'm ready. We're going. We're already going. We're going. We're going. We're
going. Where is it? Got it. No, wake up. Oh, because the game's called Melatonin. Never mind.
All right. This is a demo. This is called Melatonin. Start the demo. Let's go. Let's go.
This game contains flashing effects like lights and colors that can affect player.
All right. So we got a warning here. We got a warning right off the bat. Just be
aware of that. So how does this work? Melatonin is a rhythm game that requires precise timing
for a dreamy experience. Make sure your sound is on and avoid using Bluetooth audio, bro, bro.
Okay. Let's start with the basics. Follow the rhythm and hit the space bar on beat with the
moving circles. You're lagging. I know. I don't know why my internet's fucked up right now.
The music made it worse for me. I don't know why. Why is my internet fucked up?
It's Twitch. No, it's, I don't think so. It is. It's the fiber optic cables. I think it's, it's
whatever. What am I going to do about it, guys? Okay. That didn't feel right. Not that right.
Let's do a quick tutorial. Recognize an audio and visual cues and reacting to them at the right time
according to the rhythm. For the first lesson, pay attention to the cues. They will be hinting
for you to react on the fourth beat when the circles overlap. That went in the circle. Every
level in the game will eventually expect you to follow the cues without the visual guide.
Wait, other streamers are having connection problems? Oh, that's annoying. Maintenance,
maintenance, maintenance, maintenance, maintenance, maintenance. Okay. Follow the
cues and react with the left and right arrow keys. Left and right arrow keys. Remember,
you're having maintenance. Yeah, it's called when you sleep. You have maintenance every single day.
Your brain does maintenance every day. Okay. There must be times when you need to start
and end your reaction at different times. Hold the spacebar on the third beat and let go on the
fourth. Oh, all right. That's kind of cool. Unique set of audio and visual cues. There's a practice
mode too. Cool. If it gets too hard, you can enable the assist options. Okay. That's the end
of the tutorial. Let's go. Well, this is like animated. What the hell? Whoa. It's an RPG.
Oh my God, guys. It's an RPG. I look probably crazy. Fuck. I hate cameras. I don't want a camera
in my house. I fucking hate this. What is this? Okay. This game is called Melatonin, by the way.
The demo is available on Steam whenever the maintenance ends.
I like it. Oh shit. It's games like Rhythm Heaven. Yeah. What? All right. Let's do it. Score mode.
This is fun. Yeah. I would just keep it on games and demos because we're going to be doing a lot
of them. So, all right, this is cool. I actually like this. Let's do it. Burger. It's not cat puke
simulator. Shit. This is fucking cool. This is a good one. This is a good one. It's like Rhythm
Heaven. What are we doing out of five? This one's Melatonin. I'm going to give you a rating on it
once we can confirm with me that Steam demos are currently downloading for people. How is it? I
think I might need a little bit more time with it. I think. Happy birthday to my friend Aaron.
Happy birthday, Aaron. The internet sucks. I don't know what's going on. Twitch's servers are fucked.
All right. Cool. That was cool. So, let's go. There's another one too. I want to do the other one.
The demo has what? Probably two, three levels. Whoa. This internet is really making me angry.
Oh, what the hell? Sick. I'm going to get 100 on this one. Use the chip. Yeah. And then
freak out because you want to get it out of the machine before it makes the sound.
It's like here it is. It's in there. Please remove card. Got it. And if it goes through one cycle of
you fucked up and you're really embarrassed and like it's an anxiety time. What? Just buy it. Wait,
what's going on? Restart. Is this right? Oh, I got it. And it's almost like I can tell when somebody's
judging the amount of as I had. Pause it so I can talk. I've put it in there before at the
grocery store, at Target, whatever. Best Buy doesn't matter. And you put a bag into the cart
and you hear, oh fuck. The second time it's like you fucked up, right? The second time it's like
that was you caused that problem. And if it happens a third time, it's almost like you can
feel the entire store all at the same time looking like get your fucking card. I hate it.
Yeah, I hate it. I don't like it. I make it like a nice sound, right? If the sound wasn't
like an iPhone alarm, I'm sure it would be fine. But restart, restart, restart. I get it. Oh,
Jeremy explaining. Imagine you were so rich that you buying millions of dollars in merchandise
is a fucking mini game. Can you imagine sitting there and they're like, wait, wait, hold on.
Be like, you're a dick. You're a fucking asshole. I would not do that. Still can't download demos.
Jerma does this at Applebee's. What does that even mean? I don't know. I don't know what that
means. I'm trying. I went after you said that I thought it was funny. But then at the same time,
I'm like, what is that person talking about? You get a bill at the very end. Does that mean
that I'm leaving and coming back and just, Hey, can you charge more breadsticks? Can I have another
bloom and onion? I just want to, you don't even swipe. They take your card and walk away with it.
Maybe I should try changing his Twitch servers. I might try that stream is going to turn off
potentially, but we'll see if it doesn't get better. I'll try a different server. It looks
like we're dropping 2% of all frames. I don't like that. This game's really cool. I love rhythm
heaven. And this is a rhythm heaven game for PC. Let's go. Dun dun dun dun dun dun dun.
The game is called melatonin on steam. It's a demo available. This is the steam demo day early.
Wait, shoot. Where? Oh, melatonin. The game is melatonin. Should I put it in like the title or
something? All right, I'm going to try. Okay, here we go. I'm going to let me see something here.
Let me I gotta test something. I'm gonna see. Let me do this. I'm gonna see if I can change
Twitch server because last time this problem happened when Twitch was having server problems,
I switched to a different server and I found one that worked. So you want to try it? I think I
could try it. I'm dropping a lot of frames, 2.5% of every frame. I'll try that. Games are now
downloadable. Perfect. So let's restart. Let's just redo the stream, right? I haven't even gone live
yet. Let's just pretend I haven't gone live yet. You know what I'm saying? Okay, let's see.
What's it? Let me check. He's late. Yeah, just pretend I was late. Just tell everybody I was
late today by a lot. Let me see if this helps. Yeah, honestly, just pretend I was late. And by
the way, I'm going to be really mad if one person is not here when I come back in like a minute and
a half. Let me try this. Let me see if this helps. I'll be right back. Give me two seconds.
It's going to restart. Try a different server. Fuck. Fuck. I'll be right back. Let's see if it
worked. I went to a different server. I'm sorry I'm wicked late. Oh, hold on. Let me do the...
No, who cares about the intro? No, it didn't work. Didn't work. Got worse. Fuck. No. Oh, come on.
Really? Oh, come on. We're just gonna have to deal with the other server because now it's worse.
Maintenance! Maintenance! Maintenance! Maintenance! Maintenance! Maintenance! Maintenance!
Maintenance! I'll be right back again. We're just gonna have to deal with it. I think I'm not dropping
any more frames. I don't want to jinx it. I don't want to say it out loud. I don't want to say this
out loud. I think we're good. I ran a speed test. I tested to Twitch. I picked individual servers.
I went one by one by one. I think I got the right one. Fucking maintenance. All right. Give me a
second. I think we're good. I'm going to move a couple things around. We're not going to do
a starting screen because we already did that. Round two. That's right. Clueless. We'll see.
I'm actually kind of concerned, but whatever. He's on Wi-Fi. Wi-Fi Andy. Look at this beard.
Okay, you know those things? Where's the magnet and you drag the weird magnet hair
around the guy's face? I have magnet shavings and facial hair right now. Why am I weird looking?
What is it? Let's see. It's definitely like here and like here. You know what I mean?
Somebody said, yeah. Yeah. That's your face. I know. I'm just kidding. Welcome back, everybody.
Welcome to the show. I'm not going to tweet this stream out yet because I'm afraid to.
What's my... What's my... Why am I... I'm changing... I'm like white balance all fucked up.
Is this guy Morbius? It's the hair flip in the back. Yeah. I'm going to go line by line here.
Is this a secret stream? No. This is supposed to be a regular stream, but I got cut off a couple
hours ago trying to find a way back into the stream. And here we are. You look tired. Yeah,
tired of this shit. Tuesday maintenance on every fucking website. I'm tired of this shit. I'll
tell you that. Searching across the nation for a server I can stream to on Twitch. Late night
stream. Yeah. Well, it goes long. I don't want to go too, too long. I just want to... I wanted to
stream today. I'm so busy, right? I'm really busy. Today, I wanted to stream today and tomorrow.
I'm trying to sprinkle streams in when I can while working on the projects and stuff.
I wanted to stream today. Why do your sideburns look like pubes?
Dude, I don't know. I haven't had a haircut in... Oh, man. You freak me out. I'm going to cut these
right now. That is weird. Anyways, whatever. You're self-conscious? No, I'm really not. I'm
very comfortable in my... I'm very comfortable with my own skin. I promise. I don't care.
You should sell your hair. The fuck are you talking about? No. Never. Are you wearing a
powdered wig? That'd be kind of funny if I was. All right. No drop frames. I think we're good to
go. I think we're ready. I wonder, is it because... Is my hair going back further on this side than
it is on this side? No, it's not. It's just the way that my hair sits. Because when it gets really
long like this, it sits weirdly. It makes my head look like it's going back this way a little bit.
He's balding. I mean, yeah. I'm 36. You wouldn't... Yeah, you dream you look like this when you're 36.
You dream. Keep dreaming you'll look as good as I do right now at 36. Keep dreaming. Wait, let me
say that again when it looks better. Do not say F, liar. Don't do that. It's more like a nightmare.
Okay. Okay. There's no F. I'm looking at it right now. I can see there's no drop frames.
All 5,000 of us. Holy shit. What was just happening there? Can I get it to stay there?
Why does this look good? What's happening right now? This looks good. Why? Again, I got to get
away from... I'm just being an ego weirdo looking into a mirror. Because right now,
because I'm just sitting here, my OBS preview is right in front of my eyes. Usually it's over
here and I can't see it. Why does this look good? Am I fucking crazy or does this look good? This
looks good. Do I look good? This looks good, right? What's happening? Yeah, this looks fucking good.
Can you please say I'm gonna... No. You guys don't even... Sony put Morbius back in the theaters and
none of you assholes went to go see it. So no, I'm not going to do that. You didn't even see the
movie. All right. I think we're good. Let me tweet this out. Let me tweet this out. You changed? No,
I didn't. You did. New tweet that's going to say, trying again. I wanted to fucking stream. We're
going to try the game demos. It seems to be that Steam is back. Please back up. I'm typing on my
phone. Relax. Should be trying again with a bunch of like the crazy, like the face like, I'm crazy,
whatever, that emote, whatever it's called. What's that called? What is that? What is that
emote? What's that emoji called? It's called Zany. I was very upset before. I'm sorry, but I was.
How can a streamer stream without a proper internet, a proper server to connect to? It's
annoying. It's like a surgeon going in for surgery and they're just like, oh hey, yeah, you ready to
do your surgery? Yes, I'm ready. Oh, well, there are no tools. You have to use your bare hands.
I guess I'm just going to go home. He's comparing himself to a surgeon. I'm not comparing myself to
a surgeon. I'm just saying that the tools that I need to be able to stream, if they're not here,
I can't stream. Stop looking at yourself. Stop it. I got to get this off. Get away. I just like,
what's wrong with me? What's that? Is there a bird or an animal that like, if it looks at its
reflection, it just can't, it just sits there for an hour. I'm not even egotistical about this. I
just sometimes locked into this guy talking in front of me right over here. This guy in front
of me is talking and I'm looking at him. Okay, let's go. Okay. What's the title? The title should
probably be different, right? I would imagine. Let's get, oh, that's right. I want to move this
down. All right. So I got called to the limb. We're going to try that. This is the demo stream
and I might just do this tomorrow too, because I want to be able to do it tomorrow rather than
just kind of, I don't know how long the stream is going to be, but I couldn't go out on that bad one
a few hours ago. Not going to happen. Okay. Put that here. Now I need, what do I need? Okay.
All right. So I need, where's my discord? Where the hell is that? There it is. Okay. And then I
need this website. Give me one sec. All right. So I'm going to open up a call to the lamb. That's
the first one that I downloaded. If you don't know what we're doing, I will give you another look.
On steam, there is this huge list of demos that are available for the next week. Every single,
there's a thousand of these. They're all coming soon. Most of them are, and you can download
demos of them. I'm going to pick random shit here and we're just going to see how it goes.
We've already, that game melatonin was really cool and I want to keep doing this. I think it's a
really fun idea. So we're going to start with call to the lamb. I already have it installed
because I knew I was going to be doing it. So let's get it open, see if it's any good.
This game looks cute. We'll find out, won't we? And three, two, one, go. Massive monster. So what's
this game about? It's a demo. We're going to find out. Is it too loud? Can you hear anything?
That's not what I wanted to do. Yeah, I know. I do. Who cares about your desktop background?
Do you really care? It's nice. It's like a beach with, it's, it's, I don't care. I don't need,
I don't need a desktop background. It's cool. I don't care. I don't look at my desktop background.
I don't care. Press X. Wait, X as in X or X as in, is it basic background? Yeah, you don't need
anything more than that. Is it too dank? Is it? Okay. You stop being a minimalist. I don't have a
desktop background. It doesn't make me a minimalist. All right. This is, what is this game called?
Cult of the Lamb demo. Let's check it out. This is a controller game for sure. Guaranteed, right?
Okay. All right. I like the style so far. Work in progress. Okay. Let's go.
This is, this is cool looking so far. So far it's a five out of five. Magicka Wizard Wars.
Mousepad Andy. Really? Really? No, don't fucking derail this. I just got it started. I just was
able to get it to go live. I'm not derailing it already. It was two hours of derailment last time.
Kneel to be sacrificed. Okay. For this sacrifice, the prophecy will be impossible to fulfill.
The heretic lies bound below will be condemned to eternal captivity, and the old faith shall
be preserved. Oh, these are old gods. Am I dead? Is this game like Binding of Isaac? What's this
game like? Come closer if you're not. Though you are already dead, I still have need of you.
Those foolish bishops thought they could keep you from me in death, but instead they sent you
straight to me. I will give you life again, but at a price. All I ask is you just start a cult in
my name. Do we have a deal? Um, you're sure. Wise choice. Take the red crown which I once wore with
it. You shall command the loyalty of followers and strike fear into the hearts of our enemies.
By the way, this is called Cult of the Lamb demo. What am I doing? That was weird. That was weird.
I don't know what that was. That was very fucking weird. That was strange.
Once you've done so, you'll see me again. All right, so I let the old god out,
put the old god's crown on, and now I have the power of the old god. Remember,
this is Cult of the Lamb demo. What's wrong with you? A lot of things, man. Where do you want me
to start? Whoa. This game suck. All right. Okay. If you're not, I am Rato. I was once a chosen
vessel like you, but those days are lost to the winds. I was sent to guide you where deep in the
lands of the old faith and engraved danger. This game is actually really fun so far.
Lead you to safety. Continue through the woods. Escape lies ahead. I'll be close by.
Yeah, so this is again for everybody that's joining us. These are all demos on Steam right
now for games that may or may not be coming out soon. There's a whole event. Would have loved to
have been doing this all day. Yeah, so it is kind of like minding my inventory. Coin. Is it currency?
Those are probably traps, right? Do I have a health bar? One coin. I got two coins. I love
the art style. It's kind of like this kind of pop-up book. That's really cool. I like it.
Who's the composer? I don't know. Good question. This is good. It feels very clean. I would say it
controls exceptionally well. Exceptionally well. The movement's fun. It's very fluid. Animations
look great. There's no screen shake, which by the way, why God, why God, God, why does every
fucking game studio now put screen shake in every single game? Why is it in every game?
Why is it there? I can't stand this new trend. I can't take it. No, it's not here. Hold on now.
Hold on a second. Everybody wait. They, why is it in every game? I don't get this. I downloaded and
started to play, just because I was curious, Diablo Immortal. And let me just be very clear
about this. Fuck that game. Fuck that game. For a reason that you might not understand.
Every time you swing the weapon in Diablo Immortal as a melee character, a default swing,
your fucking iPad shakes. You can't turn it off. It drives me crazy, crazy. I'll sit,
it hurts my eyes just watching the screen shake. And I do this thing a lot of times where I type
into Google Diablo Immortal screen shake sucks, just to get the confirmation bias from myself
that other people agree with me. And I can't find it. I can't find it. Nobody agrees with me. Turn
those off too. But man, I don't know. Screen shake doesn't add anything. It's just annoying.
It's annoying. It doesn't add anything to the game. It's just obnoxious. I don't,
am I crazy? Have I lost my mind? He's a boomer. No, I am not. I am not a boomer.
It's a screen shake in every game now. I never remember a time when I used to play game. Okay,
this is, I just said used to whatever, where I had to turn a slider down. So my monitor didn't
shake. Oh, I hated it. Everyone's talking about Diablo Immortal's like pay to win bullshit.
I am like the screen shakes and I uninstalled it. Cool. We've reached safety. You've done well.
Okay. Someone tell him his monitor doesn't shake physically. I think he's afraid of damaging his
computer. I want to add screen shake to my streams. Let's see how you guys like it.
Every time I talk loud, the edges of your visual is going to go like this, like this.
I don't get it. This game. All right. This one's good. We're going to get this one five more
minutes. Oh, also Diablo more. Oh, do I even really? I mean, everybody's already had their
take of this game so far. Do I really have to add myself to the takes of Diablo Immortal?
Do I have to give you my Diablo Immortal take? I mean, you've heard everybody's given their take
every single person. You don't need to be, I don't have to give it to you, but I might.
Okay. All right. I will. There are 15 items in Diablo Immortal that are there. There are literally
15 items in the game, whatever it is. It's just like you run these rifts to get the same like 15
gems. There are 15 items in the whole game. All the other stuff. I don't know. Who cares?
Let the anger flow through you. Speak. Speak. Okay. So I got a follower. Indoctrinate into cult.
What? Wait, you make, you can make your own like cult members? Why? I want the pig. Variant?
Just say microtransactions are bad. That's that's really not even what I mean, though. I just mean
that there are actually like 13 or 14 items in the game that you try to get. The whole time I was
playing through the portions Diablo Immortal, just on my iPad, because I'm an iPad gamer.
I'm just sitting there going like none of this other gear. I don't care. Like this gear doesn't
matter. I'm just opening a box at the end of a dungeon and hoping that one like a five star
version of the same 15 items shows up. It was just, it just ruined everything. I was like this,
this is this is ruining the entire experience for me. Okay, I can give, can I change these?
Lose minus five faith whenever another follower dies or ignore dissenters when they preach.
Minus five faith when a follower is sacrificed. Huh. Okay. Chop trees? Okay. Wait, what?
Your cult will grow powerful, but your followers cannot live on prayer alone. They must eat.
This game's sick. How come Jerma is at a different hue right now? Because I don't know, man. I'm tired.
Okay. Build. Build it. Collect. Oh, I have to do it myself. Okay. I can't chop that tree down.
Wait, is that progress bar that small? Why did I pick the biggest tree at the camp?
That was stupid. Okay, I'll do that one later. Cool. No, but like, okay, micro transactions.
Look, I'm not going to sit here and go off on micro transactions. You've heard everybody give
that take. My take is get screen shake out of your fucking video games. That's the most important
takeaway. Stop talking. I'm a live streamer, man. Can I help? Okay, so let's build it.
This is supposed to be demo night, but this game is good. All right, I'm going to move on a minute.
We're going to do one more minute or this is how I'll end it. If you're going to have screen shake,
please be like these god tier developers and make it so I can turn it off. Be like these god tier
devs that knew and they decided to make it available if you turn it off. The demo is just 30
minutes. All right, cool. The followers need to eat. It's up to you to provide meals for them.
The hunger of your cult can be seen in the top left of the screen. When this gets low,
followers will begin to starve. Find more food while crusading. Pick routes that pass through
foraging locations. Plant farms to grow your own food. Seems to be purchased while crusading.
Like berries? When is this going to come out? I want to play this. Oh, I have to hold it. All
right, you can cook food. I only have one follower so far. What's this game called? This game is
called Cult of the Lamb. Cult of the Lamb. So far so good. Okay, let's cook some food.
15% chance of the follower pooping instantly. That's weird. What'd I just do? What'd I just do?
Oh. Oh wait. Okay. So is that pig going to eat this? I need more followers.
Okay. Slay them. Go find gold and find recruits. All right, this game's cool.
Yep, this is a good one. Kill M. Deuceous. One follower Andy. Hey, you gotta start somewhere.
You gotta start somewhere. You don't just wake up one day with... How many followers do I have? 50?
Okay, Darkwood. All right, I guess we're just going to Darkwood, right? Who made this game? I have to
read this. Jerma, if you were dreaming right now, would you show us your penis? You know how many
times I've panicked in my dreams about something like that happening? Why would I do that deliberately
in my dream? Mods let that pass. No, I caught it before it got deleted. Would you stop? All right.
Oh, items. Quiet. You didn't have to read that. That person needs to know. They need to be corrected.
Okay, I want this one. Hell yeah. Let's go. Wait, I take them both? Dude, you take them both.
Whoa, this is good. Oh yeah, this is a fun game. This is a fun one. Absolutely. Put this one on
your wish list for sure. Hell yeah. Yeah. Yeah. What is this? Praise Lamb, conduit to great power,
promise liberator of the one that waits below. So the card showed me once many lifetimes ago,
or has that yet to be. I always have drawn your cards, Lamb, and yet this is the first.
Take these cards and I will draw another each time we meet. When drawn by me, they will grant
you a power. A power that's both known and unfathomable. The cards they shall decide.
I think this one. Yeah, whatever. Okay, cool. Got it. Tarot cards. Oh, these ones I have unlocked.
All right. I only have three hearts. Everybody be careful. Oh, there's food. Nice. Nice. Does
this get the German 985 stamp of approval? Yes. What's going on? Whoa, what? How can this be?
You were put to the blade, Lamb, as all your kind were, and yet here you stand before me,
unrepentant. The crown has power, could it be? But I am stronger still, turn tail and run little Lamb.
Leshy, wait, inscription? Interesting. Okay, inscription. All right, everybody show of hands.
How many people listen to the angler's theme song at least once every couple of weeks?
And just sit there in your chair and go like, let's do the question mark.
Whoa, that's a good room to go in. The angler from inscription. One of the bosses.
You guys don't know what the angler theme song from inscription is? How dare you show up here?
Play it. I'll play it after this. I'm going to die. I got to be a better gamer than this.
I'm kind of sad that this is just a demo. I want to play the rest of this game.
All of these different weapons. Pogjam.
When slaying a foe, I'm talking. When slaying foe, summon a ghost that will attack nearby enemies.
Cool. Projectile that spreads. What? Should I try this? This is a projectile.
You can recycle stuff too. What does recycle mean? Wait, what? Oh, that's cool.
It's just huge range. All right, recycle it. Ah, it's money. Got it. Nice. Nice. Press Y.
Yeah, I've been wasting it like a fool. Oh, it puts that tar on the ground. All right,
I got to kill the boss. Bat chest. Flower necklace. Oh, I think this is the boss.
Let's go. How do I build up the meter? This game rocks. It does. I would have moved on
a long time ago. I want to see this demo to the end. Land the 1C3 combo. Oh, that one. What hit
me? Are we dropping frames? Nope. Good. So, see what I mean? It's just so fucking weird. It makes
no sense. You've gone far enough. My followers are willing to do anything for me. Can you say
the same of yours? I give myself to the cause, oh mighty leader. By the blood of the great ones,
destroy the red crown. Amdusius. Oh, wait, I can, I, really? Convert me to your cult,
I will follow your teachings faithfully. Ah, 13 berries, follower form, or berry bush,
berry bush, berry bush, berry bush, berry bush. That one. Very cool. My face is so itchy with this
beard. Locked. Return to cult. Is that it? Did I get to the end? Did I reach the end of the demo?
That's it? When does this come out? Oh, no. Ah, August 11th. All right, write that down and
put it in the recommended. I want to play this game. This game's cool. All right, what's next?
That was, that was cult of the land. Put it on your steam watch list. I would highly recommend it.
What else do I want to do? Do anger foot. Hold on. Let's, let's, I thought I just got electrocuted
for one second. I was like, I'm getting electrocuted. Uh, okay. So now let's go down here.
What do we got next? Anger. Hold on. Let me move this a little. Anger, anger foot. This looks pretty
good. This looks cool. Hold on. What else? Midnight fight express potion permit roots of Pacha
renowned. These all look, these all look wicked fun. What happened? Am I, do I just not pay
attention to anything or is this just a shitload of good games that they're curating? All right,
we'll do anger foot and I'm going to, I'll put on the, uh, the angler theme so you can understand
what I'm talking about. Anger foot is coming up. It's cause they're new. This is cool. I didn't know
it was going to be like this. Yeah. So people don't know what they're here. This is what I'm
talking about for those of you that need to know. The song is crazy. It's very, it's very simple,
but it gets, I just think it's cool. You ready? This is the one. This is the song I was talking
about. Play the Trapper song. I'm sorry. The Trapper song is not the angler.
That's not going to get played on my broadcast. I'm sorry. You're a psycho. What I, what, why?
Actually, that is like kind of weird, isn't it? Why am I listening to like scary jaws type music,
right? I'm listening to like a scary song. That's not the only thing I listened to.
The meat grinder calls. No, I, the whole soundtrack I listened to. I just think this one's really,
this one's really cool. I just, I just see the kind of scene play out where he's like at the
whatever. I don't care. I don't care. All right, let's go. You guys ready? I'm trying to get this
really streamlined here so we can make it very quick. Very, actually hold on a minute.
Where's my Twitch dashboard? Who took it? So we're going to do Angerfoot coming up here. Cool.
Oh, I am logged in. That's fine. Good. What is this title? Delayed, delayed demo day D stream
D stream. What is a D stream? Okay. Let's check it out. You guys saying this one's good. Let's
see if you're, if you're accurate. I know that this is devolver again is 92 high for this timer.
Is there already this timer already? Where am I going? Where am I going? Holy shit. This
game's fucking incredible. This game is amazing. Why don't these games come out? Am I just, do I
don't play video games? That was amazing. That was some of the most fun I've ever had in my life.
That was some of the most fun I've ever had in my entire life. In my entire life.
Okay, cool. Let's go. Let's do it. Level two. Oh, this is fucking crazy. I'm dead. Fuck. Why is he
twerking? I'm confused. How do I reload? No, give me that gun. How do you reload? Damn, this is good.
This game gives me a headache. Yeah, me too, but it's fun. I got it. I got it.
I gotta hold. Okay, don't shoot the gun. This screen shake. This, no, it's not, it's different.
Yeah, it is screen shake. I'm kicking doors into people's faces and I'm punching exploding walls.
Okay, I gotta get it right. I gotta hold. There it is. Why are they, what kind of toilet is that?
What? Where the fuck am I going? I don't know. Uh, what? Where do I go? Should I be doing this?
What? Oh, come on. What the hell is that? I don't even know what,
what direction am I supposed to be going? Oh shit. Oh, okay. This is cool. Again, this is called
Angerfoot. Okay, for a second. I thought, I thought I was naked. I'm not going to kick the
table over, am I? Oh, no, I don't want, this is, this is fucking weird. I'm just so bad.
Somebody said, put it, no, I, oh, I don't want to do that.
I don't want to do that. No, don't, don't do it. Don't do it. Oh,
no. Do I answer the phone? Hey, want some wine? Here, have some wine.
He's going to puke. I'm not going to puke. I can't, I'm trying to give the wine over here.
Oops. Do I have to pick it up with my foot? No, put the fucking popcorn down.
You'll regret interfering with the crime gang. Oh, this is fucking funny. Check your fax machine.
How am I breaking shit? I mean, I can't read it. This is so fucking weird. Oh shit.
This one's hard. Okay. Blow it up. Blow it up. Blow it up. That was pretty dank.
Oh, fuck you. Can you please smoke cigarettes on stream? What are you talking about?
What's wrong with you? What are you, why are you saying that? Come on out.
Oh, a secret. Oh my God. What am I doing? Why would I do that in reverse?
I should have done that the other way. Why did I do that that way? That was stupid. Dumbass.
What the fuck are you talking about? Shit. Oh, this game is so good. This is the best game ever.
It's so addicting. I can't stop. And then, and it's going to end soon. I know it.
Oh my God. Okay. This game is so good. I'm going to lose my mind. Yo, you, you weren't even close.
I'm addicted. Where's the other guy? Where's the other guy? Where's the other guy?
Where's the other guy? Fuck. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Oh, get out.
Holy shit. This is wild. How's everybody doing? You guys doing all right? New weapons.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. What's that? Drink soda. Oh my God. What is it?
Oh, I don't like to, I'm not drinking one of these ever again. I beat the level. This is like hot
light. Way too dank. Is it too dank? I'll turn it down. Is it too dank? Are we all right? We good?
Wait, I can change the tacky town? Whoa. Great for kicking doors and kicking ass.
Regain ammo with every kill. I'll take those. All right. So I get ammo with every kill.
Oh, new shoes. Nice. These look good. Wait, did I just do this?
I just did this. How come it's the same little turn it up louder. I'll think about it.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Oh shit. Where am I going? Okay. So why did I do that twice?
Level five level. Oh, there we go. Level six. That's a grenade. Wait, where do I go? Oh,
I probably kicked the grenade back, right?
Huh? Huh? Oh, I see. Okay. Okay. Okay. Oh shit. Okay. All right. All right. All right. I got it.
I got it. Do start over. Start over. Start over. Start over. Start over. Start over. Do it again.
Start over. Start over. Whatever. Don't start. Whatever. My nose is bleeding.
I got crushed. Let's go. I missed the days when you didn't do cocaine on stream. Turn the volume
back up. I know level seven. This is a pretty long demo. New gun. All right. This is what is.
Oh shit. All right. I'm going to die in one hit. You didn't deny. I don't do. I don't do drugs
besides Marrow marijuana enemy. Do you count Tylenol? He admitted to it. Yeah. I take Tylenol
sometimes. Who cares? Sometimes don't overdo it. No, no, no, no, no, no. Too many people.
Oh, come on. Please give me a break. Turn it back up. This sucks. Oh my goodness. Fine. Go.
The health. All right. I gotta be careful here. Bring it on. Bring it on. Bring it on.
I missed the barrel. This game really has that one more time mentality on it.
What are you doing to me? What is going on? What the fuck? I keep dying. I keep exploding.
Oh my God. It's the barrel. Let's freaking go. I have an idea. Where's that pistol? All right.
I have an idea. Here's my idea. Ready? Run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run, run,
run, run, run, run. Got it. Okay. Now where was my shotgun? I want my shotgun back. How do I get out
of here? Nice. Oh, this is the end of the demo. Probably right. No, I blew it. Fuck. That would
have been so cool if I got it. What? My computer. Holy shit. This game is so hard. Fuck. How did I
miss with every shot? What am I doing? Am I drinking? Is this alcohol? I don't know where
to go. There was no reason to do what I just did. That was stupid. What? What happened? That was
so clean. What was going on? What the hell happened? This game's fucking crazy, man.
Is he dead? All right. We're good. Okay. Now what keeps happening here? Seriously?
Okay. They blew up the whole room. Who cares? Go. Oh my God. My feet went in the air.
I like dove in there with two feet. Nice. Just seeing if I hear auto. Is that auto?
I've got like music blasting in my ears. It's kind of hard to hear. Damn. All right.
Those guys got shields. Okay, sirs. Blow it up. Blow it up. What the hell? Thank God. Oh my God.
This game is too fun. I can't stop playing it. That's the strategy right there. Oh, come on.
I almost got in. Fuck. I think Jerma is doing exactly what they would do. What? What's going
on? Why is it already freaking out? What's wrong? Am I hallucinating? No, I'm not. I don't think it's
talking shit. It's impossible. The game's impossible. I want a pistol. No, I don't want it.
Oh my goodness. There's a lot of people in that room. Oh my God. Does it matter? I don't get it.
Shit. What do I do? Fuck out of here. Level 10. This game is cracked out. I love it.
That guy exploded. Why did that guy explode? Whoa. He's got a machine gun. Give me that
shotgun. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. What's that? Nothing. Come on, computer. Stop lagging.
Not going to fool me with that bullshit. Give me the shotgun. I thought someone was just knocking
on my door. Oh, fuck. Oh my God. There's too many people. Holy shit. New shoes. All right,
we got to wait. We got new shoes. Blasters. Charge up a powerful long distance kick. I'll try it.
Wait more floaties. So soft. You feel like you're floating away. I kind of want to try these.
I think this is a boss level. Oh, it's somebody. Okay. Goop cop. What? I need a gun. Is there a gun?
Don't go off the edge. Oh boy. I went off the edge. Idiot. Oh shit. I got hit right in the head.
That was a good shot. Don't do it. Whoa. No. What the fuck? Why?
Okay. Stop it. Oh my God. All right. Back up. Back up. Back up. I need a hill.
Give me different shoes. I want different shoes. Floaties. Turn doors into bombs. All right.
How do these work? Whoa. Okay. That might actually be a problem. Wait, why are they all floating? Why
is everybody floating? Wait, everybody gets the shoes. Everybody gets them. I get it.
Does that work? Is that doing damage or no? No. All right. Don't be an idiot. There it is. Got it.
All right. Let's start with me a little. What? Oh God. What's going on? What's he dropping? Oh,
he's dropping bombs. Why will this not hurt you? Everybody's floating around. I don't know who's
alive. What the fuck? Don't hit me. All right. Is that it? Did I get it? Oh my God. There's a
phase three. They're just in a car now. Holy shit. Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Don't even. Holy shit. That almost took my whole head off. That almost took off my head. Damn.
I mean, that was amazing. Can I get that a five? I think that one deserves a five. Yeah. That was
a demo. That demo was more fun than some whole games I've played. That's definitely a five. First
five of the night. Damn. Very cool. All right. What's next? Let's take a look. When does this
come out? That's a good question. 2023. All right. That's a little wait, but it'll be worth it.
That was phenomenal. Like straight up phenomenal. Okay. Let's go back and take a look at the list
here and see what else I want to try. Guys, should we just do this tomorrow too? I think we just do
this tomorrow to agent 64. Okay. This is actually really, really fun. I really like this a lot.
Okay. Agent six, this one here. I think I got it. Do I have this one already? Agent 64 spies never
die. I think I installed this one when I was kind of away for an hour. Agent 64. Let's give it a
try. Yeah. I think I pretty sure. Yeah. I got this one. I had this one already. All right. Agent 64
spies never die. Let's go for it. Agent one. Let's do options. Make sure there's no goddamn
screen shake. We're good. Wait. I'll keep it on for now. I'll keep all this on for now. Okay.
Let's give it a try. Story. Tower escape. Agent special agent or a 64 agent. Sims music. Let's
just do agent, right? What about special agent? Free civilian hostages access ground floor.
I'll try special agent. This is agent 64. All right. Reminds me of time crisis. Action.
Man, why these games are all so good. It's like golden eye. Yep. It's golden eye, right? Yep. Yep.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. You play as count Dooku in this game. You don't. Should I go? Where
should I go here? Elevators are locked. Press mouse to target and shoot the padlock. Yeah,
it is golden eye. Was that hostage? No, I was just trying to kick that guy in the face.
That was not going to work. Got it. This is fun to play too. This feels great.
Okay. So now where, where do I go from here? Is there a sprint? No, there's no sprint. It's
golden eye over over here. That's a little dank. Stop shooting. Stop it. Even the switch to the
decoder. Got it. Is there a crouch? It has to be right. This just is the facility from golden
eye. I remember because I used to replay this over and over again and I would just kind of hide
in the bathroom. How many guys treated the facility level or golden eye in general? Kind of like
a hitman game. It was kind of one of the first iterations of there's AI and then be careful,
hide from them. Oh God, I'm dead. Give me a different weapon quick. Why is everybody coming
out of the toilets with machine guns? Do it again. Do it again. Do it again. Oh my God. I
fucked it up. I fucked it up so bad. All right. Last try. Last try. Last try. I'm going to move on.
I get it now. I understand what the game is. Dude, why do I have this distinct memory of golden eye
when you got to the end of the game and I remember unloading on that guy, the last boss,
and you can't kill him, but he took like 700 million bullets. That happened, right? Wait,
can't you kill that guy in a random place or something? And like the game kind of messes up
and the game doesn't like understand that you beat it because you killed the boss way too early
because you unloaded like a thousand bullets into his back or something. Why is this locked?
Did I not get the key card from somebody? I didn't have the tutorial to teach me how to play.
I forgot. I got this. It was like an hour since I last played this part.
Nice dodge. Can I do that move? Why would the box explode? All right. I almost have a ton of ammo
for this gun. I do. Here we go. I have a lot of bullets. Shut up. Ammo is so important. Okay.
Let's get that open. All right. Now don't blow this like an idiot. All right. Let me try to do
this stealthy so I don't get every single person in the whole room attacking me. Did that matter?
All right. All right. I need to help back so bad or I'm going to lose. Is there any health in here?
Come on, man. I'm going to die. I'm out of bullets. Abort mission immediately.
No, I'm not leaving. I can still get the flash drive with all the coordinates on it. Where the
hell it is? Got one. Immediately. Abort mission immediately. Excuse me. I'm not leaving until I
get the... I'm going to beat the level. German, stop playing this like angry foot. I mean, I kind
of have to. Please, I need it. It's important. Shoot a fire link habit. I need to know if a fire
link habit will explode if you shoot it. They do. There you go. What about the bureau? Yep. What
about the table? Yep. Everything explodes when you shoot it enough times. Okay. That's actually
pretty funny. How do I beat the level? I already failed. I can't progress anymore. This one was
really good though. I like this. All right. So that was Agent 64. It seems like a really close
retelling of a... Kind of like GoldenEye. I would say very much fun. Very fun game.
What am I... Did my head explode? All right. That was a very fun game. I like that one a lot. I would
give that one a four. I give that one a... I give that one a four out of five. All right. What else
can we do? Agency. That was really good. I really like that. Really fun. Let's take another look.
Let's take a look at the page here. Okay. I mean, the one that's featured is Metal Hellsinger.
Should I do that one? That one is featured right here on the front page here. What do you think?
Metal Hellslinger. Potion permit. Renown Metal Hellsinger. All right. I'll try it. This looks
pretty... This looks pretty cool. Is this a rhythm game? I don't know. Let's check it out. Would my
enjoyment and rating be better if it was offline? I don't think so. There are a lot of FPS games.
There are more here that are not FPS. This game potion permit looks really cute. Midnight Fight
Express. This looks kind of crazy. When am I going to get through all these? F. Yeah. The reason why
you're seeing F is because I'm downloading a game. So it's a fake F. It's not a real F. Don't worry.
It ain't real. Okay. So that was... Is this game going to be loud? I would assume. Probably right.
Potion permit next. Should you watch the streamer or watch Stranger Things? I mean, Stranger Things
is going to be available pretty much at any point. Whenever you want. You can open up Netflix and
watch Stranger Things anytime. I'm only here right now. I don't know. Stranger Things. Whatever. I
mean, season two to three was... Was that right? You know, whatever. It's okay. But I mean, season
four. We're getting to the end of the show and everything. It's all right. You haven't even
watched it. Nope. I saw 10 minutes of the first episode. All right. This is a double headphone
game, I think. Okay. I guess I'm going to accept the agreement. This looks good too. Video latency.
This is a rhythm game. I thought you guys were full of shit. This is a rhythm game.
The screen shake, right? Okay. It's fine. I definitely want to visit 90. Whatever. This is
fine. Let's try demo. This is Metal Hellsinger demo. Okay. Metal Hellsinger is automatically
configured to provide the best... That was really quickly speaking. Okay. If you're using wireless
headphones or the devices with high latency, I'm not. I'm wired. So I think I should be fine.
That sounded fake. Her coming to get me. I am. It's like a storm coming from far, far away.
I did not feel it in the air. Then me. You didn't do that to the beat. Didn't count.
Well, that's a wave. Let's get this shit out of me. That's still too high. That's still too high.
Holy shit, dude. A two, three. Okay. We're going with three sensitivity.
That's... I hated them. Is this a rhythm game? Okay. Okay. It has to be on beat. That wasn't on
beat? No, wait. Hold on a minute. Go get, go get, go get, go. Go get, go get, go get. I'm trying to
swing and hit when it lands. You know what I'm talking about? Because the sword will be landing
on beat. Go get, go get, go get. Tap E. Slaughter gives you life. Nice. Go get, go get, go get.
We didn't need words. We understood each other without them.
Guess it sounds like love at first sight, don't it? You see, the whole universe has a rhythm. Well,
it's... It's one, two, three, four. Not three, four, one, two, three, four. Sort of. This is
her voice. All right. Let's get it. Paz can be used for keeping fury up even without demons around.
Okay. Fury meter. We need perfect beats. Fury boost. Is this me singing? You can find all the
tutorial. Yeah. This is pretty... I like this one. This is cool. Mosh pit. Let's go. Enter hell.
So are these... This is actual music, right? This is actual songs. All right. Let's get a real taste
see if I like it. This is going to be a real test. Okay. I want to swing that fast. I get... All
right. Here's what I take. This kind of feels like doom if the doom guy got bored in the middle of
the game and he's making his own fun. That's not a bad thing. So many souls here makes a kind of
electricity. Music's really good too. Yeah. Every successful attack charges up weapons. Ultimate.
Fire the ultimate. Oh shit. All right. All right. Where do I go now?
This game is fucking phenomenal. Holy shit. 200k. How do I heal? Oh right. I know how to heal.
I forgot to blink. You're right. Let's go. I already know, man. I'm already a professional.
I only have to reload on the beat too. I just swallowed a bunch of spit. That was gross.
All right. Where do I go? I'm so locked in just playing the game. I don't know. I don't know what
direction I'm going. I'm going backwards. Where do I go? How did I turn around? I don't know.
I've run through a door. Why am I going? I don't know. Am I going backwards? I don't know where
to go. What am I? Why are you drooling? I'm not drooling. What do you mean? I'm not drooling?
Dude, you're really fucking up the flow. I'm sorry. Am I going the right way?
There it is. I'll make it up for you. I'll make it up for you. I'll make it up.
Oh, lightning. Mop shit. Yeah. That was an advanced technique. I wouldn't try that if I were you.
Where do I go? Right? Where do I go from here? Offbeat.
Okay. Now what? These games have been absolutely wonderful.
How come? Why do I not find other with these games till last second?
These have been really wonderful. This has been a wonderful experience.
Four by four hogwash. Boss time. Well, there's your four by four hogwash. It ain't four by four,
is it? I don't know who the boss is. Ow. Oh my God. Resurrect. Fuck.
Whoa, whoa, whoa. That music changed. What? I'm so confused.
Oh shit. No, don't kill me. There's stuff over here. Whoa, I'm good. No. What happened? I'm so
confused. I don't know what just happened. Resurrect. Resurrect. It has a lot of stimulation.
It's a lot of stimulation. It's a ton of stimulation. Damn. That was crazy. That
was so stimulating. That was very stimulating. Is that the end? There I am. Gas can.
45,414. Why am I clicking up here like it's a menu? That's not bad. How many people are on earth?
All right. I give this one a... All right. This is definitely a game that's absolutely... Okay.
This game is going to be very hard because you know the music is going to change halfway through
the game here and it's going to be unbelievably difficult to keep tempo and fire and dodge at the
same time. So I'm going to give this demo. This was Metal Hellsinger.
A 3.9. I'm going to give this a 3.9 out of 5. For the demo. For the demo. 3.9. It could have been
like a... It could have been like a 4-6, but I feel like this game is going to be way too hard for me.
I think this game is going to be very difficult for me. So I'm going to give it... That's not a
low score. I think that's a pretty good score. You give Agent 64 a 4 out of 5. Oh shit. You're
right. Okay. Flip them. Agent 64 is a 3... Hold on. Agent 64 3.6. No. 3.4. Hellsinger 3.9. That's
better. That's better. Okay. Very cool. Let's check. What else can we do? Let's do another one.
The three or four games we played today have... I mean, I wish I played more, obviously, but the
stream had to start much later, which I'm glad that we're not having any internet problems.
So I'm glad that's solved. That's low? No, it's not. A 3.9 is a solid like B, isn't it? Like a
B+. Okay. We did all these three. Potion permit. Should we give this one a try? Midnight Fight
Express. Roots of Pacha. Okay. I'm going to be honest. I'm going to scroll. I'm probably going
to skip things that I don't think I'd be really interested in in the first place. There's Agent
64. Goodbye World. Escape Academy. This one could be good. Frozen Flame. This could be good too.
Any on this list that I don't want to skip. I don't know. This looks kind of... This looks
cute though, doesn't it? How many are there? Hundreds. This game's a visual novel. Is this
a visual novel game or is this a... Even it is. This is fun. I think I'm more into this one than
this one just because I like... I don't know. I like kind of jumping around and shooting.
I'll try Midnight Fight Express. By the way, we're going to do this tomorrow and we're going to...
This... I wanted just to come back and actually have a stream today, but tomorrow we're going to
do this all day, so don't worry. We'll try to get to at least a few dozen of these, I think,
over the course of the day tomorrow. All right. Midnight Fight Express. Is this a beat-em-up game?
Is it controller? Let's give it a try. Now, you're going to see many F's when I download a game.
Okay. We've seen a lot of... This game contains bright flashing lights warnings. Loading failed.
What? Oh. And there it is. And there it goes down to zero. Let's take this down to zero too.
Thank goodness. These are all cracked out games. They kind of are.
Blood settings. This is fine. All right. Let's go. That's fine. Don't matter. I think it's good.
What default is good? Let's just go. We're going to do normal. Let's do it. I don't want my mom
to see police turn the blood off. This game is made by one guy, by the way. It's a baby face,
right? I'm going to call you that since our records don't show anything else. Kind of like
you're a ghost. We don't like ghosts. They have a tendency to cause trouble and disappear. Classic
ghost. Listen up, you claim innocence. No memory from before the attack began, so you were just
trying to help. But am I? Do I have any clothes on? But we know that isn't true. You're part of
this whole thing. The attack on the city, mobilizing the gangs, all of it. What we don't know is why.
If we figure out the why, we can figure out the how, and then we can stop the how.
Come on, buddy. Tell us the why. Help us save the city, and maybe you won't get the death penalty,
maybe. Retrace your steps. Don't hold back or else we certainly won't. Now, what's this about
a talking drone? Stop the how. Okay. Damn. Okay, cool. A is interact with objects. This chaos
sit in the city. There's criminals everywhere. Be careful. Take care of yourself. Let me out of
here. Oh, it's the drone. Okay. Don't think I need to tell you. Beautiful city of tomorrow
has gone to all sorts of hell. Could really use a little saving. Here's the deal. You're a sleeper
agent, a brutal mercenary in a trance, waiting for a drone in shining armor like yours truly to wake
you up from this little dream. I only ask you one itsy bitsy favor in turn. Help me save the city
and all the good hearted schmucks in it before sun up or the crooks will get full control. Do that.
You'll get your real life back in the city sees a brighter tomorrow after all. I know I paraphrase
every thing a dot. Look, I know I'm unbearable. If there's dialogue in a game, you get two options.
Let's love us. It won't be tomorrow. Okay, or they or a limitation about tomorrow. And I'll tell you
we need to save this city. Yeah, I either go full on voice acting or I just paraphrase every sentence.
And I'm sorry. That's just the way it is. I don't I don't like I don't read dialogue.
Okay, I can't. Who am I fighting? Give us the second option. Fine.
I mean, it's always just Mr. Satan talking. Yeah. Oh, I almost forgot. Gotta reactivate you.
Applying a little noise cream should warm up those muscles right up.
I have this music.
It's a music game. And I got to do it to the beat. Beat him up. Rip bozo. All right. All right.
Okay. Do I have I don't have rip bozo on this channel. Block. Oh, it's the Superman game stuff.
On perfect blocks hit left bumper and then hit left bumper afterwards.
Left bumper doesn't do anything. Heavy strike. Ah, I see. It has to be a perfect dodge.
Oh, off the building. Wow. Why can I not get the that's not a perfect dodge. Hold on. Let me try
to get this down. Swing at me. I'll get it. I can do rip bozo. Holy shit. You can't read.
I know I'm doing a heavy strike right now. Hey, listen, bozo. It's fun. It's all right. It's fun.
The rage meter builds up and when you get enraged, you do combat moves.
I don't hate it. We're getting that idea. I don't hate it. Wait, they think I'm the pizza guy.
Dude, pizza tonight. Pizza tonight. That's what I'm thinking. Is there like a dodge roll or anything?
Okay, break their defense. Melee weapons. Yeah, it's just it's Batman. It's Batman. I could say
you could get really good at this and it really string combos together and stuff.
There's probably melee weapons. Oh, there is a dodge. Okay, now the game just got way better.
Oh, I can pick that up. How do I pick it up? I want to pick up the weapon.
I definitely can pick it up as soon as I can. How do I pick that up?
Right bumper. Oh, nice. All right. Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool. Cool.
Give me the bat. Don't come any closer or I'll slit this. You have a wrench in your hand?
It's dangerous. Jesus. Okay. Focus. You can scan the environment. Interesting. Okay.
This is fun. Photo mode. I got a good photo. All right. Whatever.
Really? What happened? What happened? Oh, I. Okay. You have to hold it.
All right. This. Yeah, this is fun. They should not have let me do this because I'm not going to do
anything else. Bozo's guns have this guns in the game too. What? Okay. This is this is a three eight.
No, it's not. This is your hideout. These levels own unique items that you can lock by completing
challenges. Challenge listed here after the level is unlocked. Learn more about the enemies
you'll fight. Each level you can earn money, skills and upgrades, appearance, the playground,
your progression tab. There's a lot here. I'm in trouble. I'm in. I'm going to be in trouble.
I'm in trouble. I'm in trouble. Okay. I want to do throw stuff at people. Grapple enemies,
follow up chain strikes, parry and count. Oh, parry. This is okay. I thought this was way.
I'm going to be honest with you. The first five minutes of this game. I was like, yeah, it's a two
seeing all this. This just bumped up to just bumped up somewhere in the threes.
Yeah. This was a two when I first started. Let's do grapple. Cool. Yeah. I want it. Okay. Assign it.
Okay. Cool. The game needs screen shake. There is a screen check option in there. Actually,
I want to make a point with this. I want to keep, I want you guys to keep tabs, keep track of the
games we're playing tomorrow. We're going to do the same thing. Keep track of how many games have
screen shake enabled in the options. This is an experiment. Turn it on. Sure. I'd like to,
let's see what it's like with screen shake on. I'm sorry. I need to, we need to prove this point.
Yeah. Like all, all screen shake does is just move the camera in closer and moving around and
shaking around. How much worse is this game now that every time I swing, I go
and this one, I will give credit to the dev here. This one's not as egregious as a lot of them really
are. I understand impact, right? But some of them, there's this lateral shake that some of them do.
So this one's going like this. So here's your screen, right? Here's your screen. This one's
going like this, like that. A lot of these fucking stupid ass games go like this. That's the one I'm
talking about. Not the one that goes like this. The one that goes, oh, I hate that trend so much.
I quit video games if it stays, but have you noticed you see what's going on here? Take a look.
Have you puked yet? Don't quit. You're so dramatic. I'm kidding. I'm not going to quit
video games because some games have a screen shake enabled, but I will complain about it.
Like a whiny little baby. Gold? Honey grab? What's a grab move? I don't really like the
impact shake. No, and everyone's putting it in every game. Bulky bozos? What the fuck, dude?
Batman didn't kill people. Didn't even get to do the tutorial with that guy. Okay. Shit, I keep
missing it. Hold on. Ready? Swing. Turn the screen shake off. It's making my stomach hurt.
It's making your stomach hurt. It's fucking with me too. Yeah. Who is responsible for this being
in every game? All right. Ladies and gentlemen, it's a 3.4. Pretty damn good. Pretty good. It's
a 3.4. That's a 3.4. Next one. That was Midnight Fight Express, and that was a good one. That was
a 3.4. Solid. I think that with a little bit more time in it, I'd probably make that score a little
higher. 3.4 is not a passing grade, is it? What are you talking about? Because it is. How is that
not a passing grade? That's like a good score. Okay. Anything on this first drop down here that
I don't want to skip? I'm telling you, potion permit is looking kind of pog to me. I think I
want to do it. It's looking pretty good to me. One dev project. Okay. A one dev project makes that
way better. That's actually insane. That's remarkable. That's one person. I'm doing potion
permit. I'm going for it. That's actually a crowning achievement for one person to do that.
I just think I need a little bit more time in it. You know what I'm saying? Okay. Let's do it.
Potion, uh, potion power or whatever the game's called. I don't remember.
Potion permit. I'm thinking this is going to be a mid- this is going to be a mid-four.
Get it over with already. What? This looks like a potential mid-4.2 game. Look at how cute this is.
Hold on. I'm going to turn it up. Guys, not every game has to have people getting punched in the
face until their brains explode. You can do a potion game, okay? Listen to the music.
Listen to the music. Attack, inventory, roll. Four buttons. Perfect for me. Resolution, 720p.
Change that real quick. Let's go. Potion permit. Let's do it. Let's go. Okay. Okay. Okay. Uh, okay.
Uh, okay. Green. Okay. And okay. And okay. And okay. This game has screen shake? No, it definitely
doesn't. What a bad- worst fit I've ever seen. It was fine. Ah, excuse me. Logan, it's me, Dr. Nester
from the Medical Association. Yes. I'm on my way to meet our colleagues on Moonbury Island.
The Association HQ asked me to say hello to you since we're taking the same train.
Oh my, I didn't realize you were bringing your dog along. Isn't he adorable? What's his name?
I don't care. It's a demo. Such an adorable name. Are you going to help out on Logan's important
assignment? No, zero, zero, zero. We're almost at Moonbury's station. While you're on the island,
you'll be representing the Medical Association. You have everything in order. This is a valuable
opportunity for us. We're all counting on you. If you're successful, we may finally be allowed
to establish a branch on the island. Camera shake. That's- we're in a train. I'm not swinging
a sword and my whole head is shaking. We're on a train. It makes sense. It's fine when you're on a
goddamn moving vehicle. Okay, let's go. There's no screen shake. There's no screen- a camera shake
is- I'm talking about impact screen shake when you swing a weapon or shoot somebody. This is it.
Logan, Moonbury Island. God, hurry up already. I just want to play the demo. I don't care shit
about any of these people. Logan, we've been expecting you. Oh yes, allow me to welcome you
to Moonbury. My name is Meyer. I'm the mayor. This is my wife, Marielle. Didn't I just skip-
didn't I hold the skip button? It's a two. I'm just- we're missing such important shit here.
Good evening, everyone. We've come together tonight to welcome a guest.
Please allow me to introduce Logan. Logan is a chemist sent by the Medical Association.
As you are all aware, our daughter has been sick for a long time. My wife and I are still trying
to find a cure for her illness. The people are shaking. Stop it. With that in mind, we have sought
assistance from the capital. I hope you all give Logan a warm welcome. A chemist, I see. Never
thought I'd see another chemist in our town. We know you're desperate for a cure, but we-
you want to watch who you bring in, Meyer. That person's upset. A chemist? Well,
shiver me timbers. I've crewmates more competent than this novice. How do you know that already?
Concerned. Nobody from the capital can be trusted. Have you forgotten what they did?
Concerned. Oh, thinking. Concerned. Sad. Thinking. Reserved.
Now, now. Won't anyone make a newcomer feel welcome? Please forgive us. Everyone is just a
little excited. Now, if you'd like to follow me, I'll show you to your lodgings. This game's probably
like a four. Just wait till we get to the menu. The crafting menu. This old building used to be
our previous chemist's house. Its former owner moved away a long time ago. Now that it's empty,
you can take it over. I realize it might seem rather odd to you that not everyone here is
overjoyed about. Yeah, what's going on with that? We've rather a history of incidents involving the
medical association. Our relationship has been rather disastrous so far. I imagine they haven't
told you a single word about all this in the capital. This is cute. I like this. You'll learn
more about it as you discover the island. Let's come back to all this after you've rested, shall
we? And please don't forget our request. Our daughter needs your help. I'll see you tomorrow,
Logan. Good night, sleep well. Dude, what the fuck? Where's the instantaneous dopamine?
You can move your character around freely while you're running. Your dog will follow you wherever
you go. Sadly, he's not allowed to come inside the house. Why not interact with obstacles around you?
You'll see a sign. I got a health bar. Okay, that was a pretty sick Minecraft sounds. Okay,
you can decorate your room. This game's so cute. It is so cute. Cool. You can acquire more furniture
by purchasing them from the bulk and bill. The music is really good too. Very good. Try answer.
Oh my god, this place is, look at this. It's a dodge roll. Huh? Good morning. I trust you slept
well. Excellent. Allow me to introduce Zhao, my assistant. This is Zhao. Very nice to meet you.
I work with Mayor Meyer at the town hall. I was hoping the two of you would get along. If there's
anything you need, Zhao will be able to assist you. As it is your first day, I'd like you to
get started and know our island. I've asked one of our rangers to meet you near Meadow
Range and show you the ropes to get there. The music, listen to this. This is wonderful. Okay.
Okay. Yeah, this is comfy. I like this. This is comfy.
Highlighted quest. Go to the Meadow Range entrance. Mini map at the top right of the screen
shows quest objectives as icons. You can apply chapstick liberally to your lips because you need
it so bad and it's not here. Nevermind. Okay. Go to the Meadow Range entrance. I mean, the art is
beautiful. Music's really fantastic. Art is beautiful. Looks really nice. It's pretty clean.
Very readable. All the font. I can see everything. Quest markers help.
There's a dog. That's a big plus. You're right. I have a phone map too. Oh, okay. Look at this
little town. Pet the dog. I don't think you can pet the dog. Maybe you can. Wait, this way. I like
the cape. Uh oh. Hey there. You must be the chemist. My name's Forrest. Mayor Meyer said you'd be coming
this way. I've got a little something for you. Call it a welcome gift. You might need it because
I've got an errand for you. Here we go. I want you to gather some herbs. I'm sure you know how,
right? Probably. An accident in the past killed off many of our native plants. If only people from
capital worked responsibly, tragedies like that wouldn't happen. That's not good. Oops, me in my
big mouth. Once you're done, head back to my cottage. I'll see you there. All right. So go get herbs?
That's all. All right. Good luck. Swing your tools at gathering points to forge resources.
Gathering points are indicated. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Stamina is consumed. You can switch tools.
Sickle, hammer, and axe. Dodge rolling. Does not consume stamina. Whoa.
Hell yeah. What did you give it a two? Wrong. Wrong. Oh shit, they're alive.
There ain't screen shake stuff. There is no screen shake. Stop it.
Get basil, get daisy. Okay. Sticky gel. How do I feed the dog? Dog interaction.
Ah, okay. Your dog loves food and loves to be petted. You can do this. All right, that's cute.
I wanted to... Wait, I wanted to open the dog menu. Apple juice? Why would you... I wouldn't
feed my dog apple juice. But okay. This is probably going to be one of those really comfy
star do-like games, isn't it? Just load it up, burn like eight hours in here, just collecting goo.
Oh shit. I gotta upgrade the tools.
I can't... I don't think I can turn it off. But it's only... It's only on certain actions though.
Did I get stumped too? Where are these things I'm supposed to be getting?
Where's the jasmine and the basil? It says it's supposed to be over here. Enemy? Spores.
I need basil. All right. I got... I got plenty of rocks. I need basil and jasmine.
Now. Am I going too far away? Is this... What is this? Jasmine. Yep. Got it.
I like it. I like it. Now I just need basil. What the fuck is that?
That's not a cute thing. That's a scary monster. Oh, this one's got moss on it.
I think it's worth more. It's more valuable. Honey? No, copper nugget. Okay. I need three...
I'm not... I'm gonna do this task. Here, have some apple juice. All right. I'm ready to give
my demo assessment. You ready? Demo assessment. Here it is. You ready for this? I think this is
going to be a game you spend a lot of time in. I feel like it's going to be really fun. I feel
like it's very engaging. Tons of characters to care about. We got a day-night cycle. It's got a
dodge roll. There's a lot to do, it looks like. There's a big town. There's a boat, which means
it's probably another town. I think I'm gonna... I'm gonna be ballsy with this one. I think this
is gonna be a... I think this is... I'm gonna be ballsy with this thing. 3.6. That's very safe.
That's not ballsy. That's very safe. I don't know. Okay. It's hard to give an assessment on this
demo because it's a demo of a game that probably has like a hundred plus hours of content in it.
I'll tell you, from what's here, I think this is very, very nice. Southeast of the plants.
What's... Oh, you didn't even see that. I got... I just got like a secret treasure map.
Southeast, where... A lot of bears. Oh, there it is. Oh, God. You're only rating the demos? Oh,
that's right. Okay, sorry. All right. The game's probably gonna be really fun, but I think the
demo is... But how do you make a demo with a game this big? Basil is true north right now. I just
got one right there. This with the... Okay, let me paint you a picture here. This with a cup of coffee.
Just shut up. Listen to the music. Imagine you've got in your hand. You're at your computer,
you're at your desk, you're in your room, whatever. Listen to the music. You got a hot coffee. A coffee
is right here and it's burning hot. I mean, you're just gonna... You're gonna hold it here and you're
just gonna smell it. You're not gonna take a sip. Then you're gonna put it down and you're gonna do
that like five or six more times until you take one sip. That's this kind of game. What's wrong?
What's wrong with me? Did I not even complete the mission? Am I too tired? Stamina, right? Yeah,
okay. Can I fail? Yeah, this is a brew a hot cup of coffee and sit here and smell the coffee while
you play and then take a sip every now and then. Like, I would just sit here and just do that,
like this, and then cast a fishing line. Lots of fails, lots of triumphs. No, we want to drink
Mountain Dew. No, drink... Just have like a nice just cup of coffee and I like... Coffee needs to
be just raw. It's got to be... I just... I like black coffee. I'm getting lost in the woods here.
You get a nice hot cup of black coffee. Oh my goodness. This game's score went up because I
thought about doing that without a doubt. This sound and this bridge, I can smell the coffee
beans and it's gonna make it a 3-5. All right, next. I failed the tutorial mission. Do you remember
you're the worst reviewer? I can't review this game. I can't even review the demo.
It's a huge game. It's very cute. The soundtrack is really, really wonderful. I like the art style.
I think the characters are really interesting. I think the coffee smell is gonna be up there,
so I'm gonna give it a 3.5. I think the demo is a solid 3.5 out of 5. I think that's good.
Let's do... You know what? Let's do, what, one or two more? I don't want to go too late. I just
want to make sure I stream today. It was 3.6? Yeah, that's what it was. 3.7. That's what the
final score is. No, it's not. 3.6. That's good. Rating demos is like the dumbest thing you could
possibly do. I can't think of anything stupider than rating a demo. What about this game? What
about this one? What do you think? Frozen? Escape Academy? Frozen Flame? This one looks okay.
Terra Invicta? No. No, this looks way too... I don't play games like this. This is like space
management simulator. Nope. Neaied? This looks kind of cool. Signals. This one apparently is
violent. Kind of interested. We already saw this one, which was very nice. The Cultivation card
game? Card game? Card games can be fun. Gloomwood? This is the... Oh, man. All right, we're saving
this. Are we saving this one for tomorrow? Should I do this right now? Dude, this game's gonna be
insane. Should we do it right now or save it for tomorrow? I want to anticipate that one for one
more day. Yeah, we'll do it tomorrow. Oh my god, I'm so glad there's a demo for this game. I was so
interested. I'm very curious about it. Ripout? Let's try this one. Let's go. Ripout. There's
20 gigs for the demo? Holy shit. It's a violence game? Save this one for tomorrow? Um, you think
so? Okay, well let's keep looking. Moonscars? Oh, it's kind of a 2D game. I kind of want to
try this. Okay, I'm gonna download Moonscars. Domekeeper? Time management? Action roguelike?
No, no, guys, guys. It's not, it's not, um, it's me downloading the game. No, no, we're good. We're
good. It's okay. I'm downloading a 20 gig game. That's why it's doing this. We'll be okay. Don't
worry. It's done in like two seconds. Trapang 2? No, we're good. We're good. Limit the download? No,
I want it instantly. It's done. Trapang 2? I kind of want to, I want to try Moonscars right now.
That's what we're doing right now. Let's do it. Oh, I gotta exit this game. Okay. Don't just go
through the popular ones. Explore the subcategories. I know I will. I will. There's a lot to go through,
so don't worry. I'm not just gonna burn through this. Just the popular ones. We'll go category
by category. All right, let's open it up. See how this one is. What the, what the hell did I just
download? What's the game called? What did I, what did I, what did I just download? Moonscars. Okay,
yep. Let's do it. Another humble game. I'm imagining this is probably a controller,
which it seems like it is. All right. Oh, it's 640 by 480. What are you on about here?
I'm gonna turn it down. Keep it at 480p. That's a weird default. My goodness. Oh, my god.
99 hertz? That's not accurate. That's, isn't that kind of, that's gonna be weird.
Just play at 23 hertz? Wait, why, why would you do that? You're out of sync? What? Oh, you gotta
refresh. You gotta refresh. Sometimes the, with Twitch. Yeah. All right. Well, I'm just gonna,
I'm not doing 23 hertz. Does that work? You're not in sync? Yeah, you gotta refresh. What just
happened? What's going on? What happened? Oh, there you go. Let's do it. Things double as you, as you,
never come to per on my knees these days. This is, I like the painting. The game makes you really
think about if you want to skip the cutscene. I felt bad halfway through, so I stopped skipping it.
Oh, it's a cat. I thought there was a person sitting on the bench next to him. Already gets
a bunch of points. I'll explain. Do you guys remember the game called Out of This World
for Another World? I'm getting serious Another World vibes, which is a big plus.
Healing. Icarus is a soul liquid, the very essence of human life. Use it collected to heal your wounds.
You can't let it go. I can't let it go. I'm telling you, I'm not crazy. I'm not crazy. It's in every
single game now. I don't, it just is. What resolution is this? What are you talking about?
Why is it 640x480? Why is it 640x480? I don't think it is. That's bullshit. It was, I don't care.
It was, I don't care. Ooh, witchery. This game looks unbelievably fun. Hold on. Let me get over
it. Yeah, it was already was the highest resolution. I think it's just doing that for some reason.
All right, so I have witchery. God damn it. I'm so mad. So I have witchery now of direct blast
forward. How do I do? Ooh, that's cool. Can you open the door? This door opens from the other side.
How do I get up there? Oh, okay. It's major screen shake. How do I open this? Go left? Oh,
okay. I wasted my stuff. How do I get that back? Witchery spoils ichor. Irma can purge spoiled
ichor hitting foes with her sword. Spoiled ichor can still be used for healing. Okay.
I mean, it plays beautifully. It's, I mean, it plays wonderfully. It's smooth. The animations
are great. The art style, it looks, the art style looks really nice. This is really, it's,
it's beautiful. I'm very, boss fights in this game, I imagine will be the big selling point.
Cool. Bone powder. 250 bone powder. Climb the ledge. Oh, I'm in here now. Cool. Kind of like
Castlevania. Kind of like, kind of like, what's the other game I'm thinking of? Symphony of the Night.
Yep. That's what I'm thinking of. Nice. It's fun. Am I dead? That's a good one. That's good.
It's fun. I actually want you to look at this though. This is important before I turn this up.
There's a lot of moons. There's a lot of moves here. Look at all this. Corpse reassembly. There's
an entire skill tree. Skill trees are a huge plus. There's a dev in the chat. This game's cool.
Dev in chat. Rant about the screen shake real quick. No, I can't. I can't do that. I have stage
fright. Stage fright. I'm like, let me try one more time. That felt amazing. I'm telling you,
this game is fun. When this comes out, there's going to be people that are playing the hell out
of this. They're going to think it's like an incredible game. It's going to be really difficult.
It's going to be hard. The boss is going to be hard. The game is really, really about skill-based
dodging and stuff. And it plays beautifully. Can you put a thing in where I can take the screen
shake off the screen, please? Can I? I'm just, I'm asking like, like nicely. I don't want to be
like a weirdo about this. Guys, if we're going to do this, every dev that, if every dev comes
into the stream and every game has screen shake, I'm going to look like a real dickhead. These games
are great. This is, this game is, I'm telling you, this game's fun. And look, I might be the weird
one. You could probably poll a hundred people, family feud style, and ask them, hey, do you give
a shit if there's screen shake on every hit? And if 99 of them say, no, I don't care at all.
And I'm the weird guy that I get it. Shortcut, heal. Oh, that's right. I have to heal. And it,
oh, that actually, that's a pretty cool mechanic. It uses that. Cool. Shortcut. Ah, all right. Cool.
Bone, found a grave, bone powder. Imagine that's probably how you level up.
If you level up, airdrop. Ooh, cool. Spite level achieved. Ooh, wait, there's bone powder.
I never really thought about it. I know. And the thing is, I, it could have, this could have,
okay, don't, I'm going to die. What are you doing? I feel like I'm just noticing it way more.
And I am not speaking out of malice. I'm not speaking out of, oh my God, all these games
stink. I'm speaking out of my actual physical wellbeing. It makes me actually nauseous.
I'm not speaking out of malice. I promise you. It just makes me nauseous.
Constantly shake so you can counteract screen shake. Are you getting nauseous right now?
I mean, this, this one, I'll tell you, this one is not as bad as some 3D games. It's a lot more
painful for me to look at. I mean, it's still here and I still, I don't love it. I don't like
it really at all. But 2D versus a 3D visual with screen shake, it kind of hurts even more. You just
played a heavy metal rhythm shooter. Yeah, but listen, listen, it's, it, you know what I'm saying?
R, B, oh, there's actually a parry. Cool. Let me try parry. That was cool. All right. I like that
spike menu. Let's check it out. Instant heal, build up effect, critical. Oh, critical. Definitely.
Spell cost. What about instant heal? I feel like that's a good one.
I, wait, you doing a poll right now for screen shake? How did only 500 people vote in that poll?
There's 10,000 people here. Oh my God. So many of you do not give a shit about this at all.
You don't care to even participate in the poll. You just don't even care. That's so funny.
That's hilarious. A majority of you do not care at all. Have you been rolling your eyes the whole
time? You just don't care. How many people voted on? How many people said to put it on? Not even
a, like a 5% voting turnout. Oh my goodness. And somebody actually said, I don't even fucking care.
Laughing my ass off. Somebody said, I didn't even know there was a poll. You're not even watching my
stream. You're not even watching the stream. God, I love this. I have so much fun. It's too fun.
That's too fun to stream. It really is. Boss fight. I'm gonna do wicked messy hair for the
rest of the day. Okay. This moon forsaken place serves as a shelter to as creatures gray ermine
meats. Oh, kind of like a hub world. Cool. Zoran, is that you? What happened to me, Zoran? I've been
on the quest head and eye. Did something happen between us? My guts ache like I've been put in a
grinder. You're meowing too loudly, kitten. It's not Zoran. It won't respond. Ah, cleft husk has the
same grim face as Zoran himself. You poor, poor kitten. I'm a cat? It may be still one of us. This
husk can shape fine clay vessels for you. These strong bodies will help you slip from the clutches
of pain, yet only for so long. Get a chance to heal your wounds, gray kitten. Just, I'm a cat.
There you go. What is this? The cat is right. I lost a lot of ichor. I can't fight in full force
with that gland shattered like that. I need to cast a mold. New poll? No, you didn't participate
in the first one. Look at how cool that looks. I love the animation. I love the art style.
Let's do, I'm gonna do hammer. Very cool. How do I put, how do I put the hammer on?
I think it's already on. We're born orphans. So it doesn't take stamina or anything. Nice.
10,000 people joined after the poll. I mean that we're, we're, we're very late.
Screen shake aside, I think this game is actually, the demo is, is very fun. I think the game is,
okay, I think this is, I think this game is going to be good. I think it's going to be very good.
Bland 3.7. If I could play without screen shake, it's a four. I genuinely think this game would be
fun. It is fun. I'm just a fucking baby. I'm not kidding. I genuinely think this is a really,
really cool game. Genuinely. In fact, I'm going to play it for another few minutes.
If Morbius gets a re-release, we deserve another poll. I have nothing to do with Morbius.
Why are you acting like I was on the team of people that made that movie? Nice. That was cool.
Shit. Ooh, I got a new level up. Ooh, another shortcut.
Morbius gets another re-release. Just wait till they make Morbius 2 and they lean so heavily
into all the memes. Look, they're going to recast Jared Leto with Jay Leno and they're going to try
to make it with makeup so you can't tell the difference. Shit. All right, this game is fun.
The Mold's grave was lost and time has passed. The moon has grown hungry, toughening the clayborns.
Putting moon right at a dart is a lot of info. That's a 3.7 and I would, if I could play it
without screen shake, that's probably a 4.0. That gets the game seems pretty great. I think
the star of the show. So what do they give the feet game? Because I need to redo that.
What do they give the feet game? That was a five out of five. Yeah. Okay. Just making sure.
All right, let's do one more. I don't want to go too late. I just wanted to stream for at least a
few hours. Let's do one more. I'm going to, this is 3.7 out of five and I think it's going to be
really fun. I think people are going to really enjoy it. It's definitely a lot of work went into
it. A lot of amazing artwork. Story seems really cool. That was a pretty cool reveal right there.
I don't know. We'll find out, but it's, I could see that being very fun. You know what I'm really
happy about though? There has been no games that I've played so far in this kind of at least a
featured one. That was like just shitty. These are all been very good. All right. What should
we do for the last one for the night? Distera survival FPS. There's moon scars. Well, dude,
we'll do that tomorrow. People have been looking forward to that. Sapiens. It's a God game. All
right. I want to do this one tomorrow. One military camp strategy, Alaskan truck simulator. Okay.
Gunner heat PC, SCP secret files. Okay. That would be probably fun. Destroy all humans too.
Resist the succubus, the end of the female night. Okay. I'm going to go ahead and just scroll over
that one. Gunsmith simulator. I could have seen the, it says literally in the title. Gunsmith.
This seems cool. Broken pieces. There's a lot here. There's no light. Whoa. Look at this one.
Pixel graphics. Bail or jail. Celico. Tyrant's blessing. I'm not gonna, I'm not playing the
succubus game. Guys. The last worker. I need one more to go out on. Come on. This one looks kind
of good. Difficult. Souls like action. I can already see the shaking screen in the trailer.
I might just get an old hype squad free to play nitro kid. Cool. Ooh. Turbo golf racing. All right.
Come on. Just, I need one. I didn't want to go out on play that one. All right. I'll try it.
I'll try nine souls. All right. I'm going to try it. I'm going to give it a chance. Let's go play
the succubus game with only the face cam on. You want me to play a game that you want me to,
this is something that you're not going to convince me to do. I just want to make sure you're
aware of that. I'm not going to play the hentai succubus game with the stream on and me sitting
here just like, guys, I wonder what's on the screen. Why would I ever do that? Trying to get
me banned. All right. Let's open it. Nine souls demo. Let's give it a try. We'll go out on this
one. Thanks for sticking around. I know we're late. I'm sorry. We're up so late, but cool. Here we go.
So you're not going to some of this game may be considered violent or cruel, explicit violence.
Wait, what? Okay. Okay. Got those. Got that. Whoa, that's not right. What's with this 80?
Okay. Explain this to me. What's with the 99 Hertz? I don't understand this. I don't see a
screen shake option, but it's okay. It's kind of loud. We're gonna raid. What's going on, everybody?
Welcome. Atriach raid. Thanks a lot, Atriach. Welcome. Hope you had a good stream. What was
Atriach doing? What were you doing? Something interesting, probably. Atriach always doing
something interesting. I got ex-squeezed. Was it supposed to be dial? Wait, is there audio? Balloons.
That game is hard as shit. So good luck with that one. Now, welcome, guys. We are doing something.
We're gonna do this tomorrow, too. We are doing Steam demos. If you go to Steam, you go to the
store page. There's a shitload of coming-soon games that aren't out yet that have demos,
and it's a big event, and I'm telling you, it's cool, and you better check it out, because it's
only gonna be here for like another week or so. So we're doing this tomorrow, too. I'm gonna pick
random games on this list. We're gonna check them out. Check them out Thursdays. No, thanks. Thanks
for the raid, seriously. This one's called Nine Souls. There were hints of a tuber in there? Of
course there was. There always is. What is with the pee your pants stuff? I mean, I did it like an
hour ago. It's dried since then. I mean, the smell was a little much, but that got used to it over
a while. Art's really good, and again, all you raiders, we're rating games out of five. The demos,
we're rating the demos out of five. The art's... Oh, he smokes weed! Oh, this is definitely like a
five. I'll give it a five right off the bat. Big bro. I smelled barbecue fish all the way back there.
Oh, that fish does not look good at all. It's like there's nothing on it. I like the sound effect,
though. Looks like you snagged a good haul of fish today. You're a true hunter. I forget that I'm
cooking dinner today. You have to leave room for my carefully prepared delicacies. Cook as much as
you like. I'll eat it all. All right, you've been here for ages. You must finally be getting used
to the food, huh? Okay, follow me to the secret hideout. Oh, it's so beautiful. It's so pretty.
Very much appreciate a demo. That just gets right to it, right to the point.
Go down. Yep. Jump higher. Cool. This game's gorgeous. What's this? Pick up dead man's notes.
Okay, is there a dash? I am not seeing any of that thing we don't like. We're starting at five.
It's only downhill from here, though. Okay, go get the crimson. Okay, so get up there and go
get the... All right, I gotta fight this pig. You guys are embarrassing us in front of new viewers.
You're not embarrassing me. You're embarrassing yourself. It's Otto.
That looks like Otto. Okay. All right, I'll bring it back. Cool. Let's move. But yeah,
the steam demo thing is going on to the 20th, right? So there's still a little bit of time.
We need to check him out. Do I fight? Sure. I don't want to kill it. Can I just take it?
I don't want to kill it. I guess I did. Okay, crimson hibiscus. No fall damage. Good.
And here's a flower. Let's go to the village. What the hell are you guys saying? You're making
us look crazy. Why are you even writing this? Market is really bustling today. It was obviously
a good harvest. Everyone's brought their surplus grains to trade before the ceremony starts.
That's all we do. Yeah, you guys have a tendency to be a little weird. I did just say I pissed my
pants and it smelled bad. So I'm at fault too, but that's not as weird as pooping your pants.
Okay, don't I don't just don't let me influence you. Okay.
We're weird. Yeah, you are kind of weird. Look at what you're writing. Everyone's telling me
to shit my pants on camera. It's like 60% of the chat. That's a little strange, don't you think?
Just ban the word poopoo. Okay, cool. What the hell? I knew I heard it. Everything looks so
pretty. Thanks for your help today. It's an old custom of ours to wear this flower during the
ceremony. Only the chosen ones get to wear it that day. There are no written rules about it,
but everyone knows that the bigger the flower, the more glory you receive.
I knew you cared about me and that you'd help me get the flower. Still today was the last time
we'll go walking together in the woods. I really can't believe it was me that was chosen. Is it
because I always try to do good or because my parents put in a good word for me with the gods?
Only God knows. I'm not fecal funny. It's you guys. That tasted like ass. This has been sitting here
all day and I just like drank whatever's at the bottom of it. That tasted awful.
We've got to get to the gameplay. I need to say I got to give you my assessment. Let's
don't ask him that. Okay, day of the ceremony. Incoming signal. What do you mean signal?
It's me. Your wounds must have pretty much healed by now. I just want to remind you that
the time has come. The passageway only opens again in half a year. If you miss it this time,
you'll be in dire straits. Make a move already. Those animals have kept you long enough.
Remember, be discreet. Don't let yourself be seen. What were you doing sneaking about just now?
I was just talking to myself. Save it. I knew there was something fishy about you.
Don't think you can fool me just because you wear that bamboo hat of yours.
A paradise in the sky? Gods? I don't know who made up that hogwash, but I know
it's odd. Laugh all you want. You wait and say I'll prove it to these morons.
Wow. Firecrackers. Okay. Let me see. That's a bit of a harsh pull. Not going to lie.
Why? Is it bad? I can't see it. Is it bad? Yikes. So what am I doing here? I probably
shouldn't have skipped all the dialogue in the room. Okay. I respect the flying throne.
What's going on here? I'm going to sacrifice this guy, right?
What the fuck? Wait, what? We're doing... Oh no, that's not good. What the fuck? No.
The ceremony is sacrifices. All right, this is crazy.
Big bro, thank you for taking care of me for the past two years. I'm going now.
Huh? Tatch foo charm.
Please spare us from your wrath, oh gods. Big bro, what's going on? All right. I'm way more
interested. I should not have skipped everything. That was my mistake. This just got really, really
interesting. And I skipped... God damn it. I skipped the movie. I'm not your big bro. What do
you mean? Who are you if not my big bro? Who exactly are you? I said, what's the dog doing?
What just happened? Why did you do that? Where are you going? I'm going to put the helmet on?
Human body treatment field. All right, let's go. Reflect. Nice. Press to attach foo charm on
enemy. Ooh. Detonate. What? What's wrong with me? Uh-oh. Oh, you fucking smoke weed, kid. Fucking
heal up. What is this? Rest? So is this like a Dark Souls game? Oh, that hurt. Okay, hold on.
Nice. 4.7. It went down. All right, there's a dash. 4.8 went up. I didn't think there was a dash. It
went up. Back to 4.8. What is this? Blood soaked... Oh, this is their bodies. This is their... Oh,
okay. That's what they... They turned into like this mush. Right, I can run up the wall, right?
Yep. What is going on here? Oh, to the guy in chat that said I was never going to use charms.
You just got timed out for two minutes. Get owned. Get owned. Ow. 4.6. 4.5. I got to get...
Okay, if I get all three of these guys in one charm explosion, it's a 4.6.
Excuse me? What the hell was that? All right, 4.3. That was... I landed. That wasn't a skill
issue. I didn't know I didn't need instant kill. This is creepy, though. This is actually really
weird. How many charms can I use? Do I have a finite amount? This is weird. Origin of ape man?
All right, I actually want to know. Okay, how do I read it? Warning. Warning.
Perimeter breach by living organism. Warning. Shut it down. It's all happening. With that
stunt of yours, it looks like new Pengly will be abuzz with commotion for a while.
E, why'd you strike that early? It wasn't part of the plan. Was it to save that human child?
If you always break with protocol, it's going to be really tough to execute our plan.
One of your business. I know what my duties are. Don't worry. It's just if you had waited a bit
longer before destroying the machine, I could have covered up the alarm. I hope you'll stick
to the script more in the future. This music is wild. Am I going to get a boss fight before
the demo ends? Nice. All right, so you get three heals. I'm getting some kind of currency, too,
in the top right. Oh, it's a checkpoint. You set up an intrusion alarm. To unlock the gate,
you have to trick out the guards. Let's do it. That wasn't too bad. Say the line again? What?
That's good. When does this game come out? Fuck it, that hurt. Quarter two,
2023. Damn, that's far away. That's far away. That's in a whole year. That's really good.
It's in good shape for that release. Yeah, I mean, it feels that way. Hell, yeah. Get in the hang of
it. I thought it went down. I guess not. Shit. He was in the wall. I couldn't see. What do you do
with the money, though? Chest up there. I want to... It does kind of feel like Sekiro with the parry,
parry, parry, parry. Ooh, skill tree. Max energy. This one. Chi explosions are from the charms,
right? I'm very hungry. Oh my god, I haven't eaten all day. I have not eaten a single piece of food.
Holy shit, that's bad. No, that's not true. I had a little... In between from when this
tree had turned up, I had a sandwich. Pizza is going to be out of the question now. I don't
think I can get pizza at midnight. No, I had a sandwich at 6 30 or so, six o'clock when the
stream went down the first time. No, I forgot that I ate. I'm good. I was right there at the end.
Shit. All right. Okay. Hold on. All right. Please somebody write this down because I don't
remember, but I want to remember this game when it comes out a year from now. Yep. All right. All
right. All right. All right. Wish listed. Yeah, I know, dude, but I have on my wish list.
Um, cry of fear is still on my wish list. I think I put it on there back in like
2010. I just don't even look. I literally don't even look at it. All right. I got it. I get it.
This is a I'm very happy with the games we play today because all of them have been good. They've
all been actually really good. I've not we've not seen one of the seven or eight games we played.
None of them have been bad. That's it. You know, that's really encouraging. I talked a lot of shit
about Diablo immortal earlier. People are still making games, man. They are. It's easy to forget
sometimes. They're all on the featured list. Are these indie? Yeah. Well, that's what I mean. Like
every time that I play a AAA game, I always kind of with some exceptions, obviously. Right.
I come away with it going. Yeah. Yeah. Like whatever. I just don't care. I'm trying to
think of what was some AAA games that have come out the last year or two that I really actually
liked. I think Elden Ring is just all right. It's a great out. It's already at the top.
Oh, you accumulate Chi that way. I get it. Yeah. Elden Ring. But before Elden Ring,
what else did I like? Resident Evil 8 was all right. Yeah, it was AAA games are super expensive.
Companies hate to risk with their money. So most of them are just kind of generic.
I yeah, but but I mean, I'm AAA games 510 plus years ago weren't like that. I don't think that's
necessarily correct. Don't bad chest me. Don't bad chest me. Don't bad chest me.
Did I just die? Oh, they were way lower budget before times have changed in the last five to
10 years. Yeah. I think that we just saw so many just world defining video games back in like the
mid 2000s. It's easy to forget that there's other games that have come out. 2017 was five years ago.
Don't even say that that Jesus world. Oh my god, world defining stuff. Compared to movies,
the money used for video games is lower. Yeah. Just take screen shake out of your game.
I think that's it. We'll be live tomorrow. I'm going to try to start somewhere like there on
four o'clock tomorrow. This time actually starting at four and not leaving in an hour because the
internet is fucked up. You kind of dried up the featured section. Yeah, we'll go category by
category and just kind of scroll through. I'm not going to play this Succubus game. No.
But that's it. I'll see you guys tomorrow. Have a good one. Thanks for watching. Thanks for
participating in the stream. I have to apologize because if you weren't here earlier, I was having
twitch server problems again. And it really kind of blew up the whole stream. I kind of
took a break for two hours and came back. I'm glad it ended up working. I'm glad I actually
got a server that actually works. So thanks for watching. See you tomorrow. Same time for
p.m. We're gonna do this again. No game on that feature list was under a 3.5 out of 5.
They were all solid games, which excites me. All right. Good night, guys. See you later.
Oh, we got a minute. So we got like two minutes while the credits roll up.
Happy birthday to please say happy birthday. Hey, star lapel. Happy birthday. What's the worst game
that you played today? I don't think there is a worst game. Baseball. Yeah, I said it in the
beginning of the stream, but I'll say it again. Baseball is moving from July 14th to July 20th.
We had to make a last minute change. The German Baseball Association will be on July 20th. Diablo
Immortal. I think all of them sat at a base level of good. The best one was definitely the fee game.
Angry Foot, whatever it was called. Green screen update. We are almost done vetting the actions.
I will give you a date that I'm going in front of the screen in the next week, I'd say. Yeah,
that game was unbelievably fun. There was a team name change. Yeah, but that's not why we had to
push the event by a week. There was some stuff with the venue that we had to we just had to move
it. We couldn't do it on that date. There was some stuff that we the venue had to change. Your team
names are the California Clowns versus the Maryland Magicians. That's one I wouldn't miss. July 20th.
It's gonna be an exhibition game. Probably right in the middle of the season because I feel like
that's a good place to do it. Where do the names come from? Well, I'll tell you. It's called Random
Name of State. That's it. Does it roll? What do you mean? What do you mean where to get it from?
This is a baseball league that's been operating for a long time. What do you mean? Where do the
names come from? I don't know. I didn't pick the names. Why are you asking me that question? I mean,
I am, you know, commissioner, owner, and operator of the entire league. But I mean, there's various
reasons why you'd have certain cities in certain states. July 20th. Don't forget the baseball mogul
doesn't know his own teams. Yeah, I do apologize again for the I mean, I streamed for like two
hours earlier and it was just frame drops, steam maintenance. It just didn't go well.
Let's get back in the saddle tomorrow. Yeah, and Atriarch. Thanks for the raid, Atriarch.
If some of you Atriarch fans are here. He is a stand up dude. I highly recommend you go follow
Atriarch if you don't already. I don't know what you're doing with your life. But that needs to be
corrected immediately. Very, very cool, dude. Yeah, see you tomorrow. Good night, guys.