Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with Super Meat Boy.
What the hell was that? Super Meat Boy here. We're gonna play the Dark World.
Chapter 2. I wonder if I'm going to freak out. I think I'll be able to get through like I said in the last video.
Probably through the first few chapters of Dark World.
And then I might rage quit in the fourth. I don't know. We don't know. We don't know. But yeah, the Dark World.
Here we go. Chapter 2 Dark World. So let's get going here, huh? Let's do it.
Gotta go backwards in this one? Backtrack. Everybody's gonna backtrack. Whoa, this is weird.
Alright, fine. You want to play that game? I'll play that game. Go!
Wow, how am I? Really? There we go. That's not so bad. That's not so bad at all.
Don't want to get myself killed. Let's do it all in one try. Dark World. One try Dark World.
I've actually seen YouTube videos of guys that just smoke through the whole...
Damn, man. This is so hard. Yeah, I've seen Cotton Alley Dark World videos on YouTube.
I don't know how the hell those guys pull that off. I mean, you're talking about, like, that is just incredible.
Buzz cut. Okay. What do I do here? Jump! Jump! Whoa! Whoa! Whoa, whoa, man. Are you serious?
How am I supposed to... I gotta, like, jump through like a friggin' circus act? Like, jump through the loop?
This is fantastic. I can't wait to do this. Okay, okay. I made it. I made it. I made it. Oh, God. It's down here too.
Oh! I did it. Blown. Okay. Hooray! Yay! Yeah! Oh, I gotta... No, no. This is not... I gotta start from the beginning.
Straight up! And then... No. What? I'm confused. Straight up and then over? Okay. And then... No, God. I don't even know...
There's a Band-Aid right there, though. I have no idea what to do here. Oh, my God. This is, like, impossible.
All right. I know you're supposed to start here. Why else would you be right here? No. Not quite. Not quite. Oh, my God.
There it is. There it is. There it is. Come on. Keep it going. Come on. Oh! No! Well, that's what you have to do as insanely hard as this is.
Wow. No, I had it. I had it. I had it. Right here. There we go. Straight up. No. Oh! Same thing. Oh, my God.
Agent Orange. Go, go! Hmm... I'm trying to think of what they want me to do here. Looks like they want me to get blown over that way.
I don't know. I just don't know. Okay. Maybe? No. Can I make that? No, absolutely not. So, you gotta get blown across the whole map.
That means I have to come down from the bottom. Oh, my goodness gracious. I keep, like, slipping off the damn edge.
Get it together here, Jerma. What are you doing? No, that's not good enough. That's not gonna work. There we go. There we go. Nope.
Oh, someone's getting arrested. I have no idea how you're supposed to do this. Like, not the slightest clue of how you're supposed to do this.
Like that. Oh! There's a warp zone up there, too. What if I just grab onto the right side? Can I do that? I bet you I can just do that and get out of here.
How did I get hit by that? That's ballsnip. What is blowing me over there? What fan is blowing me over there? There's no fan blowing to the right. It's blowing to the damn left.
I'm gonna do that. I'm gonna try that. Just try and bypass it completely like this. It worked. Everybody's happy. This is insane.
No! God! There's more! There's even more. This is, like, level two. Or four, or whatever it is. My God, I want to take a look at that. Look at this. This is just madness.
And we're not even a quarter of the way through this. Oh, I just wanted to go. Sheer Noble! Oh, yeah! Just jump! No, that's... What a troll! It knocks you right into a wall of spikes.
That's just... Oh, my God. Wow, I actually survived it. Can I make it the whole way? Yes, I can. Wow! Wow, man. It's not over. Oh! Oh, no.
The amount of difficulty that this is going to... Take me out to the ballgame! I might not even be able to do chapter two, let alone chapter three or four.
Why can I not do that? Why am I so bad at this game that I can't do that? Oh, my freaking God. I'm gonna spit up my guts in a second. This is so hard! This is so difficult.
Now, if I can just not screw this part up, like... Good! Yeah, fantastic! Are you serious? It blows you even further? Oh, make it... God! My goodness! Wowzers.
Oh, level seven. The moon. No fans here, right? No, like, cheap-ass fans. All right, we're good. This is not that bad. It just takes patience.
I'm just trying to see what's going on in the bottom of here. That's fine. I'll take that. It's not gonna break away, is it? No? This is very, very long. If I make a mistake here, I'm going to be very, very bad.
How long does that guy stay? Okay, no, he's down. No mistakes here. No mistakes. Let's just... Let's do it. Okay, what the hell is that on the right? Oh, wait, wait, wait. Slug's coming back. The Slug's coming back.
Okay. Don't want to get hit by that Slug. Hmm. Ah, that wasn't so bad. The only problem with that one is if you make a mistake, you are in a lot of trouble.
Grape soda! Whoa. Hmm. Oh! I barely even touched it. And that's supposed to be grape soda. Grape soda doesn't hurt you. It's delicious. Get out of my way. Get out of my way.
I didn't know those things broke. Oh, man. I had a little rhythm going there, too. Oh! All right, note yourself. Those ones break. So you can't stand with your finger and your... Oh! Wait for that.
I wonder when the mental breakdown is going to happen. Sooner or later, it's going to happen. Oh, there is no way I can even grab onto this. Okay. Oh, what just... I just ran like super speed right there. What the hell am I doing?
This is so... This is so long and so... How is one supposed to do this? That's an easy go right through. Oh, no, dude. No. Oh, my. The centipede. How am I supposed to go over this again? Oh, like that. Right.
Right. This one ain't too bad. I say that right before I die. Holy crap. Oh, this one really isn't that bad. I just have to not be a fool like that. I tried to jump and it didn't register. Register my jumps or I'm returning this controller two years after I buy it.
Okay, good. There we go. A plus. The Kraken. Hi. What? Why do I keep jumping a second time? You got to be kidding me. You have got to be kidding me. I got to go all the way down. You... I think I might quit the game right now. I think I might just quit the game.
I accidentally went down there and got that and I screwed myself up. This is it. Come on. Yes. I was like seriously going to just exit the game. Spineless. Okay. Wow. Oh, come on. No, dude. I'm going to cry. I got to get up on top of this before that happens and boom.
Boom. Go, go, go. Gray matter. So they're going to go horizontal and vertical now. Oh, this is fantastic. It's all a pattern. It's all just a damn pattern. How did I miss that? Oh, I just fall off edge right down, my idiot. Just go fast. I'm just not going to stop moving.
Not one time. Look it. Look what happens when you don't stop moving. When you start moving around and start being all cautious. That's when you lose your rhythm. Like right now. I'm going to run into one of these saws because I just have been sitting still for so long. I've lost all my rhythm. It's such a blur right now. I don't even know what time zone I'm in. Hold on. Right now. Phew. God, the dark world is no joke. Wait for this guy to move. Jump over.
Come on. That stupid pilot. God. Just go, go before he comes up and then go again and then run into it. Speed run. Speed run. Speed run, baby. Will you just? Oh, that would have been really bad. Wow. Wow. Whoa. Whoa. Whoa. What? Oh, my God. They come right here. Is there another key on the other side? This sucks so bad. Go. I have to wait for him to come back.
There you go. Wow. I almost just waited way too long. Are you kidding me? Are you absolutely kidding me right now? You got to be kidding me. That is such bulls. I landed on the side. I thought it was going to. Let's go. You stupid meat slug. I'm going to have you over for dinner tomorrow and I'm not going to offer you dessert. That's how much I don't like you right now. You can have all the meat and potatoes you want, but if you want some of that key lime pie, you're not getting it. That's it.
Get down there. Thank goodness. Get out of my way. Just I didn't hit that guy. I didn't hit that guy. There's no way I did. Wait for it. Wait for it. Oh, what? What? How am I? How are you? I'm speechless right now, guys. Absolutely speechless right now. I swear I am going to just swallow my own head.
And just anger. Now, what am I supposed to do here? Not get that key and like draw. I don't get it. Whatever. Let's go. Like, oh, okay. I understand now. I understand. Forget the bandaid. I don't want it. I'll do that later. I go up or down. Looks like down. Well, I got another key to get. Words cannot even express how much patience you have to have, which I don't have any for this game. Please tell me I'm going to make this. Thank you.
Oh, number six. Didn't see that at first. Now I do. Go. Fine. That's fine. Shoot it. Wait. Be patient. Patience. Patience is a virtue. I don't know where to go. Did I just come down here for the stupid bandaid? Oh, my God. Yeah, I did.
Go. Oh, yeah. So where the hell am I supposed to go? Up or is there another way to go down? I didn't see anything over here. Maybe. I don't know. Oh, what? What? I have to go out here and then just jump over it. It's like a dilly dallying or almost killing myself. Either one of those two things.
So you have to jump out outside and then around the corner. Thanksgiving turkey. This is ridiculous. So I have to wait and be ready to go right now. Oh, hi. This is so stupid. I'm losing it here now. I'm losing it. The last two levels. These are going to be the most difficult, but I'm losing it. I've lost it. Just wait. I know. Whoa, why am I lagging? I just like jump in the air and I just lagged.
This happy place is a pool that is full of chicken McNuggets and ice cream. And I just eat it. And that's not true at all. But I'm just trying to make myself not mad at this part right here, which I'm going to accomplish. Oh, yes. Is this it? It's either this one or the next one. That's the last one. Lasers everywhere. Freaking lasers everywhere, dude.
10 bucks says I have to go back up and I'm going to throw up if that is the I just walked into the laser. Make your way down. Make your way down. All right. Back where we were before. Let's go. Go. Come on. Yes. Yes. Yes. This is definitely the last one. I don't know. I'm not sure yet, but there's so many lasers. I think I'm doing this right. I didn't even I can't even determine what I'm doing. My brain is fried.
Oh, no, I know what to do. I know what to do. Don't worry. I know what to do. It's up here. Do the same thing. You jump around like this. Then the same thing again. Again. Now what do I do? Okay, I gotta wait till yes. Oh, that wasn't that hard at all. That was the last. No, this is the last level. What? Okay.
No, they last longer. That just lasted so much longer than they typically last. Yeah. Come on. One key. And now I know what to do. Oh, I just freaked out for no reason. Now I'm trying to get up the whole thing and I can't do like that. Come on. Let's let's be smart here.
Now go. This really isn't that bad. I just need to have patience, which I do not have any of as you all know. Same thing on this side. Up, up, up, up, up. Second key. Last key. Hello, sweetie. Hey, plus and that is going to come. No, it is not. I have one more to do.
Please tell me this is not going to be a thousand years long. But seeing as how it's level 20, I'm going to say yes, it's going to take forever. How did I just do that? You can't make those kind of mistakes in the dark world because that's what just I'm doing.
I'm doing it. Splendid. Why can I not make this if you see KING jump? Why can I not make this jump? It's so easy. Look, look at how easy that was. It's just jump. Just jump over it. There's no reason for you to freak out over that. This is going to be so I need to be very, very patient here. This is going to take forever. Oh, my God.
Can I go out this way? Yeah, I can. Good. Good. I'd rather take the easy way, not the long way. Here's the real kicker. Up. All right. It's done. I just have to do. It's over. Oh, yes. Dark World chapter two complete, baby. So yeah, that's going to wrap up chapter two. Chapter three. I don't even know if I'm going to be able to do it. But if I do end up doing it, you will see it on this channel.
Of course, if you want me to keep going, let me know in the comments section or as a like or something like that. Let me know if you want this to keep going, because my sanity is what's at stake here. No, I'm just kidding. But still, guys, I'll see you guys all next time. And of course, take care, everybody.