Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with the Midnight Launch of Mists of Pandaria.
I'm actually here with MLC Stealth Live here. Say hello.
Hello, everyone. We're making pandas.
We're making pandas. The Mists of Pandaria just literally launched like five seconds ago.
It is three o'clock in the morning here right now, so it's very late for me, but still I want to make a panda.
Gotta be playing as a monk, the new class in World of Warcraft in this expansion. Found Darian, the race, and let's go, let's make him.
Alright, I'm gonna be typical panda color.
Dude, I might be like tabby cat panda. Like look at, I look like a cat. This looks like my cat that's in my house right now.
That's so funny.
That's what I'm doing. Yeah.
Alright, is he gonna be a male? Face. Alright, he's gotta have a really stupid face.
Female panda looks kind of cute. Not gonna lie.
Does it? No.
Oh, MLC Stealth loves those female pandas.
Alright, let's go back to male. Oh, did I lose it? No, I didn't. Okay.
Oh my god.
Are there a lot of people here?
Oh, hey, hey, look at everybody. I wonder if you guys just installed the game.
I just see a thousand people climbing these steps.
Dude.
Wow.
There's so many people here.
We all look the same, like ridiculous.
Wait, what do I got for my first move? Jab?
Look at all these people just practicing.
I can't even click on the quest giver.
Where is he?
Oh, man. Oh, this guy broke the, I wanna hit that thing.
Oh, wow. This is cool. Oh, everyone's training.
What is this, quickening palm?
Oh, man. Oh my gosh.
Look how fake this looks. We're all wearing the same armor and it looks ridiculous.
Hey, did you see my Winnie the Pooh character yet?
What the hell was that? What the hell was that?
What the hell was that over there?
What just came out of the water? Something enormous just came out of the water over here.
I don't know what you're talking about.
Hold on. Did you see that?
No. Where are you? Can I jump down there?
I need to add you.
Okay, Jerma, I'll give you a hundred dollars if you can find somebody who's not panda monk.
Hold on. Oh, I found a priest. I found a priest.
Congrats. You're the only panda priest in WoW.
In WoW.
What?
We're supposed to kill trainees in here. There's no way we're getting like a kill for this.
Are you serious?
Get in here. You're supposed to kill six of them.
There's no way. This is impossible.
This is just chaos.
Wait, did I get hit?
Oh my God. Can we just make a raid and just...
Oh, wait. Yeah. Nice. Nice.
Hold on. Oh my God, dude.
Yeah, like you were saying before, I love how this is supposed to be very, very personal.
Look at how personal this is.
Take a look at how personal this is.
I'm being trained by the Shaolin master monk.
And he's training like just us.
He's just training me right now.
I'm being trained, but me and Stealth are the only people in here being trained. It's so personal.
I don't even know where we're supposed to take this.
Hold on. Burn the Edict of Temperance.
I don't know. I love how everyone's doing the same jump down the stairs.
It's so... That's one of the most addicting things in Warcraft.
It's just jumping down the stairs.
Everybody does it.
Over the bridge. Right, which bridge?
This place is awesome looking.
Just hold on. I've got to get into Alt-Z here.
I want to... Look at this.
This is really, really cool.
Alt-Z, huh? Oh, that takes for the HUD.
Yeah. I'm going to take a look at some stuff first.
Oh, wow. Look at that water. Look at the stream.
Everything is so beautiful.
So finesse. So wonderful.
Yeah, look at this.
It's so lovely. I just want to live here all day.
Oh my god. What are you doing?
Did you die?
No.
Oh, it is going to be such a pain in the ass for you to get back up here.
We've got to wait for the cart driver.
I wish there was an AOE move. Just like...
Are you ready?
Wait, wait, wait.
Get it! Get it! Get it!
We didn't get it.
I didn't get any. Did you get any?
Wait, I don't think we were supposed to be killing these.
We need to kill those because they have the stone supplies.
Oh my god.
Get ready again. You ready?
Ready? No. Ready?
Hold on. He spawns right here.
I'm going to seriously just go into first person mode.
Get it! Get it! Get it!
I didn't get it. This guy beat us.
One more time. Third time's the charm.
Hold on.
This guy's going to help.
Here it comes. We've got to get it. We've got to get credit for it.
Get it! Get it!
Yes!
You got that one?
No, I didn't.
Hit him!
Oh my gosh.
That's so funny.
I can't believe this is how we're doing this right now.