I typically greet everybody in the live audience, so I typically greet, but today is going to be a
little different. If you're watching the VOD right now, welcome to the VOD. Welcome to this piece of
recorded content. Those of you that couldn't watch live, welcome to the stream. VOD watchers.
Everybody else? You get greeted every day. Well, three days a week, four days a week. Sometimes
we have to reach out to the VOD watchers, so say hello to them right now. How you doing guys? How
are you? Welcome to another stream. I'm looking forward to this one. I did not realize what this
game was until I really took a look at it. We're playing like a Chuck E. Cheese simulator today.
This is going to be probably my favorite game of the year. I'm not going to lie. This is an arcade
simulator where you go into an arcade and you try to win tickets. My voice sounds deeper? If it is,
probably is. Sometimes I get a little froggy. It'll perk up. Don't worry. I should play Gary's mod.
No, I played Gary's mod like 15 times in like 2013. I think that was all I needed to do.
You sound like you're about to cry. No, I sound like a broadcaster in the car. Maybe I should
try out for NPR. We all know the criteria for trying out for NPR. We're being on NPR.
It's sounding like you're just a little too close to your microphone. I should get the job.
Anyways, it's called the coin game. I am a little froggy this afternoon, am I?
I promised I wasn't at like a football game yesterday screaming.
That's what I did on my days off. Yeah. I had painted my whole body the color of the team and
just was screaming at the other team. But anyways, tomorrow, there's no stream tomorrow
because I have a meeting tomorrow for the carnival stream. So that is really picking up now.
So we'll go along today. Chat is moving so fast. Chat's moving so fast. It really is.
But I do want to reiterate one more time something I mentioned a couple weeks ago is that
streams are going to have to pull back a little over the next four to six weeks.
I'm trying to do double time here on this. But there's a lot of moving parts on this stream
in particular that I'm going to give you the company explanation as to why there's going to
be like three streams a week rather than four company explanation. Very let me get close to
the mic to make sure this is really taken for real here. Company consideration. Reasons why.
Thank you for listening. Anywho, let's go. I've already tweeted. I've already got like the
fucking frog voice. Here it is the coin game. The footlong sub is no longer five dollars.
I hate to be the one to tell you this, but Subway is going to close forever within 10 years.
I just I'm just telling you that this is what I think to be the truth. So instead of so the
footlong sub is gone. Subway is going to be gone. It's not going to happen. Trust me. Ten years
from now, they'll get replaced by Bank of America's. Don't worry. Here we go. Choose your player.
Hold on. Male clothing. Let's see. Can I have different kind of clothes? That's me.
It's a locked button. I got to get the unlockable clothes. Well, that's not without the glasses.
That's me. I don't wear. I'm no, I don't do horizontal stripes. I'm just white t-shirt
and jeans guy. Yeah, that's fine. A birthday mode? What? There's a survival mode and a
birthday mode. A birthday party just for you. Fun and relax so you can just play the games.
When money runs out, just hit up the money grabber. Teleport around an island from smartwatch.
No health? No. What do you mean this health? No curfews or parents. Oh no, it's not ready.
In survival, you work odd jobs to scavenge to earn money, pawn your prizes and get cash.
My parents just don't understand. Your rich uncle Phil has rented the arcade. You can act like the
brats that you are. Go ahead. Money's no object. Also, feel free to check out the entire island
and your... Stop. Hey, kids, relax. Everybody's going to get $5 worth of tokens. There's no reason
to scream. No one's going to get any more than anybody else. All right. Now settle down.
That's when you throw all the tokens in the air and like all the kids, they start freaking out.
Everyone's trying to grab as many as they can. See? All right. Let's go. Does it delete any saves?
Oh, that's fine. Let's rile up these kids. Okay, kids. Yeah. No, no, no, no, no, no. Everyone's
going to get the same amount of tokens except for there's going to be one person that gets
10 extra tokens. If they can scream the loudest starting right now. I could be like, I could,
I could rile up like people. It's like the first thing you don't... I'm the person that the parents
are like, the worker at the place is just like, uh, hold on. This is the worker. Happy birthday.
Rowdy. Enter here. Click grab? Wait, this is a new text message. Tab is to look at your text.
Happy birthday, kid. Hey, thank you for purchasing the coin game. We're extremely grateful. Well,
this is Uncle Phil. Being a new favorite time waster. You can always refer to this menu for
all your received messages and all info about the current game. Below this message,
you'll find a small helper message that explains a little about how to use the player controller
in machines. If you enjoy the game, please consider giving a positive review on the steam store page
and help further development of the coin game through early access development.
Thanks, Uncle Phil. I ain't clicking that. I'm not going to click that. Uh, smartwatch tutorial.
Let's just take a look at this real quick. You've obviously found the smartwatch menu and know how
to read the messages. Here you will find five menus that will help you through your coin game.
Okay. So the info menu. Uh, so the top left to check the balance of your health remaining
curfew time and job. We don't need to do that. That's not in the game yet. Coin balance,
tickets and bus pass balances. Okay. So that's like our top left of this one's balance.
It's really all we need to know because we're on birthday mode. Uh, you must eat and drink
to keep this up through the day or you will die. Why can you die in this game? That seems a little
much. I'm going to say. Yeah. Yeah. We don't, this is all survival stuff. We're not doing that.
It's not ready. All right. This is the messages. This, uh, menu will write you, right? It'll store
all the messages from the game. You cannot delete them. Right. Map menu. This is the top down
mini map of the whole island. I'm going to click it. What? Why is this so big? This seems very
elaborate. Larry's arcade. Okay. Well, so that's, uh, yeah, it has a little major locations marked
for you to explore, including your current position and the current position of the
Islandville bus and all seven bus stops on the island. You can also check the progress
of delivering papers by checking the amount of red mailboxes that have yet to be delivered.
Okay. Uh, 12 spot inventory backpack for you to carry things around the island. Simply click
the pick up button on an object to add it to your inventory. Right. And then click the image of it
in your inventory menu to drop it. Okay. Simple. Once it is full, you have to drop an item in order
to have a new one. And then these are stats. Got it. Uncle Phil, you need some more money.
You need some more money. If you run out of money, you can always go into the VIP birthday
room and get them in the free money blower machine. I took care of Larry and told him to
make sure it is full whenever you need any money. What the fuck? Imagine, imagine being like the
janitor here and you just see the kid. Hey, hey, uh, hey, janitor, uh, Joe. Yeah. You got to fill
up the money machine. Uncle Phil's little shit. Kid's going to go in there and just grab hundreds.
Okay. Like what? What? Just to put, just, just put it in his checking account. You don't have to do
this shit. Barry's pawn shop. Come on down to Barry's pawn shop located at the flashing yellow light
in the main hallway, main highway. We'll buy anything. We also have a vending machine for you
hungry young whippersnappers. Take the bus to stop number five and we are right across the street.
Open 24 hours. Okay. All right. I think I understand how it's going on. Let's go.
The audio is a little low. Okay. Key F inventory. What? Can I, can I pick this guy up? Wait, why
can I, I can drop already a full letter grade. Oh yeah. It's a full letter grade already. That's
cool. Why would I be able to do this in this game? How old am I supposed to be?
Zoom out? Press tab to lean forward. Wait, why is there a, why is there a gun?
Is there, oh, it's a beach. Why is this sub training? GPS is just like, well, you're in the
middle of the fucking ocean. Whoa. Oh, we found the wall. This invisible wall. We found it.
Phil, Phil, I need help. I don't have, I do have a flashlight. What the fuck did I just shoot?
Am I still in the water? What's that noise? You hear that? Follow the moon. Where's my GPS? Okay.
How do I just read, let's just read it again. Your golf cart has been towed to your home garage.
Oh wait, that's right. I can't teleport because this is the joke mode, right? This is just the
birthday mode. Oh, it's that easy. Wow. Okay. What? All right. There's too many things to look at
here. Let's go. Let's go. Hold on. Look, there's a construction yard over there.
I'm supposed to be playing ticket games. Where are we going? Wait, is that, that thing's moving
around. Can I take the truck? If I can drive this truck, that'd be pretty awesome actually.
I can't drive the truck. What the hell? What is this? Power. What? Why can I do that?
Is it police? Why is this an open world like beat up pedestrian game? I don't understand.
It's my birthday. Oh, thank you. Thank you everybody. No, no, no, no. Thank you. What? I
love this. This is awesome. I wanted to go to like Dave and Buster's too. I was thinking about it.
I want to go to Chuck E. Cheese. There's like, there's like five Chuck E. Cheese's. All right.
Which one do I want to do first? I don't have to go anywhere. This is perfect. Okay. How do I play?
I have to scan my Chuck E. Cheese card. Am I supposed to be a robot? Yeah, I don't know.
I have like normal hands. All right. So I got 50 bucks. How much does it cost to play?
A dollar to play? Shit. Here we go. 20 tickets. 50 tickets.
Very, very loud. That hurt my head. Try again. No, I'm going to flip. Let me see the other ones.
How much? So how many tickets do I have? How did I get zero?
Nope. 70 tickets. All right. Hold on. I'm going to get stuck here. I know I am. But let me like
drop that audio. It's too loud. Sound effects. That shit was just out of control. What about
this one? How much is this one? Drop coin with E. Aim. This is just one of the coin pushing games.
I'm going to irritate people so much because I'm never going to leave. I remember Kim and I one
time went to an arcade and we became like psychotically obsessed with these machines.
We sat there for like three hours. Okay. So what am I going to go? I want to get the money thing,
right? What do you mean we? Yeah, no, no, that was very much a we scenario. How can you be bad at
the coin game? I'm not bad. What do you mean bad at coin game? How many, how many credits?
How much did this cost? A dollar? There's a game show in the UK based off of these coins.
It's stuck. I have to, how do I shake the machine? Can I punch the machine?
All right, here we go. I have to get at least one satisfying push.
Fuck. It's going to take a while. I got to get bingo. There it is. Single?
That makes what? Oh, it's coins. Coins.
Yeah, that's what I meant to say. Coins. All right, hold on. Here we go. This is going to be
satisfying. Watch this. Almost. I got to tell Kim about this one. Come on, get it. Come on.
I got to get that S. I'm not going to leave until I hit the S. Wait, this might be good.
Got it. Five bucks. It only just crunches as loud as it can in your ear. Okay, we're good.
Five dollar bill in there. Why am I, I'm just holding the tickets. All right, I didn't get the
S. So I, final push. No, no, no, no, no. Put the money back in. I want to do it again. Do it again.
Yes. Okay. I'm up right now. I want to get the stapler, whatever that is. Get the fidget spinner.
I'm going to, I'm going to clean this whole thing up. I need that S. Give me the S. Give me the S.
I just need the S so that I can move on after I get the fidget spinner. Got it. Okay, here we go.
Oh man. Oh man. Oh man. Oh man. 40 tickets. All right, what's that, a walkie talkie?
Yeah, it is really fucking loud. I'm going to, I'm going to do you guys a favor here. Hold on.
I'm turning it way fucking down, like way down. And then I'm going to turn the music up. That
should help. How's that? Better? No, it's too low. How about that? That's probably a little bit
better. Wait, wait, where, where am I going to get the lighter? Why is there a Zippo lighter in like
a kid's Chuck E. Cheese? I don't understand that. $2.50. All right, let me get the fidget spinner
and then we can get out of here. Let me get coins one more time. And so the kids can smoke.
I'm going to get a lot from here. Nice. Come on, do it. Do it again. Lighter? It's a, what do
you mean lighter? It's a, no, that, that's a, like a nail file. The other thing was a lighter.
Got it. Okay. Something big. It's not that bad. Just put, put the lighter back up there. Did I
take it? I need the fidget spinner or chat will literally never let me leave. Don't you understand
guys, this community, if I don't get the fidget spinner six months from now, someone's going to
have their username be German lied about the fidget spinner. You understand? Like people will
say, Hey, when are you going to get the fidget spinner? Are you going to like go back to the
coin machine to get the fidget spinner? And I'll be like, no, and it'll just become a thing. I have
to get that. It's already taken. So you see somebody is preparing. There's no way in hell
that somebody could have made that username as fast as I just said that. So somebody was already
preparing. My point has been proven. I don't even need to say anything else. I just have to get this
stupid fucking fidget spinner. Oh, that was, that was the mother load. How many, how many tickets
is that? All right. I almost got it. I almost got it. There it is. It's right there. It's so close.
Got it. Yeah. All right. Now nobody can say shit. Now you got to remake another new username.
Get the knife. I already got the knife. That's just hanging on. Hold on. Look at this. How many
tickets are coming off? I just want to get the middle one. I don't even care. It's a dollar.
I have $55. I'm just going to span. I got it. Okay. I got it. That's all I wanted.
I don't want anything else. By the way, this is the worst strategy when you're playing one
of these machines. I'm going to get coins again though. All right. Something big. Oh my fucking
God. Oh my fucking God. I did it. Okay. Let me see if I can get the middle lighter again.
Strategic drops here. Got it. Come on. Look at that. Look at that. Perfect drop.
I'm pretty good I think. I think I cleaned out that one. All right. What else is there? Cool.
How much money do I have? 60 bucks. I got more than what I came in with.
My investment in Chuck E Cheese is going pretty well. Oh shit. Right. How many tickets?
That's a lot. I literally played Big Bass as a kid. Yeah. What does he say? What is it? I got
it in my head somewhere. It's in there somewhere. Oh yeah. That's a good fish now. Something like
that. What is it? It's here somewhere. Let me find it. Come on. It's in there somewhere. Oh,
don't you know that's going to be a big pull now. It's going to happen. Just trust me. It was
something like that. Did I do it? Hold the handle. Oh. 15 tickets. Come on. This thing's expensive
too. It's always the most expensive thing in the whole arcade. How much is it? It's a dollar. All
right. Let's do it again. Oh, you got yourself 40 tickets. I have to find one on YouTube and I'll
play it. Oh, 40 tickets. Don't you know? No, this game is a scam. Fuck this game.
No, I don't want to see like an actual Big Bass. Let's see if I was right.
Does it? Come on. Let's see what she can do here. Okay. Let's keep an eye on things.
I just want to hear. No, I want it. Now this is YouTube. This YouTube channel is about playing
arcade games. I didn't even know that. Big Bass arcade voice. Do it. Oh, you got 100 tickets. I
told I was right. No, no, I'm not playing that one. Give me my tickets. Let's get the hell out of
here. I remember this one. Wait, let's see. We got to go in order. I can't just run around like a
child. In order. Treasure in the sand. 50 cents for one. I never played this one before. How does
this one work? Use joystick to move arm and knock off coins. Like what? What's my time limit?
This is just like a bunch of hit markers. I just called in like the AC 130 in Call of Duty.
Okay, game sucks. I don't want to play it again. Dumb. Oh, don't go. What do they got here?
It's a coin machine. I like that. I'm gonna get the cards and I'll be fine.
It's another one. Yeah, but these ones are fun. I can only get one dunko with three cards and then
I won't do it ever again. Come on. Give me the dew. Got it. Got the end. Oh, perfect. Yes. All right, 500.
I'll take 60 tickets. That sounds good to me now. Be a good sport. Play again. He does that too. We might have to
listen to that. Oh, you got eight tickets now. But honestly though, that machine. Fuck that machine.
That machine's stupid. Not because it's in this game. Like it's cool to have that in the game.
That thing is always like six bucks. It's like four to six dollars to spend that thing
at every arcade I've ever been to. All right, I'm gonna get them all right here. You know, they make
these for adults in Vegas. They don't make this shit like this in a slot machine. If this was real
money, that would be pretty fucking fun. No, I don't want to sit there and spin like the one-cent
machine. I want to put like quarters in here and have the quarters come out. Oh, come on. What'd I
get? Dunk again. Yeah. But what did I get? What was that? Was it just eight tickets? Eight tickets?
Yeah, I know about pachinko machines, but hold on. All right. Aren't pachinko... Can't you not do it
with real money? Isn't it kind of like you pay and you get like these balls and you can get...
You can essentially do the... It's like ticket redemption. Yeah. Imagine these were just like
silver dollars in here and you got them. I don't know what those are doing. All right, let me go
for this last one. Yeah, some casinos in Vegas still have the old coin machines, but they're
not a thing anymore. Come on. Shit. All right, I'm giving up. I don't care about it. No, I don't care.
I don't care. So look, I set it up. I set it up for somebody else. Some lucky kid's going to come
over and get that. No, I've set it up for somebody. What's my inventory? I have an empty backpack.
How's that possible? Anything good? No. All right. What's this? No, that's rankings. It's a ranking
system. Hold on, guys. I'm trying to open a jar. Hold on. I can't do it. I'm trying. Kim came in.
She wanted me to open a jar for her because I'm trying to get strong, but I'm not strong enough.
I'm trying. No, I can. I can do this and I'm going to do it. Hold on. I need like a grip.
Yeah. Give me that. Give me that thing. Face cam. I don't have any clothes on. I can't put a face
cam on. I'm going to get this. Yeah, I got it. All right. You're welcome. That was fucking impossible.
Thank you. All right. What would we do? Mountain Dew. Is that what we're going to get? How much
these cost? Oh, I can get one of these. You can actually, can I drink them? Oh, which one? I always
go right in the middle because for some reason, everybody that uses these machines, they do the
first two or they do the bottom two. So you know how you get, that's not that. Wait, hold on. I'm
just coming to a realization here. If nobody presses the middle button, doesn't that mean that
the freshest ones are not in the middle? You should always do the top one because that's one
that gets filled, right? Fuck. I've been doing it wrong the whole time. Jesus. Well, you slammed
that one. Do you guys do redemption here? Can I get five cents for this? What the hell? Oh, no,
no, no. I'm not ready for that yet. One point ticket. Oh, wait. Ticket redemption center.
Oh yeah. That's right. You put this in and then you feed the tickets in.
169 tickets. Cool. All right. Oh no, not this thing again. This, that thing seriously ruined
my entire childhood. Prize master. Wait, there's a show going on in there? Not yet. Not yet. Hold
on. Wait, I need to play the games first. Oh, isn't it? Yeah, this is the one we have to push
the thing perfectly into the slot, right? Okay. Let's try it. How does he, how do you start it?
Start it. How do I go up? Oh, what? No, no, no, no. Okay. So you have to move it and then you have
to hold to, and then you have to release. All right. Let's do it again. Right there. Shit.
This is fucking expensive. This is really expensive.
One more. Get it? It's right there. I can do it. This is actually the worst machine in the
whole entire arcade play. It really is. They also do have one where you blow up a balloon
and you never play that one either. I don't even know why that's in the arcade.
No one touches it. I think that's it. I got it. How much is it? How many tickets? Oh no,
I don't want to play again. 100 tickets. What a dog shit prize for five bucks.
Just wait, just wait till you guys get the chance to play this one. I can't wait for that. It's
going to be so much fun. All right, let's go 500 right here. You got to let me do the thing
where I turn and look into the side like everybody does. I think that's it. I think I got it. Which
one is that? 10 tickets? Come on. Do it again. Just watch the edge. I should be able to get it.
Well, I broke it. I broke it. Hey, I got a free game. You notice that? I'm going to get that one
right there. 500 tickets. I got it. Oh, sick. Thank you. Why am I doing this so many times?
How many times am I going to do this? Another 500. 500,000. It seems easier than it should be.
There's a hundred over here. Why do I get to do this so many times? Give me the hundred.
The claw is actually clawing things. I know. Weird, right? Wait, what? I have to actually pick them
out of here? Get out. It's 500. It is 500. It's 500. Get out of here. Somebody just said that's
five. No, it was 500. Get out of here. It's my birthday, not yours. I know this one, too. This
one's awful. Okay, let's do this one. Same deal, but with rings. Let's try to get the hundred in
the corner. I think now. No? Well, I'll take 25. You piece of shit. I'm just going to go in. I'm
going to try to feed it through the middle of these two right here. There's a 50 right there,
too. It might work. Let's ring it through. Come on, get like four of them. Oh, this is a freak out
scenario. If I was a kid, aw. You pick up three things at the same time, you are more likely to
get struck by lightning than have that happen to a claw game. Nice. All right. Should be able to
feed through. What's the green? Is the green 500? Oh, shit. All right. I'll take the hundred.
The green's 500. Get the green. Oh, no, no more. I got enough. I got enough money.
Yeah, this one sucks. I'm going to get stuck here for like at least 20 minutes.
This is the one where you have to gently tap the spring to make it so it almost gets all
the way but doesn't go all the way. So how do I do it? Where did it go? Can I get a better view?
I want a better view of this. Okay. How to play. Find the green light. That's where you want to
get the green light. Press and hold. Green lights up. I can't see it. Do it again. Yeah, you want
it to land on the... Okay, you want to land right there. But I also want to be able to... I want a
better view. Get it. Get it. Oh, that's too bad. Do it again. It's all the way up. Oh, shit. Too much.
Another hundred tickets. I like this one. Where's the green? Where is it? On the other side. All
right. It's like in the middle top right. Oh, whatever. 20 tickets. I'll take it. How much money
do I have? All right. Right there. All right. Come on. Ready? No. I have to get it at least once.
Right there again. 100. It's fine. I could probably do this noise perfectly.
I'm getting a lot of tickets though. It's 2,500 tickets. Damn it. Too hard. Make the noise. I'll
try. I gotta get away from the mic because it's gonna be loud. The first one was perfect.
Okay. Come on. I have to get this one time. All right. I refuse to move on until I do this.
You understand? You understand? I will call Uncle Phil and have him deposit five grand into my
checking account. That sound is easy to make. You just have to go. Uncle Phil. Look at this shit.
It was always so fun to see that. You always got jealous of that motherfucker. When you walked by
and that person was sitting there with their hands on their hips like, oh yeah, well the thing just
spit out hundreds of these tickets. Like I primed it. I prepped that fucking thing for you.
It takes like 20 minutes and they don't even pick them up. They just let them pile up like this.
Guys, it's 2,500 tickets. I have to do that. I have to get the PlayStation 4.
Come on. Come on. I just need to do this once. Same spot. A little bit harder.
That's the one. No, it's not. I had it. That's the easiest one to get.
Find the green light. Right there.
I have to do this.
Who cares? I care. I do. It's not close. Imagine going into an arcade and I'm standing there.
I'm hogging the machine right now. There are children that want to play this.
Children. And I'm like leaning in and like lifting my legs up. Oh, whoa, almost. Can I try?
Just turn and look at them. I can get this. I can do this. Excuse me, sir. Can I play?
And turn and just fucking yell that over there. I don't even know where it is.
What a psycho. Going in. How much money do I have left?
I'm kind of like sicko millionaire. Like goes in here with like 500 bucks to.
No, I've got to hit the green. I've got to do it. I don't give a shit about this.
It's just not even real currency. I don't care. I plan on just walking by and throwing this in the
trash. Just a few more. You can afford a Tootsie Roll and an eraser. Yeah, I can get a box of nerds.
Don't worry, guys. Only eight grand worth of these gets you the PlayStation 4.
I can also get a sticky hand, too. Why have arcade even like Dave and Buster's does this?
And I don't know why. Is there some kind of weird racket? Weird, like cornered market with
ticket prizes? It's always like fucking sticky hands, Tootsie Rolls, like the finger traps,
shitty stuffed animals, and weird alcoholic joke shit that nobody ever uses.
I don't want that. What do you mean what? The ones that like the it's the top is
look like it looks like an hourglass. It's it's empty at the top empty at the bottom.
You flip it. You can take a shot either way. It's real jokey. You guys have never seen that before?
What are you talking about? This is the one. That's the one. That's the one. This is the one.
I hate you. I hate you, game. Oh my fucking god. I'm not leaving.
The ground is going to be tickets more than ground. I don't care. How much money do I have?
I have a dollar left. Uh oh. How do I call uncle? I have to get it right now. Shit. No. All right.
Just hold on. Let me get some more money. Nobody touched those. How do I get more money? I have to
go to the money machine, right? Just making sure. Tickets. Tickets. No. No. Where's the
where's the money machine? All right. How do I get more money from uh from Dr. Phil? Whatever
his name is. VIP birthday room. Okay. I need to go to the VIP birthday room. I thought this was the
VIP birthday room. Watch out. Little Jacob has to go into the money machine, guys. I'm not even
part of the party. Is this all I care about? All right. I took my shower. Is this how like
billionaires take showers? Just wet one dollar bills. I gotta turn it up. New song. No. New
song. Whoop. I think I just killed someone. What? What happened? It's shining flashly. All right.
What else is over here? Is that it? Little goodie bags. Ooh. Cheesy poops. Why did I even buy a
drink? I want to do a money shower again. Is this some other kid's birthday party? I think I could
do if these existed I think I would be really good at it. I think I could get almost every single one
of these. If I had to take a bet, hey you give me a hundred bucks and you go in there and you try to
get as much as you can, I think I could make more than like two or three hundred dollars. Keep that
in mind. Keep that in mind. Keep that in mind. I want one of these. I'm gonna get one of those.
Keep that in mind. What else is over here? Is this like the actual birthday party?
Are these the adults? What's? I don't understand this. Islandville Times. Carnival coming to town.
It is coming to town. You're right. Pinata? What a spoiled little shit. It's not even time to do this
and I'm just gonna break it. This is an hour or two from now. That gets hung over there. But I'm
gonna break it now. All right. I'm good. Let's go. I got my money. I'm going back to the duck machine.
Whatever the hell this thing is. Move. I'm ready. Here we go. First try. I'm sorry. I have to do it.
Each one of these has to be completed somehow. This is the best one to do. That's it. That's
the one. It is. Oh my god. You know what's actually kind of funny? I think I have sat there
at an arcade doing this machine cursing at this thing. Doing the same. At least it's for free.
You know there's like peep. There's like the families and kids around. I want to hear them.
So I just like put my hand up to my mouth and pretend I'm sneezing while coughing.
So every time I miss you know you have to be playing it like fucking 60 times.
You just go like and like you move your head forward like you sneezed every time.
It's easy. People think you're sneezing or coughing.
It would look so obvious.
Yeah I know. If somebody sat there for that long. Is there a policy in arcades? Does anybody know?
If there's somebody getting anybody work in an arcade. If there's of if somebody getting overly
frustrated. Is there a protocol where it's like okay like we should probably what do we do?
As long as you don't puke you're fine. All right I'm only I this can't be the whole stream.
So I'm gonna only try this like 30 to 40 more times. I got plenty of money. It's all right.
God damn it. This is not gonna be the whole stream. Try to fill the building with tickets.
Just he says don't pick up any tickets. Oh god. They're not taking anything. It's fine. I have
to accept defeat. I'll accept defeat when I go to zero in my bank account.
I just realized how unhealthy of a thing that was to say.
No no guys. I'll stop when I when I go to zero in my bank account.
What? That's not what you should be saying. That's not what you should ever say. Somebody just said
I'm never gonna hit that green light. I can come back to it. I'll come back to it later.
After I do this like another 10 more times. This is the one right here. Come on. Ready? One
two three. It's the one. Fuck. Not hard enough. I'm doing it way too soft.
Is this the whole? It's not going to be the whole stream. I can't even leave.
I can't leave. It won't let me leave. I'm stuck. All right. I'm fine. What's this one? Mega drop.
Oh I remember this one. This one's cool. Tickets. They'll be fine.
How many balls do I get? Just one? Yeah you the mega jackpot's almost impossible to get here.
Say I know that it's impossible.
1448. Get in there. What's that? What happened? Add bonus ball. I did it. I could do more.
Hit drop bonus. Hit drop bonus balls for rapid fire bonus. Oh you gotta get it in. That thing
has a ring around it though so it's impossible. What was that? Mystery bonus?
That's not bad. That's 212 tickets. How come they're not coming out? Let's go straight in.
250 tickets. There we go. Do you want me to do it again? I'll do it one more time.
Almost in there. 40 tickets. I used to time the ball falling straight into the highest prize
one. It takes time but I perfected it as a kid. Yeah you can just time it just to go straight in.
Give me the mystery bonus. What is this? Like roulette wheel bullshit? This is just roulette
wheel for kids. Get in there. Give me the 50. You're still checking to make sure the tickets are on
kind of. I want to make sure that they... I want to fill the whole house. The day even busters here
you put an out of order sign on this machine because it was too easy to get constant jackpots
out of order. I thought they want people to win. One more time.
Ah it was right there. Get in there. Get in the mystery bonus.
I can't wait to play skeeball. Oh it was right there. I want to just try to get that once.
I'm gonna try timing. We have a new noise to make.
Oh I did it. I actually did it. I actually did it. I did it.
Oh there's gonna be more bonuses. What? I thought that was like super bonus. Drop bonus. I thought
I just... I thought it doesn't drop. I thought it drops like a bunch of them. Like rapid bonus drop.
I needed to mash the button. I was clicking and didn't do anything.
Imagine getting the bonus first try and not hitting the button to get the bonus.
I thought I was. It just disappeared.
I did it again.
Wait what? What happened to that one? No I gotta hear the Yoshi sound one more time.
There it is. I love it. I love the Yoshi sound. I have to hear it like a few more times.
Got it. My brother could kick your ass this game. Tell him bring it on.
Well that was like three or four consistent bonus balls in a row.
Damn it. All right I'm gonna try to get the jackpot. I'm gonna try to go for it.
I'm gonna try to time it. Like right here. Ready? Oh that was close.
It's that like stupid toilet bowl lid that fucks you up.
One more time. Get in there. Rapid bonus. Mega bonus. Oh no.
The tickets are not gone. The tickets are still there. I can see them.
Oh shit. Get in there anyways.
Here we go. Ready?
And try it last time. Get in. The tickets didn't despawn. I have an eagle eye on them.
Mega jackpot. Get in there.
Oh.
And that's the way he went. What? That's not what it looks like.
Are you serious? Why is this like such a tiny pile? Just making sure.
Come on. Come on. Let's go. This is the one. Come on.
I got my muscle memories wrong. What happens if it goes in the toilet?
There's no skill to this. Well how? What do you mean no skill to this? How have I not hit it?
It's forward momentum and spring-loaded action. Don't make me get one of these for the carnival
stream and have you guys prove me wrong. Don't make me rent one of these. Come on. Get it.
Can I do it? Oh my god. Damn it. All right. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out. I'm out.
After this last one here. This is the last one and then I'm out until I come back.
I have to do this at least once. My brain is wired so fucked up. You know what I'm saying?
I have such a fucked up wiring of my brain. I have to do this even if the stream is off.
This stream could not be online and I will sit here until I do it.
And now I'm just not even close. Kim will come in here and ask me to open another jar.
My hand will be too weak from clicking this mouse. This is it. This is the one right here.
Oh damn it. What a loser is what he just said. What a loser. Oh my god.
I have to win to prove that person wrong.
You can do this with cheering you want. Thanks guys. I need more cheering.
This is getting really high. I'm gonna be able to make a ticket snowman.
This is gonna hurt somebody. That's a hazard. I'm only gonna try to get this one spot here.
Ready? I'm gonna have to count here. Ready? This is this spot right here. One. Two. Nope.
It's less than two seconds. Yes, I'd like to play again. One. It's a little more than one second.
Less than two seconds. More than what? That doesn't make any mathematical sense.
It's more than one second. Less than two seconds. So it's like 1.72.
It's like 1.82. It's fucking hard.
I'm turning into an ape. That was so fucking loud. I'm so sorry.
I'm so sorry everybody. That was fucking loud. That was rigged. It is. I did it.
My god. It wanted to do it too. All right. I'm gonna do it. I got it. It's gonna happen.
Here it is. This is literally a podcast at this point. He hasn't moved from this spot.
This would be the shittiest podcast I've ever listened to. Hey everybody. Welcome to the podcast
here. Yeah, hold on. Hey everybody. Welcome back to the podcast. Today's episode is...
Almost. Now we're gonna take our mid-podcast break. Please listen to our sponsor. Why would
you download this podcast? Imagine that for like fucking two hours? That's what's happening now.
You don't have to imagine because that's what's happening right now. That's what has happened.
It has been an hour and 25 minutes. You don't need to imagine or pretend.
Okay. This is the one right here. They're not giving it to me anymore because my
cursor's on it. The game developer put in a feature. All right. I'm serious. This is like
the last three or four times I'm gonna try this. Okay. I gotta get like three or four more attempts
with the green being there. Which one is it? This one? It's this one right here. Oh shit.
Fucking psycho. Go cash your tickets in. That's it. I know it. I know that's the one.
Okay. Here it is. One, two. Get out of the way. Come on. Whoa. What just happened?
God damn it. Don't let the chicken win. Okay. At this point people have their phones out
and this is like watch this guy at the arcade being insane. There's like people,
there's like 10 cell phones behind me. Oh my god. I'm gonna freak out.
One, two. Oh my god. What do I do? How do I get out of this? I have to like rip the,
I have to rip the ethernet cable out of my computer I think. I have to rip the power out.
All right. One more try there and that's it. And then I'm moving on to the next machine.
That has to be right there though. Please do this forever. No. Don't enable me.
Get out of here. This is, this is my ticket. All right. Oh fuck. One more. No. That's it.
That's it. I gotta get out of here. I have to leave. That's it. I can't do it.
I can't do it. I'm out. I gotta leave. I can't do it. Just rip it out.
I can't, I can't do it. But what's, there's no reason to try. I can't do it. I can't move.
You know, this looks like somebody, it looks like you've
squashed this and all of its guts came out. What's this one? I love this one. No. In order. In
order. In order. I'll be back motherfucker. I'll be back and I'm gonna, I'll take care of that.
Don't worry. All right. Let's play skeeball. I did it. I did it. I can leave. I can leave. I did it.
What's this? Okay. I went. I went. Okay. I'm out. That's enough. I did it. I knew I had it in me. I
could feel it. I could feel it. I just had, I knew it. I, you know something you just know.
I just knew it. I felt like, like a, like a guardian angel landed on my back and was like,
Jeremy, you can do that. I was like, okay. Oops. Ooh. This is fun. Cole, RG, thanks for the five
community subs, Cole. Thank you for those. I gotta get a hundred. Hundreds. It's so satisfying to do
swish it. Oh, come on. What a dick. Swish it. I gotta get a swish. Oh, one swish and then I'm done.
Oh, use the tickets. I will. I will. I'm just making sure that nobody else can touch that machine.
I have it reserved. A hundred. Oh, they're not going to despawn. I got a, I got a good eye on
him. Oh, shower please. Okay. Let's get him. You ready for this? You ready to pick up our
baklava? This is going to be so satisfying. What? What do you mean stop? Stop. Stop. Stop. Why?
What are you talking about? Okay. That's it. Just want to see if I had, if lightning can strike twice.
I'm done. All right. Let's go count them. How many tickets do I have? How many tickets do I have?
10,000. What do I got? 80, 80, uh, 8,800? All right. What's next? Ski ball. I want to get the,
I want to get better ski ball. Let's do the one on the right.
8,600, 800, 8,641. How many points do I need to get on ski ball before I move on?
I'll determine that in a minute. I gotta find the hundred and just keep it in the same place.
That's the strategy. Just don't move the fucking mouse. So I'm going to, let's see.
Let's see right here. Maybe like right there. And then we're going to go halfway up. No, not even
close. No, a little bit less than that. I need to get 800 points to leave ski ball. Uh, that's never
going to happen. Why do I keep moving? I'm not moving. It's going, it's doing that automatically.
It picks up the ball. Yeah. Just climb up on the machine and put it in the hundred
and then get yelled at and you get told, don't do that again. Oh, okay. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
Yeah. Just walk over there, reach up and drop all the balls in there and then get yelled at
and have your mother get called. Oh my God. I have to get a hundred points. What a pathetic score.
90. I can't, come on. I can't even get my IQ in this game. Let's go. I gotta get at least my IQ.
Come on. You can't get zero points. See that you, you are on top. You got that one. You're on top
of that. Why is it so hard to get the hundred? There it is. All right. Right there. I know where
it is. Just don't move from this spot. Ready? Shit. All right. I'm, I'm, I'm almost at my IQ.
So I passed it by just a little bit. All right. I got the hundred. That's all I care about.
Is there one more? All right. 180. No, I'm done. All right. Let's go and get these up. 180 tickets.
All right. So that leaves us with the ones in the middle and then there's, I think there's another
floor. Yeah. I know there's like another floor, but I remember this one. You have to speed drop
this. All right. Let's try it. You got to try to get all 50, right? Press the button to drop
balls into the buckets. You got to try to go like, yeah, you have to like spam it and get it in.
So like this, you got to try to get five in each one. If I remember to get them all.
I can do all 50. I can do all 50 guys. Just relax. You got to go one, two, three, four, five,
one, two, three, four, five. Ready? What? What? What? Why? Why? Why? It delayed. It was lagged.
What the fuck was that? Pull back that button. Listen to the clicks. He wins another one.
Another 500 tickets. Another one. Thanks guys. You want to see me do it again?
Yeah. Do it again. Do it again. Yeah. All right. I guess I'll do it again.
Nobody was watching. That one didn't count. Okay. Here we go. I can do this twice. Ready?
Oh man. That's an easy. I'll do it. I got it rigged. I will get. Thank you. I'll do it again.
I'm going to get like 5,000 tickets one more time. I got to get three, three times.
It's a drum. An easy 1500 tickets. Shit. It's okay. Sorry. Cash out. Cash out. No, no. I'm fine.
All right. Let me get it one more time. Let me try it one more time. Ready? No, I didn't mean to
click. I clicked accidentally. My fucking death adder. All right. I'm done. I'm going to go to
the next one. I won it twice. That's all that matters. This person's even wearing AirPods.
She can't even hear me. Right? I'm fine. All right. Here we go. This one will. I had to do
this one last down here because this one's going to fuck me up so bad. I have beaten this in real
life before. I've gotten the last prize before. I have done it. You remember this one? Minor prize.
Go for the major. Oh, fuck. It doesn't, it doesn't every, it does that every time. It doesn't,
it does it on purpose. It does it on purpose. It does it on purpose. It pushes it forward.
I'm rushing. I thought I had it first try. Come on. No, major. Give it to me. You fucking piece
of shit. Major. And I fucking just, my hands are greased. I had to dump my hand in oil before I
played this one. All right. Fuck. I have to win this. It's, I'm locked in now. No minor prizes
for me. I got to get the last one. Sorry. Fucked it up. I'm like too, that's too much pressure.
I wish I had the button in front of me. You know, the big like, what? What? That was correct.
That was correct. That was correct. And something you need to know about this game
in real life. I don't know how it is tuned in this one, but you can actually inside of this machine,
you can tweak to make sure that even if it's done correctly, the person doesn't win at all.
It just skips. So I don't, it could, this one could also be rigged. I don't know.
I thought I had it that first try too. Holy shit. Relax. Okay. I did it. Oh, I got headphones.
No, what that was, that was, that was all, that was a wound of a bunch of tension that just had
to come up. That was just a bunch of like neuroticism that had to release from my body.
Oh, nice. Wait, what? Can I put them on? That was a feel good ink laugh.
10,000 tickets. I win. I beat all the games. I did them all. I beat this one. I got the 500
tickets on this one. I got the 500, a hundred tickets on this one. I beat the chicken.
I got the jackpot on this. I got a hundred. I didn't beat this one. What are you gonna get?
You gonna get hockey? You gonna spell hockey? I did beat the chicken. I got the green light.
I said where's the 500? I got 500. Let me try to spell hockey.
I blew it. That was 500 right there though. All right. How many chances do I get?
I never got the mega jackpot on the draw point. Yeah, but I got the regular. I got the jackpot.
This is gonna be hard to do. Shit. How many times you get to do it once? Three times? Four times?
Hello. Hi, guys. Well, that was weird. Strangely enough, the internet just cut to zero.
I don't know what happened. I don't know why. It was pretty perfect the whole time.
So that's really fucking irritating. But hey, we're back. Welcome everybody. How you doing?
Let's see if it happens again. Probably not though. Who knows? So sorry about that. Let's
try this again. Hey, we're back. How are you? Uh, Pinman. Thank you Pinman for the 10 community
subs. Appreciate it. 10 community subs from Pinman. I'm gonna make the- I'm gonna re- I'm
just gonna tweet again just because people probably thought that might have been it.
But it's not. Can I- can you retweet your own tweet? What happens if you do that? Is that- is
that- can you do that? No, no, no, no. That's stupid. I'm not gonna do that. I'm gonna redo
the tweet. Did anybody see my tweet? I'm gonna redo it again. Retweeting your own tweet and then
quoting that tweet in another retweet. I'll just do this. Damn it. I was- we were writing- we were
in the groove too. That's- that's so unfortunate. All right. Don't let it bother you. Don't let it
just- didn't happen. Didn't happen. Didn't even happen. Let's go. It bothered me. It bothered me
too. Let me spell hockey. But thank you for your patience everybody. It's 10. I don't think it's
even possible to do this. You gotta get them lined up together. H- okay. H-K-E. It carries over.
Oh shit. Okay. So I need the O, the C, and the Y. Okay, let's try to get the O, the C, and the Y.
Bingo. Oh, that was- that- that was just right off the grid. That's perfect.
C. All right, just need the O. What's the jackpot? That- that would be the jackpot, wouldn't it?
Where's the O? There it is. Damn it. I blew it. It's all right. Come on. Wrap around again.
2,000 tickets! Are you fucking kidding me? That's like the biggest jackpot so far.
I almost just did an evil laugh. Let's get these counted. I did it all. I- I- okay, now we have to
move on to the next set of games. I got the fidget spinner. I got the- the hockey jackpot.
I didn't get the jackpot on this, but this thing's stupid, so I refuse. I don't know
what the jackpot is on this, but I don't know. I refuse. I got the cards here. Let's count these.
I'm not gonna cash in yet. You only got one of the three fidget spinners.
I'm not gonna get all three fidget spinners. All right. This is my birthday party. Should I
spend them? Ticket redemption kiosk. I have 13,000. Do I get to hold on to these? All right,
let's see what I get. All right. Glow stick is 250 tickets. I'll take a glow stick.
Okay, cool. What else do you got? A stuffed coin? Dumb. Nobody wants that. Paddle ball? No.
It looks- that'll go into the trash. Basketball? No. Fuzzy dice? No. 2,500 foam hand. Stuff ticket?
No. Stuff donut? No. That's ta- how many do I have? 13,000? 25,000. What's the most expensive
thing here? A mirror? A slingshot? Does it work? Can I actually use it? Piggy bank. Headphones. I
already got the headphones out of that thing, so I don't need these. Salt rock lamp? Yep.
Those things are so cool. 100,000 tickets is for the boom box. 50,000 for teddy bear. All right.
He just lifts his hands up over the counter and lets it go. All right. I'm gonna save my tickets.
I got what I want. I got a glow stick and I got a salt lamp. How much is the PlayStation 4?
It's not on here, unfortunately. Can't save indoors. How do I get my card out of there? All
right. I'm giving my stuff. Okay. Let's go to the next part. I've completed all these ones.
So how do I go- how do I get to the next area? With games. I know there's more games. Go to my
golf cart. Jerry's the pier. The beach. Is it the pier? Oh man. There's like rides too? Are you
serious? How much does it cost? Your wallet balance. So I can do eight pack ride pass.
Let's get the mega pass. Wait. I can only afford this. Okay. There's the eight pack for the ride.
Okay. Eight ride pass. Should I bring more money in here? I'm getting- I gotta get more money from
the uncle. Hold on. Yeah. Back to- hold on. Back to Larry's. I need to go back in my money shower.
Go rob your uncle. No. My uncle just stashes one dollar bills in here for me to take whenever I
want. And give me some of this too. Just do the money shower for 10 minutes. I'll get 200 bucks.
We'll do this until I get 200 and then we can just- we can go do the rest of it. Just stay in one
spot. Is one of the tricks for this thing? People freak out and they try to grab all over the place.
No. Just keep your hand here and just grab. Grab, grab, grab, grab, grab, grab, grab, grab, grab, grab,
you'll get as many. You don't have to freak out. People freak out in here.
And make sure you put them in your pockets or in your underwear. You know, people are like,
oh my hands are so full. I don't have any more room in my hands. Just stuff them down your pants.
Like stuff into your underwear. Keep grabbing. Okay. That was weird. Because it's hard to do
your pant- your pockets. You might be panicking and it's hard to get your hand in your pockets if
you're stuffing bills in there, but your underwear is just a gigantic elastic pocket.
I would just be grab, stuff, grab, stuff, grab, stuff, grab, stuff, grab, stuff. I would take them
all. Once you have 10 bills in your pocket, it's going to be hard to put anything else in there.
One more time. Tuck your shirt in your pants and then your shirt isn't bagged. Yeah. And then just
start feeding it down. First put like rubber bands around the bottom of your pant legs
and then just become an inflated guy. All right. I got 200 bucks. 199. That's fine.
I'll take it. Get out. That was like very clear. Get out of my way. All right. Let's go to,
is there a, uh, how did I get to that before? I have to be outside. I was just thinking about
doing the chicken game again and I freaked out and stopped. All right. Um, let's go to,
let's go to Barry's. Let me sell my stuff. You know, I had to try, right? Barry's. All right.
Please use the other door. No, I'm using this one. Pawn and swap. Barry, we buy anything.
What's my hand? Oh, my card. Cheesy poops. I thought they were poops. Okay. My uncle gives
me these for free. Why would I buy them? That's enough of that. Uh, what's this? Okay. So, uh,
let's go here. We have to put in the headphones. How much are the headphones worth?
I thought that said 4,500. All right. What about the salt rock thing? I don't think I want this.
Yeah. I don't want like the zip. Yeah. I did say it was cool, but that's whatever.
Keeping the glow stick. All right. Let's go to the pier. I'm ready. I got my pass. Let me get,
I need to get me get another pass. The super pass. I have like 40 rides. I have like 30 something
rides. All right. Let's dart over here. 20 coins for $5. That's one of these machines. I hate these
things. Ah, hold on. I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it. Shit. I hate these ones because
it's travel time. What is it? What do those chips do? Can I hit the machine? I probably can,
but it's going to get me in trouble. I gotta wait. I gotta time it. I'm going to do this way.
No. Damn it. Hit it. I'm not going to hit the machine. That's again, that's illegal.
That's against the law. No, I'm not going to do something against the law.
We're going to win this the right way. This isn't even working.
This doesn't even do anything. I'm trying to get it like, what am I doing? Why am I trying to do it
like that? I don't know why I'm trying to get it to land on top of that. It makes no sense.
Pick a prize. Hammer. Four prize credits. I don't have any prize credits. All right. Let's see this
again. I can do this. What's over there? Look at how empty that one is. All right. We're going to go
now. Ooh, dropping more prize tokens. Why is this not moving? Are these just glued on here
under the coins dropping down a hole? Wait, why? Why can I, why would I be allowed to do this?
This seems like cheating. Tokens have no real value. These machines are not regulated in any
way and are most likely a scam. Do it again. I'm just going to put all the coins up at the same
time and try to just knock something up. He loses even when he's cheating. Watch this. I'm going to
strategically place these coins in the corner here and there's going to be a big push. I wish
they would not stack on top of each other. Why are they doing this? Why are you doing this? Stop
doing that. Why? That doesn't make any, all right. I've got magnets. They magnetized. I get it now.
Do it. What? That doesn't make any sense. I don't believe that for a second.
Those prize coins don't do anything. They don't move. I'm going to do this one more time.
You can't even get them. Oh, I can get the three down here. All right. These ones are actually
not glued. The right side is the one to do. Look at how stuffed that is too.
This is depressing. This is not real money. This is not even real. Yeah, we've got floating coins
over here. It's bullshit. All right. I'm going to at least get the hammer. Let's see what I do
here. Ready? Watch this. That was not, that was unfair. All right. Push forward. Watch this. This
three is going to come out here. That felt really good. Only four at a time. That's all you need to
do. All right. I got three game points. How many do I need? Five. I think that's all I need. I
might as well get the lighter. How many more points? How many more points? They're right.
They're all right here. I got to try. All right. All right. How many do I have? It's one for the
crayon. I'm going to get the, yeah, give me this. I don't know. What? Where'd it go? Where is it?
Where's my prize? Where's the prize? Did I just get scammed? Oh, did you just like throw it over
here? I didn't know it went over here. All right. I did it. I won. This one's out of order, out of
order. No, we beat that one. I got the fish. That's all I care about. What's this? Island time customer
service out of order. Oh well. I'm doing, I'm doing the thing that your dog does when they go in the
backyard. Just run around the perimeter like three times and then come back in the house.
I need to check the perimeter. Beer tent. I got like a flashlight. Am I allowed in here?
Oh, come on. Am I not 21? Coins on the ground. Some kid will be happy that he finds that.
Bumper cars. Ferris wheel. Hold on. All right. Let's do the Ferris wheel.
Holy, why am I running so fast? I made it. Okay. So is this a stranger? Hi. I'm just gonna say the
Ferris wheel is probably the worst ride that's ever been invented. You just sit. You don't do
anything else. I mean, yeah, that's cool. Nice. But you can just look out the window for an airplane.
And like, y'all look, I can see the ocean and other stuff there. This shit's like 40 bucks to
do this. Can I stand up? It just skips it. God damn it. Well, that was fucking like seven dollars. Oh,
well. Just get on the airplane that everybody has. Yeah, just get on your airplane.
Okay. So what's over here? Look at all these. There's a bunch of other games over there. All
right. Hold on. I'm getting overwhelmed. I don't think it's supposed to be on. Somebody get their
kid. Shut it down. We've been a kid. How do I? I want to do this. No, sorry. I'm just looking for
my kid. Jerry. Jerry. Oh, here we go. I would like to play, please. All right. Bumper cars.
Peel out. This is so dumb. Is there anything else I can do while I'm in here? Or no, I'm gonna try
to get only go from corner to corner. I'm gonna try to pick up some speed and just ram into
somebody. This is what I used to do. You guys want to have a secret tip for how to do bumper cars
right? Drive around in a circle because everyone gets stuck in the middle. Build up enough momentum
going around the circle and then bang, you just smash into somebody. Otherwise you just do this.
For five straight minutes. Everybody sticks in the middle. That's the butt. This rat right here.
Well, it's not, there's usually not that many people. I'm very all right. All right. Well,
bye. Lemonade. Oh, they have the tower of terror. Okay. Hold on. Which way do I go? Over here. Wait,
wait, wait. Now wait for me. Wait for me. Come on. I'm going to get off for free. This is the
quickest way to get like your head, like your neck broken. Wait for me. Wait for me.
All right. I'll get on it. Oh, it's a security guard. How am I going to get on this?
Oh, I think it resets it. Yeah. All right. Here we go. Uh, I do not like riding these.
I don't want to be on this because people puke on these all the time. And if Guy and Sombrero
ahead of you here pukes, this is going to hit you. This is going to be, you're going to,
it's going to cover your whole body. It's going to spray you across your entire body, head to toe.
Don't ride these. If you're going to puke on one of these, lean down and like try to puke this way,
but it might get just caught up and swing up in the wind and hit somebody. I hate this. I'm
getting off. Or just lift your shirt up. Guys, if you're going to throw up on a ride, don't be the
dick. Like you're throwing up, right? So try to do just, you're going to, your day is going to be
fucked up after that. Anyways, grab your shirt, lift it up, tilt it. So it makes a big cup and
just puke into your shirt down. Don't ruin somebody else's vacation. Just, yeah, just
underwear. All right. Sucks. Who wants to ride that? Let's keep going.
I'll do this one. Isn't this now the guardians of the galaxy ride now?
Imagine seeing somebody go, Oh no. They're like pulling their pants and just puking down.
That would be the funniest thing I've ever seen in my life. I would never get over it.
Ever. That would be the only thing I could think of for the rest of my life.
Okay. I'm thinking right now as if I've seen this. I've never seen this, but I'm
laughing because of it. This didn't happen. People puke on this thing all the time too.
That's why the vents are here. Can I stand on it? I can't like stand in it.
I'm not sure I can get a free ride here guys. Maybe I can. Let's see what happens.
Nope. All right. Another game coming up. Wait, here's another ride that you should never ride
because all this ride does is make you feel like you're peeing into your stomach.
It doesn't do anything else. No, no, I'm done. I can't. I hate this thing. You could put me on
a roller coaster that goes 5,000 miles per hour. I'll ride it every time. Sorry. I don't want to
ride the thing that specifically just makes you feel like shit. That's all these rides do.
There's no other purpose for these rides. They don't do anything. The only thing they're here
for is to cause you stomach discomfort. And for one thing, I, I tried to do the, but I couldn't
get them out. I couldn't get it out. I tried. So he's just standing there. You never should ride
these rides. And I'll tell you another thing. And the thing just hits him right in the face.
That's not funny. All right. What's that? There's a couple of games, right? Here we go. One race
is fun. Ooh, this is the, you spray the, I can do this really well. You're going to spray the
circle. Is that me up there? Why am I going so slow? All right. Let me tell you something.
Number four clearly did not hit the circle one time. Look at number four. Watch number four.
No, do it again. Let's go. I'm going to put my DPI down for this. Way down. Did I do it? Three?
What? All right. I'm going to put DPI down even more. Try this one more time.
No, it's too, my sensitivity is too high. How do I turn my sensitivity down with my mouse? Hello?
Oh my God. My, the DPI is so high. I cannot even use my mouse on my desktop. Did I break it?
Uh, I think I broke it. Yeah. I can't get out of here. Shit. No, I was, I have to win. No,
it's not. I'm doing the DPI. I think I just broke it. I mean, I can alt tab, but I'm going to have
to, let's go back in. I can beat that. I just need to turn my mouse sensitivity way down because
there's no mouse settings in the game. So let me turn them. Let me turn my mouse like pointer speed
down to like tiny, tiny, tiny amount. Pointer speed. Let's go like down here. That looks good.
I think I just crashed my whole computer by changing my mouse speed.
How the fuck does that make any sense? All right. We're good. All right. Here we go. Survival. I
can't do survival. It's not ready yet. There's fireworks in this game. All right. Let me get
some money. I don't care about any of that. Just give me money. Why is it so loud now?
So much louder than it was. Why can I not change the audio now?
Load game. Um, well here's the thing. I never saved it because you can't save inside.
All right. I got plenty of money. Let's go. Uh, one more time. Generate. I don't think I even
need to click. All right. Back to the carnival. Just do the crane game. No, no, no. Everyone's
saying that. Oh no, I didn't save. That's all right. Because I can do the bucket machine
or the hockey machine and get 2,500 tickets guaranteed every time. Everything's gonna be
fine. All right. Back to the carnival. Hello, sir. I'd like to buy, uh, eight ride passes
because the rides, I don't want to ride rides. I want to play games. And there's like 10 that
I haven't played yet. So let's keep going. Back to the water spray. Is lemonade a game or no? Is
it just a lemonade? I think it's just a lemonade. 450. Are you out of your mind? What did he say?
Where's my lemonade? Oh, now the volume is too low. Why? I think I broke something.
Um, when they're strong. All right. I weirdly drank that out of the cup. All right. Here we go.
DPI is better. Time to win. I have to win every single game or riot. The DPI that I didn't do
anything. I changed. I lowered the mouse DPI and lowered the mouse pointer speed. It didn't
matter. I have to do it without it. Let's go. Oh, to relax. I got it. I'm going to have to do this
with my feet in a minute. I think I'm going to do this with my feet. No, I'm not kidding. Start
over here. It's still, I can't. I can. I'm trying to find, where's like the sweets back? Why is it
freezing up? See what I'm saying? Like why does it keep freezing? Take three as a spot. I don't think
I can do, there's nobody at three. I was trying to, I have to be at five. I'm going to try to aim
a little bit, a little bit more down. I did it. I did it. I just did it. I win. Holy shit. All
right. What do I want? Ice cream cone. I want the ice cream cone. Two of those. All right. That one's
done. Congratulations. You win. I wish I could eat those in real life. All right. What's this?
Lucky duck. What's it called? Lucky duck. I don't have to jump to see this. One duck for two bucks.
I don't understand. What does that mean? Oh, you just pick the ducks and one of them is correct.
It's this stupid thing. You can't win this one. There's no way to win this.
What are you? Three? Plus three credits I think is winning. Get pushing. What's pushing? The snake or
the cat thing? All right. Hold on. I will. I will. I'll do it. I'll do it. I need to get a plus three.
I did it. I win. Gotta win every single fucking game. Is it a bowling ball? That thing is huge.
Wow. That thing. That's the snake. That's the snake from the children's book. All right. Well,
here's this one. This one's really hard. Five balls for five dollars. You got it. Yellow is three.
Blue is two. How do I throw it harder than that? This is pathetic. I can get it in the middle. I
can get it in the middle. Let's do it again. Right in the middle. I can get it right in the lily pad
in the middle. Come on. What do you mean? No, you can't. Shit. I don't know why my brain is so
stupid. I thought that just said literally pad toss. I did it. Yes, I did it. Why was that only two?
That was on a blue. I wonder what's the middle word then? There we go. Right there. Done. Ah,
shit. This is just the chicken game again. I have to get it in one particular. It's that easy. It's
so easy when you do that. You hit the jackpot. I'm going to hit it twice. Three, two, one, two
times. Did I even get any credits? What did that even do? Give me the goldfish and the hot dog.
I win. Did I get a secret? Am I being watched? Does this guy think I'm cheating or something
of my counting cards? Shoot. Oh, that. I am excited for the one over there. I don't care
about anything else. Hundred shots for five dollars. Let's go. I'm really good at this.
It's it's I win. I did it. It's over. I won the whole thing. Give me, give me whatever
the credits you're going to give me. Perfect. Oh, I everyone wants you to get the banana. I'll get
the banana. Perfect again. That's how you get it done. Louder, louder. You turn your volume down.
Sorry, sorry. I still fine. Banana. No! Okay, I thought it was about to fall backwards.
No, that was easier than I thought it was going to be. Balloon time. Darts, right? This is the dark
game. Oh, there's that ball roller. Oh, there's so many games. I can't wait. All right, let's go.
What's worth what? Okay, I got three darts. Shit. What? Is it painted on there? One credit. Let's
get a skill shot over here. Are they all worth the same? Are they? We're getting all kinds of ideas
for the carnival stream. You guys might get to do this. I think they all just worth one. I'm going
to try to get like one of the cool ones up there. That was worth a shot. Throw it at the guy. I'll
take the hammer. Throw it straight up so it lands on your head. I can't. I can't. That went through
that guy. I won. All right, over here. This is the roll the ball one. Carnival stream. Oh, for those
of you that don't know, at some point over the next couple of months, I'm working with a robotics
team and a certain producer that is going to help make a twitch robot controlled carnival.
That's like the next big stream. It should be a lot of fun. So I need to roll this and I'm not
trying to... I don't want to give that many details because I don't want to obviously talk about it
and say, hey, this is what's going to happen. How cool is this? We're going to be here for like an
hour. You just got to get it over the hump, right? Does it have to touch the thing in the back?
You can go ahead and admit that there's going to be a dunk tank with you dressed as a clown.
Yeah, but I've already said that. You guys already know that. I've been talking about that for
months. Get in there. Shit. How much is this? Do we have to pay? No. You do not. Touch it? No.
I never understood this game. Do you just have to get it to sit in that little well?
Or does it have to touch the button? He will play this game all the time and I just like don't get
it. Is it going to be a random audience member chosen? No. Well, there's still a lot of ideas on
the table, but the theory is that it's going to be like Twitch control, like Twitch plays.
So you guys are all going to be fighting with each other to try to shoot a pitching machine
controlled robot at the dunk tank. That's as hard as I can throw it. That was as hard as I could and
it didn't do it. And we're not, no more, we're not going to talk about it anymore. Just know that
it's high. Does it matter how like where I'm looking? Just shoot it with the gun. I still
don't understand. I don't understand how, where are the rules? I don't, I did it. I just did it.
I did it. I win. I did it. They clap for me. Now I demand it. This is my stream. When I say clap
for me, God damn it. That means you do like that. I don't think you can hit the button. I'm holding
it as long as I possibly can. No, you don't hit the button. You just get one credit. I'm going to
hammer. That's a golden hammer. What else we got? Oh, basketball shot. My turn. You got to hit all
three of them. I'm actually pretty good at this when I do this in, in real life. I just jump so
high and throw it really high in the air. Okay, hold on. I can do this. Where is he aiming this?
I feel like he's not aiming in the right spot. Well, that was pathetic. If you do that at the
carnival, oh, you better not be around a bunch of friends. You can't even make it halfway up. Come
on. You can do that. I got it. Okay. I got to get three in a row though. What the hell was that?
No, I got to do more. I got to do three in a row. At least two in a row. Shit. Come on. I can do
three in a row. That's just two. I can do three. Let's do three in a row. I promise it'll happen.
I found the spot. Yeah, I kind of did. There's one. There's two. Oh, this game's fun. This is,
this is just a fun little time waster. Fuck. Just reset it. You promised. What did I promise?
Wait, what did I promise? What are you talking about? What did I promise? You promised. You
promised three shots in a row. What do you think I'm trying to do? What do you think of what, what,
I am promising that I'm going to get three in a row. So that means I'm going to do it until I
get three in a row. Stop failing. Oh my God. You guys are getting in my head.
That's not how you do it, son. I don't roll it. No, you don't. Oh, I had to roll. One, two. All
right. All right, kids. Okay, kids. I did it. Three. Imagine going to one of these things and paying
the money just to have fun and do this. But you're trying to get three in a row and your other two
balls, you just lift up, put them on the ground and say, no, I want to do it again. What a fucking
weirdo. That's not going to go in. Oh my God. I'm fucking going to lose my mind. Just, I'm just
going to grab this in one hand and crow hop and just push shot put throw it as hard as I can.
Did that just go behind me? How does that make any sense? Why is this not doing this now? How
did I, what am I wearing? What am I doing wrong? All right, I got this exact spot that I need.
I know exactly where to go. It's right on the wood. Oh my fucking God. Why is it doing this to me?
I know I promised. Just relax. You promised. How many, it's like the teacher going with
chaperoning the students and the whole bus is sitting behind me. You promised. I'm trying.
All right. All right. This is the last one. It's the last. I don't care if I don't do it.
This is it. This is the one. This is the last one. I don't think it's going to happen right
now. Let me go get a goddamn ice cream. All right, kids. All right, kids. I'm going to do it.
Oh, just get on the bus. Get on the bus. Everybody get on the bus. Go, go, go on the bus. But you're
not on the bus now. I can't, I can't do it. I can't do it. I don't think I can. I don't think I can
do it. I really don't think I can do it. It's like lagging and bouncing. I can't do it. I'm just like
the angry guy. He just like fucking whips it as hard as he can into the net. Oh my fucking god.
Get me out of here. Just stop. Just get out. Just leave. Turn around. Just get on the bus.
I'm out. I'm getting on the bus. I don't want any prizes. I don't deserve a prize.
I want to give me a donut. New text message. Oh, I'm out of money. I'm out of money. Was it a pizza?
Okay, that was fucking, that was not, that was rude. I need more money. I need, uh,
is there any other games or is that the one that beat me? Is that the last one that's going to
beat me? Do I still have my ride pass? No, let's go in here. I'm just going to make myself and
everybody watching sick, I think. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Is it still here?
Are we live? Oh god. Get off. I don't want to be on this ride. Not when the internet's having
a problem. What the fuck is happening? This doesn't make any sense. This is just strange.
What are they building over here? The UFO. Oh, is it? I know the UFO they're talking about.
When you get in, you sit, you stand and your back goes against the wall and it spins you around
really fast. Can I go in? No, fuck this thing. I hate this. I think I've only read, uh, read one
of these. Yeah. Red road. I think I've only rode one of these once and I said never again.
I only read one of these. All right. Well, that's cool. Let's go back to Larry's so I can get my
money back. Oh, I want to like play these again. All right. I'm going to just run to the machine
and I have to beat the, I can't be beaten by the basketball. I just can't. What's the, yeah. Why
do you need a flashlight in this game? There's really no reason for it. Wow. I'm just going to
turn it off. I'm going to get one of these. I'm going to get one of these for that stream.
I'm going to prove to you guys that I can do it. Okay. Now here we go. It's coming back.
UFO arcade arcade has different games. It's not a ride. Oh, that's cool.
I can't hear it. Look, I'm a fan. Hey, hey, give me that back. Yeah. Hey, that thing's worth money.
Isn't it? That's, that's worth a lot of money. Oh God. It's right here. All right. I got money.
Let's beat the basketball game. I'm going to beat the basketball. Warehouse factory. So these
aren't done, right? Are we still live? Yeah. I don't know what the fuck's happening. I have no idea.
I wish I had an idea. So is there any more games to play? Is this the last one? Go to the gas
station? Okay. Come on. All three of these. Come on. Just do it. I did not do the fireworks either.
Fuck. Oh my God. Let me, let me try a different spot.
Make sure the ball's level. Yeah. It's just bouncing around. I need to get a swish.
That's probably the best spot to do it. Right here off the backboard, but it's just so,
ah, you promised. I know. I know. I promise. No, it's, I gotta have to do it that way.
This is bird. What? Yeah. What's with the bird thing? What are you guys saying? Bird, bird,
something bird, Larry bird. What are you guys saying here? That's not it. I fucked it up.
The bird game. I don't know. Somebody said like, oh yeah, this is bird, something bird.
Did I just make that up in my head? No way. My God. What was the reference people were making
when I was sitting here playing this? Somebody was, people were saying something. I gotta go
higher. No, higher. I swear to God, somebody, people were saying like, like blue or something.
There it is. These people in the bot are going to be like, oh, that's what he's talking about.
All right. Here we go. This is it. I can finally be done. Oh, every time on the third one. Why?
That was in the same exact spot. That was in the same spot. It really was. What did I do wrong?
Now I can't do anything. Damn it. It's not worth it. This is, it is worth it. I'm going to leave
again and come back after this try. I'm going to go play the fireworks or something. Whatever.
I'm going to go to the gas station, gas station. Let's go. I don't want to play again. No, I'm done.
Thank you. No, I don't want anything. Bye. All right. Let's go to, uh, where is it?
Pier, Larry's, Barry's? Was there a gas station? Jerry's? Sorry. Jerry's. Okay. There we go.
Jerry's gas station. Soft drinks. Can you play with these? Oh no. 25 dollars. Get the 25 dollars.
No. Match three to win. Reveal three boats and get the special prize.
Not a winner. Two, none. I gotta go get some more money. Match three sevens.
No, no, no. Not Barry's. Larry's. Going and spending uncle's money on scratch tickets only.
Well, for a game that's just about like 15 to 20 little carnival and arcade game,
there seems to be a lot more you can do. One guy is making this game. Yeah. Okay. Back to the gas
station. You can do a paper route. Is that in the game yet though? I feel like is that something
that I can actually do? It is. Okay. Well, hold on. Let me buy a couple of 25 dollar scratch tickets
and then we'll go. Win. I get three, three fires. Oh my. What a piece of shit. Come on. Really?
In a row. Three boats. That's a fish. I need two more fishes. Ooh. A trunk full.
Okay. It's two fifties. Give me another fifty. No more ones. Oh my god. This is a 25 dollar ticket.
All right. Let me do the paper route. How many of these do I need to deliver? Is it a plane? No.
How do I do this? So I have to deliver a paper here. Where's my golf card? I have the papers.
No. Not again. Not again. Don't do it again. You've made us suffer enough cocks with this nonsense.
Come on. All right. So I need to go over here. All right. Which one of these does it have to go in?
There's a lot of mailboxes here. Which one is the one that who has the subscription?
All right. I'm getting stuck on the cart. Give this to me. That's two dollars. In the time that
it just took me to do that, I could have been in a great Uncle Phil's money machine for 10 seconds.
Oh, I'd love that. I'm going to get a hundred bucks and then from there I'm going to do
five scratch tickets and four scratch tickets. I have to win a scratch ticket once. We have to
win every game once. I'm going to go back and do basketball again too. It's impossible to win.
What do you mean? Hawn the newspapers. Are they worth more than two dollars?
Why am I stuck? What are they? What are they? Oh, they're little. It's like string. You shoot like
little stringies. It's a rubber band. Okay. One more. Just pawn stuff to that. Just hold on.
Let me get my bearings and see where we're at. You know what I'm saying? I might have 150. That's
enough. Okay. This is my last 150 I'm putting into scratch tickets. Pawn one of the robots. I don't
think I can do that. Remember when I won that one? Oh, I felt so good. All right. Let's pawn all
this shit. You're right. Let's get rid of it. Oh, no. I've been live for 17 minutes. No. It's
actually been like three and a half hours. It's just the stream has made a new vaude like three
or four times. They can't come in. All right. Let's pawn some stuff. Make some money. This is
all my possessions. Hey Barry, I'm here with all my stuff. I have three newspapers and a bunch of
pool toys. 50 cents. It's just a giant coin. All right. Can I put more things in there at one time?
Let's see what happens. Can I do more than one? Yeah, you can do more than one.
14 bucks. Really? What else is this stuff worth? You're selling memories.
But the memory of me being addicted to a basketball game for like fucking an hour?
I don't think that's a very good memory. The fish was 30 bucks. My last two possessions.
The snake from the... I'm keeping you. How much does it work? 80 bucks. Holy shit. Get rid of it.
All right. 330 bucks. 340. All right. Here we go. I'm the only person that's coming over.
What did I have? I had 340, right? That wasn't done. It's all right. Four. All right. I'm doing
all right. That's... I just need one more fish. 12 dollars and 50 cents. I lost 50% of what I put in.
Car. Car. Ugh. You're playing minesweeper. Let chat do one. Okay. Chat can do the last one.
All right. This is pretty good. Need one more fish. Holy shit. That is a boat right there.
Need two more of those boats. This... All right. There's two. One, two, three, four, five, six,
seven, eight, nine. There are nine slots left. Two out of nine has to be a boat. Okay. Whatever.
I made my money back. You piece of shit. Come on. Got the money back. Three in a row. They're just
sitting in a row. Unbelievable. I need one more fish. No more twos. Ugh. I just need to win the boat
or a fish. All right. Somebody just... Somebody just wrote he's so bad. You can't be bad at picking
random spaces. What does that even mean? Just give me the car. Ugh. Stop being so bad. I'm making a
mess. All right. You guys can do the last ticket. You want to show me how it's done? Let's see. Show
me how it's done. Good. Let's see how good you guys are at picking shit. Huh? Let's see how everybody
is at picking things. It's going to be impossible to do this. I can't zoom in far enough. Do your
best. Let's see how well you do. Nobody talking shit about how you're talking shit. All right. Go
ahead. Actually, it is going to work pretty well. All right. Right there in the middle. I see 25%
of you clicking that one. That's the one we're going to do. 26%. Okay. Let's do it. Here it is.
There's a three. 1250. Go again. What is the next scratch going to be? You guys are playing
connect to four. That's how spread out this is. The one that's 13%.
The one down the bottom right. That's the only has to be that one. Yeah. The one that one. That's
14%. The car. It's the $50 car. Not a bad choice. Not bad at all. Okay. Keep going. By the way,
all clicks on the left side on O, S, and H are not counted. There is no consensus here yet. Okay.
There is 16% want to do that one over on the left. That's the one it's going to be right here.
Sorry. You were not. I was incorrect. Ready? Three, two, one. It's okay, chat. We can do it.
Up in the corner. I'm doing it. Here we go. 30%. It's a four. Okay. You have two, three,
four in the tank. So you're pretty spread out so far. Not bad. Where to next? You guys almost
have a straight. Yeah. That's correct. Hmm. Pretty split between down the bottom and no,
it looks like it's right there in the middle. Bottom middle. Somebody said at least we don't
get ones. Oh, there's a hundred dollar fish ever so closer. You guys have almost every single one.
That's a good thing to do though, because then you can deduction statistically. You are making
it easier for you. I'm going to zero again. No, I'm not. All right. We're good. We've proven that
you're bad at RNG. That's not really 73% of people want to go that way, right? That many people want
to click the top left one. That's unheard of. We should do chat plays view in battleship.
I mean, we could do that, but that would require me to have another person in here because I could
just see you guys have every single one. All right. This is actually really good. Well, you
don't have the boat yet. The last one that you're missing is the boat. I'm going to go down and
scratch the void if removed. Is there any explanation as to why the void if removed
is scratchable? Why would they put that there? All right, let's go. Oh, fuck. Oh God. You guys
are in a good... This is the best spot you could possibly be in. One more fish and you have the
second best prize you can get on this ticket. Go for it. You guys are going for it. Could it be
the coveted three in a row? It might be. I don't know. That's where you want to go. That's where
we're going to go. Nope. Are you guys going to leave here with a measly $25? Better than me. I
got 25 like three times. All right. Is this your final answer? 47%. Good luck, guys. You would
never... Yup. Congratulations. My turn. I do one, you do one. Okay. My turn. I do one more.
All right. Your turn. There's so much trash everywhere. I can't even pick it up.
All right. Your turn. Your turn. What's wrong with this one? What's the prize under there? Can you
see? This one's broken. Oh, it was a three. It was a three. It actually was a three. Oh no. Keep it
going. It was the money symbol, but the other way. Kind of. Right here. You got it. First fish of the
evening. Again. I would laugh so hard if you guys got three votes. Ready? You sure? Okay. Uh oh.
Sorry, guys. That was not the right spot to be in. If we get three votes, we get to keep the
winnings. That's not written anywhere. Okay. Here we go. It's a two. Two means none. If we get three
votes, then you have to play salmon max. No. What? I'm going to do that anyways. All right. Let's...
unanimous. Oh, shit. All right. There's the vote.
Go ahead. We need a better incentive. What's something that you want me to do so bad that I
won't do? I mean, I've played two seasons of salmon max. It's not like I wouldn't do that.
What incentive? Doki doki? No. That... by the way, there's no consensus here. I gotta wait
like another few minutes. Eat another McChicken. All right. We've got a majority.
We're not a majority. We have just a winner. 1250. That leaves me one more chance to do it myself.
Fuck. No, no, no, no. I don't want to come back here. I want to go... That's it? That's not even
enough. That's not even enough for me to do it again. No, no, no. And I gotta... Oh, the F...
Right. It's zoomed in. All right, guys. I'm going to... Here's the plan. Just relax for a minute.
I am going to go get like $500. Just hang out. I'm just going to go get... I'm going to go just
take a withdrawal of $500. Fuck. I need to get... I'll do it again. That was a weak poll.
Biggly's close. Be the voice. Oh, well, look at what you did there. Oh, gonna try to get
a big fish here now. Oh, that poll was a big poll now. Oh, you got yourself 10 tickets now.
100 tickets. 100 tickets. Oh, 100 tickets. No, it's not 100 tickets.
You got yourself a thousand tickets. Come on. I'm gonna do as hard as I can and then leave.
No, wrong way. Wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong. Wait. Is this fireworks? What do you got there?
Where'd you get this? Where did you get this? Where'd you get that? Is he getting in trouble?
All right. I'm out of money. I'm out of money. I don't know what to do. The beach? Hold on. I
need to go back into dads because I need to make some money. Let's get some money. You guys all
stand and then wait. Okay, just hang out for a little bit. Just chill. What's the best way
for me to get money? I gotta be like in the right spot. Right here? Right here looks good.
The banana guy's worth 80 bucks. Where can I get the banana guy? You're right. From the
okay, I'm just gonna win the I got to go win a few times off that stage. This guy, this is the
person in the suit though. I can't like bring that. All right. I got the idea. Hold on.
I know what I'm gonna do. Let's go to the pier and I'm gonna go win the banana like 10 times.
I'm gonna have like three grand. We're gonna buy like 40 scratch tickets.
Where is he? It's the darts, right? That's the easiest thing in the game. I win. I didn't get
anything. What? I know it's loud. Just turn it down a little bit. That's three. I gotta do it.
There's whack-a-mole. Where's whack? Where? Where? Where's whack-a-mole? I didn't see whack-a-mole.
Oh, let me help you here. I'm gonna turn this down. This is probably killing you.
Oh my god. Did I mute it? I turned way down. You should be able to still hear it. Dang, sir. Why?
What are you talking about? I'm... What's a movie I could watch at any time? Um, Gremlins 2. That's
it, right? Okay. One more. One more. And that's 80 bucks. Because I'm in it. You guys know that
friends of mine, way before any of you guys made that reference, uh, friends of mine told me that
same thing. That I'm just the guy with the tie. It looks... It's... We're identical twins. Okay.
You had a friend before Twitch? Yeah, I did. Okay, so I got 80 dollars... 80 bucks there.
There's gotta be a better way. I can swish it, I think. Hold on. Pay for it again. How many
credits do I have? How... What's the mo... Okay, I can turn this back up. Uh, yeah, I didn't know
I had that many credits there. All right, so this is fine. So that's... How do I have to back a truck
back here? Oh, no. Not good. That's all my inventory space. It's... It'll be here when I come back.
Let me find where the swish is. I'm gonna say if I go, like, let's go to the top, like, up here.
Okay, hold on a minute. This actually might work. I gotta find the swish right between the A and the
B. Right under the A. Right, like, at the blue line. Nope. A little bit lower. Top of the backboard.
Close. Top of the red. That's it. That's it. It's a fucking exploit. That's two. No, dude, I need three.
I need three. I found it. I got it. That's the one right there. Right at the top of the red in the
backboard. It's a swish. And here we go. Get... Everyone get back off of the bus because this is
gonna be it. Swish. Again. Oh my god. I'm gonna get it. I'll do it. It's gonna happen. Why do I choke
on every third fall? Why? Just get it up there. I just started itching my armpits. Right there.
How does it... How does it change from the last time? How did it change from the last time?
Consistent power? I'm... I am. I'm holding it down the whole time. That's why I'm trying to find the
one spot where I can be in. It's probably something stupid like... Yeah, like somebody said the wind.
I wouldn't be surprised. I... Yeah, I know it sways in my hands. That's why I've been waiting for it
to get in the middle. It goes back and forth. That's why the line in the middle... I'm trying
to keep it just right in the middle. That's why every time I've waited till it was in the middle.
Like that. This variance... This is some kind of variance when you throw it. It's never gonna
happen. Yeah, you have to get lucky. No, I don't want to... I want to stop this. I can't even click
done. I can't... I can't get out. I'm stuck here now because I have no inventory space.
All right, get this shit out of the way. Free stuff, kids. Take it. It counts! It counts! It counts!
Counts! Counts! Counts! Counts! Counts! Oh, I keep... People are gonna say it didn't count.
It counts. It went in and went out. In real basketball, if it does that, it counts.
It counts. It counts. It counts. No, it counts. It counts. It's over. I win.
In real basketball, if it goes in and then goes out, it counts. Yeah, I win. I did it. I did it
three times in a row. All right. Okay, cool. Guys, thanks for watching the video. Weird how I did
that first try. All right, let's get the fuck out of here. Wait, can I scan these and take them out?
And then pull them out? No, I can't. I can't scan the machine. What are these worth? They're worth
$14 a piece. That's actually really good. How much are the cats worth?
Eleven. So why would I even get the cat? It's worth less. That's a lot of money. Is it given
to me in ones? All right, I got 228 bucks. All right, that's enough for good old scratch tickets.
Fucking mess out of the way. How am I gonna get? Like eight? Ten? Okay, I'm gonna do the first three
and then you guys can do one. All right, cool. Slow down. I got two cars. I got a boat. Come on,
look at how many spaces there are. Oh my god. I'm gonna do a technique. The whole
just the whole bottom row and then the whole top row. It's our turn. No, it's not. Not yet.
Why are they missing spaces? Got it. Four bucks. Yes, I am brute forcing scratch tickets. Yes,
I am. Okay, they're deleting spaces. I'm out. All right, here, your turn. Okay.
Yeah, you can do that. Yeah, let me do this one. Okay, you can do this one. You can do the,
yeah, here. You can do this one. Here you go. Wait, now you have to do with it. Okay,
we want the other one. We want the other one. We want. All right. Okay, all right.
I'll let you do that one here. All right, you can do this one. Okay, go ahead. I don't know
if I can even click this one. I'll try. Ooh, it's the trunk full $50. Nice work so far, guys.
Can you keep it up? Oh, you guys. Oh, but I don't know what you guys are. I don't know. Okay,
well, you're clicking it. Yeah, I guess you're clicking it. Did you get the ad? Because I just
played an ad. Apparently commercial break failed. Commercial breaks are only allowed once every
eight minutes. How does a commercial break fail? That doesn't make any sense. I just clicked run
ad. No, sorry, it didn't work. But you can't click that again. All right. Well, I can't do it. I
tried. Do it again. Try again. It's because nobody wants to sponsor you. I don't need a sponsorship.
I have 5,000 friends here. Think I need a sponsorship? He thinks we like, he thinks we're
friends. They think we're friends. He thinks we're friends. Why are we both lying to each other? What
are you talking about? Nope, don't act like that. There's a four. Sorry, guys. We're not real. You're
very real. All of you. Hmm. Very split on this one. Looks like this is going to be the one.
We have five community subs that just came in. Thank you for the five community subs.
It was Piffinator. Thank you, Piff. Guys aren't doing so well on this one. But thanks for the
community subs. I was just like, I just burped really loud. Hopefully you didn't hear that.
Win. Which one? Where do you want me to go? Event? I have to get the car eventually.
We're going over here. You almost, you're almost done. One more three and that's it guys.
I'll click over here. Click, click feet. No, that's okay. That's not, that's like the
soda machine. Torpedo sneak. Thanks for the five community subs. Another five gifter come through.
Thank you so much. Congratulations to the people that got those subs right here. Oh no. Oh no.
What are you guys going to do now? Tingy, thanks for five community subs, Tingy. That was five,
10, 15 community subs. Back to back to back. Thanks guys. Right here. First fish. Where is
the next fish? Gnarly five community subs. Even more. Yeah. More back to back to back to back
here. More. Another one. Five community subs from Gnarly. Five from Invaderler. Invaderler. Thank
you. Both of you. The community subs. Much love to all of you. Thank you. You got one more. Tingy with
another five community subs. Subs just rolling in. Will they get the trunk? Who knows? Thank you for
the five community subs. That was like fucking 30, 40 back to back there. And there's even more.
Magellan, thanks for the five community subs. This is the one here. This is it. Okay. If you
guys don't get this, then I get to buy five more and just spam them. You actually got it. Holy shit.
They did it. Okay. $50 winner. Nice work, guys. That's my turn. Give me another spade. All right. I
won two. I won two. I have to win on this one though. I got two for the price of one. You see,
that two came out. Thanks for winning the $50, guys. I'm putting it to great use. It's my turn
to get the car. I have to match you guys. It can't be all right in this area. Oh my God. There's a
boat. I did it too. I did it too. We're even. I did it too. And I'm going to get the fish.
What happened? Oh, okay. Let's come on. I can get a fish here. Damn it. I can't click the spades.
It's empty. Come on. No, I can't say it. Holy shit. I got a hot fire. Oh, okay. I need your help.
I need everybody's help. This is 250 bucks. I need your help. This is the ultimate win. Help me. We
need to do this together. The broken space? I don't know if I can click the broken space.
I'll try. That wasn't it. That wasn't it. Got it wrong. I had to click that like 10 times.
You think it's going to be three in a row? It might, but it might be three in a row
this way. Not this way. I don't know. I guess. All right. Oh, guys. Come on. No. No, it's not
working. Thankfully, there's still plenty of spaces because that's the only one I have two of. Okay.
Right to the right. See if it's three in a row. Hot fire. Hot fire. Hot fire. No, it's water. There
are now two waters in play. This is our only opportunity to get the ultimate win on any of
these tickets. I think, you know, there's an equal chance of winning no matter where you click. And
this is all pointless. What are you talking about? What do you mean? God damn it. Going
into a gas station and seeing this shit. This would be really, really, really fucking bad.
I would have gotten thrown out a long time ago. Hold on. Come on. Not a bad start. Come on.
Pawn the old tickets. I can't actually do this, right? Well, I got enough for one more. What's
with the fours? This is... I can do it again. I only clicked on threes. Fuck. Come on. Just let me win
a bay. Let me get a hot ticket item. We're just going to zero. Who cares? We're going to one cent.
I got it. I got it. I got it. I got it. I'll fix it. All right. We're good. We're good.
Let's go try. How much can I get for the tickets? Can I just feed them into there
if I look up high enough? 50 cents. It's not even worth doing this. I can go just get money from
Uncle faster than this. Yeah. I might as well go on the money sheen. Money sheen? The money machine.
Rather than just throw in like the crumpled up ramen bags. What is that? Fucking three bucks?
Five bucks? Eleven bucks? Six bucks? No. Just leave them. I'm still holding the arcade tickets?
Oh. Let's go. Let's go back and get some money. I'm gonna go to the beach. We haven't been here yet.
Are there any games on the beach? There's fireworks at the beach. Watch out. Watch out. Watch out.
How much are these? Ten dollars? Five dollars? How do I use it? Like that. Okay. Taxi? Taxi?
All right. I want to go back here. I'm going to get some more money and then I want to... What's
the... I want to... What do I want to do? I kind of want to play more of these. I'm fucked. I really
want to play these again. Which one do I want to play? Let's go get money from Dad first.
What's the most expensive thing? That's like the ultimate win, right? A hundred thousand tickets
is to get the boombox. I think I can do it. How do I escape this? Cover your ears. What can I sell
the boombox for? That's the question. Probably a lot. Okay. Let's go play the... Which is the one
that's easier? The ball drop one or the hockey? You can tell I've lost a step since when I won
this last time. No. No. No. No. What... This one. This... I just get... Go for the ones that are 500.
This is probably the best way to do this. Five, 10, 15, 20, 21, 22, 23, 24, 45. All right. I have to
get 10 of these to get 5,000. I missed. I need to get 200 balls.
Well, that's not going to happen. 200. At least I'll be able to get... Well, we're getting a good
start here. Not bad. 1,500. The hockey game is 2,500 if you get all the fucks. Yeah. Tickets?
One more ticket. Oh, right. It's a thousand... What about this one? How bad is this one?
What are we looking for? The green ones, right? Just go anywhere. Isn't there green rings down
there somewhere? See? Dizzy Bird. I wasn't making... Oh, that's the name of this game.
When I was shooting the basketball, people were like, oh, at least it's not Dizzy Bird.
Not Bird. Dizzy Bird. I'm like, what the fuck are they talking about? That's what I was talking
about. That's a pretty good haul right there. It's not as effective though. Come on. Pick up
like fucking eight of them. I'm going to try to get this 100 right here. Grab that one right there.
Slide it. Oh. Didn't get it. That's a pretty good haul. It's a pretty good haul.
Okay. Let's give Dizzy Bird a try. I feel like he's going to help us out here. Look.
Oh, man. I thought I did it first fucking try. I thought I did it... Oh, well. I tried. It was
close. What about this one? This one's pretty good. Uh, pond, pond, right?
Getting the Mega Jackpot. Come on. What's that? Mystery? Mystery bonus?
I'll take it. That sounds pretty good to me. Nice.
Shit. I got to get that. What's the Mega Jackpot? It's not even listed.
Jackpot. It's 2,100. What's the Mega Jackpot? It's not even listed.
Oh. Add a bonus ball. We're going to wait for that. Wait for the Jackpot to come back again.
Pretty close. Under the table. What about it?
Bonus ball. Oh, it's just doing it. I didn't even click. What does this mean? Get in there.
Oh. That's coming to the side of the machine. There are tickets over there.
You're right. There are tickets that way.
Get in. I thought I was going to go on the jackpot. $50. I just won 50 bucks right there.
Bonus ball. The ball of koala just gave me $50 and then I got the jackpot. This is fucking 10,000
tickets. This is going to be a big haul. I bet you can't get the double green on Dizzy Bird.
Thanks for the 50 bucks, ball of koala. Bonus ball. But first of all, we've got to talk about
the big haul that's coming out through here. I reset both the jackpots. Bonus ball. Two Mega
Jackpots. Do it. All right. This is like 12,000 tickets. Jesus Christ. How is that not 12,000?
What? The top was like 4,800 and the... What do you... What's this mean? What do you mean by that?
We're like 10% of the way there. 14 tickets, guys. Who cares? Who even wants these? All right.
Okay. Let's do the hockey. I gotta get a hockey. That's 500. I'm all right with this.
It's too slow. It's too slow. The fish game. The fish game's not gonna... The fish games
will be very inefficient. Just like the Bruins. What? Get in there. We want the bird game. No.
That's not efficient. This is more efficient. If I can... I gotta get hockey at least once.
2,500 guaranteed tickets. All right. I gotta be early. Like right... The bird is not efficient.
The bird sucks. It's not gonna help us at all.
This is actually turning out to be very inefficient as well. Am I scoring on my own goal?
All right. I got the C. We've got plenty of time. There's a shitload of tickets on the ground.
Oh. H. Oh, you kidding me? Really? Do they stay forever? They have to, right? Well, the one...
At least the one cool part is the soundtrack, the sound right now is doing the thing. When you go
into a place like Radio Shack that has a keyboard and it's on display and you're allowed to play
with it, you just do the same four chords like the same chord like a thousand times. That's
like all I hear. You turn it on. You put it on like the horn and you just press down on the same
chord. It was hard for me to say that because it was so loud in my ear that it was making me
hard to talk. I was getting speech jammed by the fucking Radio Shack keyboard. All right.
I just need an Y and an H. All right. Sir, sir, sir, sir. Can you stop that, please?
You're really pissing off all the customers here. $2,000.
2200 tickets. All right. Let's get them. I don't want to play again.
All right. Let's go. Feed it in. How many do I have?
10% of the way there. All right. What's the most pumped? What about these ones?
No, this thing's really bad, right? What about the stackums? What gives the most tickets?
This thing is awful. The Big Bass is the worst machine. It gives like four tickets, guys,
even if it was a thousand. That's not worth it. I can go get a thousand right now from the hockey
game. Oh, you got yourself 10 tickets. That's terrible. I didn't give this one a chance.
So you knock down all the stuff. Don't touch shovel handle. What happens if you get all the
chests? That's all chests. That's it? What's the top one? I don't have to get all the balls off?
I'm gonna do this like a lawn. All right. I'm ready. Here we go. How the fuck are you supposed
to do this? Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait. Why was it? Was it not counting these treasures before?
Let's get inside out. What? Oh, I touched the shovel. Shit. Do it again. Inside out. I'm out of
time. I feel like this one's too rigged. I'm gonna do one more technique.
It's not a bad technique if you go around in a circle and you push out.
Last try. Yeah, it's like scrubbing a toilet. It is. Let's try that again, but I'm gonna start
right from the middle. I'm just gonna do a circle around it. Just get right here. Don't touch it.
You just go like this. Oh, fuck. That's how you do it. I know that's how you do it. You gotta go.
You get a toilet brush it. You just gotta be very careful. This game's stupid. This is
dumb. All right. What about the coin ones? Why is he so bad? No, stop that. Stop saying that.
You know it makes me angry. Hold on. I'm gonna do this. I'm gonna stop at the minor prize this time
and see how many tickets it is. All right. How many tickets is the minor prize? What a joke.
Not even worth it. How much was this one? A hundred? Does it increase in value as you
go up? I bet it does. Did I just fucking do that first try? I did. So how much is the top row?
It has to be worth something. If this is a hundred tickets, then why the hell did you ever do this?
All right. Well, okay. Terror. That sounds good to me. Just do that every time. I can do this.
No, a little too early. I can hold it a little longer. I need to do this 88 times.
And you want me to do the bass game? What's more reliable? I did it too high. Too high. The bird is
faster. Let us play the lottery tickets again. But yeah, I have to have money before I do that
and I make money by doing this and then get in the boom box and sell in the boom box. That's it.
All right. This is stupid. I did it first try. Nobody who cares. Just give me my thousand
tickets and get me out of here. All right. Prize balls. This seems the fastest.
1500 is ski balls the most reliable? Is it though? How many tickets do you get for doing ski ball?
Come on. That's a good, that's a good grab. Yeah, it is. Do ball drop. Just, you can ace it every
time. Is it, is it 500 or a thousand? Doing the ball drop. I mean, this is two grand. You
know what I'm saying? Like how long is that? 30 seconds. Five, 10, 15. That was 15, 10. All
right. Hold on. Let me feed that through. How much does the headphone sell for? Um, I think 100.
Let me see. How efficient am I in this one? I'm usually pretty efficient, right? It fights. What
is it? What's the jackpot? 500? 500, right? All right. This is the only game they come over to
congratulate you on. Do it again. Let's go. I just need to do this like 115 times.
Okay. Until I, do it until I, until I don't do it. And okay. Go. Go until I lose.
What is so funny? This. Okay. I fucked it up. Got it.
Weee. Only, this never before. Is anything like this ever possible?
I fucking blew it. It's, I need to move on. I'm like, what I'm doing right now?
I'm playing a fake arcade machine. There's a, this is a, there's a real version of this and there's
like 5,000 people watching me do the fake arcade machine to try to make
100,000 fake tickets to buy a fake boom box to scratch fake lottery tickets on stream.
It's like starting to get in my head. All right. So.
Okay. I need to fucking relax. What do I have? 15%? What's the most? Okay. Ski ball. Somebody said
do ski ball. Is this actually efficient if I just do it right down the middle? That's 40. A little
bit higher, right? Right before the yellow? No, that's too high. That's too higher? Higher?
That's too higher. I'm sorry guys. That's a little too higher. There it is. What was up with that?
Jerma, wake up, please. Stop that.
You want to know what your tarot reading said? My friend says you'll freak out.
No, I don't want to do tarot reading. I thought about it would be fun to do like a tarot reading
on stream of myself, but it's probably going to be like death, death, death, puke, puke,
like you're going to lose all your money for that pathetic display. That's not bad. Hold on.
What is up with this physics? The claw. Somebody did the math and that was another thing I was
laughing at. Somebody did the math and they said you just do the balloon claw game and try to get
what free 500 balloons. And if you just do it efficiently, it'll take 22 minutes.
And then I'm sitting there thinking, is that, is that, do I really want to do that?
I don't know if that's something I actually wanted to. 600. Come on, give me 600.
You did the bird game for 54 minutes. That's, yes, that is also true. All right, let's go.
Um, what about these? No, that's not that efficient either. Okay, I'm going to go for
balloons for a little while until I can't take it anymore. You've been playing this for five hours.
You can do 22 minutes on the balloons. Yeah, but it's, there's a difference between
bonds at 22 straight minutes of me picking up 500 ticket balloons. That's a different story.
I missed. Bird game streams are entertaining to watch you.
You know, if it was allowed, 22 minutes is a one episode of Spongebob. I would just put it on the
screen and just do this. All right, let's do it. Hold on. What happens if you do, can I overflow
the balls? Put it on the background. No, I can't do that. I will get actually like terms of service
screamed at. What's the red ones? How much are the red ones worth?
250? What if I get them all? Just have text to speech, read a Spongebob script.
You can't fit that many characters in a text to speech program. Just read it and play every part.
I can't do that and play. Hold on. Let me just get out of this. Is it, is it okay? Is there a website
where I can have that happen that can take like a like that's too long to put in a text to speech
box? You read it. I can't do that. Put it into Google Translate. Oh my God. Hold on. Let me wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Is this even possible? This is Spongebob.Fan. This is the Mermaid Man and
Barnacle Boy transcript. Is this actually the right one? Is this a fan one? This, this is,
this doesn't seem to be very much dialogue. So this is the Mermaid Man and Barnacle Boy
of reenactment by, and we're going to do speed, speed like three or four. Okay. Okay. Here we go.
Just relax. Oh my God. It's crashing my computer. I think.
Also these guys. Barnacle Boy enters the Krusty Krab. Barnacle Boy. I told you I'm not hungry.
Mermaid Man. Mermaid Man and nonsense. Barnacle Boy. We've got to keep up our strength for the
fight against evil. Barnacle Boy. Want to dive Mermaid Man to the register. Runs to the register.
Can I help you? It's too fast. It's too fast. It's too fast. It's too fast. And that's like the
jokey. That's like the meme guy. It's gotta be somebody else. All right. We'll try this.
Squidward. Can I help you? Mermaid Man. A double Krabby Patty and Coral Bits for me
and a silly meal for the lad. Barnacle Boy. It's not for the toy. I just, I've got to fit in the
tights. Why can't oh, he smiles nervously. Squidward. Whatever. Five dollars. Please.
Mermaid Man. You got it. Bucky. Removes his left seashell cup. Opens the shell up like a clutch
purse and pulls out a metal nut. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Did I get
fucking linked to something fucked up here? Is this the, is this an actual real one? This is not
something fucked up weird like mermaid man porn thing, right? This is the episode. Okay. Close
up of the nut and a timpani noise is heard. Squidward. No Barnacle Boy. Confront Squidward.
Listen. Big Nose. Points at Mermaid Man. That guy has been saving your butt since before you were
born. Don't you got a living legend discounts or something? Squidward. This is a restaurant,
not a lending library. What's wrong with this guy? Pokes Barnacle Boy. And are you calling
Big Nose? Pokes Barnacle Boy again. Big Nose. Both press noses against each other. Barnacle Boy
gets out a $5 bill from his hat and he throws it to Squidward. Barnacle Boy. Well, next time
danger threatens. Don't expect any help from us. Squidward. Grabs the bill. Sarcastically. I'm
shaken. Hey. Mermaid Man and Barnacle Boy. SpongeBob. Slowly breaks through wall. Mermaid Man and
Barnacle Boy. Must get autograph. Stretch his arm to pull the pen from Tom's shirt pocket and
stretch his second arm to grab a paper from the window. Mermaid Man. If you wanna grow up strong
like me. Shows his fat belly. Shocking Barnacle Boy. You gotta leave room for seconds. Here comes
our waiter. SpongeBob. Runs while making a weird face. Autograph. Barnacle Boy. Holy sea cow. It's
that sponge kid. Mermaid Man. Quick lad. Pants falls down to the invisible boat mobile. Runs outside
while holding his pants away. Barnacle Boy. Where do we park? Mermaid Man. A SpongeBob. Can I have
your autograph? Can I have your autograph? Can I? They're gone. Gasps. Mermaid Man's belt.
Mermaid Man. Wait! We'll find it with the invisible boat alarm. He pulls it out and makes
his depressal button. Why was he acting there? A car flickers in and out of visibility. Thrives.
Making beeps as well. There she is. They run over and jump in the car. Barnacle Boy hits the seat
divider. Barnacle Boy. Wait! Rubs his behind. I told you we surely got the automatic. SpongeBob.
Hey guys. Wait up. Pulling out Mermaid Man's bell. Slow motion. I've got something for you.
Barnacle Boy. Both speed off in the boat. SpongeBob. You forgot your belt. You forgot.
Mermaid Man and Barnacle Boy drive away Mermaid Man's secret utility belt.
The emblem of submersible justice. For 65 years, this belt has helped prevent the fall of nations
and pants. I can't believe I'm actually holding it in my hands. Well, I guess I should return it.
Makes one step in the boat's direction then sprints back to the kitchen with the belt on or not.
Giggles. I could just hang onto till after work all alone with Mermaid Man's belt.
I wonder what this button does. Presses the belt and a pickle barrel shrinks. Whoa.
Grabs the shrunken barrel. The small ray. He giggles and smiles mischievously.
Squidward, here's your shake, sir. He starts to hand him the shake, but he starts making loud
noise from the kitchen and SpongeBob's giggle, causing him to accidentally drop the shake on
the guy's head. The guy punches Squidward in the face and storms out. There are more flashes,
noises, and giggles from the kitchen. Squidward gets up and he holds his head.
GRR. SpongeBob hands a tiny Krabby Patty to a cockroach. There you go.
That's not even real. This is a fake episode. Squidward, SpongeBob, what's going on in here?
SpongeBob wears a tiny hat and holds a tiny spatula and the cockroach is eating a Krabby
Patty while sitting on the shrunken dining table. Why is everything all tiny? SpongeBob
turns the belt around to hide it from Squidward. I don't know. Squidward, what do you got there?
SpongeBob, nothing Squidward. No. Really? SpongeBob, nothing Squidward. You've got something?
All right. Let's see it. Krabby Patty grabs SpongeBob and sees Mermaid Man's belt.
What the hell did I just get? SpongeBob, no. No. Squidward gasps. Is that Mermaid Man's belt?
SpongeBob, yes Squidward. Wow. I can't believe he'd lend it to you. SpongeBob, me, I either.
Chuckles nervously. Squidward gasps. He didn't lend it to you, did he? SpongeBob, please don't tell.
Squidward, angry. You stoned. SpongeBob, please don't tell. Squidward, oh, I'm telling.
SpongeBob, Squidward, if Mermaid Man finds out, he'll kick me out of his fan club for sure.
Please don't tell. Squidward, uh-oh, points at the phone hanging on a kitchen wall. There's the
phone. SpongeBob, don't. Is the episode almost over? Squidward, I'm walking towards the phone.
Slowly walks towards the phone. How long is this episode? SpongeBob, no. Squidward, slowly reaches
for the phone. I'm getting closer to the phone. SpongeBob, sobbing, do-oh-not. Squidward picks up
the phone, ready to call Mermaid Man. And now, for the moment we've all been waiting for. SpongeBob,
wails and tears himself. I'm begging you. Squidward, hello. I'd like to speak to Mermaid.
SpongeBob shrinks. Squidward, he lands on the table. What the? What? Phones hit Squidward on
the head. Ow. Mermaid Man on phone. Hello? Hello? Squidward, what did you do to me?
SpongeBob, I'm sorry, Squidward, but you made me do it. Squidward, SpongeBob, if you don't return
me to normal size right now, you're gonna be in really big trouble. SpongeBob, uh-huh, okay. Uh,
Squidward, I said no. SpongeBob, uh, belt is shown to have several complicated buttons. Uh,
Squidward, do you hear me? SpongeBob zaps Squidward and he appears with multiple eyes
with hissing snakes. Holy fish paste. Get it off me. Get it off me. I can't take it anymore.
Take size off him in pants and fear. Don't you know how to work that thing? SpongeBob, uh,
I can do it. SpongeBob changes Squidward into a burning mess, then changes him to have an
enormous nose, then to have no skin, then cut in half by scissors. What? Then changed into more
things off screen while SpongeBob looks in fright. Squidward screams whenever SpongeBob changes him.
Squidward looks burnt after SpongeBob's failed attempts to revert him. Stop. I've got an idea.
You stopped my game. Let's call Mermaid Man and SpongeBob snatching Squidward. No. I can't let
you do that, but there must be someone else who can help. Someone smart and wise with years of
life experience. He runs to Patrick's house where Patrick is sleeping. Patrick. I can't do it anymore.
Okay. I'll do it like speed, like five. I can't hear it anymore. Let's, uh, Mike, take it. Take
us away, Mike. He runs to Patrick's house where Patrick is sleeping. Patrick, Patrick, Patrick,
Patrick wakes up due to surprise. Oh, hi, SpongeBob, SpongeBob, Patrick. I was at work and Mermaid Man
and Barnacle Boy came, and I got this belt. And look, chose Patrick, the shrunken Squidward.
Patrick, a Squidward action figure. Grab Squidward, let me play with him. SpongeBob, no. Just give me
the ones in the corner. Imitates jet plane diving, machine gunfire, and explosion noises dive bomb.
SpongeBob, Patrick, Patrick, about to punch Squidward, and then comes a giant fist.
SpongeBob, Patrick, no, that's not an action figure. That's the real Squidward. I shrunk him by
accident. Patrick, oh, about to punch Squidward anyway, and then comes a giant Squidward screams.
SpongeBob stops Patrick. Wait, you don't understand. This is serious. I don't know how to
unshrink him. Slow it. I could be stuck like this for the rest of his life. Patrick, oh, don't worry
about it. He'll find love one day. SpongeBob, you think so? There's no comedic timing, but it'll be
with someone his own size. Pulls out a pickle like this pickle. See, they like each other. Squidward,
and then Patrick bangs them together as it's a kiss. Squidward is disgusted. SpongeBob, oh,
if only I knew how to work this thing. Patrick, let me take a look at it. HMM, you know what the
problem is? I'm not going to be able to get this done. Patrick, you got to set the points to the
M.M. formula when it should be set to turns M around W. I'm going to have to. I got to play
the game. I don't think wumbo is a real word. Patrick, come on. You know I wumbo, you wumbo,
the cheaply wumbo. Wumbo, wumboing, we'll have the wumbo, wumbo-rumbo-wumbology, the study of
wumbo. It's first grade, SpongeBob. Squidward, while Patrick is saying we'll have the wumbo,
I wonder if the fall from this height could be enough to kill me. SpongeBob, Patrick, I'm sorry,
I doubted you. Patrick, well, all right, then. Let her rip. SpongeBob uses Mermaid Man's belt and
presses something to try and regrow Squidward. Only Patrick and Squidward are both shrunk,
now it worked. SpongeBob, oh no. Patrick, look, SpongeBob's giant. SpongeBob grabs them,
can I be giant next? SpongeBob, Patrick, I'm not giant, you shrunk too. Patrick, you're kidding.
Pulls out his pickle, good thing I still got his pickle. Kisses the pickle three times. Pan over
to Squidward. Squidward, they. Now will you take us to Mermaid Man? SpongeBob yells in Squidward's
face, no. He can never find out, but I'll think of something. I promise. Gets a jar and puts them
in until then. You'll be safe in this jar. Patrick, you know what's funny? My pickle started out in a
jar and now it's in one again. They. It's like a pun or something. SpongeBob, it's only two people,
no big deal. Somebody said this is giving me a stomach ache. Sandy suddenly appears. Sandy, hi,
SpongeBob. SpongeBob screams Sandy. Shrinks Sandy. Sandy lands on the ground. What did you four
crying out? What did you all do to me? SpongeBob, I'm sorry, Sandy. Mermaid Man came in and Larry
appears. God damn it, why? They. SpongeBob shrinks Larry. Nat, they. SpongeBob, I shrinks Nat.
Nancy Susie Fish. Hi, SpongeBob. Shrinks Nancy. SpongeBob screams and makes a run for it.
What is this? It's coming out of the. SpongeBob shrinks Mrs. Puff. It's out of the machine.
Shrinks Scooter, Sandals and Dennis. Fish number one. They. SpongeBob. This shit's out of the machine.
Fish number two. SpongeBob. Hi. Shrinks Fish. Fish number three. They. SpongeBob. Shrinks Fish.
Fish number four. What's up? Sponge. Shrinks Fish. SpongeBob tries to fit everyone in the jar,
Wu. I'm going to have to get a bigger jar. Squidward, SpongeBob, will you just face facts?
I think it's almost done. You've got to go to Mermaid Man. SpongeBob. Oh, Squidward,
he'll be so disappointed. Sandy, well, you can't leave us small forever. SpongeBob, you don't
understand. SpongeBob's mother is seen in the jar. Mrs. Squarepants. What do you mean it's not?
It's about halfway. You need to admit your mistakes. I'm not at halfway. SpongeBob. Mom.
Mermaid Man, your mother's right, son. Mermaid Man will understand. Barnacle Boy, you're Mermaid Man,
you old coot. Mermaid Man. Oh, yes, SpongeBob. Mermaid Man, I'm so sorry. It's just that I'm
such a big fan. And your belt. And Mermaid Man, comforting SpongeBob. Oh, don't worry, son.
I understand. SpongeBob smiles, with tears still pooling in his eyes. Why? I remember back when I
first used the belt. The year was 19, not 11, 12. Why I believe the president. Everyone, just tell
him how to unshrink us. I need to have a different person doing this. They're all freaking me out.
Let's have Rachel come in. Everyone, just tell him how to unshrink us. Mermaid Man. Oh, yes,
the unshrinked ray. Let's see. Did you set it to one bow? Everyone, what? The jar rumbles from anger,
and everyone flies out of their jar, spells out and form Get SpongeBob. Get SpongeBob. Climbs up
SpongeBob's body and into the holes in his head. Squidward, now I have to drive five miles to go
to the bathroom in my own home. What? Kicks SpongeBob's stomach. Sandy, and I need an elevator
to climb one stair. Why does he keep doing this? Punches his brain. Mermaid Man, we've been shrinking
for years. Barnacle Boy, but this is ridiculous. Both kick his eyeballs. Dale kicks his pelvis.
Nancy chops off one of his lungs while hanging onto his spine. Larry kicks his knee. SpongeBob
is shown getting hurt from the outside. Everyone, everything's too big. SpongeBob, I've got it.
Squidward soars a blood vein and Frank tries to break a bone, but stop when SpongeBob shrinks
the city. Tarder. Everyone looks outside through his holes. Since I couldn't make you big, I made
the city small. Everybody leaves SpongeBob's body, and now only one more thing to shrink. Cheese.
Turns the shrink ray into W and towards him like a camera and shrinks himself. Squidward,
I guess this is okay. Larry, yeah, what's the difference? Nancy, good idea. SpongeBob,
everyone cheers. Balloons and other party items are flying. As a bus comes back and Plankton gets off
of it. It is a classic, you're right. Plankton, well, it's great to be back. Really, it's great
to be back, SpongeBob. That's the whole episode? That's it. Okay, it hasn't been 22 minutes though.
Hey, you guys want to watch more TV? Because I'm only at 30,000. Oh, that's right, SpongeBob
episodes are 11 minutes long. No, I'm not, we don't have to do any more SpongeBob transcripts.
No, no, I, we just did that for like seven straight minutes. What the fuck is that? This is,
really? I can't, this actually exists? All right, I'll put this one on. I gotta replace this. Hold
on. Okay, let's do, um, Rod. Okay, Rod, let's hear it. Rats, rats, we're rats, we're the rats.
We pray at night, we stalk at night, we're the rats. Giant rat, I'm da giant rat that makes all
of da rules. Rats, let's see what kind of trouble we can get ourselves into. Dick, so sue me for
being thorough, I wanna know that you know what the plan is. Trenchcoat man, look, seriously,
mate, how many artifacts do we need to steal before you trust me with these jobs? Dick, well,
I just want to make sure you know what's happening. We're gonna get the treasure, we're gonna get out
of there and we're all stars mumbling. Blue man, who ha ha. Dick, and we must get it. That's the
most important thing. So beyond your game, we go now. Blue man, I get to drive the car today
because it's my birthday. Dick, no, don't let him get in the car, please don't let.
Blue man, quietly, come on. Dick, oh, he's driving, whatever. I can't, put it down. Bloody hell.
It's trying to get out. More importantly, it's trying to get out. Did we have a rat problem?
Dick, we don't. Get in. Let's go, speed it up. Yeah, that's the speed I'm looking for. That's
the kind of fastness I want. Asterisk cuts to the town asterisk. Dick, I don't even know where you're
going at this point. We've been driving all night. Blue man, it's my birthday. Dick, hey you, you just
you're running over a guy right now. He's fucking serious. Trench cold man, can you remind me next
time we do this? I'm getting my nan to drive. Asterisk camera cuts inside of a cafe shop asterisk.
Clerk, um, excuse me, sir. Yeah, you over there dancing. It's actually $10 to dance in this
building. So you're going to have to give me, we're all going to die. Dick, ladies and gentlemen of
the jury, may I have the attention of the class? My name is Dick Dastardly, Richard, and I'm here
to take the treasure chest that's in the back room. Go get it, boys. I'll follow you in. And let me
tell you something, clerk. If you so ask, move it muscle. I'll make sure you stay buried in that
ground there. All right, let's go. Dick goes into the Mayan temple. The golden statue comes alive
and follows him. Dick, all right. Gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme, gimme. Is the treasure in there?
Is it in there? Trench cold man? Yeah, it's all here. Dick? Oh, yes. No, that's what I like to hear.
And now we are invincible. Gerard? Not so fast. Gerard? You stand before Gerard, guardian of the
treasure chest of the Mayan temple, and they will make sure to hey. Giant rat picks him up and throws
him into the abyss. Trench cold man? Oh, fuck this. I'm off. Gerard? Hey, what are you doing?
Rats? We're the rats. We pray at night. We stalk at night. We're the rats. Dick? All right. Yay.
That's cool. Yeah. I like rats. Nothing bad with rats. But let me tell you something. Over my dead
body. Are you getting this treasure? Rats? Rats? Rats? Rats? Rats? Blue man? Oh, man. Look at that
flock of birds over there. That reminds me of my favorite movie. The movie. That's your favorite
movie too, right? Giant rat? No, my favorite movie is Frozen. I like Elsa and Anna. Okay,
now I kill you, kick. Got it. Blue man? Wow. No, that's great pick choice for favoriteist movie.
I wonder if I have to think that now. Small slash giant rat. Now I get to be the giant rat. Cool
surprise. Camera moves back to the town where the police have arrived. Police officer. So you're
trying to tell me that inside this building right here, there is a giant rat. Among other things,
did he say Pickles? Or am I putting that in there by myself? Whatever. Sergeant Pickles is
going to go in there and check it out. We're going to make sure everything's okay. And I'll get me
some candy corn too. That's a weird request. I know, but just get it. Camera cuts back into the
cafe shop. Giant rat. You guys are going to drop it and we're going to be in big trouble. So quit
prancing around. Yes, it does. Hello, sir. Welcome to the rat cafe. There's no rats here. There's
just the hamburgers. Police officer too. Yeah, that would be real nice if that were true. That's
it. Two sixty. You're a rat, aren't you? Giant rat. No, no, why would that happen? That's not
we're just, we're just people. Police officer too. Man, I'm going to be taking you in then.
Jerma, you know, wouldn't this be funny if it were real? Haha, just kidding. Be careful. Apparently
there's a giant rat around. Giant rat. You have a good day, officer. Officer leaves and camera
falls to the town. Police officer. So, you figure anything out in there? Police officer too. Nah,
he's clean. It's back to the drawing board. Police officer. Well, that's, that's great. I don't know
how to draw, so you're going to have to do the drawing. Cat police music starts and the cat police
arrive. Scratchy scratch. Sergeant Scratchy Scratch of the cat police reporting in. You are now
relived of your duty. Police officer one and two. Jerma is simultaneous or proving the cat
police. This is the kind of shit that happens when you have a text to speech enabled stream.
What's that on you? Police officer two. What? Scratchy scratch. Are you wearing a rat on your
shoulder? Police officer two. Why would I be wearing a... Hey guys, so, um. Yeah, so I have
some merch if you want to check out my store. Small rat. Boss, we got big problems. The cat
police are here. I gotta try to drop these balls into the... Can we try to drop these in here?
Let's get it. Get us the fuck out of here. Okay. Hey, you drive the car. You gotta get five in each
bucket. Let's speed it up. Because when you get five in a bucket, it's easier to get 500 tickets.
Rats. Inaudible screaming and yelling. Scratchy scratch. Good job, cat police. You did it again.
You saved the world and that's what we do as cat police. We make the world a better place.
Camera cuts to space where earth blows up in a ufo with a cat head is nearby.
Credits to Jerma985 for the video. Movie idea in all concepts. Script was typed up completely
by me with edits from the community. We really are getting an NPR outro. That's an NPR outro.
Is it over? Okay, it's over. How many tickets? 37,000 tickets. Let me just put these in.
This is less efficient than the... I had to get away from the co-op for a minute.
God. I'm doing this one at like times 10 speed.
This is no... Why would somebody do this? This one is actually going to be as fast as I can make it.
I'm not suffering through this for long. Rats. Rats. We're the rats. What? We pray at night.
We stalk at night. We're the rats. No, that's not... I'm that giant rat that makes all of the rules.
Rats. Let's see what kind of trouble we can get ourselves into. That's not as close to being...
So sue me for being thorough. I want to know that you know what the plan is.
Stop. Okay. You're not getting... I'm not going to slow this one down.
Here you go. You've reached the 20 minute daily limit for voices. Oh god damn it. That means I
have to do David. Hello ladies and gentlemen. Welcome to episode one of Jermacraft, the series
where I play Minecraft. This is going to be a single player let's play and when I say let's play,
I use that term pretty loosely because I'm an idiot in this game. You're gonna see lots of fails.
You're gonna see lots of triumphs, at least I'm hoping. So go grab yourself a nice hot cup of
coffee, hot cup of cocoa. I've got apple cider right here freshly brewed. Let me take a sip.
Sip off. That's good cider. All right, so let's get this started. Create new world.
World name is going to be Jermacraft. Sounds about right. Yeah okay. Game mode is going to be
Super AI Survival. That's the most interesting I think. More world option C for world generator.
Okay this is important. I got named as something crazy to get cool structures and stuff.
Gonna name it umm how about. Diamonds are forever lol cheese. Alverga dot all right.
There's that's our world generator seed. Diamonds are forever lol cheese b-u-r-g-a-h done.
All right let's see what happens. Create new world. Let's do it guys. Building terrain. Oh my god
this is so exciting. This is episode one. I wonder. I wonder where we're gonna end up. Where are we
gonna end up? Okay what what? Where the hell am I? I spawned on top of a mountain top. Okay hold on.
Sound has to be lowered. Definitely. Okay a little bit of that. A little bit of that. Maybe a
little lower. That sounds about right. All right. So uh apparently I spawned on top of a mountain.
I kinda this is a good seed. What's that? We're going to explore it right now go. Dies from fall
damage oh. Jerma laugh. All right we're going to try that again. This time I'm not gonna miss. I
want to get down to DHA. That's the home right there. I want to live right there. Don I don't
even have to explore. See if I can't do this. I gotta. Hold on I got an idea. I got a plan.
JermaCraft episode one. This is how we do it. You guys ready? I don't know if you. I don't know if
you guys are actually really ready for this. Here we go. I'm going for a skydive. Remember if you
hold shift you don't fall off. That's something I didn't know when I used to live stream this game.
Embarrassment. Weez hehe. You guys ready? Ready to go see our new home? Jerma laugh. All righty then
what the hell is that? Oh it's an octopus. Look at this quaint little place. I love it already.
Hehe. All righty. So exhalation. I'm so stupid. Why see I'm this is why this is why I'm an idiot
guys why see why would I I need to get wood and I just jumped off th okay remember this where are
we pointing east I have no idea gotta get some trees that's the most important part of Minecraft
you gotta get trees that's the first thing you gotta get let me take a sip of my apple cider
sipping sounds oh that's good stuff hopefully you guys picked up a thing of cocoa like I told
you to because that's the most relaxing thing in the world sitting down playing video games doesn't
get much better than that okay come on now oh we got sand too now explain this to me all right
is this an ai that created what personal email and explain to me why there are cows that are acting
like mountain lions I'm gonna kill each one of those cows in just a minute you watch all
damage how well at least there's one tree over here try to remember I gotta go back that way
because that's where the house is gonna be my awesome dirt house so if you are an old subscriber
I mean really old like at least four months ol on 44 or five months you'll remember the original
germacraft it was like two episodes and I built a dirt house this is gonna be completely different
I'm going to actually spend time and make some cool stuff at least that's what I'm pretending
that I'm gonna say that got some wood I got Gino still it's Minecraft skin from Mario RPG one of
the best games of all time if you have never played Mario RPG I suggest you play it all right
got some wood I need more trees over here I can dig up I'll get this one too excruciatingly slow
wood punching more wood punching so I guess they added a hunger feature now too if you're hungry
you die or something I guess who knows even more wood punching a little bit more wood and in my
live streams I was always a tradition that when I played this game I would sing a song when things
got really boring opportunity right now to sing a song so I'll let me just prep my vocal chords
for a second six apple cider clears throat okay so we're getting wood right now right
ingestion do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do do we're chopping wood down
k h dot do k h every single day k h do k h do k h do I gotta get my tools tch m do k h
any which way tch dot k h do k h for I can't seem to reach this stupid piece of wood so I gotta put
some blocks down to get where I should I'm gonna cop him tch tch nhh tch nhh I'm gonna chop right
now dot nhh tch nhh tch doon dot doon tch doon tch I feel like I'm at an auction let's get the
hell out of here yeah splash so those of you that don't think that's gonna be in the back yeah
I put my battle on castle so here's the goal by Christmas time of this year 2011 I want to have
a giant castle like as big as that uh that mountain over there begins breaking blocks so let's clean
this up a little bit 2011 why don't we huh yeah all right all right maybe put a little bit of
dirt down here make sure I can you know D did I really run out of dirt wonderful my first wooden
tools it's just like going to your first day of school and get punched in the face by the bully
what speaking of bullies I got a funny story for you first ever story on German crap
while I do this mundane stuff so when I was like in the fourth grade I was a kid that lived down
the street from me his name will stay anonymous because you know I don't want him to like if he
watches these videos I don't want him to come like feed me up not that he would ever remember
this to begin with but I was probably like the fourth grade and it swallows I was a little s
word guys I was a little I was a little little jerk when I was younger so essentially what
happened was this kid he was a big big fat kid scary not very nice and my brother got in like
a fight with him like a little time before this V when I was like the second grade my brother's
a little bit older than me and let me pick this up so my brother got in a fight with this kid and
like I heard about it and so at the bus stop one day because we were at the same bus stop because
he lives right down the street from us at least at least he did I don't know if he does anymore
so I'd know why I was in the fourth grade this so much of a little jerk I was so my grandmother
used to pick me up from school after I got from the bus stop because you know obviously you don't
want to walk you know the mile and a half back to your house or whatever it is mile cause the
bus stop wasn't that close so my grandma used to pick me up and he was at the bus stop as well
and one day I decided that out of the back window I was going to give him a double middle finger
as I was driving with my grandmother one day I'd know why I don't even know why I did it guys I
can't I can't tell you one reason why I gave this kid double middle finger this is a real story
he just kind of gave me the w like a weird look like what I did I actually did this and from that
day forward I would run run as fast as I could to the bus stop and wait to the bus stop where
my grandmother was gonna pick me up and it was like that for almost six months yeah and he never
beat me up or anything like that he and he I don't I don't I was like overreacting actually
hold on a second I don't need this what am I doing with this I was just putting blocks down
actually no no no I was I was doing the right thing I want I want these cause I want to make
like a wall kind of let's keep that going so yeah so I guess the moral of the story is never give
a double middle finger to a bully dot cause you'll be scared for the rest of your life
and I still am scared when I like open my doors to like go and get the groceries I'm scared
that bully's gonna come get me for me giving him the bird yeah that is actually a true story
I did not make that up it I was scared for like at least six months and nothing ever
happened either and like like I didn't get beat up or anything so all right now is there is this
all is this going to be down in okay cool we finally give drugs to robots in this game when
people are watching I really don't think it's happened ambient cave sound is that oh there's
a light somewhere around here oh geez it's right here oh nice maybe there's coal right here too
that'd be pretty awesome I was good for at least six months I was scared for six months you know
for six months I'm gonna kick your butt I can't get that low up go on go on what do you think I
care you can't hurt me I gotta shovel I'm gonna shovel your face in creeper explodes and takes
off more than half of Jervis health gasp okay well that's done chuckles there's not coal just
right here somewhere there has to be see this is why they always tell you right when you start you
need to go get coal you need to go get wood and everything but I was too busy talking about a
bully me giving him the middle finger so looking I'm trying to see if I can see coal sometimes
it's just right on the edge of these mountains stairs into pitch black and I am not pleased
let's at least do this I need a sheep too I need wool I'm being a real piece of crap
that's it that's it okay okay yes I did give this random bully out the window the double middle
finger for no reason I don't know why I did it so I was the bully I was the one that was the mean
kid but I you know I flipped that story sideways oh yeah the bully the bully that that I gave the
finger to for no reason right I only got 40 50 tickets this whole thing oh I have 40 000
I need a break for a minute after that one I haven't picked up a 500 in like 15 minutes I
know I have to pay attention right here and they've all it's also been glitching out the
thing's been freaking out when I get around a green one I need to save the all right I'm
gonna walk out and save you right that'll be a disaster reset the arcade yeah okay I'm gonna
reset the arcade not a bad idea let's reset I need money too let me just get one more 500
that should be it right okay let me get that one there we go no no I'm not gonna do a Seinfeld
episode I turned this all way down and it doesn't even matter okay I'm gonna go outside I'm gonna
save the game save yes okay game has now been saved we're good I feel like that's been that
was on for so long I kind of miss it being there somehow uh tingy came in with 10 community subs
thank you tingy 10 more subs from tingy I just need to get the boombox and then and then I win
I win the game just a little bit more money buy lottery tickets I need ticket tickets
nobody has German craft episode 2 transcripted I don't believe that tingy give 10 more community
subs thank you tingy holy shit that's like 40 or 50 subs for me or something today isn't it
well thank you really appreciate it just play the actual episode of times two speed
it's not German craft unless you have some crazy happens I'm gonna go fight this asshole over here
get this house dude I didn't have this so this is gonna be interesting I should have just made
one I should have just made this over wait do it why am I doing this why am I going after this guy
right now what does the matter with me see my brain does not work in ways that you would think
it should I'm definitely gonna die this is the stupidest idea ever that was the dumbest thing
I've ever done in this game I don't even have a spawn point oh great at least there's cows
amount of cows it just feels like the robot whoa where's my diving board where's my diving board
I made a diving board where is it oh coal this coal right there this coal right there get away
from me get away from me oh it's three creepers what are you kidding me this is insane what the
hell come on now notch you can't get up here don't blow up I dare you I dare you good I'm right next to you
blow up get out of here get the hell away from me everybody just blow up right now blow up
I want to see the hole that made I'll leave my diving board all right that actually looks kind of
cool did I make it I made it wait a second how did this happen they're all here too there's like 10 people
I don't want to I'm not doing that tingy just gave 20 more community subs holy shit dude
20 community subs I'm not playing that it's fucking with me thank you for the 20 more subs
it's a lot of money but I I ain't doing that I can't I'm like hearing myself as a fucking robot
talking like eight years ago it's it's freaking me out I gotta go I gotta get at it
did I get it knock it in there just do the transcript movie script movie I'm not doing
spider-man hilarious story from today's stream oh my god oh my god no way all right this is important
am I on premium voices all right David's gonna do this one
hello ladies and gentlemen no no welcome oh I'll get one okay hold on wait wait wait how do I make
a new tab okay hold on bear with me here I know how to make a tab all right how do I make a new
tab I know how to do it okay here we go here we go this should be good I'm looking forward to this
one we'll see if anybody can pick up with this one is ting tingy just give another 20 subs oh
my god tingy uh I can't get it to work so we have to just do David it's okay honest to god
the cat seriously was up in the tree I put on swim mice right to try to climb the tree better
maybe there was gonna be a grip for the swim mice and I'm shuffling up the tree and the cat
is just like re and I swear to god this is seriously one of the most ridiculous things
to happen in my life.the cat pukes as I get right up to the cat I'm about to save the cat stuck in
the tree and the cat throws up right in my face and it's all like what oh but I still had to hold
onto the tree.so as I'm holding onto the tree I almost lose grip like twice but thank god I
had those swim mice yeah know what I'm saying like lol I finally get up right to the perch
and I have to wipe off the cat puke on my face and I go back on top and I'm sitting.the cat has
moved over to the end of the branch by now so by the time the cat is sitting on the end of the
branch I'm like please don't do that I'm trying my hardest to save you a bird lands right on where
the cat is so the cat has now got his attention on the bird so honest to god it was unbelievable
so you've got a cat sitting on the itch and you got the bird sitting there and the cat now has
the attention on the bird so the bird is skvocking at the cat at this point and then they're moving
the branch back and forth and I'm like shaking on the branch like holy shit dude like the branch
is shaking the cat is fucking screaming the bird is screaming and honest to god I'm not even
kidding about this the bird just starts throwing up and I don't even know how that happened you
know what I'm saying it makes no sense so the cat is on the branch and the bird has now thrown up
and I'm sitting up there with my swim mice on trying to how am I gonna I gotta save both of
these animals up here yeah know what I mean and the fire truck like we oh oh we oh oh we oh oh
it's flying down the road and I'm stuck in the tree now trying to save this bird and save this
cat and the fireman has a big megaphone ee oh oh ee oh oh and he's like hey can you get down from
there son like what the heck am I gonna do about this so they brought the trampoline over yeah I
know this is crazy so finally long story short the fireman starts crawling up the tree because
he has to climb up the tree too by the way the cat is already on the ground cat just climbed down
the tree on his own the bird just flies away and the fireman now has to help me get down from the
tree dot my mother came out it was so embarrassing dot it was the most fucked up thing it was all
over the place and finally the fireman said hey at least you tried right that was the last thing
at least you tried I just somebody wrote on that thread it sounds like a like that's like trump
like a trump tweet honest to god the cat was seriously up in the tree I put on swimmies right
to try to climb the tree better maybe there was going to be a grip and for the swimmies either
I'm shuffling up the tree and the cat is just like yeah I swear to god this is seriously one
of the most ridiculous things happened in my life let me tell you this is for real oh my fucking god
put on swimmies right to try to try to treat better oh I have to let me tell you something
seriously oh my god I read that whole thing as as a trump oh that's fucking funny I can't
I can't do it is there a trump text to speech no way is there I think I found it okay I think I
found it how much can I have here honest to god this is gonna can I put the whole thing in here
I think I okay you ready for this shit come on do it shit is it too much I don't I think it's too
many too much text how much are you allowed to put in here is it loading the whole thing oh please
let me do this you have to let me do this this is too funny is it loading I'm gonna give it a second
yeah all right let's try splitting it in half we'll take a little bit of a little bit of time
here I need to know what this sounds like less than that less than that fuck I think you can
only do like one sentence honest to god the cat seriously was up in the tree I put on um right
to try to try the tree better maybe there was gonna be a um the um I'm shuffling up the tree
that does not sound right that's a youtube poop it really is
there's a better one is there a better one where's where's there a better one
oh wait there's other like presidents no I can't get it another 20 community subs from tingy
holy shit dude wait wait wait wait wait what is this no that's not it it's not it it's not it
let's see can I turn your sound on type your message here what is this you can make your own
text to speech based off your voice yeah clash what the fuck is this what does this do honest
to god the cat was seriously up in the tree I put on swimmies right to try to climb the tree better
maybe there was gonna be honest to god the cat seriously was up in the tree
I put on swimmies right to try to climb the tree better maybe there was gonna be
what the fuck all right that's too much for my brain um best streamer um me
okay let me fucking go back to the game I can't put the whole thing it is a character limit
I'm trying to have him say germany 85 best streamer this whole thing has been
shut up Jeremy okay so we're going to go back how much I need like 60,000 more tickets
I'm sitting the cat has moved over to the end of the branch by now so by the time the cat is
sitting on the end of the branch I'm like please don't do that I'm trying my hardest to save you
a bird lands right where the cat is so the cat is the attention of the bird I'm gonna fucking
lose my mind I can't even do it it's too fucking stupid I can do like a pretty solid five or six
out of ten trump I can't do it right now it's too fucking dumb pay somebody pay a trump on fiber
to do that no I don't want to do that
do the Peter Griffin TTS no I don't want Peter Griffin text-to-speech guys you know how much
that would cost on fiber that would be like 500 bucks that wouldn't just be five dollars it's
five dollars for like fucking three like five seconds it's worth it okay I'll see what I can do
I'll see what I can do I keep sinking it right in the 18 all right how many do I have 40,000 how
many how long has this stream been like six hours of this bullshit I tingy has given like a million
dollars holy shit tingy that's another 20 subs from tingy let me like turn this audio kind of
back on a little oh that was way why is it so loud now it's so soft all right that's better
I was gonna hit the mega jackpot like 10 times it would cost a hundred dollars to get a trump on
fiber yeah I know it wasn't five dollars it would be at least one to two maybe even 300 bucks
to get them to read something that's that long why is this all fucked up oh
all right 448 tickets when does this place close is my question because how would I be able to do
this just do your own trump and read it yourself no but it's funnier if it was an actual rehearsed
trump on camera all right was this how much about could we get a lot in here
I feel like we can get a decent amount through don't go yeah we're going back to the basics here
get it got it 500 oh what's the bonus the bonus do I have to find out that's three in a row
all right I can put more money in I wonder what the bonus does
give me like a 10 000 more more more let's go and this every time here why is it taking so
we get in there come on get the d what I get oh I got the cart okay there's d
here comes the old bonus got it all right bonus time got it holy shit what do I do
what happened what all right all right hey let's go I'm not leaving this up to me
are you kidding me no way good luck it's up to you guys what do you want to go first start clicking
now 20 free spins that might get us 50 000 all right look you're looking like top kind of middle
right okay I'm going right there right here seven free spins times two not very good not very good
try it again remember you have to get three you why are you clicking you low mid all right down
here you sure I'm never gonna get this bonus ever again you sure you want this one let's go
you're letting me down big time uh come on now let me down here I'm sorry I'm sorry sorry do
it yourself then well here's the thing the reason why I'm not doing it myself is because when I get
five times two three times everybody calls me stupid idiot dumb moron so I'm letting you guys
seal the fate here bottom right let's do it better better okay keep it up better closer warmer
got middle or in the corner which one is it gonna be it's looking like the corner give it 10 seconds
four five top left what what thanks for the times three what is happening why is it doing this
okay why is it doing that I'm trying to click the ones that you guys clicked on
oh this whole thing's gonna fuck up isn't it all right try it again you clearly saw me clicking
on the one on the that was very clear I did it twice 20 times three is so important here
because that will probably be like 20 000 tickets holy shit everybody wants to go right in the middle
is that right in the middle well it looks kind of split it's definitely the top in the middle
area is that in the right spot 15 not bad not bad guys there's no more fives and we're good
there's no more fives oh 32 versus 49 down the middle this is that shitty suitcase deal show
oh yeah do or don't all right we're going right in the middle underneath 15
god damn it guys it's times two this shit's times two
cards are dropping though all right hold on a minute cards are dropping
I wonder if those are worth anything we don't deserve to lose okay hold on uh cards have been
dropping so hold on we lost because of your shitty computer that's not fair all right let me see
let me collect the uh the stuff my shitty computer and what if it was your computer that did it
we can do that again not one of these is lit up give me the fucking dunks I'm gonna pick
next time to get that again bonus see what's that card see that card right there that lawn care what
does it say the other machine has more I'll go to the other machine after I do this one last final
I want to get that whatever that card is see this one dropping right here too what what are those
cards come on don't go my turn it's my turn it's my turn I'm gonna do it my turn 15 right off the
bat seven five seven it's not that's terrible it's better than better than you guys dude
oh pretty trigger that bonus come on pretty great there's another one there's a seven
so what just fell out what was that what does it do stuff up this right side is it tickets
it's probably tickets okay there it goes down then it just disappears
is it just turn maybe it's just turning into the tickets
1300 61 all right we gotta get we gotta get the d
there it is bonus what's the goal here I need to get to a hundred thousand tickets it was supposed
to take 22 minutes but I got too distracted by the spongebob episodes transcript and it derailed
the whole spring let me just try to get the bonus one more time if you get 20 spins at times three
that's like 10 000 tickets or even 15 at times three still haven't gone to the ufo arcade
didn't I try to go to the ufo door and it didn't open I thought I tried to do that already
that just not happened almost just got an instant spin it's pretty rare that that happens so wait
could I I tried to go in the ufo are you sure that is currently not part of like the early
access or something and eventually we'll have an arcade or is there an actual arcade in there
that I didn't see whatever let me get these two cards down and then sit there they go nice
all right that felt pretty good and we already got like one more donko like
lined up here so might as well do it come on just hit it hit it hit it hit it all right bonus
all right okay I don't need I don't care about the donko anymore I'm just gonna put them all
down here grab the tickets I'm gonna go to another machine final push is a few more coins whatever
get this pink card why is it good I'm being serious like should I get that
all right well let's see what's it worth I might as well do another donko while we're here
you know while I'm here push it in so I can be done with this there it goes okay I'm done
see if I can get another donko no I'm out pick up your tickets and get the hell out of here
I'm right here I mean you might as well get another donko
what else am I gonna do right what else am I gonna do
let's go for another bonus we'll just try here we go I'm what else if I'm up here might as well
those you get one more maybe if it's possible you could probably it's possible to get another
donko here it is well I mean you get two donkos you might as well let it ride all right
cash in the tickets that's it I didn't I get like a thousand like five times
all right almost at 50% that's so bad what can I get what's the
got it one thousand what do you mean the cards there's no cards in the thing there's nothing
down here they just disappeared there's nothing in there nothing there guys what do you mean he
doesn't know yes I do hockey I got 500 probably is not that hard again oh that was loud this is
2000 get in there one two three really the arcade is closed because the kids are all gone
yeah but I greased the guy at the door I gave him like a hundred dollar bill and he let me
stay overnight get in there all right oh okay I only need the o and the k here comes a beep
tickets though 200 100 200 200 300 I'm staying here
just turn your monitor off so you don't have to turn your monitor off and turn your sound
off until you don't have to listen to this okay got it fuck give me the k
around oh my god I missed it it's okay get another hundo I actually think this is pretty
efficient because eventually you'll get to a thousand you know I'm saying like I'm getting
500 800 400 500 every time and I and I'm then you will get 2000 if you sit here long enough
I fuck it up every damn time the ball claw machine is the best I sat there for like
40 minutes I need to do another a different game that's not the balloons
it is really loud I know it is oh my god I fucking missed it again
just put some shit in there the chicken again I don't know what it is about this k
but I can't not fucking get it it's pissing me off more than anything
America runs on dunco yes it does
okay 500 right here 500 oh I'll get it just teleported it was bullshit just teleported
all right I'll take the 2120 let's go cashman that's I think that's a solid like five eight
percent we're at 50% I'm just gonna now I'm gonna do the boring ball game no I'm not I'm gonna do
this do this until I don't do it got it oh I was I actually really did get it
I really I did I really did I think she looks like iPods in these it's gonna be close
this one's also way too expensive I don't want to do the money machine thing again
there it is all right that was perfect I refuse to play this again
oh I tried to get out but it I did the screen didn't even pop up for me
all right here we go here I am let's go figure out the ticket balls this one's broken it used
to work really well I need to get 100 500 balls do you understand the thing that you are telling
me that I need to do and how I don't want to do it stop spinning around so much no spongebob
no there's only a certain amount of spongebob that I'm allowed to take
17-hour stream no I'll get there quicker than that I think dunko might be a better bet I really do
I just got an achievement for getting 50 000 tickets all right I'm gonna I'll get let's do this
20 more times yeah back to the claw and then sometimes the claw just doesn't work
oh I'm a chicken wheel that's a good idea too what was the minor prize for the blocks game again
was it a thousand it was wasn't it it was 100 oh that's not worth it go back to the water gun
game now the water gun game doesn't give uh it gives credits it doesn't give tickets what time
is it right now I've had like two streams or three streams restart because of the internet being
weird earlier this is four and a half hours then two hours how long has this stream actually been
that's next level play right there and it didn't even go in it just teleported back to the
that's absolute dog shit it's been about seven hours well it's kept my attention for seven
hours somehow I don't know it's just like fun to do these things all right let me go and check
let's go I'm gonna go after one more ball and I'm gonna go to chicken game there we go come on get
it in there does that even is it counting I don't think that's fucking counting
almost there we're mostly there now don't you understand no that's just that's just cuckoo coins
bonus shot so if you do twice in a row you get 2,500 that's all the way up there is too hard
this one sucks it's fun to play but it's not it's bad it's not going to get us another 48,000 tokens
the 2,500 is 75 it's definitely 25 what we'll just go for red how many times do I have to do
that if I just landed on red 500 times 500 more times the ball drop game is actually pretty good
it's pretty consistent too all right I'm gonna do this I'm not gonna do this again I'm not gonna
put everybody through this a second time I'm gonna get like three or four hundred more tickets from
this game there's always that chance that I get all right here we go this is the shot right here
I'll take a hundred it's all right that's about well I'm looking like two or three more of these
get it oh what that would have been 2,500 too much I would have had it too all right so let's play a
game called there's 42 4,300 people here right now right so what we're gonna do is some people
probably coming back you know trickling back trickling in leaving coming back after well
we're going to pretend that I've been here the whole time
so I want everybody in chat right now for like the next five minutes to just to just be talking
about stop playing this dude you've been here for like fucking six hours it's not funny anymore and
shit like that and then we're gonna have like an argument okay ready someone's bound to come back
and like after like five minutes of this I can I know I can do it though like I'm seriously I've
done it so many times I know I know I know you think you are frustrated about I'm fucking
frustrated too this is incredibly fucking frustrating if you don't understand how like you
don't think I fucking feel bad about this like trying to stay here for this long this sucks and
I but I fucking have to do this otherwise I'm never gonna hit the end of this oh my fucking god
stop stop stop can we get can we clear the chat or something please because like I this is
actually fucking annoying come on look people have sat and played a game for long enough people
have sat and played a game for like fucking 10 hours straight on the same thing so what's the
difference people play like fortnight and shit for like fucking 10 hours straight what's the
what's the problem god damn it that was it can you put it in sub only for a minute please
just put it in there for a little while what one of the wait one of the mods there something too
what are you wait wait wait you'll be fucking unmodern that person just stop just let me do
what I'm gonna do okay let me do whatever I have to beat this level you don't think I you don't
think I'm fucking mad about this too I have to beat this I can't stop it clear the room
clear the room over and over again I know I know yes I've been here for fucking four and a half
hours I know I know I'm the one sitting in the chair guys oh come on come on come on
what just needs to relax I'm relaxed you don't sound that relaxed I'm relaxed right now
all right take it off sub only I think they've learned their lesson
do you still listen to my voice I'm fucking relaxed right now do you hear my voice my voice
sounds fuck I'm fucking totally fucking normal everything's fucking fine I'm totally fucking
relaxed stop stop it stop it I can do it no god damn it no this is not what I wanted
I wanted to play this fucking carnival game for people I'm not gonna cry stop saying that
I am not going to cry stop saying that look if somebody actually really is mad that I've been
here for like five hours doing this one thing for five hours you know it's what what do you
want me to tell you if you have that fucking mad about it then then you don't have you don't have
to fucking watch you know I'm saying like if you're that upset about five and a half hours
of this fucking thing I'm punching the wall right now I'm so upset about this game
dumb fucking thing I'm just trying to make it funny but like I'm fucking so
fucking mad right now I can't even contain myself I'm fucking furious unbelievable this
dumb game play something else five hours get that I want that person actually banned from the
channel fucking remove them I don't want them I don't want to see that name ever again if that
$50 from flugboy thanks for the 50 bucks jerma I'm fucking begging please stop don't understand
if you can't win it stop it seriously people are unsubbing thanks for the 50 fucking bucks man but
like I'm I'm thanks a lot for the 50 bucks and dumb fucking thing stupidest fucking thing
in my whole fucking life in my entire fucking life it's shit like this like that makes me want
to fucking stop streaming like forever like just be fucking done and don't do it anymore
like you know I'm saying like this is honest to fucking god thanks for the 50 bucks appreciate
fucking god damn it thanks thank you thank you for the 50 fuck I can hold on the anonymous
cheerer thanks for the 50 bucks that's a lot of fucking money thank you for the 50 bucks
buy an anonymous cheer huge thank you to both you and flugboy trying to you know trying to do that
trying to cheer me up a little I try to cheer me up the streamer you know I'm saying thank you
and boys and girls oh we just did it oh yeah we just did it I just did it we did it
and that was holy fuck all right wow wow oh boy can we get to can we get some fucking
that was
that's right
we're gonna rise till we fall
let's say we got no no no no future at all
when the kinky keep us out can't hold us down anymore we're gonna ride ride ride ride rise till we
fall
wait is it gonna be the mod it is all right never mind thanks everybody for hanging out for that
and I know I have to apologize in about half the things I was saying there
I banned 42 people I'm gonna unban them I banned somebody got like caught in the in the crossfire
there I banned somebody because they they were talking about like their favorite fucking um tv
show I just didn't want to fucking even listen to him so just I just didn't want any other
conversation I got to replace my fucking wall I really I and this is gonna be spread and I said
I said a lot of bad stuff and I want to make sure that I did before I'm gonna get in front of this
um sorry for making fun of all the people that were here sorry for talking I threatened to quit
streaming I think like 10 to 15 times I'm really sorry all right let me actually get out of this
let me actually leave this I need to actually I'm gonna actually leave this game now I'm gonna
that's how you get the fucking academy award oh shit look at this
they call that professionally trained we call that a trained professionally
theatrically trained actor oh by the way uh for real though thank you an anonymous
cheer plug boy and the ball of koala I really do appreciate the fucking 150 dollars for real
dude I'll fucking pay you to stop it's been five hours all right now here's the worst part about
that I did that that went up one on for long enough where at least probably 100 people came
and probably will never come back so uh well what am I gonna do right it was for the art
imagine like kim or like italics had opened the stream like oh let's check on the stream
and that's what they hear
I'm gonna go downstairs and kim's gonna be like and are you like done streaming forever or what's
going on here all right don't go how many tickets do I have 54,000 oh god okay I gotta
fucking just get this going okay somebody do the math if I get one 500 balloon per minute
how many minutes will it take for me to get to 50,000 if I get two if I got a thousand tickets
a minute it's over an hour god damn it all right what if I do a thousand a thousand tickets a minute
is 50 minutes what about 1500 tickets a minute I can do that I can handle that 30 minutes that's
not that bad no that's not that bad at all that's not a big deal all right we're about
3000 tickets a minute I only have six dollars it's okay I can go in the other room and get
money immediately a hundred thousand tickets a minute and you'll be there well um hold on I
gotta one step at a time in before I black out and save loss I'm not gonna that my power is not
gonna turn off although wait a minute have I paid the bill 6,000 where it's so close
I'm gonna say a little bit of dunko one round of dunko and then we're gonna get money
I need some gamer fuel like almonds because that's all that's that's just eat a few almonds
just eat fucking 10 almonds or eat just like three or four spoons of peanut butter
you don't need any fuel I'm gonna get all these cards how much cash do I got plenty of cash
German's the guy that hands out apples on Halloween no I hand out
the king size on Halloween that's right king size apples
I hand out streamer business cards on Halloween I know I do not do that
come on give me a dunko twitch cards how do you get a twitch card
I've seen those before how do I get one fuck no no they do like special like twitch streamer
cards don't they do it from twitchcon you gotta be you gotta be a popular streamer
are my eyes deceiving me here or are there 4,300 people here
this is am I do have to squint my eyes is that something else
come on I get the big jackpots right that's a big jackpot I'm the guy on twitch it gets like the
jackpot my twitchcon card would be like sevens and then it'd be me with like dice in my hand
and it'd be like a bubble over my mouth it'd be like Viva Las Vegas and I'd hand out three of
them the other it's like 6,000 that got printed would get like shredded bonus come on you should
be the joker card the bonus is fun you guys all said that we did yeah can I play some dizzy bird
nah I don't have enough money dad eight quarters I can't wait for this 100,000 tickets
in the boombox to not be worth it at all and it's probably only going to sell for like 50
I still have the prizes of the basketball game you're right I do
they always just get in the way 60k come on come on it's so I just need a good bonus
and then we can be done with this is there any game that I haven't like totally completely
flexed on the bass that's right no you're right you're right you're right I have not won the
bass machine yet it's like the only one and the treasure machine yeah but that's I think that's
impossible have I saved I saved a little earlier I'll go and save again how long have you been
playing dunko no we're not gonna do this again we're not gonna I'm not gonna do like the
pretend like hate everything and I've been playing dunko for six hours Vilemi thanks for
the 50 dollars Vilemi actually thanks for the 80 dollars that's a lot of money Vilemi says you
haven't gotten the high score on the gamer fuel one is there a gamer fuel joke one and then they
say germa you know you want that mountain dew gamer fuel no I'm not gonna don't don't even get
don't make me like slander a company please I'm not saying anything I don't say anything about
companies anymore thank you for the 80 fucking bucks a huge amount of money all right let's
time this correctly three at a time three at a time I want that card over on this side yeah
let's get that pink card and I mean while we're here may as well try to get another dunko bonus
got the card and here's the final dunko bonus I don't want to have to pay any more money come on
get it come on bonus back to the ball drop let's do this one like 10 times okay I'm gonna do I'm
gonna do this 10 times in a row that's 5 000 why does it only come over here on this again hurry
up let's go this person on the right is freaking me out get away from me don't look at me
okay six I was doing six there he's being toxic again and away we go this one's really easy
you know here here's the thing I'm never gonna have to play any of these ever again in the
arcade I am getting my total fill from these games that I will walk right by them I don't
have to go to the arcade again I've seen this machine in a dozen arcades I don't even need to
play it who fucking cares I already did it like 50 times and neither do you unless you want to
try to show me up yeah fucking retweet this video if you think that you could beat me
right guys oh it's all right I still I got like 223 000 last one and then I'm gonna go back over
to I don't know I need that in the basket I'll get a thousand in the basket and win
basketball doesn't give tickets
this is absolutely
I'll settle for 100
uh
it's the worst machine in any arcade now riddle me this why are these machines always
full of people there is always somebody playing one of these there's just at least
five of them lined up and every single one of them has a person on it
low skill high reward no it's low skill low reward you get like 10 tickets every time and
it's like four bucks this is the worst machine in the art again I don't talk about companies
scared me I'm in my own world so much that this person scared the shit out of me
oh
no statistically speaking there's no way it's not gonna happen guys it's not
there's nothing to this besides land on one one percent of the whole wheel
if I don't get this you're gonna unsew what if I do get this
should I prices right this and try to get it on 1000 and do like a one tiny little spin
let's try this let's try doing the prices right technique
it's gonna work I'm gonna get there and then I'm going to farm 1000 tickets stop stop stop stop
stop it's so diabolical I love it I'll get there slowly but surely yeah what do you mean zero
tickets oh fuck it actually went over it come on man you have to go one space all right I
understand so you have to at least go over one square so as long as I get to the yeah it was
landing on the same one it was actually working then yeah make sure the tickets are actually
coming out give me the hundred hundred uh will it still count as a hundred if I go if I get on the
hundred no I don't think so let me at least hit it just so I can go to sleep oh come on evil fish
just gave five community subs thank you evil fish lots of community subs tonight big subs
it works it works I did it oh 100 tickets now can I do it again nope I can do it I can get
through those it actually would have worked all right now we know it works I gotta go a little
faster than that that actually did give me the four still all right it's coming up here right
what is it the next one when is it it's still less efficient than the ball drop no I know but
I just I have to I have to beat this I have to get a thousand to come out of the machine therefore
I can say that I completed it here it comes okay stop all right little pushes
somebody said if you land on a thousand and then do a full pull it'll land on a thousand
not well is that real so get to a thousand and then land do full speed
what do I have to lose you're right why do you read chat comments like a radio host
because that's what this is I'm how is this any different what this is this is a radio show
why would I not read the comments you want to look over and go
nice dude and that and that's what I deserve for fucking oh my god
that's a funny thing you said dude land on it organically come on back there again
do that one more time and then uh here it is all right okay all right fuck okay I
ha ha ha yeah you have to do it so light uh I'm gonna turn the audio off I'm gonna
people it's freaking me out I just pulled my headphones off because there's no way I can't
that what a sad person how much money is that old guy spent on the machine I don't know
at least $400 I'm just leaning back in the chair I pulled up a chair by this point
it's still ringing in my head yeah like this
I almost just accidentally pressed it a tenth of a percent harder almost there hey thank you
demons V for the five community subs thanks a lot my new sub sound thank you for the that's my new
community sub sound appreciate it hope you guys like it every time I get a community sub that
song will play all right I gotta be careful it's a sneaky way of asking the subs hey look at that
is it sneaky or is it just like completely and totally like just out there I'm not gonna make
that the sub sound no way this hurts so much to watch it won't be in a minute I promise
we're almost there it's almost done and then I'm gonna do I'm gonna get on a thousand I'm gonna
full blast it speaking of sub sounds are they actually basically dead kind of kind of all right
here we go what's happening okay ready two more of those I think you're freaking me out
no um there's no overshoot joke you're freaking me out stop freaking me out fuck yes a thousand
tickets all right so they said do a full blast from here you lied well what do you mean I held
it down I actually held it down I swear to god stop oh all right I'm out I was trying to get it
just trying to hit it one more time sometimes you gotta try oh where am I let's see 61 000 all right
back to this I want to let me hit this at least one more time I think that's pretty good
no no no it was it looked all right it's all right um uh the treasure game I'll try it it's
gonna that's I don't know how I don't understand how this works you joystick to move arm and knock
off coins don't touch the shovel so how what's I can't even read if there's a thousand tickets
if you get to what I've knocked all the uh all the shit off the sound yeah I'm gonna turn this boy
down this is obnoxious I'm still not getting it do you have to get all the coins knocked off
I still don't get it the coins have to go forward is that what it is the front doesn't count I
thought the front is the thing that counts does anybody get what the hell this is actually going
on here I mean damn man like how the fuck are you supposed to do this front doesn't count how did
I only get five coins oh now those are definitely counting go left and right starting in the middle
is a bad strategy you talk about just like sweep left and right let's try this let's try just
sweeping up here like going like this that's too thin um this this one's stupid that's what I was
thinking I was thinking going around like a swirl like this this probably is the way you're supposed
to do it just break the glass I need to I need to figure this out how the hell are you supposed to
try doing a square around the perimeter not a bad idea so far it's just hard to grab them all
especially because you keep um I really hope this is not in any arcades because I feel bad
for the company that made it because no one plays it no I just I do get the treasure off
I can't even go back far enough to get it I'm not done let me try let me try one more time
I'm just gonna go back and then forward with all like the big chunk parts like that okay
there's not enough time to do this I even knocked off all the treasure chests
what the fuck I'm off doing it this last one I'm gonna try like an undulating technique
that might actually work that might actually work what the fuck that was fucking perfect
oh all right that's a hundred how many do you need I'm gonna try that again oh yeah that was
that was why was it 50 tickets all right last this one's dumb who cares I don't need to get
the thousand thousand that's a pretty good push right there that was a lot pretty good push again
come on man what oh all right come on last one that's it I'm going right down the middle
check this out right down the middle on this side right down the middle the other side
I fucked it up the game's like lagged did you see that shit the game lagged I need another
attempt without the lag that was clean I was just throw up why can I move the mouse in here
why can I move this just lock me in just out I'm out this one's dumb what happened there that
was so different are we doing the skit again yeah yeah man this is the just this is the skit again
this is the joke again that's what I'm doing here and now that thing is stuck back there
this game isn't even real because if it was real they would suck that's a pretty good attempt right
there give me a hundred a hundred whatever I'm pissed right now I just threw this one away
just get it out I don't want to play this one anymore where's like the put foot through glass
button this game's stupid dumb the game eats ass I have one cent right by the bat at the prize
counter look at that I'm so close why did I move from the spot this has been a very long birthday
party excuse me please move why don't you get in there they always do the same thing they always
stick themselves into the door all right what I need some efficiency here there's five community
subs from an anonymous gifter thank you whoever you are thank you for your five community subs
500 good all right we're good here we go go go go this one's pretty consistent I think I'll be
all right 700 tickets I'm staying here there's the K just give me the Y the O the C there you go another
hundred that comes to see bingo almost it's all right I get at least three to four hundred tickets
every single time I play this and then you I'm gonna be good that was bullshit he's still on
the hockey game after this much time time guys I don't think I'm gonna get to the hundred thousand
tickets I'm already kind of failing right now my like my brain is starting to start fail
just grind out some green balls I will after this oh my god thanks for watching though thanks
for sticking around hope you had fun we're gonna have a ton of fun when I get that boom box
it happened again I can't believe it I don't okay why did it teleport over there
give me the O where's the 500 right here there we go come on now give me the O
stick it in there hockey does somebody else play this right now for me does somebody else play
can I just watch why does it have to be so quiet
fuck it's like a person that person just like fucking couldn't take it anymore and threw up
in their mouth it's because somebody else take over for a minute I just need I need a minute
hmm where's the oh I miss it every fucking time all right one two now I
give me the 500 I want that instead hey wait there's a better shot than the broods
remember that one from earlier today I remember that one 2000 tickets 250 oh this is when it just
goes absolutely haywire oh he's gonna get a ball let's go why am I so excited about this
I got uh fucked over there uh I'll take 140 let me get the 2000 one more time this is reliable for
me double let me see seeing them why let's see you gotta do it so early I mean I just close
I saw the opportunity for the 250 and I had to try to take it
okay I'm just seeing some opportunities that I have to try let me see nephew I'll just buy
you a boombox yeah I'll just buy you a boombox please stop going through my pension money
well that's the title of the stream that's why the stream is that title for you to get any
interesting item from any of these arcades you are talking about thousands of dollars of game
time a ps4 is fucking 300 bucks just buy the ps4 either way I spent over a thousand yeah I had to
I have to have spent over at least one to two thousand dollars in this arcade I keep that thing
keeps screwing me over the little switchblade on the left I saw an opportunity I had to go for it
oh well 2000 all right I'm gonna do this a couple more times I'm seeing opportunities left and right
another opportunity oh that's 500 play the coin game ost what are you talking about
so I'm addicted I'm addicted yes I'm addicted to getting a hundred thousand tickets let's do a
little okay let me I need to I need to I need to cash out no not yet saw an opportunity that's
all right 620 what I am you're gonna be very surprised with the almost the 10,000 tickets
I have writer come on get that 500 in there there the letters are in really really bad places right
now check to see how much money you've spent it's in the last tab yeah I will we'll see we'll take
what do you guys think place your bets I saw an opportunity and I took it all right let's go let's
let's find out let's find out let me get these tickets that's a lot I'm thinking the hockey
machine is the most reliable we're almost there it is no I'm not gonna check that tab yet I want
to see how long the journey was let me get there first all right those are in a decent spot ball
drop is faster what do you mean ball drop ball drop is crying what are you talking about which
ball drop you mean mega jackpot ball drop what do you mean like red ball drop red ball drop
I disagree I don't think red ball drop is faster let me get one more like good run on this one
and we'll go over to uh mega jackpot is the why okay that 500 will go in I need to see
there it is all right let's get the 500 too oh getting pretty good 2000 all right let me
get some more 500s there it is a few more of those and we'd be good to go damn it that's
standing up right now is that going to be a problem for me is that going to be a problem for me
get in there you didn't play the chicken version um we have a few times hold up there's a lot
there's like two 250s in there damn it oh
I'm losing it I can see the end of the tunnel I can see the end of the tunnel and I'm running
out of gas in my car get in there get the fuck in there I need someone else to play this I need
someone else to play this I'm getting tunnel vision my only view is like a four inch diameter
around my eyes I can't see anything there we go I can see again there are two 500s I need
to get those there's one I gotta get that other one too guys this is going fine there's that other
500 it'll come around again I got to see I need the e the h and the o ah e h o e h o e h o
I'll take it that's a lot what's that 500 buried over here somewhere there it is no no oh there
it is come here come here the h and the e what a fucking blunder damn it
it's I have to finish it you know you know when you start something
you just have to finish it get in there I'm gonna lose my mind this is 250 at least it's 250
h and e forget about the 500s double motherfucker ah where's the e
all right now I'm gonna get the 500s I'm gonna clear the 500s and I'm out that's a clean 250
right off the bat there's a 500 there there's a 500 right here bingo just get the other one
there's one more in there there it comes shit oh my god okay I'm out one more 500 I'm done this
one right there there it is I'm done I have a couple more chances to get it I got the h
got the c this is the y two h's oh damn it this has come to an end yeah it is gonna come to an
end pretty soon because I'm gonna get the money I needed I should have been doing this a long time
ago I'm consistently gonna have 10 grand where's the uh the k and the e and that's it I'm just
opened I just I missed it again I'm fine everything's fine what are you guys talking
about why is everyone freaking out what's wrong what's better is the oh you have to go to work
in the morning we will be done within the next 25 minutes that would have been a 500 here comes
okay slap shot I love I'm still trying to put in like interesting commentary here really you
really still trying to do that all right okay here we go right here oh my god what are you doing
nobody touch my uncooked spaghetti please you son of a
no I'm gonna be at like 8800 all right give me the k and that's it sneak that 250 in there
is there any 500 I haven't seen a 500 in a long time come on right here you piece of crap
oh no what the fuck here's okay I got a 500 finally all right give me some more fives
and I'm out I'll take a 250 all right I'm out print it this is a shit load I'm gonna be nearly
I'm gonna be like 10% away there almost this is gonna be 10 000 84 000 all right now we're gonna
do a little bit of relaxing balloon catch just relax um I haven't gone to the bathroom in eight
hours I haven't done a bathroom break have I this whole stream have I you have gone you just haven't
noticed right right yeah how much water have I had uh full like probably two glasses of water
that's why am I lying to you guys I've you I've been sitting here that's a lie I just I lied
right to you I've been here I've been sitting here I had a big cup of fluid here and then oh
yeah I've had like maybe two glasses of water oh really um because I can go back through the vod
and see that you haven't left once and you haven't drank anything get it together all right let's
get okay that was that a clean 1500 that's 1500 let me get like six to seven thousand here when
your internet went out yeah I was just sitting here though actually I walked out uh to see if
the whole house's internet was off and it was so then I kind of came right back in after I do this
we'll take a break um I'll come back and we will we'll finish up we've been going for a long time
this vod may be deceiving but it's been about eight to eight and a half hours or so just pick
it up I'm not ending well I mean I'm yeah I will not right this second all right what's that get me
to we're very close um I'm thinking I'm thinking mega jackpot here mega jackpot is 6200 just need
to hit it once what I get I add a ball let's wait for the jackpot get in there so anytime your
friends ask you if you want to go to Dave and Buster's or Chuck E Cheese or something usually
that entire experience is about three to four hours oh wait he's talking about companies again
yeah probably shouldn't be talking about companies drop them all in um I don't think I can you can
only do them one at a time yeah I can't do it right now this is a different version I think
yeah no I don't know this one's too random I'd rather just do the uh I'd rather just do the hockey
game or uh chicken little let's do chicken little got it okay bonus oh almost happened
this machine no this machine no it's not gonna happen I don't want to play this one
no no no no no no going back to the hockey machine that's the best one no I don't want
to play again I'm gonna take these I'm gonna take these tickets I'm gonna go outside I'm gonna save
the game okay let's go to the hockey game all I need is I need like 13,000 tickets I'll get it I'm
gonna do two of these I'm gonna just knock it out of the park right now this is the o here comes the
y why I got the k didn't even try to get it and I still got it here comes the o and the c
sorry this is fine it's a good start bring it around again e good just need the h we need the h
and the y I'll take another 500 I'll take that that's pretty good I'll take it I'm happy with
that you got another 500 what you've noticed is German's number of tickets have not gone up and
we were in hell well that would be bad I missed you're gonna grab a drink don't do too much while
I'm gone um I definitely think you have enough time to get back get in there come on I gotta
get this quick I need like another 10,000 you stupid game it's because yeah I haven't gone to
the counting machine this is it right oh so close I'm so close finally he's not gonna make it I will
definitely make it before midnight like that's certain before midnight Pacific before I turn
into a fucking gremlin this will happen why would I just swing right there I don't know
with those kind of mistakes you're not gonna do it h ah no ah what did anyone know what's on the
ground how much is on the ground right now 20 22,000 all right how much is on the ground
several okay let me get a good count here hold on I need just about 8,000 so close we're just going
for points now I don't who cares about the h's the e's the k's who cares 8,700 good good good
70 6,700 good get in there 500 that's all right I'll take these little thousands that's fine see
comes the coming at you with a boo now I just need the h and I we're gonna be very close
how did that go through all that I don't understand how that happened what's with
running water does a running water sound why do I hear running water he's pissing himself
that was pretty funny get in the h got it all right 2,000 give me some of this come on give me
some of this where's the 500 it's 250 coming up oh it's 500 right there all right what do I got
cash it in we're almost at 100,000 tickets with 97 326 now I'm going to play a thing as a game
that I like I just have to do this three times that is pretty damn close how is that not accurate
oh yeah 2,000 more what do I how do I end this what do I do with this how should I do what should
be the last thing I do bonus get that card in there nice good drop got it all right okay now
I can that was fun let's do some of seven else hey gosh I've got a funny idea I let me try to get
like a good like 500 from this it's been five hours I can get that one it's 200 tickets that's
not bad ah overshot the damn thing I don't even know where it is I only got five minutes left
it's 1146 we talked about it's like 14 minutes left oh 14 minutes until what until I have to
have 100,000 tickets all right I get a bonus swing here not even close you need more money
too well the idea is get the boom box and see how much I can sell the boom box for
that's bullshit I tried all right I'm out here I'm out I'm out I'm out last one this is actually the
last one of the whole night better make it a classic nah that's not I can't go out on that one
here we go better make it a classic going out of the classic here we go where's the green ball up
there it's okay all right whatever I got 500 tickets I'm about okay feed in the last one and
see what the last number is 99 394 I need a stacker this is it check this this is the worst
possible place this could be thank you 100 and that's I need what a dumb game let's go out on
skee ball no I just got the the bonus I got the five I got the green light on the chicken why would
I go back to chicken oh my god that went right into the 10 why am I so bad at this finally
100 tickets I know what I'm gonna do I'm gonna do the um I'm gonna do the the balls the the drop
the ball thing that'll be a clean I want to get to exactly 10,000 tickets I'm that much of a
fucking weirdo I mean 100,000 okay let's see how much what do I need okay 996 I need to get like
400 three I need three 356 guess what I want the hundreds give me these little the little
yellow ones one two three even if I get 25 it's all right too I should get it it's 25 that's all
right all right what do I got now those are 10 these are 10 fucking tickets what's that of money
I got eight minutes I got plenty of time I'm just going in and dropping it in random spot
it'll always get at least 10 whatever I'm gonna go check I'm gonna go cash these in and see what
it is grab the 50 grab the 50 no more tens stupid game I've been here for over 24 hours kid
you don't know the shit I've seen 99689 what that's just five bucks it's got to be skateboard it has
to be can I get one point that's three tickets right no is that 30 or three I saw do you know
you understand how hard it is to do it in this game give me a real one it's at the same speed
at the same place and it's just fucking ran into the wall oh look at me oh damn it sucks look at me
all right what was that how many tickets 160 hold on nine nine eight four now I need one ticket
claw machine what do you mean how do I get I don't have to drop I think I have to drop one coin down
yeah I gotta drop a coin down one single coin don't want to get too many coins here
no I don't want the bonus I just want one coin to drop let's hold on give it a second
hey here we go let's drop one one we drop two that's okay the ball drop you're right the
bike just dropped one in the bucket you're right okay I gotta waste these I just want to pick them
up okay it's gonna be a shitty amount of tickets who cares let's see how 99869 was it printing
how many is that it's only 20 thank god okay I need to go to the hold on somebody in there
I'm gonna do the ball drop machine I got three I got plenty of time was it 4949 I'm not even
it's even if I run out of time it's fine I'm I did it I did I'm there I did it it I I'm here
I did it I have 99 800 I could just go sink a hoop right now and be done but I want to have
exactly a hundred thousand so let's do it's 49 49 here we go let's do 49 49 let's go 49
whoa 500 tickets what I didn't get I didn't sink that no no stop cheering for me get out of here
I didn't go in a bowl just don't touch those ones wait I'll move them out of the way come
I have to move those 22 okay move these out of the way okay this 20 I can't get the exact number
guys I can't no I can't do the exact number look it's all it's 10 I need to get one ticket
how do I get one ticket I don't give a fuck I just got an achievement hundred thousand one
hundred thousand tickets check this out now I'm gonna buy okay that's it hold on I need I need
it another I'm not gonna buy a thousand glow sticks who cares about exactly a hundred thousand
it don't matter I win give me the boom box one hundred thousand credits boom box I care I care
I you guys really gonna fucking be like this just wait oh all right I can't even get one single
ticket it's not possible there's no way for me to get one ticket it's gonna have to be like four
no fuck it bye see you later goodbye give me the boom box I don't think I give it do I really care
about that buy the boom box there it is my hundred thousand ticket boom box can I turn it on I don't
think there's an on switch all right how much is this worth $41,000 I thought it was gonna be two
three almost forty two thousand fucking dollars to get the boom box oh my god that's an entire of
years income that that's like a that's that's like a fucking like after taxes and until like
oh my fucking god all right let's go see how much this is worth all right Barry what do you got
we took 41 grand of uncle Phil's money I'm saying all right save the game first
not like I'm gonna really ever play this again until there's more stuff to do
all right moment of truth was this worth doing what can I get from my $41,000 boom box this is
such a like a degenerate thing look at the ground why is nobody cleaning this up thanks uncle Phil
the internet not at my final moment here I see one more car one more car oh come on your turn not
yet come on just give me the boat it's all I want is the boat fish one more fish one more fish
fish all right you guys can do one you guys can do the last one all right you get to your turn
hold on hey hold on your turn um all right I'm out I'm your turn go ahead before the internet
like turns off on us it's your turn you deserve to play you've been very patient right before the
if the internet kills us if the internet like turns us off thanks for watching everybody that
was at least we got the boom box uh well it's it's not winning so that that's not it's not
winning all right here we go for 25 bucks not a good start not a bad start either though all right
what's wrong with my twitch because I just tried to click the add button again and I
it doesn't work I cannot run ads commercial break failed I tried it uh well besides commercial
break it looks like you're going right here not good why am I trying to run ads because
people are clicking on ads I can't do it I have to I have to wait eight minutes before we can do
that again did they like shut me off what did I do did I say like the f word too many times
but did I say like fuck like 2000 times is that like the threshold I can't click this one pick
another one try again I can't do that one look see I can't click this one do you hear this
I'm going to try this one more time all right you guys are in a lot of trouble
imagine taking this seriously I'm taking it dead serious this is the final scratch card
I'm just going to take the whatever the highest percent is I can't click this one so it's going
to have to be this one down here uh-oh you got one more three where is it going to be
top right top right oh sorry everybody sorry that's my turn thanks for watching everybody
oh wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait not yet hold on not yet not yet I want to go
actually light off fireworks I want to buy some fireworks let's go take another like 10 grand
from our uncle by the way if you're just catching us later here there's no stream tomorrow typically
I do two three days in a row but there's no stream tomorrow tomorrow I am having a meeting
about my own carnival stream so there's no stream tomorrow I'll be back a day late I'll be back on
Sunday trying to get shit done as they say all right let's go back and get some money oh an
official business meeting carnival tell us more I've spoken about it a few times there's probably
a few clips I don't really want to get into it fucking kids please I just want to buy fireworks
what game is this this is called the coin game it's currently in early access it's essentially
just a arcade game that also has a little carnival in it with midway games just little ticket
redemption games a little time waster it's pretty fun so they plan on adding a lot more stuff I guess
they're adding rides though the rides are already in it there is a full-on carnival that is down the
street I just got stuck in here because I freaked out and had to get a hundred thousand tickets
all right let's go to the pier I want to buy some fireworks and I'm going to light them off
no that's we'll see that's what I'm talking about you can get on all these rides you can play all
these little mini games we did them already a few hours ago the beach beach pier pier beach you know
same damn thing all right here's the expensive ones big thunder damn it I don't have money for
it's okay bye bye let me try it all right let's light one up is this a lunchbox oh shit
I had it the wrong way there we go happy fourth of july everybody that's not safe well it's okay
um hold on I want to do this everybody out stay in here don't come out I'm just I'm just
doing it I'm getting rid of the treasure machine we're just doing maintenance is this even shooting
at it oh that was lame I want to look at let's light them all up no what the fuck have you guys
lost your damn minds we're gonna go somewhere safe oh you lost your damn mind on the beach
all right ready wait is this facing the right way yeah here comes the grand finale that's right
big thunder I want to try to get him like in a circle he's gonna die I'm not gonna die
in a ritual circle no all right ready here we go
hey what's the sound I yeah all right excellent work everybody very cool all right let's keep
going here very cool oh look at no no no no no no no no no no go up fuck am I even
I'm sucking back up tickets get me I got the tickets a hundred thousand tickets
that was a lot of cars okay I made it shooting flares up where is there no sound at all it's
all gone well that was it that was fun I don't think I've even been this is my house what is
this wait wait wait this is my house I didn't even know I had this surfboard can I take the
surfboards can I take anything this is where I'm supposed to bring my cool stuff I could have put
the boombox here yep well that's sad can I take any of this stuff anything at all and I mean I'm
talking about can I have anything can I pick up anything over here what is that oh it's a light
yeah see the UFO is not done see under construction it's not done you can't get in see there's no way
to get in reload the save for the boombox uh I don't I think I don't think I can I think it
has to like exit the game and come back that's all right I have that save we're fine forklift
can I do anything with the forklift that's it that's it that was fun I'm glad I went through
that whole thing that was worth doing so I will see you guys on Sunday glad we got to get at
least like an eight or nine hour that was almost a nine hour stream right so far yeah nine and a
half the last two streams have been very long I don't know what it is but I am going to go
to the bathroom I'm gonna go get a drink of water and I'm gonna use bathroom and we'll come back
we'll do bits and subs let me just ban me coward why would I do that no you're staying unbanned
uh pretty cool pretty fun it gets the job done how much is that game that's that's how much was
this I don't think it was that expensive is it like eight bucks not it's nine bucks nine dollars
eight ninety nine uh and that they just put in that carnival that just went in not even like two
weeks ago and apparently they're gonna put even more in so we'll see pretty cool the coin game
on steam but uh let me go I'll be right back I'm gonna go use bathroom I'll see you guys in a
couple days have a great rest of your night if you're leaving if you are sticking around
we'll do the bits I'll be right back see you in a minute okay hello let's take a look at
our recent events here over here
do more dunco I don't think that's not gonna happen so let's go back to uh nine and a half
hours ago really holy shit that kind of just went by me thank you to trident jacks for the
five dollars uh did you say bleed purple thank you trident jacks for the five bucks appreciate it
uh s10 wd update I know that's not your name but I kind of like saying it
hey German this might be the last of my bit streak I'm kind of busy making a feature length
germa video it's basically a retelling of the doom story from one to eternal hopefully
it'll be my first big project like this I was gonna announce it during the green screen encore
but that plan changed so I do have a trailer for it with the release date hopefully hopefully you
can see it and enjoy it good luck in life and thank you for being great trailer ready for this
let's give it a watch if I can even add it see if I can that's not it it's that
that
this doesn't be a grenade
oh
fucking idiot oh no
January 23rd 2020 that's an actual full length movie that was fucking awesome thank you wish me
luck what's luck with that hopefully you can get it done whatever you do sure it'll be fucking
great so thank you for that good luck with that when you say full length uh do you mean a full
length movie 90 minutes I don't think there's even enough of green screen footage to do a
90 minute movie maybe there is but good luck that sounds uh fucking hilarious so thank you
kind of oh my god holy shit a 90 minute movie wow well that's that's gonna be one for the books
thank you though for that and thanks for your 250 thank you to crazy burger for the 10 bucks
hey germa first time donator have been watching stream for a couple years and you're absolutely
the funniest man on the internet I have been crying from laughing so hard at your terrible
jokes thank you for being such a great streamer thanks in 10 bucks and if you can think the dumb
shit that I say is fun and funny that I'm glad you think it's fun and you think it's funny
my jokes aren't terrible though some of them are I think like 30 percent of the jokes are terrible
and the other 70 percent are fucking like wow am I watching a comedian on stage or is this
is this like a stream I don't understand thanks for the 10 bucks I appreciate it uh gnarly thanks
for the 350 gnarly uh you ever gonna do a watching my old video stream again I loved
hearing the director's commentary behind the scenes tidbits on your videos thanks for being
a cool streamer maybe we'll do that soon you want to do that soon what's going on on sunday I was
gonna hmm I was thinking of playing sam and max on sunday or whatever like the next video game
on stream was going to be sam and max is satyr dos dead no I've just been streaming a little less
so I have kind of been trying to put things in that I wanted to do at least the last like two or
three weeks have been cutting back a little um maybe we'll just maybe we'll just do that on sunday
and then the next like video game stream whether that's monday or tuesday we'll do sam and max
or we'll do sam and max on sunday and do that on monday or something or tuesday or whatever
we'll figure it out I'll bet that you that'll be within the next couple streams see that was
a lot of fun it was interesting to do that we'll see expect what whatever the next two streams are
whenever they are it'll be that and then sam and max or vice versa it's it's chill it's fun
I'm into it well there you go there's your answer thanks for the 350 gnarly
also we had 15 dollars from delicious turkey boy they just say you suck or you sucks sorry
you sucks thanks for the 15 dollars appreciate the 15 bucks thank you hey creepy teeth thanks
for the five dollars creepy teeth uh bad day today can you please spell i cup yes i can i
then the letter c then the letter u followed after the u the letter of the alphabet named p
that's how you spell it hey thank you 21 for the 250 video games really have come a long way
it's nice that they can provide unique experiences to those who wouldn't normally be able to have
otherwise take these carnival rides that you're too short to ride in real life for example hope
you had fun time and then they say i'm sorry yeah yeah okay okay thanks for the 20 dollars and 50
cents appreciate it thank you 21 thank you engelbert humber dinkle for the 15 dollars
appreciate the 15 bucks hey germa i've been watching your streams since 2017 when i started
college and these streams have helped out as i felt depressed i figured out what was bothering me
uh i had spent too much time away from writing and drawing but i'm back at it and happy again
maybe one of these days i'll post something in the art channel of the germa discord when i have the
courage i also need to socialize more life of an introvert anyway thanks for all the laughs and
good times it helped my pleasure and yeah don't feel like you have to he said don't
maybe if i have the courage to put it in the discord that creative channel
they are channels that just they're there for people just to share you know i
i don't want anyone to have to post stuff there and have it be like well uh this is not good
enough no it's not that's not the purpose of that channel so thank you so much for the 15 dollars
definitely share something when you have it or if you feel like it and don't feel pressured to do
so either but don't feel like you'll be judged for doing so but thank you for the 15 bucks
and it's my pleasure also alamitos gave two dollars and 50 cents alamitos why does the
vessel sometimes disobey us and then says something like this to us what is that what do i say what is
this jerma talk jerma don't talk hey you shut up be quiet why are you talking
where are the jokes pay attention do we have like a poll in chat here i hate you guys so much
yeah well i was talking i wasn't talking about the chat i was talking about the stupid flying
gargoyle enemies in metal gear rising jerma talk jerma don't talk jerma tell a joke jerma
jerma why are you not paying attention to the game jerma shut up i don't think that's funny
i thought that was funny do it again it's okay to vent your frustrations i was not talking about
chat i swear to god it was lined up wrong i was talking about the stupid and i immediately after
that freaked out it was like no no no no no no no no no you can that's taken out of con you
got to see the next part that is a fake clip and it was just the what is it what's it that's it
from uh the thing from scooby-doo what's was it what does he say yes cool cool'sville i think
cool'sville sucks yes you what that happened to me thank you for the 250 for the weapon appreciate
the 250 the yuda wang thanks for the 250 oh god it's a comic hold on did i save it did i get it
i did no i just did i just save this what i just saved that too oh i hate computers
god i was like i really just don't want to have computers are really really good
and they they don't have any problems at all and i would really hate to be captured
out of context saying something like i think computers suck so no wait oh it is big
clip it clip it clip it this is not even that i really just don't out of context saying something
like i think computers suck you gotta just get this part so i think computers suck i think
computers suck there and then all right we're gonna do the comic hey can you win us a second
banana you promised hey talos could do this way better well you suck lol fuck fuck this
game i'm gonna stop when i'm at zero stop no please you're addicted no you have no money
shithead child by the way is on here i didn't write this i didn't write this
oh that's awesome the comic as a whole is fucking hilarious thank you but thank you for that
that was liuda wang we also had five dollars from zac 13
jesus germa you're making me laugh my ass off this has been too good
i'm not sure what i said but i'm glad you thought it was funny and then bala koala had with i think
i missed this it was 50 bucks from earlier bet you can't get the double green hits on dizzy bird
was that when i was in meltdown no that was not i had those two meltdowns there was the real one
that was about 45 minutes of me not being able to do it then was the fake one was that during the
fake meltdown or the real one i don't remember but that's a lot of money thanks for 50 bucks
you gave another 50 bucks earlier i mean uh later too so thank you so much for that there was a
ton of community subs tingy gave what seemed like 5 000 community subs thank you tingy for
your insane amount of community subs today uh nico cat gave 10 bucks hey germa me my brother
charlie always love watching your streams together you're the funniest streamer we've ever seen and
we love every joke you make from the best plus twos to the worst minus twos today's stream has
been great uh but he couldn't watch today's stream because he's in the hospital for a seizure
do you think you could wish him to get better soon it would really help him feel better thanks
germa you're the best i'm really sorry to hear that but hey charlie hope you get better soon
feel better soon me and all the rats will pull them for you take care charlie get well soon
we miss you we want you here but thank you nico cat um anytime i hear that people can connect
somehow whether it's a friend or a relative or something watching these streams uh that makes me
really happy because that means that this this community this stream here is um something that
can bring people together which is nice so and thank you for the 10 dollars too i really appreciate
it and i'm scrolling up here we got tingy more community how many how many substance you have
today over 100 had to have been it's got to be like let's see 100 yeah there were at least 100
well that's a lot 120 oh my god sometimes some of you guys get so generous and you just drop
hundreds and hundreds of dollars thank you and tingy with five dollars here on top of that i
don't know how much of my paycheck is left after tonight but it doesn't matter i had fun and you
deserve it as much as you think so i really appreciate that but also take care of yourself
too you are way more important than i am so hopefully you can take care of yourself too
because that's number one that's most important but thank you so much tingy that was that was
ridiculous so thank you we also had 10 more dollars from crazy burger i can't believe i stayed
up till 7 a.m watching this stream have some more money germany we all really love you greetings from
denmark greetings from las vegas viva las vegas viva denmark viva las denmark both of them both
those places thank you uh thank you for the 10 bucks though crazy burger really appreciate it
and uh hello sorry you stayed up so late hopefully you get some sleep hey flug boy
flug boy anonymous and bala koala gave 50 dollars back to back to back here during the uh the please
stop pretend meltdown thanks to the three of you don dingle gave five community subs i think i
missed it during that but thank you don dingle if you're still here flug boy thanks to the five
dollars i did a fucking 50 dollar joke and i'm proud of it hope your days have been well friend
i also seem to have taken the first napkin napkin taking the first napkin it's a jojo reference oh
thank you i thank you thank you sniff for the 250 when's the next anime like all right thanks
for the 250 really appreciate that thanks for the 250 appreciate it uh thank you to
anonymous gave five community subs i missed that well i also missed dr mcninja gave five
community subs as well not even 20 minutes ago thank you doctor and speaking of community subs
let's get them on the screen why not why not right these are going to get cut off unfortunately
because of and look look at how fast these are going and the first like two hours of them have
been caught up annoying because this has happened the last few streams uh somehow for some reason
and i don't know why this is new usually we drop a shitload of frames or the internet will cut will
turn off but what's been happening recently is this weird stream completely just disconnects 100
and i'm still on the internet that happened once tonight and this weird like going to zero and
coming back but like the internet's not completely off i feel like the second time was not even a
cox problem the first time i think was because the house's internet was off but the second time
i was still online i was talking in chat this is a new problem we're not dropping a shitload of
frames anymore the stream's just turning off which is arguably worse so they're scheduled to come and
do some maintenance here some real maintenance that has been planned for months apparently so
we'll see if that helps frames are still dropping yeah but looking over here there were 4,600 frames
dropped a 4,664 in almost seven and a half hours that's pretty normal even if you have
perfect internet you're always going to drop over the course of six to eight hours on a stream
you'll drop like at least two to four thousand frames it'll happen but thank you to all the
subs everybody that's resubbing continue to resub all the gift subs you keep this channel fucking
chugging along so thank you guys and then some and then some so thank you everybody
and you're gonna let us know when the carnival stream is happening beforehand oh yeah
once i have a date for that i'm gonna be hyping it up like crazy at least a month in advance like
two or three weeks in advance at least you will know when that day is i'm gonna have a pinned
tweet about it i will have at least three or four streams over the course of a month where we talk
about it they i'll make sure it's on the discord as a pin message i'll make sure that it gets on
the reddit as a pinned message so you'll be able to find it there'll be a command that's right i'll
make a command for it i'm gonna make the i this this stream is gonna cost a lot of money and a
lot of people are gonna be working on this so i want to make sure as many people that want to see
it that want to have fun and enjoy it are here so i'm gonna make sure it's in every single avenue
but i will give those details when they come i don't want to talk it up like crazy until i
have a real date which should be i mean i have i literally i'm going tomorrow um i have a meeting
with uh the person that's producing the whole thing so i'm sure i'll have some more hard data
tomorrow as well we will continue to discuss it don't worry you will know uh one one two one one
one two e thanks in three bucks hey germa yesterday was my birthday do you eat ass
a happy birthday happy birthday one one one two thank you to demons v for the three dollars and
33 cents really appreciate when streamers don't yell i like to zone out a bit while i watch
i'm a yeller i'm a screamer i'm a noisemaker it happens sometimes hopefully you're not asleep
thank you yes is online for the five dollars i'm very drunk right now but thanks for showing my
green screen video when i remixed the shining i couldn't make this in time for the encore night
so i'm gonna send it through here so for the future green screen videos i think i'm gonna have
a system where because i know there's a lot of them that have still been made and people are
still using it and instead of um doing another night i don't think i'm gonna do another uh green
screen night so what would probably end up happening is i think maybe a channel in the
discord might be interesting to have uh just a spot for people to put videos and for anybody
to enjoy them and obviously that discord is moderated so you can't put up any like just
junk like just crap that's not appropriate you know it's not going to happen but because of how
many people uh continue to make green screen stuff it might be worth having some other avenue
like another playlist or something or another channel or something eventually
let me get this loaded and but uh we have uh 250 from uh sniff thanks uh when's the next anime
stream because i'm not i don't just i don't plan anime streams it's just if the game is good and
i want to play it i mean there's no like anime planned anime streams look you play one game
with an anime character on there 50 percent of people think you're just an anime streamer now
and 50 percent are like oh so happy that you're an anime streamer now can't i just play a video
game that i like that it's about selling toys anime i'm glad you don't say it like anime anime
anime it isn't it anime anime well this is gonna play us out here this is a potential vaude muter
this is uh germa's beautiful dark twisted fantasy this is germa 95 and kanye west
he is silent vaude beaut is this is this a full song should i just like play bits of this and
like then put it in the chat this is gonna kill the whole this is like a is this the whole song
was the best kanye album fucking answer i've actually never really listened to a kanye album
before i i haven't but i don't i haven't listened to kanye what the fuck is this
do you eat ass what are you talking about that's your question it's that's a piano that's true this
way how do i get a pair of pants that's kind of fit this thing what the fuck
did you was that edited did you edit that five nine like how do i get a pair of pants that's
kind of fit this thing i actually said that was a shit face oh there's more hold on this is
bullshit this is not even real this is fake this is a fake like outro card because there's more
no it is that that's it i thought it was a fake outro card i forgot youtube has like this stuff
that you can all right right oh that was fucking hilarious thank you that was awesome good show
good show good show let's also pull up the bits that may have crashed from earlier let's see
let's pull up those bits because the screen did turn off let's see if i can pull them from earlier
hey i got them or do i not no this is from this is this the mustard site has the same ones
yeah the mustard site has the same ones plus two minus two analytics do we have
i don't is there a chart that's made do we have any plus two minus two analytics
that's a pretty high score i don't think it's been charted but that's a high score
uh looks like i got yeah i got they're all up to date according to the other site
okay that's a pretty good one let's drop it no no no i'm trying i'm going to turn the stream
up before you drop it but uh no that's that that's it i'll see you guys on sunday thank you thank
you thank you thank everybody for watching that was a stream it was a interesting one
uh wish me luck tomorrow so i can continue to figure out this next big stream and i'll see you
guys on sunday we'll do a watch movies kind of thing we'll do sam and max maybe we'll see how
i feel it's gonna be one of the other take care guys have a great rest of your night or early
morning some of you probably just waking up take care and yes i will feed you in stream legends
don't work that they'll do it right now my way there now here we go i'm clicking the button right
now did they come you should have just got it all right good night guys