Late. No, no, no. I'm not late. I'm contractually obligated to be here!
Holy shit. What? That sounded weird.
That was like... I don't know what that... I don't know.
My, like, throat just took that and blended it up into a bunch of liquid.
I don't know what that was. I'm sorry.
Anyways, hi. Got a lot of stuff going on this weekend.
I'm not even supposed to be here right now.
Usually the intro screen is there for two, three minutes.
I was just ready.
Yeah, we're going to be live for three days in a row.
We got today, tomorrow, and Saturday.
Lots of games to play, including, of course, Gotham Knights.
Sponsored to play Gotham Knights.
Then this is an Omega sponsor because it's three days in a row.
But, but Gotham Knights is only going to be for a couple hours a day.
And I'm going to be here for at least five to seven hours each day.
We got a lot of shit to play.
Omega gaming weekend.
We want Scorn. I beat Scorn.
I literally beat Scorn three days ago.
Do it again.
There's not even a second ending.
By the way, okay, let me tell you about Scorn.
I sat down and after an evening and after sleeping on it,
I kind of realized how much I liked that game.
I really liked it.
It was, I don't know, it stuck with me for a little while.
It was just like, whoa, that game was weird.
It stuck with me for a little while.
It did play the sound.
I actually still have it.
It's still saved here.
That's so stupid.
But yeah, so you probably saw the title playing Crash Bandicoot 4.
It's about time.
I have, well, the title already says it.
I've never played Crash Bandicoot.
I don't have, I probably have like maybe 40 minutes total across the whole franchise
across various demo discs.
So we're starting with, in the middle of the Star Wars franchise.
Have you played it?
Have you played Uncharted?
No, no, I've never played Uncharted.
I don't even know what, honestly, I don't even know what that game is.
I know that Uncharted is about a guy that runs around getting treasure.
And then sometimes when something bad happens, he goes,
oh, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no, no.
That's it.
I don't know anything about, I don't have nothing.
I don't know anything else.
Should I play Uncharted?
Should I just do it?
Is it fun?
Is it a good game?
Is the Uncharted series a good franchise?
And do a poll.
I want it to be at least, it's not 80% at least I won't play it.
Is Uncharted a great franchise?
I want to see a poll.
And if it's over 80%, I'll play it.
Okay.
And I didn't say good, I say great.
Great franchise.
Okay.
Whoa.
Oh, no.
This is not what I expected.
I thought everybody loved this franchise.
Really?
That seems pretty high.
40, 50%.
What?
The later games are much more enjoyable.
It's good, but it's not great.
Are we going under 50% here for is it a great franchise?
Okay.
Well, I guess maybe I'll pass on it.
Maybe one day I'll play it for fun.
All right, let's get started.
Let's go.
We're playing.
We got like six or seven games to play this weekend.
And of course, Gotham Knights.
But that's not right now.
We'll do that later.
The way that this is going to be sectioned off is
for like the first two, three hours, maybe first few hours,
we'll play some stuff.
And the stream will always end with Gotham Knights.
That'll be like the second half of each stream.
I'm ready to play Crash Band.
Am I going to like this game?
How do you even play Crash Bandicoot?
It's like an RTS or something.
Imagine if he thought that.
You jump and run.
Okay.
This is kind of loud.
It's loud for me.
It's a little better.
All right.
Crash Bandicoot 4.
It's about time.
Oh, cutscene.
You look like 20 today.
24.
Let's go shaved.
Quiet.
Crash Band.
At last.
I, the great Neo Cortex.
Have you right where I want you.
And now the final blow.
Is Jimmy Neutron this guy's origin story?
Hush, simpleton.
Is it what he turned into?
Face it, entropy.
It's going to fail again.
At least Uka Uka and I attempt to free us from this prison.
I won't sit idly by and listen to your inane ramblings for another decade.
Whoa.
That guy's design is crazy.
Little clocks.
I feel like I should.
I'm not allowed to play this game.
Crash.
Like I have to put my save file from the first three games.
Otherwise, I'm not a real fan.
All right.
How do I play?
Fluid.
It's fluid.
I got to warn you.
I'm in a fucked up mood today.
But damn, I'm in a fucked up mood.
I got to get this out before the sponsor portion.
You know what I'm saying?
Okay, cool.
Dude, can I play the first three games on this?
Dude, you get apples, right?
Is there a double jump?
There is.
All right.
Oh, Joe HUD.
Okay.
Is this okay?
Is this a remake?
Or is this a brand new experience?
New game, original game.
All right.
This is kind of fun.
I remember this style of level being in the demo disc.
We must go.
They actually have a good shadow in this one.
They have pretty clean looking.
You're right.
Okay.
She shields me from damage.
You can take one hit, right?
You die in one hit in this game.
Oh, my God.
Wait, can I?
This is parry.
I'm biting my whole mouth off.
I don't know why I do this.
So just run.
What happened?
Oh, that was TNT.
All right.
That's Crash Bandicoot 4.
That was fun.
It's pretty good.
I'd say you should give it a try if you like it.
Are they bosses?
Will it blow up?
All right.
I get it.
Didn't they make like five racing games?
Yeah, I'm not playing on the retro mode.
I'm playing on the modern mode.
Is that bad?
Oh, shit.
This fluid checkpoint.
Cool.
Did you have two shields?
No, why would I play this scorned sound effect right now?
Oh, I can crawl.
Okay.
Ooh, all right.
I feel like this is a fun game to speed run.
Are you okay?
Yeah.
Why are you asking that?
Bonus round?
Nice.
Oh, wait.
Let's go get it.
Okay.
So how does this compare to the other ones?
Do you guys think it looks good?
How come you're not laughing hysterically at all the cartoon sound effects?
Why would I?
Bullshit.
Holy shit.
That's the only time I'm doing that for the whole night.
I promise.
Okay.
I will tell you I can not do that during Gotham nights.
Like, I can't.
I literally can't.
Like, I cannot look up at Gotham City,
at like the big sprawling city and all of a sudden you hear scorn.
That can't happen.
I genuinely think that I can't do that.
You have to.
I can't do that.
I'm missing four boxes?
You better remove that from your soundboard then.
Gems and skins?
Gems unlock skins.
Earn gems by breaking crates,
getting wumpa,
finding hidden gems,
and beating levels in three lives or less.
Okay.
All right.
That's kind of cool, I guess.
Is it just in-game currency?
I don't think you have to pay for anything.
Golden wumpa crates give 25 wumpa.
You didn't even tell me how to grab the fucking pole thing.
You didn't even tell me how to do it.
How do I do it?
How do I hold it?
I gave the whole jump.
Okay.
They didn't say that.
Where's my tutorial?
I don't know why I just tried to dodge.
There is a dodge roll.
Okay, there is.
You're too big of a streamer now?
Wait, what did the person say?
What did you say?
I know you're a big streamer.
Just don't forget your roots.
What do you mean?
You're gonna ban that guy?
No.
Why?
You need longer hair.
I'm gonna hit this, aren't I?
Oh, okay.
You've changed.
I don't know.
I don't...
Okay.
I know everybody says this.
I don't think I have.
I feel like I have the same brain,
same thought process,
the same way I approach everything
since I was 25, 26.
I feel like I haven't really done anything that different.
Maybe I have.
I don't know.
It's hard to tell.
Whoa.
All right.
We're good.
Where's 2018 gerba?
Did you just kill me?
All right.
What's that?
Can I jump over there?
I thought that was like a magical item.
That looks like a secret to me.
Grabbing that little rat thing.
There's no iframes.
Okay.
I can't be losing in this game.
I just...
I physically can't.
If I die to this guy one more time,
I will do a scorn in Gotham Knights.
Thank God.
I physically...
I think that's literally not...
I think that's like the contract.
Okay.
All right.
The game got a lot harder in one tutorial level.
Hold on.
Bonus.
Cool.
While holding B, double jump.
Oh, it's like a Super Mario 2 Luigi jump.
That's kind of cool.
Oh, shit.
We're good.
We got it all.
12.
Oh, that's 12 right here, right?
Nice.
All right.
I got them all.
100%.
What game are you playing?
This is Crash Bandicoot 4.
Does this still count if I'm off screen?
All right.
I get it.
It wants you to...
Oh, my God.
I fucked it up.
Yes.
You listen to a Goo Goo Gaga game.
Super Mario 1 is one of the hardest games ever.
Sorry.
Crash Bandicoot PS1 is one of the hardest games of that generation.
Is this your fursona?
I mean, no, but it's kind of cool.
I don't know.
Is it a bandicoot?
What even is a bandicoot?
Cool.
I don't know.
I made a movie with this guy.
Can you see a 3D animated series?
TV series.
Oh, come on.
Two.
I missed two.
Can you please do the crash?
Whoa sound.
How does it go?
What does it sound like?
It goes, whoa.
Like that?
That's not even right.
I'll try it.
Whoa.
That kind of sounded like Luigi.
Time and space will be within our grasp.
Engine, embryo.
You had some little projects you wanted to tell me about?
Master, my mechanical marble will hypnotize you and I.
And my potion will make me and them unstoppable.
Right, yeah, fine, sure.
Have fun with your ray guns or whatever.
Pacing your steps.
By my calculations, our enemies are already moving against us and we will prevail.
Cool.
I don't know what the sound effect is.
Welcome to the dimensional map.
Here you can select levels to play.
Switch between Crash and Coco.
Change skins and replay levels to take on time trials.
Time trials.
Okay, all right.
This is the actual sound effect.
All right, hold on.
Whoa, whoa.
That was not even that different than what I did.
That was not even that different than the thing I just did.
Try it again.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
I win.
All right, B level to unlock time trial.
Should I try this?
Hold on.
Wait, did I unlock a skin?
How do I get this?
Unlock in Rude Awakening.
Oh, shit.
There's so many skins.
Digital download.
Oh, look at that.
Totally tubular.
Should I use this one?
Unlock in Insanity Peak.
I mean, it's Halloween.
I'm going to do...
Do they have the same moves?
Are both characters the same moves?
Let's try.
They're exactly the same?
Okay.
It's cool.
Go!
Wait, A's world?
Oh, this is kind of weird.
All right.
The depth is hard to do here.
Hold on.
I want to try to get as many boxes as I can.
Shut up.
Oh, my fucking God.
I'm never going to beat this.
Oh, my God.
Don't freak out.
Like, stop.
I don't like...
What's happening?
I don't...
I genuinely don't understand.
Is that jump way larger than I think it is?
I'm going to lose to the second level.
Why is this jump five times bigger than I think it is?
That jump is huge.
Okay, that was the problem.
I'm good.
I like that sound.
Sorcery, sorcery, sorcery.
What about it?
I should play it?
Yeah, I will.
One, two...
Oh, I missed dialogue.
Shit.
Don't kill me, please.
Nitro crates explode on touch.
Is that a bad thing?
That's a bad thing, right?
How do I do this?
Is this a bad thing?
But do I...
Okay, I have a question.
Do I have to break those?
Does it count to my total crate count at the end?
No.
It's not that complicated.
I'm just asking a very simple question.
Okay, no health.
This game came out in like 1994.
What do you mean no health?
Well, this one came out like yesterday or today, whatever it was.
Those...
All right, so don't touch these.
Oh, relax.
I have to break them all.
I'm just going to go with the fact and assume that I don't.
No.
Okay, so there is a butt drop.
I did it before.
Hang.
Oh, missed a box.
I got a golden pear.
You missed two.
Whatever.
This is not 100% playthrough.
This is a kind of sort of playthrough.
Go back.
I can't even go backwards.
Why?
I've banned that person.
Time that person off for 10 minutes.
My god.
I'm so mad at that person.
No, and it ruined everything.
How many lives do I have?
Gotham Knights contract.
No scorn.
Sign here.
It's the baseball signature.
That's pretty good.
I don't care if I get...
Whatever.
Jesus.
Okay, move on, please.
Uh-oh.
I have a time limit.
That's like walking on a Dark Souls banister.
I like this level.
Oh, I thought that was a fucking button.
I'm so...
Don't start me back.
I like this game.
I like it.
It's tricky.
It's...
I like it.
It's tricky.
I gotta get all 22.
Does that do?
Oh, it's...
All right.
Let me calculate this.
Calculated.
Shit.
I thought that was...
All right.
So now I think it's gotta be this.
Yup.
Okay.
Thank you.
That's them all.
I got 22.
Pretty sick.
Oh, secret.
Get out of here.
Did I miss any behind me?
No, we're good.
Oh, my God.
It's gonna fall.
Why did I do that?
Dude, too loud.
Too one-up.
Okay.
So what did I...
Oh, okay.
I know.
I know what I did wrong last time.
Okay.
Wait.
Wait a minute.
Excuse me.
What's under there?
Nothing.
Okay.
I can't...
How?
It just told me to crawl.
Dude, there's a fucking invisible wall right there.
Did I skip Luigi?
There's an invisible wall.
I thought I had to jump up there.
All right.
Why hold B to crawl?
I don't get this.
I actually just did that.
Whatever.
I don't care.
I just...
I did the NG teleporter kill to myself.
All right.
How are we doing here?
Oh, my God.
I didn't...
I pressed the wrong button.
I shouldn't crush them.
Wait.
I like the level design.
It's actually really good.
The level design is actually good.
Sometimes they make a game like this and it like sucks.
You know what I mean?
Come on.
Get up there.
Damn it.
Okay.
Cool.
Let's don't fall off.
Destroys all nitro crates in this level.
146.
It's all right.
I'll take it.
My FPS dropping on my camera.
A little bit.
Restart the level.
Wait.
I can restart.
Play level.
Time to beat.
Is that one hour and 39 minutes?
Wait.
Do I actually fight against a ghost?
Do you actually see the ghost on screen?
I did not beat this level in a minute and 39 seconds.
This took me like 20 minutes.
Do I get to...
Is it like a...
Okay.
Here we go.
Oh, let's go.
He's a fucking idiot.
He's going to fall like three times at this part.
Hey, wait.
What the fuck?
That's not me.
I didn't do that.
That's not even me.
It's a speed run.
Oh, I thought that was me.
I thought it was like a ghost thing like in Mario Kart.
All right.
Let's go.
It's a speed run.
I thought I was racing against the ghost.
In Mario Kart.
Stop referencing Mario.
It's the most celebrated video game franchise in human history.
Guys, the cavemen even knew who the fuck Mario was.
It's...
You cannot not make Mario references.
Okay, cool.
What else you got?
I'll be very honest.
I really thought this was going to be kind of shit.
I'm going to be just very upfront.
I just didn't think I was going to care.
I thought it was going to be like each one of these levels is kind of just...
Oh, it's like world 1-1, 1-2, 1-3, 1-4, 1-5.
And they're all like the exact same.
It's like no difference.
It's just kind of a slightly different level with different platforms.
But each one of these levels seems pretty different.
I like the design so far.
Game critic Andy.
I like the design.
I like what they've done with this so far.
Like, what the fuck?
Who cares what I think?
I eat boogers.
Like, you know what I mean?
Like, who cares what I say?
What is in here?
Wait.
Don't forget about the secrets.
Yeah, I got to get this out of me.
I have to get it out of my system.
I can't say I eat boogers on the sponsored part of the screen.
I got hit?
Who made this game?
What's the company?
Don't touch that.
Get back.
No, go back.
I want to go back.
Just die.
How do I fall off?
How do you fall?
Okay.
That's nothing.
I think I just lost the level.
What is that then?
Whatever.
Oh, shit.
No.
Whatever.
What's that?
How do I even get that?
How do I get that?
I keep missing it.
I don't know how to get that.
Oh, yes, I do.
Stupid.
How do I get up?
Oopsie.
Okay.
Well, what did that do?
That's what it was.
Is that what it was?
It's your favorite 2D platformer of all time.
I really kind of don't like them that much.
I enjoy them, but not really enough to care that much to have a favorite.
I enjoy them, but it's not like, oh, wow, my favorite.
Name some iconic platformers.
I'll tell you if I play them.
Mario.
Yeah.
But I mean, what's the easy question?
Celeste was really good.
Yep.
Celeste was very good.
It's probably up there.
Doodle jump.
I never played it.
This is not timed, right?
Yoshi's Island?
Yoshi's Island was pretty good.
How do I tackle this?
I don't know.
I definitely can turn this back on, right?
Let's see.
Because I don't want to get rid of them.
There it is.
Oh, okay.
Very cool.
All right.
There we go.
Number two, 20.
Where's the 24?
Oh, my God.
I didn't leave one.
Oh, that sucks.
What did I miss?
I have to leave at least one there.
There's one above here.
What happened?
Oh, my goodness.
I thought I jumped.
Something wrong with this dude.
I love how hard it is.
It doesn't hold your hand.
My favorite part is that it doesn't hold your hand.
Oh, there it is.
Left one.
There we go.
Okay.
Don't miss.
This thing can crush me, right?
It almost happened.
I almost have a three.
No, don't die.
There's no checkpoint.
Why is that here?
There it is.
Okay.
Do I have 100% so far?
I think I do.
I think I have 100%.
No, go back.
What the fuck just happened?
I thought that stuck out further.
Okay, you have to do super jump.
Seriously.
The super jump.
I was still pressing it so I ground pounded down.
Okay.
There we go.
All right, we're good.
Did I get everything?
I can't tell.
I actually really don't know.
That way?
Nothing touched me.
No, this is hurting my brain a little.
Okay.
Oh, shit.
Okay, I'm good.
No.
What happened?
What does it hurt my butt?
Dude.
What?
Okay, we're good.
Nice.
Is that it that's over here?
I can jump on top of that.
All right.
Now what?
I'm just gonna go for it.
That was the dumbest fucking thing I've done in like a month.
That was the dumbest thing I've done in like two months.
Why did I do that?
I used to do that shit in Mario 3.
My Super Mario world, right?
You would like do the boing, boing, boing.
And you didn't even care where you were going.
You just knew you were going right.
I'm gonna, you gotta be, that doesn't make any sense.
I can't feel it.
You can't stop a ground pound, dude.
Now I'm just, okay, I'm pissed right now.
It's B, B, okay.
B is do big jump, but B is also ground pound.
So I keep hitting like, okay, I'm gonna do a jump and I'm holding B
and I'm still holding B, but I accidentally touched it again.
Oh, a shitty craftsman blames his tools.
It's not hard at all.
I just can't do it.
Oh, wait.
It's right bumper.
Oh, that's way better.
Okay, thank you.
Oh my God, I pressed.
Okay, I swear to God, I'm not doing this on purpose.
I flipped it.
Why is Switch, I swear to God, I'm not doing this for like funny.
Look at this like funny compilation of this fucking idiot.
They can't play Crash Bandicoot correctly.
Why is Switch, you know, whatever the spacing.
Okay, come on, dude.
Should I go this way?
No, there's nothing over here.
That's all that's over there.
That's it.
All right, finally he made it.
Oh, this is a bad run.
Anything down here?
I don't care.
Whatever.
I'll take it.
Can I buy a skin?
I probably have enough to buy a skin.
Should I?
Look at it.
Flashback tapes unlocked.
Rewind time back to the 90s.
Play flashback tapes to experience Crash and Coco's training in Neo Cortex's test chambers.
What does that mean?
Let's find out.
Unlocking.
No, I can't.
All right, we'll go with this one.
Let's see.
Subject 218.
Flashback tapes.
Are these like super challenges or something?
This looks hard.
Cool.
Oh, I like this.
It's like a little puzzle.
Oops.
Oh, shit.
It's okay.
I don't think it's okay anymore.
No.
Shit.
All right, I'll do it again.
I'll do it again.
I thought it was going to break when I jumped.
I thought it was going to break when I jumped left and then over.
I thought that was only whatever.
One, two, three, four, five.
Yes.
Okay, I got them all.
Nice.
Got them all.
Got it.
118.
So what do I get?
I like those.
These are fun.
Cool.
What do I get for that?
Okay, hit the road.
I almost hit the boss.
Hey, Bruce Wayne here.
I'll pay you a billion dollars if you do a scorn.
I don't want a billion dollars.
I just don't.
No, fuck that.
No.
Look at these levels.
Look at how many baseball streams you could do with that.
Oh, okay.
Are you talking about like a personal income?
Like personal money you get?
Or are you talking about like financing stuff?
How did I go behind that?
Are you talking about like company?
Like I got a billion dollar company and I can make like whatever I want.
I don't want...
I don't personally want a billion dollars.
But if I had like a billion dollar valued company...
Okay, well, what?
How many employees do I have?
What do my sales look like?
I don't want a fucking billion dollars.
No way.
When you cross the billion dollar threshold, that's when you start to go like...
Oh, you know, I had a dream that I had a bowling alley in my fucking living room.
So I'm going to do it.
It's like, I don't know, man.
I don't want to do that.
Hey, you know what?
I feel like this very specific type of cheese this afternoon.
Get it!
And like somebody gets on a plane and flies to get this cheese from Italy to bring it to you.
Because you wanted it today.
I don't know.
I feel like that's too much.
I think it's way too much power.
I don't want it.
And I died.
Oh, there is a jump on the head.
Okay.
Stupid.
If I ever had a billion dollars in money...
I'm being completely honest.
I would take 10 million.
No, 20 million.
Yeah.
I would take 20 million dollars and just keep it.
Anything I ever wanted.
And then I would just like, I don't know.
I would go try to rebuild as many schools in America as I could.
Right?
Just like, just do it.
But I'm keeping 25 million.
I am.
I'm sorry.
No, maybe 50.
I would, I want 50.
Why can I not kill this fucking guy?
That's like two schools.
Well, I don't know.
How much?
Okay, you had 800 million dollars.
Like, could you cover like half the textbooks
that like college students would need to buy in America?
How much would you need?
And it'd be like, it'd be like the, I don't know.
No.
Would that be for like one school?
No, it would.
A billion dollars to buy text?
No way.
For one school?
What the fuck's happening to your education?
I've touched that every time.
Anything else?
Yeah, I'm keeping 20 million.
You bet your ass I'm going to buy that vintage Pac-Man machine.
Signed by Pac-Man.
You know I'm buying that.
The Pac-Man?
That's what I'm saying.
A tape?
How come I can't get this?
Why is it grayed out?
How come you, why are you acting like you're not already a billionaire cheese heir?
Oh shit, should have done that.
I have to come back.
I think, yeah.
Okay, I got it.
Do you not have any makeup on today?
No, I shaved my face.
Yes, guys.
I'm way far behind.
Guys, humans look a little different when they change their hairstyle and their facial hair.
Shaved the makeup off.
Oh, hold on, I got a face of makeup on.
It's time to shave it.
Wait, no, I'm just wrong.
Where's the thing?
Back here?
There, okay.
Let's go.
Okay, didn't hit it.
Looks good.
Am I doing this right though?
I don't know.
Kind of afraid.
Guys, you have to slide and just jump.
Can you do it?
Okay, I can do a slide jump.
Like Breath of the Wild?
Maybe eventually.
Do I have this first part accurate though?
I don't want to step on this yet, right?
I think that's correct.
And then I get these and then I step on it.
Okay.
Oh my god, how did I not die?
All right, now I go turn them back on, right?
I turn it on because now I have to destroy them.
Okay, nice.
There it is.
All right.
What are you doing?
I just, shit, I fucked it up.
I just poured.
I just opened up the spout and went over to a chef.
Making like a three-day fuck and just jumped salt in it.
Just around the corner.
Just held it out with the spout.
Like, you ruined everything.
I have to lose.
Will the nitro destroy the blocks that aren't active?
Will that, is it, it doesn't?
No, it won't work.
They have to be active, right?
I'm gonna test it.
I'm testing this.
What even, why did it explode?
I thought I touched it.
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
I thought you had to break it to have it blow up.
No, touch it.
Relax, everybody.
Let's try this.
Don't do that.
Okay.
So, don't break anything because I don't, let's see what happens.
Did that work?
I don't know.
Did, right?
It did.
Thank god.
Yes!
Just don't get killed because I don't have a checkpoint.
This game is so brutal.
It does not fucking hold your hand.
God, that's why I like it though.
Game doesn't hold your hand.
This is brutal.
Oops.
Oh!
Swing already.
Jesus.
Oh, you can't be fucking serious.
You hit me with the, you hit me with the backswing?
You weren't even in the middle of a swing and you hit me.
Thank god I didn't have to do the bonus again.
Yeah.
How do I see the HUD again?
Okay.
Oh, that's crazy.
You should eat an apple on stream.
I don't know.
I don't know why that's a, that's a, that's a weird request.
Don't you think so?
Oh dude, eat an apple on stream.
Why?
Like that's a, that's a weird request.
And I lost because of that person.
I don't know what the fuck I thought that was.
I thought it was going to fall.
Oh, does it come back down?
Don't just have patience, please.
Eat an apple.
I don't like apples.
I like Macintosh apples and that's it.
I really like green apples are okay.
We already did the tier list thing.
You already know.
Oh my god.
Yeah, it's okay.
What the fuck, man?
What?
You aren't very good at this.
This game is notoriously difficult.
It even says it on the box.
All right.
Let me see if I can get this right.
Nope.
Um, you can't get up there from that way.
Yeah, this bullshit.
Some of you guys have told me that you have permanent fight marks
on your PlayStation 1 controller because of this game.
I just forgot how to play.
I'm...
Oh, I thought it was already there.
Wait, I need to break this.
Can I break this without breaking that?
Yeah.
Okay.
Shit.
Come on.
Hurry up.
Sorry.
How do I get up there?
I think I have to fall.
Checkpoint.
Thank god.
How do I get up there?
Ooh.
Um, okay.
How am I supposed to do this?
Got it.
Diamond.
I need to destroy this.
How am I going to do that?
How do I break that without getting hurt?
Oh, the night...
Okay, it will.
It will.
All right.
It will blow up.
Oh my god.
I didn't even see what was happening.
Did I get this?
I got that, right?
Yeah.
This game is way harder than the Spongebob game.
Come on.
Are you kidding me?
I jumped behind...
I jumped behind it.
I think I can still get it.
Yeah.
All right.
We're good.
This game's hard.
This game's kind of hard.
I'm scared.
Okay, you can still jump.
I didn't think you could.
It's hard to get all those.
That's so fucking hard.
Part two.
Jesus.
Nice.
Oh.
How come there's no taunt?
I can't be like...
Boom.
It should be.
That's unfortunate.
It's okay.
That's still a lot.
You get this game for a kid that you hate.
What?
The game's very good.
It's a very...
This is a very good game.
All right.
This is it.
Let's switch to this one.
All right.
This is a boss.
Let's do it.
Rocket head.
All right.
Target.
Oh, I got to get up there.
All right.
Go.
Come on, Crash.
Hurry.
Oh, I hit the fucking back of the head.
Come on, Sora.
I didn't get the Sora right,
but I got everything else.
You're going to throw somebody out here already?
All right.
Let's go.
Oh, shit.
Play Kingdom Hearts?
No.
I'm sorry.
I don't have a spare 400 hours to play that on stream.
That's just for the opening cut scene.
So I just don't have time for that.
Oh, my God.
I died.
Did I start over?
No.
Kingdom Hearts 2.
That's all I remember.
One more.
Oh, shit.
Oh, okay.
Excuse me.
This is some frogger shit right now.
Oh, my God.
I missed that.
Where did they go?
Are you kidding me?
Oh, what a bad place to stop for a second.
See you.
Phase two?
I don't think so.
Oh, I like the way this one looks.
Cool.
Booty calls.
And he looks so proud of himself.
Mom said it was my turn.
Well, it can be all of our turns.
It's cloud gaming.
Whoa, I don't think I can hurt them.
Are you high?
No.
Yeah, what a great idea.
You honestly think that would be a smart decision today?
Do you think that's a good idea today?
Think about it.
I want you to I just want you to think about what you just said.
I want you to think it's a good idea.
I don't think the answer is yes.
I think the answer is a 100% no.
Yeah, fucking.
Fuck your rivers of blood bullshit.
Should get the past that shit out of the game already.
They did good.
Oh, you can hit me.
Let's go.
I like this outfit.
You don't play Elden Ring anymore.
Yeah, because I need to forget every single thing that happens in the game.
And then once every year or two, go back and play the whole thing again.
That's how it works.
Did I get this?
I guess I already got it.
The best part about the from software games is you just forget about them for a year or two.
Come back and play a class you never played before.
And it's just a completely different video game.
It's the best way to do it.
All right.
Can I even attack this guy or jump on his head?
Right.
The DLC is coming.
Yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
Getting up here.
Did you do me strong?
No, I didn't.
I floundered.
I flaked on me strong.
Oh, should I just die?
Just die.
That's I don't want to miss that way too important.
Okay.
Why would it be a question mark if I know what it is?
Excuse me.
How do I get over there?
Did you see that?
Oh, my goodness.
Well, I couldn't know.
That was hard.
Actually getting 100% there would be difficult.
And there was a whole nother thing of that section with.
You know what I mean?
You know what I'm saying?
It was very pretty.
Everything from here to all the way down there looks really nice.
You know what I'm saying?
Webcam is getting annoying.
Hold on.
We got to change this better.
Not as much movement.
Yeah, that's better.
The lights are going down for Gotham Knights, though.
You better believe it.
And by the way, nobody said anything about the shirt today.
Can we please get a Bane impression during the Gotham Knights game?
Yeah.
Which one?
Do you want the iconic today?
Right.
That's the iconic line.
I can do that.
I think I can handle that.
That was a bad idea.
I'm in trouble.
Does it come back?
Thank God.
Troll.
Dude, there's no opportunity to go anywhere.
I'm going back because I don't want to miss any cubes.
I don't care.
I have the exact same acne as you right now.
You mean this?
No, I caught myself shaving.
That's a shave cut.
Yeah, that's a shave cut.
It's a giant pimple.
It's not.
It's a shaving.
We'll blow that one up, too.
Okay.
What do we do about this?
Why was it there the last time when you had facial hair?
It wasn't.
How do I break that without getting hurt?
It was.
No, it wasn't.
It was not.
22.
There it is.
How do I get out of here?
We should grow a Gandalf beard.
I don't know.
If I grew a Gandalf beard, I probably would get it all scooped up and twist it and put
it in my mouth and be like, oh, oh, I don't know.
And people would be like, what the fuck is he doing?
How did you start choking on your beard?
Dude, bro, how did that even happen?
How did that happen?
It's not even that fucking funny.
It's just everybody hates it.
Everyone's fucking pissed.
That's what's doing it for me right now.
Everybody is pissed that I just said that.
That's so stupid.
Why are we so mad?
Okay, I'm going to play the game.
Huh?
Dude, I just keep picturing.
I pictured Gandalf.
I keep seeing Gandalf in my head with his whole beard in his mouth.
And he's going like, and they come into the room like Frodo and Sam and they're like,
Gandalf, what's happening?
Ah, he's like freaking out running around like smash and bumping into bookshelves and shit.
Who told you that must have been a ringwraith?
No, I told you it was a weird day today.
I did warn you.
I was very clear.
Why are you still laughing at it?
I don't fucking know, dude.
I don't know.
I don't, I don't know.
It's because the chat's reaction was too good.
Stop.
I hit him with that.
I feel like something's hidden up here, right?
No?
Three?
Nice.
Okay.
Grabbed my nose.
I don't know.
That's a lot of money.
Dude, Frog Detective 3 is coming out on October 26th.
Please, you're going to play it, right?
Um, yeah, probably.
All right, let me get to the end of this section.
Let me do the boss here.
This is a great game.
I like it.
I don't know.
What do you think?
Do you think we go right into Gotham Knights?
What are you guys thinking?
You guys feel good?
I want to play this for a little bit longer.
Yeah, I'll take a pee break.
Maybe in a few minutes of this.
Another, like, I want to beat the boss here.
Wait, who am I?
My new character?
This is a different character.
Who is this?
Well, I never mind.
I think the story ended pretty quickly.
Dude, I can't get the image of Gandalf out of my head.
It's up there permanently.
Hook shot?
Whoa.
Does it do damage?
It does do damage.
All right.
Cool.
Very cool.
All right.
Okay.
Ball jump.
That's pretty clean.
I like it.
Are there emotes?
That's clean.
I like it a lot.
That's a very clean move.
Come here.
I'm trying to do my joke.
I could probably do a pretty good scorpion.
I'll try it.
It's going to be loud.
I'm going to do it loud.
So just be ready.
I think I could probably do a pretty good job.
Get over here.
Come here.
That's all right.
It was okay.
It needs a little work.
Yeah.
Try to grab this stupid.
Fucking thing.
I got to go for the stun.
Stun.
Stunned.
How do I get that?
Like that?
Okay.
Cool.
Holy shit.
Okay.
I'm fine.
That thing says you're going to die.
Watch out for the shock.
Nice.
What are you talking about?
You just literally turned around.
I'm rushing.
Okay.
Don't fuck this up.
All right.
I can't touch them at all.
Even if the back is, excuse me.
You don't.
Well, I don't even fight you.
What the hell am I doing?
Who cares?
I feel like that was there for a reason.
I don't know what though.
Probably was there for a reason, right?
Oh my God.
What?
Shoot.
Much better.
There we go.
Oh boy.
96 out of 100.
All right.
Cool.
That's good.
Okay.
Somebody's linked me an edit.
The mods just linked me a Gandalf edit.
That's not what I'm talking about.
No.
He got it wrong.
Thank you so much.
Wait.
Tana?
But you're different.
You're not from our universe.
It's good to see you guys.
It's been a long time for me.
We lost touch in your universe too, huh?
Yeah.
You could say that.
What did we like die or something?
What?
No.
Nope.
No, definitely not.
So how are things in your dimension?
The usual.
A bunch of evil scientists attempting
It's crashed.
Hawke.
Huh.
So what you're collecting?
Crystals?
Gems?
Masks.
Ooh.
Fun.
Well, good luck with that.
Wait.
You're not coming?
Sorry.
I fly solo.
But I'll lend a hand where I can.
In fact, I already have.
Oh, he doesn't really talk.
He just kind of goes like.
Ooh.
Tape.
Two tapes?
Okay.
I want to do the tape.
Oh, wait.
How come there's no other tapes?
How come you're not talking?
I am talking right now.
You have to find them in levels without dying.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Good to know.
After this boss, we'll move on to Gotham Knights.
Seems fun.
Just tried to grapple hook.
That was a mistake.
I'm not going to get the tape in this one.
I get it, though.
I swear to God, I don't even fucking get it.
I get it.
Talk louder.
Why would I talk louder?
What is?
No.
This is the volume I'm going to be speaking.
If you've got a problem, then I don't know what to tell you.
So what characters are you?
I mean, I'm starting with Nightwing, right?
I'm going to be playing with Nightwing.
Oh, my goodness.
That was he.
What did he hit me with?
Holy shit.
I just blew off the screen.
I had like 600% in Multiverses.
Or Smash Bros.
Multiverses.
Let me say Multiverses.
I had 600% in Multiverses.
Stripe was fun.
I played with them for a little while.
I think I'm too stupid for Rick.
Too many gadgets.
Oh, my God.
All right.
This game now just got really hard.
Time to stop messing around.
Actually pay attention.
If one hit and you die, this is old retro game.
Holy shit.
Young Sheldon?
What's the reference?
Are you saying that I look like Young Sheldon?
I don't know what the reference is.
It's going to be weird.
True.
What the fuck?
Ooh, cool.
What the fuck are you guys talking about?
What?
It's not even remotely close, by the way.
Not even close.
What did I just save this file to?
Save image.
Where did it go?
Young Sheldon.
Save.
Okay.
Where is it?
I can't save this file on my computer.
Should I just call it PNG or something?
How do I get it to show up here?
There we go.
Get that fucking off full screen.
Okay.
How do you see this?
This is not even close.
It's not even close.
I don't look like this kid.
I don't look like...
I don't, right?
That was actually kind of scary.
Okay.
Let's go back to what we were doing.
I have human facial features.
Oh, well.
So what?
I look like other humans.
That's weird.
I don't even...
Okay.
I don't look like young Sheldon.
I don't.
Holy shit.
Okay.
I didn't think I was going to blow them up.
I don't look like young Sheldon.
We got a raid that came in from...
Who did that?
Pat stares at.
Thanks, Pat.
Welcome, everybody.
Did you come to the young Sheldon part?
What the fuck did I do that for?
I can't...
But I...
All right.
I'll do this one more time.
I'm going to do this one more time
because there's another person, apparently,
that I look just like.
And we're going to find out who that is.
This apparently...
I look just like this, too.
What angle is this?
No.
What the fuck was that face?
That's like the Joker.
That's not my webcam.
I thought it was for a second.
Okay.
Hold on.
Oh, shit.
I stretched it.
Is that normal?
It's weird how just simply stretching a little bit
makes you look so fucked up.
All right.
That was fun.
Something's still wrong, though.
Should I keep this for the Gotham Knights portion?
My head's a little too squished.
It's like, why is my face so thin?
I actually don't think I can get this right.
There we go.
That's fine.
Dude, can I like take a portion of the webcam
and make my like forehead bigger?
You know what I mean?
Just have like a big forehead.
Maybe.
Dude, I can't.
Okay.
Pay attention for one goddamn second of your life.
I have to just jump over there and wait.
Dude, big cheeks.
Am I all right?
I think I got a glass of water, dude.
I need a glass of water or something.
I need like a peanut butter or like a jar of peanut butter.
Okay.
I didn't take into account the one on the left counting down.
I thought I had another second.
Oh, shit.
Hey, 29.
Yay.
The edible just kicked in.
You need peanut butter.
No, actually, that'd be messy.
No, I don't want that.
Is there a duck?
Easy.
Yeah.
I can't.
Somebody electrocuted me in my chair.
Who did the channel points to do that?
Oh, my goodness.
Dude, who had the million channel points?
What the heck?
Oh, my God.
That hurt.
Dude, how do I get those faster?
Oh, what?
I was in the thing.
Okay, I got the thing.
Goodness.
What's this?
Find the hidden green gem at another level.
Okay.
What is that here?
That's why.
Where did that just go?
Where did that go, though?
I think that went that way.
Did I miss something?
I think I missed it.
Right?
It looked like there was something over there.
It's not.
What did that activate?
What was the point of that?
What do I do with the mangoes?
I don't know what these are.
Dude, come on.
I didn't mean to press them.
I didn't mean to press that stupid button.
Stupid button.
All right.
Speed it up.
Clean.
Oh, shit.
Perfect.
This is the sus guy.
It's one of my things.
Still got it.
All right.
Come on.
You didn't hit it?
Oh, this is bad.
There we go.
Why did that?
It didn't happen last time.
Why?
Yes.
Boss time?
I missed a lot.
It's all right.
Okay.
You don't drive into it.
So now what?
Crash into it?
Yeah.
Oh, what?
That was not bad.
How did I miss that stupid thing?
How do I leave?
Exit game.
I like this game.
This is a fun game.
Cool.
Short and to the point.
Love this guy.
It's cool.
Why am I so stretched?
You good?
All right.
Are you guys ready?
You can't see it.
It's time.
Are we going to play Gotham?
Let's do Gotham Knights.
It's time to do the sponsor segment of today's broadcast.
Let's go.
I'm going to pee.
I'll come right back.
I'm going to get started.
And I'm going to play Gotham Knights.
And I'm going to play as Nightwing.
And I am going to.
It's going to be sick.
All right.
I'll be back.
Give me two minutes.