What up? Hey, what up? How you doing? I didn't even tweet that. Somebody mentioned that I need a
Twitter update because uh apparently my last tweet is my dog is in the ER and it's been like that for
like three weeks and people that go to my my last tweet it just I gotta have something here like
dude can you please just write fucking anything and I'm like I don't I don't know what to write
tweet pog face no but that's like I can't I can't do that anyways I'll be right back I'm gonna tweet
that all right so today we're gonna be playing a game this game is unlike some of the others we've
played and what I mean by that is this game was 250 dollars it's the most expensive game I think
I've ever bought uh this has it has to be the most expensive game I own and it is an old classic
you're gonna love it I guarantee it why not emulate it because I want it I remember playing
this shit and like loving every second of it I want a copy of it I want to be able to say I'm one of
the 16 000 people that have a copy I've got you for about train simulator no I I I did I do I own
train simulator I think I think I did I think I bought it do the halloween thing let's see
do I own trains I think why do I have this weird memory of me just pain painfully purchasing train
simulator because I really yeah I have it because I really wanted to make that joke
what do I have installed in train simulator let's see dlc right okay properties uh where do I find
this battery four sounds lame you about I okay that's fine that's fine you you can have that
mindset but I'm about to get you got you're about to have sushi for the first time
I don't I don't like that looks weird I don't like that I think I don't think I like that
and you get a spicy tuna in your mouth and all of a sudden now it's your favorite thing in the
world what I don't like sushi well then I don't know then yeah I don't know maybe you won't like
gotcha force but I do and there are no vetoes allowed tonight because I'm gonna relive my
entire childhood 2003 how old was I uh night 18 19 I was just a baby seven what 17 maybe
well let me relive my adolescence how long are you adolescent for a vessel thanks to the five
community subs vessel go ahead and just get this started get this moved over here there you go
gotcha force uh this game has atrocious voice acting to a point where I might mute it eventually
because it's it's very very very annoying the game where you collect robots and fight them
and this is a rare game and everyone was like holy shit this game's so good this game was so
good that they've remade it they've re-released it for gamecube like recently I think like within
five to ten years I actually like put it back into manufacturing back in 2012 yeah in japan only
now I don't want you to see that because I'm one of the naysayers to see that when
how this plays out in 2012 they wow that's fucking hilarious thought you were doing world
of warcraft tonight get out of here because of suckers that paid 250 dollars for the game
yeah well I'm one of those suckers okay because I want to display this on the fucking reddit shelf
that's fine I want you all to remember I want us to remember this because we've got some naysayers
in the chat and in like an hour I can't wait to see their their pogging smiling faces
it's okay here we go this is gotcha force by capcom and it's animated at 12 fps that's the main
character gotcha I think that's actually the person's name look everybody gets their own
gotcha bot thing and there's backstabbing there's there's deceit there's action
it got your forces and then there's aliens that you have to fight and have bad guys there's team
up we have to make a team digimon it is not digimon these are not monsters they're got your
forces okay it's different it's a different entire series here we go the day after it hurts safari
it's not even what that says
hoping to find an adventure what he found was a palm-sized robot that has a mind of its own
the little machine was also a life form known as a gotcha board from the planet
I feel like this is how I went to a school play and this is a kid like reading the bible
like oh here's like the bible school play but did this small toy just talk
hi my name is g red I have a gotcha board and I've come to earth to find and stop the evil
army known as the death force I need your courage to battle on this planet
huh please lend me your power and become our gf commander all right you ready
you ready to wake the fuck up let's go
they are the death force that's right they are an evil gotcha board corpse that fight only to
conquer yeah bad you're fighting into gf energy which is my hey thank you mick for the five
community subs appreciate it give me your oh don't worry I was gonna just shut up about
4200 people say and like oh I'm sorry what was something wrong oh I'm sorry was something wrong
you get there are thousands of bots in this game that you can unlock and play with you make a whole
team you make a bot team and you there are thousands of thousands of them 65 chance to hit
you've done it g red yeah thanks to you my home planet called megaborg was destroyed by the death
force now I must stop the death force from destroying this planet at any cost
you're willing to fight alongside us can you please tell me your name sure
come on what should it be
this game looks more janky than monster rancher well you think that's a bad thing
how about redditor yeah how about redditor that's a good one
hey curve bumble thanks for the hundred dollars ten thousand bits hundred bucks
thank you so much they say jerma I cannot express how excited I've been
for the day this stream came right and I wonder why that is been planning dropping big bits for
it too so glad you also like this great beyond hidden gem right please don't let chat veto and
ruin it or anything and one important I'll oh there's no way one important tip never put
anything in the 20th force loadout it's missing levels it's missing and there's levels of bugs
and it's exploitable wait what I'm gonna put anything in the 20th force loadout what does
that mean I gotta remember that thanks for the fucking hundred bucks all right how about um
teeth how about uh cruncher make his name veto
that's fine thank you thank you veto nice to meet you g red honor to battle with you
let's join forces we will protect you and your planet from the death we are the gotcha board
corpse of justice known as gotcha force this game I love this game it's great here we go
so we can choose where we want to go we can go to the elementary school and go to our home or we
could go to heck ever is home there's a menu save the game here open open playing field here
uh let's just go to the elementary we can't why not oh we have to go here battle with
kicker rule I see veto's gotcha board is called g red well why don't you have him fight against
my sasuke okay face your opponent get ready go yeah I can fly too and I can dash I only get
five bullets by the way everything is upgradable in case you didn't know
about the way in case you didn't know everything is upgradable in case you didn't know
yeah the kid does suck what do you want to say he's the tutorial vision uh sasuke and I will
join your fight and become a part of the gotcha force that's right we fucking assimilate things
now we have kakeru right I assume you're not very familiar with this town since you just
transferred right here we go okay we need to go to sunny side park or manas let's go to sunny
side park skip the lore please battle with kitsune are you strong enough to challenge my mighty isaac
I think so don't skip this no I'm not gonna skip we want lore you're gonna get lore
you'll be easy you look strong enemy 230 I got dumb I'm fine what did I do how the fuck did I
just do that what does x do oh shit hold on x is like a dash oh if I hold the charge of it
all right that was pretty sick so you hold up the whole time you do a blast
you need to go bang bang bang bang with the last four I was trying to not get hit once
fuck out of here kids sucks too this is what happens when adults
play uh like basketball versus kids what happened darn you shall pay all right save the game
you killed him wait until what did I say wait until three hours from now when he's screaming
about how he's getting off I think this game does get pretty hard but there are thousands of bucks
what you're seeing right now is just it's like this is simple monopoly board
so save mana's partner now
kakiro veto please help us now is in trouble okay we've got it's three heroes manna is that
supposed to stay too all right yeah I've got two allies now I think you can change who you're
targeting too oh I changed yeah there we go let's see but not a fucking ammo dude yeah this bullet
travels where's my health all right I'm gonna go in for the kill autumn left all right all right
it's what's the top left then I don't remember this character sucks I need to upgrade him oh you
suck this is the first time he's ever played this game it's not but I mean it's been it's been like
16 years so I mean I forget a lot of things all right we're gonna unlock like the ship
repeat the death force unit
all right select your allies commander dealer or damage dealer please help me please help me
all right I'm staying I'm staying away let's get some because they're gonna keep spawning
top left is what we okay I get it I get it I remember now
oh for target you're right oh shit all right I didn't know I could buy what was that
come on how did I miss a melee that close he's left oh big guy
eventually the whole screen gets filled with it gets hard but not every game has to be hot
okay every not everything must be fucking hard what is it I don't understand what x does
okay that's a few tons in super delayed voice audio
really this game sucks where are the drugs hold on wait wait right one two one one I know the
problem is I didn't do it here I know the problem is I know the problem is I know the problem one
two three four five yep okay so I I didn't I didn't do it I didn't change it to uh okay we're good
one two three four all right we're gonna team here defeat Nick Kobe and Kitsune
hey you so you're Vito huh I don't like you
it's Sue me let's teach this brata lesson I think I want DPS for this one what do you guys think
help me help me out here help me help me choose help me out here guys
we just think of the chat yes all always girl I mean why heels always man oh why
you're an old match for me okay I'm gonna lose if you oppose Katsumi you'll regret it
would we focus first brown it's gonna charge right at the back I don't want to go throw my ammo
is there a recharge button I can just press she's getting beat up all right just keep just keep it
busy I'm sorry you out no I get it all right watch it back back back back back the guy's like two
swords I'm going to be melee into x sounds pretty cool these are all mean kids
I was really trying this game's fun he pulled his punches on purpose he isn't that right
that's sue me what yes of course I'll be serious next time got 800 gf energy seems your gf energy
has increased Vito try assembling your force you can edit your force with the x button
oh what's that oh what are the thousand we have normal ninja revolver gunman I have a limit of 800
so what are you worth you're worth 300 so I've got 500 more what are you worth 250 I think I can
take them both all right good yeah you can have and simply somebody said don't put anything in
the 20th slot it fucks with everything games too loud is that better do it no balls why would I do
that where here's the warehouse list I think you can buy them too that's fine all right we'll
confirm this can't buy them yeah you you get them from somewhere though all right here we go
training with kakeru look I have a successful assembled my force why don't we have a test
battle number one g red force this is the one it's too quiet now this bed's too soft this bed's too
hard this bed is a sleep number and it's fucking expensive just deal with it fight all right how
do we switch between two I know I know I can switch the LZ I don't know the way you can do it
shit
all right how do I change LRZ up down left c stick oh you I have to die all right you don't get
that's where the strategy comes in because you're gonna die oh this game of what pokemon
game reviews forgot your force are three out of ten yeah all right you want to go back and like
read reviews from 2003 oh so sorry a bunch of fucking reviewers were wrong game just opened
up I'm gonna edit the force I'm gonna put the uh we're gonna we're gonna put one of the shitty
guys up front all right we got construction zone which is to feed the death force unit
feed the death force let's just go over here it's bad for two though wait a minute you have new
characters all right because you're you make people too we only have two all right let's check let's
check out a new guy we don't have to start with our strongest unit first that's a mistake
see we got 20 shots in this thing oh man yeah I can fucking spam and he has a dodge roll
he's perfect what does the x do oh it's a double shot he's a triple jump oh yeah it's all coming
back to me it's all coming back to me why this game's a fucking at least eight out of ten
yeah who's next oh I just have to spam I love it I know I have I have to save the shots but still
they have travel time and everything it's so fun this guy's still fine not even hurt oh
all right I gotta wait I'm gonna spam when he lands oh shit okay this is where it gets real
I don't know you had that move oh fuck you dead I gotta stay back oh there we go
I gotta get rid of one of them activate super mode I don't have it I don't have someone
oh oh shit she healed me oh you did your fucking job oh so satisfying when they all
fucking landed a roll oh you motherfucker yeah didn't even need to use my main hero
it was na aim what 50 well that's because I was spamming what oh what is it what is it what is it
I got I got your board kung fu master I wonder how much fucking fp is or whatever it is let's find
out 260 oh do we get rid of the normal ninja I can do let's try him that's pretty good I got
that's a rare drop let's try this there are only two borgs considered to be bad in the whole game
and kung fu master is one of them well we're sure gonna figure that out he's super rare
let's give it a try whatever what does this move what's it moving like hey it's pretty slow
all right he has a little bit dash oh all right all right I don't hate him
I don't hate him he's got a tornado move too all right
get in there all right he's not I don't hit him oh that's a good combo fuck in there
I feel like that's me it's just too hard holy shit that recharge time
almost dead oh no I got healed thank you who's left all right a few more
I'll give you one thing you want to hear something about this game that holy shit why has
what's with every developer on earth what happens when you go behind a wall are you seeing this
are you seeing this shit as to why what why has every game not done this camera
what the fuck that's unbelievable you can actually see what the fuck is going on if you touch a wall
get in there god damn it he's too fast well that did a lot of damage
I'm gonna wait till I get hold on let me recharge a little
get in there ah all right just I this is a hard counter how many games have it idiot I'm saying
why didn't more games not have it nice hit no I did it you were there I did it all right we got
some battle with usagi and sutomu I've never seen that gotcha board why don't we battle huh
I don't think you can defeat my leopard I forgot to save or even save it to the cloud okay
let's do it I feel like I want to bring let's bring some bringing dps
we're gonna stay with this this team sagi and sutomu all right let's go
holy shit that looks like a little squidward people from nintendo what are they called
focus fire you didn't even stand a chance was that your main hero
you gotta get close with this character that's probably what bullying kids
I am a kid of what are you talking about I am one of the kids
I mean lands you're in trouble oh he's dead don't worry I got the best character oh shit
there's a lot of damage let me reload you got what would you get the fuck in there and do
something man there we go holy shit I got a lot of damage that's why why is the double barrel
shotgun all right let's lose points total cost oh right what's the point of this game
there is one it's battle toys with your friends who sagi has joined you I should join the gotcha
force too okay do I have enough for no I don't um I don't I kind of like this one okay but I
do want you first I like being able to go you're a last resort I'll say this one battle with tetsuya
and met hey you're gonna got your work too let's battle huh you are a novice
all right hold on wait wait wait wait wait wait the tank can be my friend
um I'm picking tank he only has one character but it's tank okay looks like it's gonna be
difficult all right tank it in there ready to go all right it's homing too it's pretty good
oh shit I didn't know you were behind me what the fuck help help
who's got me who's what are you doing oh it's this fucking thing he's dead get me out of here
how the fuck do I get off this he's got me all right fine I'm bringing in the fucking real guy
yeah all right all right I'm Hank you suck help do something kill him is he dead
oh shit it comes down to this guy where's tank Jesus holy shit that's close what was it was he
even in the map he wasn't even in the map that was overkill better luck next time strategic
retreat there has to be a more efficient way gotcha force I hate them that was fun let's do
this again let me see what I can go in here and I can hold on oh you can look at the specs
oh wow it's like a card it's like look it's like the back of a marvel card
shot attack and then shinobi bomb it's got oh oh I'm gonna try I'm gonna try it I'm gonna try
this one here to you put you in front you best for last 100 150 all right let's go
I'll try the little ninja guy wait I didn't look at the other stuff you have good defense
good shoot good attack good speed double recoil fast shooting nice good shit well that's not even
as high as it goes either guys all right here we go oh let's go stone river defeat these two
go back and read the lore all right well the tanks suck I'll try uh Usagi save the game you
dunce call me a dunce ever again but there'll be consequences
you want pain don't you you'll be easy oh that's kind of cool pretty it's slow though that's really
slow what about the little bomb because the explosion area that's not bad actually
all right I'll focus on this dude here oh get them all fuck I'm so greedy why am I supposed
why am I like this no I'm I don't know why I don't know what I'm doing I'm trying to
come on explosions got it I actually like this character he moves around pretty quickly
how much health does he have all right we'll focus on the guy with the swords because he's
gonna close the gap on me and he ain't gonna do that I just I'm gonna get in close let's try
this uh melee move huh oh that would be pretty cool wouldn't it he's more than what he's got more
than one character I'm going in holy shit I just did like a link pounce on his head what the fuck
was that holy shit how did that happen how did I do that how do I know that that's how do I know
that's an indicator of how did I do that hop right all right it's a bad hit ratio but it's
all right I'm gonna jump around her holy shit read the manual um only what 250 dollars buying
this game buys you not the manual not that it's the disc I know it wasn't fucking worth it but
yeah it was of course it was I'm gonna fucking polish this disc I'm gonna like tilt it and put
it on a little display it's worth it it was worth it can you finish fellowship with a ring please
no cooperate with the gun borg unit okay I'll keep it for now
just buy any game cube case and print out the cover to replace it
by the way what the hell were those game cube discs even called
holy shit I hit every single one that was awesome I what were they called like little
little dvds that doesn't make any sense how are they little dvds get in here and
slashing ab dvds I don't think that's what they're called ab dvds
everyone's saying disc no but they weren't regular discs they weren't like regular cd roms
they were why were they so little and they were nintendo ab dvds well how could I have not known
bb db ab dvds making proprietary hardware and that's what you call it
I gotta get higher than 60 crit rating whatever the hell that is
unlockable oh I got two of these now oh yeah who needs anything else
they're different stats this one's a d long range type fast shooting punt no he's just he's a
he makes the same thing yeah I want let's just do rapid fire guys please lore all right hold on
let me save it bilateral itch thanks for the 5000 bits by luxury 50 dollars huge amount of money
thanks again we're doing this like three or four five times a week it's insane this game came out
of nowhere to be my favorite game of my childhood it even has basically infinite new game plus good
choice I know I have you awoken you all are welcome that's good lore got you bork who was
born to protect people from death forks revolver gunman has a great sense of justice takes enemies
down with deadly shots from his double gun great lore glad we read it all right we have a lot of
options here uh how about just up there flying death force thank reddit what about the other
lore all right this is just a bunch of lines robots beat the enemy got your boy
okay yes I agree no this guy's these guys are perfect for this holy shit that was a huge red
line get it oh all right reload watch he's gonna shoot he's gonna shoot he's gonna shoot he's gonna
shoot he's gonna jump all right that's fine I know my accuracy sucks who cares it's gotta be a more
efficient way 16% if it's too bad you can't say 16.47% with an omega low because I know y'all would
wait 16.4 out of the four whatever uh over here training hey veto it's time for some training
let's go manna okay manna you have a new character what's up what's the training for
what are we training for face shotgun he didn't stand a fucking chance that was embarrassing
and wait no no no no no no I hate those things what oh shit it's like a defense can I break
through it oh you motherfucker I'm this slow break this shield was dead all right up and spam oh it
hit it did nice all right kill none of those hit how what the fuck oh my god why are you so good
oh shit okay back up there it is all right finally
shit hold on kill the healer kill the healer heal heal heal heal kill the healer
holy shit that's huge stuff uh freddy dredge's game 50 community subs 50 of them freddy's just
just that's huge fucking contributions crazy all right that's insane another 50 subs watch this
this view i've infinite shotgun blast get her no fire good thanks so much for the 50 subs though
dude you've given so much money to the stream it's fucking crazy get her i'm trying hey better than
20 percent better than zero like give us a new robot give us a new robot give us a new robot
and oh we got a battle girl how much are you worth our battle girl is worth 230
what's the cheapest thing i have 150 a battle girl stats insane speed not very good defense
pretty much bad in everything except for speed remember did you sing this song
i don't know no beam knife and missile launcher we'll we'll give it a try battle girl was trained
as a secret agent she has good mobility and can attack over a wide range her missile launcher
expands on contact with air to blow away the enemy okay did you sing this no why why is
kung fu master so expensive sing it sing it i i can't all right a hundred rounds from the
gatling gunners what the hell does that mean what manna you got to save it fuck all right we're
good nice to meet you people happy yeah let's give this a shot
okay so she's fast yes she is she's got wow that's pretty good holy shit that dodge is insane
i still got hit all right let's try the sub machine gun and then well i just hit nothing but
oh that's actually not bad a little sub machine gun reloads fast enough look at this speed
oh fuck well i got the right character for this that's for sure although you stand still for
too long to do that with these dudes get it off way more there let's kill both all right reload
i love that huge arc when you go so fast you just watch the bullets just
he loves it yeah i do it's a lot of fun oh that's pretty sick right in the head nice uh battle girl
i think it's gonna stay i don't see why i would remove battle girl at this point you need more
gf energy dude get him on stream um uh i want to like the tank but the tank sucks
just be cool they need to be put in their place oh really you get on my nerves kill them
let's go kill them oh you have a fucking missile go over your head and miss
yeah you probably have whoa what oh is it an eye frame from dodging or something
come on she's fast oh my god this last actually is not bad no i hate that move that move sucks
i think we're about to see the end of battle girl here oh fuck bye battle girl and in comes
uh slobbering sam spam and sam i just dropped my oh my god i just dropped my accuracy by like
12 at least oh slobbering sam no that's the that's the stupid board game from like 1997
i'll be playing that and like oh by the way by the way by the way
okay i might have something to tell you guys let me just double check and make me just get this see
if i got this so i can talk about this okay okay never mind uh the easy bake oven stream and green
screen dlc for free will be happening back to back within the next two weeks i don't know the
exact date yet i don't want to waste actually fine it's wasted physically capable getting there
we showed them it's obvious is it gonna be tomorrow no how are you gonna do are you gonna do vr
it's coming up that'll happen soon as well is it gonna be 15 minutes uh the green screen dlc for
free stream will end up being at least four hours there's a shit load of things that i have to do in
front of that skin it's gonna last a long time let's settle this with a one-on-one oh shit one-on-one
oh wait a minute if you want to do one-on-one i gotta put i gotta put my real guy up here
i said i didn't save it but yeah uh i will be in studio for the easy bake oven stream
and green screen dlc stream they're gonna happen back to back a double feature
holy shit this guy's got a big sword he's got it he's like tied to me what what the
fuck is he doing to me holy shit he's chainsawed me all right give me i gotta get away from this
guy he's wait how come it's 20 is two on one right now what the fuck what is this bullshit
it cheated me dicks what's the right again oh all right come on it's up to it's up to spam
slobbering shooter whoa all right we got it get give me that double shot all right
oh god damn it he's closing the gap i gotta keep going back back back back back back back back back
out fuck how do you have that many still
oh it was worth it it was worth it okay let's uh speed girl i'll get this shit oh my god why
did mine land on the ground oh shit oh god i'm dead i'm dead i'm dead i'm dead i'm dead no
oh come on speed girl oh look at that hit ratio come on now kneel down before me
do the easy bake stream and the green screen stream at the same time i don't think that'll
work out considering i have like 15 easy bake often recipes to make i don't i think that's
gonna take more than a couple hours all right uh i'm not gonna do let's go this one we're not
strong enough bake something green what kind of costume are you going to be wearing that's a good
question um none i'll just be in that same shitty suit that i'm always in when i go to the green
screen oh you mean for the green screen stream well that depends that all depends that depends
on oh what i need to do the hell of it oh what are you guys doing over here come here
here we go all right this looks like anthill is fucking everything up all right here we go
oh shit there's more than one there we go that's a juggle right there get up there get up there
yes i hope bugleberry doesn't crash the green screen i can't like maybe maybe bugleberry would
maybe possible get it now yeah then you could have bugleberry read your favorite scary story
that's not a bad idea nice jump king save oh yeah i did fuck that up huh
i completely yeah i why first of all like i said that that night why why would they make delete
save part of the start menu in the game delete your save because i was drunk i was i mean i
had a few drinks i i had i had up to three drinks fucking up four all right i like this
we're getting rid of this guy you said five well i said up whatever i had five how many did i have
five drinks for 140 pound persons too much well i wasn't doing like triples i was doing like one
ounce of fucking alcohol i was doing like 1.2 ounces of alcohol there was there was like one
half of it i was fine i'm about 140 pounds i'm like 148 come on counting drinks is not cool man
yeah and by the way exactly what since when do we start counting my drinks yeah i i drink
i drink like once every three months i'm gonna count my drinks now i'm getting my ass kicked
hold on holy shit i got annihilated i gotta i gotta kill this guy first he's slow as shit
he can't handle the button spam he i missed every single shot he's got a double i i want
to control that character i want to control that guy all right come on get it oh i was running away
from you i'm sorry i forgot you were a healer oh you're so slow get over there attack attack
looks like he's been drinking today i haven't been drinking today i had like i had a few drinks on
fucking public domain movie night but say it again this is the this is the wall here
did you know about bella lagasse that was so funny i thought i was losing my mind
i feel like the eighth time somebody wrote that i was like wait am i am i going fucking crazy
all right i'm ready check this out one of these days that's gonna work out for me i promise
cheater cheater cheater cheater cheaters never win cheaters never win cheaters never win
wow i just got just canned i just got fucking trash can all right i got one
oh my god this is hard i gotta keep my distance i'm not going anywhere near them
all right watch out watch out what don't let them come near you oh oh you piece of shit
wait till he lands wait till he lands wait till he lands wait till he lands god damn it man these
characters are not the characters to play with here maybe the ninja character will work out
risk of rain to rip this off where the hell are you getting that from all right i gotta get you gotta
die now okay good how many power what do i have left three people did you just seriously teleprag
me let's keep doing the mid this guy's slow as shit keep doing the missiles oh you have the same
idea all right i got the power i'm not gonna use it yet guess i will what the who am i fucking kidding
this launch of volley he can't dodge them all it's so much fun how do you beat the game you have
to defeat the whole uh invasion of death boards wherever i don't know what their name is whatever
it's called they're aliens get rid of them i can't i think oh i got magnet robot plus check that out
that was so cheap oh be quiet oh i knew i was going to lose oh that looks like a boss
okay well let's let's think this through here what's he gonna do support type all right
pretty decent all around 350 health that's a lot machine gun magnet arm and then magnet scope
magnet robot was created by the natural resources unit his magnet scope enables him to collect
materials like meganium meganium meganium from mines built to carry heavy loads the magnet robot
is ultra strong that's a pokemon this is okay how much is he worth 400 what on earth hold on
he's worth more than the main hero that's actually a pokemon all right let's go with
damn it i can't um wait hold on what if i get rid of a hero the main guy
and then two machine gun guys all right this team sucks but i'm gonna try it with the girl battle
girl where lead with battle girl all right i'm gonna lead with battle girl yeah make sure you
use your level two gunman oh shit he is level two wait they level up oh he does he's level two
oh how much helps does this one have 155 he's got an extra five health all right yeah let's try it
dude the dreamcast bucket sucks this ain't even dreamcast man that little hill yes show
who is that guy uh that dude destroy the flame dragon there we go i got a feeling that the
death force is close stay alert defeat the boss all right this is important who do i pick
thank please save but i didn't i already did didn't i
thanks gonna be tank
you need a chad with lots of energy um he's got lots of bots
thank you defeat the dragon
dude that's based and tank filled i stop it i don't even all right when's the dragon show up
her melee is actually pretty good okay here comes oh wait do i get one of these he's a big target
that didn't go over there oh shit oh this little guy's she's really really good
can i just level her up like crazy okay we go watch this shit missiles everywhere oh man
dude you know that was unbelievable didn't even i just you were easier than the last little mini
thing i did we showed them it's obvious you have energy plus 100 nice
uh d red give up on your futile resistance who is that this boy it must be the leader of the death
force galactic emperor seeing everything in this universe will belong to the death force
you can't do that galactic emperor however the gacha force will always be here to stop you
that's right we will defeat you galactic emperor
tutorial chapter complete we will always band together and stop you i want to see what this
guy does i died in the tutorial yeah i did you had a problem with that the ultimate cannon light of
destruction defeat enemy gacha boards oh tank has another tank now okay that hold on a second
what's that uh what's that reddit shelf image that people will keep linking these characters are on
it this is the reddit shelf character i swear to god at least two or three of these are on that
shelf i want to see what the green guy does oh yeah the links have been now and then we're
gonna stay banned till next week it is next week oh right um right it is next it's next week it's
monday okay okay take it off links are now allowed again holy shit that is a mega cannon what's this
guy do oh i love the double oh that's what that does okay well just don't get hit by the cannon
when's he gonna shoot the cannon he's gonna do it like right now
just hit me in real life you got beaten too many times all right links are available again but if
you if you write like fucked up links you just get you're gonna get banned like you're gonna
get banned you're gonna get banned what all right i got the we got our privileges to post links and
chat again ah it's been a little while it's been like a week might as well just get myself
permanently banned from the channel now within five seconds of him allowing us to post links
that sounds like a great idea all right i gotta change this up now this guy sucks but this is too
slow she's good for this um yeah no um yep yep linking the slap even waiting all week
let's battle all right we're gonna clear out the the trash watch out for the immediate laser
fuck let's do it just keep flying around that's fine just stay out of the way there we go
oh my god i just blew into it oops okay don't get hit by it this is the hit of i got my own laser
man when's he do it when's he do it he's gonna do it now oh fuck my god how do you get the giant
cannon robot that's a great question because i want one minus two ready it red idiot did you
just call me a red idiot you didn't just say that right listen you didn't just say that god
i i don't like this character i like um he heals again my voice is still desync how's that how
this annoys me let me check it like from your body
get it up there all right i'm getting in close i'm gonna go in close with this no i don't
yes i will all right just shoot missiles that thing's dragging me around can you give me a heal
thanks for the hill appreciate it don't get close this guy will just suck me in
the combat of this game is so much fun i just don't even wish that they would make a game
like this again like i want a game that plays like this what is now come on fly away
can i still grab fucking helicopter what edf yeah but edf is okay edf is more shoot five million
enemies on the screen this is like a little more concentrated mine suck me up i'll just hit you with
axe you don't want to grab me anymore do you edf edf yeah i gotta get up there kill here we go
go ahead do that what armored core yeah armor core is oh what i like would i actually like
armored core i would oh shit he's powered i can do that too i apparently i can't it's much more
complicated than this dragon ball z kakarot is a lot like this
better luck next time all forces retreat a lot of people don't have the patience to get the
controls of armored core hey um they still make robot games that play almost like this they're
called gundam versus games i just i just beat the shit out of these two why are they still here
um no i like this actually but let me watch you 150 let's start we're gonna start with fast
she's good to have to ski around with the last resort oh level two right right right
dude you fucking suck at this game
oh they both they're both level two who's closer to level three
variants 10 okay here we go the red attackers go boom i'm coming for you veto
can you rename bots i don't think you can virtual on we said virtual on is not this game huh
sorry i just finally fired you yes yes yes yes pretty cool sound board don't move if i don't
have to can i charge this no go yes go go i want some bombers too i want all these
these guys are too fast for me this guy's gonna have to die yeah you're gonna have to die i need
speed here well that's great to have speed uh not you wait can i pull you in yeah i'm gonna pull
them in you shoot them get them there we go that worked teamwork all right last dude pull them in
let's see this guy dude doesn't do anything else oh this he is he can't dash in the air that sucks
but is this an almond dirt or is it a wi-fi i don't know this is good commentary all right let me fix
that what look out watch watch watch watch watch watch shoot shoot shoot got it got it got it got
it got it pull them in oh no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no no oh i got it got it got it
got it no you fucking idiot stupid asshole get up go off you're off the fucking team
get there turn in your jersey these guys suck too just kill me i need to get all right
one of these will eventually hit you oh no this is gonna be bad accuracy shoot them how do you
turn in your e jersey i think we got a rare one oh absolutely we got a plane wait what's that
data crystal n147 what's that collect two different types to form red attacker shit i
need to get two two different delete your save just pay to win no it's just well i mean that
depends how you look at this this costs to buy probably the same amount as like a two or three
weeks worth of gems in an ipad game so i don't know not it's not what you think but
the team is the team sucks team we gotta think about this team for a second here guys
you gotta go i don't i don't like them i'm gonna put them down here damn it okay that's fine
this game is literally a gotcha pawn imagine paying 250 dollars for a data on a piece of plastic
like but that's then then nothing has value like a call of duty modern warfare 4 whatever
the hell it was that came out it was 60 bucks you just that's a piece of plastic and that was
new and you bladed somebody did pass upon two waiting bro you'll get it don't worry you'll
get it soon it's not even close to right now we want it today you can't have it today
okay this is what your mother made you today okay you can't have fucking you can't have
wendy's right now i made this little farting out of here we want wendy's we want wendy's i want
wendy's i want wendy's i want wendy's i want wendy's and this is when we yep oh you just
got a fucking annihilated all right what this guy this guy's cause a problem you gotta go
come on when i want when i want wendy no you can't have one of these because wendy's gives you gas
and i don't want to fucking put up with that right now don't die don't die watch it right there
where's my healer where the fuck's my healer healer all right i need to go i need to get
you gotta heal me you're really fucking this whole thing up for me all right heal where are
you get over here stick me with that needle what are you doing help what are you doing
gotta get that fucking shield down all right that shield's gotta go right in the back stop
dip do it are we really gonna let this guy with one health kill us we're not going to let it that's
not gonna happen right holy shit this guy's insane yeah ain't gonna happen a little too fast for you
sorry you're the worst that got you for it we showed them we did it thanks for nothing
it's a child's game it's exhausting i want to go to wendy's i want to go to wendy's
i want to go to wendy's stop saying that because now you make me want to go to wendy's
i want to go to wendy's what the fuck stop that pretending death commander orochi appears
am i ready for this my name is orochi i am the gf commander of death force
what now you must fight me i always wanted to be the gotcha force gf commander this one says
tough stuff on it that means a hard one you let me down last time man i'm not gonna be you
um we haven't used the keru i want to change this up i know oh he's the worst he's the worst but
let's do you first i like his he's got a really powerful uh ranged ability i like this better
you make this song this looks like a game my dad plays on his ipad well your dad's the man okay
the mighty commander of the death force okay let's play the smart don't go don't go don't
go in so hard what are you doing just blowing this whole thing in here we go now that was what i call
a combo good watch it all right sorry if i lose one as long as he loses one too
see if i can get him around the corner fuck sorry i got it all right good he wants a wendy's combo
why are you guys trying to turn the stream off wait no stop saying this that sounds great
no don't stop turning the stream off they have a special i'm not going in all right that's a good
trade sorry that was a good trade that was a good trade we're still we're still fine
damn it not good it's one of these shield assholes oh my god bad who's tough stuff man
tough stuff all right i gotta jesus do it do it do it i don't even know what the fuck is going on
get over here holy shit should have saved it yeah i know i remember this get me right
going in holy fuck that was bad stay alive stay alive stay alive
i'm done i'm done playing the video game again i'm done screaming i'm never screaming again
we've lost so that was hard i love looking over and seeing good wait i lost my i lost my opportunity
what okay wait i probably could have got like a wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait wait
i probably could have got like a rare thing right do i reset i don't want to save and quit
i just want to quit reset randy you're not going to beat her no rewinds oh damn it oh
all right okay all right hey that means when you play this game when you spend 250 dollars on your
one of like 12 copies in circulation you can give it a try cooperate with mana to protect her room
my room is filled with death please help me veto all right i'm ready please read this i did
and i read that word and i guess you got me thanks for participating let's watch this dude
stationary yeah this dude's good for stationary shit because his ranged attack does a lot of
damage you win this round go to lindy all right you guys do this tomorrow get them all okay it's
like the i'm what i'm a i'm like a seafood and i like obsess over it it's like if you ordered a
pizza and invited me over your house and you didn't ask if i like wanted a pizza you just
use this like delicious crispy crust pizza and i'm just sitting there while you eat it and i can
hear the crunching and i can like taste the i can just taste the air the air tastes like pepperonis
and shit and i'm just like fuck i want one of those and you didn't even ask i'm gonna go in
and try this guy's tough yeah i know you have to get in there this is smooth we got healed
i got a healer too stupid yeah you guys never you guys ever like walk into a room that where
like a pizza has just been and you go and you now you heal now you're a healer all right let's go
this guy still won't die you know i think that's just you is it me i think it's you
you know that said it talking about like breathe the air in and taste it when there's a pizza
that's been in the room like within 20 minutes i don't i don't know what the fuck you talking
about guys no you all right he's gonna die but it's a good trade get in there all right speed
girl was this one labeled a tuffy as well or no it was kind of a tuffy where's my ally did i pick
oh i didn't pick right damn i think it's just these three those missiles are so fragile
make it there we go good i think my ally's dead me versus three people this is great
well what's gonna happen eventually all right here we go i gotta hit some of these god damn it
holy shit i just got caught in the combo bad bad bad bad oh come on he thrills on the ground
all right come on got your red whatever the fuck your name is let's go oh we showed them
we did it got a hog face all right give me uh another uh data capsule i want to make one of
those planes data capsule plane wait but can i combine these two like a drill plane
you should go get a baconator and there's a gold one it's a gold one oh i think that's regular
you got a gotcha borg megaton robot
holy shit all right let's take a look so wait a minute let me data crystal collect two different
types to form reddit wait dude is that just a that's the same one why are you guys saying
reddit hold on reddit you said a reddit attacker whatever 470 holy shit what do you what do you do
short range machine gun megaton arm and then megaton hammer wait i know the lore the lore yeah
this got your board destroys everything in his path with his megaton hammer however he has to
pick up the hammer after throwing it all right let's try that first one last year
i don't have to get rid of somebody uh i want yeah let's that's too many he's so expensive
uh i'll just try this for now it's wrong i'm wrong g g red yeah yeah yeah yeah the gunslinger sucks
i like the gunslinger though for some stupid reason just buy her so rapidly okay here let
cooperate with usagi to protect the market space these ones are difficult
all right we're gonna try the bomb dude the hammer dude it's kind of taking up the whole screen
uh that's a major downside my head's gone oh you have to pick up if you get hit you have to
pick the head up how much damage does this do i mean it's pretty good it's just it's an instant
kill i think for a lot of people that's not bad either where's my head going where is it
it's gone shit's gone oh right it's passed up it has to recharge holy that's not good
okay let's try uh out i'll use it on a guy with two health let's try it on you oh that was pretty
good that was pretty good i do have an infinite ahead uh this dude's actually fucking incredible
he's just slow his standard attack is pretty good too though i just gotta make sure it lands
explode this guy this guy's all blue wait are they supering i think these guys are supering
give me my head back oh good okay i'm dead they're linked together
get them lower backs profit are you fucking manipulating what are you manipulating
what are you guys manipulating for hey i started this company you can't do this to me
talking about wendys and pizza trying to get me to stop screaming do you know how much i sacrifice
i had to go all in i was thinking about it if i go all in it's like the tasmanian devil
it's like i'm sitting at the i'm sitting there going oh if i don't do this completely fucking
all in it's not gonna be good so i had to had to go all in for it please don't shout we'll do better
imagine like kim hearing this i just imagine kim right now is like in the other room and she
hears how could you do this to me do you know how much i sacrificed we're like holy shit what the
fuck is going on in there like knock knock knock is everything all right she's probably used to
use doing that by now hey veto let's do this quick and thorough i agree let's do this quick and
thorough no she's you like she's used to hearing she's used to hearing me scream in a room where
i'm streaming not but you what's that instant kill again instant kill again instant kill
i like this dude i'm gonna level this guy up
melee is good too i actually i'm pretty smooth with this guy i like the movement the move i'm
me and this dude click we do i click with this dude more than i do the main character
aren't i so different i know a lot of people like really think the main character of the show is
cool but like i like the side character i like really click with this one not the main character
i'm not like the normal person i'm i like this character because it's a different character
shut up you're so nosy what spam spam spam no don't die i want to spam this come on do it
yeah you're so noisy oh hey that guy's a nosy all right come on data cap data capsule come on
i'm not like most streamers oh machine gun heavy weapons kind of guy
i'll get a wendy's baconator right now what stop doing this
stop i don't i don't want you to tell me to make me to go do that oh i a new character
anybody on somebody 100 no 150 eat a nasty burger on camera oh this is my room a nasty burger
oh see it has um most melee right do a wendy's review um it's good i've had it probably two to
three thousand times it's good i like it well anyway i need to pretend like i've never had a
wendy's hamburger before on camera take out those sentries what's that wait like a vacuum cleaner
what's that thing oh no it's behind oh this guy didn't have a dash in the air
that uh you stink i hate your stock market if you don't win or lose you don't gain anything in the
stock market that's joke stock market you just you just get to watch me fail or rise there's no
you don't have to pay anything sorry i had to keep over killing that one all right here we go
ready uh give me some big guys big guys and really thought that was a disaster
oh i still got two people whoops give me this time it's all right we're good oh yeah we're good
going for some uh melee never tell you guys that i thought the word was actually melee
until um probably like 2008 2007 i need 30 more gf energy and i can put another person in the party
operate with kitsune to protect the construction zone help just calm down don't panic
like why is chat in slow bro mode uh i bet you pronounce that yeah i pronounce it massamune
i do that's the massamune it's my helmet that's not yeah massamune i don't say don't say massamune
you're making me hungry for a trigger now i'm gonna want to have you're making me hungry for
like old rpg's all right just throw the head pick it up pick it up pick it up pick it up
because the new spawn they can't even spawn we killed them so fast we're just losers you're
sucking me in when you do that beautiful if you ask me you bet i didn't have this guy for the hard
mission it would have been so much better i might have still lost but it would have been closer
go to wendy's and order some massamune introducing the massamune hamburger what the
what the hell would even be on that blood all right would you guys eat a hamburger from wendy's if it
was it was blood on it but that was a part of it it was the it was the blood burger it was the
wendy's double blood burger all right what are you chicken the whole tagline was like don't be
don't be a wuss whose blood i don't know somebody's so human blood
no you know come to think of it i wouldn't eat a hamburger that a human blood on it either i
would be like no you can your commercial can call me i'm not gonna eat a human blood hamburger
all right it was just a normal hamburger but there was like a teaspoon of human blood on the burger
you're what a wuss all right this one is a look at this this thing i got i that's a secret one
i'm gonna get it cool i gotta level up first no i don't like those robots thank holy shit they're
they're a praying mantis enemy that means i can have one oh i waited for the perfect opportunity
and it was perfect didn't hit it now he's in the ground what how did i not get you the bugs kind
of suck away with the blood burger remember the blood burger sounds like a fake wrestling move
you'd say when ronald mcdonald kills somebody in the 2020 rumble well you're automatically assuming
that ronald mcdonald is gonna be in the next rumble i'm not sure that's the case here's the
real battle right here this dude what do these things do what is your god all right don't don't
get cocky nice come on three for three yes three for three come on four for four god damn it the
wendy's four for five dollar four for four dollars that's my as my five for five dollar fill-up box
what is that kfc which one is that it's my five or four pieces from wendy's fill-up box which
what what is it which one is it i want it right now what do i get it who has it you're crossing
over he's being brainwashed this dude's fucking wacko you've been get out of my space man
have you guys noticed this character is so good i don't i haven't we haven't seen another
character in like 30 minutes i feel like i got a fucking rare drop every fast food place has an
xx deal didn't taco bell just give away free tacos all day didn't that just happen
no they did i've been doing that for four weeks straight let's go back to manna dude you're a
taco with no meat shut up is that is that implying that i'm i'm all what i'm all
fluff or something i'm all lettuce i got they don't meet here i'm all lettuce and tomato
so i'm just the gross shit that's on it all right this guy i love this character so much
it's so good you're all tortilla this is gonna kind of be completely out of nowhere but do you
guys remember a lot of you are probably too young to remember the commercial for i think
it was what a and w root beer i'm not sure why this spots my head but the guys at a job interview
and the dude the dude's name at interviewing him his name is mr dumbass the whole time he's
just like hey so dumbass let me ask you a question dumbass so mr dumbass am i your man mr dumbass
and he leans at the end of the commercial after saying nothing and goes
the name is dumas and it goes like oh that's pretty thick yet it's just like a frothy a and w
root beer i'm about laughing my ass off with that commercial he keeps calling him dumbass
that's the whole commercial he's like oh so dumbass i think i'm i'm the one for this job
dumbass name use your mom that's pretty thick headed yes yeah let's watch it you got it this
is it right hey hold on oh thank god links are back yeah this is it a and w root beer dumbass
i can't wait it's been so long don't watch it don't watch it watch it with me okay let me sure
i can't wait
hold on wait here we go i can bring a lot to dumbass and dumbass go get her dumbass material
all the way so am i your man mr dumbass the name is dumas that's pretty thick headed
but nothing compared to the rich thick frosty mug taste of an a and w root beer so mr dumbass
i can bring a lot to dumbass and dumbass
dumbass and dumbass it's perfect i would hire this dumbass material all the way
so am i your man mr dumbass the name is dumas that's pretty thick headed but nothing compared
to the rich thick frosty mug taste of an a and w root beer with a and w it's good to be thick headed
what a dumbass i forgot about the end
uh that's a classic absolutely classic mr jeff that react andy what i played one commercial twice
oh wait i gotta get mine i played a tv commercial this got so loud for something
uh if i was developing this game i would nerf this book did you see how you see that
it's unbelievable make seven up yours oh yeah we got this new slogan make seven up your
hey that's right man make seven up yours up your hey what the fuck oh the guy didn't say
what the fuck you can't say it on tv get through get through that shield i'm back
because he played the wendy's ost yet you just missed it we just got to the part where they were
going that wasn't funny that wasn't funny that wasn't funny that wasn't funny that wasn't funny
that wasn't funny that wasn't funny that wasn't funny that wasn't funny that wasn't funny that
wasn't funny that wasn't funny that wasn't funny am i your man mr dumbass that wasn't funny that
wasn't funny delete me delete me somebody delete me but it was funny yeah i know i'm just putting
up a veil of like i didn't think that was funny so like therefore oh he's making like a funny
like joke about he wasn't funny so like i think i'll give him a pass thanks for the heels person
that's just kind of been in my team double here you need to relax relax psycho what stalks and
negative well hold on to be fair there was a point in the stream where everyone was just doing it
to make sure that it was going to be down they like they were doing it on purpose like five
straight minutes germa is oil stock germa is oil stock germa is oil stock omega low
wow robot check it out it's high like high attack quaternary missile iron claw iron spin
a robot type got you board who was created to defend cities protect citizens from invaders
with his hard metal claws and quaternary missile attacks where do you buy germa stocks you don't
you only sell them god i don't think i've ever seen anybody buy let's try claw born with germa
stocks all right i gotta get the team together how many outstanding how many germa stocks exist
in the world five thousand that's just the number of people that are here that's the first number i
thought up because i saw that's the first number i looked at holy shit he shoots missiles oh that's
cool all right let's get in by getting close that's a good escape how did what's his movement like
anyway it's not bad what the hell is with that camera angle i'm assuming his melee damage is
better than anything else yes it is it's low though can drop below 400 what well that's just
manipulation though it's not real follow the fucking germa exchange commission on you guys
by the way it's me they're all going to jail jex germa exchange commission missiles are all right
they're kind of boring though i mean i guess if you can spam them like this it works out pretty well
brush teeth quick the joke tracker wait are you guys let me see this shit what's going on here
you guys causing a problem oh you guys know that it was a point when i was thinking about having
an extension made for this channel keep the plus two and minus two out of the chat let's talk about
this holy shit i just get destroyed and have it be something you could do but you couldn't just
like spam it i mean it was like it would be like actually like it would be like an indicator
and every once in a while we would just check on and see how it was but the reason why i didn't
do it and this is the reason why i probably won't do it it's because um i don't we make
jokes about like oh minus two and plus two that's like just i don't know if i want to have a like how
bad is your stream today how not funny were you today oh no today was good but this one oh this
is a real time indicator this stream is i don't think this this stream sucks i don't think i want
that information i don't think i would want that because then it would just get in my head
and every day would just be like let me check that joke indicator and see
well what do we have plus no no i can do better than that i can do better than that and then i
have to start trying to like make jokes as hard as i can and then that's going to make it worse
we just got a spinner girl okay yeah i gotta play with hatchet night best game on the game cube
very expensive though let's see we got we got three jumps you see that's better than we have
all d's hatchet hatchet boomerang and rolling hatchet i was on a game show playing this and
won what this got your borg is warrior in the night for corpse he can hurl his large hatchet
at enemies wait are you serious who was that that's the one guy i mean yeah that's a pretty
important one guy i think video and arcade hold on this is real this is like a real thing
wait who was that i who was that person can we can we i didn't we went by it fast
that's fucking awesome i just want to remember who that was it was a trick that's so awesome
what are we talking about somebody in chat played this in a game show and won that's fucking
incredible that's i i don't think that's a debate that's a really weird debate in my opinion
here's a spinner girl super beam yo-yo and super beam yo-yo bro is the biggest one guy ever an
outlaw from the planet megaborg she is also known as the red-haired demon those who cross her will
regret it let's have it okay when i take out these two big guys i'm gonna do act guy and
uh yeah uh you're expensive let's see if you're worth it i won a raffle once and got cool socks
nice all right hold on i gotta go over here all right so i let me try the night the big trouble
night guy i was in a raffle and i won a playstation 2 that's pretty good too
i was in a raffle one time and won the logical journey of the zoom beanies real story
it was my little league raffle i believe all right i gotta get close to this dude
the nice thing you went the right way and throw the act oh you have to charge it to throw it
how far does it go that's pretty far actually but it stays out his speed is so bad though
melee is good in this game but not really i'll be honest you gotta get in close people can move
around so far i think this guy's too expensive for how kind of shitty he is i mean it's it stays
out okay that's good that's the one decent thing is it actually keeps spinning around
really ask our gotcha force expert if they're any good i'm sure they probably were unbeatable
at one point good for big groups it's a long time to charge yeah it's all right can we turn
the right way please all right let's see what's see speed uh speed drill oh that's super short
range huh she didn't have any range wow wait hold on a minute um i mean i'm not feeling it
i mean can i hold it out there what about like a good combo i mean it's actually it's not that
bad you can just fly around and just get this out that's pretty good damage i haven't really been
able to do much else wait did that just do a lot still thinking about kfc yes i am of course i am
i'm thinking about how they keep changing the colonel like voice every three fucking months
did i do that and let's activate the bat system i don't even know what the fuck is going on
but i missed i actually am i'm gonna lose all right stop playing around quit fooling around
that's a new enemy you got a lot of health all right get rid of the
make that guy the last thing oh it's two of them get rid of this dude oh by the way he's he's
got an extra shot in his um blaster cannon thing now that's cool i can't stay range on this
oh it's grounded there it is oh you ain't getting away from this shit now you're dead
oh did i die oh you can charge instantly in the super mode really that's cool didn't even
realize that data crystal give me something else yes i've ever played custom robo i own it it is on
the shelf behind me you will play it eventually it's one of those turrets all right we're almost
cleared with this all right you you gotta go you're down in the you're down in junk tier
okay here we go um some are in a i think yeah d i gotta i can do this by tier okay s tier s
tier s tier who's s here up here okay what would it put you i'll put you in a i'll put you in b
okay this is uh i i think you're down here okay that this is pretty i think this is yeah that's
correct so now that i know where people stand what do i want to use 25 and what's this one
i like these guys i don't think it's terrible and people are like don't fucking play with this guy
he sucks but i know bomb guy let's hold on to bomb guy because i want bomb guy to be
in case it goes wrong what do i have 220 250 all these guys are too expensive i could do a um
aim it okay we can do yeah all right let's play right here i like it the music's driving me crazy
yeah it is fucking annoying isn't it yeah and i know i know i can turn it down
i want to turn it down training yeah it's good but there's a lot of it thankfully it
only happens sometimes all right who is a teammate
so
i love how positive vanna is the mirror it's a mirror excuse me bye bye oh you're different
you could fly i don't i can't tell if these are ever hitting i feel like i should be doing
them when they're closer or something i don't know i'm just making stuff up so you think i know what
i'm doing the ost is good it's it's good it's catchy i don't even know who that character was
that just did wow this is like the ultimate trade this is my starter shit character can't even get
by it it's kind of embarrassing i know we're all kids here but like come on throw up oh they
activated wait a minute everybody in the chat putting in all capitals just relax is referencing
the people talking in the game oh i was i thought people thought i was going crazy
like dude fucking relax i've addressed it like three or four times i thought people thought i
was like who like wound up for something like dude just relax and i stopped like pressing buttons
as fast oh he's dead it's all right we got fucking sniper girl wait what's why is your sniper girl
different than my sniper girl holy shit that's why the premium skin
actually here's another premium skin what the fuck let's just spam rockets point blank rocket
get the fuck out of here hey we did it well when next time you got beaten too many times
oh come on something cool a premium skin premium skin no that's just a regular ninja that's sad
ah another chance damn it i feel that's disappointing two commons well i guess the
good news is i could have two uh sniper girls no i can't not yet it's 250 yes i can all right
yeah look at that that's a screenshot right there 1180 perfect do i like cheese who doesn't like
cheese that was a VPN VPN uh crap so i i know i do i can't lie you know the fucking people i know
i look i said that's the way it is let's go you guys hear me wait did you guys hear what i said
anybody hear what i said oh okay let's talk about it now uh that was my fault and i know people are
gonna i know you're gonna give me shit for this i know you are okay i know just listen um that
was that was my VPN VPN crashed i okay i oh i can't believe you're gonna beat me i want to say stupid
i know i look i know i know that was it was the VPN okay cool wait it's okay everyone can we can
just rejoice that nothing's wrong it was hey it was the VPN and whatever and why is he on a VPN
because i am and fucking deal with it no i whatever all right so close this
let's get back to it that was uh that's cool oh it's about cheese right okay rant about cheese
my voice is fucked up hello hello hello what is it good now are we good hello oh okay we're good
all right how does he sound like this is just it's a twitch bug i think the viewers are a twitch
bug too i don't know maybe it was a twitch thing was it i'm so confused i looked at my VPN had a
problem all right let's just play we're good wasn't twitch having problems earlier today too
am i just trying to deflect away from uh the VPN crashing oh whatever let's go what about the mac
and cheese no it wasn't mac and cheese it had nothing to do with mac and cheese no i said i
liked you i said everybody loves cheese but the problem with cheese is cheese cheese is not like
the best thing for you and if you eat too much cheese it can like kind of weigh you down and if
you have lactose issues everybody loves cheese that you just got to try to limit how much of it
you can a lot of people can't really have it and hate cheese um cheese i mean you that's all right
some people just don't like milk that's okay if you don't like milk you don't like dairy
you don't think you think milk is gross like whatever that's that's for you that's on you
i would say a majority of people like the taste of cheese but you don't have to like it like a
requirement bam no one can stop me this music doesn't give me a panic attack i can turn the
music down this game is actually like a great game from 2003 you can do you can just like settings
all right i got another sniper girl you didn't think i had two what are you dumb
eh oh who is killing me all right who's left you this game hurts my eyes and ears
i'm sorry turn up oh i just wanted to i love the little spam things it's i love it i love the
little blue tick tick tick tick tick tick i just want a game that does that i want a game that
does like tick tick tick tick tick tick quake no quake doesn't go like like that i mean kind
of does doom no no no no no no not i'm talking projectiles projectiles that don't do a lot of
damage but like you need to be placed and can be spammed and you have to like don't make them
anymore our force is half one how do you half win something have oh right right right oh i think
can i make this i've almost cleared the whole thing hold on okay i've got new drill robot victory
machine army robot gatling gunner drill robot how do i uh a 134b a n 134b drill robot what's this
what's what's this different oh alternate color ah what really well this one's a super secret so
we have to be prepared for this one i want my i want people leveled up don't worry because
okay i'm gonna replace one speed girl with my main hero after this how do you not get killed by a
point blank missile i gotta do more melee melee into range that's so much better
okay people just got booted all right you look scary shit trying to dodge it shit this two of them
oh
all right
i know what you somebody said do it and do an impression of the grape stomping lady
are you talking are you talking about oh oh oh why do you want me to i
you want me to do that do an impression of the grave stomping lady do the do it louder
i can't do it i've waited years for this why that's the best i can do i don't understand i
don't know that's just it came out of it just came out of nowhere it came out of fucking nowhere
do it i can't do it louder what do you mean do it louder that's just that's me doing it i wonder
if this guy's any good whoa what is that what's that what's that thing that's an a i almost just
discarded it three i gotta get three of these to form the samurai shogun am i rotating it or is
there just a jpeg in there come on what is this damn it okay all right this is important
this is new did i try it on this level i can i who can i hope it's gonna have i have okay 400
it's 300 who's down here anyone have 400 you but you suck he does he sucks show the great video
yeah who hasn't seen this video my favorite part about this video
is i'm gonna do an impression here with the cam on obviously right so my favorite part about
this video is the part where the lady goes like this so she goes i guess that was the last image
that was captured i don't know what the fuck that was it was from like six hours ago uh hold on she
goes i don't know what's going on i don't know if the video fucks up or something but she goes
like this she she's hold on see me okay you'll be able to see me so there's a point there's a
point in the video the lady goes like this she's stomping stomping stomping and then she goes like
this she goes like it's weird it's like boom boom boom boom boom you'll see she's like point
point point point she gets like stuck you didn't even plug me in the fuck has nobody seen this
no everyone's seen this but how is it i guess maybe you weren't like alive mr dumbass i can
bring a lot to dumbass and dumbass i'm a go-getter dumbass material these buckets are filled with
grapes what kind of grapes these are filled with chambers and grapes and the winner this saturday
you stop music eating international food having wine tours and tastings seminars
she took a hard fall off there oh no i think she's actually her anchors are fucking ridiculous
why is it still playing in the background oh you know i think i think she might actually be hurt
uh and again i don't have anything being captured and there's just about the subject
it's just stuff playing in the background i don't know where this comes from like i got it i found
it but yeah it's like anchors it's just like yeah of course of course she probably is hurt
she just felt like she just felt like seven feet onto her chest oh you are ouch i think maybe she
might have gotten hurt there oh um yow cheese pop rope there you go there's your oh oh oh
i'm trying to move on yeah and that's and that's like the one the one sad thing about like the
the nature of like the internet and internet culture is if you if you if you turn into a
meme somehow it's just that's just there and it's just always going to be referenced it's unfortunate
like you no uh maybe i don't know i oh guys i slapped myself in the fucking face
on accident and that's the first thing all of you spam when you're allowed to post links again i
think i have some idea maybe what what could potentially that that could be i mean you did
so like 20 years from now somebody's gonna link me the slap have you seen that have you seen this
video this guy slapping himself and he goes some stream is gonna do an impression of it
some stream is gonna be like look at me slap
everyone's gonna go holy shit that was pretty good impression of that guy that's
fucking ancient now i like this team this is just the hard hitters go you're already ancient i know
this what's up here it was the funniest thing all right this was this one's protect the park
at any cost hopefully i can do this good can you just be honest and say please help me
beat the enemy you want to fight you want to fuck but don't fucking come at me
yeah somebody will do an impression of that like 15 years
all right how's it how you play with this guy probably should have figured that out before
i started um well you're you're incredible wow okay what's the x do the big spin
what about the melee the melee is good too all right don't get cocky this is yum yum yum
bullshit yum yum yum yum yum what is yum yum yum one bad thing about this character is
you kind of are vulnerable when you attack kind of i grew up you know what i mean you kind of go
like oh hey fred i mean you end up going forward and you go like oh hey fred that's tough epic
burger skills did i do it no not now no no stop i come on i what i said hey fred and all of a
sudden no i i i like strangled you yeah let's get serious instant death bye goodbye who's left
goodbye this guy's so good he's just he's just unbeatable this is the end of the stream boys
okay guys uh all right i'll see it no not yet not yet oh we should talk about what we're gonna
we should talk about what was that holy just relax uh we should talk about what we're gonna do this
week besides this of course i'm i'm playing i you think i'm not gonna get my 250 dollars worth i'm
i love this game i'm gonna play this tomorrow kill kill how do you even kill just play it every day
this week i'm gonna play until i'm done playing because i've done and it had fun
solid get dad so that was a secret mission so we should get something worth talking about
not worth talking about all right what's this yeah i want to see this yum yum yum what is this
from this is from uh this is from uh oh i know what this is i i'm not gonna watch it i refuse to
watch this this is this is a this is fake you're just making me try to you may try to make me look
bad to new people oh he actually joins the party all right nice i still want to use you i think he's
good 110 now this guy put this guy down at fucking d minus tier do yum yum or ride it speed sonic
slash blood slash and blood dance i got you poor who obtained a light draining sword in exchange
for incredibly destructive power must slash others in order to stay alive his blood dance move will
suck an enemy's body dry in seconds and it's just so yummy yum yum yum yum it's just so
yum this context there though you have to understand the context you can't just watch
that and go this guy sucks and his jokes are bad well i guess you could i mean yeah you could do
that if you wanted to i mean i'm talking about this particular instance uh we'll go the new guy
stop being funny we're almost at a minus two plus two equilibrium
oh we both start with yeah we both have these guys that's good oh you they are very long range
it seems oh it seems bad choice bad choice bad choice bad choice bad choice of character
bad choice bad somebody has a cannon over there all right whatever bad choice it's okay
because it's over fucking made me angry and now we got hammer throw bot what's that kill it
he's playing was it a bard what is it i almost got a thingy it's over what is this match
all right back up back up back up back up you're in the way and you're making me angry stay up here
why why go anywhere oh it's time yes got a lot of people on this team play kingdom rush origins now
over 1500 i for a second i thought you said 1500 dollars and i was about i was about to be like
you're gonna pay me 1500 bucks to play you said 1500 downloads i was like i was gonna tell you i
wouldn't do it for 1500 all i'm serious i would not play that game for 1500 all yeah i don't
think okay i don't think i would do it for 15 000 like i'm so lazy right now i would
that i have to like go get my ipad and shit no wow i have to go get my ipad
for fifteen thousand dollars can you imagine being that much of a fucking messed up for
oh how do i fight i not fight unleash you probably shit out 15k oh my god
jesus christ no i don't shit out 15 000 dollars turn that poop into gold all right i'm gonna lose
if i'm not careful i gotta pay attention but i do it for 5000 i don't i don't want to play that game
i don't i this is a weird i know i don't think i would i don't think i'd want to
if i lose here i'm over by the way so come on
oh you motherfucker you're almost dead back up one more don't blow it here don't blow don't blow
don't blow don't blow it we're good um but i don't even know what the game was it was kingdom um
kingdom came rush kingdom come rush kingdoms of alamore what kingdom come rush what is it called
um amalor not alamore kingdoms of amalor kings of al of alamore all right what's that thing
amalor is based as fuck you know actually i wanted to play that what i just get a capsule what was
it it was a data crystal killer girl watch out demon samurai uh i'd rather have support i'm honest
this game looks cool it is it's very cool uh they they do a lot of damage don't they this
guy's hiding back here i uh melee versus melee let's go oh my god this guy's getting stomped
don't you feel like if your swords were that big it would be a huge problem
it would just scrape all over the ground and shit what is going on with these swords why are
they doing this this is this supposed to be happening oh shit all right watch out for the
bombs here okay watch out for that bomb it's following me fuck damn it i missed oh fuck oh
all right get in there fuck out of here i want one of those guys because those weapons are crazy
do i get one no i think i might have enough to put uh 130 in it
i kind of like this guy though put it in the 20th slot hear him up somebody said they got
chibi robo and they were so happy about it yes when do you unlock mew too soon what do you
guys think would happen to the channel if i decided that i was gonna start from the very beginning
as of like as let's just say let's just say as of tomorrow this is a hypothetical not real
scenario just make that clear um if i decided i was gonna start at pokemon red and play every
single pokemon game back to back to back until i got to the new one what would happen that's the
all that literally is the only thing i did on stream until it was over and it took me like three
months to do it please do that no i would never do it it's a fun thought project but what if i
did a stream where i just planted grass and i just streamed the soil every day for like eight hours
until there was grass there and then i and then the end of that stream the end of that whole arc
of like a month is i just a lawnmower comes from off the screen and just runs it all over
and then the stream ends oh what am i doing i'm getting three kills in five seconds what are you
doing is it woody from toy story it is what is this guy this is like a premium woody skin
that move is so good it's unbelievable give me woody give me woody oh that's okay though
that's kind of cool wire gunner speed support not it's not a really bad attack really bad
everything actually would assault punch wire shoot set wire wire gunner is an army member
and specialist in trapping enemies in uh that web well have to try everything at least once
that's kind of the rule right sell i think you can discard you can't sell use the me gunner
it is a me gunner yeah versus what nothing nothing on the screen
i like the way that this character looks what is this got plenty of ammo wait a minute you did
what is this am i supposed to be grabbing them oh that's kind of good they touch it they get hurt
it's kind of like it's just a shotgun blast is that what that's doing it's shooting five
ow you guys i think that's not doing great why would you use that when you just do this
why why it's a harpoon oh oh i get it i get it oh okay that's a lot cooler now like so how many
that he's taking a lot of punishment i can't i need like a melee would be great here actually
you can bounce them around wherever you want this is a gimmick character
yeah not yet are we minus two see i'm telling you you guys are just manipulating everything
what happens if i do four and then now i missed whenever you talk it's minus two holy god
that's the kind of comment that makes me want to just take a break and then like throw water in
my face and like smush it around a little bit be like jeremy it's all right get back out there
from what you're made of hey you're doing great buddy thanks carriage is kind of cool but not
really not really more kind of advanced gameplay uh i haven't even eaten it yet here that's how
bad i don't that's how yeah we gotta we gotta move some people down here this is too gimmicky
okay i have enough to perfect look at this perfect let's let's start with you put you
at the end and then for you because keep the big guys for later i made brownies would you like
some i love brownies but brownies are a thing that i never ever ever have because i only eat
them if somebody else makes them i love them though they're so good okay do you guys like
crusty brownies or chewy brownies very important i'll tell you my answer after whoa this is this
is these guys look hard what these guys are are like rares they this is like a that's like a
megazord right there oh my god sorry i got one i got one i got one i got one i just healed all
that health oh so much damage please yeah give me that help god damn it why i have to fight
somebody at the same time get away from me he's right fucking behind me he's right behind me
come on got it all right focus on the little ones first because i got two big guys after this
i like this little ninja i should put more of these guys in look at my whole face is itchy get it oh
he's slow he's really slow give me somebody to got it and kill the bad guy
all right he's dead i got him can i get one of these guys these guys looked crazy uh chewy
brownies by the way you're curious the chewier the better i like my brownies to be like i could
mistake them for gum they're that chewy to a point where they they bunch up and it's like
and you think if you bite if you pull your teeth up too hard you're gonna rip all your molars up
that's how chewy i want them and you just you put a little bit of milk in your mouth so it makes it
a little softer but still you gotta like i want my jaw to hurt from how hard i have to work to chew
through these fucking things a good strategy here and then go in with a twirl get up there
yet i need characters that can fly you know i'm saying like i mean really fly like that kind of
fly i want to be able to truly fly kill it uh thermos salmonella king oh i also love cookie
dough too cookie dough is seriously like my absolute favorite thing on earth i remember
i used to my mother used to make cookies and i didn't really even know how bad this was
for you until i got a little bit older she would be making cookies and i would just go over there
and just the beater would be there and i would just go in there with like a spoon and eat like
three or four mounds worth of the cookie dough that was in the thing that she was making
and i years later i found out that you know that's it's not good as bad for you it's actually not
great but whatever i'm still alive i guess what is this thing on me raw egg is good as long as
it's not been out for a whole day i'm still alive with this guy and i mean still still gotta be
careful all right another flying insect everything will kill you in the end i know i'm just spamming
i know but i mean at some point you gotta just go for it you give me melee and i'll i'll i'll
destroy them all right get in close get in here yes ah why does everybody have wings in this level
it's not fair everybody has wings except for you you should have put wings on this why i how am i
supposed to just fly this character doesn't have wings just get surgery yeah let me bring this
guy into the toy surgery shop put him down and just staple wings on him i don't know what you
want me to do that all right i want ninja guy first what about the scene in in toy story where
these guys flying all right the ninja is good to have first oh also i want to bring this up too
we got we're full of we're full of announcements tonight with we where there's so many i'm full of
announcements yeah this is perfect these flying fucking insects so we're gonna be adding uh some
new mods and you it's gonna be a secret of who they are you'll find out soon enough it will be
at least probably probably shooting for like at least five or six new mods i'm gonna shake it up
a little bit here even the new mods don't know some of them do still want to obviously throw it
out there to some other people said finally yeah it's been a while mods are redditors i don't know
why i i keep i keep addressing like the redditor messages better just dodge just dodge just dodge
i mean like just dodge fucking butterflies ah i need anti-air so bad it's killing me
okay finally can i have no uh i don't think i even have anything that's anti-air wire gunner
uh yeah i could couldn't i do the same shit happens in the hulk and it's just i got flashbacks of
that game all right just kill me just kill me just kill me kill me kill me kill me kill me kill me
kill me kill me kill me kill me so i can just do something else i want to play as a different
character just kill me i want to play as a different character this character is not good
for dealing with any of you can only jump three times and then they're gone all right die okay no
more air oh god damn it just please thank you if it's even worse maybe not even worse it's a huge
arc uh 20 community subs just came in from goiki goiki thanks for the 20 fucking subs freddy gave
50 earlier goiki now frozen 20 thank you that's big money big money i'm just activating this i'm
going to spam this thanks a lot goiki seriously and congratulations to all the new computer
it's super mario noise person's buying mod you can't buy mod that no that doesn't that's not
that doesn't make any no there's no buying mods you can't purchase a mod spot it's based on
five factors activity ingenuity engineering skills comedic and how well you can cook
uh am i describing mods or am i describing like the perfect man
i'm not so sure this level sucks i'm so i don't want to do it kill this by the way i got all those
things in case you're wondering what it looked like play trapeze sim i'm gonna i'm gonna look
this up because i've no idea what the fuck this person keeps saying this for trapeze simulator
what is this this is not even a real thing realistic simulation trapeze rail system
like this person has written this in the chat like five 75 times trapeze simulator
i don't this doesn't even oh shit i just got a ring valkyrie i think i fly uh anyways goiki gave
50 back to back back to back all right we got our ear uh goiki thanks for the 50 bucks
and they say equilibrium has been reached stop saying i'm buying mod i'm buying equilibrium
because it was reached total eight wait total eight what does this mean i guess this is i mean
this this is true i guess it's it's the it's that's four and four i don't know what does this mean
oh wow it happened
and
i'm not gonna play trapeze simulator give it a rest this is a c holy shit that speed
magic shot stick of time gold and quick spell and then fly if you're stuck against agile enemies
try calling for the quick valkyrie all right and then we have this one too d also speed
ring shot or blade ring crash and fly angel board with white wings who is shaped like an angel
really couldn't see never losing her cool she attacks with light rings which rip everything
apart she likes to stay clean and will destroy those who dirty her all right let's put them in
they can be the scouts 230 and two and perfect let's go okay okay keep it clean chat all right
but goiki thanks for the 20 subs and the 50 dollars thanks a lot a lot of fucking money uh
anybody else have flying things i want to be clean all right let's check this out
okay can i just can i flap my wings forever whoa you you shoot the whole clip in one shot
wait what's the charge do oh oh that's the debuff thing actually pretty cool you gotta get up high
get this shit off me all right grab him come on hit you're throwing for views i can't get this
fucking plate off of me this thing get it off me bad character i need to get this thing off me
what's a melee like oh not bad actually ending he's a liar he's a liar he's a liar he's a liar
he's a liar he's a liar he's a liar he's a liar he's a liar he's dead all right let's try this one
whoa the charge dude ah look at that wait that's cool kind of kind of impractical though
all right let's go air fight i just that was awesome dude where this character is cool but
hard to use got a weird pattern very trajectory my brownies are done they turned out extra gooey
nice combo brownies now that's not so good gooey and chewy and stuck on your teeth
like when i eat a brownie i want when you talk to me i want you to be disgusted because i have these
gross witch teeth like it's stuff it's like brownies are to me need they're like the popcorn
of the sweet world i want them just to get stuck in every crevice ice valkyrie like if i would have
bite down eating the kind of brownie that i like and hold my teeth together like if i took one
little chunk and like and on one side in one chunk and it would it would form it would form a like
it would be like glue and after about 30 minutes it would form a fucking epoxy and i just uh oh
you wouldn't be able to pull your mouth up you'd have to go get like surgery that's what i want
that's too far is it what is it too far magic shot stick of ice oh that's where the ice shit
is coming from an angel borg with cold eyes who flies using wings of ice she hates to sweat and
tries to fill the hot battlefield with ice pillars uh guard witch huge defense this is the shield
person right what's that what's that what's that strawberry character's name strawberry sharon
what's her name rubbish strawberry shortcake all right yeah i was close barrier spell i'll try it
uh you're not so good going down dumped here you're good hard to use but still good
let's try the uh guard which can't well we could do guard which and take off you and then you're
who's uh who's somebody here is 290 who is it dirty oh i could try i'll try you too
okay that's fine don't take the support borgs they're not worth it i'm just giving them giving
it a try mr bean did the stuck teeth joke already well i mean i'm not gonna do this
joke i wasn't planning on it i would need dps because i want to support dps uh you
okay let's shield our allies um how do i think i have to stand near them hey whoa whoa whoa whoa
oh no it blocks them from attacking oh shit this is hard this is horrendous to have this happen to
you although holy shit she just gets beat up nice high defense all right let's do the uh ice girl
on charge that's a cool move but it takes a long time looks to be instant i gotta get up i gotta
get high all right from above all the way up skybox freeze freeze freeze frozen you're the only
person here just die but i can't freeze you it's kind of dumb you kind of have to do like a bombing
run like that okay i see stop throwing i'm getting one of my characters has not even died if you hit
him with all of them they actually get stuck that's cool does that actually work dodge bye-bye chat
it's sleepy time well maybe we'll see tomorrow i thought that we'll see you on the next stream
after that which is be the day after tomorrow if you don't show up for that one maybe we'll see you
on the next one after that one the day after that and then and then that's it and then that's it
time for spam this character is for the super move where you just get the infinite cooldowns
you just make a chain of death or new was there a valkyrie for every element
happy so all right i'm gonna do some re all right we're gonna the boss i'm gonna do some
research on trap piece simulator and tomorrow um yeah i'll do it i'll do it for like five minutes
all right we gotta have this team sucks absolute asshole uh we've got to rethink everything
rethink everything um what do you do valkyrie stick up tornado sure the tornado valkyrie
likes flashy things and wears colorful costumes it tends to be mischievous and beats her enemies
by generating typhoons all right we need to actually a solid team here all right bogus head
who do i know i want on this team battle girl wait which one has higher level okay battle girl
um vampire knight and either ninja or uh no two revolver gunman i like the revolver gunman
all right last resort is gonna be that speed girl there we go it's good to me am i winning
um yeah i guess you can play silent hill too uh that probably not oh wait these are all
important encounters beat the death commander orochi gravity trap battle the cosmic dragon
and the pit battle with show let's do this one pop stuff fuck i got it i got this
i got it i got it i got it i got it i got this i got this i'm going for it that's a dream team
right there if i've ever seen one missile right off the bat immediately ow ow ow ow ow i'm not
trying to do the lady i promise shit all right sorry i'm sorry it's all right it's all right i
got i got fucking vampire holy shit that comes at you fast god damn it god that's so hard to
fucking avoid it's all right don't worry oh fuck you can't even dodge roll it back up back up back
back back back up back up back up holy shit all right come on come on bogus he'll never win
he'll never win against my fucking rare bogus no way he'll never win against fucking rare bogus
fuck oh my god i gotta throw that fucking head at him right no i did it i didn't do it i didn't do
it yes yeah i didn't do it i'm not gonna get the fucking i'm not gonna get the rare no but these
These guys are terrible these guys have like shitty enemies. I got this. I just need my helmet
Monteen bogus just an airplane guy
It's another one of these fucking things
Those things are so hard. He's got like
He's got the best
This is guys are too good. Those skies him. Look I had it's all right. Whatever. Damn it. All right, let's go
Give me the death wars unit
When I get a friend not fair
Did I remove all the good bots from my team? No, I I like these guys
actually losing to a kid
What's wrong with speed girl good? I wish you could use some more HP, but I mean she's solid she's good early game
Yeah, she's good. She's fine. But we don't have to get all those super rare unlockable like hog champ robots
Our rare bogus is good enough. I want one of these shield dudes and even get a chance to spawn
I feel kind of bad for you right in the back. You're the space marine
Could be what can I do with the first character?
Probably not he's got a dodge. You got a dodge, right? I didn't I didn't I fucked it up
And I could activate this but why I bother why is everybody something that ten years old?
I think they're supposed to be ten years old
All right, something good something worth putting in the team permanently
Permanent upgrade. All right, that's a normal night doesn't sound very exciting short range the
Broad sword cross-shape slash and then shield slash this gotcha board
His warrior in the night board corpse. He wields a broadsword and his shield repels any attack
I'll give it a try
I feel like my characters suck. I have where all the good unlock where all the good
Rng is giving me bad ones
Are the tornado? Oh, I will after this. I'm gonna try the shield guy
After this we're gonna do the losses
Let's go support
All right, so they can't hurt me from the front only. All right. Well, I don't have any moves
But you you can Captain America
I'm not gonna lie. I don't hate this character. I mean obviously versus enemies that are not on the ground
You can get a good slash on here and then you block everything from the front of you
like that
Yeah, look at this
Actually kind of good. I wish it wasn't normal night one. Of course, you like the reddit character
America's a reddit character now
May that heal heal
Yes, so what's a not reddit character? I'm sure it's not Deadpool a positive
There's that hurt anybody oh fuck it does you gotta be really close for it though
Just keep people in front of you. I'll tell you if I got a better version of this guy. I'm gonna I'm putting him in
Every superhero is reddit. That's not fair
No, but Wolverine that Wolverine's probably from reddit. Um
What about uh?
So what the hell is a superhero that what super hero my let me actually rephrase this question. What superhero am I allowed to like?
The Joker I'm allowed to like the Joker. What about um, what red and Stimpy?
Bane I can like Bane. That's at least that's good
Reddit Stimpy you guys hate this place
You guys fucking hate this place
Have I seen such powerful anger before let's check. Let's test this theory out. Okay, that's actually pretty great
You can instantly charge that I'm glad I took that person's advice two and a half hours later
What about um Hulk another battle girl got so many of these I don't know what to do with them
I'm gonna keep this team for now for now. I don't I like it
Try tornado girl and replace a shooter guy
I have 170 slot 20. No, not slot 20. No
Hulk used to be based but after endgame like after Infinity War and after like the Avengers saw yeah. Yeah
All right. Well because they made him like cool or something. I don't get but what? All right, I'm going for it stone river
feed enemy got you Borgs, uh
Let's go with the saw crew. That's the guy with the
Bowser's castle swords
Let's try this in the air up in the air up in the air up in the air up in the air
Yep, in the air up in the air up in the air. Yep in the air up in the air up in there
Let's try this
Looks cool. That's a fast charge
Whoa, that's a huge incapacitation
Holy shit. This is actually kind of good and then you go in
Well, I mean I wouldn't go in on their main hero. That was pretty dumb. That's pretty dumb. I'm out
It's kind of a support character. Well sort of working. I
Didn't get it. Go back. Go back sad face
Go back. This is Metal Sonic character. Oh
Run can't block that. Oh
Getting just
Dom don't just get these just styled on me. I was horrible. I get me in there. Let's get in close
Goodbye
loser and loser
Go back. I don't even know we'll go. Wow. Let's go back. We're
of
superpower versus superpower
Who is it winning? I think it's me
Nope, I got hit by it, too. Oh
Okay, gotta be careful here. He's got
Come on bogus. I need that head
Get it
Hit him pick it up
That I think my partner sucks. I know I'm blending my partner. What a great teammate
So why do you think you lost that match last night? Well, I think there's good my teammates suck
Not me though. I'm the best. I'm a star
They already have another special
I
What they both have these like hyper beams
All right, get rid of the get at least
Dump through start off strong bring back the vampire
Was a good counter to that shit. Uh
Angel you think so
Why do about this? Maybe this weirdo will be good here angel spam will shred health. That's true
Mmm, this isn't enough
Normal night. I got my ass kicked with normal night. I'm gonna put you down here. All right, let's try this
Magnet and it's so expensive. I'll try this
We're gonna do anything about it. If not that and I'm just not ready
My ally I don't think was very good either
This guy's pretty good support
support air
I
Walk everything I didn't block that why I
Why are you not blocking anything?
So the no blocking man, you have a shield of use it
Use the fucking thing
You block it
Better going good. All right, just stick with it. Stick stick stick stick stick stick stick stick stick
Give me that head. Give me that. Give me that head head head head head head it
Got it. I hit it. I hit it. I hit it. I hit it
And good, I gotta get I gotta bridge this he's got like a look at that night
That character is so cool
Get over here. I think this is the last guy right in the back. Do I get something?
There it is finally the huge long arms and a hundred GF energy
Nice, okay
five miles sword guy
D
yd
random slash soul ball and then demon knit poor Ryu
God report who rose from a samurai grave his bloodthirsty sword grows as it absorbs spirits
His special random slash move shows unbelievable power
This guy's fun. I can't even put him on here right now do this and then add
In Joe right say the game this is like bionicle, uh more so like I
Don't know what you would you compare this to?
But just it's the death for his base. Wait, what defeat the Dark Knight?
Beat the no, I'm already for wait. What about a dragon? There's a dragon here
Gravity trap battle the cosmic dragon. Who should I fight first?
By fight one would like cancel out the other like the dragon. Okay, I'm gonna get man. Oh
Let us vote. I feel like voting for characters is something we could do tomorrow
Because I'll have enough to actually make it make sense. This dude's cool. I like it. I is it hitting I think it's hitting I
kind of
Yeah, I am hitting him seems a little unfair. It's a downside. It's low. Here it comes
He turned into the dragon. Oh, that's a cosmic dragon over there. That's for sure. I get a burn this guy
From that shit. Give me that back. Come here. Give it that way. I throw it into the hole
Alright, don't attack. It's probably gonna shoot it back at us. It's spice over. Watch this. That's
That's so ridiculous
He's so good
It's so broken. Okay, the team look like no I didn't get anything. Was there a chance I could have gotten something?
Come on, did I really get our NG didn't get anything? Let's go Dark Knight
What?
You play something with fucking wicked nasty blood and guts
I want to see a game where you can fucking rip someone's head off and
Hold on. I want to read this
You'd play something with fucking wicked nasty blood and guts
I want to see a game where you can fucking rip someone's head off and blood sprays out and your character can start licking the
Blood and the blood splatters on the screen is wicked fucking gory and cool. That would be so cool
Let's go ally
Mmm, where's another dragon? I
Just beat you have to fight you over here, too
Getting close that reason to be far away for any reason
Plus this guy's gonna go underneath. Oh
That hurts. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay. It's okay
Alright, let's do it. Oh
You are fucking slow, aren't you?
No, that was cocky. He's dead. Don't worry. I'll win. He's slow, but he has huge damage
He's done. Yeah, I don't I'm gonna win music. It's like super monkey ball. You like that. Where'd it go?
Well, that's not it
Dragon was just a normal enemy. He had
way out. Yep long-range
Still worth it. That means it's gonna be a oh, there's the real enemy. Oh
This just got bad fuck. I need that
Hi
Who's even attacking who?
Stay back dude. Who is doing that? Where can I get one of these guys? The purple shield guys are fucking insane. I
Wonder if this guy wait, he might wait what he did it. Yeah. Hey, he doesn't go to stab him
Nice job. He just had to go up and stab in the neck. I thought the Dark Knight was a roachies partner
It is some strange data in the gotcha box. That's the data. They stole from me gotcha red band 2.0
Neo-g-red my true power has returned
Of the death force has lost their death base things should remain calm for a little while
But I know that the Galactic Emperor hasn't given up on this planet
Actually, I fear that the battle has just begun
We must continue to grow the force so that we will be ready for the Galactic Emperor when the time comes
Vito I'm counting on you
You bet. I'm counting on you, too
Animated cutscene take a look. Ooh
He's much better
Plasma blade beam gatling and G Buster with Neo G crash. Nice. Oh, you're definitely gonna let's try you up
Too much. She's worth too much now
500 oh
Shit, he's worth a lot. I can't hang him. I have enough for 70. I play with
Law
Valkyrian
Sword about yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, and I can do a ninja. Wait, I can do somebody else, too
Can somebody 170? No, I keep thinking somebody's 170. No, it's you level two ninja. I only have two images right now
We saw the team. I'm gonna try one more fight and then we're gonna pick it up tomorrow
It's don't even play this game for six hours straight. Well, it's only been like five
Right. Yeah, good the new
G forces
Booyah turn penis. All right, funny that I laughed you got me
He's way stronger. That's you looking how much faster that shoots to look at the reload. This is great
He's hey has to be in every fight. Okay, hold on
That's so much better. Look at the member. Yeah, I love this. It's great
What about the charge? It's better. So it's much better too. Yeah. Oh, it's way better. The sword is a thousand times better
She's in through under the table
Okay, that's what I'm gonna call it tonight. We're back tomorrow
But before we go, I do want to bring up some things that we'll be doing
We're gonna play job. I've got your first tomorrow and then on
Wednesday depending on how I mean I I might want to beat the game
So we're gonna play this until I've had my fill. Let's see what happens tomorrow
Though tomorrow Wednesday and Thursday is the kind of tentative plan right now
So we'll see how it happens over the next couple of days. I'm gonna do brownies
Custom robo. I don't I mean custom robo right after this
Might need a break from robots toys fighting each other
At some point I want to play I do want to play the GTA online casino update
And I came out like a year ago and I haven't done it. We'll do that this week to brownie cooking stream
Well, I mean the I think the easy bake oven has a brownie. I'm fairly certain of that
So we'll see you tomorrow. I'm gonna play gotcha force again
Unlock some more robots
It's just fun to fight with robots and unlock stuff and keep upgrading it. It's just like a never-ending toy
Having a lot of fun. It's a great game. So I'll see you tomorrow sticking around. We're gonna do the bits and subs and everything
We'll see you tomorrow how gotchas work
Yeah, it's true. Don't forget to save. I just did let's get some music on here. Oh, I just punched you. Sorry
It's good to just turn off
Very good. We'll check back with it tomorrow
So now we're gonna do the bits from earlier
It's on the right screen
Do a rewind here
We had for three dollars noodle is bad at gaming. Thanks for three bucks noodle in 2003. I was born
Derma old looking ass
Derma old looking ass, right? Some of you guys are young
Johnny nice mountains. Thanks for the five dollars. This show featured the last voice acting gig from the deceased actor Bella Lugosi
Interesting little tidbit of information. Thanks for sharing it an anonymous cheer. Thanks for $15 and bits 1500 bits just anonymous
Somebody just drop in $15
Thanks a lot. I'll take it sticks renegade. Thanks for the 250 good week so far
I managed to grab something off an online store. That was hard to get I got a pizza pepperoni with double cheddar cheese
It's good. I swear you're streaming our state is giving 300% more unemployment money per week
And I approved the proof for stickers with a stickerola my stickered Toyota Corolla
Sounds like pretty good week, and I approved the proof for stickers
the
Stickerola thanks to the 250 sticks glad to hear things are going well Vinny D. Thanks for the three dollars Vinny
Thank you, German. This is my favorite game from my childhood. We did I think we caught this no no no no no we didn't
This is just another person's favorite game
I told you you guys trust me sometimes makes me so happy to see you stream it and give it attention to deserves
Please save often there is a save data corruption glitch in the game that is prevented by saving often
I pretty much save after every fight, so I should be alright. Yeah, it's kind of a monk
I guess I would say I'll keep it up to date. Please remind me. Please remind me
Transparitas thanks for the
Five dollars what am I watching? I just want easy bake time easy bake is gonna happen a little bit later than I thought
It'll be back-to-back with the green screen night. It will be
15 recipes all of which are varying skill yes
There is a pizza if you're wondering there is a pizza
one thing that's gonna be really really important is I gotta check the expiration dates on this shit because I
can't I
if I get these packets in the mail and
They expired in June of like
I'm done. I'm not going to eat them. They're all they're all gonna be expired. I don't think so right I'll try
I'll take a bite of each one, but that gross it's gonna be it's gonna be gross
I don't think I want to look well
It'll be a game time decision a curb umble on top of the ten thousand bits and hundred dollars gives another five
This one last bit drop because I forgot to mention these you look up the vocal version of the game's theme
We are gotcha force the Japanese vocals were removed from the localization since that's just how things were in 2003 I guess
vocals
Let's see. There's not YouTube see
get this and
gotcha force
theme song
with lyrics or with singing or
Opening full version gotcha force Japanese opening this one is good, but that's not the one I meant wait what it's not the right one
This is Bella Lagasse. He's the last to ride, but he's singing the song
Keep playing it wait, so why why do they take this out is the right one?
It was gonna be a TV show and that he in a line of toys that didn't sell well, so they didn't do any of it
Use your clout to bring back gotcha force
Hey Capcom hey
German on eight five here. You might know me from
moderately successful YouTube channel and
Twitch live-streaming experiment German nine eight five
I have to bring to you today a request
There are a lot of us that care deeply about the gotcha force franchise
animated toys
figures
new games robot fighting I have made a petition and it has been signed
Over 31 times if you could please have it in your heart to check out maybe bringing it back
We would really love it. We would appreciate it me and all the germamites. Well, let me say that again
Me and all the germamites. I was a little better, please Capcom
Here are prayers and I will end that I will end this petition with a song Capcom
We're all waiting for it. You know what to do
German on eight five and the germamites out also one of the thing if you could somehow could bring back Gino
It's a great character in the Nintendo franchise
Super Mario RPG. I mean, let's be honest if we're asking for shit
It'll never happen. I might as well throw some stuff on top. Let it play us out with a song. We are gotcha force
That's right. We are 31 of us, you know what to do Capcom
We we love you
That got really loud all the sudden sing along I don't I can't
Lyrics all right. I'm gonna turn on the lyrics to learn Japanese. All right. Well, that was fun
I'm sorry that I just I just don't think you woke up my mom. Oh
I don't know the petition
That'll get us to 32
Every one of these signatures counts man. Come on. That's a cool franchise. It just was you know
It was kind of I mean, it's not even like the game was dumpy at all. I mean if the game plays very well
It's a very polished experience the games fun
I think it's just kind of released at the wrong time. I was not gonna say I was gonna say dumpy
You're right, but it's not pretty well-made, but thank you curb humble shit Wembley TTV
Thanks for the 250 this awful voice actor reminds me of Dynasty Warriors 3
I do miss the time where Japanese video gaming companies would just get anyone who would speak English and act for the lowest price
I actually think a lot of them are phonetically reading the lines from what I've understood a
Lot of the Japanese to English voice acting that you hear is phonetic
They just they don't even know what they're saying. They just are told the way to say it
So I mean that's that that's pretty incredible if you think about it
Shenmue 3 did it on purpose
Really? Thanks of the 250. Hey the Pablo. Thanks for five dollars. Happy four months from the vaude gang. Hello vaude gang
Whether you watch live or watch after the fact you still watch
Thanks for watching
Let's see if I can SMBF sleeves
sleeves
Thank You SMBF for the thousand bits ten dollars massive shout out to D who showed me this channel
They're a legend and so are you
glad you think so, thank you shout out to D and
Thanks for watching. Hi, welcome to the channel with the German lights here
I
Was gonna go off on the whole speech about
I'm so glad that you were added to the list of people signing the petition
But I you know, sometimes you have to let a joke die and that's where I'm gonna do that's where I'm gonna kill it
Thanks for the thousand bits. Welcome
Castline. Thanks for the three dollars chat hates Jerma having fun Jerma Pluto. I don't think so
I think I think originally people were like, you know games fucking stupid
And then they saw the gameplay and then I think I said was gonna happen they saw the collectible robots
They saw the characters and all of a sudden flipped the other way told you was gonna happen. They left
That's fine. You stayed
Hey, you stayed
So we can we can enjoy the game together if people don't want to watch
They don't have to and that's fine. They left you stayed and we got to see the fucking voices
we've got to see the cool gameplay and we got to see the collectibles and
We got to sign the petition to all of us. But yeah, that's that's all right. Don't matter
You don't want it. Look if you don't want to watch a stream, you don't like you don't have to
Not like hey, wait, wait, wait, wait, you left cuz you didn't like the game. No, you know
I'm sorry, you're you're glued to the seat. You're chained to the seat
I don't know what you were doing this afternoon, but it's this
No, you can don't want to watch you can just go to something else. It's all good
Sweetie spanky. Thanks the 250 any update and bring it back the clips
And they are by the way the plan 9 movie in the VOD got muted and deleted all my clips not free
Not so free public domain, huh? Really? That's kind of wonder why that happened. Well, that sucks. Why?
It's public domain movie. I want to check into that. Hey s 10w update slow update. Thanks for the 250
How's it going? Jerma eight six seven five three. Oh nine
eight six seven five three
Oh
Thanks for the five dollars here
They say fuck I forgot the rest of my message anyways glad to support you and can't wait for you to bake
Napalm with an easy bake oven on stream peace and love and best wishes
Well, I have to be careful. I'm not gonna like do anything dangerous
Johnny nice mountains. Thanks for the five dollars. You were so pissed drunk that stream shouting crying and puking everywhere. It was so funny
I would never there's like a little there's a limit on what how much I'm going to drink with a live stream on
It's it's like between four and like maybe five six drinks max
Maybe five I that I'm I would never
Go to a point where I was I don't even drink like that if I'm not streaming anyway, like if I'm just going out somewhere
I
Don't like get just shit-faced like that
Yeah, you can get drunk and accidentally delete you jump. Okay jump cave
You jump King save file jump can't save cave King. Okay, I get it
I see where that came from you can you can be a little sloppy and delete you save file accidentally
But doesn't mean do you like puking the five dollars though a freak out. Thanks for the five dollars Jerma
I told you I worked at Honda, right? Well in some Honda related news
Uh
Kristen this person is was a mechanic at this place and I got fired
That's unfortunate. I'm sorry here that thanks to the five dollars though. Oh, there's a great company
It's a whole system. Hold on. It's
This person if I was talking about drinking on the job to what wouldn't this person on thin ice?
Yeah, they were this is false lore
well, anyways
Thanks, Jerma lied about the turkey joke I did that has actually happened those either don't know what that is
I was supposed to have I supposed to get footage of
Me or somebody in a big turkey mask walking by my window in my old place in Massachusetts and I bought the mask
But before I moved to Vegas, I didn't do it and I didn't bring the turkey mask to Vegas
So it didn't happen. It was gonna be in video. I don't even know that. How do you know that?
I don't have I don't think I've ever publicly talked about how the turkey joke did I or
As you think of something else and did I just did you just do the to take you did the detective thing?
But you were talking about something else completely and I just admit it to all the crimes
Hey snoozing copter. Thanks for the 250
You just said you're looking for a game that plays like this and there actually is one but it's only on the 3ds
It's the kid Icarus uprising multiplayer mode. Really people actually still play it online
One of the most underrated games it's so good everyone in chat that played it back me up here
There's a ton of weapon and item variety. It was directed by Masahiro Sakurai himself
Unfortunately, you can't stream it, but you still enjoy it on your own. It's definitely worth it
So good. It's so good. So good. Oh
My god, yes kid Icarus uprising of this shit. It's pretty good
Get Gino in here
Get him in here. I would play it I would try it
I didn't I didn't play any kid Icarus games ever. So give me a nice
Dunking my toes in the water for that franchise. So maybe I would give it a try
Hey video games McGee. Thanks for the thousand bits
Am I the only one who thinks you look and sound like someone who would play JFK in a scary movie spinoff?
I don't know about that
scary movie spinoff
Like a Charlie Sheen scary movie like scary movie for I play JFK somehow. Is that what you mean by that?
What do you mean? Like a scary movie you have to mean that
Disaster movie epic movie that type. I don't know. I'm too young
I would need it another five years or so. Maybe
Thanks for the thousand bits. Hey one one one two E
Thanks for the 250. This looks like a game. My dad plays on his iPad
We I've read this one, but it made me laugh. So I said it earlier
Thanks for the 250. Hey Das Knight. Thanks for the 300 bits. Hey, Jay loved watching you play GF
Hold on a bit gas a
Glad chat seemed to like it, too
I found memories playing the game on GameCube in the early 2000s with a girl at college
The game a thing we bonded over actually I was an English major and she took film studies
So we took it in turns to fight Borg while the other person explained recent lecture content sounds boring
I know but one fact she mentioned that always stuck with me was how Bella Lugosi died before plan 9 began production
Wow, so what did they do?
What could they have possibly done?
Hide that fact in the movie. That's interesting. Thanks for the knowledge
Yoda 985 gave 250. I said this one out loud, but I want to address it again
Remember the blood burger sounds like a fake rustling movie. You would say when Ronald McDonald kill somebody in the rumble. Yes. Yes
Peaceful Haley. Thanks for 250 speaking of when you talked about cheese when I was a kid
I would always pour shredded cheese in a bowl and just eat it like that all the time
So I would have bowl issues all the time as a kid because of my consumption of cheese
So one day my stomach was killing me wait bowl you bowel bowl
One day my stomach was killing me and I went to the hospital
he took my blood and etc and the doctor comes in and just shows me a grape and says you heard of these and
after that I had a
forced down prune juice and shit. I will never forget that
Has you heard of these ever hear these kid is called a fucking vegetable
Where did the grape come from? Yeah, why did the doctor just have a grape?
Was it all mushy and rotten?
Was that his pocket grape that he showed to young children to scare them and then make his joke to the parents?
That's funny. Thanks for 250. Hey errorless. Thanks for 250 any interest in chroma squad
This game reminds me of that never heard of it
Roma squad
practical RPG
About five stunt actors who decide to quit their jobs and start their own Power Rangers inspired TV show
Cast-actors purchase equipment and upgrade your studio. Wait, what is this?
Cool. I'll put it on the list looks alright
Seems kind of cool
On the list. Thanks for the 250. Why don't we share the credits? Let's do it
incoming sub credits
Not until I move over
Changed to you all leaving the theater
Thanks for the subs guys. Probably wondering why it's going a little slow
because about
An hour ago an hour and a half ago the stream crashed because my VPN died
So these are the people that have subbed in the last hour and 30 minutes hour and 20 minutes. I
I can't the chat just what's exploded. It was so fast when I said the word VPN
I saw like a bunch of omega lows and like VPN omega. Like he was immediate
But anyways, thanks everybody sorry some you got
axed from this list
All right about that. It was the because of the server I picked won't be picking that one again
But we will finish the bits as always. I really appreciate anybody that subs this channel
nobody ever is obligated to
What you do and I can't I just I can't believe it. Thank you
Thanks for giving me money on a fucking consistent basis some of you for like years
He's a lot. Thank you
Let us finish the bits ghost Ori. Thanks for the three dollars. Hey, Jerm I love this frame fun fact about gotcha force
I learned on the wiki the original voice actor who voiced the main character
Ko Shishido was originally going to be
Hello, Lugosi, but unfortunately he died during production. They had to hire his grandchild to do the lines
All right, you I
My eyes rolled a little bit when I saw Bella Lugosi, but then his grandchild coming in he saved it
Saved it my eyes came back
That's funny Yoda 985 thanks to the 250 if chat keeps acting up you should spend a week playing Pokemon as punishment
That would be punishment to me too. So I don't think so. I think that would punish me more than you guys
Super paradox thanks for five dollars Jerma
Now you have to do Pokemon streams. I would literally bother you about it every stream. Don't please don't
Please don't do that. Don't bother me every stream about playing for I'm not gonna play it
I guess it was like a little hypothetical thing
I'm not gonna know don't bother me every stream. I'll ban you. I'll just I'll ban you
Hey, you asked for this. I'll ban you. Oh, don't bother me about this every day. I'll ban you play trapeze simulator
I'll ban the okay
But I'm playing that tomorrow if that's a real game and it's not like some stupid thing. That's not even real
I'll play for like five minutes. It's not even real. It can't be real. Thanks for the five dollars paradox
Appreciate it. I don't want to ban you moss lion. Thanks for 250 a tip to all the youngins in Chad
It's never too late to develop a skill or talent
Even if you're as old as me and Jerma taller than him though, just to be clear lol. What was that for?
Started off so sweet there. It's a strong now that you said that I feel like you're not taller than me
I feel like that's about what that's what somebody says when they're not the thing that they just said
You got to add that in just to make sure people know but I don't think you are
Thinking face a yoda 985. Thanks for the 250 when it comes to cookie dough
You got to cut out the middle man. Just put some chocolate chips on vanilla yogurt
It'd be a little honey and go to the refrigerator grab four raw eggs and eat those instead
Hey dark soul. Thanks for the 250. I mean, thanks for making me a mod. That's pretty pog
I use reddit like every day and have positive karma if you eat your veggies and snort your Funko's chat
You can be like me, too
Thanks, hey opster narwhal. Thanks for three dollars and 57 cents Jerma
I just got told I just got told to kill myself while playing overwatch
So I thought I'd come to be here for a little while some positive energy
Also, I'm remastering Jerma walk. So that looks like a little cleaner and loops better, too
Why is everybody to fucking be so mean and hate each other online?
In like video games and stuff. Why I gave why they were to be like that
Why is everybody like tell each other that kill themselves? It's online. Yeah
It's just like it's
We need to like relax. No, I think that a lot of people would would like do well
With having some device that if it detects if it detects you do it
This is something you set up on your own if it detects you saying something fucking crazy. It just plays it back in your ears
Because believe it or not if you hear yourself
Say something fucking really bad and really kind of fucked up and crazy. It's actually kind of embarrassing it is
You know what I mean? If it's like just be like like in your ears, not anybody else's like hey
Why don't you fucking kill yourself? Oh
Why don't you fucking kill yourself? No, I didn't why don't you fucking kill yourself? Fuck. That's embarrassing. It's really embarrassing
Do I sound like that? I sound like that. Oh fuck dude. I'm sorry
I'm just like just kidding around that decided we'd really angry and fucked up there. I didn't I don't like that
This is why we clip off
Don't you know what I'm doing? All right, don't even I'm clearing that one
But my point is is like sometimes if you hear is something you say
You know, it's like but nobody else needs to know you just have to hear it and go. Ooh fuck. That was a little much
Okay, I'm gonna turn it down a little
Text community nights gonna be something else. God damn it
No, oh
It's gonna be everywhere
It's gonna be everywhere. Don't I know that I'm being recorded
See it worked now. I'm like I'm embarrassed for saying something like that out fucking rages
And now it's been recorded and I heard it star used to record people like that and play it back to them
Anger is a funny thing because once you stop being angry
You can you kind of look back and go that really wasn't even a big deal at all
like anger is such an interesting emotion because half the time when you look back it's like
What the what who cares
Why would I let that get to me? You're like who cares? It's not even a big deal
Anger makes you delete your jump King save. No, that's
Intoxication. I think they're two different things. I'm so
Long be only fucking thinking about that one of the bath tonight. Oh
No
Like is that I was saying it too
very very strongly and
That could have been like me in a game holding the voice chat button
my god
What have I done? What have I done?
What have I done?
Whatever. Anyways, let's keep going. I'm gonna make it my ringtone
Hey
Hey, cano canoli
Was that your name?
Okay. No, it's
Only thanks for the 400 bits and watching for a long time now subscribing your passive support
LGBT folks means a lot. Yeah, I've said this I've said this a bunch of times. Just do you you you know you
Nobody can tell you
No one can tell you who you are cuz it's you you know that nobody else knows you you know you and do you
Other people are gonna do them and you're gonna do you this, you know, you I still don't know you don't who knows me
You do like I can't tell you who you are
How the fuck would I know?
Hey, I
This is who you are. I know who you are
You know, I've done I've no idea. So why would I pretend to just kind of this is my theory on it
Whoever you are, whatever you whatever walk of life or
however, you
identify
It I do I can't what why would I not support somebody individually
Doing what they want to do with your life. It's your life. It's not mine
I can't tell you how to run it and I mean that with everything and that there's not much more for me to say I
Live my life the way that I want to
At as best as I can as best as I know that I can now how I know myself. I hope you do the same
That's it it's my money and I need it now that was word soup I
Mean it wasn't it wasn't word soup
It was you I guess it kind of was a little soupy wasn't it? But alright, but you get my point though
That's all that matters. What if I want to sell drugs and kill people? Well, that's illegal
Like that's we've we've all agreed that that killing people is not. Okay, that's
almost every living human knows
That like killing somebody is that's
Your you are taking over somebody's life. You are taking control of somebody's life by killing them
You are putting power over somebody else's life
That's how that works. So come on streamer says up. Wait, I decide when you like no
I'm moving on
Long story short, I I can't tell you how to be you only you know that and I'm not gonna tell you how to be you
Cuz you're the only one that knows
Fucking soup eat it up. Hey go. Okay. Thanks for the five dollars
Reddit jokes are all fun and games until they call one of your favorite characters a reddit character. Oh sad face. Oh
oh
Oh
No
Not my favorite character, but Slimer and
Qbert he's a fucking dork. He's mocking us. Yes, of course I am
You know how much shit I got for Slimer back here wait till your characters are reddit character and then we'll see how you feel
Who cares? It's a fucking news website. All right. Hey dinosaurs Rex. Thanks for the 250
Hey German for the German rumble
I know you're already spoiling us with getting us to vote for the characters that will get in but hear me up
You should try doing a character creation contest
Each member gets to create one character and the character with the most votes gets put into the rumble
It could be pretty cool that's an interesting theory the one issue with that is turning it into a popularity contest
Because let's say for instance somebody makes a character that knows is gonna get up votes
versus a character that's incredibly well made but
Isn't part of the like kind of popularity contest in a way, you know
I I would have to pick them if I was gonna do that
I would go through and I'd pick the ones that I would want to put in
Yes, something like you up vote something so if we were to do something like that it would only be for a certain amount of
Slots like they would be one community character or like I have three community characters or maybe the community characters could be
part of their own tag team, you know if there was like a three like a six-way tag or like a
Tornado tag match it could be the community characters versus
Sam and Max shit. That's one of the fucking matches. That's not kidding
They'll probably be in it though. It's like a thousand different characters that haven't been made. But now it's a good
It's a good thought only give it a shot. Yeah, I would just choose because then it would just be like, oh Jerma
Just picked these he didn't pick mine
but he
There was just there was a ton of things to choose from when he picked just ones that he wanted and that would be it
Hey the the
uber noob
the uber
Noober the uber noob. Thanks for three dollars. Jerma loved playing this game as a child and actually just revisited it
And found it just as fun as I remembered. Yeah
It's it holds up pretty well
Glad to see you're enjoying it and even though chat kind of even chat kind of warms up to it
Yeah, they did depression has really been kicking my butt as of late and one of the few things I look forward to are your streams
Thanks for streaming this big part of my childhood much love from the UK at 430. That's late. That's very late
Well, I'm not sure if I should say good morning or good night. Either way one of those two. Thanks for the three bucks
Thanks for hanging out. Glad to have you here. Hey a friendly spider
Thanks for the 550 yo Yerma
Just want to say even though this is like message number 5,000 that you're a fucking awesome guy who always provides great entertainment
No matter what please keep doing what makes you happy cheers always
I will always try to do things that make me happy and make me have fun and especially on this stream
I'm going for it trying thanks for the $5.50 and thanks for the incredibly nice message a clowers V
Thanks for 250. I remember back when German refused to play some ads even when chat was begging for it now
Jerma talks non-stop about fast food chains
It even makes us watch their adverts and he does it for free Ernie Pog
Nobody has to pay me to tell you that the McChicken is like one of my favorite things in the world
I would somebody why would they need to be a transaction there?
Like that's just a fact from my mouth like the McChicken is my favorite one of my favorite things in the world
I nobody has to pay me to say that that's just a what it that's just a real fact
Oh, I had it too and it fucking trumpeted off at the end. Damn it. Whatever. It was close and then it just like
The hey, hallelujah. Thanks for the 300 bits $3. Hey a German
I don't know if this is be feasible back when he played rollercoaster tycoon 2 you mentioned needing servers to use the twitch integration
I was wondering the FTK service could be used. Oh, I don't I don't think so because I think they're I don't know
I that's a that's a question for the FTK guys. I have no idea
Anyway, hope you're doing well much love and stay safe you as well right back at you off. Let's thanks for the $5
Just want to say hi. Hope you're doing well. Thanks for giving me $5. Hope you're doing well, too
Thanks the fives smack a roadies cast line. Thanks for the $3
Please please please please look into playing armored core for answer for the PlayStation 3 I'd pog so hard
But it's not your thing. That's fine, too. It might be I would take a little bit of research
Why for in particular though? Dr. Noob Stein. Thanks for the $5 German if you tried I bet you could be huge in Japan
You'd be in that little box in the corner of the screen doing wacky reactions while some girl gets
Spanked in front of a studio audience with everyone laughing wait
What and you do the look of me as your trademark and the Japanese audience would collectively lose their shit and cheer for you
You know what I'm saying?
I'm sure someone from chat could get you on a show in the corner doing just wacky reactions
Oh, yeah, I would do it. I would do I would go on one of those
I would go on with those shows and just do like that
It's like three or four times that would be with like the hands up
I'll just hit you that would be fun
And there would be an excuse to be in Japan and visit Japan eventually
I don't know if anybody has any pretty knows anybody that does do Japanese TV shows
I don't know how that's probably pretty that's probably not very many people. I don't know that'd be fun a goober juice
Thanks for 250 if the look of me taunt becomes a TF2 taunt would you play TF2 again? I don't I don't know man
the look of me taunt the look at look at look at me is just like me pretending that you're talking and
Like look at me. I'm talking look at me like I
Have that he hates to him too. No, it's not the lion pose. Look at me is. Oh, look at me
I'm fucking know everything. I'm talking. Oh, I everything I'm saying is fucking stupid. That's that's what the look at me is
It's like you am I you're explaining your joke. Don't explain your joke
Well, I don't people don't but people have probably have no idea what it's probably some people here
They don't even know what you're talking about. But why they say why they saying look at me
Let's be honest if you're still here, there's no way right like if if yours here right now, you probably know
Well, somebody said it was the lion taunt. So I had to correct them. No, it's the one where you go
Look at me. Let's see. Somebody said that. Hey go over here juice. Thanks for 250. Hey dumbass 985
How come brownies always get the attention? I wish German would bake me easily in an oven
But no for real. Yeah, play armored core or zone of the enders. What what?
I think this is a typo. Hey germ a lot about the turkey joke. Thanks for five dollars
I bought more bits just to tell you the name was about the mr. Bean turkey on head joke
So you did just admit to the crime. I had no idea about the other turkey joke. Yep. Yep
Well, you got me. We have a few more bits to do but we're gonna call it an end. Good night guys
I'll see you tomorrow more got you force around the same time
Take care of yourselves. Have a good night
a good sleep
Wherever you are, we do have a little bit more to do we have sticks renegade for 250 Pokemon or Jackie Chan stunt master
Pam band guys. See you. I
Would play I definitely would play Jackie Chan stunt master before Pokemon. That's a fact
Moo means moo. Thanks for the $4 bella legosi died in an unfortunate walk-in of an accident. That's unfortunate
Hey edge. Thanks for three dollars German return on smart click maps. Thank you. No, you're gonna make a dick happens every time
Maximum watts thanks for $5 a German
I just want to say I really appreciate your words on the matter of people telling each other that to kill themselves
Not that anyone cares, but I've seen family members and next-door neighbors take their own lives and it never leaves me as a human being
I know people are going to joke and laugh and that's okay
Doesn't dark place today remembering a lost childhood friend interesting how you bring that up today. Thank you
Let me know I can look nobody wants to
Feel shitty. You know, I mean nobody wants to feel bad about stuff
That's why it's I've always thought
There was some it was something like a level as you just kind of just don't you don't like
Especially in a setting where you don't know anybody and I guess that's the reason why people do it. It's why people do anything like that
you could say and wicked just awful shit because
These pretty people don't know who the fuck I am and who cares
so it's unfortunate, but that's just kind of the nature of
The internet where it's just kind of people just kind of say crazy shit
That's the way it is at this point
It doesn't mean that it can't affect somebody, you know, I mean if like somebody if you hear that and it's like well that sucks
Cuz I like know somebody that happened to do that and fuck now you have to think about that
Where on the other end it's just like somebody just kind of talking shit, right?
Just the nature of kind of anonymous
Everybody because the person that's saying it does not know that about you and
You know that they you don't know anything about them. They don't know anything about you and it's just kind of noise
It's way that's a way I would call it word soup. Yeah
Word soup, this is nonsense. This is all nonsense. What?
Am I like hearing myself talk? Am I like going crazy?
TL DW too long didn't watch
Try to relax on the fucking internet
You know, you just just pump the brakes a little
Just relax the board and we're cooped up. No, but you don't I mean
But people like talk shit
but this talking shit and then his
Trying to be as like awful as possible. You know what I'm saying? I like jokey shit talking
I think a lot of people do I do
It can be fun
regardless
Thanks for the $5 and it does affect people as you can see
Hey app key. Thanks for the $5 derma any plans to play DBZ games. It'd be pretty neat
I think I don't want to watch the DBZ show before I play the DBZ games
Which has not happened yet and might never happen
We'll see a somnus. Thanks for the $5 Jeremy so excited for the League of Legends and Valorant back-to-back stream tomorrow
Pokemons more likely. I'm gonna have that tier system set up. I got a question though
Does chat ever overwhelm or exhaust you? I can't imagine being called a fucking weirdo for hours by thousands people without losing my mind
Um, yeah
No, I mean if I start to well, that's when I turn streams off, you know, I'd like
If it's like okay, I've kind of had enough
Not of chat but just in general like usually I kind of just gauge after four or five six hours if it's like
I got kind of gonna take a break and kind of get out of here
So
No, not necessarily overwhelm or exhaust but I
kind of just gauge how I currently feel on a really
almost minute-to-minute basis as
You see some streams can be and I mean the reason why I'm making streams four to five hours now
This one will be about six, but it's just because of medical reasons
I'm just trying to not sit in the same place for more than four or five hours of time and
It's it's helping so that's the reason for that
but no
You'll know I've if I really need like to take a break. I usually just go alright, like I'm out of here. I
Don't I don't make a big deal out of it. I'm not I oh you guys are so exhausting the absolute fuck out of me
I can't take it anymore. Goodbye. No, that hasn't really happened
It doesn't really happen at all
But yeah, it usually goes pretty smoothly
Thanks for five dollars. Hey travel boy. Thanks for five dollars. Your take on LGBTQ is the libertarian take on LGBT q
We finally got a political opinion out of you
You're centrist. Oh
Oh
How does it wait? How do you go from libertarian to centrist? Oh
Here we're going down the rabbit hole
He's a centrist libertarian communist. Yeah, that's whatever. That's whatever. That's fine
Let's just say that that's all right. I'm gonna just say Bernie Pog. It'll fix it
You guys already do I I don't
We don't talk politics, but I give you beliefs and I give you kind of stances on stuff
I think you could piece together kind of how I feel about the world
I think it wouldn't be very hard at this point hates the lower class. Oh
man
He picks that message. Well, it was one there you're gonna it's gonna happen to you eventually
but no, I whatever I
Everybody you can think what you want. It's fucking be a mystery forever
Thank you edge for the five dollars. You're my about 500 more bits to do this turn on smart clip max
I'm not gonna turn on smart clicks
No, I'm not turning it on. No, no, no
I'm not gonna turn it on. I'm not gonna turn on smart clips
I'm not gonna do it and you're not gonna be able to make me do it. Mr. Turtle. It's not gonna happen
John Oliver there
It's weird new character. John Oliver's not like he's a person. He's a guy
You guys are too fun. All right dinosaurs Rex. Thanks for the two dollars and fifty cents
Remember you skipped a few donations in the past few streams also be more careful
Have I I've tried to be pretty I've been I thought I've been pretty on top of it. Have I miss been missing a couple?
I skipped one. Oh gooberry juice. Thanks for the 250. Hey, there's one right there. Could you please ban me?
No, for real
I got some work to do tomorrow and I need to make sure I don't procrastinate by watching you
It would really help me out if you could just ban me for 24 hours
Yeah, I'll make it easy for you. Chewy brownies are redditor brownies. Also hash house a go-go sucks
Their burger buns were so wet. I swear that the chef spat in my
Anyways, thanks again, you'd be at Vandus Purse. Yeah. Bye
They're gonna go get your work done
Go get your work done. No excuses. No, and I'll see you guys tomorrow
Remember what you don't you want to know what the current plus two minus two score is. It's plus 1,000. Nice
He was just joking. Why'd you do that? I
Don't see it. Just joking in this comment. They said that I I
Have to make sure I don't procrastinate by watching you. I have a lot of work to do tomorrow
So I did it don't tank it and what did I do?
All right. I'll see you guys tomorrow more gotcha force. We'll see how far we get
Tomorrow night. Goodbye
Have a wonderful rest of your day
It's 10 o'clock at night Pacific, which means it's like 6,000 o'clock at night everywhere else. Good night everybody, right? Right?
All right, let's write. We were right. We read
We got Bernie. I'm not reading Bernie Bernie. Is Bernie like a streamer now?
Is he live every day?
Are you guys lying to me or is like Bernie Sanders streaming? What does he play? Oh, I didn't play
He doesn't what do you mean? What does he play?
Imagine if he was fucking sick at counter-strike
All right, where we going for real? We got who's streaming right now Vinny streaming
criken streaming
Let's go say hi to Vinny vertical. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, you know what, you know, we actually we haven't
Let's go say hi to critical. It's been a long time. You're doing say look
What's it? What's he doing?
You are doing
playing Valorant
See if it's any good boys and girls. Let's go. See you guys tomorrow night