He goes, hey, what's up? How are you? Good to see you.
How's everybody doing? I don't know what you're doing. All right.
Just sending out a tweet. Sorry, I'm late. Yeah, whatever. You know what? I'm not even gonna say
that anymore. I'm not even gonna say that anymore. Do I? Okay. If you're late every day, are you late?
Are you just a piece of shit?
Oh, sorry, I'm late. Oh, hey, I'm late. Oh, hey, I'm late. Oh, hey, I'm late today. Hey, sorry,
I'm late today. Hey, I'm late. Oh, hey, I'm late today. At what point you're not late?
You're just a dick. I'm not a dick though. For God's sake, what? No, I'd rather look, I'm gonna take
the incredible wisdom of Nintendo. Somebody at Nintendo once said, I would delay the fucking
game three more times if I knew it was going to be a better video game when it released,
when kids got their hands on it, right? Somebody said that at Nintendo. What's going on? Why is
my voice like this? Why? Whatever. I would rather be live when I'm ready than turn the stream on,
not be ready, have a little bit of a headache, sit there and go, oh, oh, my head. And everyone's
like, oh, his head. And I'm like, oh, ow, ow, ow. For like 30 minutes. No, I'm gonna stream when
I'm ready. And you know what I noticed? Since streaming, since going back to, when I say back,
I mean, since going down to like two days a week, obviously Elden Ring was a lot different,
right? Because I was streaming that a lot more. But since doing two to three days a week, like one
to two days a week sometimes, right? I feel like I haven't seen you guys in a while. So I just
absolutely unload on you with just weird stuff that I've like thought of in the last like five
days. I think that's why the streams have gotten odder in the last like year. Because there's way
more stuff for me to say to you. And there was, you know, if I were to stream every single day,
I wouldn't have had that Dunkin Donuts drive through scenario, right? Maybe I would have,
but it wouldn't have been as in the front of the head. Because you lost your mind. No, I'm just
messing around. You guys know that. Hi, how are you? Welcome to the stream. Today we're gonna play
Elden Ring. Not regular Elden Ring. We're gonna do multiplayer. I'm gonna start, we're gonna do
some invasions. We're gonna pick a spot somewhere. I'm gonna put a sign down. Or you'll put a sign
down and then we'll have a group password. We'll do some PvP. Maybe we'll do some summoning. If
you're having trouble with the boss. Hey, maybe I might help you kill Godric. That's very possible.
What system? This is on PC. I'm not going to tell you anything yet because I don't want...
Okay, here's why I don't want to tell everybody what the information is. I think I'd rather just
slowly trickle in because I don't want like 5,000 people to all put their sign down right now
in the same spot. So just hold on. You have multiple characters for certain levels. No,
unfortunately I have one character that's 153 and then me strong who is level 10.
So I'm gonna be playing with this character. Just use a password. Levels don't matter.
Well, here's the thing. I'm not gonna do like just PvP only. I want to do like some invasions
and stuff. But that's the plan. We're just gonna play. We're just gonna hang out. Tomorrow,
I'll be live tomorrow. We're not playing Elden Ring. Tomorrow we're gonna do DOS games. I'm gonna
grab a bunch of random stuff. Play for a few hours. That's tomorrow. This is today. If anybody has
any recommendations for DOS games, please put them in the recommendation channel in the Discord.
Uh, we've played a lot already. Bringing this back. I used to do this. I've done this probably
like five to ten times. Maybe total. So we have done a lot already. It's gonna be really hard
for me to remember what those are. So we're gonna... I will collectively have a pretty decent list
tomorrow. But I might pop in to the Discord and ask a few questions. All right, let me just tweet.
I'll be right back. We'll get started. It just took me so long to do that. Yeah, I'll get around
to the BTTV emotes. I know. Oh yeah, I'll get around to that. Oh, yeah. You know what? I've
been kind of... Oh yeah, no, I'll get around to it. Yeah, me strong will take care of that.
All right, let's go. It took me so long to tweet that. Why? Why did that take so long?
That should have been so quick. I just had to look at the keyboard. I actually, honest to God,
I'm not kidding. I just said, all right guys, I'm gonna go tweet. I'll be right back. Let's tweet.
I went like this. I was just looking at my keyboard. What the fuck happened? I was just
looking. I was just like, oh, that's... I'm gonna look at the keyboard for like 10 to 15 straight
seconds. All right. Hi. Welcome to another stream. Today, I'm gonna be summoning people in PvP.
This is not where I'm doing this, by the way. I'm not doing it here. I know that I'm gonna look down
and it's gonna be like... I'm not... Don't. Stop. I'm not doing it here. See? There's already one
right there. I'm not gonna use the katana. Maybe I will. I don't know. You guys see? Okay. How many
rivers of bloods are we gonna see in the first 30 minutes? I didn't even tell you what we were
doing yet. Here's what I'm doing. I want to start because... Let me get the hang of this first. Let
me like figure out how this works. I'm gonna do some invasions. I'm gonna try to invade somebody's
game. Where should I do this? Rest till night at this bonfire. Is there a place that I should do
this? I feel like I want to do it somewhere weird. Go to the mountaintops. Why rest till nightfall
here? Is there where I get invaded? At the divine bridge? This is like a perfect knot. Rest again.
Rest again and walk to the shack. Hold on. I love how I'm still... I like beat the game and I kind
of finished the actual kind of campaign of the game. I love how people are like, all right dude,
rest at that bonfire. Wake up. Take 10 steps forward. Take 10 steps backward. Look at the
ground. Look at the sky. Swing once and a boss appears. I don't... What's he... What am I even
doing? I'm supposed to be invading? Okay, now walk to the shack. Bell Bearing Hunter. What happened
to this weapon? Oh, this is fucking hard. Dude, it's so cool. They added like a boss bar for PvP
encounters. That's so cool. That's awesome. I'd say they should have added that a long time ago.
That's a cool move. Where'd you get this weapon? Also something finally added. Thank God. It's
being able to scale your player model and stuff. Like, bigger head, bigger arms. Nice. Okay, they
can kill the NPCs in a bit. I don't even have two headphones in. This doesn't count.
Oh, now I'm not supposed to drink. I know. Whatever. All right, stop with the fucking
PvP joke. Just kill this boss. This guy's easy. Get in! Stop respawning. Oh my God. All right,
this is not supposed to be a game where I play Elden Ring. I'm supposed to be PvPing. I'm stuck
in the tree. Thank you. Yeah! How come you look like you're 17? Because I moisturize every day.
I'm gonna have youthful skin for the rest of my life. Like, internet just freeze. What was that?
That was weird. All right, I'll kill this guy. I'll kill this guy. This isn't Fortnite. Okay,
come on. Now I know what's happening. Wait, is he gone? Why is he not here?
Okay. All right, I'm not playing Elden Ring anymore. I'm playing Elden Ring PvP. They're
two separate clients. Two separate EXE files. I shouldn't even be seeing these enemies. It's
ridiculous. Okay, so here's where I'm gonna go. Beat him first. Fine. All right, I'll beat him.
I got it. I got it. I beat him. I was here for like four hours. I was here for like four hours.
Medicine peddler's bell bearing. All right, cool. I beat it. There we go. All right,
I'm not gonna use the moon veil in PvP. I'm not gonna do the thing that everybody thinks I'm gonna
do. Here's what I'm gonna do. I'm gonna use the baby rattle. It's gonna be people are not used to
fighting the baby rattle. All right, so let's go. Are you ready? I'm gonna I'm just gonna invade
somebody. Just right here. Can I invade somebody here? I just want to see how this works. That's
a summon set. Now here we go. Attempts invasion of other players world. Yeah. Phantom bloody finger.
Okay, now what? All right, I gotta kill this person. How come they're not on the minimap?
Where are they? This be anywhere? Oh, they are in the mini. They are on the minimap.
No, they're not. Wait, what? Do you see me? This guy afk. Let's get the shit out of this guy. Oh,
fuck. I scared him. I scared the shit out of him. Never seen a baby rattling PvP. Have you?
Fine. I'll do it too. Two sorcerers back to back. He's being a weirdo. He's being a weirdo. He's
being a weirdo. Wait, who's? Wait, there's a is that a go to guy? Why? Who is this?
Oops. What's happening? Oh shit. Okay. Okay. Okay. Is healing illegal? Oh, oh, oh, oh. Oh,
he just baseball swung me to midair. How come I don't get a tag team partner? Oh, I got him.
Now what? Now what? Now what do we do? Do I have to fight him too? Whoa, I did it. I kind of feel
bad though. That like, that's annoying. I kind of feel bad. Like that person was just afk. Like
hanging out. The person probably, what did they lose their souls? They do. I feel, I feel kind of
bad. That was fun though. I don't know why that was fun. They're five feet from the grace and
it's fine. That's true. Oh, so what I can do that anywhere. I've never done PvP in any of the souls
games ever. So I can just do that anywhere in the whole world. What's a weird place that no one would
ever invade you at like a front door LB on the map. What is this? What is this?
Multiplayer status. This is where people are hot spots. Oh, for Dan swamp. That is kind of a weird
place. Or what about the, I mean, the front door actually has a lot of, uh, activity. What about
like over here? Like in right in front of the divine tower of limb grip fight them on the elevator.
Here we go. Oh, I can't use it here. The guy was an afk. He was waiting for me. He was hot spots.
Why? I repeat. Well, well, that was kind of fun. I'll do it again. How about just over here? Whatever
right here. Doesn't work in all areas. Okay. He used the taunter's tongue. Lunaria is full of
tryhards. So is this sectioned off to kind of like skill level? Lunaria is for the tryhards.
Limgrave is for the people that don't even understand the mechanic is in the game.
Kaylet is for people that want the like kind of animated background, like in street fighter.
The capital are for people that said, look how far I've come in the game so far. And like, I'm like,
look, I'm at the capital. I played the game for a while and the mountains is nobody cares because
nobody plays. Nobody wants to be here. Right. I look at how far I made it into the game.
It's based on your level. Oh, Oh, let's just do it right here. Whatever. I have like, I got a shit
load of these. Let's go festering bloody finger. Let's use it. Invasions are one V two.
Did it work? I didn't even look. Did I teleport? Cancel. Oh, it's not doing it.
You can only evade people who are in co-op. You can one V one viewers by making a password for us
and put them down the duelist sign. Like what's going on here? Well, go do something so I can
invade you. Oh, there's nobody around there. Okay. There is somebody around there right there.
No one is here. God damn it. All right. How about like, how about like the cat? Yeah. People will
be like right here. Right? Yeah. Get a fight club going. I just turned. I just started.
Relax. I don't, I'm not going to start the fight club before I even know how to
PVP everybody. This is a good place. Uh, Ray Lucario game is good for PVP.
Let me do it. I want to do some more invasions. People play this game. The Hallux. Oh, oh, oh,
oh, oh, oh, it's a dead game. All right. Here we go. I should dress like a weirdo, right?
All right. Make them think I'm fucking lagging. What was that move?
Starlight. Oh, that was a bad idea. I was going to do this. Freak them out.
What the fuck just happened to me? Oh, what? That tracks. How much does that track? Oh my God.
I'm going to get embarrassed. I got him. Nice job. GG. What happened? So I should, I should dress up
as the baby then. I would be furious right now. That person had 15 bigger.
Okay. Why did I, why did that, why did they die? I hit them with the swing for the baby rattle.
That hits. Then the explosion hits. And then like a second later, he would hurt them.
That was weird. All right. Cool. I actually kind of like this. It's fun.
You played the entire game without following up an L2. Um, maybe rattle does not have an L2 follow
up. Everybody scream. No L2 follow up. No L2 follow up. No L2 follow up. No R2 follow up.
Look, no R2 follow up. No L2 follow up. No R2 follow up. No L2 follow up. And by the way,
the person that said that you have to understand, I played the first like 50 hours of this game
without the flask of wondrous physique. I mean, there's that I'm, I have a tendency.
How much is like right in front of the ear tree? Kind of fun. Like at the throne. Yeah.
Let's do it right here. And let me change my outfit because who cares about actually winning games.
Let's make ourselves just look like scary and weird and creepy.
Yeah. I'm going to be an assassin. Hmm. There we go. Big oven mitts and mushroom legs.
Oh, that's ugly. There you go. I just put on like a boxing glove and go punch people.
I just want to walk around with two shields. That'd be fun. All right. Uh, where's the katana?
I just want it in one hand and I want a parrying dagger in the left hand. I want people to think
like, Oh, God damn it. Do I really have to fight against this fucking, this guy's just going to
try hard the whole time. Where's, uh, where is it? Here you go. Even if it doesn't work, I don't,
it doesn't need to work. It just needs to look like I'm trying to do that. Yeah. Like right here.
Yeah. I want people to be like, Oh, come on, man. Really? I'm going to start like this.
They'll think you're trying to use moon bill. All right. Here we go.
You can't do it here. You can't do it on the throne. Huh? What about just like here means bed
chamber. What I want to, whoever I invade right now as the, I'm the moon veil, try hard guy.
I want to make, here's what, here's the ultimate. We're going to make somebody's day
because I'm going to come in there and I'm going to make sure that I lose.
So that person fucking jumps up in their chair and they're like, yes, like new piece of shit.
See, like I beat you. I want to make sure that they think that. So let's do it. I've even,
how long have you been drinking matcha for? Um, not that long. Don't pander to the three V ones.
Wait, there's a, what started fighting the boss? Oh, that's unfortunate. That's so funny.
Get me in there. I'm going to hopefully find somebody that's about to go in the boss door.
I want to stand in front of the boss door. That was a waste of a finger.
That should return it to you. That's not fair. And I got a bow too, right? Oh, moon veil. Oh God.
Oh, here we go. A bit of menacing. I am. They're talking. They're in a discord call right now
going like, man, I, people, people just net decking. Yeah. Nice net deck kid.
That's what they both are saying right now. All right. This time I'm actually going to try it.
I'm going to make somebody angry. No, they're saying what the fuck was that? I'm going to
actually try this one. I'm going to, I'm going to be the moon veil guy was going to the boss door.
Damn it. Shit. I wanted to backstab them so bad. I will go off and backstab somebody at this box.
I'm wasting fingers. Whatever. I can buy them from merchants. Who cares?
Invade away from the boss. I want to go up there and I want to, I want to scare the shit out of
somebody. Why would you ever get invaded here? Right? Like dude, there's no, like what a shitty
place to fight. First of all, people are just walking into this boss door. The recusant finger
is infinite. Okay. I got to get up there quick. They're going in. They're going to go, go, go,
go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Quickly. All right. Do I have any? There's
anything what's really long range a bow and arrow. Right? Could I like shoot him with a bow? Like
should I turn instantly and shoot the bow just like a bow? No. Use a great bow. Can I even hold
a great bow? I'm an Azure with a common I common. As they're my take too long. Use the red as a bow
And I does that go actually go that far? How annoying is that? I don't okay
I don't also don't want to be annoying the whole time. I want to see if this works
Invasions are always annoying
Invading is inherently annoying. Am I being annoying? You don't have a staff equipped. Oh god damn it
That would be so scary, I don't think anyone expects it and you know, somebody invaded
Oh, I wonder they're probably far away
I'm just at the bottom of the stairs put the fucking staff on dude. What a waste of
If this works, this is so stupid. I hate this. Okay, here we go
So just use the other finger. Is there any
Benefit to using this one that I had because I have them
Is there any reason to ever use these ever is it the exact same thing?
Use the taunter's tongue. I'm currently invading the exact same. Okay, see if I can do it
I
Am I up here? Is that the person? Oh shit. I got moved. Oh shit
Let's work. What's that? Why did he fall down?
Stop oh my goodness
No, I'm trying to kill him in one hit
What that was such a good fight? What the fuck? That was such a great fight. What happened? It didn't rage quit
Okay, I kind of like that. Let's go
Like what kind of stat combination is this?
Also, I want this person to be like, I don't know what the fuck's going on this guy
But I'm gonna like just pretend like I'm gonna walk around like my connection is bad. Wait, they're not here yet
shit
You can jump over the railing I think you can jump over the railing
You can jump over that railing. Oh, you know how I know that because I've seen speedrunners that do that
I just not whatever
Imagine somebody getting in there. He's invade someone else. I'm not invading the same person
Hotkey my beloved Omega. Well, he thinks he can God free skip
Nobody thought I could I will skip and I didn't two tries and I just want to so badly just be the boss
I want to be standing there when they get there
All right. I'll go in somewhere else. I'm going somewhere else. Fine. God damn it. All right, where's the where's the uh,
Activity, why is there a lot of activity inside of these dungeons? That's kind of weird the top like the mountaintop
Do the main gate at Ray Lucario?
Let's just try here. Whatever. I'm having fun doing invasions. Oh fire mazula. That's right
You should skip 48 minutes of waters. Why I'm invading I'm having fun getting invaded in the dungeons actually pretty cool
All right. Where are you? Can I get on horse here? See me? Oh, yeah, let's get this shit out of somebody
What
Why did mine go into the ground what the fuck is happening with these people get away from me
shit
Why?
Why did my beam go?
Two inches in front of me and do nothing. I did the beam and it went this far. What happened?
I want it. I want to kill up against those people again. You aimed it at the ground
I was targeting somebody you hit the rock in front of you. I didn't know that there was a madness beam
See them right there like I don't see him. What the fuck is he doing?
Hope you have fucked now
Stayed next to this thing. This is so unfair
Am I hitting him shit? Is it my just cheap? Oh, he killed it. Fuck. Oh my god. I didn't get okay
I honestly didn't think he killed it. I was I don't know what I was doing. I don't understand what happened
I I was like, I didn't think he was gonna kill that thing
But then I forgot that like other players probably don't think that the hand is that big of a deal
I was like just watching him fight it. All right, no more messing around like I'm not gonna like Oh cutesy
Look, I'm not gonna attack you. I'm gonna pretend like I have a connection problem. Oh, I have an idea
Let me invade somebody and pretend I have a connection problem and then they kill me great fucking fantastic. I'm killing this person
Here we go. I'm running another cooperator. Where are they? I'm not since in any movement. I'm gonna get sniped use the compass
Oh
Right. I forgot that exists. He's just sitting at a fire
Where are they at them a person tried to summon a friend it didn't work. That's not them. Is that them?
No, there's inside the building it below you. How do I get over there? Oh, that's unfortunate
You'd reinvade with finger. I'll try this one more time. I'm gonna go somewhere else. I actually think this is really fun
No, I love this at a password. We will we will I just want to invade. Well, actually
Does the password do invasions thought that was just for what was that? The password doesn't work for
Invasions does it? Okay down here. Is this the same thing? Are they underneath me like all the way?
Are they actually here? Why does it keep putting me up there? Yeah, what?
No, I promise we will do I will you guys can put your signs down and I'll bring you in
Alright, and well, I want to some cooperative stuff, too. I want to like have people summon me to help fight
Godric. All right. I must be spawning above them, right? So use another finger
Use another one and then it'll redo it jump it down
I'm gonna I'll die. That's them right there. Oh shit
Move the person this guy's gonna die
But he doesn't know where I am though, right? This person's not paying attention
No, I don't want to shoot you want to shoot your friend friends. Not even fucking here. Let's go
Get in there overwhelm them. Yeah, this guy even here. This guy do it
Is he still alive?
All right. Well, you've got no friends no more
What's that person doing? This guy's probably pissed. What the fuck is happening?
What is it? Is there was there another there's another person here. I'm so confused. We're gonna kill this guy. Come on
Yo, yo
damn it
God, who is that? I can't tell these people apart
Who's this guy what happened I have I have no idea what's just going on what was just going on
Another invader invaded you that was his compound invasions
So you tell me that guy I?
Invaded a player that player
Asked two other players for help. I killed one of those helpers as an afk
One of those helpers invaded that game and killed everybody in one swing
That invader was your teammate. Why was I dead? Well, he killed me in one hit
Invaded the host you got a helper but friendly fire is on. So did we win?
Did we did we beat it?
That's so funny. That was mayhem. I couldn't even tell you what was going on if I wanted to
That guy came in and just waved a magic wand and killed everybody. What the hell was that?
Like I was a referee. That wasn't even a player. He just came in and like he blew a whistle. We all stopped
Oh, you told me to get that up. Oh
shit
Thanos snapped doesn't Thanos have like a big hammer
Thanos has a big hammer, doesn't he? No, he's got the twin blades. He's got the glaive. Yeah. Yeah, you didn't have a
Spike that's not an accurate cosplay and also doesn't have a tabard. That was so funny, though. I almost beat him
You know what? I want to do so bad. I just want to freak somebody out like crazy
I want to just jump from here and land in front of them and die
Maybe like where did they come from? Why did they just fall? Are they all right?
They right there. Is that them sitting right there? That's a fault. I mean, I'm gonna try. I don't know. That's a marionette
They're at the bonfire
Damn it. Oh, well, you know I'm saying I just want that person to be walking around and a red invader just falls into
Like in their field of view in front of them and dies
With the fingers and your hot bar. Yeah, I will. Okay same deal. They're probably all the way over here
It's the same guy you don't know that I mean it could be because I don't know how many people are currently in Mount
Gelmira in the US matchmaking right now, who knows
Last guy was here. We're here
Person hiding that they were over here. I don't see any movement use the finger again. I didn't mean to do that
They see it though
I'm gonna be careful. I'm gonna end up in like an Elden Ring
funny moments compilation I
Was to go somewhere else how about like here let's look at some hotspots people fight here a lot
All right. What about over here? This is where the try-hards are, right? Okay
Use the invisible crouch talisman. Do I have it seals wear while crouching? Oh
Shit, I actually do have it. Okay. All right, let's go
I'm gonna have to turn crouch on because I'm not pressing X every time. All right, let's do it. So I'm invisible
You say so when I crouch when I get in the game, I'm not I'm invisible to the people on the other team
Has been only when you move away. You have to be in a distance. Do I have to stand completely still?
What can I move you can move this person doesn't see me how this is look at these Christmas lights. What is this?
How close is too close?
Can you see me now? Oh
Okay, I've already scared him. I would do a bow
Let's go
Got dabbed on I
Had it too. I I'm doing it again. It's the lag. It's the lag
I swung and it like went through his body and then like a second later. It's like, oh
But it was a glancing blow apparently. It was a glancing blow apparently this thing is okay
So I'm gonna I'm gonna just try to it's BM though, isn't it? And that BM kind of I just invaded
Ranny the witch's game my god, I mean I'm gonna be trouble
All right. They're trying to do something weird, which is I think they're trying to go on top of the house
I'm invisible. They don't know where I am. They're trying to do something weird. Okay, here we go
I got another wait. I have a friend. Hey, all right, so this is a friend. It's time for some fucking classic PvP
No, you're a friend. All right, let's go. All right. I don't know if you're watching the streaming up
I mean, I'm not gonna assume that but I'll I'll take
I'll take I'll take rain of the witch you go for a flame
Zealot you got it. All right, let's go
Make sure you bow first
Really a bit recess from software PvP is recess. I'm not gonna
Yeah, what why didn't I didn't get a backstab? Why not gonna expect that for me? Are you packed into it? Hey, what happened?
I didn't start that by the way. I just finished it. We did it
All the host was the okay. I see I didn't do that that guy
Shot a bunch of mold out of his hands and I didn't have anything to do with that
What level am I 153? I'm gonna do it again. Where's the pouch? Yeah, let's do this. I'm gonna
Just break a bunch of remembrances in there. What can I do? That's just weird put the soap on somewhere
Just do clean myself. I put this on all these this is gonna be weird. Nobody does that
I'll do like another okay. I'm gonna do like maybe
I have a five or six more and then we'll do some we'll do some PvP
What does that was put you can put your signs down use the mimic veil. Are you still red? You're still red, right?
There they are did I just go invisible on their screen? Oh my god, I was bowing
This guy's like do you have any other moves
Oh
Fight good fight. Those are some really cool moves. What the hell were those go to the main Academy Gate?
I will try that now. Okay main Academy Gate. Oh, those are faith spells. They've those are cool. Let's seem fun
dragon and crucible faith moves
So, okay. I see why this is a PvP zone. It's just a circle. I want some new clothes, too
As I'm not I don't need to do the comedy thing anymore
What do I actually want to put on I guess I put on the hat I look like a dickhead though, all right
Um, I'm still medium with these big pants on this place is for duels not invasions
Who's to say that?
I'm doing it right now. Is the mimic the mimic fail actually works
Put it on it works. How is that nobody to invade here? Oh, there we go
Use the red sign on the ground I will it's cross region enabled. It is not
I'm sorry to all the people that are not in the United States
But I'm not going to get swung at dodge and then two and a half seconds later take damage for it
It's just not happening. All right. Well, well, come on. I'm a hundred and fifty three. All right, here we go
If you want to put a sign down, I'll put mine
The multiplayer password is cheese doctor. It's like that. I'm gonna put this
I guess I'm just gonna have to pull people in it's probably easier for me to pull signs in right?
Me you can't see it. All right. Well, okay. The password is cheese doctor capital C capital D cheese doctor. No spaces
No period cheese doctor er smooth face cam. All right, my goodness. Well, I just told you what it was
Here cheese doctor. See it. All right, here we go. This is trying to invade another world over and over again
The last time I did this in Dark Souls
It was insane how many signs are on the ground turn off the invasion use the remedy. Oh
Okay, how do I turn off the invasion? What happened? I finally found somebody to invade
Why would this be out here? It's Garfield. I don't think he notices. All right. Well, that was cool
No, no, I don't take it off
Like that's gonna fix it. How do I take this off? How do I take it off?
Wait, is this too obvious? I can't see I can't see the painting covers it. Oh shit. Oh shit. Oh shit
That's so funny. All right. Where are the signs? That's right. Ladies and gentlemen
I might invade your game terms and conditions do apply
Could you be the lucky viewer that germa 985 invades? This is a weird thing
Oh, well some some like some celebrity will do that and they've never played they don't they're just part of the promotion
They just don't give a shit at all. They invade like two people. That's the whole thing
That's the big wow. I can't believe it. They play for like eight minutes
All right, let's do this one. Oh, no, we're going against the joker
Two huge hammers
That's not a viewer. How do you know? I want to invade somebody in like hide. I think that's so fun
You ready? I don't know. I just did what you did. This is weird
This looks like a cartoon
Whoa
Oh, I had no stamina
Didn't think it was gonna be twice in a row
Good game good fight. That was cool. Nobody expects twice in a row. Who are you? How about billy bobbertson?
That's that sounds fun password password is cheese doctor capital c and then dr
Capital d cheese doctor. This is still not a viewer. How do you know that?
You don't know that
All right. Let's incorporate some uh, some more sorceries here a dodge always for I didn't mean to do that
All right. Here we go
You can always say i'm ready by doing the strafe strafe strafe strafe
Oh, I got it off
He's panicking
Oh nice bait. That was good bait. It was
Whoa?
Don't waste all your stamina
Oh got me signs with circles are viewers. Oh shit
Okay, that was good. That's good fight. So that was not somebody watching, okay
Really? Yes. There we are. Okay. So this person that's not there's no circle
Oh, are we going to go up up against?
Shpee. Oh, it's the circle on the bottom. I thought it was gonna be up here fine
I need some better emotes. See mine. There's like like I these are like default dances in fortnight. Get them off
Oh, it looks like I was mocking. All right. Here we go. Ready. I'm ready. Hey
That's excuse me
Excuse me. He's drinking flask. Where's referee?
No, I fucking don't this is all the rules wrong. I'm drinking i'm gonna drink i'm not gonna let that happen
If you get one I get one good fight. Yeah, I ran forward
Immediate pivot that was a good fight. That's the soul level 153. This is really fun
But this is really fun. I understand why people do this now. All right, I need the ones with the circles
Here we go right here. Zoram. We're uh, we'll go zoram first
Yeah, okay, how about peeing myself that sounds that's good i'm that might not even been a viewer
I don't think that was a viewer. What are the emotes I have?
Let's do this while they're before they hear her
All right. What do you got? What are you wearing? I don't see any weapons mistake right now. He's like, oh shit
the forward
Uh dash the forward dodge is just oh my god. I'm ready. I gotta be ready
Okay, let's do it
He's metal
What's going on
What
Is happening with this person?
I'm so confused
Wait, what's going on? What the fuck is going on?
I'm so what happened
Oh, he's peeing. Okay
He also drank flask too, which uh
We all know that's uh, not allowed
And he liked he was like teleporting. That was weird. All right. Yeah, I do a password
All right. Password is cheese doctor. You can't see it, but i'll move passwords cheese doctor cheese doctor
Touch chugged flask before a fight. Is that cheating? What should I do for a flask?
for you
Uh shyness boy
Sure, i'm not gonna use that right now
Wait, actually tell me the truth is using the wondrous physique flask
Em in pvp or no, is that fine? No, okay
I don't know where this person is but they're not here. I think this is fucked up. What about over here?
All right. This is
Is there xbox that's an xbox username
What does this say? No skill ahead all the more dung ahead
Try summoning. Oh for the uh ranala
How are we?
Here we go. What the fuck what happened?
That actually worked
All right. That was i'm not using that again
Is that was that kind of unfair?
I'm sorry girthquake. That was not fair. That was just stupid
That that's that's so dumb
uh, how about
Hilarious
I want to even get one of these off from the beginning like right when it's like let's go. Let's go. Let's go, right?
That works shockingly. Well
Is that fire damage?
So technically you could put on a ton of fire resist drink that blow up and then fight them
Totally really that's weird. Oh, whoa. Whoa. Whoa. All right. Okay, we're just going you just got here
Hey
Scared the shit out of me. I thought that was
Is the magic bullet doing that?
Oh
Wowie
Oh, I wanted to jump but I didn't have enough stamina
Nice fight
You're allowed to use a blue flask. You are
Well, I can drink blue. Okay, cool. So blue is allowed. Okay, it's fun. Pick me pick me, please
warrior
Millennia
I'm sorry, but there's no respect here at all. This is absolute
I'm just gonna go go straight up disrespect if this is you playing right now. Just be aware
I'm going full on disrespect mode full disrespect. You don't come in and come in here with a millennia cost plan
What the hell
Do you want to play that? All right, we'll play that
No, not that stupid thing
You gotta be fucking kidding me
She has this move where she goes in the air
And she slash slash slash you cannot fucking avoid the
Yeah, well, maybe if I didn't drink the take
Uh two-thirds of my health off in the very beginning by drinking the exploding flask and I didn't I didn't time it right
Hold on. Are we certain that the summoning signs are that accurate the circle on the ground?
How actually accurate is that?
Don't growl at me. Okay
So you can drink these that's cool. All right
I'm maybe i'm gonna change up my spells too. These are pve spells
I think i'm gonna change that up. I'm gonna put on
Just weird shit that people that people are gonna be like annoyed to have to deal with
Pve. Okay. Yeah, like shooting glintstone ice crag. You're gonna no it's not gonna work in pvp
Let's do it
Whoa, you can okay you that you poised through that
Oh fuck
Okay
I you can't he poises through it
You poise through it you poise through okay
I I for some reason I thought that the magic glintstone ice crag was gonna break that poise
But you just said you cannot become out of that animation
I didn't know I didn't know I didn't know and if I knew you would have lost by the way
That's if I knew you would have lost that fight. Okay, this is not gonna work, but maybe this will
Yeah, let's do that
That's all right, what about that was weird like freezing mist like who the fuck uses this
meteorite something weird
and
What else should I do?
crystal release
Demo or ice storm. All right, let's just be kind of like an annoying weirdo
All right, zoram. Let's go
Crystal burst is good. Oh wait, I don't want to do that
That's kind of like bad because it'll start attacking him and I don't want to start attacking him before he
That's like kind of unfair
All right, here we go. You're missing half of the pvp spells. I don't whatever
These aren't just gonna shoot over there, right?
Get out of the emote
All right, you can
You can drink you can drink that wasn't fair. That wasn't fair. You can drink that wasn't fair
Uh, that wasn't fair. You can drink
Here we go, right?
Freezing mist is weird. Nobody expects it
Holy shit
I'm alive. I'm still alive. I'm still alive. I'm still alive
Kill him kill him
That was a 99 99 int play right there
Do I just go put 99 points in int and okay no zero points
Zero points in anything else besides mind and int
And just hold down that spell
That's so dumb. All right. Maybe I want to play normally a little bit longer
Okay trans rights
Let's go for it. Get the crystal tier that makes spells cost nothing
Oh, I do. Wait, wait, wait. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. He's fine. Yeah
Zero cost. Oh, I don't have to do mine. You're right. Okay
Here we go. You ready
Oh
You're not gonna expect this right now
That's the first parry that we have seen all afternoon
Flail what you can't parry a flail. That's right. You can't parry a flail
It's good for pvp. All right. All right, let's go
Poth what's the swear?
Poth hot head. What is it head? You can't your name can't be head
Uh group password is cheese doctor capital c lower case h e e s e
Capital d lower case r and that's it. Why are you like five times bigger than everybody else? Hey, this guy's huge
Am I crazy or?
What the hell? Why did it come up before he threw it?
This is a cool character though. Can I be honest?
You only have a certain amount of those
Holy shit, what?
Good game
That's a cool character
Just throwing pots
I like that. That's fun
That was good. How how do you catch people off guard with that though?
Because if you come in if you have the jar, I think that you have that hat that jar on your head, right?
I'm gonna know
All right galaxy. Let's go
I will do the just put I need okay. Where do I get some of the pvp spells?
Use the cannon. It's the ead which qualifies as a square because it's an acronym for e to a dick
really
Eat eat. Oh my god
All right, let's go
That was weird, but I got you you're not gonna fuck with the guy and so far as ice storm. Are you?
Telling you nobody expects you to do that two times in a row. Whoa. What was that? He's got knives
Oh, that's right consumables exist
That was that was a good that was a good idea throwing daggers
Yeah, everybody does the Thanos snap. I should do it too then right? I gotta do the meadow. How come I can't throw these?
Because you could really okay, you could freak somebody out, right?
if I
Like stew a soap. Hey, what about this weird shit?
Gravitational shockwave like who's ready for that? We already saw you
Uh rock strongo, okay
Like if you think i'm doing something, but it's like wait, he just did soap
You gotta freak the gamers out with soap
Level, uh 153 earthquake was the guy that you cheesed. I didn't cheese anybody
How are you? Welcome to the fight?
Let's begin
Oh, that's not good
Good fight fight caught you right at the little tail end of that
That was very close to you. Not getting in the hitbox
It would have been lag would have been like cool
Okay, but your password and the level on the screen so people don't ask anymore. That's a good idea
Let me do that real quick. Okay
password is
Okay, and
It's all level 153. There we go
We're gonna go
All right. That's okay, right?
All right. Oh shit. We're playing. Okay. Here we go
What was that?
Oh
Good fight. We both have the exact same idea. Uh platform pc
It's done. Well, do you want to put my pc specs in there too? Hold on. That's good. That's fine. That's fine. That's fine
That's fine. Okay, that's fine. Interesting. Okay, you got those horns
I wonder if you're also gonna have the um
That move the weird one. It's not aligned with the ruins bar
I actually was thinking that somebody was going to be very very upset about that, right property of germa 9-8
But yeah, like a watermark
Imagine watermarking you stream like that like I mean huge like across the whole thing
I'm gonna do that in a minute. Not right now
Hello
I want to just bow that's not bow
You got a big sword. All right
Oh shit. Oh shit. You do have that thing. Okay
Okay
Oh, no one's ever ready for it. But
That was the unfortunate triple tap. That was a triple tap. That was unfortunate
Okay
I like that build the build school
Add using xbox controller
Okay, germa boy
Germa boy
All right. What's the overrunner that this guy walks off of the balcony and dies quick before they come in?
It's pretty high. What are you doing?
You can hear us
Right now going through this viewer's mind
is
Fuck
I want to fight the streamer because I want to kick his ass on stream and embarrass him in front of an audience
But also I want to jump off to make the joke happen, right?
Holy shit. All right
Jump off the balcony you can do both
That was insane
It was actually a boss fight double whip humiliated. He pointed down. I don't care
Oh, I want to try that. All right
Um mug
mug mania
Mug maniac go to the coliseum. I want to go back to invasions were fun, too
We'll jump around we'll do this for like another 10 to 15 minutes
And then I want to do some more invasions because that was I that was really fun
I'm gonna go change the character to be annoying
Okay mug maniac. Hey, how are you good to go?
Good to go
Oh, I tried to bait him
Good game
I was hoping that I was gonna run and then he was gonna turn and run and I was gonna jump again
Again, don't ask for the password anymore. Is that too? Is that too?
hard to see
Killer andy got an interesting costume on killer andy
Here comes an average germa viewer
Well, I mean there's a lot of germa viewers in this spot right now because we're doing this right now
All right. Let me get a look at you. Okay
devil horns
Is that a katana? What is that moon veil? I'm not sure
Let's go
Can you wait you can
What happened? What happened?
I don't understand
He parried you
I got parried
He did the insta kill exploit
Oh
Okay
You know what the best part about that was?
After it happened
He stood completely fucking still like this
No moving no taunting just still
Completely still
You would think that oh you'd come up and like point at the ground and be like hey
No, he was over here
He was just doing this
It was so menacing and strange
I could see his yeah, I could see him breathing
All right. We already fought you
We already fought germa boy
All right. All right. Let me let me reload the area
Actually, maybe we should go somewhere else any new signs here. I guess we just fight
Let's fight boar
turn on cross region
I'm sorry
I'm sorry. I don't want to lag and then I don't want to die to lag and then blame you
I gotta pee
Okay after this one i'm gonna pee
Refill my drink come back and I want to do some more invasions. Here we go. I don't think people
Are ready for this move
I don't think people are ready for it. It's just stuff something. Did they just not you just don't see it that often
One more one more. That's a good game. Good game
I thought I was dead in that first one second when I missed and he went boom boom boom. I was like, oh it's over
fight
Well, this is hi germa
Are you different a different name?
You should do a few cross region. All right. I promise that before I turn the stream up I will do at least
Five to ten cross region matchmaking games promise
How you doing? I don't know what that is, but it looks interesting
Nice duck it. Oh, I got it
Good game. I think I actually ducked under that it was weird. That was the moonlit sword. Was it? Yeah
All right. Let me take a quick break
I'm gonna pee i'm gonna refill my drink and i'm gonna do some more invasions when I come back
See you guys in a minute. My camera's getting dark too. Hold on. We're back dude. Where the fuck is he?
It's fucking case. What a god
This fucking guy goes fucking brb and doesn't fucking come back like 10 minutes
British what
That's not british british germa
Was that british? That's weird. Okay, here we go the watermark on we will eventually
Cannot hear the game at all. I cannot all right two more
Okay, three more pvps
And i'm gonna and then I want to do some invasions for like a half hour
And then I want to do I want people to summon me to help me beat the boss that you're having the most trouble with
Whatever boss you're having a lot of trouble with
You get me in there and let me help you out here
better cool, so
Got an opportunity here. Is there any new signs?
Okay, zach of lothric
Sure, let's do it
melania
Okay, if you if you summon at least three people I will I will be in that fight with uh melania
Can you help me with the tibia mariner?
Don't summon me for the tibia mariner, but yes
Hello
Here we go
Sounds fun to me
Holy shit
What the fuck? Why didn't I not do my move?
Oh shit
I didn't want to get uh flawless
Okay
You are bad. What is your name?
Germa the enjoyer with like a bunch of zero
What is that name?
It's an average germa fan
No
Don't say that we have to
All right, two more two more two more two more. I promise two more
rampa supreme
Oh, this is a morgot cosplay
Remember my internet isn't working. I can't help
Well, the internet has internet's a weird place. It has a bunch of problems
Sometimes internet just doesn't work. Hey grandpa, how are you?
Let's do it
Oh, you're lucky. I didn't get that off the fight
What was that move? That fire move was cool
Is it still okay? We're good
All right last one and then i'm gonna do some invasions. I want to pick some cool places
Where my sign isn't showing well, we're gonna do this again
All right, we fought yzoram already doesn't mean we can't fight people more than once
or
the fist
Do co-op invasions with the taunter finger
Yeah, i'm what?
Let's do it all. I mean i'm here for a while. I'll be here for at least like another three or four hours
I want to get a good multiplayer experience today
I don't just want to do pvp for six hours
Right. I want to do invasions. I want to do summoning. I want to do help. I want to be double invasion. I want to get invaded
What is going on
Was that was I bad?
I mean, I I was just r1ing right like that's I was I was hitting r1 r1 r1 r1. That's like kind of bad, right?
All right. One more one more one more
Glintstone gelen. All right, your reviewers panic roll too much
Okay
Come on, let's see your sign
They learned from the best I was gonna say
It's true
Hold on like my cameras
That better too bright. That's good. Oh shit. I can play
Hey, are you ready glintstone gelen? I imagine you're a sorcerer sorceress. Are you doing the same thing?
Whoa, you're gonna get
I locked missed lock on
Good game. I knew I was dead. Fuck. Okay
flail
Need a little bit more reach panic rolling. I wasn't panic rolling. It was a good game. All right one more
This is too much fun to just do and that's it one more
This is actually the last one
Promise last one. I would have just skipped this one, but i'm going to try as hard as I can
Where's the sus guy? I'm sorry. I'm sorry imposter. We I don't think you're here. Okay. Well, we tried
No, i'm sorry. We tried
iver
sail
well
Eve
You know now round two
What do you mean? You know now, you know now round two
Wait, did I fight this person already? This is the poised guy. Oh, okay
They changed their name. Ah
I see
You know now round two
Do you know I mean I remember the move but I i'm probably gonna lose again
It's the one shot suck explode person. All right. Well, let's don't tell them. Don't tell them. Here we go
There's the gravity on this shit. Why don't you?
What was that?
Oh, come on
Oh, you don't expect that on second time do you
Oh, that was good good fight
That was really fucking close
I figured it was gonna happen and I had the health was not that high
That was a good fight. I was like if this gets here before I do then i'll win
All right. We gotta we gotta go against giga moth, right?
There's no way that I don't fight
How are we looking today?
Mog
Oh that range is not there
We're playing that game. We're playing that game
Why didn't I jump? Is that a stamina? Okay mog
It's so funny
How if you heal if you drank during a fight?
Like people from the audience is gonna start throwing shit
You know what I mean? Like that if they would be like
Cups
There'd be chairs people like from the stadium like it would be full of like fucking coffee cups and fucking hamburger
Containers and stuff if somebody were to drink to it. No
That's the one way to get everybody completely not on your side. Yeah, like popcorn. It would like pizzas
It would be a mess
Uh, sure
I knew what happened. It happens immediately too. It's like the second that you drink
There's just fucking popcorn containers chairs screaming people booing boo
Whoa, you suck
It's immediate
Now i'm not saying that because like I don't whatever it's for fun
Can you imagine if mog during the boss fight just like
That'd be so fuck i'd be funny. What the fuck just happened somebody shoot me from the other side of the map, bro
I know that move
Yo, oh
Pressure's on pressure's on
Dude, are you okay?
Did he all that for?
What the fuck did it happen? Did you unplug your router and plug it back in?
What happened?
That's so funny
Now all of a sudden he just started sliding around
Oh god, that's oh my goodness
You see what actually happened there
Is you you like you you like unplugged your router and plugged it back in and you pissed off a lot of people
And somebody threw a fucking full large soda from the audience
And they hit me in the back of the head and you you I didn't do that
Like somebody fucking hit me in the head with like a fucking box
One more like they hit me
If that was just a coincidence, that's really funny
And if I don't care whatever it's funny, uh, one more. That's it. This is why dark souls would ever be in esport
How cool would that be though?
uh
interesting
I mean, this is the one here. This is this is the best two out of three, right?
This is for the the world series
Let me make sure i'm ready
This is the worst game for pvp
I think this is really fun
All right. We good
That means we're ready
Round three. This is for all the marvels here
And i'm waiting for you to do it
ready
Good game
That was about to be really close
If you pulled me in
like one second earlier
You win good game. All right. How about one more? No, i'm not peeing myself
scam god
All right, you have scam in your name. I'm like kind of afraid to summon you
How about beep?
All right, I promise i'm gonna go invade after this it would be actually really cool
If from software
I know they have like the you collect fingers and phantom fingers, right or whatever. Yeah, there's like they had the covenants before
Having an actually ranked system in this game. I think would be really
right
Stat stamina
Oh
Oh, what a comeback
Oh, what a comeback. Damn
That was really that was what a great comeback. I was trying to get too fancy with it
I should have just went in and swung. That was yeah, that was
No, I didn't throw that was a great comeback. I ran out of stamina. I tried to dodge and I didn't no that's not throw
That was a great come that was great gameplay from the other player
All right, last one no
Yeah, this this person looks interesting
all right joseph
Joseph has a slab of concrete. It's a fingerprint shield resident sleeper. What does that do?
Why is it for it? Okay
What are you doing?
Um, wait, do I do we get to wait till he does all those like warcraft buffs or what can I attack him?
I don't okay. I'm just going i'm going in
What are you doing?
Joy tag are we ready? Oh this guy's a million poise. Never mind
Shit should have dodged in front of him. Oh
God that was close
That was a boss
That was a boss for me. That was really hard
That was a redditor. How can you tell when somebody's a redditor? I don't get it. I'm thinking about it
All right
I mean we have to summon the person that's called
Barf drinker, okay, and then that's it
You have a disgusting name you obviously have any outfit that you have on
Your name is barf drinker
And then I promise i'm gonna go do invasions. I promise
This is the last one
If I do another pvp summoning sign thing in this spot
right after this fight
And within five minutes of this one, you know, I don't care about semantics
I'll delete my channel if I do not
You know what I mean? Like if I do another one in a row right now in the next five minutes
All right barf drinker, but what's up?
Oh my i'm gonna get bm'd aren't I?
It's so stupid
He's throwing rocks at me
What the fuck what the hell is happening here?
How did you avoid that?
You dick. Oh dick
He wants to poison me and end it your cockiness is gonna be the end here for you
His cockiness is gonna get you killed man. I'm telling you this cocky behavior is gonna get you killed. I'm saying it
You want to end it with a fucking oh i'm gonna shoot him with the cannon
No, you're not this person's freaking me out. I don't know what they're gonna do next
Fine
I can play that game too. You know
I thought I was gonna kill him too. That was crazy
I'm telling you you that would have that was close
All right, i'm leaving
i'm gonna go to
Like up here the halong tree or something like up here
Yeah, like right up here on the roots
What was my record anybody keep track?
What was the uh kd there?
Come on someone someone in the group has become a lord
What?
What the hell does that mean?
Does somebody using this password beat the game?
That's so funny. Can I not invade anybody on the tree?
Somebody just ended the game. That's that's so cute that it does that
Wait and you get a buff too
Really? That's pretty cool
All right. Nobody wants to fight here
Oh, they're not people right here. There's so many people. Uh,
Soul level coming in here
That's impossible
Sometimes it says lord sometimes it says elden lord. It's really weird. Sometimes it says nothing
It's weird. I don't know what the fuck I was just doing
I just walked off. I for some reason thought I was in a different zone
I was very strange. I don't know why I just did that
It depends on the ending. Oh, that's cool
All right. Well, i'm gonna that was apparently a bad place to do this. Anyways, this is this probably more people here
Your level is very high. So it might be hard to fight people
Yeah, I mean I am
like end stage final ending
I was 150 when I beat the game right 145 maybe all right, let's do it
Where are they at defeat pea break?
What's going on over there? That was really weird. Okay
I hear footsteps. Where are they?
Are they on top?
Oh my god, that was terrifying
I guess they could just turn the stream on if they're if we have the same password
It worked. That was a really loud scream. I'm sorry. That was fucking horrible
Invasions don't work with a password. Oh, all right. Oh, come on
At okay, whoever I invaded
Oh, man, you would you probably went like this
No
Just barely missed came right down sliced in the animation landed right next to me
You must you must have been lining that shot up being like, oh my god
He actually doesn't know and you just miss
Oh that would that's so sad. I'm so sorry
I almost went off with you though. I actually almost fell off with you
The lunge attack never works. I honestly don't
I feel like it got worse
I remember in dark souls 1
and dark souls 2
Ball r1 was
Insanely good. I feel i'm terrified. I don't want to use it in these newer games. I feel like it's awful
I think I could never get it to work
It still is did they made it harder to hit then probably
What am I doing?
i'm trying to invade
Fair mazula should be non-stop invasions at this level. You know, that's a good point
Okay, we'll see if this works
Jump r2 is really good. Yeah jump the jumping r2 is that's one of the probably best move of the whole game
This is probably the best single move you can do to anything in the whole game
All right, 10 more seconds and i'm gonna go to fair mazula. All right fucking just die because like i'm not gonna be low
Oh
Reminder that you promised you would eat a glove if the three stooges were I didn't whatever that's doctored footage. I didn't say that
All right fair mazula
Where should I go? Just kind of right here
right on the bridge
Right here. Yeah passwords don't matter for invasions. Yeah, that's that makes sense though, doesn't it?
otherwise, wouldn't you kind of just be able to
farm invasions with your friends
I actually don't really know how this works, but
Really? You're having trouble finding people 150 here
Please germa help me beat the last boss. I'm on it right now and it'll be my first win
Yeah, i'm gonna do uh help
I'll try to help spam the finger. I go to the one of the other bonfires
150 plus is considered over leveled
Um, I don't I is it though. I thought maybe like 180 or something one. I was like
120 when I was here like 140
Who died?
Who died
What somebody's dead? Who the fuck are these people? What's going on?
I came in and somebody died
We didn't even bow yet
What happened?
The reason why I I zoned into the game and it was like, oh that person somebody died
I was like, oh am I gonna get i'm gonna get returned to my world. I don't know what happened
It said recuse and die. Was that another invader?
That was a different invader that died and then I came wow. We will look really stupid
Back-to-back invasions and the
I come in and just kind of walk around and die and I didn't even fight anybody
That was so bad. I just kind of fell off the edge and they just bullied me
Yeah, there are no rules in it. Okay. Yeah. Yeah, I gotta
I gotta get that into my head
I have to act like a from software
NPC i'm gonna show you exactly what that means
Okay, please don't go in the boss room
You're both there you are
Boy, this is the actor who is this? This is the actual person
What how many people are there? What the fuck?
Hey
What if he's gonna fall off?
Host plus two co-op helpers. Oh shit
Okay, I get it. I get it. So you I just gotta go for it. I get it. I did. Okay, that was confusing
Okay. All right. I get it. I get it. I get it. I get it. Let's go. Let's go. Let's go. I get it
No mercy
There's no honor dude. Stop. Okay. All right. Fine. No honor. There's no honor
Someone in the group defeated the shard bearer
Use the tree sentinel to your advantage. Oh my god, just stand next to it
Stand next to it and taunt
Tree sentinel is usually dead
All right, let's go
This is bullshit
This is it's bullshit. This is bullshit
Yeah, this is this is absolute. I look like an asshole
Wait, i'm invisible. All right
Where's the other player?
Are there two players?
I don't know how either one of us didn't get hit by that
What the fuck use the explosive flask?
I
I mean, it's so
If it was me
I'm just trying to think of this if this is me doing this like playing and somebody invaded me
And I was fighting the tree sentinel like I had just gotten here maybe like 10 minutes ago
I'm fighting the tree sentinel
And somebody invades me and drinks the exploding flask and lols me at the boss. I'd probably fucking be pissed
I would probably flip out. I'd be like
I would be so mad
That was me. It was a connection error. Ah, too bad. Good fight though
Uh, I did try to bm and cheese you and that's uh, that's what I deserve to be disconnected for that
Here we go. It's like you were waiting for me. You knew I was gonna spawn in this spot
All right, it's free sentinel alive
Fuck you killed the tree sentinel you guys played
All right. Okay easy
I was I don't know what I was just doing that far. I was trying to freak him out
Like I don't know why I figured like I don't know sometimes people do like the monkey see monkey do thing
Where he I jumped up on the balcony and jumped and people I i'm kind of one of these people
I'd be like, all right fine. I'll do that too. I'll show you i'm not an idiot. I can do it and then they jump up
All right, let's actually go for it
Duel so you don't get ganked and dunked on. Oh, I mean, it's fun regardless, honestly
Okay, i'm not sure if they've been here yet
Oh my god
Why I think it's I think I think I
This is so scuffed
They just hit a wall
Your sword hit a wall
I'm, so sorry if that was you that was kind of horrible
All right. I'm gonna go somewhere else somewhere. That's not just a bridge
On the rooftops here. Yeah, like over here somewhere somewhere weird
I like this
Is they gonna be jumping around here, especially in this area right there? They're gonna be jumping to that area
Here I can fight. It's a good spot. I want to fight somebody right here
Who's willing to do it? Let's get some signs right here. You're willing to do it. You want to fight me on this ledge
When I come back, I think they're up top
Okay, get up there
This poor guy
The birds were dead up here
Were you trying to run off the edge? I think he was trying to jump off. I think he was trying to to get killed
If he'd stayed up there, he would probably had a better shot
Why scarlet rot?
Uh, we got any signs here?
Okay, who wants to where's oh my god
baby dragon sure
try
Okay, how you doing?
So this is a 1v1 up here
Gotta be careful
One wrong dodge gets killed ready?
Let's go. What the fuck?
What the hell
That was insane
No disrespect, but when you laugh, why doesn't your face move?
What happened there though? That was fucking crazy
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. I want to do that again. What happened there?
It moves a lot that you
Oh, so she jumped off turned and did the move. That was crazy
I see. So that was the last that was the latch last ditch play
That was a oh fuck. I'm gonna fall. I gotta kill him now
Why doesn't your face move?
All right. Uh, who else we got?
All right. Yeah. Yeah, we're gonna we gotta we gotta bring in the barf drinker
I don't know what the barf drinker is gonna do up here, but good luck
Does your face not move? All right barf, let's go
He's going for the cannon
Oh barf drinker. Good try
All right
who uh
Who wants to go for it?
Okay
Who wants to go for it? Who wants to go for uh?
This is gonna be a disaster
You can wear a helmet a helmet of your choice
I don't know if I like that. I kind of like that. I kind of like this
All right, we gotta go. This is a grinch
Is there a block or a parry or anything?
Here we go. All right grinch, you know the rules. This is gonna take fucking forever
Uh-oh
I just baited it up
Damn it
oops
I was gonna go
That was fun. Let's not do that ever again. All right. I have a new game
the new game is
and you knock me off this platform
In one minute i'm gonna look like a total dickhead. You have to get you have to knock me off the platform in one minute
I don't how however you do it. Whatever means necessary
All right, how much strength do I need to put on some of these great shields?
Okay, I can put this one on this is 90. I know I need 100
28 30
20, okay
Uh, i'm going to go respec to 99 endurance
And like 30 strength
We're back. You have one minute to get rid of me. Uh, yeah my current stats here. Somebody remember this
Because I won't here we go
This is so annoying
All right 95 I need not mine
I need enough to hold two great shields in my hand 20 27 do it
30 strength should do it right
Soft cap is 80
strength per shield 35
60 is soft cap
60 60 60
And we use any weapon you can use anything you want you can use literally anything in the game
No, I want I this I think this is fine 80 is hard cap. Yeah, okay. I think this is fine
Am I going to be naked? No, absolutely not. Uh
I need the heaviest shield in the whole game
Probably one. It's probably this
Uh, what's the heaviest armor in the whole game? Probably this right the lionel stuff or is it the pumpkin head?
Old goat old goat everything. Yeah now I need
uh
Greatly increases maximum hp
I need
Uh the equipment. I don't care about equipment alone. I need
Extra enormously boost physical damage negation. What else vastly magic defense?
and under stamina
Good luck shield talisman. I have it on raises defense when hp is at maximum go upgrade the shields
I don't have it
Should I go upgrade these bolts plus 10? I feel like that's such a waste
At least like plus eight or plus nine. Yeah, I don't have the runes to do that
I have remembrances that i'm not going to use I got a lot
All right, i'm gonna both these shields are gonna get plus nine
Oh nice congrats
30 000 should do it
You can only block with one of them. I think the one on the right is more effective, right?
Let's see if I can do it
Which one is better the one on my right hand is more damage negation, right?
Upgrading shield does literally nothing for their defense. Does it do anything?
Just increases the damage. Oh, okay
Fingerprint shield has 100 physical damage
Makes them use less stamina when blocking it increases. Okay, i'm just gonna do it who cares
If we break your guard then can we yeah, you just however you can get rid of me
This one's good though, right?
This thing I think this is the one what I don't want to go get the other shield
And how how how easy is it?
Is it like simple to go get it?
Not very. All right. Well, i'm just gonna do which one is better for defense. This one's probably this one here
All right, i'm going for it
Hold on how many do I need?
I have access to every single stone in the game besides the plus 10 one
All right smithing stone
How many do I need?
a 15 30 29
25 i've said shitload of these
12 per step. All right. Well, we I don't have any plus one smithing stones
I need you don't even have the basic ones. You don't have access to smithing stones one. What the fuck
You missed out on a lot of early dungeons
Whatever. I'm just going i'm going to summon people
Zero exploration andy that's not true
So I got one in my back and one on my front. I'm good. Let's do it. Good luck everybody. You have uh, you have one minute
Get rid of me. I'll knock you off. Okay
I'm gonna get right in the middle
By the way, I can I can push you if I want to
It's just bob-omb's battlefield, man
Oh shit, not gonna happen
It was the first person. Yeah, but I shouldn't have been attacked. All right. I get it. I get it. I get it
I shouldn't be attacking
Congratulations, you knocked the guy off. I should I know attacking I can knock you off too, by the way stay still
Sorry
This is so annoying
All right, you got through the defense
Oh, you got it. All right, whatever then we said this sucks. All right, this one's for
This is this is dumb who cares
Oh, you gotta come in and notice. I feel like i'm in like the eighth grade
This is like the oh man, let's put on a bunch of gear and you try to knock me off
I'm in the i'm in the seventh grade. No
Hmm. All right fine. You get me
In the first move that must have walked out
Okay, this sucks
All right, this sucks. This is stupid. This sucks
That's all right. Whatever that was like whatever but wait, I have enough strength to put on
All right. Now i'm gonna play with like a big two-hander or something
I don't have any weapon upgrades. Fuck. I gotta go back. Okay, here's what i'm doing
That was awful two handing a shield. Yeah
i'm gonna do my other uh
shithead build
99 int you have so many mana flasks pvp. Yeah, but I wanted to be able to hold the same move down
Actually make you cast faster
That's true. I can't move
All right, okay
uh, how about
Okay, raise intelligence. Yeah
I like this one. They can stay on
uh this one
and um
fp
Okay, use the sore seal. Oh, that's right
This doesn't do
um
Yeah, the stats I want
Whatever. Okay. My equipment load is so bad
I'm still at medium. How that seems impossible. What?
Oh, I didn't have a weapon equipped
All right, just give me the staff
Now it's heavy load. Shit. Okay. Well, that makes sense
Okay. Now I want to do moves that I want to do the fp flask
They could sneeze and kill you I know but i'm gonna be able just to spam moves
If I touch somebody with a move they did
Where do I want to do this?
How about like right? How about where um?
Yeah, like down here. No, no one's gonna be there. Maybe like one of these uh, like the church or the hallowee tree
Or the foot of the forge
The image is not going to be that crazy. Well, whatever
Now if our result was fine, let's go here
Worst build that takes five minutes to set up
All right. I need to put on the fp stuff. All right, that's just an experiment. Let's see what happened
I want the
All fp consumption and the magic boost
Where is it?
Is there a magic boost one?
I don't think so
stamina
Oh, there it is. Okay. Okay. Here we go. This is so bad, but whatever
I'm just gonna be annoying. I'm thinking the moon
I have a ton of decks too. All right
What would be annoying here?
probably
this
Maybe like collapsing stars. That would be kind of annoying
I'll try this
magic downpour
That's a good idea. Actually i'll do that
Yeah, the moon's gonna take too long
founding rain of stars
or
I think i'm gonna try founding rain of stars. I feel like that's really irritating
Magic downpour i'll try it fine
Here we go
Do all mana flasks you didn't die in one hit. Oh, you're right
It's all right
I'm gonna confuse the person that I invade though because they're gonna hit me one time and i'm gonna die
All the way over there
Oh, you're so far away
How am I gonna get over there?
Use the finger again. How do I do it? How do I use the finger again?
Oh repeat
Ready? Here we go. Come on. I want to do my stupid shit. That actually might be really good. What about crystal release?
Oh, that's annoying too. Okay
This one is what does this one do? That's actually probably really annoying too
magic downpour
Magic downpour I think is the best one to do with this much intelligence
Quickly, hurry, hurry quickly. Oh my fucking god. I'm not even close to that
I'm going far away
This is a bad place to be too. This is gonna be great
Are you eating a glove if you're having this many invasions problems? No, i'm just in a bad i'm doing it in a bad spot
Here we go. This is better. All right. Here we go. Three two one action
What the fuck thought that was them
Where are they?
What no, fuck. I thought they were right around the corner. No
I thought they were gonna I heard the fighting right there. All right, i'm just fucking running at them. No more hiding
No more and my voice is doing the thing
Paramazula is too content. There's like too many bosses. Everyone that's here is doing one of the two bosses here
Where did it put me?
Where the fuck are they?
Are they above me?
How do I get up there? I don't I don't remember the layout of this place. I did it one time. How do I get up?
This does stairs go to these stairs don't go anywhere. I actually don't know how to get the fuck up there
God damn it this fucking inventory. I just put
I gotta get a fair mazilla fair mazilla is like chunk chunk chunk chunk chunk chunk chunk chunk chunk and there's two bosses
Everybody's doing it. No fuck this place. No, there's like three bosses like here here in here
And everyone's just gonna walk in the boss door
I gotta go somewhere else
My game just crashed. What happened? I'm going over here. I'm going i'm going to fucking lindell
frozen lake, ah
Let me try this. Let's see if it works. Come on. Where is it?
Where is it the inventory?
There you are i'm fucking ready let's go enough of this bullshit there you are
I just saw you you right here
Oh shit
Oh my god, why did I not what they didn't hit him?
How did that not hit him? It is him directly in the face
What?
the fuck
These moves suck. I have to okay
Somebody said dude all you did is effectively turn yourself into one of those shitty magic enemies. I died. I really am
an enemy
Oh
I really just turned myself into one of the the mages from ray lucaria that die in two swings
Not even one swing
All right, npc build
Collapsing stars i'm just gonna spam it
Minus one larval tier they give you like a hundred. It's fine
Okay, two more summon signs. Yeah. Oh, yeah, we will
I want to I want to get summoned for a cooperation after this though. Okay. Where are you? What the fuck was that?
This is a hacker. This is a hacker. This is a hacker. This is a hacker. He's blowing up the quick and leave quick
Quick get out. I have to leave. I gotta leave. He's gonna crash my computer. He's gonna crash my computer. I gotta go
Okay
They were gonna crash my computer. I had to run
It's a gene engine. Oh fuck. I need to back up my save. Oh fuck. No
I want I should I try a different area
But I how do I back up my save?
What how do I back my save up quick?
Where do I go to back the save up? How do I do it? How do I do it quick? Tell me
Defrag your hard drive. All right, i'm gonna defrag my hard drive. I'm gonna back up my save
I'm gonna you're fine. Okay. I'm gonna i'm gonna put it on a floppy disk
It's app data. Okay
Dude, dude, you gotta do a full virus scan now
All right. All right. I want to let's do some more pvp
Oh, no, who needs help?
I let me get it. Let me even I want to fight some people with this build
I want to see if I can at least kill one person with this. Hello. This is kaspersky security. How can I help you?
I'm using my elven ring game
and they
Did a bunch of exploding spells
What do I do?
That was insane though. What the fuck?
Okay, uh, let's do science. All right our speed wagon
Um
Yeah, I tried to summon you already didn't work
All right. How about you? This is gonna be so bad now
I mean who knows I might be I should actually kill somebody
Well at 153 soul level I was more concerned about my like computer crashing
Why do I have like five vigor? It's because this is
I was doing an invasion build where I would go in and try to kill people in like one hit
I got embarrassed three times in a row
and then I uh
And then and then I had to come back here
They seem friendly. You should still back up the save. I I mean as long as they're not, you know
Try to get mad. I don't know this cross region stop west to east coast
Uh, i'm sorry. It didn't work
There's a classic barf drinker
All right captain luke harrier
You're gonna die twice and spend 10 minutes trying to fix the npc build. Oh, I just realized you have to hit me once
All right, just let's go
What the fuck? All right. I'm done. I'm done with this build. I'm done. This build is just
I just why am I using magic downpour by the way magic downpour is literally a serial block skill
You get it you use it once and then you fucking delete it from your bar. You never put it back on
This is no reason to put it on
There's no reason to put this back on. All right, i'm just let's go the let me go. Let's
So bad
I just wait
I'll be right back. Nobody move
All right, let me see. Let me what do I got my
Okay, it was 50
I believe it's 50
Or like no 30 maybe like 35
Let's do it. I gotta be one. We'll do 35. It sounds better
Okay
25 decks should I even have decks at this point? I probably yeah
65 intelligence
Wait, that's including items that I had on isn't it? I think that's kind of I think that's pretty good
Does not include this does not include items. I think that's because of the baby rattle was what was my decks?
Uh, it was 25 65
Oh my god, I have no points in endurance. That's why
All right. Um mine is a dump stat. You can just chug for more. Yeah, I gotta pee again
pretty
565 I think this is fine. I'm actually I want like 30
30 mind
30 30
That's fine. Yeah, that's that's pretty much where it was before
I could wear something better than this though
Back to reality here
It's not the right one. Okay, here we go
It's time for a couple more pvp duels after I pee
I'll do one before I pee same place
Have I been playing for four hours?
That's kind of blown by
I must be having fun
I don't know. I just summoned somebody I think
Tired
I don't know tired low
Oh, I have such these spells suck. It's okay. I really only need these two
Tired hollow. Okay, it's because of ho
Oh, that was rough
Oh good game. Damn it
Good game. I thought you were gonna come in a little bit further
Were you gonna help people fight bosses? Yeah, i'll do this for a little bit longer. That's that was a tuba reaction to
Becoming aware of that europina
who else
Luna
Pick me strong spells, but you should help people with milania
I will stand and I will help people outside of different bosses. I will that sounds fun
I guess I could take this right wondrous physique blaster. Okay
We good
You good. Are you good? Hey
Okay, here we go
Good fight. Yeah, i'll do cross region in a minute
Stealth archer. I don't know but I don't know about this one. This one's kind of freaking me out
Does that mean that the character is going to be invisible and they're going to shoot me with bow and arrow?
That's kind of sus
Dude, you got this is the best class in the game. Hey, what's up? All right. What do you got stealth archer?
I get it. I can see you you move into clothes. I you shot in the sky. I'm so confused
Okay, i've never nobody plays with bows in this game, huh?
Bow seems so cool. God damn it
Those are cool looking they're like little crystals
Fight that was actually really cool. What are those arrows?
That was really cool. They're rainbow stone arrows. That's really all I actually kind of want to play as that character
Oh
My computer crashed
Did my whole computer crash?
Come on
Can you level up a few? Do you have to be the exact same level?
I don't think you have to be the same exact level
Was it like it's like five level range 10 level range the level? Oh level doesn't matter with the password. Okay
So wait, so that means that people could I could be fighting people that are way way lower than me, right?
Technically. Yeah. Yeah, I thought I got banned. I was like, oh no, I saw the pop-up the second pop-up and i'm like
Oh, no
I have not used seeing a second pop-up window. I think that was just an actual crash
Which so what happened between dark souls 3?
Sekiro and this game
because
game crap like hardware
Those didn't happen in sekiro
They didn't happen in dark souls 3 either. I don't remember it happening
Did the game crash one time when I played?
Because open world all the shaders maybe yeah
All right. Yeah, let me go p i'll be right back
back p
I'm back
Okay, so we'll do a few more of these pvp rounds and then
Uh, we'll do some summons to do bosses. That sounds fun. It's cross region on
No, that's i'll end with that
We'll do that like in an hour or two
Hello and the audio back on
Alrighty
Cross region, you know, let's just do it now
I'll put cross region on do it from here. Oh, it's like an actual setting settings. Okay
Uh cross region perform matchmaking. Okay
Do I have to reset of the game?
I wonder if it worked. We'll do like a few more five to ten more
What do you?
okay, uh, should we go against should we go against the jeremy elbertson with the um
Let's go. Are you wearing is it wearing the same armor that I am?
Clone fight is this the real jeremy elbertson?
All right, just going for it. You get the big shield and think that shoots fire. I know that for a fact
Walk forward with it
Oh, I got through the shield
Oh, you've no idea how badly I want to backstab
He's just running
Get over here. How's it charlie brown?
Does a charlie brown yell in this game?
I've never heard that before
Oh, it's already on okay
based buffalo
Now the bow user
The bows are cool. Hold on. What else we got? Uh
based buffalo
I think so. Let's try it
I think it's the bow is fun. Nobody's using the black bow for some reason
Uh sl means soul level. I know it's probably wrong for elden ring, but
Okay, I need to put that on my bar, too. Right? Like let me just say hello
Okay, here we go
shit
Oh
close
Oh going for chip damage. That's what it is
Good fight good fight one of those arrows kills me so if I had of them would really
Is it those those not do that much damage? I wasn't really paying that much attention
I was trying to see how much they hurt for
That was an interesting build though. How do you build a character?
So you'd be able to use a great sword and a bow effectively at the same time just
quality
Does that work?
The character's ugly
Why do you just take damage? I like that one you're moving around kind of weird
I don't know
I don't like how weird you're moving around. I don't like how weird you're moving around. I don't like this
Where is this person? Okay. Um
Oh, no, don't drink
All right, but seriously though like what's even happening the guy was connecting from the moon
Cross region omega low cross. I know but whatever it don't matter
I like your name birdbrain
Oh, come on. What the fuck
Why?
Why do I keep crashing?
Uh, that's not that's not the multiplayer. That's just the game. I think your hard drive is all no my hard drive is not all like
Bunged up. All right. It's fine. It's a virus. They're sending it to you through multiplayer
Crypto miner installed
Uh-huh. I know I know I know I know
What's the password?
Cheese doctor cheese doctor. This is ramander from the toontown national bank that you still owed chad a debt to play toontown
I'm gonna say okay if this crashes again, i'm just gonna go do boss summons because what the hell what is this?
Do I dare?
summon
Do I dare summon hog rider?
that mask that
Torch interesting
Welcome to the game hog rider. You're gonna fight me with a torch. I feel like this is gonna go
Oh my god, this is fucking weird
Is this weird?
Can you upgrade the torch?
That was cool. That was really good fight. That was really cool. That weapon was actually
Can you actually play through the game with a torch?
Tvp and from software games is atrocious because of netcode
And I mean it actually really hasn't felt that bad tonight. It really hasn't it felt pretty good actually
But yeah, I mean sometimes yeah
I don't know what what is this? I don't I don't know what that says
First has like the bug stuff
sorcery
Hello
Wait hell
You can't say hell in from software games hell
Wow, there's no reason to take it seriously, but it's fun
Okay
Do you think that from software pvp would be more interesting to you?
if
You could not use
any
Like outrageous weapon arts. What if there were no weapon arts? Would you think it was if there were no weapon arts?
Would it be better or would it be boring? It would be boring. That's interesting
That's the fun part
But then what how come there's um
This game is these games are so popular. Oh, we couldn't get you. Sorry
We try to get you
unknown
none
Seems like this is gonna be a tough fight
um
How did people
Can you connect real land and play elden ring like is it possible?
Did you even do that?
No, but if you were on the same, okay
If you did no cross region
And you were playing from the same room on the same kind of like us west or whatever. Would it be fine?
the same router
Get to it. Here we go. All your clothes are off now
I don't know. I don't know what this person's doing. They're freaking me out though
They had a full costume on now. They're naked
Holy shit
Why did I almost kill you?
What was what was with the naked?
Was that to have more than
What was it? It was funny
It's a min max build
They were trying to flex on you. It was an ego boost
Well, you know, they almost did it. So it's a I it's probably more a reason
I think we already fought shpee
gravity plus fall guy
I'm interested
Does that mean you're just gonna walk off the edge?
You're gonna hate to see you fans
Hey
What are you talking about? I got it's i'm cross region right now
So what does gravity plus fall joke mean? I wonder if he was in his equipment menu
I don't think so
What do you wait?
That was
He was no way was he in an equipment menu?
Maybe he realized that he was like, oh he's this guy's using the stupid ass bullshit. This guy's doing red as mastery
What a chump. All right. Well, i'm gonna put a different weapon on
You beat him up before he could do the joke
I think I think there was ample time
There was time
Let him do the joke
I I held the router's mastery for a long time and then I fired it
That wasn't a bad fight. Whatever he was in the equipment. I've done that before
cool
What the fuck
You're gonna do it again, aren't you? I gotta be ready
This is a sheep
Oh that hurt
I didn't even know that moves in the game. That's crazy. Good fight. That was actually pretty interesting bill
So you drink, uh
the stamina
Blast and you can just roll for like a minute. All right should be
augustin augustine sure. It's a weapon art for what weapon?
Literally roll so I didn't want to talk because I didn't want to burp
Let's do it. What the hell?
Why do they just blow up?
Holy shit, that move is actually kind of ridiculous
Oh good move
That's that move is broken pvp
Like you can't dodge it it just glues to you
That was a good fight though. I don't think you can dodge that
Can you dodge these?
That move is kind of broken. You have to roll it. You have to dodge it, huh?
Stars of ruin are a better version. Let me see
Do I have stars of ruin don't what about founding rain of stars?
These moves are useless. What the hell am I going to do with these?
Let me try founding rain of stars. I feel like that'd be weird
and
The arc onto
Get rid of this
Let's do the gravity pull
From selen's quest line. Okay. I wonder how this works. I feel like this is gonna be really annoying to deal with
All right bird brain my computer crashed when I tried to summon you last time. That's kind of scary
Bloody crow. Let's try it again bird brain. I hope you don't crash my computer again
Because i'm gonna fight you. I actually I really want to fight you. Don't crash my computer, please
please
We're good. We're good
You know what happened by now?
They probably crashed
But bird brain, i'm really sorry. It's the world does not want us to play against each other in elven ring
Yeah
I'm sorry. I think you crashed
I just our computers can't interact with each other. I might jump
Okay, like off the balcony or
What does that mean?
Who is this ghost guy that keeps running? I don't know man
All right, I might jump
You will jump
Hello. Sorry. I was like afk putting on a lip bomb
Shit I didn't get it
Actually pretty good. It's a ton of denial
Bat roll, that's not good
Oh shit. Oh, no bat roll. Must have maybe an equipment issue
damn
Okay. Good game. They only jump
Oh, I get it
Right. Okay
That makes sense now that I think about it. Okay
Uh, sure bloody crow
They're audio issues. This shouldn't be
Maybe one of the good when the crash happens screwed up nice grip
It's okay, it's kind of a disney movie comic relief character
Oh got into the magic brain
Holy shit, what's happening? I just exploded
Whoa
This exploded
This you're a little late on the snap though
You were a little late. I was already disappeared. You had to get it after this last hit boom
Because otherwise i'm already gone
That was a really cool move though
No, good game. Good game
Uh, who's next?
I was the other guys
I don't contextually. I don't know what that means
I was the other guy
Who else from the top rope? He's got the joker makeup on
perfect
Uh, bounding rain of stars is actually really good
It's just irritating
Put on your um
No, what do you got? I feel like this is a talent show. All right, what do you got for us?
Whoa, you don't have a lot of health
Hit swing
It'll hit you that move is absolutely broken in pvp. That's the new metal that thing is undodgeable
It happens so fast
Dodging that it's I mean like maybe it's just weird
All right to the next person I summon I apologize. I'm gonna be a total asshole. I just need to experiment
So i'm really sorry whoever this is. All right. I was the other guy. Sure fine
I just let you know that i'm gonna i'm gonna be a total uh total dick here
I'm just curious how this works. I mean if you if you can beat me with this, I mean then
While I do the kind of annoying cheese experiment
I could dodge it
Br josh, where's your sign?
See it br josh
It hasn't shown up. Oh, I could give you a password
All right. I was the other guy. Here's the why are you doing that?
Why why can you interact with that? I don't understand. Why did you pull this? What was the point of that?
You can interact the stuff in my world
All right. Here we go. Ready? Good luck
Dude, this is I mean honest to god. That's so horrible. That really is annoying especially in the very beginning
This is too active with non viewers
Actually, really good try though. That's really irritating
Yeah, you know, that's that's a really good point. We should go somewhere else
So we don't like kind of mess up other people's thing going on here
It's a good point. I want to place it like nobody would be but that's not
Bad to fight in go to a secret spot
Yeah, we'll go to um
What are the?
Alaketh area. No, there's a lot of people there
lake of rot underground area
This might be annoying to get back to volcano manor is good. Yeah, let's do
What about like right out here?
This isn't I mean, it's kind of an there's a lot of like
embers floating around but
Now that's that's too much. We need we need a gamer. We need to be able to see things
Turtle church, that's a good place
Yeah, that's a good one
Like right here. Yeah pat all the info is on the bottom right right here
We're inside the church
Right here. I don't want to do I don't want to accidentally kill the turtle
You guys are gonna make me founding rain of stars on the turtle and he's gonna die
All right, right here is good
Seems pretty open
Yeah, I'd say right here
uh
By josh get a password josh. I'm very curious
All right. I I don't want to show you guys the password though. So you guys can't see this
Okay, so there's multiplayer password and then there's a group password
Can I should I just change them both or keep keep one? How does it work? Is it just okay?
All right, new password is
I'm almost set
uh
Josh you understand that like the last letter can't fit so just just do just write it out and then with no last letter
All right, let's go
Josh what are you playing as?
I don't know why I thought that was I thought that was you
We got vr. Josh is uh is one of the mods for the sign
No, would you uh put your sign? There it is. You're one of these
puke barf people
All right
Puke people
Let's go. You look so sad
Let me get a good look at you
You're why you're so small
Is this weird or you okay? No, that was weird. I was like, why am I so much taller than you?
All right drink drink drink drink drink
I don't know that that was a weird face. No drink. No, that was not part of it. That was not part of wait
Hold on. We're not doing it yet
Just um, all right. We're doing it
All right. All right. All right. All right. Wait, let me get the point. Let's wait till the poison runs out
Okay, it's about poison. Let's go
All right
E modem
E moded
All right. This one's for real. This one's for real. This one's the real one. This one's for real for real for real
So let's do it for real
That right there oh not here where is it
You should refund that
I mean that was a fight, but that wasn't a real fight. Now. This is actually going to be the real one
Sometimes takes a second
No refunds. I mean you bet
You did bet
Here's your sign. Come on. Where is it? Where is it? I don't know why I can't see the sun
I turned it off
Oh shit. Okay
That right there. Yeah. All right. This one's for real do whatever you want buff wise
You want to buff up get ready? This is the real one if you want to bet by the way you can
Do anything you want?
But before we do anything there is an asshole over here. That's it. There's like
I'm not gonna attack you but look there's like this weird shit going on here. Let me take it here
All right go
Watch the stamina. Oh environmental problems. Oh my fucking god. Don't be an idiot
No
Oh
That was close
What is this build you've got frost poison and rot what is or blood that was that's insane
That's actually a really cool build. All right, two out of three. It's two out of three josh
You know how it works
That counts as one
It's really yeah, it's a really cool build. Oh my gosh
No
Vr josh, why did you hack me? Oh my whole computer might be going down here same spot. I'll be back man
It really does not like the multiplayer, huh? That's like the third fourth crash of the night
All from multiplayer. I somehow got sent to your world too. Well, don't mess anything up
Don't don't take my peaches. Don't dig holes everywhere
I'll get out of there. I'll get out of there. I don't want you there. Yeah. Okay
Yeah, I mean other mods in that that I put it in the mod chat
other I mean if any of the mods
Are watching you want to just I could summon you
Give me a second. I could put it in the other chat too
You need to watermark the stream already
Yeah, but I mean it's like I'm
I will I promise
So we're still best two out of three
Let's see if we can get this work
New there is currently a new password while I
I've got a little thing going on here with vr josh
There is a paragraph over here in mod chat from vr josh like just fucking pissed
There's a ton of spelling errors
It's like three paragraphs like talking about my build is like shit and i'm like a fucking lazy meme build or something
That's a lot of words here, man
All right, so a different approach this time
That's a fortnight emote, right? It looks like it here we go luck. All right
Oh fuck, all right, this is bad
Oh shit
Oh, all right. All right. All right. All right. Okay. I got I got I got it. I got it. I got it
I got it. I got it. I got it. All right, let's do it
Erica
Got a new idea
It's gonna be tricky
Yeah, all right, let's go
This is the one this is the big one
final fight, uh against vr josh
who is a um mod
Oh, I need to use the thing
All right
back to the uh
uber nurak I gotta use i'm not gonna say on stream because
Oh, she's definitely watching different weapons, too. You got tons of builds
I'm like one build andy over here. All right, let's do it. Here we go
Well, let me all right on the map. It's right here
Okay, one two three. I got a new plan and here we go
Oh
Oh close, holy shit
That was really close. Wow
It's holly here. Stop fucking spinning around. You're gonna make us sick
All right. Hold on. See you she's this this she's let's see if she's available
All right church of vows
I this is gonna be tough. This is gonna be tough. All right
Yeah, let me all right. I think this is on
Hold on. She's still like getting the game. Oh, do you need help? I'll be right back. I'll show you
Are you in the game visually on the way? That's two out of three
Oh loser sleeps on the couch. Oh my fucking god
That's so fucking stupid
Josh you want to go one more time? Well, uh, while she gets ready or anybody else. I mean, oh, let me uh,
Losers asleep in the dog bed. Let's go. This one's just for fun
Are bleed builds allowed? Yeah, anything's allowed. This is this is vr. Josh. By the way, this is not holly. Holy shit. That's fast
Oh, there's no more magical power in that thing. Here's the thing. I think I think holly's actually going to kick the shit out of me
We'll see we'll see
Sorry, I was trying new weapons
I love that when they just kind of go like I I don't understand. Why does it not work? I'm moving
I'm i'm twisting with my arm
You bet on me. Uh, this is just for fun. Do not throw i'm not gonna throw
Yeah, you can use anything. Here's the thing though. I've
Been a big fan of watching holly play through this game
Seeing a lot of her playthrough
I know all of her moves
I know all the moves
Are these are these us?
I think no, these are the people that's playing here. Okay. All right. Do I need to use the thing again?
Maybe reload go against dr. Schmeichsen
uh there
Dr. Schmeichsen
Did you put it down? Oh, sorry
I know I didn't do it until before this stream either one sec
Okay. Yeah, it's kind of confusing before you when I never did it for the first time. I was like what the fuck do I even do?
He's recharging. What do you think like what what do you think that means? They're like going doing like drugs
Oh band name band name
Let's go. I'm going for it. The fucking game crashed. God damn it. All right, let's
Let's try it again. Why is this game hate being online? I just want to play elden ring multiplayer
Why does this hate? Why does it hate me so much? Oh, no, you just got hacked
Imagine I summoned holly and and she just fucking started floating around and doing the exploding thing
You're like
What the fuck?
All right, we're gonna go for it again after this you can summon me to fight some bosses and then i'll turn stream off
Whatever. I swear. I have a girlfriend my game just crashed. Haha
That's actually really funny I have to prove it okay
Okay, same thing
That was weird that happened to after I said, uh accepted it. That's weird
Oh, wait, you guys gonna be able to see the password if I do that again
What are you looking?
All right. Here we go
Now don't crash
All right. You ready?
I bet on germa, but I hope holly kills you
Let me know when I can stop covering my eyes
I'm just kidding. I'm kidding. I'm kidding. Okay
Okay, so how this works is is we bow first
Okay bow
Ready? Oh shit
Okay. All right. All right, you got dragon moves, right?
Okay
What's that? Oh i'm out of stamina. All right, I gotta get stamina. Hold on. Oh
Come here
Oh
Good first fight good first fight
You're cheesing your own girlfriend
I i'm trying to win
Okay
I'm trying i'm trying to win
I'm cheese. I
Is this not this cheese move?
All right again, let's do it again. That's fun
That gave the dragon hand
That does a lot of damage. I thought the bet was for
black ops 3
What are you talking about?
Okay. All right
I'll put it down again. Let's do it again. This isn't rust
Careful, dude, you're gonna end up maidenless
Get out of here. Get that out of here
Oh, that's bad
That was all right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right. All right
All right
Okay. Okay. This is the one she kicked your ass
Yeah, what she doesn't know is
I mean, she's literally right there. So she can she of course, you know, it's just literally gonna hear me say it
I don't know if she's gonna be able to handle the founding rain of stars
Gonna be tricky
All right. This is the one
Do I need to do this again? Oh, I the the password's already leaked password leaked. This is the last one
Yeah, the password was yummy food, but you can't put a d at the end
That face when no gamer girlfriend to beat my ass and elden ring pvp sad
All right. You ready? Let's go
All right smart
Holy that does a lot of damage. Don't use all your stamina sweetheart. Don't use all your stamina
That doesn't count that doesn't count. What the fuck this doesn't count
All right, we gotta get rid of these people
Okay, i'm gonna heal and then take me down. All right, hit me once
Okay, hit me one time
That's not fair
Yeah, I won't take me down to where I was where where was I before?
Okay
Let's just heal just heal the full health
All right, heal the full health you got full mana
Oh, that's it
I missed. Oh my god. I missed
It's all right. Sorry. That's good fight. Good fight. Good fight. That's a good fight
You you still you cheesed and still lost I look I thought she was gonna do the lightning move again
I thought she was gonna do this. I was afraid of it. Good fight. Good fight
All right. All right. All right
That was really fun
That the dragon claw does so much damage. That's like a really good move. Is anybody anybody else in the uh,
mods or community leaders or anything
Want to give it a go?
Maybe doesn't look like it. Oh it leaked right? All right. Let's let's do some boss. Uh,
Clean up. Let me help you guys clean some stuff up
That's fun. Thanks for playing holly. You're our josh also
Please help me with the tree sentinel
Yeah, sure
Free sentinel got it. Where is it like right here? There's a level cap. Oh
I'm sorry. I don't think it can't work. I'm sorry that you have in trouble with the tree sentinel
Where can I go not with a password?
Wait, really?
All right, put it down. Let's do it. I get the the the password is you saw it already but
Uh yummy food with no d
It will work
Let's do it
Where where should we where do you want to put it?
Y um, oh the password right? I gotta change it on here. There you go password yummy food with no d
Okay, so who needs help put down your sign. Oh, okay, but wait
If I put my sign down here aren't there like 15 000 people that can just click it
How the hell is this gonna work? Okay. Well, I need a private password
Okay. Well, I mean why would i'm gonna put my i'm gonna put it down here
Okay, the person that wanted to have me help you with the um
You want to have me help you with the tree sentinel? There it is
Right down here. I think you need their password
And that's not a bad idea
I don't even know what that person's name was
You can only be summoned by people with the boss still alive in the area
Oh, okay
I think it was me. All right. Yeah
Or zappy i'm standing right here
My sign is right there. Let me go kick that tree sentinels ass for you. Let me go take care of it. Take care
I don't see the sign you have the password on. All right, of course zappy. This is very important
You're gonna go into multiplayer
You're going to go over to over here multiplayer password
It says multiplayer password. You're gonna put yummy foo
Right there at the top
Yeah, you would have been using playstation. Um
All right, you got it
I think you got it. That's not me
Oh great
Okay, bubble pop
Bro, you've already burnt the urn tree that what even is here
I'm supposed to be helping somebody
What do you want me to help you do?
Where are we? All right, you lead the way you lead the way where we're going
I'm following you
We've got invaded
All right. Well, good luck
Why does it make the inception sound?
Holy shit, that's not fair
What the fuck
What the hell was that? That was insane
What
All right. Where's core? Where's core zapper? I want to help you beat this boss
That was ridiculous. That guy drank like five potions and then killed us instantly
All right core zapper core zapper. Don't tell anybody. This is just for you
with a map
This tree right here
No, right. Yeah that tree right there core zapper
Right there
What I want you to do
Is I need you to do this for me
You could not do cross play
What?
Oh, you're not on pc
Oh, that's too bad
You're not on pc
You are on pc. Okay. Well then
Core zapper. We're good
All right what I want you to do
Core zapper go into your uh, your multiplayer inventory
And you're going to this fur calling finger remedy
You need to use this
It'll do like a ding and then that will let you see summoning signs on the ground
I'm going to put one you might it might take a second or two
Get a password from him
Okay. All right. Yeah. All right
Can one of the mods uh dm core zapper or core zappy and get get a password so I can put it in here
Why are you talking to him like your tech support? I'm just trying to help
And in the mod chat, uh, what's the password?
Help me with godfrey
Make a group password. Yeah, I mean I gotta get in touch with him
Yeah core zapper. We'll get we're gonna get you in touch with the mod
By the way core zapper. Let's i'll beat the whole game for you
Let's just go boss by boss
Imagine this word boss by boss by boss. What's core? Am I saying your name wrong?
C o r z. What is it?
Is something say something in the chat? Oh, it's in the mod chat. Okay. All right
Okay
I got the password. Don't tell anybody that password core zapper. Don't tell anybody. That's just for you and me to have
See if I can see it on the ground
So now i'm no no. Okay. Now i'm gonna put mine down right here
You should be looking for it looks just like this. You're gonna go over to it
You're gonna you're gonna click it summon me to my world. I'll be standing there
And then I will go and i'm going to destroy the tree sentinel for you
I didn't leak it. What are you talking about? I didn't what do you mean leaked?
This is it. Okay, this is you
All right, you ready?
So what you having trouble with this? Let me take care of this. Let me take care of this for you
Wait, why is the tree sentinel alive?
The tree sentinel shouldn't be alive right now
Why did you need help doing this?
You're just you're destroying it
Oh, it's new game. Okay, it's new game plus plus plus you're welcome
Dude, we just did that in tandem. That was awesome. That actually was really cool. I can't believe we just did that accidentally
That was cool. All right
Wells needs help. Please help me with the fire giant. You got it
Uh mods who have said that?
Let me say, please help me with the fire giant
We need to get a new password
I'm gonna put it right outside the door
Is my where's the horse?
All right, I took all this off right put the sign directly out in front of the door
Which is I gotta go this way across the chain, right?
I mean, yeah, somebody wanted help with godric and I said I would do it
Oh, you know what? It seems like a lot of people need help with fire giant
So i'm just gonna put it right here and the password
um was uses
I mean like a like a 12 piece mcnugget or something. That's what the password was
It's right outside of the fire giant if you need it, it's gonna be hard not being able to get on the horse
Oh, whatever should help with eldenbeast too cams blocking the password. Uh, it's 12 one two
No spaces 12 piece
Please help me with godfrey. I've shat my pants six times. Uh, i'll go up there after this
Remember, you gotta use the item
You have to use this thing. There we go
Stuck on millennia. I'm probably gonna make millennia harder for you
Okay, this
All right female germo ready to do this
Jesus
All right, let's get the fire john. All right, somebody invaded us but we're in the door already so they have to leave
All right, let's go
Nice work nice work keep it up bully gotta get the bully watch out watch out
No
Dude, i'm so sorry
Oh, no, that was going so well. That was going so well
Oh, that's so sad
I hope you beat it. But now the boss has two times as much help
That's unfortunate
Oh, i'm, so sorry
That was going so well, too. All right. Well, I don't know if he's still there but
I'll put it back down
That's actually yeah, that's bad
Help me with the festival. I have not been able to reach that area
Somebody said this is probably what superman felt like when he first got his powers
Superman I need help my come help me superman. You're gonna help me kill this person superman
Help me kill this bird. Well, superman didn't kill any. All right that superman didn't kill anybody
It wasn't superman helping people kill people
Superman, I really don't like this person. Could you like use the laser eyes and vaporize them?
Summon signs back down. What about your pve spells? I honest. Oh, wait a minute
There you go. Uh, this is probably my best move that I have on this character
besides um
Icecrack at least i'm stuck in the dryer
Okay. Yeah
You're in a trans drama. Okay
Let's go
You ready? Is this the same person?
Are you guys ready?
Don't invade anybody, please. Can you avoid this attack?
I don't think I can you can't avoid this, right?
How do you avoid that lag back leg back leg back leg back leg?
Easy easy easy. Watch it. Oh my god. I'm I'm the one that had to watch it. Did you?
I don't think I was even hitting them that place to be right now. I don't know. There's an edge nice work
Boss holy shit. Okay
What the fuck
All right, you can handle it. You can handle it from here. You can handle it from here
I don't know why this keeps happening. Why does it keep happening?
Does their game keep going because I mean that you're at phase two
Are you telling me with commander neil commander neil?
Maybe just find another. Yeah, I don't know what that that's unfortunate. I'm sorry everybody
We'll go. Uh, we'll go somewhere else. I did say somebody wanted me to help with godric. Let me do that
I'm just accidentally griefing people
Fire giant has notoriously shitty netcode. Oh, that's unfortunate. All right, let me help this person with godric
I need help with neil as well
It seems like a lot of people are having trouble with neil
After godric i'll come up to neil
Uh millenia is gonna be tough because I feel like i'm gonna make that harder for everybody
It's the anti-cheat. That's wreck wrecking havoc
They said godfrey. I know somebody said godric
Somebody said godfrey, but somebody said godric a long time ago. They've probably been sitting here waiting for it
How could I make that a fight harder when you get summoned the boss gets more?
Health so if you die if I get killed by water, uh dance
In the first 15 seconds
The boss does not reduce their hp. They stay at like times two hp 50. Yeah
So if you go in if you let's say you play with your friend and you're both trying to kill, uh, millenia really badly
You summon your friend
Millenia has 50 more hp your friend dies. You're still in the game
You just made it 50 harder for you. What's the password 12 piece?
What why what's going on here respect to the?
Raya npc mod use all power consumables and launch out the comet azura at every bus
That's actually true. I could yeah, but that's kind of just like cheating, right?
Oh, you can't walk into the okay. Can't walk into the bus room
12 piece i'm going to godfrey after this
Does nobody actually need this?
If you're here and you need this to be done multiplayer use a furl calling finger remedy
You should see my make sure your password is set. It's also in that menu up in the top, right?
Oh my god, uh, it is the multiplayer password not group password
You look like albert wesker seven minutes
I I I don't know. Is it everybody? I
Whatever, please help me with the tree sentinel. I'm level nine
Well, you just you have to level up a little bit
All right, summoning sign is going right here
People are saying I need help with godric not the shade one this one
I'm level nine
So you made a new character?
And walked out the front door, that's so funny. All right, jesus
Hey
Amen. Yeah, it's me jesus christ
Let's kick his ass somebody invaded us
I thought you couldn't happening who's doing that move? Is that you? Is that jesus?
Stop who's talking?
We're gaming over here, man
I love this fight so much. It's so good. Oh stay alive
No
Just back off and heal. How can I not hit this guy?
Dude, what the fuck is happening?
I hope you can beat it because this oh this happens every single fucking time. Wait, they're a hacker
What do you mean?
He wasn't taking damage. I was wondering what was with that spell
That spell was fucked. Yeah. I was like why why i've not seen that spell that was fucked
He wasn't taking damage
Okay, does anybody need to help? Uh, I don't think can we even complete one of these encounters?
Am I gonna have to go back to invasions?
He had speed
I'm like doing callouts
And like oh back it up. Heal it up. Heal it up
Got your back
Dodge it dodge it
This guy can't take damage and just rings are everywhere and he's just walking around
I need help getting to godric. I'm trying to run past the ballista
Actually, I can have I can help with that. He was casting instantly. That was so weird
It's crazy. People use like the okay
like
People have like diablo trainers
It's like oh, yeah, I got this character. I did diablo whatever I can spam frozen orb a thousand times in a second
Anybody need this?
Like I don't think anyone's doing it
That guy wasn't hacking dude. That was actually jesus
Oh, yeah, I didn't think about that
Looks like nobody needs godric
Please I need help on soldier of godric
Okay
What about elden beast?
If you need help with soldier of godric, uh, I got your back
Can I kill soldier of godric in one hit okay, it's right here. This is where it usually is, right?
No, no, it's after the
This is no no. Yeah, it's right there. Okay a little bit further. Yeah, it's after the guard counter tutorial
What am I doing? This is so stupid
Can you even summon for this boss? I don't know
Is this it?
No, I'll laugh my ass off. Okay. Here it is. I'm gonna laugh my ass off if this person dies the soldier of godric
Whoever you are
Where did I say I was gonna go? Where are we going? Elden beast?
I'll help with elden beast something with godfrey, please
I all right. I will I but what the heck?
I want to help there's somebody that actually wanted help with godfrey if I get someone into jesus's game again. I'm jumping off the cliff
Okay, here it is
You really need help with godfrey. You're just going through so much trouble. All he wants to do is help a noob in need
yeah, I don't know this game is a hard and
if there's some
Person that's just I don't I don't get it then I can get in there and I could just whoop some ass
Why not ready to do this?
All right. Uh, just keep in mind that when the boss gets down to like 30 hp i'm going to disconnect apparently
So let's go
If you can handle it after it gets to that part
Oh shit
Get that front stab nice
We both did it at the same time does it count?
Oh shit, I wasn't ready
That's bad. That's bad. That's bad. I might die
It's all right. I disconnected panic rolled. I did I I fucked up
I wasn't ready. I think you actually didn't help him. It's all level 53 by the way, whatever relax
They have two times more hp, but they're in phase two and they got like no look. I that was my mistake. It's all right
That guy definitely killed the boss
Let's
Absolutely beat it phase two is harder. Yeah, I just I got I got caught I got caught that's what happened
All right, malden. You ready? Let's go kill. Uh godfrey. Thank you. Let's do it. I did not hit him one time
Oh my god, i'm fucking throwing no get out just back it up and heal. I got it
I'm so sorry
Okay, we're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good. I'm sorry. Well, I
i'm dead
I just I I fucking can't oh my god. I like love this boss. I'm you know what it is
All right. Here's what I like. I'm not used to like just kind of being like in the room and
And like not having aggro and just kind of running. It's like I it's weird. I feel like a summon. I am a summon. It's weird
Okay, he's I promise i'm not griefing viewers on purpose
All right. All right. All right. I'm good. I'm gonna
You know what? Okay. I'm just gonna help people kill bosses. I'm putting let's go you respect. Oh, yeah, that's right. I can sit it
Mimic tear is better than you a mimic tear
I've never i've never done this before i've never done this i'm trying it's a different environment. It's a completely different. It's a different environment
It's like i'm there but some he's not fighting me but he is sometimes and i'm just like all right
I'm not taking one point fucking damage
All right hamburger helper, I promise i'm gonna you're the one i'm gonna actually help
I'm not gonna be an anchor to anybody else. Let's go
Check this out
Dude, it's fucking weird. I like it's weird to not get targeted. But then
I got this. No, I can't get a rhythm. I'm just like fucking running after the guy
All right, let's go
No
Try to help get away everybody. Oh my god. He keeps suplexing you
Let me take aggro. Let me take aggro
All right, heal up you heal up. I got it. All right, just a few more hits. You got it. You got it. You got it
Watch out back up back up back up back up
No
Let me kill him before you die
Oh, no
He was out of heels. I'm sorry that was close
No, we'll get it. We'll get it. We'll get it. Come on. Let's do it. I'll take aggro. I've tried
I was trying to just get in there
I was trying to get in the way so just be annoying so then he could run away and like cast spells
Use the aggro talisman
Oh, that's right. Hey Kratos. Let's try it so we can get it. I'm gonna sneeze in one second here
Summoning another cooperator
Are we gonna do this like three people?
I'm gonna sneeze
Come on
Who's the oh wait, that's
What happened
No
Oh, no, dude. I'm sorry. Oh, that's so that's sad. I'm sorry
I promise
We will kill one boss like this. I hope
Rhea allocate flasks
Oh, it cuts it in half. Okay
Who is it? All right. It's a tough one. We got it
Let's go for it
We're gonna get this
Trust me when I say that we've got it in the bag right now
Here we go. You just sit back there and cast that shit man. I got this
Just keep doing that shit. We got it. I'll watch it. Oh god
Stacker. Oh my god. I'm dead. Oh my god. I thought oh my goodness
I thought I thought the staggering. I thought I was gonna get stagger
Actually griefing I
Playing this game with two people against a boss. It feels weird
Like i'm trying to fight it but like my brain is like no, it's i'm not fighting this
And sometimes they'll do like a combo where he's like one two and then he's like
You and he just comes he just comes for you
Now, you know what? It feels like how to be the boys
Uh, that's all right. Use your spells. I want to do moon veil. How come you're griefing your fans?
All right. I gotta look I gotta get in the zone here
I will
Beat a boss with someone I will help somebody I will actually I promise
You're doing this for content. I mean
hamburger helper two
Okay
Uh, we'll get it this time
We'll get it this time
What are you talking about game what?
Let's get it
Ah
Nice nice get it double tap just kill him before he does it
Nice good work
Got it
See we actually did one
We actually got to do at least I got to at least help one person
Hooray. Oh nice job
Actually help her this time
Please help me do mine again and don't die. I feel so bad
I actually feel bad
All right, i'm gonna put it down again because there are people that need this
up with elden beast
Uh, I I hate that boss. I'm probably gonna it's i'm gonna be way worse
You do not want me to help you do elden beast. I'll get like i'll rage and like turn my stream off
All right malden
Let's get it this time. Let's go for it
No, don't apologize. That's my fault. I'm giving i'm making the boss have 50 more health and ditching you at phase two
That's not you. That's me
Oh shit got him too close
Shit. Oh, he did it twice. Okay, we're good
It's all right
No, you gotta get out get out get out. Don't say it
I'm dead. I'm dead. You got it. You got it. You got this. You got this. He's got these. He's low
He's low. He's low. He's low. You got it right now. You got this you can do it
Be careful
You're so close. You can do it bro. You had two heals
What?
I had all right. I gotta get these fucking mana flasks out of here, by the way
This is stupid
All right. We need to confirm that he did it
Why do I have why am I why do I have seven mana?
Bro, I need one fucking mana flask. I need one
one
Did you get it confirmation did malden beat the boss?
He didn't I need two or it'll be zero. Oh my god
We didn't beat the boss. Oh, no, i'm so sorry. I
I come in here with three heels like an idiot
You did this it's all right. We'll get it right here
We'll get it. We'll get it the aggro talisman. I feel like that's gonna be worse
We'll find out
This is a bad idea. We got it. This is the one
Yeah, all right. We got ira and we also have malden as well
By the way, i'm not even using this so I need to put on
Let's go in case I want to cast a spell for some reason. Let's go
Really? Oh my god, I died
No phase two. What the hell is going on? All right
Let's go
Fuck you
God damn it. I'm so bad at that part
Got it. Nice job
nice work
A man of my word dual moon veil. Yeah, that's all good
All right. I got malden. I gotta take care of malden. That was
When you tried to summon me you crashed my game
and it seems to be a kind of a
Thing that happens. All right
All right malden, let's go
Where you at and then we'll go to commander neil after this. I gotta get this win for malden though. That's not that's not cool
This is so fun
Got it on the ground here. Hopefully malden didn't uh, didn't rage quit or something
That'd be sad. There we go. I've been doing nothing but co-op bosses since beating the game
It's it it definitely feels a lot different
It's like when you have a summon out but the summons there the whole time
It's really cool
What do you uh, yeah, we're doing dos
This is different. This is a different player. Okay snaggle tooth. Let's do it up with elden beast
We'll do um, I want to do a lot of people what we're talking about neil
Far away get a stagger. Come on
There it is
Phase two. Yeah, there we go. Got it bro. What happened? How did that happen? That was so weird
No
Animation continued and happened in phase two because we caught it right. That's unfair
That's unfair. That was unfair
All right, last last attempt on whatever on whoever gets it
Hopefully, uh, i'd love to do with malden and then we're gonna go to commander neil. You look really greasy. I know it's I am
Do you understand like I am like i'm a greasy fucking person. Okay, cool
oh
Stretch it out a little
All right, somebody else. I apologize to people that I couldn't beat it
It's my bad, but hopefully we get this one
That's so like loud. We're a stagger here
Can't see anything
It pulls it up right
Careful
He's dead. Oh
Boy
You gotta we gotta get him one more hit on him and he's dead
Let's go excellent work
Get it
This feels good
It doesn't feel good when you die in the first 10 seconds and you know that they have to just leave the room
Did malden do it? I don't think so
Despite you being bad at the game and dying. I enjoyed coping with you
Malden you can we get a mod confirmation of malden is still here. I tried helping malden and I died
No
Malden just can't malden can't catch a break. This is something it sucks. All right malden
Mods can we get a private password for malden, please?
Yeah, let's get up. Let's get a special password for malden. Who is malden?
Uh, he's a player and I lost twice
Well, we got him down to one hit
It's too bad. We'll get it. I'll make sure malden gets a uh gets the win here. He's the main character
Hopefully malden's here
Malden might not even actually be here
They might just be playing the game not even watching the stream
Oh, no, that's impossible because the password
anything
About 10 more seconds and then we're gonna go to uh, neil
Sorry, man
Let's go to uh commander neil first commander neil. Oh, we got malden. All right. Yeah, we do have malden
All right. I need I need I need a special password for malden under the multiplayer password
We got I promise you that we will beat this. I'm not going to leave this seat until uh, horror louis dead
Uh, I just will use this password password confirmed
Let me get the sign on the ground
Go fucking around this time. I'm out. I'm gonna go for it. I'm gonna win. I'm not doing elden beast
No way the password mcchicken is not
All right, uh malden is confirmed
Got the password
This time I have a healing flask
Do I have the password right? Let me make sure I do
Yeah, there we go. Okay. There we go. Order one mcchicken every time you die actually
Maybe I will get some mcdonald's later. I don't know
Oh, dude, we got it. We're going with the double here
Please help. All right. Well, then we'll take care of you and summon up some of the actual summon at the door, too
So let's let's mario party this bus
Josh was already here
Let's go
I can't even tell what's happening
We're gonna die
There's too much going on
god
Is that still gonna land?
Did I do it? Oh, no, it was malden. All right, we're good
We did it. We did it
Yes
Congratulations balden
Good luck with the uh, good luck with the last part of the game. It sucks asshole
Have fun. All right, let's go to commander neil. I should go level up. Oh my god. I have a ton of souls
Uh, yeah, let's do neil
It's the best bonfire
Please help me with mog
Oh, I find there's a lot of people that want help
But here's the best part
Here's the best part. I can leave you guys
With that password that you guys could that password can stay
You guys can help each other, right?
Just use that same password
All right. This is the room. All right, so it's time
All right, whoever needed help with that commander nail. I'm here right here neil or
O'neil
These people are idiots. Don't leave me
All right boogers just came out my nose. I think i'm i'm ruined
Oh the password
It is different password is no longer yo malden
It's now we'll go back to cheese doctor. That's better same when we had at the very beginning
Let's do some commander new
Although actually I no, that's fine. It's fine
Cheese doctor or cheese drive. I mean it's supposed to be cheese doctor, but I couldn't fit anything else
If you're just joining the stream if you'd be I don't usually use the moon veil
It's a good helper weapon
Is nobody here?
How have I not been summoned yet?
Do a diagonal
How do I do that? I know obvious
Can I even can I make a diagonal?
Rewrite the summon sign. Oh shit
I want to make a diagonal. I don't think I can make a diagonal
Transform hold on
No, you can't
Make it smaller
Hold on. I gotta add one more thing
Oh, right. It's you
I should put like sounds in the background too like
Um, okay, so where are we going from here? Oh fuck the wrong weapons wrong weapons
That's so fucking annoying. I hate that. I don't want to do it anymore. All right, get up
Oh shit
Oh
I'm in the corner
Careful back it up. We got it. I forgot. This is all on here
Subscription start at 1499 subscription start at 1499. What the fuck was that?
It scared the shit out of me. Why did it not play before that actually scared the shit out of me?
I don't know why it didn't play before. No, fuck that joke. I thought somebody like hacked my game was in my call
I actually thought that somebody was in a call like hacked my computer or something
I know for a fact somebody else needed help with this. So
Why did it take so long? That was weird
Okay, I know there was another person that needed help with this badly. So come on. Let's do it. There we go
Help with lord of cinder
Oh, it's pot friend. Okay
Well now I know why you need help with this because your character probably sucks
Who the hell what's going on? Why's my health so low? What's going on?
Bro, I don't know what you want me to do, man
You're like you're like level 15. All right, let's do it again
That way the person was level one. Oh my god, that's stupid
I was gonna say that something was off about that one. Oh jesus again. Jesus
All right, I'm leaving. I'm leaving. I don't know what he's doing. I don't he's freaking out. He's freaking me out
He's freaking me out. I don't know what he's doing. He's moving around weird. He's moving around get out get out get out get out
He's doing weird shit
All right, that was he's freaking me out. I don't like it
He was like he was going like this
That was fucking scary. I don't know what he was doing
I don't know, dude. I'm sorry. I might be freaking out but when the character's sitting there going like this
It's like okay
You're like you're hacking the game or something and like you're about to like throw up like a fucking thousand pixels on the screen
And my computer's gonna crash
All right, froggy chair
What do you say? Let's go for it
Cool good start. What are you doing? What was that?
He's exhausted
That was fucking weird
Shit, good job. All right, this should be it
Nice job. All right. So was that the person that really needed the help anybody else need help here where jesus is in chat right now
What what he what?
I don't know. You scared me. It was scary. I don't know what was going. I was scary
You look like a greaser not greasy. Oh, okay. How do you even get the name on twitch?
real
real jesus christ
I feel like I feel like that's gonna get caught by a filter eventually
That name is just so fucking weird
All right. Is this jesus? No, it's not
Whoa, that was kind of scary
The real jesus christ
That's so fucking funny
Good careful for the boss boss is right behind you man
careful for the boss
Watch out back it up. You'll be able to stagger here
Oh, no
Back it up back it up. You're good. Oh my god. I thought he died. Nice job
Imagine if the second coming happened during an elden ring stream
You're gonna play the new lego star wars didn't that like the end game already come out. I'm confused
Everybody would spam pog
There's a new one. That's is it better than the old one?
All right, maybe one more of these
One more of these and then i'm gonna wrap it up with a little bit of pvp
Just came up. It's pretty fun
The actual actual second coming of christ, but he spawned an elden ring
It includes all the new movies. All right, okay
That makes sense
Maybe we did maybe everybody is done with um
Neil are we good? Did the three or four people that needed did uh, are we good?
No help with millennia. No, that's not happening. I will ruin all your games
Okay
Okay, i'm gonna give it 10 more seconds
Here we go
Millennia is easier without help. I would imagine so
Because if she kills your co-opter and heals off of them, then you just have to deal with a way worse version
All right, ashley
cool weapon
I like the uh giddy and off near stuff
This boss is dead
Do you kill this already?
What are we doing? Where are we going? What are you gonna do?
Where do you want to go?
I'm i'm following your lead. Where where where we're going. Let's go
You didn't have to do that
You didn't have to do that. We could have just walked around. No, I kind of feel bad
Well, it was cool to see you for the few seconds that we were there
It was just a short cameo
All right, let's go to
I'm gonna do some pp. I'm gonna do moonvale pvp. I'm gonna be an asshole
We're gonna pick a spot. This is that we're gonna finish the stream this way
How about like somewhere in caitlin? We're here somewhere. I guess we could do it here
I'm not over here by virgin
Yeah, like right over here
Password is still cheese doctor. So
Your sign's down
We'll do this. I'll do another like three or four
And then i'm gonna call for today
Oh, you can't do it here
And what do you can?
Is that not I hear is that wrong?
okay, um, how about
That church of vows was pretty good spot. Yeah, this was a good spot
We're outside. We're ever gonna do this again. I don't know. I mean, this is really fun
You guys want to do this again, I would definitely do it again
This was a good spot
All right. We have an uh, we have actual psycho
I'm gonna do moon veil. I'm curious how it is
Even it makes me an asshole
Sorry, what's today? Stay saturday
Actually might not be able to stream tomorrow. We don't have to do dos on monday. I don't know why I thought it was friday
I thought it was friday
Did I?
Summon somebody I just did all right this barf drinker again. We might uh do a rematch. All right a gamer boy
Do I have a backup save?
Um, I think i'm fine. I'm okay
there's been like one or two hackers, but it was just like kind of I mean it was
It was pretty funny
It was just like insanity
I don't mind people just kind of fucking having fun as long as as long as nobody like actually tries to you know
Hey break my game or something, but you know
Hello
Did we confirm that jesus christ was a hacker? I mean
in the video game
That's unbelievable. All right. Okay. All right. All right. I'll take it
Okay, i'll take it up. I'll take it. It's my
Oh, hi. Yeah, you can heal by the way. Yeah, that weapon's fucking awful. That weapon's unbelievable
But good luck dealing with uh, good luck dealing with this
All right, you can heal again. You can heal again. You can that's that's really stupid. You can heal again heal again
All right, I just I got I healed so you should heal too. Let's just start over
Let's just start just start over just start over start over
That wasn't fair
Heal all the way heal all the way. Yeah, there we go. All right, so now we can actually go let's go
What the fuck is happening with my controller?
Oh, I have my weapons flipped my weapons have flipped let me let me fix my weapon
I was wondering why because I was the spin actually was pretty that that was doing work
Uh good game though
Fucking stupid. All right
Now i'm ready to pvp
Done you actually have a gun
Do you think jesus has ever?
bl jade
and wait, you mean like
wait like the
That thing that means right? Wait, do you think jesus is going like
Probably I would make it would make sense. All right, how are you? Let's do it
I weren't ready for the fucking rain of stars
Where are you going?
Yo, oh, that was cool. All right
goodbye
damn
Okay
That person looks like they had a camera
They're just snapping pictures of us
gg. Good game. All right, let's get a good one here
helicopter
Kind of need to know and you need to know what the helicopter character looks like
I think i'm not doing spells. I think it's gonna go just two handed
This is an exploit
Whatever. Hey, hello
Dude, you got nice recovery though. It's gonna be close
Oh
Good game
Who died first?
Oh
Oh, we got a tie
That was cool build. I still have the aggro ring on. Oh, that's right. This is no I don't yeah. I do
What was on there before?
Physical damage, uh, I think it was magic damage
Yeah, put it
Oh
Operator turned into atmosphere
I'm for it. Let's go
We hear shito
Uh, yeah, we keep cheese doctor as the community password after the stream. Yeah, that sounds good
How are you?
That's a weird move
Whoa
Holy shit. Nice. Okay mode that that was weird
There's a little purple thing. Okay. Arian slicer is really good. Don't I have it? Do I like dairy queen?
It yeah, it's fine. It's good
Would gigachad have that weapon I feel like gigachad would use like the big hammer
How are you? Holy shit. Oh my god
Oh, that was so close. Nice fight
That move what that move did almost 100% of my health
That was ridiculous
That is how much I had left. Good fight. I mean barf drinker has been patiently waiting. All right
Why do I get so tired all of a sudden? I'm like tired
I don't know what happened summon code is uh cheese dr cheese doctor cheese
Cheese drive probably makes more sense. All right
Going on barf drinker long time no see
I'm sitting in the bonfire with you
I like this guy
That's cute
Wow
All right. Well now that you dropped our fps by about 20 let's go ahead and fight
On fire
I don't know why I feel like i'm fighting an old lady
Piece of shit
I feel like i'm fighting an old lady and she's like throwing just random shit in her kitchen or like in her living room
like she's just like
shh
I like where i'm like up in an old lady's attic and she's just like throwing fucking paintings at me and random shit
Hey grandma, what are you doing up in the attic?
I'm just like going through some old books and stuff and she's just and she fucking just starts throwing them
Why are you so it's so weird. It's so weird to fight you
Is that a bomb? That's a mine, isn't it? This is a mine
Yo, what is that?
Grandma, where did you find this in the attic?
Come here. I want to backstab. I want to backstab grandma to end it
God damn it
Get over here
Come on
Fuck you grandma
How are you still alive? How does it do two damage?
No, no, no, no, no
No, no, no, i'm not gonna let this happen
Oh my god, i'm dead. I can't believe it
Oh
Grandma, we just grandma was like fucking breathing out like a crack pipe at the end
I was trying to get a backstab. I was trying to go I I could have killed barf drinker
At any moment at that at any moment, but I was trying to get the backstab. I was trying to be cute with it
Pretty much what i'm saying is barf drinker put it back down
You're around too
I can't believe you died to barf drinker dad of air fryer
It's pretty that's a pretty good name
Literally, you don't own one
I don't own an air fryer
And I don't think I ever will
Let's run. It's perfectly fine. Hey, all right dad. Let's do it dad. You got low hp
Yeah, what level are you just a little uh bigger?
No air fryer
By the way, i'm not even sure that guy owns an air fryer because why would you make an air fryer character and not have?
like heat moves
Like where's where's the fireballs coming out of your hands and shit?
All right. Here's uh, ashley that you jumped up the flip before barf drinker part two. Oh, yeah. Well, don't worry
Let's go for it. Here we go. That weapon is scary looking
That's a good move actually
Oh, I caught right in the air
I'm doing it too. You jumped over it
All right. Well, I i'll get to drink. I can drink another one because you drank too
Shit okay if they heal you can heal that's that's the uh, that's the
If they heal you can heal too, but never don't ever go more than they if they let's let's say somebody drinks two
Then you can drink two somebody drinks five
You can drink five if somebody drinks one. You can't drink five
Now let's get that that weapons. What is that weapon? The weapon is actually really cool. I really like that fucking thing
But there was no reason to say the f-word
Why did I just say the f-word
I've received an air fryer in the mail by mistake. I've kept it, but I never used it
Is it just in the box?
That's the gargoyle twin blade. Okay. Yeah, we begin
Holy shit. What's that? Is that the hammer?
Oh, man
I've never seen that before
That thing's crazy
But that weapon seems really fun. It's the final boss soul. Uh, right, right, right, right
All right, let's do uh, i'll do three more. I want my rematch
With the barf drinker
I mean pea brain. Yeah
He brain is just a big
dumb guy with a hammer
Why are you pea brain?
I'm gonna I hope this person just holds rr1 the whole time just r1 r1 r1 r1 r1. It doesn't do anything else
Stake
I love doing that
All right, let's go
Hey, yay. Hey, stop
Oh, I thought I got mine first. I did
Oh
What happened? Oh you came back too too quickly
Let's drop pea brain
Okay
That first move is crazy
Okay. Uh a couple more. It's millennia
scum
meet ryan tilde
All right, i'll come back to you
This guy looks like a world of warcraft human
Is matchmaking on frost region matchmaking is on let me just make sure it is
Look at vr. Josh here helping
All right, i'm not gonna fight you I just want to get a look at you your character it looks
I'm not gonna hurt you. I just want to see your face
about the extreme movement like snake everybody everybody in from software is snake it's just
Sudden movements freak them out
Okay, just wait. Wait, wait, wait. I can I like let me get a close view face
All right. We're good. We're good. We're good
Let's do it. Okay
Are you ready?
Uh, let's go three
I'm just gonna fight you. Okay, let's go
I know stamina shit
Oh my god, those things are floating around
Good good good very good
Fight good fight
All right, where's where's puke drinker?
welcome to
pea brain
Actually
That weapon is so cool. I want to use it
Oh, I said I would come back to you
Yeah, also not a lot and not everybody knows the uh, the pvp etiquette, right?
So what I don't matter. That's fine
It's fine
So if somebody heals whatever, I mean not everybody's like studies the from software unwritten rules
All right, meet grog run tilde
Let's do it jumped in a little too early and that's gonna be the downfall
Whoa
Nice dammit
Like that's a cool move that attack is sick. It is
All right. All right. What one more and it's gonna have to be versus the barf drinker
I don't even know if barf drinker's still here
Are you still here barf drinker?
Where is barf drinker? I'm gonna reload
the lonesome
barf drinker
Hmm
We might have to reload a new area
He have a brilliant gold mass
And so giddy and off there
You all know
All right barf drinker. I want you one v one
I want you
over here
At the outer wall battleground
I want you right next to this grace and I want to see your sign
Right here. I want my rematch right here and i'm gonna get it
Will barf drinker answer the call?
interesting
Oh
A lot of I got a lot of calls
All right. I'm not messing around this time. We're going full fuck face mode
It's not him
Is this not the right person?
Yeah, it is right. This is a fake barf drinker. No, it's not
That's how we can tell it's a real barf drinker. Wait a minute. This is a fake. This is a fake barf drinker
This is horseshit. That's a fake barf drinker. You know why because he was
Barf drinker was putting graces down before not these
This is not real
Let's get out of here with this
All right
Let's go
And drink this
Take a sip of this
You see what i'm capable of not even the real fucking dumb drinker. Whatever his name is
Where are you going?
Come on
Get over here you dung eater
All right. Where's the real barf drinker?
Everybody's gonna start to uh, I don't think i'm gonna be able to find the real barf drinker guys
Are you kidding me? Look at this. You ready?
Everybody's gonna be that now. Okay. Thank god
barf two
Come on now
Keck w. Okay
All right melvis. Yeah, look at this guy
How about fighting no, I want to I want to fight the barf drinker
But I also want to fight
This guy
Yeah, they're all putting on the barf drinker helmet
Where's barf drinker?
I don't see the barf drinker
I I do okay. That's hog rider again
Summon multiple people and have a big battle royale
All right. I am now only summoning barf drinkers. I just want to make sure that's very clear
What item do I have to take to fight like three barf drinkers?
All right, nice
All right, I want
How many people can you have in your game?
Three I want three barf drinkers right now
So how do I do that without any?
cooperators
They use this
So summon somebody and then use this
I need to see some science here
I need a cooperating. Um
We got him by the way
I want okay. Hold on. No, what happened? No, where did it go?
Use the tongue first
Okay, where's barf drinker? He was just right there
Okay, I bet you his game crashed
Shit, I just had it
Someone summoned him
Oh, you can't you can't name yourself barf guzzler
All right. It looks like we're gonna have to wait till uh barf drinker wins this fight
But I need to summon somebody right?
I need to somebody put a sign down to I want to I want a barf drinker to come to the game
I have a barf drinker. My sign is done
Shit
You have to be near soul level 153. I think without I think you do maybe not with the password though
All right, we're gonna have to move
All right bar all barf drinkers attention all barf drinkers
Head to the power of bounty
race
Password would use in this one is on screen cheese doctor
Attention all barf drinkers
I need barf drinkers to invade me and I need barf drinkers to put their signs down
Um, why can't I do anything?
Okay, there we go invaded by okay. Well, that's not a barf drinker
I need a barf drinker
Not a gig of barf. You can't just name yourself barf something with barf barf slurpee
Darth. Okay. I want I want Darth Maul in the game
Oh shit. Oh my god. Okay
Hey, somebody put uh, I need a barf drinker with uh
Come on. I don't know who this is. I am dumb. All right. Welcome to the game
They hurt each other. They can't right?
They're gonna gang up on this guy so bad
I actually kind of want to just watch
I'm gonna be stupid
Where is he barf drinker? Can you do it?
2v1
Oh, where's my thing? I'm gonna watch
You guys think barf drinker can do a 2v1?
Good luck barf drinker. I I I believe in you
It'll be one to go that way
No, turn around
There are
Wait, why do you leave?
There's an invader here
kill the invader
What the I just want to be the camera from barf drinker. I gotta turn the hut off
Uh-oh barf drinker. Look out
Be careful
Oh
Oh my god, it's just unfair
Bro, where are you going?
I don't I don't know where to put the camera
Nobody touches the barf drinker on my team
Get him barf drinker. Get him. Get him. Get him
No
What is this fucking move?
What is this move?
Barf drinker, I want your sign back. I want I want to watch that again
Barf drinker, please put your sign down again, please
An invader though. All right. I want barf drinker as an invader and I want a barf drinker as
a cooperator
This is the original barf drinker. I think
Where's the imposter a barf drinker?
Hold on a sec. Let's see who the real barf drinker really is
I mean, maybe I should just summon this guy. This guy's kind of a weirdo
Maybe all right barf drinker versus whatever. This is a michelin man
I'm gonna get a good view. What's the oh, it's that stop
Where's the barf drinker? Hey, what's what the bar? Where's the barf drinker?
What are they doing?
He's just going in
Is the one on the left the barf drinker without the barf drinker outfit the official officially licensed barf drinker outfit?
Oh here we go
He missed. Oh my god
Oh, no
You did it. He looks so happy
Why the barf drinker put on different clothes?
All right, stay here. I need you you're actually
Let's go. You're actually a pretty good bodyguard. All right, we need some invaders. I need a barf drinker invasion, please
No signs on the ground anymore. Hey genius 2.0. This is all you
Oh shit amy's business
Nice
I gotta get a little closer. Come on. Come on. You got it. You got it. Stay with it
This build is so cool
Blaming boxing kind of like iron boxing gloves watch the camera man
Oh
My god, it's hard
This is ridiculous. This fight's going on for a long time
Nice job. Oh, that was a good fight though. Holy shit
You can heal. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I don't know that freaked me out. I don't know what how come why are you
Aren't invaders supposed to be red?
You freaked me out. Sorry
All right, go for it. Why what's why I thought invaders were red
Where are you going? I'm good
I'm really this is intense. I'm really into this
nice good exchange
Gotta watch that overhead watch the overhead swing
That's good. Here. Are you referee?
I'm just cameraman
What?
What the hell happened there?
damn
Nice job
All of you that was good
You're very good
And there's somebody else here
Your turn. Uh, oh, this could be the end of the michelin man rain
Here comes spaghetti
Oh, no disconnected that sucks
How many healing classes to cooperate again?
All right. Well, that was a good job
Very very good job. Where's this other person? There you are. All right. Good luck
You got to kill the michelin man
Oh
Get a course review
In the way
Hell didn't rain
Oh, no
Who's that? All right now you two fight
This is so stupid
So this is so this is so epic
Oh my god, look at all the fireballs everywhere. This is so fucking epic. Oh my god
This actually is really cool though
All right. Here comes. Uh, I don't know how to wait. Where's the move?
Okay. Yeah, here we go. Good luck
I gotta make hazards
Nice work. I won't i'm not gonna backstab you again. Don't worry
They're gonna turn on you. No one's gonna. All right, let's get another cooperator in here. And then this is the real fight
This is actually the fight
I want another sign, please
I think someone's already invading. All right, you and me. Let's go. I don't even need a hud. Let's do it
Here comes a super epic fight
Dude, we look like it's like red versus blue. This is cool. We look pretty simple
Shit, I don't know what the fuck that was
I want you on my team for sure without a doubt
Which is the right one?
All right. We need uh, two invaders to come in actually there's signs on the ground. Maybe these are uh, what piss drinker barf drinker
I'm actually really happy to see you here
Welcome to the fight. I need to turn this on
No, no, okay. All right invaders probably just gonna come in
So now this is a one
No more bullshit. This is a 2v2
Turning the hud back on
Grandpa, I just want to make sure you understand this is for real because this is that that's that's barf drinker right there
And there's also a ludbud warrior here, too
Hey, i'm gonna be tricky. I'm not I don't pick items up. I don't know what the fuck that is
I would pick that back. I would pick that back up because I don't pick items up on the ground
It could be like 99 humanities
Okay. All right. Um
All right, let's go get him. Let's go go. Let's get him fight. No, no, wait, wait. Oh fuck
This is the real one. This is real fight. Let's go fight
Somebody start fight start fighting somebody fight somebody
I don't want to be I don't want to do the first swing somebody fight someone
There it is
What what happened? Oh my god. I forgot i'm actually playing a game. I was uh, oh
Kill him quick
You don't have any mana left. Kill him quick kill him. You don't have any mana kill him quick
I was just running through trying to get a backstab. I didn't look at my health
All right final one. I want to I want a real 1v1 versus barf drinker and that's it
Just 1v1 versus barf drinker. That's not you. Guess what?
I don't think I have that helmet
never mind
We do the imposter. Um versus
All right. Hey real barf drinker, please put a red summon sign down
I want you to fight your imposter and then i'm done
That is the real one. It's down. All right signs down
Wait, can I not um
No, that's definitely that's barf dash drinker not barf drinker
Guys, i'm kind of I don't I kind of don't know it's mega mind
All right barf drinker. Can you think you can take two?
I have confidence that you can
Wait, I need to turn my HUD up
Why are they fighting?
It's so dumb. He's he's fucked. He's not going anywhere
This is the weirdest shit. I feel like I feel like this is like fucking halloween
These these kids have like shaving cream and like eggs and stuff. This is fucking halloween night
Where's the other invader?
He's so fucked. Yeah, I wrote every enemy. Oh my god. You're fucking dead, dude
Where are you going?
He's got he's coming back. He's coming back
Oh my god
What is happening?
There's another invader apparently
Hey, hey, i'm the cameraman
Dude, i'm not involved. I'm not involved. You have to fight the barf drinker
What are you doing?
He's all bloody. He's all bloody
Oh
He's using the camera as a shield, which was a very smart idea very brilliant brilliant tactic by the barf drinker
Oh shit. Oops
dude barf drinkers already across the map at this point like
He's gone
I don't I don't even know. I don't know where he is
I mean, we're only gonna wait for him because that's what we're doing
Now now what happens now these two are fighting now barf drinker is gonna come from back here
And drop like a fucking grenade on them. I'm telling you if I know the barf drinker and by the way, I do very well
Here he comes
damn
Where is he? Is he fighting over there by the thing? I what is happening? Hold on
Where's the barf drinker? Is he?
Barf drinker, where'd you go? This is like kind of i'm like kind of nervous
Heard something
Why are they killing each other? Where's the barf drinker?
I don't give a shit about any of that by me
Oh my god, you wow, you killed him bad
Does anybody know where the barf drinker is?
fat millennia
He's gonna attack my dog
What the fuck is he being attacked by?
What is that?
Where did you get this?
What the fuck
Where did you get this thing?
Where did you get this?
Help me, please help me
Kill that thing
Did I get it? Oh shit
Okay, we're good
That guy looks
Very very dangerous. All right. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Start it up. Start it up barf drinker versus
fat millennia and
Oh my god, how am I alive I have absolutely I was like, what are you pointing at?
How am I alive? I was standing in death flight
Doesn't make any sense. What?
All right, we're gonna clear this shit out
Oh my god, this is such a disaster. We have to get out of the way
All right, everybody follow me follow me follow me follow me going this way this way this way this way
Oh my god
Follow me. Where's where's the dung drinker?
Where's barf drinker?
We good
Dude, I swear to god if I die, I'm gonna be so pissed
All right
Okay, guys
It's your 2v1 versus the barf drinker. By the way, he's very very strong. He's incredibly hard
He's one of the strongest
Mini bosses in elden ring
He's just fighting this thing. Okay, wait
Oh good a golden rune one. All right, he's just running over here
Everybody let's go up here
All right barf drinker
Go for it. Let's stop fighting the enemies
Can I get barf drinker as a summon I want a spirit summon I want a barf drinker spirit summon
All right, go for it
again
Begin and you don't even I don't think you're even the real barf drinker. This is a fake barf drinker, right?
You want me to follow you?
Okay
Guys, we're following the barf drinker
I have no idea where he's where he wants us to go, but we're gonna follow him
This guy's trying to get wants to get a back step so bad and trust me. I get it. So would I
I don't know where we're going
Fucking crackhead wizard of Oz
Is this where you want to be?
Why do you want to be here?
I don't I mean, I'm just the immense wisdom of the barf drinker. I can't say no
I can't say like no, we're not doing that barf drinker, right? This is incredible wisdom that we're talking about
Okay
That way
What do you want me to go?
Please help over here. What do you want over here?
Okay
What are we doing up here? Uh barf drinker. What's what are we doing up here?
What's happening?
He's running away
Where are you going? Uh, oh, I think they've had enough
It's a 2v2
All right. Fine. You want? All right. All right. All right. All right. All right 2v2 2v2
Oh, no, no, no, I don't know what that does. Oh, there's no back step
Holy shit
Oh, no, I died. Oh, oh, oh
Shoot him quick. Shoot him quick. Shoot them. Shoot them. Shoot them quick. That was fucking outrageous
All right. That's it. I'm going to bed
That's it
They wanted you to die
Please help
That was crazy
All right, that's it
Uh, so I said tomorrow originally but it's gonna be monday
Because I have some things I gotta do tomorrow
Uh monday around four o'clock pacific. We are going to do dos games
We'll also keep the password that uh cheese doctor cheese drive whatever password
You guys want to play with each other by all means, please do
Be you know, be nice be like crazy have fun
That was a lot of fun
uh
Will I do something like this again?
probably
I can imagine probably yeah
So i'll see you guys on monday for uh dos games. We're gonna get quite the collection
Try to do at least like five to ten of them
You promised shito
All right, if I don't play shito on stream on monday
I will eat his shoe again
Is the community password gonna be yeah, the community passwords stay the same
What is dos games ms dos old games?
old dos games from old, uh
Free windows pc's maybe some windows like 3.1 probably too
Everybody that played sorry if I didn't get to your summoning sign
Or if I was summoned to your game and I lost and made you lose over and over again
That's fun
Thanks for hanging out as always. I'll see you guys on monday
Uh, take care of yourselves. Okay, you have to eat a glove soon. Yeah
so
Apologize to barf drinker
barf drinker is
My new favorite character
Uh what I I apologize what I do?
Yeah, also by the way if you have old dos
Recommendations and they are available
very easily, right
Uh, please throw them in the recommended on discord
I'm gonna be compiling a list over the next day or so
Good night. Goodbye. Take care of yourselves. Thanks for watching. See you soon. See you monday
Good night guys