My tweet is still about the urinal. It's alright. Don't worry. My next tweet is going to be about TwitchCon.
My next tweet will be a selfie in front of the TwitchCon arena.
We'll be doing the peace sign and going, made it! Here we are!
That's it. And then I won't tweet for like another four months.
I'll tweet like four months later. Just got off the plane! Back from TwitchCon!
Oh, it was awesome! You were at TwitchCon for four months.
Anyways, I wish you tweeted your updates instead of only posting them in Twitch chat.
Come on. I'm a Twitch streamer. That's what I have to do.
I'm not a Twitter streamer. I'm a Twitch streamer. So if I'm in Twitch chat...
I'm not going to... There's no Twitter chat. This is the platform.
Jerma, how come you don't... Jerma, how come you don't ever update your Facebook?
Because that shit's run by aliens! And they're taking all of our data!
Oh, dude, this guy is woke. No. I kid. I kid.
I just don't... I don't really do social media. I really just don't. I never have and never will.
Guys, I call grandma. I don't put a thumbs up on grandma's post about her birthday.
I go to grandma's house for her birthday. Come on. You are the grandma.
And I can't wait until all my grandkids, they all come to grandpa Jeremy's house.
I'm going to be so angry if I have a grandpa's 80th birthday party and my 40 to 50 grandchildren,
like 48 of them just do like a little thumbs up on a picture of me.
And two of them show up. I'll be very upset about that because I know.
I know what that is. Those two are the good ones.
Anyways, we're going to do some more FMV tonight. Hopefully internet permitting.
There's been a lot of weird issues with the internet that we're trying to figure out.
We don't think it's really Cox related. We think it's construction related.
Because it's been odd. It's been very odd.
There's construction going on outside. It's like, what the heck?
And it's been kind of shutting us off. So we'll go, we'll see how far this one goes.
Also, if you have not, hold on. If you have not given a submission to the Activity Book Discord,
that stream's happening in a few days. This is the last day you can.
Where's Waldo? A dot to dot, a activity image.
If you want to contribute something and you think it would be fun,
we're just going to pull the ones that we think are the best.
And if there's more time, we can do other ones too.
So today's the last day. After today, the submissions are all going to close.
Am I crying? I thought I was, I thought I could hide it.
I thought I could hide it, but apparently I can't.
I've been trying to hold it in for like five straight minutes.
No. I like burnt my throat drinking coffee too fast.
I needed it. I took a sip of coffee when it was way too hot and it ruined me.
It ruined my voice and this is just what happens.
I'll be fine in like 10. I sound great. What are you talking about?
I sound good right now. I sound very bass, heavy.
If you've got a system, if you've got like a subwoofer,
right now, if you turn everything else down, turn all the treble to zero,
turn the mid down to zero, just to have bass, you're going to hear this.
It sounds fucking great. I can hear it. I can feel it.
Anyways, let's put a name in because the first game we're going to play on our
journey through the world of old full motion video games is
Steven Spielberg's Director's Chair.
This game, you have to make movies in this game.
I did this this month. This here's a potential, right?
Let me tell you, this one will last 30 minutes or three hours.
You have to pick and edit and shoot a movie with real actors.
Let's go. First name, last name.
No, I can't do wouldn't you like to know.
Jeremy Albertson. Let's go.
Hopefully it's not too loud. It's probably going to be very loud.
I haven't done any of that. It's all right.
Oh, it's very loud.
Steven Spielberg presents a Jeremy Albertson film.
I didn't do anything.
Starring Jennifer Aniston and Quentin Tarantino.
This is what you do when you're like 14.
Penn and Teller, Catherine Hellman and Barry Corbin.
This is what you do when you're 14 and you're like envisioning yourself as the
director of the movie.
I'm going to have Jennifer Aniston and Quentin Tarantino and Penn and Teller
are going to do magic.
It's like, OK.
What are we looking at?
Is this one going? State 17.
Watch your back. Am I in jail?
Oh, where is this one going?
There he is.
Me? Smiley.
Now making movies is one of the greatest jobs in the world.
You've got to have talent and intuition, patience and energy.
OK. And the real innate ability to tell a story and a comfortable pair of shoes.
Of course, a great crew is also essential.
So I've handpicked some of the best people in Hollywood to work with you.
And I'll be around to guide you through the process from writing the script to
premiering the film.
OK.
The movie you're about to personally make.
I'm going to make the movie.
Go to Studio Operations and please sign in.
OK.
What the fuck is that?
Why is there an earthquake?
What?
Whoa.
Just a minor tremor.
Nothing to really worry about.
Huh?
Welcome to Southern California.
I'm your P.A.
That's short for Production Assistant.
Come on into Operations to sign in.
You can't start production until you do.
What's it like?
Like Mother Goose window.
OK.
Coming to Studio Exit.
Free Pro.
All right. Let's go in here.
Here's my computer.
I'm here to assist you.
If you ever need help, just click on the pager.
I'll leave it here on the desk.
Oh, I know I have it here somewhere.
One second.
Pager.
Got it.
Just throwing it over here?
OK.
Now this is Studio Operations.
She just like underhanded it under the desk.
Grab one of the blank slates and then sign in.
Is that supposed to be a...
Oh, OK.
That was him pressing the button on the computer.
OK.
Blank slate.
If your name is correct, hit OK.
No.
That's not my real name.
I'm going to use my director name.
Don't you guys know?
You've got to use a stage name.
I'm not going to use my real name.
What the fuck?
I've got to use my stage name.
No, that's not...
What's a better one?
No, that's...
Hatting...
Jeremy...
Hey, what's your name?
Oh, yeah.
It's me.
Jeremy French Film Director.
Jeremy French Film.
I like it.
Jeremy French...
French fries.
Jeremy French Fry.
What a stupid fucking name.
All right.
Jeremy...
It's me.
Jeremy French Fry.
Click on the newspaper when you're done reading it.
Daily Variety.
Jeremy French Fry hired to direct film.
That's such a child name.
OK.
Let's go.
The guys at the studio are thrilled you're directing this picture,
but they run a tight ship here,
so they're going to monitor your budget and schedule on a daily basis.
How much money do I get?
Here.
Take a look, then click on it to move on.
All right.
Let's take a look at the budget.
Click on the budget when you're done reviewing it.
Hollywood is filled with stories of people who've cheated their way to the top.
While strongly recommending that you advance by hard work and raw talent,
we do provide the means to cheat your way up to more advanced levels of play.
Click on the PA pager button and check the user's guide for details, but beware.
Am I already getting, like, time to cheat your way to the top?
Director, Jeremy French Fry, movie, total budget $845,000, 22 days.
Click on the...
No, let's go.
You should go next door to pre-production to start writing your script.
Click on the exit icon over there to go out to the lot.
OK.
No, I'm not cheating.
I never cheated in my YouTube or Twitch career.
Why would I do it here?
It was hard work.
It was sweat.
Just move your mouse to the right or the left and have a look around.
All right, so where do we need to go?
The production office or...
Seagull.
OK, why is the seagull animated and these ones are the JPGs?
I don't understand.
Why is this one animated?
Stage 17.
What did she say to go?
I was talking over her.
This is studio graphics for...
Oh, my God.
Product credits.
Studio theater.
All right, where do I need to go?
This one here?
What the fuck is that?
Am I getting, like, the birds coming in, too?
It all begins with the written word.
We owe our careers to the writers.
And my saying has always been, if it's not on the page, it's not on the stage.
So we got you a couple of positively and really amazing, terrific writers,
Ted and Terry, or Terry and Ted, who have their own ideas.
So learn early to collaborate, knowing that in the end,
it's you who must make the final decision about the story that you want to tell.
So this is your first time up at that.
Keep it nice and simple.
Keep it simple?
The story that's been greenlit is that of a prisoner wrongly accused of murder
who's about to be executed unless his girlfriend can find who set him up.
What?
Unfortunately, this studio is only willing to let you tell one side of the story.
So whose story do you want to tell, the prisoners or the girlfriends?
Oh, shit.
I think we got to go.
We got to go in.
We got to go in prison.
We got to do prison.
I'm doing prisoner.
Great choice.
That's exactly the way we would have gone.
My name's Ted.
My name's Terry.
We co-wrote the animated film Aladdin.
And so in Hollywood, we're the perfect pair to write a prison picture.
That was an instant flex.
We're really excited to be working with you.
Instant flex.
Hey, we're your biggest fans.
Biggest fans.
Now listen, do you want to give some creative input in this story,
or should we write it alone?
What am I doing here?
Now, I want to do it.
Otherwise, I'm just a camera that walks around and looks at stuff.
I want to work on the script.
Okay, great.
So it's just you and me.
That's like the Lord of the Rings.
Click on the outline so we can read through it.
All right, script outline.
After you read through the outline,
click on the sequence you want to use for the opening of the film.
And drag it over to us, and we'll write it.
I'll write it.
We'll type it.
Isn't it already written?
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
It's already written.
Okay.
Interior.
Prison.
Day.
TV news report about Jack Cavella,
who is about to be sent to the electric chair.
All right.
Interior.
Two prison guards watch TV.
A priest comes by, and the guards accompany him to a prison cell.
Why is it...
The priest enters the cell of Jack Cavella, who denies all charges.
Jack is escorting...
All right.
Let's go back.
Wait, wait, wait.
No.
No, no, no.
Wait a minute.
Is that good?
What do you think?
Hey!
Exterior.
Prison.
Day.
Turnkey and screw wheel.
The still smoking sheet-covered body of Jack Cavella
up a ramp from the prison basement.
The warden watches and smiles.
Photographers flash their cameras.
Ma looks on, devastated.
The father of Laura's praise, Laura cries.
All right.
The scene is finished.
Why don't you take this masterpiece,
lay it in the script book.
We're on a roll now.
Excellent.
That's the whole movie.
All right.
Put this in the script book.
Anniston joins friendly cast of Jeremy French Rye's film.
Now that you've got the hang of it,
go back to the outline and select the next sequence
you want us to write.
The next sequence?
Keep it up until we finish the script.
Oh, that, this is, okay.
Uh, the warden gets a call to pardon Jack.
Jack is set free.
I mean, yeah, that one's pretty good.
I like that one.
Do you see any other writers in this room?
I don't see any other writers.
Why don't you let us, hey,
why don't you let us write that thing?
I think that was a pretty,
I think that was a genuine hey, man.
What the fuck?
Let's see what they come up with.
Mm-hmm.
Let me read it.
The warden and the executioner
stand by the electric chair switch
looking at the clock.
The phone rings.
The warden answers.
Hello, yes, Governor?
Yes, yes, of course, right away.
Hold on, it seems you,
your girl's been playing
beat the clock in one.
Get him out of here.
Okay, that's in there.
After he's released,
Jack and Laura are ringing out
on the prison steps.
Hold on.
Jack is escorted by the two guards
and he frees down the last mile
towards the electric chair.
Jack's mother meets him
at the end of the hallway.
She tells him that his girlfriend Laura
is looking for him.
For the real killer.
Guard takes Jack away.
Come on, Jack.
Kiss goodbye.
Yeah, the music really does not
match the tone.
You're right.
That was your first day
of pre-production.
You made it.
Jack is back in the chamber.
How you feeling?
On top of the world?
I'll bet.
Keep it up.
My budget.
Days to write.
I did it in one and a half days.
Total budget, 845.
Cool.
Jack is...
Tarantino signs on to Jeremy
French Fry's new film.
There's more?
I gotta do more of this shit?
Come on, compadre.
Wake up.
We already did that one.
I can't do it twice?
Okay.
Here.
Let's just end it.
Are those darts?
Laura stands behind crowd
at the prison steps.
Jack walks out of the prison door
at the top of the steps.
He takes a deep breath
and shields his eyes from the light.
The crowd applauds.
So I think I just have to do them all.
Yeah, why does he have a crowd?
It's good.
I like it.
So you're halfway through
your writing schedule.
Halfway through?
Hope it's going well.
What do you mean halfway through?
Can that be it?
I'm running out of time.
Holy shit, dude.
You're late.
Let's walk.
Yeah, well, I don't want to be late, do I?
I did.
Does this matter?
I don't think this matters.
I like it.
I don't think this is the scene sequence, guys.
I think this is just like
they're writing random lines.
I think this is just for fun.
It's starting to get annoyed.
One more day.
That's when the real fun starts.
Okay, this is just a test.
We're going to do the next one for real.
It's good.
I like it.
A grim-faced turnkey is looking out
in dark prison guard.
Okay, sure.
All right, final scene coming up here.
Yeah, you actually have to do
every single one, I think.
We're just doing this one.
All of this might be for no reason.
I think it's just to get the scenes written down.
Sorry, that's it.
No time for more writing.
The studio needs you to start production now.
We'll do the best we can with what you've got.
Oh, fuck.
Okay.
What?
I have every single scene.
Finished.
Assignment complete.
This script is hot.
What an edge.
What nuance.
Now, get on out to production
and shoot this thing
for some two-bit hack.
Steals all our great ideas.
Okay.
Relations on your script.
Ooh, working title.
Now you're going to see the film
a working title.
Don't worry.
You can change your title
at any time back in the relations.
How about...
Because that's essentially what I did.
I just put the fucking script in the dryer
and just took it out and took random pages.
FYI, by now, all the major papers
and all the online services
have read your script,
so you'd better do something original with it.
By the way, your script is now available
in all locations
and can be printed out in studio operations.
Okay.
Let's film it.
Stage 17.
Script.
All right.
What?
Are we ready?
Okay.
Your screenplay is done,
and it's been approved by the studio,
which means that now you're ready
to start production.
Production is tough.
You'll have to consider
every decision you make,
and because this is your first time,
this studio is going to be constantly
in your face on the budget and schedule.
Don't worry.
That happens to me too.
If you plan your shots
and you stick to your script,
I'm sure you're gonna do great.
I never start production
without first hiring
a brilliant director of photography.
Who should I hire?
Are you gonna give that to me
or do I have to do that myself?
Hi.
My name is Dean Cundy.
Some of the films I've shot
include Jurassic Park, Casper,
Back to the Future, and Roger Rabbit.
Wow.
One of the most challenging sequences
I've ever had to do was the raptor scene
in the kitchen for Jurassic Park.
The excitement of the storytelling
had to be told by the images,
which was greatly complicated
by the fact that the images came
at different times and from different places.
Sometimes the actors were in empty rooms,
sometimes the actors worked
with large mechanical dinosaurs,
and sometimes the dinosaurs
came from the computer.
And all of this had to be tied together
by the lighting and the camera angles.
And you're definitely not cut out for it.
Movies are about images.
Good luck, scrub.
And translating the director's vision
of the story into images is my job.
So I've read your script, very visual.
I've broken it down by moods,
made choices about which lights to use,
which lenses, and even what film stock is.
I'm gonna overstep the fuck out
of everything it says.
I want you to open the script
and click on the first scene
that you'd like to shoot.
Okay.
I'm gonna be like,
nah, nah, nah, nah, excuse me.
cut them off and stuff.
I'm gonna be the unbearable director
that nobody wants to work with.
All right.
In the dryer.
Let's film it.
Great place to start.
The green viewfinder shows you
where our master shot is set up.
Master shot is a wide shot
that shows all the action of a scene.
As a novice,
you'll be shooting all master shots.
Click on the green viewfinder to load your shot,
then the green camera button
down there to roll camera.
What?
Okay.
Remember, at the novice level,
you only have access to master shots.
After you finish this film
and move up to higher levels of play,
you'll have a huge array of additional shots,
including stunts, special effects, coverage,
and actor improvisations.
I can only film in one place?
Hi.
I'm Yvonne,
the hairdresser for your movie.
It's gonna take about 40 minutes
to get Laura ready for the movie.
Okay.
Yes, I get...
No, no, let's go.
I don't have time for this.
Let's shoot.
I want to shoot this now.
Let's go.
Hi.
I'm Yvonne,
the hairdresser for your movie.
It's gonna take about 40 minutes
to get Laura ready for the movie.
No.
Laura's fine.
I want to shoot this right now.
Let's go.
How do I...
What do I...
What do I do?
Oh, my God.
He's in an electric chair.
Wait.
This is going by scene by scene.
Spoilers.
Hi.
I'm Yvonne,
the hairdresser for your movie.
It's gonna take about 40 minutes
to get Laura ready for the movie.
Sure.
You just killed that pig.
Okay.
Laura's ready for make-up now.
What do you mean by that?
Okay.
Laura's ready for make-up now.
I'm gonna be ready for make-up.
I thought this was what you were doing.
Hi.
I'm Allison,
your costume designer.
We shot so late last night,
all the costume houses were closed.
I didn't have the priest sizes
when I left here last night.
It's gonna be an hour.
Sorry.
Why is there really...
What are you talking about?
We're all waiting here.
Do you want to wait for the priest's costume?
No.
The priest doesn't need to be in a costume.
Mm-hmm.
Okay.
Got it.
They sent me on a run.
But don't worry.
I'll be there for you.
If you need me,
just click on my pager
and then drag it over to the place
where you have the question about.
Now, this is a special pager.
I programmed it
to give you the information
you're looking for.
If you get lost
or you just want to know
how to do something faster,
click on the PA pager button.
It'll show you everything
you need to know
about the room you're in.
Well, that's another call.
I gotta go.
Yeah.
Let's go over here, then.
You ready?
All right.
We're gonna film
and then we're gonna proceed
first, apparently.
Uh, action.
This will be picture.
Quiet, please.
Rolling.
Speeding.
Action.
Any last words?
Cut.
After you watch a shot,
click on the red reel button
down there to print it.
That means you'll be able
to take it to the editing room.
If you don't print the shot,
then you won't have it
when you get there.
If you'd like to see
the shot again,
click on the picture
of the camera again.
Once you've printed a shot,
the viewfinder
will become a screen.
Okay.
The viewfinder
will become gray.
If you want to shoot
a new scene,
any last words?
You can either select
one from your script book
or use the scroll bar
to find the scene you want.
Okay.
So let's...
Cool?
Looks good.
All right.
What about...
Oh.
Is it another shot from here?
Hi.
I'm Allison,
your costume designer.
We shot so late last night.
I know.
All right.
All the costume houses
were closed.
I didn't have any presizes
when I left here last night.
It's gonna be an hour.
Sorry.
Okay.
We're ready in wardrobe.
We can go now.
Who are these fucking people?
These are people that apparently
work for the studio.
The paint on the electric chair
is still wet.
It might be really dangerous
if you try to shoot that now.
What?
Why is this shit not ready?
There's the entire production
team of people.
The first day of shooting is over.
You can relax now.
What?
But not for long.
It all starts again
on the second day.
Here, you better take a look
at the schedule and budget.
The only thing you filmed
was any last words.
This is gonna be one shot
in the movie.
Fuck.
Okay.
Here we go.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Pull it back.
Back, back, back.
I want this back.
$150,000 for that.
All right.
Let's go.
Scene four.
Did I just film this again?
Was it the same thing twice?
Print it.
Okay.
Now we have the two guys sleeping.
Budget.
Oh, I'm at $300,000 for that.
All right.
Action.
Very quiet, please.
Speed on tape.
And action.
The scene.
Ravenswood Prison.
Behind these cold stone walls,
Jack Cavello eats his last meal.
Here's his last rice.
And at $12,000,
and at 12 noon,
we'll walk that long last mile
to the electric chair.
The world was shocked
when it learned of the brutal slaying
of heiress Victoria Hemmerdinger.
The killer's motive,
theft of her famed jewelry collection,
including the spectacular
Diamond Tiara Del Fuego.
Her trusted chauffeur,
Jack Cavello,
was arrested and convicted,
but the jewels were never recovered.
Instrumentals captured
were Sigmund Payne and Leroy Terror.
Magicians, escape artists,
and personal psychics
to Mrs. Hemmerdinger.
That's Penn and Teller.
It was they who led police
to the murder weapon.
A pearl-haired saber
bound in the trunk of Cavello's car.
I don't want...
Okay, we'll print it.
Print.
All right, is the paint dry yet?
The paint on the electric chair
is still wet.
It might be really dangerous
if you try to shoot that now.
Well, why the fuck did you paint
the electric chair?
It's wood.
It's made out of wood.
Why would you paint it?
And the dryer faces stiff delays.
Okay, the paint's dry.
You can shoot now.
We delayed the movie
for paint to dry.
You've gone through
half your scheduled time.
Plan carefully for the rest
of the filming.
Are you fucking kidding me?
Let's go.
Stand by for picture.
Roll sound.
Speed.
Action.
What it came to pass
from the training town toward heaven
This is so bad.
I can't do any cuts.
I have to do long, wide shots.
This movie sucks.
Total ass.
I want to do cuts.
I want to do close-ups.
I want to do other angles.
I don't want to just do this one.
Print.
You do the cuts in post.
Well, if I don't film them,
how do I do cuts?
All right, I'm almost out of time here.
What are the other scenes?
There's a priest coming down.
All right, this is the walk.
Let's get this one here
with the grandma.
There's paint on the bars.
Hi, I'm Yvonne.
I'm your hairdresser for the movie.
It's going to take about
20 minutes to get Ma ready.
Why is Ma wearing a wig?
Why can't you just use
Ma's real hair?
Hi, I'm Yvonne.
I'm your hairdresser for the movie.
It's going to take about
20 minutes to get Ma ready.
All right, 20 minutes.
Delay the movie because
somebody needs to put a wig on.
Okay, Ma's ready to go
into makeup now.
All right, let's go.
Why would you...
It's six days to shoot a whole movie.
Doesn't it usually take like
three months to shoot a whole movie?
Roll sound.
Sound speed.
Action.
Clinic.
You need to speak up.
What?
You late to your own execution?
This will be picture.
Quiet, please.
Rolling.
Speeding.
Action.
The Lord is my shepherd.
He made me lie down in green pastures
to restore my soul.
Yea, for I walk through the valley
of the shadows of death.
I fear no evil,
for Thou art with me.
Surely goodness and mercy
shall follow me
all the days of my life,
and I will rarely come out
to the Lord forever.
Cut.
Okay.
One more day.
That's all that's left.
Make sure you've got everything you need.
All right, we got one more scene to shoot.
Print it.
Print.
All right, now can I get
this scene shot over here?
Not Ma's wig.
The one that I couldn't do
in the very beginning.
This one.
All right, right here.
Let's go.
Roll it.
Quiet on the set.
And rolling.
Sound speed.
Action.
Why is he...
Why is it like...
Why...
What?
Why is he smoking?
Why is it dry ice all over?
What?
Jennifer Aniston's in the movie
for one take.
That's it.
She's a reaction shot.
I can still do another one.
He's in the dryer.
Steaming from the dryer.
You're kind of between
a rock and a hard place.
You've used up all your time
in production,
so if you want to continue shooting,
you'll have to trade for time
in post-production.
No, I don't give a shit.
That means less time for editing,
sound effects...
No, I want to edit
and put sound effects in.
I want to put like clowns like...
Who's going to be fucking funny?
Uh, no, no, no, no.
I'll go with what I have.
Let's go.
All right, I'm good.
Let's do it.
Look back to editing.
Editing.
All right.
I'm prepared for this.
We're using actual fucking discs today.
You didn't think
I came fucking prepared, did you?
Uh-oh.
You didn't think
I came prepared today.
I fucking got a virtual machine
running Windows 3.1.
You don't think I fucking got that?
There's an old Hollywood saying
that all great movies
are made in the editing room.
You're going to take the footage
that you've shot
and you're going to assemble it.
Editing is about making choices
without all the pressure
of physical production.
You and your film editor
will be looking for
the most original way
to tell your story.
This is a time
for making decisions like
faster or slower,
funnier or scarier,
longer or shorter.
Funny or serious?
And this is the place
where the director
has the most control.
And for me personally,
where I have the most fun.
Hi, I'm Michael Cahn.
And a few of the films I've...
You might know me
as doing way cooler shit
than you will ever do
in your whole life.
Editing is always fun.
By the way, let's now talk
about what you have to do.
It's a new challenge.
While editing Schindler's List
and Crackout Poland,
we were also finishing
Jurassic Park.
We used a satellite transmission
from the visual effects company
in Northern California
so that Stephen could view
and approve the dinosaur footage.
But even with all this
technical wizardry,
we never lost sight
of the importance
of telling the story.
This is the editing room
where you'll be creating
your own story.
The first step
of editing any movie
is to view all of your footage.
Your PA will show you
around the flatbed.
You know, that might be
my favorite stream moment
in the last six months.
The editing process
can be fairly complicated,
so I'm going to go through it
step by step.
But before I show you
how to start editing,
I should probably take you
on a quick tour
of the editing bay.
By the way,
I'm in control now.
Your mouse isn't broken.
You'll be working
with two decks.
The one on the left,
deck one,
is your selection deck.
That's where we'll be
loading up
each of the shots
that you printed
during production,
so you can clip out
the parts of the shot
you want to use in your film.
On the right is
your assembly deck.
That's where we'll put together
the edited shots
to make them move.
I have to fucking pay attention.
Both of these decks
are controlled
by the single control panel
in the middle of your screen.
You can tell which deck
is being controlled
by the panel
because the light
on top of that deck's monitor
will light up.
I'm going to go ahead
and load one of your shots
into the selection deck
so I can show you
how the control panel works
and how to make it
all edit.
The first thing you need to do
is click on the script
and then click on the scene
that you want to start with.
Okay.
Use the still frames
at the top of your screen
to select which shot
from production
you'd like to start editing.
The master shot is always
automatically loaded
into the selection deck
to the left.
If it isn't the shot
that you want to start with,
you can load another shot
by clicking on one
of the other still shots
at the top of the screen
or by selecting
a different scene
from your script.
Okay.
Now that we have a shot loaded,
you'll need to find
where to begin your story.
To do this,
we need to use the buttons
on the control panel.
The first button to start with
is the play button.
This will play the shot
on the selection deck
until we tell it to stop
by hitting the play button
a second time.
If we already know
where to start our edit,
use the fast forward button
to find the place
where we want to be.
If we're very close
to the start of our edit,
we can use the step forward
button to go ahead
one frame at a time.
Yeah, yeah, I know.
The three rewind buttons
on the left side
of the control panel
work just like the forward buttons,
except they play
your shot backwards.
Once I've found the frame
where I want to start my edit,
I have to mark that spot
on the film.
To do this,
I'll use the mark button
on the control panel.
This will turn the cursor
into a clip
that I can then clip
onto the film
so I'll remember
where my edit begins.
This is called the end point.
Now that I've marked my end point,
I need to find the frame
where I want the edit to end,
called the out point.
I'll do this using the play
and rewind buttons
on the control panel,
just like I did
to find the end point.
Yeah.
We want it to be right there.
I can't get over it.
I'm sorry.
I'm having trouble
getting over that.
The mark button
on the control panel
turned into a cut button
once I marked my end point.
That's to remind me
that my end point
has been set,
and the next frame I mark
will be my out point.
I'll click on the cut button
to select the end of my edit.
This time the cursor
will turn into a pair of scissors.
Cut it.
Now that I've marked
my in and out points
on the selection deck,
the cut is made
and the cursor becomes
a piece of film.
If I like this edit,
I can put this clip
on my assembly deck
to make it a part
of my edited movie.
Or if I don't like it,
I can throw it away
in the trash can to the right.
All right.
So that's the movie over here.
This is the actual movie
on the right side.
The clip I just edited
is now loaded
on the assembly deck.
The last frame of the clip
I just cut is on the monitor.
The assembly deck is active
and is being controlled
by the control panel.
If I'm not sure
about what I've edited,
I can use the rewind
and play buttons
to take a look.
If I want to trim
a little bit more off
this edited clip
and throw it away,
I can use the mark
and cut buttons
just as I did
on the left deck.
The assembly deck
has another added feature.
The scroll bar
below the monitor
lets you jump through
the different cuts
in your movie,
just like the scroll bar
in production
let you jump through
the different scenes
in your script.
Now that the first edit
has been made,
you'll want to go back
to your script
and load up the next shot
and add that to your movie.
To do this,
you'll go through
the same process
that we went through
for the first one.
I know this sounds complicated,
but don't worry about it.
Look at the hang of it
after you've made
a couple of edits.
Then you'll just be
flying through the footage.
You've still got my pager
if you want to get more help
on the buttons
or other items in the room.
It's like you can also
take your tutorials again
if you want.
Just click on the
PA Pager button
and then the
replay tutorial button
on the help screen.
Okay, I'll clean up
this mess I made
so you can
put together
your movie.
Good luck and
don't forget
that you're still
working under a budget
and a schedule.
A schedule, okay.
I thought you were going
to clean this shit up.
Oh, okay.
All right, here we go.
So we've got
interior, chamber.
Here we go.
Jack is brought
into the chamber.
Now, if this isn't
the scene you'd like
to start with,
go back to your script
and pick another.
Get away from me.
Otherwise, let's get
to work on this one.
Why are you paging me
for this?
Okay.
You double-paged me.
The best thing to do
is watch this shot
to see exactly
where you want to
make your cut.
I know.
To do this,
hit the play button.
If you want to stop,
I was a goddamn YouTuber.
That goes for all
the other buttons too.
Do you see my edits?
Once you go,
again to stop.
When you decide
to start your cut.
I cut 40 times
in a tenth of a second.
Nobody even knew
I did it.
Up to the film on the left.
I'm a cut master.
It will set your end point.
That's where you'll
start your edit.
It was like
you didn't even know
what happened.
Cut, cut, cut, cut, cut.
There we go.
So I want to start.
It came too fast.
Wait.
Back it up.
End point.
Right here.
Bingo.
Now that you've
marked your end point,
play through the shot
to find where you
want to end it.
Once you find
a good spot,
stop the deck.
Pick up the scissors
and use them
on the film
on the left deck.
After clicking
the scissors,
you should see
a piece of film
in your hand.
That's your cut.
Drag it over
to the assembly deck,
the one on the right,
and click it.
They really, really
were concerned
that nobody
was going to get this shit.
They were so scared
that nobody was going
to fucking understand
how to do this at all.
Done.
Got it.
Bingo.
Cut it.
Great.
You've gotten the hang of it.
I told you it was easy.
Now select another shot
to follow this one
and follow the same process
you did the first time.
I'm going to re-
Each new clip will follow
the frame being
displayed on that monitor.
Okay.
So let's go.
New scene.
Here we go.
That's them.
Okay.
Bring them in.
Next scene.
News process.
No.
I don't even want that
in the movie.
Okay.
I talked to Laura.
She's that...
No, no, no.
Get back.
No.
No, no, no.
Back, back, back, back.
Jack and Father eggs at the cell.
How do I-
Okay.
That's how you go back.
There we go.
This is what I want.
No.
I don't want that actually.
There it is.
Okay.
Here it is.
I was looking for that.
Any last words?
Why is it filming
the whole thing?
Back to the beginning.
All right.
In point here.
Any last words?
Cut it.
Bingo.
Did I just fuck that up?
No.
Okay.
Any last words?
Now...
Hold on.
No, no, no, no, no.
Now I need...
No.
I need the kiss.
Can I put this
in the beginning of the movie?
How do I put this
I want it back here.
You know what I mean?
I want to put this here.
Okay.
That's fine.
I want this to happen
in the beginning.
Hold on.
I want to change the point.
I want to change
the edit point.
I want this to happen
to be this.
No.
Trash it.
Trash.
No.
Why is this here?
There we go.
Okay.
Hold on.
This is fucking...
This is memento.
No.
That's it.
Fuck.
First day in the editing room
is always terrible.
What?
Don't worry.
Everything looks great.
Oh shit.
I don't have
very much money left.
Wait.
Is this two back-to-back kissing...
Is this two back-to-back kissing scenes?
Just make the whole thing
different cuts of kissing.
I want more...
I need more time.
I'm running out of time,
so I have to go to the end here
and I have to put...
I got to put...
I'm coming out.
They didn't give me enough money.
Where is it?
Where the fuck is it?
Where is him coming out of the dryer?
Is there enough time?
Can I do another one?
I wish I could get a bigger picture of this shit.
It's red, right?
Where is it?
If I can fit another big kiss scene,
I'm going to do it.
Wait.
No, that's Kiss's forehead.
There it is.
Right there.
I still have to add sound effects and shit.
How much more can I do with this?
Why is the studio letting me do this?
I thought that...
I thought I had...
I thought I was out of money.
Am I out of money?
Where's my budget?
No, I'm not out of money yet.
Okay.
I think that's good
because I need to...
I need to put music in and shit.
I need money for that.
Can you put in reversed clips?
I don't think so.
So do I...
Is that it?
Can I leave here with this done
or do I have to put this somewhere?
Do I slam dunk it?
Have there be two dryer scenes?
No, that's...
I can't do that.
What do I got for days left?
Total days.
Days to edit.
Three.
Okay.
No, no.
That's what it is.
Wait, you guys want to bring out
more than two or three people?
No.
No, no.
We need the you're late.
I need the you're late.
That happens right here.
And he's late because he spent so much time
kissing his girlfriend.
Okay.
Where is it?
You're late.
Not the broadcast.
Here it is.
You're late.
Let's walk.
Well, I don't want to be late now, do I?
Mom?
Well, I guess this is goodbye.
I have to.
I have to do it.
You don't tell me I can't do it
because I'm going to do it.
You only have a day left to finish up.
This is plenty of time.
Take care of any loose ends
and nail this thing down.
Check the budget one last time.
Hold on.
Mom?
I guess this is goodbye.
I have to fucking focus here.
Now, do I?
Mom?
Right.
Well, I guess this is goodbye.
I can't be stopped.
Oh shit.
Am I?
Well, that's it.
It's been a pleasure working with you.
Now, head upstairs to the foley stage
and start creating your sound effects.
No!
Okay, I got one more.
Mom?
I guess this is goodbye.
Any last words?
Okay, we have to go and edit.
So, I now take this masterpiece.
Oh my God.
My fucking head.
We go to the sound bay.
Jesus fucking God.
Sound effects.
Please wait while the foley artists prepare the studio.
What the fuck?
Okay, I thought he had a gun.
Now comes the part of filmmaking that's always fun.
I looked over at you guys.
You brought your edited film into the foley studio
where you're going to work with the sound designer, Mark,
to add sound effects.
Hey, those are all my achievements.
I was nominated for five Grammys.
I'm a sound designer.
We're here on the foley stage,
which is where we create sound effects for movies.
Some of the movies I've designed sound for are The Flintstones,
three of the Star Trek movies, Beauty and the Beast, and Aladdin.
When it sounds like it's raining in a movie,
or it sounds like you're in the middle of a tropical rain forest,
those sounds were put together by people like me.
One of the most fun parts of designing sound for movies
is getting to create sounds that don't exist in real life.
So, for example, on Aladdin,
to create the sound of Aladdin being chased by a tidal wave of lava,
I recorded the sound of my mother's spaghetti sauce
simmering on the stove.
Your PA will now show you how to lay in sound effects.
That was very clearly you putting your mouth around a straw
with milk and blowing bubbles.
It would have been easier that way.
Clicking on the record button, followed by the play button,
then clicking on the appropriate prop at the right time.
It might take some practice, but just remember
that you can erase sounds by doing the same process,
but hitting the mute button instead of a prop.
Record button and play button, hold on though.
Let's just wait a minute, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I want to see, I need to see if this is going to work.
What are these sounds?
Oh God, that's fucking loud, okay.
Ah, ow, my, that, I actually just got, I think I hurt myself.
I really did, I just hurt myself.
Shit, no, how do I, how do I remove a sound?
How do you remove a sound?
Undo, is this undo?
What, are you talking?
What did he say?
I don't hear any sound effect though.
It should be right like here, right?
So why is it not playing?
What the fuck was that?
What?
Yeah, why is it muted?
But record and then play, record, play.
Any last words?
Everyone has to applaud this.
No, no, no, no, I'm not going to do that.
I need to see what the other ones do.
Ah, something's wrong with me.
My like right, lower right side of my stomach is killing, it's like a knife going into it when I laugh.
What the fuck is wrong with me?
I think I pulled a muscle laughing at this shit.
Ah, is there an, did anybody like bend over or anything?
Uh oh, we've lost audio on the help.
$819,000.
What is this?
You know, I got to do it.
Do you know what I mean?
I have to do it.
Print it.
Let's go.
That's it.
I did it.
Movie over.
Movie done.
Add the shotgun?
No, that's too much.
It's overkill.
I know where I can put that.
I'm almost out of budget.
Last day.
He's like, he bites off her ear and then starts kissing her.
No, no, no, no, it's too much.
It's too comedy, too much comedy.
No, too much.
That's too, that's over comedy.
I'm not going to over comedy this.
No, that's over comedy.
I'm done.
That's, that's comedy overload.
Done.
No, I can't.
I've got to get out.
I will over comedy the fuck out of that and I don't want to.
Graphics?
This is the room where you'll create the marketing campaign for your film.
You'll have the opportunity here to create advertising that will communicate to people
all over the world the reasons they should go out and pay to see your movie.
If your movie doesn't open to big audiences, you get to blame all the people in this room.
Okay.
Most people think that once a film is finished, the movie making process is complete.
In fact, there's quite a bit more to it.
Hi, I'm Buffy Shutt.
I run the marketing department.
Our group designs the posters and ads that you see in newspapers, on buses,
and at your local movie theater.
I've created marketing campaigns for such films as Babe, Apollo 13, Casper, and T2.
When we envision a campaign, we often find the key to it is in a music cue,
a single image, or a line from the script.
I can't wait to make the poster.
Good lines sell the movie.
Great lines become part of our vocabulary.
Frankly, my dear, I don't give a damn.
Houston, we have a problem.
I'll be back.
Let's see if we can come up with something unique for your film.
Oh, oh.
Click on the poster maker, title vision, or the ticomatic,
and your PA will show you how to create your film.
Poster maker.
I gotta get a good poster.
I'll bet you're sitting there with your stomach in knots, terrified no one's gonna like your movie.
Well, no, it's for other reasons, but it still is.
Well, let's get to work on the marketing campaign.
If you want to start on the poster design, click on the drawing table.
To print up tickets, use the ticomatic.
Use the title vision machine to print credit titles to add to your film.
Let's do poster.
Okay.
That blank spot in the middle of your desk is your canvas.
In order to place a graphic image onto your canvas,
click on the stacks of pictures on the left.
When you click on a stack, you'll see all of that stack's images displayed.
Click on whatever image you want, then drag it to the canvas.
Place as many as you want to work with.
Once they're on the canvas, you can select your images and move them to the foreground or the background.
Resize them or erase them.
If you make a mistake, use the undo button.
If you don't like the image, click on the eraser and the selected image will disappear.
If you want to add words, click on the stencils.
When you're done, you can print your poster with the print button.
If you have any trouble, use the help screen on my PA page for further detail.
No.
No, undo, undo, undo.
Use the pen.
How do I use the pen?
I want this in the, here we go.
Switch to the back, I want this in the foreground.
Okay.
Now I want, now it's going to be big like that.
Alright, how do I use this paint?
It looks like shit.
That's the kind of cover that somebody makes when they make their own DVDs.
I've probably made college DVDs where I had to DVD label maker.
And I thought it was, I was so cool.
It wasn't too big.
No, this one's better.
Up a little more, like right, right there.
Alright, this is, I don't, I don't like the pink.
Yeah, it's going to have to do.
Anything else?
Oh, fuck.
Oh shit.
I'm done.
Next, next picture please.
Needs more kissing.
This is, that's better.
So that's it, right?
I'm done.
Print it.
Post it done.
Is it right here?
Windows 10 print.
No, no, I don't want to print this.
I don't want to print this.
I don't have a printer hooked up.
In the dryer poster heralds a hot new film.
Tickets gone with the wind.
Okay.
Title vision.
You may press the left arrow at any time to change a previous entry.
Press okay to move forward.
This is where you'll make your titles.
Just answer the questions that the title machine asks
and you'll get to make the credits for your film.
Okay.
Do you want to change the title?
No.
Click on the window to cycle through the title effects.
No, that's not, that's fine.
George Lucas wipe?
That's good.
Click on the window to step through the fonts.
Good.
Click on the window to split the foreground colors.
Red.
Ugh.
What do you think?
Should I do 3D glasses?
Yeah, I think we should do look at anything else with 3D glasses on.
That sounds good.
Ugh.
That's fine.
No.
No, just black.
That's good.
Do you want your credits to play before the movie?
After the movie.
Would you like to credit your writers?
Would you like to credit your DP?
Would you like to credit your production assistant?
Would you like to credit the rest of your crew?
It was me.
Stunt coordinator.
What stunts?
Press okay if you'd like this disclaimer to appear in your credits.
Disclaimer.
Select a musical style for your credits.
Okay, or...
That's better.
It's a lightning strike too.
Alright.
Steven Spielberg presents.
Are you just going to slap your name on this?
Okay.
Now the tick-o-matic.
Whatever this is.
Oh, it's the ticket.
This is where you'll make tickets for your film's premiere.
Just answer the questions as they come up.
And when you're done, you can print out the tickets eight at a time.
Only eight.
Do you want your name to appear on the ticket?
Yes.
What is the price that you'd like to appear on the ticket?
Twenty million dollars?
Nobody can go.
No.
It would...
Uh...
Let's make it...
Let's make it like a...
Fifty-five hundred bucks.
Fifty-five hundred dollars.
Click on the ticket to step through the ticket styles.
That one's good.
Click on the ticket to step through the ta...
The fonts.
Alright.
Are these movie tickets or are these like boyfriend girlfriend good-for-one back rub coupons?
Click on...
That's good.
Make that huge.
This doesn't even matter.
Press the print button to print it.
Eight tickets fit on a letter size page.
No.
They really did want you to print this and give it to your parents and then they watch
what you did in here.
That's why they have a monetary number here.
I get it.
It's to get the family in the room.
What do you mean print it?
Why do I have to print this and put it in the Discord?
You know you can just press the screen cap button and just crop that and just use it
for whatever you want.
Print it.
I don't have a printer!
We're good.
Jeremy French Fry writes own ticket on In the Dryer.
What?
We're good.
Let's go.
What about the lab?
What's the lab?
So the suspense begins here because this is the lab where your film will be processed and
it can take a while so we'll keep you posted.
What?
What do you mean it can take a while?
Start the...
I'm your music editor and I can't help but notice you don't have any music in your movie.
If your budget can afford it, come back with me to the music studio and let's get to work.
Alright, let's put some music in.
I'm going to put in like five seconds of music.
The movie is only like 42 seconds long.
You ever watch a movie on TV with the sound off?
Something's missing and it's not just the dialogue.
The music that plays under each scene is such a critical part of movie making because it
might set a delicate mood, it might make us cry, or keep us in gut-twisting suspense,
or tell us when to be scared and for how long.
Hi, I'm Laurie Higgins Tobias, your music editor.
I'll be doing the same work on your film as I did on the Flintstones, Stargate, and Independence
Day.
A lot of Flintstones movie makers here.
A music editor helps create a useful concept and foundation for the movie.
While working on the Flintstones, playing music from the original cartoon series underneath
early edits of the movie, helps the director decide which style of music to use in the
finished film.
I've watched your cut, selected some music cues, and broken them down by categories.
The Flintstones live action?
You will have to decide what kind of mood to set by matching the music cues with the
scenes you have already cut together.
The music is broken down by category in the book down there on the mixing board.
Your PA will tell you how to lay down your music track.
I know, you're going to have to hit record, then play, then play a song.
In the beginning levels, you'll only have access to a few instruments, but with experience,
you'll be able to add the sound of a rock band or even a symphony orchestra.
To lay down your music, open a music button and select the kind of music you want to work
with.
From there, select a music cue and the instruments will set up to play.
To record, hit the record button followed by the play button.
To play the music, just click on the instruments.
Okay, so let's see.
Small orchestra, strings.
I don't understand.
Why are there pictures in here?
Literally click the instruments.
What instrument?
Oh.
Why would you have the light off back here?
What?
What the fuck is going on?
Oh, this just turns the lights on and turns the lights off.
I didn't do that.
What the fuck is happening in this movie?
I didn't put this music in.
What the fuck was that?
It's cursed.
Oh shit, does that mean it's loud?
Alright, well, I don't know.
Figured it out.
Alright, so it's open book, pick thing, click up here.
That is very dumb.
Alright.
What?
I don't have enough money to do this.
I don't have enough money.
I gotta get out.
Okay, here we go.
You ready?
This is it.
Three, two, one.
Action.
Hey!
No!
Why is it not doing it?
That just costed money.
It didn't do anything.
Oh, you motherfucker, really?
What the fuck?
Oh god, the game's breaking.
Alright, alright, alright.
Why?
What the fuck?
I can't record it.
I don't have any money.
Alright, well, fuck it.
That's it.
Print it.
Let's go.
I'm out of money.
Process.
Is it working?
No, no, no, no, no, no.
Maybe it'll remember us.
There's no save game.
Maybe it might just remember who we are.
You know what I mean?
It could just remember that we were doing this.
It's a Windows game.
Definitely not.
You never know.
Because when I'm during all that, like cutting and shit,
I think it's just dumping shit into the C drive.
No!
No, it was going so well!
It was going so well!
At least we got to see it.
Damn it!
There was so much more to explore.
I can skip that.
Welcome.
I've chosen you.
Okay.
Whoa.
Yeah, I don't think there even is.
I'm gonna laugh my ass off, please.
I would laugh my ass off if the poster's still here.
No.
We were so close to clicking on this.
We were so close.
I'm not giving up yet.
It's not here.
Okay, now this is Studio Operations, where you get started.
Oh!
It's here!
Wait.
But what?
I don't want to write over this.
Hold on.
Am I gonna write over this?
Like, just, that's the movie, right?
Just hit okay.
Just, that's the movie, right?
Don't, don't, don't, don't.
Just go to the theater.
Look up what it does.
Guys, nobody's ever played this game before.
I'm gonna go to the theater.
Disc three.
I got it.
Where's disc two?
I freaked out and dropped it.
It's right here.
I got a piss tube really bad.
All right, come on.
Let us, let us watch it.
Let us get the, we've been here for like almost two hours.
Mit one.
What?
This isn't my movie.
Okay.
All these, where's your movie?
Is this the credits of the game?
Imagine you went to watch a movie and it was just the credits of the movie.
Well, that sucked.
What a shitty movie.
Oh my God.
All right.
I have to, we have to try to load the other one.
You know what I'm saying?
Go back to the save.
Hold on.
I can't make decisions like this.
I'm gonna pee my pants.
I can't make a decision with a piss building up inside me.
All right.
Give me, I'll be right back.
I'm literally going to die.
I'm going to piss my pants if I don't leave right now.
I'll be right back.
All right.
We're going to try to load that save.
American dad music.
Back up, back up the files, back up the files.
I think, I think this is this.
I'm here to assist you.
What happened to it?
Oh my God.
You're going to give me a fucking heart attack.
There's okay and there's delete.
So snapshot VM.
I don't know how to do that.
I have absolutely no fucking idea how to do that.
Test it on an empty slot.
Got it.
Bingo.
Bingo, bingo, bingo, bingo, bingo, bingo, bingo, bingo, bingo, bingo.
There it is.
Options.
Export, import.
No, this is fine.
We're good.
I'm just, we're just going to watch it.
We don't need to go to the fucking lab.
Let's go.
In the dryer.
Yeah.
Oh shit.
Fuck the lab.
Oh.
That's bullshit.
Fucking disk two.
Disk swap.
All right.
I ain't going to move.
I'm not touching anything.
I'm going to let it just sit here for a second.
Nobody move.
I have start and I have stop.
Okay.
Here we go.
Start.
Okay.
Don't move.
Now what?
I don't think we can print them.
I think they're unprintable.
We're just going to have to view the work print.
That's all we can do.
We know we're going to have no sound effects.
Damn it.
Oh, well, whatever.
We can still do it.
It's still all right.
Export it.
Actually sad.
Well, that's unfortunate.
But you know, these are all a complete gamble.
Every single one of these games that you're going to see that you have seen is just throw
dice in the air.
Is it going to work?
Who fucking knows?
I'm just really happy that we at least got to see this shit.
I'm going to try to export it.
Welcome.
Whoa.
Here we go.
I'm here to assist you.
Don't scare me like this.
Okay.
So German French fry loaded up.
I'm going to go to options and I'm going to go to export.
Export to where?
Hold on.
Let me just.
Oh, this is not.
This is not doing what I think you guys think it's going to do.
I did it.
It's a dot.
Dat.
Here.
Why is this not on?
Look.
Okay.
It.
That's what I just did.
Export dot.
Dat.
You know, let's go.
Let's just watch the movie while we have a minute.
We just need to see it.
It's a save file.
Not the movie.
That's unfortunate.
Will VLC play this?
Oh, well, let's go into the dryer.
Let's view the work print.
Got to do what we got to do.
Load the dot.
Dat and windows media to view it.
I highly, highly suspect that that's going to work.
At least give us this.
Give us this.
Let us at least see the damn thing.
Even without music, it don't matter.
Here we go.
There's nobody in.
Oh, right.
Because it's $5,000 a ticket.
That makes sense.
Nobody here.
Mom.
I guess this is goodbye.
Any last words?
Impresses the studio with sharp director's cut.
Ooh.
Did it.
Try the lab now.
All right.
I'm going to try the lab.
I'm going to try the lab quick.
I'm going to do lab.
Press button.
Start walking around.
I'm not even going to give it a second.
Ready?
Watch this.
Here we go.
One, two, three.
Start it.
It's going.
Here's the thing.
I'm fucking leaving now.
Leave.
Quick.
Out.
Leave.
I can't.
It's frozen.
Stop it.
Oh.
I caught it right in the middle.
What should I do?
Should I say yes?
I fucked it up.
So now should I say yes?
Because right now it's like, hold on, wait a minute.
I caught it.
Keep going.
Stop it again.
Like, you don't.
No, don't.
Like, I'm just trying to keep it from crashing.
You know what I mean?
Like, every, like, five, fuck you.
No, it's not going to work.
I thought I could, like, intervene and, like, make it think again.
No.
It's not going to work.
Oh, well.
The dat is a media file.
Open it in...
Hold on.
Wait a second.
You telling me that's a media file?
Let me look.
I'm going to laugh my fucking ass off if that's true.
All right.
Let's go into director's chair.
Here's movie, movie dot dat.
Okay.
There it is.
It's 63 kilobytes, guys.
I don't think this is going to work.
Okay.
I'm going to open this with VLC media player.
No, that ain't going to work.
It's not going to work.
Oh, well.
Let's keep going.
This next one we're going to put in is going to be a very interesting.
At least we got to see it.
At least we got to play it.
And I kind of want to do more of that.
Put the dat file in your router config.
Why would I fucking do that?
All right.
The next one is called Piper, where you play as the Pied Piper.
It is a children's game.
Give me one sec.
Will I move this around?
Piper.
I might have to move the viewing angle around a little bit.
Let me get into here.
Okay.
Are you ready?
Let's go.
Episode one.
Midas Valley Mayhem.
Episode two.
Piper's Promise.
Episode three.
Rats rule.
Rats.
Episode three.
Rats rule.
Rats.
Episode four.
Showdown.
Midas Valley Mayhem.
I love this voice.
I already love the voice.
All right.
Let's go.
Let's do episode one.
Level two is fine.
Video adventure.
Rat movie the game.
Video acrobatics.
Ooh.
Can't wait.
Oh, fuck.
Is he having a fire?
What the fuck?
I think that's the fire.
Is episode two.
I think you might need an audio codec.
This is I have to take my headphones out. This is fucking horrendous
Do you hear this? I?
Alright
Wheel is okay. What do you mean? We've seen we've seen rats before
we're no longer getting the
Like you're inside of a blender
This game has rats yeah, I can't just quit
humans rule
We're gonna have to skip the gist of what's going on
Don't do it
You have to hear this
Why I can't keep playing that guys that's good. I'm gonna that's gonna cause pain
Look at this is a perfect game. This is so perfect
Watch it on YouTube fix it. Oh, I it's the dentist thing
I can't fix this
This is really drilling in my teeth
What are you here for?
Well, I'm the Pied Piper. I heard you had a rat problem. Is that true?
Well, yeah, we do kind of have a rat problem, but maybe
Yeah, I heard the rats are in my shoe and they're making this shit in this pasta sauce. It's disgusting. I tell you
Yeah, and I'm scared of the rats too because rats are weird and furry me too rats are furry
Hmm, and I guess I can help you all out here. I the guys I can't as far
I have to try to put this shit like far away from me. I can hear this
That's the Green Ranger. Yeah
Why does this all sound fine
Jason David Frank
No
I'm out. I'm up. We're going to another one settings. It's big and small are the settings guys
I need to know the lore the settings that that is the settings it opens up this compartment
What about practice? Wait, here we go. Got it
I have two minutes to do this. Why the fuck do I have two minutes to do this?
Oh
I get all right. We can we can just do the puzzles. What about episode 2?
1872 1870
This is just memory
1872 1872
1869 1869 that's 71 69 is up here
70 63 is over here
63 right down here 71 71 over here
63 over this way
69 up here
74 over here
74 right next to it
71 up here
63 down here. Okay, I'm done
I'm
Not even paying attention I'm reading chat
I'm literally clicking random places and looking at chat. All right. Now, let's see what things are
63 up there seven sixty three seventy one
sixty three sixty three
See guys, will you fucking relax I
Have an idea this idea might work give me one sec
I'm just gonna cue up the cutscenes if they're on YouTube and
just
Mute this and just play the cutscene. Thank you the tickles for the five community subs. Thank you
Appreciate it. Is this shit on YouTube? I would be shocked if it was thank you for the five subs. Oh for real
Let me see if this works
Just give me one second chunky baloney five community subs. Thanks both you guys
Okay, I think I got it he's just like a whole cutscene here I'm gonna try to cue this up episode 1
Episode 1
Alright, here we go. Ready? I gotta try to cue this up. I get it's muted
Yeah, okay
Hold on. I have to go physically in here and do the mixer. I can't mute this cuz I'm gonna mute everything
Alright, that should work
All right, here we go and I fixed it three two one. Oh, come on
What the fuck? No, great. This is bad. I think oh no, the whole thing's coming down
Here comes if the first force quit of the night out of the the virtual machine
All right. Well, that's it for that one. I have to I have to force close this shit
Cannot carry out the commands and apparently it's still paused. I have to give me a fucking break
Crunchy ass stuff. All right, here we go. Coming back. This next one is
called paparazzi
You have to take pictures of celebrities, I guess
Well, whatever. I'm not gonna put it back in ever again. Anyway, all right, here we go
Now this one hopefully works. He's sad if it didn't it's the dice you roll during these streams though
All right, let's go open open close close
paparazzi
Incoming. I swear it's incoming very soon here. You'll see it in just a moment
Is there a cry
It's loading and
All right, uh, why is it no audio? Oh, it's cuz I turned it off right paparazzi
tales of tinseltown
Click on a face to
Choose your persona as relative Biff Zoe
Luciano Hilary or rat so I mean this has to be rat so
It worked before
They tried learning it again
Open go
Ratso, okay. Well, there's another swing and a miss apparently
I'm gonna try one more thing. Did the Steven Spielberg game break the VM? I don't think so
Around the setup. I think I already did that. Oh, I mean, I don't want you to see where my files are going
I already did this
Come on do it I could hear it. We're good. Are we I have no idea how good we are
Calls
Jellybean scandal
Well, it was just at our customs office in Florida and our investigation just uncovered an invoice for Iranian jelly beans
shipped to tinseltown I
Think there's some sort of deal going down tonight in one of those dark alleys and none of our photographers are in town
Okay, I don't get anything
Our bureau chief says you can sell the photo to us
I have to take a picture of you sell jelly beans because we want to break the story first. I
Gotta go. I got a plane to catch. Good luck and hurry
Okay, what about Goldie?
Reisenstein
All right, so I gotta take a put take it what about I got a tip for you that I thought you okay
What about the TV?
Burn your feet. Yeah, right right dad. Yeah, you gotta pull them away. Whoever that actor was was just like, oh fuck
I can't keep it here
You can't go that close
Those are some ugly ass socks, too, by the way
He's an ex-cop on the run framed by evil people free fray by evil so he pretty da
Was pyro
By George Spielman stay out of the kitchen if you can't stand
I
Mean soon to a theater near you. That's a much better movie than I made like 20 minutes ago
Tip rib-eye on sports not your own tip rib-eye sports in the celebrity endorsement department
Tennis star Andre McConnor just signed on for a reported 3.2 million dollars to do a series of commercials for Mikey shoes
No word yet on how much they're paying McConnor's babysitter
I
Was like that's it what kind of pizza is that
What is that? Is that cinnabon all of the ingredients are coming together and then voila
Magnificent. I make it is every Friday for one of our base the customs
This is freaking me out
You and me have a date with destiny so
Then what is that? Is that a Christmas tree true?
Pictures of stuff
Okay map alley go to the alley
Get a picture of the deal going down. Oh, here we go get a picture of the deal
Oh, I just took a picture fuck wait, how about right now got it, right? He just looks he's looking right into the camera
Try flee
Click on the photo. You want to sell this one the one with he's got the briefcase open looking right in the camera
5,000 click on a buyer place magazine. What was that guy's name? Yeah, the FBI is only gonna give me 250 bucks for this
What was the?
That guy that said give me that picture. Don't sell it to anybody else
I didn't get the guy's name
place magazine
Eight grand. Let's go the jelly seller. There it is
All right anymore calls
I already did
Again
Assignments for you yet, but don't worry. I'm looking out for your ride to just hang in there
All right, let's go to bed. This is the sleeper. What just happened. Oh
They're gonna park go to the park. How do I go to sleep?
I don't know who this is
I
Just jumped in front of me and I just took pictures of them day two. Here we go calls
Thank you for turning me on to their cheapest cameras
I thought it was going to be some hole in the ball place
But I found the lens I was looking for and their cheapest fellow. He told me where I could get Sean Pendleton
I want to thank you. You are making me a very rich man. This is German a German accent. Oh
All right
I
Senator Frederick Frederick's was briefly hospitalized today when he felt severe stomach pains after eating at Sigismund
He ate the grilled salmon platter
Frederick said it's not the restaurant's fault. I just didn't realize there was fish in that dish
Frederick's was released soon afterwards and that's the news for fish and
Chip somebody please delay him smirna. Smirna. We're all in the same boat
Almighty will you ever stop remember for news? We're the big blue one. Oh
Here we go, come on, let's see breath of the wild theme song. This is all you're gonna do
Join me on tip revise on sports every day every hour on the hour. It's every day every hour
What the fuck and this is just the channel with the fish on it
Something fishy but Bambi and Trixie be your guides to the hottest fishing holes in Big Well Lake
Just throw in a minute and you might come up with a walker
Face our MasterCard excepted look at your dad
This is new I don't have any calls. All right, what about um, the mall the motel let's go to the motel
See if we can get somebody go to the camera place. That's not a bad idea, but
What are you doing?
Okay
camera store
Awesome
You've never licked a nine-volt battery. No, I never in my life
Why would I awesome an icon camera working out for you needs some new filters?
Oh, well, you'll want one of these for sunset shooting
Hey some guys came in here a little while ago and bought a bunch of lenses and lights and stuff
Said they were doing a shoot for a shoe commercial or something and they put it all on that big shot producer George
Spielman's account big spenders, huh? Well good for them. Hey, I'll be seeing you
Mystery man
It's actually actually doing an inspector gadget impression
What do they do
You know, it's probably hard to say paparazzi
Yeah, you can't say it's hard to do that paparazzi nope actually that's pretty good saying like five syllables like that
Now thanks for calling my phone, I don't know I don't know what the fuck you want for me, okay
All right, uh, let's see anything else
Lots of people chip it makes great pie. I did not know that good night
a wonderful feeling
All right. No news there for me to follow
This is Kurt loaded with an MVT news retort
Screaming fans were on hand to greet the return of sucking chest wound after their successful Baltic tour
We took the time to talk with these musical trendsetters and here's what they had to say
Clearly a fucking wig that's a party store wig and glasses set
sucking chest
Just tighten the valve cover
That dude's just tighten the valve cover. I think this is gonna repeat
Let me tell you about Jackie ray guns psychic fiends network. Just call one
900 predict let the stars decide what lies in your future
Is it wealth or just world domination?
Predict our psychics have it all figured out just call
1-900 predict I even used it to help shape my husband's national policy. That's
1-900 all right. I know I know what to call just 699 per minute kids parents permission before calling
Wanda
My guest tonight is
figure skating star Katie Johnston
She captured the hearts of America with her gold medal performance in the winter Olympics
Now she's coming to Tinseltown to start her modeling and acting career
Welcome to the show Katie
I just used to watch you all this so much footage in this game
How do you feel about being here at Tinseltown? Oh, I'm just so excited to be here with all the
Studios and all the glamour and even my favorite rock stars, especially
sucking chestwood
Axel Greece
Okay, we'll be right back
They're sexy they're tough are they too much woman to handle we're not mean people by nature
It's just a service. We're just giving all those male chauvinist pigs what they know they deserve
You won't believe what they say and you won't believe who they see
We'll talk to the dominatrix's of Tinseltown coming up next
Well, give me some details
This is news. I can't make any calls
All right, let's go to
I'm gonna say
Maybe to the club
See if we can get anything
Why do I want the details so I cuz I'm paparazzi. Let's take pictures of the guy going in to
See the you know
Got him
Still let's go back let's go to the court maybe there's somebody come out of the courthouse
Yeah, I do realize that my character is an imbecile
Why is this guy everywhere who is this guy why is he in every he's everywhere he's in every scene mom
How does she send this to me that's not accurate old people don't know how to use technology I
Would have gotten a letter in the mail you can yeah, I'm not that old. Let's go to the hotel
All right, the guy in a different hat doing magic tricks, what do you think?
I
Get him
Don't in that car, this is the guy it's stalking me. All right, then I'm gonna go to the blue bug
That's actually pretty good
What hold on where
Get where I don't know what that is a motorcycle check the TV
That was the
Those
Steve Ballmer it is
The dark channel not bad actually pretty good what? Oh shit
We had to wait all mail all day
Let me tell you about Jackie ray guns psychic fiends network
We saw this one, all right
Yeah, this just exits out to the menu
So I need to find
Where this person is?
the Grand Hotel Country Club the park
The alley let's try the alley. Oh my god
Hold on wait, this guy's now robbing me
Okay, so
All right, let's go back to the camera place I can't fight back I lost 500 I lost 500
fucking four times
Give me some info here. Wait a minute. Oh my not this fucking guy again
God damn it. I gotta find this hotel mall the motel
Report today Griselda was looking very late and fashionable. We gave her a b-plus
Well, we're sure looks well
Don't go away. We'll be right back where the weather could be rain with a 50% chance of apocalypse
news one the only one
I'm Rob Esther Sheen, you know, I used to think that life was just fun and games and that I was bulletproof
Maybe I am but not everybody else is
Listen don't drink and drive you go on a bender you may lose more than a fender this message paid for by actors against drunk driving
Rob has to she and juicy Rogers are
He's an ex-cop on the run
Are you ready for the burn purge those pounds
Now get a 30-day trial membership for just $39.95 summer stickers of what?
That's it that's all it's on this channel
Interactive purchasing what is that?
Guarantee, what is it?
For great taste and true spiritual enlightenment. Try your done yoga
Officially approved by the Maharishi yoga do it for yourself do it for it
Just call this number for a prayer request or yogurt order. Everything's a 900 number
Yeah, I'm just looking over these credit card receipts like you'd ask me to it seems like our boy fast Freddy isn't so fast after all
Let's see. He's got some charges at the hotel and they charge some gas and groceries and a fishing boat rental or something
Looks like he's spotless to me
Hotel I was working out at the gym just the other day, you know, just to stay so bad
And I saw Jackie ray gun there
Anyway, the gym the dressing room and she was using a towel from the aroma
Maybe she's got a new presidential sweetheart
Motel you might be interested
Motel motel we're gonna get a we're gonna get an affair here. Here it comes
Oh
Let's get it come on I need some money I gotta start making cash somewhere
Where
We've been out to now lie for the caption, okay
The there's a lot of fucking people
Okay
There's a lot of fucking people in this game the names Cheevers the man to see for photography
Your
What home is what say that again
For us three and plus one more home is three
Three ten plus four
I'm flash Rockman and I'm here to tell you about the clogs for tops program
Every day there are children all over the world who can't afford decent shoes
Clogs for tots helps these less fortunate little ones get the shoes they need
So if you love children like I do you'll give generously
Go to the motel now cuz it's nighttime. I'll try it
Let me explain it logically
It's these feminazi's who are taking over the country
Bill re and all of her friends are out there meddling in the government when they should be holding Tupperware parties and such
Hey, we didn't vote for it. It's all the same you see
these feminazi's think that they could whip us all into shape and and tie us up and have their way with us and
make us kiss their feet and put us in handcuffs and
I can't stand it anymore
Today on a steamy affair
Princess Griselda, she's going to get the last laugh on the prince
She's independent wild and finally free of the old bore
Just because it is ready to a royal family does not mean
I love my mother-in-law
She's just going to have to realize that I am my own woman now royal family or no
Black sheep of the royal family next
All right, so it's nighttime I'm gonna try the motel again come on get us something here
Bingo really good shot of his face
Fuck
Did I get one no
I just got a picture
I thought I just got his face fuck
One intro screen
Let's go. What the fuck is going on? I can't believe I missed it
I I thought we just had to get him go
I didn't know that was gonna be a whole part two there where he
Ten we take you now to a live press conference Liz Naylor and Flash Rockman get together to announce their new Cologne soul to soul
We've come together to make a special announcement
It's a brand new kind of cologne the first of its kind for both sexes it's pure attraction
We're calling it so
Too slow
There's a real drop of fish oil in every bottle. Oh
We got George Spielman to direct the commercial
We now return you to do a regularly scheduled program
I could do better one that
A match made in music heaven ended this week when Sharon share like broke off her engagement with ex menudo star
Jesus de la tortilla
Share like said and I quote people used to line up for miles to see him
But now he is just too old and set in his ways. I just need more spunk
More spunk
Get that dick don't do that. What are you doing as you can see here?
Bob is lubricating the master screw
As you can see here
We're talking today with women who only have one love in their life
It's chocolate and where the might surprise you it's supermodel candy. I'm as Baker
Let me get this straight
You like chocolate. Oh
Yes, I love it chocolate kisses chocolate truffles, especially chocolate ice cream
I'm a hog
Chocolate explosion. I have to have it every night. Is it like a bakery or something? Did you hear this ladies?
She's got to be kidding. You don't look like this on a diet of chocolate ice cream
How do you do it? I just have a high metabolism in a good workout plan
Nothing
Doesn't she make you sick
Then we already see the underwear one she just finished her latest work many past lives all is first wives
Please welcome former first lady and reincarnation expert Jackie Ray gun
reincarnation expert
Wanda I'm hardly an expert but when you've had as many lives as I have well you can learn a lot
I'll bet you can I also hear you're into astrology. Oh, it's not astrology
I call it astro science and it really works
Like the time the Chinese Prime Minister came over for dinner and I found out that his lunar cycle was in the seventh house of
Jupiter that's really fascinating
Jackie now let's go see a special friend of mine taught me all about
AstroScience that now let's go to commercial a pea
We take you now. All right, what do I got nothing one zero one zero one zero?
What I what is
Subjects Mundo, let's just go here
Don't skip the water cooler. That's the worst fucking TV show on TV
No, it's this guy again
All right, what about maybe the
1-0
Is that like the bus be one? So we said one zero made in music heaven ended this club
Club lingo or the country club. It's binary and it means nothing
What about the market?
On this guy again
Fuck this guy public library
Library our records show that someone has overdue materials at this number
This message will repeat. This is the temple town public library
What our records show that?
Hey
Remember me
Look, I understand if you don't want to talk to me right now
Maybe you could give me a chance to be on your side. Yeah
Look, I'm in jail. I'm fragile
Just find it in your heart bail me out. Just this once make it worth your while. Who the fuck are you?
I promise this one is a real cash cow
What do you say?
Bail me out
Please it's just $2,000. Oh god. Damn it. Do I have $2,000? Yeah. Thank you
One of my soon-to-be ex-fellow cellmates got arrested for spying on Princess Griselda
Turns out she works at the gym every Tuesday Thursday and Saturday
Thank you, you will not be disappointed Tuesday Thursday and Saturday go to the gym on Thursday tomorrow
What is the gym I don't I don't know about you, but I just love my little
So look at that dog your pet you will either get it spayed or neutered a
Message from the SPCA
Give us more than that, please. Whoa, it looks gross
Answer it
All right, so let's see here
Which one of these is a gym?
Would a country club be a gym?
Or is it club lingo? I've no
ruts Rosie
What is this place
No, it's just skip again
Right. Fuck. Damn it back to the motel
So Rosie is like a bar. This is a mall. What is the blue fog? We went there before
Motel time. Let's try
Or Grand Hotel
What we looking for? I'm Princess Griselda Marie. You're charmed. I'm sure
That's it. All right. I'm gonna try a motel
Watching TV using the no no no your dark room selling your photos saving and quitting money and integrity tips and hints how to win
Tips here. Oh what?
Wait, wait, wait, wait
Go to don't stick around when someone's threatening you
You can make a fortune of blackmail watch every channel on TV every day before you go anywhere
Telephoto the authorities to help out your integrity go to the cheevers and the blue fog first if you have time
Okay, what are you doing? I just clicked on resume was it? Okay. It's not I'm gonna try a motel again a
Roma motel
village the blue fog
cameras
hotel tinseltown courthouse
country club club lingo
Just trying to see if it says anything. Okay, let's try the whole motel. What about the park call your mother
You can't make outgoing calls in this game, but no, it's just him again just standing there
We missed our opportunity
All right. It's Thursday
It is Thursday
Let's watch TV
Like yourself and remember to come to my big conference
big conference
Sean pendleton ballroom draw
Hog and pigs chocolate explosion is one of life's guilty pleasures
It's good. So good, but i'm not gonna say it's better than sex
hog and pigs
Almost as good as sex
Sean penn
Well the big frisbee golf championships are coming up
We're going to talk to us today about the contenders as one of the true legends of the sport barry begonia
There he is still recovering from his knee injuries and two broken thumbs. So he had the time to join us today
How's the man on the course doing today barry?
Well, i'm just glad to be here tip. All right
Well, let's get down to business the championships who's gonna wear that red bandana this year
Well, tom thomas looks good. I'll give him three to one to finish in the top three
But I have to go with randy williams odds are his putt will win it
Well, what about clip haskell? He's got a mean drive. He's a long shot
The safe money's on williams you can bet on it
Not that any of us would bet on anything. No, no, no, no, of course not
So there you have it
Thanks for joining us barry
Okay, thanks for watching tip rib eyes on sports put it in the books because this one's out of here
the male channel again
This live from the set of her new movie pure heat
Let's welcome jucia roger
How'd you see it?
A newlywed i'm gonna go to the country club. What's it like being married to gotta love it?
I'm just so happy. I don't know what to do with myself
Of course, there's still a lot of cute guys out there, but gada is the one for me. Oh, come on
Isn't it just a little tempting?
I mean after all you're working every day with that hunk rob esther sheen
Not really i'm used to it. And besides gada visits me every day on the set unannounced
So, of course, there's no hanky panky wanda
Every day on the set where they film in that where are you filming?
Let me tell you about jackie ray gunn's psychic fiends network. Just call
1900 predict
Let the stars decide what lies in your future. Isn't wealth romance or just world domination?
Our psychics have it all figured out
Just call 1900 predict
Okay, here we go country club, let's go for it. See it's thursday. Let's see if we can get it
I need to make money. I gotta get this right. Okay, hold it hold it hold it
What what about my pictures I have to run away
Oh, come on
No
Fuck I thought that we were oh god. Damn it. Oh, well here we go
Get the middle finger
Got it. Ooh
We got some we got some offers here
4000 from nosy neighbor
famous faces sports
national geographer
I gotta do nosy neighbor
Bingo the nosy neighbor cheapest paper in america
Princess grizzled a bad girl for giving the finger
sneaky
nice
It looks like rob esterstein's finally gonna get his day in court. He's supposed to be shooting some drama about a tough ex cop
And a luscious district attorney george spieland's doing it. She'll probably see a lot of splotches running around left. Yeah, love your work
Okay
court
This is news
Uh
Your regularly scheduled program for this special report
A flurry of eyewitness accounts have just poured in regarding strange lights appearing in the night sky over tinseltown strange
aliens
What the fuck
What the fuck was was that supposed to be like the fbi
Because they started talking about aliens
Okay, so at night it's night time the park maybe what is this music video my god
Let's get this
It's a pretty good they might be giant song
This is I think on their third album
Check out this week's special that super value leader market fillet of red herring half off great for barbecue
Red herring 12.99 a pound fresh packed shiitake mushrooms
Just 25 dollars a box get a free facelift with a purchase of maybel midnight shadow makeup this week only a super value leader market
That's a funny way to put a red herring in a game
He's the hottest thing going in rock music, but what about his personal life
We have an exclusive interview with lash rock band's ex chauffeur
Here's the stevie
You know, I I used to drive him around a lot
But it never because I was any chicks or anything
you used to always ask me to stop by buster brown and stuff but
Well, I thought it was kind of weird because you know, the boss doesn't got any kids
What does flash rock man?
Fucking god
All right, we have any calls yeah go to the courthouse or go to the park
Court or the park for the uh, ufo
What do you guys think
Park court park park court park park park park park court court court court
I have to nail this because it's the only one I got one opportunity here
Hey god damn it. I've got one thing to say to you
No, we're not going to see the ufo in the park and now it's still okay we still we can do the court court let's go
Hey got a new sport park you like football 63 47
God damn it
Well now we can go to the court now
It's just andy warthog again
It's preordained this night is born a birthright stained court
Who are we looking for here
Zip
Got it
Which one this one, uh go back I can I can still do it
No patience. Well, I I don't even know what I'm
When shells leveled the neighborhood and 121 people were killed in local news
Tinseltown is gearing up for a charity event this weekend. It's the third annual tinseltown
family fair at winston a bigwell memorial park
Saturday there will be pony rides and an egg toss
And sunday there will be food a three-legged race and even a shoe toss for the kids
Maybe we should shoo out of here and go
Put a sock in it chip
Okay. Thanks for watching news one
Once we're on
We're on
Now we've seen these already a lot of shit on a lot of shitty stuff on tv today
Wow, this is news
All right, uh, so what can I try now?
I don't even know what this place is
hotel or
Get a better camera didn't I already go here, but I went here already
Wasn't I already here?
Yeah, what are you talking about? I was here already
What the fuck is this?
What was that? What the fuck is going on?
What should I when should I take the photo what am I taking a photo it's an alien
Run, why didn't I flee? I tried
I don't know what the guy didn't know. It was an alien. It was a guy with like a ski mask on
That wasn't an alien. That was a guy with like a fucking like
It was a guy with a mask on
Yeah, I said alien took the photo and then I tried to run
This is news
God damn, what was he doing in there?
And why was an alien in the camera store? Like how am I supposed to put two and two together like that?
They wanted a camera
I'll tell you
Sometimes good things happen to bad people after all they're supposed to go into court for that
invasion of privacy charge
They said they all tied up with something else my lucky day, huh?
I don't understand so he's all right
But
Hey, let me tell you you get a bad rep in this town things go very bad for you
I mean you have to bribe your way in the places people do not want to talk to you the police even harass you
Let me tell you it sucks big donkey dogs
Yeah, give me a lead
What?
That's it streak the dust from embers burned
I'm so sick of this guy. I'm so sick of this guy. Hey, this is important up your mom's too
Streak the dust from embers burned before the darkened skies turn head up the court
after tv
Saturday and Sunday at the park. That's right
I'll knock this again
Sucking chest wound played a media elite only gig at the rosy conch to show off some new material from their upcoming album
Tentatively titled assault and battery
Axl and the boys seem to have taken on a much harder sound. Here's a listen
Sucking chest wound this new segment brought to you by mickey shoes
It doesn't matter if you win or lose as long as you are wearing mickey shoes
The background's freaking me out. Okay, shawn pendleton ballroom brawl
Rob has to shoot and juicy rogers are
pure heat
He's an ex-cop. Yep, darling is the doxon channel. I don't know about you, but
I just love my little foo foo
Don't skip grass. Don't skip grass. Don't skip grass growing channel for great taste and
Okay, so let's uh, we're gonna do either courthouse or
Or park park is I mean it's still gonna be daytime. So i'm gonna try to hit the uh
It said park on saturday and sunday
Let's try the court
All right, what am I looking for here it's this guy
All right park
It's saturday and sunday
What am I supposed to be taking a picture of her?
I don't know. I don't know. What should I get here?
it's just
Is this a
It's like a magazine or something like like I got the kids on the horse
Got it. What's this for? There's nothing. I have nothing
I just have kids riding the horse
Nobody wants that
Why?
Okay. Well now it's nighttime
Why would I take those? I don't know because you put it in like a pamphlet
You can put it on I have it be like on the oh, I haven't been like a fucking greeting card or something
Should I go to rosy? I think yeah, let's go to rosy. This is the uh, the the bands playing here, right?
Or at least they are they did
Watch it be somebody in the background there
All right. I got another chance here
Should I go back to the camera place? See if I can get the alien again?
I wonder if that'll happen again
You got to get it right when he's coming out the door and then run
I haven't even been to the mall
Let's try it
This is it
Okay. Here we go. Here we go. I'll get you ready
Right when he walks out take a photo run
Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go. Here we go
one
Got it
It's like a kind of toilet paper around his face
Sell it to the fbi for five thousand dollars
Yep, you have photographed classified information
The fine for that is five thousand dollars
All right, I need disc two where's disc two I have it right here somewhere
Disc two, where's disc two?
Come on. Where the fuck is it?
I just dropped them all I just dropped them all
Shit my fucking pants
All right, put the button when it's in
Let's go
This game is fun though. It's just weird
Why are we on disc two now?
Come on. Come on. You can do it
I know you can do it
Pull through come on
Go go go go go go go
Yeah
Think think thinking thinking. I don't know. I'm not sure I have no idea
I can hear the disc being spun
Come on
Get it
It's pulling it. I can hear it
Good to go. And what happened to you?
You know, I used to tell myself sure you're a paparazzi, but you're basically a nice person
And as it turns out
You're just another lowlife like all the rest of them. Did I have to put this into lose?
darlings
I don't know about you, but
I just love my little foo foo
I don't want to see it. We've seen it already like redone
Today in sports the national union of ball inflators and makers went on strike
So now the sports industry truly has no balls
And if there were any balls, they'd be deflated anyway
The union is demanding the firstborn son of all sports fans before play can resume
So that's your sports for today
See you next time. What the fuck are you talking about?
baby channel
Wanda
What's this game called? It's called paparazzi. My next guest is definitely tails from tinsel town and definitely controversial
She's the virgin mary
And like her or not
She's here to sell her new book
I can't say the title
I'll just call it
Fred
What's the matter? Wanda? You're afraid to say
No, I just think fred is safer safe
Life isn't safe, baby. You've got to run with the bitches if you want to be a big dog, honey
Let's just talk about the book
Well, the book is about sex, of course
Are you afraid of sex? Wanda?
You don't have to be
look at
Oh, she's gonna stop showing photos. What does it remind you of?
Don't turn that over here. I know it's so hard to tell so close up, of course, but
It's me
Good for you
Is this a porn game?
No
I promise
Skip darling. All right, so we go. We don't have any uh, any leads or anything
You know, I used to tell myself sure you're a pop. We don't got any leads. Where should we go mall?
Grand hotel
Go to the park
camera store
Let's try the park because it is technically sunday
It's gonna be clowns like juggling or something, right?
What was that?
What watch out for the dog let's go to the fog
Always too early. Well, I don't know what i'm supposed to be looking at
No, the guy with the thing up his nose
I actually have to take that what I just took a picture of that michael. Jackson guy. That is that I got him
That's gonna go at night now
try the club club or
the uh hotel
I'm probably gonna say
Fug go to the fog go back to the fog really
Why are you fighting against i'm gonna go back to the book?
at night
Oh good good you showed up, you know, I am not always this generous with my competition
But tonight I shall offer you the chance of a lifetime. Yeah, well you see in my position
I have an invitation for the opening party of the ballroom brawl at club lingo
No, you know, it's tomorrow. I don't know who's going to be there tomorrow
Oh, yes, but I tell you you better look out or he will lay you out on the tile
Now for you I should let you have the ticket for just 2000 sound good. Yes, i'll take it
Splendid but tomorrow I will be in cancun anyways. Yes dipping my toes in the sun with a drink in my hand
Oh, I only wish that you could be there to join me got a good picture of shawn pendleton tomorrow night at club lingo
All right, let's get it. I want where's shawn pendleton. I want to get a good, uh, let's see
That's it shawn pendleton
Get out of my face. All right, that's the guy
That's the guy we're looking for
So what do I want him to what am I looking for? Not just a picture of him. I'm looking at a picture of him doing something
Punching someone from beating somebody up. There's no lyrics
Do you have any idea why my shampoo is so good for your hair? No, why it's a secret ingredient
What is it? Well, it's red and it looks like celery
No, it can't be. Yes. It's rhubarb. Oh my god. That's astounding. Oh, I can't believe it
Oh boy
Okay
I hear that oprah salad raffle is going to shoot some shows on location next week around tinseltown
Now, I don't know actually where they're shooting so I need you to keep your eyes peeled for me. Oh got another call. Love ya
Wait
Well, I can't hear you gotta
Just around town next week
I hear that oprah salad raffle is going to shoot some shows on location next week around tinseltown
Next week, I don't know actually where they're shooting. I don't know to keep your eyes peeled. Okay, you got it
All right. So we we got
One more day tomorrow is the is the club lingo party
What do you think back to the blue flag?
Try to get some more leads
Go to the mall at night, huh? Go to the alley
Not a bad choice
No, this guy tries to beat you up
All right is now monday
During the day, let's see what we got for calls
Our records show that someone has overdue materials at this number
This message will repeat
This is the tinseltown public library
I've seen this already
It's the tinseltown triangle with your host dink winklestein
And bella star bright
Just choose the star you'd like to answer the question then guess if their answer is true or false
Okay, helen the first question today is worth five hundred dollars
What was used as the model for the champagne glasses we use today?
Okay, helen pick a star
I don't know
Which one should I pick?
Oh shit
um
shawn pendleton
axle grease andy warthog
axle grace
andy
Definitely andy andy
He's speaking backwards
Um, well
Sure
All right. We have a winner
Thanks for watching tinseltown triangle
You're watching skip
When you care enough to lay the very best
Smack me
What it's more than just a fishing tour. It's something fishy
Let bambi and trixie be your guide
Let me tell you about jackie ray guns psychic fiends network
Just call i don't want to hear about the psychic network anymore
All right
Here we go
So we're looking for the uh, we look we have to look around town
We also have a club lingo. Is that that that's tonight not today, right? That's tonight
Let's check out the mall
That's tonight, right
Let's go to the mall. All right. I gotta hold on to this shit. Don't just
Take a picture of nothing
Hey
All right. Well not there
Maybe at the market
camera store
He's not gonna mug you in public
You think that?
I don't know
Something really strange happened to me the other night. I was just leaving work
I walked across the street on the way home. I'm just walking along the scenic path
And all of a sudden this little stupid dog runs up and bites me so I kicked it
Then all of a sudden some lady is hitting me with a purse and yelling in hungarian
I tell you I hightailed it out of there
Great, um, I don't know why you're telling me this I wanted a camera upgrade
All right, it's club lingo time. We're looking for shawn
We're looking for him to do something wrong
Let's go club lingo
I gotta be ready. I gotta do it. Come on
He's gonna like punch somebody in the face he's gonna like
Smash something. I gotta be ready and I have to flee too
Where will you wait for shawn?
Go to the bar go to the men's room go to the dance floor. I don't know which one of these to do
Go to the dance floor go to the men's room
the dance floor
I'm not gonna go in the men's room
I'm saying dance floor. All right, here we go. You gotta do something wrong
There he is
No, where is he?
Hey, what the fuck?
Am I all right?
You gotta be kidding me
I didn't know everyone tells me to wait to wait for something and he fucking blasts me
I don't that sucks
Is it still going on?
Go back
And this time wait in the men's room
Let me try it again to see if it's still available
Men's room of the bar
I'm gonna say i'm gonna say no not the men's room. That's like that's guaranteed. I'm gonna get punched in the face
Okay, this is my we get one we get one shot here
Go to the bar go to the men's room
But what am I supposed to wait for him to do? I'm just gonna have a camera in the fucking men's room
I'm not even gonna get a second
No, I don't know
Early again well guys it took him like eight seconds to punch me in the face in the first one. That's his face. I got it
Damn it. Hi, it's your old friend vela
I haven't seen you in a long time and would love to catch up on some things with you
Could you meet me at the blue fog tonight? Okay. Bye. Sure blue fog tonight
I'm gonna go we have to keep looking around. It's still this week. Let's check out the
Uh the market
We're still looking for that girl doing the shoot
We've tried the mall already. I'm gonna try the market
Because I went to the mall yesterday during the day
Let me try the park. That's not a bad idea
What's that
What am I doing here? What am I doing here? What am I doing here? What am I waiting for?
Arrested
Wait for arrest wait for the arrest
Arrest here it is
Got it. Did she just hold on I teach them shit on
I'm realizing that okay
Shit
Um, okay, which one?
I'm talking to the officer. They're gonna be having a good nice conversation though. This is like you're under arrest
Oh, yeah, you and me vanities famous faces
I didn't even take that
How about you and me?
That's absolutely gets busted
entertainment weekly
nice
Now is the time in the show where I sing a little song for you a e i o u
Sometimes why?
a e i o u
Thank you for your patronage why would you do that though people who must have breakfast
cereal eaters on today's okra-sodded raffle
I try to go to work without eating my special k, but
Oops, I i'm a nervous walk. I understand your problem
You're not alone. Many people have the same problem
You're going to be okay
You know, you're a strong woman. You'll pull through the greatest crisis. Do you really think so?
Don't go away
Let me tell you about tomorrow's show
We'll be on location in utensil town. Yeah, it's about shopaholism
At the mall where they shop tomorrow at the mall why they can't stop
Got it on location tomorrow at the mall skip. Okay, so
We are looking for we're just going to be looking just go walk around in circles trying to find random shit
How about the let's go to the hotel? We haven't been to the hotel in a while. We've got a blue fog later
Here we have not been to the grand hotel or the motel for a long time
Go back to the camera place again
I don't know if I want to do that
I'm going to the hotel
See if you can find anything find something
What is it who is it I get it she's blocking her face
That could be your face though, that's her chin
I was like waiting for her to like fucking break something or punch somebody
It's still worth it. Whoa
Holy shit, who is this?
And why are they worth 14 000?
other people
Should I get some integrity?
I need integrity
Don't ruin my integrity. Okay. Well
This s t y is integrity, right?
Uh-oh
Integrity equals more story
I'm too I don't have enough money, but I'm all right. This will put me at about 10 grand
Integrity later big money big money
Off her diet
All right. We're at night time
Tuesday what was supposed to happen here?
Landlord, what did he say?
You'd pay me my money. How do I pay them?
I got money
This is news one
One big star has been brought down a notch today
Lhasa abso former star of the tv series green junction was arrested for assaulting a police officer with a piece of dog dung
The officer reported that he was simply trying to get abso to clean up after her dog
That's when she became that's pretty cool and threw the offending opal at the officer
Lhasa was sentenced to serve 200 hours of community service for the city cleaning up poop in tinseltown park
And that's a scoop to me
Thanks for watching news you're on the news don't miss
this one
It actually knows rib-eye sports in today's sports
Absolutely, nothing happened
I've been in this business for 12 years now, and this is definitely the first time this has happened
That's all
There's no baseball games. No tennis
Not even a curling match. Nothing. Nobody is playing anything anywhere today
What else is there to say nothing
That's awesome
For great taste and true spirit. All right, so what we got with tuesday night
We're going to the fog
We're meeting up with this, uh, this new contact. I don't know who it is
I'm so glad you came
I'm sorry. I haven't talked to you for four years, but otto was very jealous
He doesn't like it when I spend a lot of time with my friends so
Unpredictable
Yeah, okay, so what about it
Hotel
Anybody want this
Go to the hotel hotel
Grand hotel, let's go
Should we try?
What am I doing though? What am I doing this for?
This was a side story
Okay, so now we have to go
to the mall
Now I just want to give you a little tip
If you happen to sell one of your photos to one of the less reputable publications
Well, who knows what they're going to use it for
Because sometimes they even put up your photos with an out and out lie for the caption who cares
All right. It's time for the mall. We have to get a picture of
Uh that tv show
Let's go what am I looking for though i'm gonna I don't know what i'm looking for
A a a mishap just a photo a good picture
Today on the okra side raffle show we're here on location at the alpaca
Let's talk about a problem. I'm just gonna get one to make sure
And we have an amish expert here who has an answer to the problem
Thank you for having me on your show today. I would just like to say that
You don't need such material things to exist
You really need the basics
Food shelter clothing don't need such luxuries anything else as fancy dresses more perfumes
Or phonographs or television sets. Wait a minute. Wait, hold on. You don't like tv or something, huh? Mr. Pilgrim when
Punch you know what you need
You think you're better than everyone else that tv's too good for you. No, what is a good thing we need contact tv
Because you sure
Oh shit did I get it
That was mid stride full stride that's gotta be some worth something right. Oh, yeah
Knock the hat off. All right, let's get some integrity
vanities
For some reputation
Or should I just don't even sell it and just keep my integrity. I do have a lot of money already
entertainer
The tinsel town tattler sounds like I think it's the more expensive the prices
The less integrity
We don't know that. I mean i'm just taking a guess
the tattler
Wait, it says it. What does it say?
integrity sneaky
Oh, so the the
That's definitely right. I'm selling all the vanities
Osr beats sjr and ow in rtg's display house is sharp. What the fuck it's all
All still sneaky that's all right
All right, should I tell the hotel again?
She says you're staying there
Pay your rent
I don't know how to pay my rent
Yeah, I was just at the grand haberne where I was supposed to be covering rob estesheen's speech at a drunk driving seminar
I was just there. Well, the problem is he wasn't there and no one seems to know where he was
Well, I guess he was just parting it up somewhere
Let's see that one again
We've seen it all
Huggins the ice cream explosion
Let me tell you about jackie ray guns psychic beans
all right, so then that we're talking about the
rosies
The club rosies the blue fog
Why did I become an agent?
Well, I came to tinsel town like thousands of other young starlets
Barely making it on tuna and ramen
Getting hit on by sleazy directors and when I did find work it was with a crappy script
This business can dry you up like a bowl of pretzels
Then I said to myself self
You could be doing this to other people
I love my job
Anything else that's it
All right, well then let's try
The motel the
Club
Rosie see the most it's gonna be one of the it's probably the bros. It's probably rosies rosies. It's one two or three
I'm gonna try rosies
So we're with a club
No, it's another day. We missed it
It's another one of these
This is news
Talk show host and billionaire okra salad raffle had just become a little less wealthy today
As she was convicted of assault upon an amish guest of the show
Eli brown the amish plaintiff won the case based on photographic evidence gained by a local photographer
We are affecting the universe okra bashing. Mr. Brown over the head
The plaintiff was compensated for home remedy pills plus punitive damages of two oxen a new car and a bony big screen tv
Those big tvs are great for pornos
You amaze me chep, it's just my job
I'm flash rock man, and i'm here to tell you about the cause for tops
Why would you say that?
Doesn't make any sense
TV's funniest family bloopers and blunders and bleepers the two disappeared without a trace
Ah
If you care about these actual bloopers in the game you will either have him sprayed or neutered
It's their own outtakes
That's funny, that's clever that's clever. I like that. All right, so let's do
I'm gonna say we should go to the
I don't have any leads right now though
What's going on yet the club club i'm gonna say what the camera place
Back to the motel
I'm gonna go to the hotel
If I get skip again i'm never coming back here during the day, yeah
I'm not going to the hotel again now during the day. Uh, how about just the park? Let's try the park
Something going on in the park every day
ducks
Let's go to the motel that was fucking horrible, but I loved it
No, here he is again
Where to
You know what to do go get him seltzer what what do you mean? He just bought some what
But you're the only one who can help me on this note in my mailbox this afternoon it says
I've had just about enough. Everybody thinks i'm so tough
Gonna go where nobody can find me and see that there's no signature or anything
Just a little stain of rocky vomit
But I think it's true somebody's really gonna kill themselves it's just awful
Uh, who is this person in the alley?
But what home yes. Yes. Yes, we've got dinked by the winkle thing now. This one's gonna be easy, baby
He just bought some flowers and his wife is out of town. You know what to do. Go get him seltzer
Just bought some flappers
Hotel, okay alley hotel
All right. What what what was going on here?
What is that?
What is going on?
Wait, how do I like stop? How do I stop this?
I don't I can't like click on them
Well, I don't know which one of these
Uh, I this it's I I don't I don't want to like sell this photo
There are no
Now I have integrity
Well, I don't
There's a difference between selling a lady throwing the poop
And getting like arrested
All right, that's that's bad, too
Where was the other one?
Oh shit
Pay tomorrow morning. Why is this guy always taking a shit? He's always going to the bathroom
And now here's smarta with the local band guide
Tonight there's a lot of great music out there at the rosy conch sucking chest wound is playing
Club lingo is a spot for scoop poop a scoop and being cheso
All right, we got some club club lingo the rosy and never
One station under god
The music world mourns the loss of one of rock's greatest screamers axel greece
He died somehow
We asked the rest of sucking chest wound if there is life after axel and here's what they had to say
So guys, what are you gonna do now that you've seen their song?
Just tap in the valve cover
Oh, what a cute baby quiet this joint. It's romantic
It's memorable
It's been chesos best
I left my nose
In schnauzer city
Yes, this unique offer gets you this never before available collection of oh big nose singing your favorites
There's love songs
That was good that was really good
That was a really good
My nose can't smell love
There's something for everyone just pick up the phone and order now three cassettes or two cds for just
1995 it's not bad. Hi, i'm vincenzo cosinostra. I didn't write any of these songs, but they sure meant a lot to me
I hope they get you some too. Have your credit card ready when you call
More funny bloopers
Bullets straight
And virgin mary we're gonna talk about pot legalization about condoms in schools
What the fuck is going on? What are you doing?
Hey, pay the rent tomorrow morning
Yeah, fuck off
All right grand hotel or uh, we have choices here
Uh, we can go to the club
We can go to grand hotel or go to rosie
Somebody's singing here
Hey you motherfucker
It's at night then
God damn it. Where do I want to go then?
Maybe just random place country club
I'm just gonna i'm just gonna go to the country club
This is news
The music you already did tv
Go back to the alley
rosie
Where do you pay rent? I think it just happens
Hey, you like rock and roll check this out
Those people are just actually watching wait come on come on nothing in there
It's now all right. It's night time
Hey, could you meet me out at the blue fog tonight? There's something we got to talk about. Okay
All right. Let's go. Let's do that
What the hell do I want to go first? I've got two choices here grant go back to the hotel grand hotel
We have to have at least one
I'll go to the fog right now
Just to make sure
I'll still have time to go to the hotel after this. I know it's strange for me to be here like this
But I had to tell you in person
Frankly, I don't think you have what it takes to make it around here
What I hope you don't take this advice the wrong way
But when you don't make money, I don't make money. I have 20 grand. Isn't there something else you can make a living at?
Love ya. How do you yeah, i'm i'm i'm we gotta
Hey
Uh, yeah, I still how we're gonna end this stream tonight
Is we're gonna I have like six more games
I want to play. I don't know. I got one. Holy night. I got one two three
four five six
I have like seven games. I think still
And some of them are gonna be really really fucking good. So I
When you get a good one, I want you to stay on it. This is a good one
Do space ace now? I already did it. I was gonna mute this because it's probably horrible to listen to
All right. So we start off here. Although that may is it digging is it different?
Okay, now I got a tip for you that I thought you might want to hear and there's not much time
You know how i've been covering that h allen eagler of guns for jelly bean scandal, right? We're gonna get the well
It was just at our customs office in florida
And our investigation just uncovered an invoice. Yeah iranian jelly beans shipped to tinseltown
And I think there's some sort of deal going down tonight in one of those dark alleys and none of our photographers are in town
alley, right? No, I don't have any assignments for you yet, but don't worry
I'm looking out for your ride to just hang in there. Here we go
This is the first one. We take the picture. We're gonna get the deal
So right when it's it's gonna it's like guns or something right or is it what's in their drugs?
Because that's the briefcase you gotta get it when they
Yeah, i'm gonna wait wait till they like take it out
I've got one
Is there a better one? I mean that's clearly like that's a gun. You know what I mean? Like that would be clear
I got it
Which one and with the pointed in the air, right?
Sunglasses at night. I think it's the right one
the left one
Yeah, not bad
All right
My integrity I have to keep it good, but I also have to make money
What should I do with this?
Just give it to the fbi
Or should I just do?
I'm thinking about this one here
2000 no, give me money
I need money right off the bat the jelly seller still friendly
We've seen these already
You're on tip ribeye sports in the celebrity endorsement department tennis star andre mcconnor
For a reported 3.2 million dollars to do a series of commercials for mickey shoes
No word yet on how much they're paying mcconnor's babysitter, but where?
Seeing this already
Yeah, we've seen these
I think now we just have to kind of look around
Let's go to the camera place
Or you know what? No, let's go. Um
country club
I don't know. We've seen all the videos. That's why we can speed run back to where we were
All right. Oh you
What are the poor people doing?
Thank you for turning me on to their cheapest cameras
I thought it was going to be some hole in the ball place
But I found the lens I was looking for and their cheapest fellow
He told me where I could get sean pendleton. I want to thank you. You are making me a very rich man
Right. Okay
camera store
And then he gives us a lead, right
How's him an icon camera working out for you?
Needs some new filters. Ah, well, you'll want one of these for sunset shooting
Hey some guys came in here a little while ago and bought a bunch of lenses and lights and stuff
Said they were doing a shoot for a shoe commercial or something
And they put it all on that big shot producer george spielman's account big spenders, huh? Well, we're good for them
Hey, i'll be seeing you
Okay, so where is that
Where would they be filming that at the mall?
mall of the park
Yeah, that's that would be like a store at the mall
I'm gonna go for it
country club
It's fucking night time shit
in this chamber
It's not it's too late now
Shit, ah
Oh well
Head down the alley. I'll try the alley. Why not?
It probably was the country club
Because he'd be playing tennis
No, not getting mugged
Where should I go?
to the blue fog
Go to the park at night or should I go to the blue fog? I'm probably going to go to the fog
Grab a picture of the alien that doesn't happen yet, does it?
The gardens at elizabeth nailer's house, you know one summer afternoon
I was visiting ladies and I was taking a shot of her working in the garden, you know without wearing one
Spot of makeup her nails and her hands were dirty filthy. She still looks so ravishingly beautiful
Oh, do forgive me i've taken this moment to reminisce. I hope I did not bore you
What are we supposed to do with that information?
Bye mom
Rob esther sheen is in town to shoot a new movie. So we've got him live via remote. Wait, this is new
Rob, could you tell us about your drunk driving charges?
Has a little girl recovered from her coma yet?
Well, dear
I think that uh, everyone involved in this unfortunate incident has learned a great deal
And I have personally
Tried to raise the awareness of this problem
And I assure you a lot of good has come out of this first of all
I've taken up dancing and the chicks are just eating that up
Secondly, I got a new movie out
And I think people are gonna eat that up, too
How did you get out of all of the charges?
I think you're gonna need to speak to my attorney
This uh, this interview's over
Thanks rob
What a great humanitarian, huh?
News one and it's romantic
It's memorable
It's vincenzo's best
I left my nose
In schnauzer city
I can't
I have to
Do you have any idea why my shampoo is so good for your hair?
No, why?
It's its secret ingredient rhubarb
Well, it's red and it looks like celery
No, it can't be. Yes. It's rhubarb, babe
Today this is
Country club, let's see if they're still shooting. Come on be shooting. Hey, I got something for you
It's a cannonball picture, baby
I feel like somebody would want this on the internet somewhere. No, nobody wants it
God damn it
He's gonna be sent to the hospital because he did that
God damn it's ducks again. I'm gonna get it for you ducks
Hey, you like ducks. They got a great documentation
Damn it. What do you got?
But what but where
on the back of a motorcycle
but where
motel
Go to the motorcycle
Ali
Sean pendleton ballroom brawl
Today on a steamy affair
I'll try the motel
Are they real? Oh, here we go
This is the ufo one. We'll talk to one expert who'll tell you what the government doesn't want camera store
It's dr. Jerry mander
Jerry tell us about these aliens glad to marry
There have been numerous sightings of these aliens and all reports are pretty much the same the aliens are
A humanoid form with long skinny necks and he's doing the the there's something about mary
that actor well saucer like and well
We've seen evidence where the saucers land in cornfields and leave the circular deposits of alkaline in in the soil
Furthermore very interesting. Dr. Mander and now let's go to a commercial
This is a the government is trying to cover this up. This is a big conspiracy
Cut it's mike. All right, so i'm thinking motel or alley
I don't know what to do
I don't know where to go. I know that I can i'm guaranteed to get the camera store. That's a guarantee
Rosie motel rosy alley. It's one of these. I don't know
Uh
Yeah, one more shot see that the this bar here the alleyway
You only get one chance
Failing the alley is it the alley you want to try the alley going for the alley?
I think it's the alley. Let's try the alley
Here we go
Oh there it is
Yeah, i'm just looking over these credit card receipts like you'd ask me to it seems like our boy fast freddy isn't so fast after all
Let's see. He's got some charges at the hotel and today he charged some gas and groceries and
Market fishing boat rental or something fishing boat rental market. He's spotless to me country club
I was working out at the gym just the other day
You know just to stay civiled and I saw jackie ray gunmail the gym
Anyway, I saw her in the dressing room and she was using a towel from the aroma boat towel
Maybe she's got a new presidential sweetheart. Just thought you might be interested
Okay, so that
Country club well the
Where would you buy a boat unless you're at the country club
At the boat store
Well, let's get this one. It's the middle finger
Okay, I don't want to sell this to nosy neighbor. How about the famous faces?
national geographer
sports
Bodybuilders number one fan sports inundated
All right friendly
All right, what's next? I was working out. It's that one. Yeah, i'm just looking over these
Like you'd ask me to it seems like our boy fast freddy isn't so fast after all
Let's see. He's got some charges at the hotel and today he charged some gas and groceries and
a fishing boat rental or something
No, where
Where would you take to go to a fishing boat at the park?
You can't put put a boat into the little thing at the park
It's like a oh fuck
Got one now. What I don't know when to take the second photo. I don't know when to take the second photo
What are you gonna do? He's gonna like take his he's gonna take his towel off. He's taking the towel off
Okay, get off the screen get it off the screen get it off the screen get it off the screen get it off the
Screen get it off the screen get it off the screen get it off the screen get it off the screen get it off
The screen get it off the screen get it off the screen
Dirty old men
Hey there now, I just want to give you a little tip if you happen to sell one of your photos to one of the less reputable publications
Well, who knows what they're going to use it for
Because sometimes they even put up your photos with an out and out live. I know I said this wasn't a porn game
It's not a porn game
four plus three and plus one more home is
three
All right. Thanks andy
Uh, all right. I'm thinking
Time it's nighttime. Let's get the let's get the alien because I know it's gonna be here
I
There it is I got it
All right motel motel at night it's nighttime
This game is fucking crazy, this is it
Okay, I have to get this right oh, there's another fucking guy it's another porn game thing
It does a zoom in on his face
He's head he turns
Thank you, uh
Czechian
She's exian for the five community subs
This is twenty five thousand dollars
Should I blackmail the mayor who is this? I don't even know who this is
33 grand basically nice
All right
Good job on that russ blumberger. How did you do it? Anyway, he had it coming to him. I'll be in touch
All right. We're gonna keep her happy
This is mr. Modem
We take you now to a live press conference
Liz nailer and flash rock man get together to announce their new cologne soul to soul
All right, we already saw this we've come together to make a special announcement
A match made in music heaven ended this week when
Got this one
We're talking today. Is this the women who only have one love in their life?
All right, we've seen it. We've got now let's explore. Okay
Let's go to the mall
I have not gone to that place at the bottom
Hi, oh my god, did I just go to this place? Let's just go i'm just gonna go whatever let's go
Let me get something here
I'm still doing all right on money
Is this guy that wants you to bail him out?
Hey
remember me
Look, I understand if you don't want to talk to me right now
But maybe you could give me a chance to be on your side, huh?
Look, I'm in jail. I'm fragile
Just fine. I got the money to bail him out bail me out just this once
Make it worth your while
And I promise this one is a real cash cow
What do you say?
Bail me out. Yes
Please it's just two thousand dollars, huh?
Thank you
I got lots of money. I'm fine
One of my soon-to-be ex-fellow cellmates got arrested for spying on princess griselda
Turns out she works at the gym every tuesday thursday and saturday
Got that we already got this though, right?
You will not be disappointed
Yeah, but he if when you bail him out of jail, he's around
darlings
He gives you more info later
gross
Okay, let's go. All right. I'm thinking, uh, it's nighttime cameras. Let's try to get that alien
You're gonna it's right when he walks out the door
Oh shit, they're both bad
This one's all blown out this one
Okay
Do not send it to the fbi. They take money from you
National geographic
the elusive
Rigel and subloid what?
Put this magazine in your closet
This is the pimple town public library
Our records show that someone has overdue materials at this number
This is my score
All right
still nighttime
i'm thinking
to the blue fog
Most dollars you poop head glad to see you can make it
uh bartender
Two round of cokes, please
Well, there really hasn't been too much news lately
I mean I live for natural disasters and fires and riots and things like that
I remember the great boston molasses disaster of 1987
Big tank molasses just explodes
It engulfs a four block city radius kills 48 people. I mean you should have seen the look on those people's faces
I had to get out of the way, too
They say molasses is slow, but uh, they've never seen a 14 foot wave of it either
well
Here's to your health
Nothing you're not going to give me any info
Uh, there was nothing there the kings and queens allied rather burdened crowns on down for nigh
Thanks, andy
So stay healthy love yourself and remember to come to my big conference
Come to my big conference
where
Where's this conference?
He said this before and we couldn't find it
We've seen these already
My big conference the country club hotel or country club the gym is in the country club
Let's try the hotel
None of the hotel not the gym
Where would your big conference be then what the fuck?
It looks like rob esterstein's finally gonna get his day in court. They're supposed to be shooting some drama about it
I remember I fucked this one up
This is news one
We interrupt your regularly scheduled program for this special report
A flurry of eyewitness accounts have just poured in regarding strange lights appearing in the night sky over tinseltown
Yeah, we already got that one
All right skip
This is news
We just need to do the get to the courthouse
During the day right or is it is it right now? No, it's it's it's during the day tomorrow
Where do I want to go then?
Should I go to like this restaurant?
Maybe I should go here. I don't think i've ever tried to go here at night
I
The bait that they give you on these all right, we got one more shot here hotel
See if I can get something here
What am I going to take a photo of?
What is this? What am I looking at? What the fuck is that?
What's going on?
If you're gonna get like sucked into a ufo
When do I take the photo?
When do I take it?
Take it right now
All right, get out get out. Give me up
shit
I got her standing at the glowing light with this flying saucer above her
What do you mean you fell for that?
A flying saucer flew through the air
It's preordained this night is born a birthright stained
All right, we're gonna go back to uh
What was the place we had to go today?
They expect to see you back here
See they try to bait you with that shit see they try to bait you so many times
All right, so we got i'm currently courteous we do blackmail again and be at uh, like 40
47 000 let's go for it blackmail good
All right, it's still daytime so i'm saying we should probably do
All right, I gotta be nice on the next photo
Go to the market
I haven't been here in a while. Oh, no, I haven't I'm flash rock man
Let me tell you about jackie ray guns psychic fiends network
I can't believe I didn't get a picture of the alien lady corresponding with the aliens
All right, it's night time get anything new no
When shells leveled the neighborhood and 121 people were killed. Yeah, we already heard this one
It's the ducks baby channel
This is water, okay
Now it is currently nighttime. I'm trying again and go back to the motel see if I can get it again
Lost my opportunity. Oh well back to the fog. How about uh sigmundos? Let's try it
Oh shit
It's a singer when do I do this
What do I do what do I do
Get out of the fucking way
I think I got it. I think I did it perfectly
Wait, wait, wait, does he do anything else?
I gotta run
Which one is better, I mean he's like clearly just like dead here
Okay, I got it
Which one I know but I mean that one wasn't a great picture
All right, so I need to
news review
That's so stupid. He just like whacked him
Nice. Okay. Here we go
Hey, this is important. This is bullshit again. Listen. Hey, let me tell you you get a bad rep in this town
Things go very bad for you
I mean you have to bribe your way in the places people do not want to talk to you the police even harass you
Let me tell you it sucks big donkey dogs
Yeah
See the news got it recorded earlier
Now we've seen this early
Sucking chest wound played a media elite only gig at the rosy conch to show off some new material from
Sean pendleton ball
Oops
You're watching the grab for great taste and
All right, I got nothing. I don't want to handy warthog. We eventually have to get
From embers burned before the darkened skies turn
That definitely means something who knows what the hell it's supposed to mean
I'm gonna try
Say that again, andy
Streak the dust from embers burn streak the dust from embers burn
Streak the dust from embers burn before the sky turns
Streak the dust from ember thryer
from fire
at night
Something at night before it turns to night time
But streak what does the streak the embers?
Say it again, andy
Streak the dust from embers burned before the darkened skies turn
Streak the dust from embers burned
aroma
Fallen arches. No
Cub lingo market. I think it's just horseshit. I don't think it means anything. I'm gonna go to the park
This doesn't do anything
It's just the they're just on the horse there we go. It's mom
Remembered me this is news
Bullets stripe the facade of news review weekly this afternoon in apparent drive-by shooting
No one was injured, but a spokesman for news review weekly said it was nothing of consequence. Just go home
Home
What?
This is kurt loaded with an mvt news retort
Screaming fans were on hand to greet the return of sucking chest wound after their successful baltic tour
We took the time to talk with these musical trendsetters. We did this already. We already saw these
Okay, let me tell you about jackie ray guns
All right
We don't have any
Does mom give us any cryptic info? I don't think so
Where do I want to go?
Back to the blue fog see when you get somebody
We're watching all reruns
There we go
Hey, it looks like you got the royal treatment. You better be more careful on those blue bloods. They'll give you a black eye or something
At least I know when to duck
Can I save this one on my computer?
Okay, so that was that
Club lingo, let's try the club
Jim again blackmail yourself
Well, we've made the part two i've got plenty of money I got plenty of
um
integrity
We're good to go
Whatever happens happens here
Wait, was that paparazzi too? Or was that stephen spielberg's director's cd too?
Uh-oh. No, no, it's the right one. Okay
Wait, was it?
Yeah, it was good. Good. I was gonna say that's not good if that were the case
Looks good
So what is that?
Very cool
So this is the half. This has to be like the halfway point, right?
It's two discs
What's the status on a pog with the voting time?
I was at the party and everyone was asking about you me. I gotta tell you friend
You are making some really big and tasty way if you know what I mean
All right, so my reputation is high I just can't tell you that you are really my favorite right now
You're really making us rich. Keep it up, baby. Good. Everybody loves me darlings
There's the poop thrower
We've already seen all these
All right
How about we open it up at the market? Let's go
What do we got here stealing?
All right, I got I got it which one left one on the right
That's why you flee
Okay, if you wait too long, then they like
You break your camera. I stay I
I sat there for a long fucking time
Oh, is this the is the michael jackson thing again?
All right. Well now it's
Well, at least i'm gonna get this
this photo
There it is. That's what I needed
Which
What
I got him like grabbing the shoe out of her hand
How is that wrong?
Am I supposed to get him driving away on the lawnmower?
Like i don't know if i haven't figured that one out
It's fucked up though. I hear that okra salad raffle is going to shoot some shows on location next week around tinseltown
Now, I don't know actually where they're shooting. So I need you to keep your eyes peeled for me. Oh got another call. Love ya
All right, so I know what that one is
nighttime
hotel the club
No, the blue fucker is always
A good choice. There's always somebody there
You could make it now sit down sit down have a seat because you are gonna love this here we go
There you go
Oh, I hope you're not busy tomorrow night. Well, it's a pass
To the opening night party of bar room brawl and club lingo
Nice i fucked this up last time now he is a hard ass so you better watch yours
It's not exactly my cup of tea, you know what I mean and you be careful over there
And remember you do owe me one
drink up friend
These are both great images that convey completely different emotions. I like them on the right foot
All right, so that's tomorrow night let's check out park at night hotel again
rosy
Let's try motel. See if we can get the alien again
No
What's this game about? It's a game you you're paparazzi photographer
And you need to take photos
of people
And sell them and celebrities doing things that are bad
All right. So it's a new week tonight. I gotta go to the club but today
Uh, where where's she at the mall?
She knocks the head off the amish guy
That's the mall, right?
It's the tensile town triangle with your host dink winkle steen
and bella star bright
Just choose the star you'd like to answer the question then guess if their answer is true or false
Okay, helen the first question today is worth five hundred dollars I think it's the mall
What was used as the model for the champagne glasses we use today?
Okay, helen pick a star
All right, let's go somebody else's time. I don't know. Let's go with the guy with his feet on deck
Who is that this one? Of course, every idiot knows it's Marie Antoinette's memories
excluding the one in the middle
I'm not even sure that i'm not sure it's that guy's legs. That's his legs. All right, we have a winner
Thanks for watching tensile town somebody else's knees in the air
skip
All right, here we go
mall
I think you win every single time
Where the hell is it then I thought I thought I thought it was in the mall
No, it's this one
Is that supposed to be the dog?
I would be that would be me doing that because i'm that close
Let's see if I can get the shit
That's way too close to the microphone
All right, so I need to be nice here
vanities
Because I don't want to lose my reputation
Or just don't
It's only 750 bucks
Still basically nice
All right, it is night time time to go to club lingo
This is philip
If you want to get into some of the places around here, you've got to get to know these people
You've got to make them trust you, huh? Otherwise they will give you no time of the day
Okay
Club lingo, let's go
Mike meyers
That really is a mike meyers character in austin powers
All right. I did the men's room. I did the dance floor. We're gonna do the bar
But what am I trying to get here guys?
Just a picture of the guy and then run away
What do I need to do here? What am I looking for?
Because I took a picture of him. He looked back. He was like peeing
And I nobody wanted to buy it
Looking for action
Let's try the bar
All right, yeah germy you should have waited germy you should have waited why did you not wait what was the point
So it has to be the bathroom
But when do I take the photo?
When do I take the fucking picture of in the bathroom?
After he turns around
All right, i'm going for it
Did I get it?
teen heat
All right, which one of these do I want to do probably?
Either this one's not the most expensive one
I don't want to lose my reputation
This one's 7500. I'm still fine
Oh my god
Hi, it's your old friend bella. I haven't seen you in a long time and would love to catch up on some things
Yeah, all right
This is kind of where we left off like not maybe like 10 20 minutes later show where I sing a little song for you
I already saw this
Yeah, all right. We're getting close to new content here
I don't think I have ever gone to the alley during the day
Maybe like once
Well, it doesn't matter if you go to the alley during the day it's always uh night time in the alley
Just go to the camera store
Yeah, this will be a good
How can a woman gain 360 pounds in three days?
I thought she was on skinny quick
Perfume I gotta quit doing commercials
Huh?
Don't ask me. I just work here
Uh, what did he just give me?
He he handed me something
Either pay tomorrow morning or use and those cameras are out of here
This is news one
One big star has been brought down a notch today
Lhasa abso former star of the tv series green junction was arrested for assaulting a police officer with a piece of dog down
the office
Yeah, we've seen these
All right
So let's go to the hotel
I'm gonna sneeze
I couldn't press the button. I'm sorry. Excuse me. I had so much time. No, because my head was reared back
Got it
Making money
All right. Do I want tinsel town tattler?
Other people or don't just keep it keep myself at the nice
other people
You and me
Sty
So
Liz gets into sty shut up. All right, let's go back to
Sty suey there. All right. Fuck. Okay
What the fuck is going on
What's she eating?
What is she eating? It's not gonna be ice cream. It's gonna be like fucking what is it?
What am I what am I taking a picture of?
What what was that?
I gotta get out of here
What just happened?
Why was she going? Why is she like moaning before?
Well, I don't know what to do with this
What?
Hey there
Now I just want to give you a little tip. Oh, no if you happen to sell one of your photos to one of the less reputable publications
Well, who knows what they're going to use it for
Because sometimes they even put up your photos with an out-and-out lie for the caption
All right, darling
I I can't even react a controversial virgin
Mary has just broken new ground in tastelessness with her new video for the hit song flex your love muscles
What follows is about all we can show you of the masterpiece
Here it is
I don't do it the virgin mary
Tinseltown open is all set to go tomorrow and it marks the return of the great one to professional frisbee golf
Yes, barry begonias back in shape and back on the circuit. We need to get some info here because this is gonna be for tomorrow
The knees all better and the thumbs are all
Thumbs up at the park. My shot's a little rusty, but a hundred bucks still says I win this thing
You heard it take it to him barry next up curly
So that's tomorrow at the country club
or
This is the show you've been waiting for me
and virgin mary
We're gonna talk about did you see her face about condoms in school?
She just was actually laughing at that. That was great all the left wing garbage she can think up
You're the only garbage I can think up right now. Oh, I see we're gonna have a real discussion, huh?
Just like that real blonde hair
Hey, it's real baby
I'm a natural blonde you want to see how
natural
Didn't I say this would happen?
What about condoms in schools? What do you think about that? It's the 90s kids are going to have sex
They may as well be protected now now mary that is like giving away
Crash helmets to people so they can speed safely not
Exactly. Well, I don't think anyone needs condoms. I mean only married people should have sex
So when it's my turn to vote at the courthouse, i'm gonna vote no just like senator frederick says
And I know some well-placed judges. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
courthouse tomorrow
I've had it up to here
I'm going to prove the powers that be that we can do whenever we want whenever we want we march to victory america
That was disgusting
Don't touch don't touch that. Oh
skip
All right. So we've got tomorrow. We've got the park or the country club and then the courthouse
But as for today
I have no idea
Maybe go to the
Go to the country club today, too
Hey to brent, I don't even know what to do that. I think it just happens
Hey, I got something for you. It's a cannonball
It's I mean, it's kind of funny every time when he does that
but
I'm sick of seeing it. We've seen it so many times
We've seen it like 10 times
Hey there, buddy
How you doing?
I think i've come down with something
You want to buy some phlegm?
Get it phlegm
Here you go
All right, it's night time
Yeah, I was just at the grand habernae where I was supposed to be covering rob estesheen's speech at a drunk driving seminar
All right. We didn't do this one before there and no one seems to know where he was
Well, I guess he was just partying
Okay, so he's not here. So where is he?
We tried here and we tried here, didn't we?
Was this the only place that we didn't look
Before possibly
No cameras allowed
No cameras allowed give him five hundred dollars
Yeah
Oh shit
Oh, that's okay
Uh, how do we get we how do we get this? We got to get this like on the fucking front page
The magazine that has the teenagers be like, yeah, I don't do this shit. I agree
place place
Got it. Yeah, I was just at the grand habernae you were watching got it
hog and pigs chocolate
let me
All right. So now we got tomorrow is the to the court and the country club or the park
I got one more thing to do tonight. Let's try
the hotel
Yeah tomorrow there's two things that I know before that I remember court and country club, yeah
Should be easy tomorrow
What is this?
Did I get it how many times after every picture did I go did I get it?
Then I should take a photo
Did I get it? I don't know. Look at the camera, man
Which one of these do I want to do probably? Uh harvey's bizarre. Don't sell it. He's your friend
Andy warthog, he's hip he's dead or is he what do you mean? He's what are we talking about his modem again?
This is news
Talk show host okra salad raffle
Testified before a grand jury today responding to allegations of assault on oh, we didn't get that photo
On an untelevised show the case was thrown out of court for lack of evidence only part of the amish plaintiff
Okra commented girl this happens all the time y'all just jealous of how much I care
Speaking of care. I care for you smart up
That's all for tonight. Good night
I'm flash rock man, and i'm here to tell you about the clogs for tops
We get the mail channel every other day
I'd like anything else
All right court
What I need a picture of i'm not sure what it is, but I know I need to go to the courthouse
Not where I needed to be all right, uh
Country club o park. Oh, this is right
This is it. All right
Gotta be ready bet. I can beat you on this drive
Oh, yeah, what's it worth to you?
100 bucks says I can go farther than you. Okay
Dude what's he gonna do
He's gonna hurt he's gonna throw it back it's gonna hit him in the face i'm gonna be ready
That one second is all you have the money in the finger money in the hand
begonia battles the bent to bet
sports betting
Go get him soldier hotel or motel
I like that hotel
Is it the hotel or the motel?
Got it
All right. Now i'm gonna wait for something else to happen here
Something he's gonna I it's did I think I got
Something else
What now?
flee
Man, that's a lot of money
Noisy neighbor $25,000. It's all good
a steamy affair
I like that one
Tinsel town, it's gonna be on
tv tomorrow
Got that one. Okay
If you're just tuning in we're following barry begonia's attempt to outrun authorities
He is suspected of gambling on a frisbee golf game after photographic evidence was revealed
What is this?
Is this supposed to be them try? Why is this why we are following a car driving around?
If you're just tuning in we're following barry begonia's attempt to outrun always attempt to out run
I don't understand
It's on every channel
This is news that's fucking funny
All right now
Go save axle. You can't I can't do anything
I can't it the outcome is the same every time
Don't flee
I can't i'm not taking a photo of that. You have to stay. I hold on
I don't want to show this again. This is fucked up. This is fucked up. I don't want to I don't want I showed it
I'm not showing it again. This is fucked up. Hold on. Hold on. I think it's over. I think it's ending
All right favorite I don't want that's that's like too that's that's too much for me. I don't want to that's I don't want to show that shit
Yeah
All right, where we going this is news
And now here's smarto with the local band guide
Tonight there's a lot of great music out there at the rosy conch sucking chest wound display club lingo
Yeah, we already know music world mourns the loss of one
Just tapping the bell
babies
We are where we were before this is exactly where we were last time just just tighten the valve cover
That's all you have to do
Yes for your condoms in school, okay, here we go
Thank you. Thank you. Thanks to each and every one of you
I guess you like me. You really like me now. What? Hey, you're cute. Do you play basketball?
Hey, don't you want me?
What are you afraid of?
Oh my god, it actually happened
What the fuck?
By the way everybody if you just want to know these are I
They are they're all worth like 20 bucks that like oh my god, and it i'm not no. All right. Well, that's fine
Okay
I didn't I was ready to take the photo too. I'm just sitting there ready
And I wasn't even thinking i'm just saying oh, yeah, i'm ready to take the photo
Hey pay your fucking rent
This is news what?
And now you're smarter with the local band guide. Yeah, we're ready to do this. All right, let's go
Let's go to the
motel
This is jeff bezos here i'm here to inform you that you're in violation
It's all right
It's a
I you took a picture when I know but hold on important. What's this one? No
Hey, is this your baddie?
I think it's still good
I instinctively took a photo
That's the worst thing
I'm like so i'm uh
It was just ready because I was ready for anything. Everyone tells me wait, wait, wait, you gotta wait. Wait, Jeremy wait for the action
And I saw action took photo
If you've seen dean winklestein or his co-host valice starbright you may already be a winner
The on-air pair from the show tinseltown triangle has disappeared without a trace. Ah
love makes people do
Praise that they're not gonna show it right one small show for man
one giant news for mankind
It's not a porn game
Every day every hour on the hour at six and ten for my two hour special every 15 minutes
Do you have any idea why my shampoo is so good for your hair?
No, I don't want to fucking hear it again. I don't care what makes your hair shampoo good
We're going to the bug
Well, how about this?
You know, i've got to hand it to you. You have got away with pictures
It looks as though I'll have to start to get busy again with you in town
Ah, but don't you get too comfortable, you know someday soon
Some new hot shoot will be along and then you will have to learn to be a survivor like me
I won
Not great. Not bad. Keep at it
That's the end of the game
I beat the game
eighty two thousand dollars
It's all good
Why are you still playing this because it was interesting
It was very interesting. All right
Let's what do I have? What can I do here? All right, I got
It's been six hours
Yeah, let's call it here. We're gonna keep going tomorrow
Because this is that I got a lot left to do and I don't want to start something that I know i'm going to spend
At least a couple hours two three hours in
So if you want to hear the plan
Here's the plan
I will be streaming
For the next four days in a row
today
tomorrow Sunday and Monday
Monday's stream is going to be the activity book stream
And that will be the last time that I will be live until the carnival
So the 16th is the last stream of that week. You'll see me again four and a half days later
Because I want to there's I have a lot of these things I still want to do
You
The next
The next like five or six fmv games will take us into tomorrow and maybe the next day, too
That was paparazzi. You know, I those are really really those were very very like
Those were good
Steven spielberg that was fucking hilarious. I I literally I actually hurt myself laughing at that game in the first like 45 minutes of the stream
This game was fucking all over the place, but it was at least worth looking at
And one or two others too, right I don't even remember
But tomorrow we are going to start tomorrow with one that
is
It reminds me of wirehead it's apparently a huge budget fmv game. It's called fox hunt
There's a lot and I already tested it out to make sure it worked it looks crazy
And I also have crime patrol too
and
That is like five six seven more of these you'll see tomorrow
We'll start with that though
That has been that's a pretty good place to call it. I think
Let's turn that off turn that off put on the outro and let's say our goodbyes
Do the bits hang up for a little bit
Little do you know that some of these just pop up with fucking ridiculous fucked up shit
But i'll see you tomorrow same time
Let's go back a little while
Oh also
Wait, don't wait. Wait, don't leave yet. Hold on stay right there
the community content
Discord channel is open
There is a long list of rules there suggest you read them
It's there
Go take a look if you're interested
at this point going forward
I will not be opening
original videos
original artwork
We're going to compile them for community nights
So if you have those things
Put them in that channel and follow the rules
Follow them because they're there and they're important
But thank you to pigeon for the five dollars earlier today
Hey germa, it's me again. I'm very excited for twitchcon
So tell me if you don't like meet and greets and prefer to hang out with fans
Does that mean that I should just follow you around?
Uh, well, I don't know if the word hang out with fans
is
necessarily correct
it's more
I
Spend like an hour or two in a spot
or
Kind of just find me
Follow him around and take exactly two photos
Because I will I will give you this. I will tell you full-on completely transparent with you
um
I love talking to people and I love hanging out love getting grabbed and like hey like let's talk
I do it all the time
When I go to conventions like this
But I kind of don't know what else to do
You know what I mean?
I kind of just like hey. Hey, it's me. Hey, it's you. All right
I don't have any fucking idea what i'm doing
It's like that's just real
All right, we're gonna go over this way and
All right. Uh
Hey
Look at me. I'm just gonna do look at me like five times and then fucking leave
What if I did that? What if I just was I got everybody in one place and I was just like oh look at me
Look at me and then I fucking sprinted out the front door
And there was a cab waiting for me and it was just like
Just took off
and I just before I left I like threw in the air a bunch of like
actor headshots that I signed
I've got like 50 of them
Do it but no, I i'll be around i'm only gonna be there for a little while though
because the
Carnival stream is happening the weekend before that
And i'm probably gonna be pretty tired
Then I come back and i'm gonna stream
because obviously I don't I don't want to have a scenario where
I don't stream for a week. Then there's one stream and then what I don't stream for a week again and go to twitchcon
Like i'm not gonna not stream for like two and a half weeks
So i'm gonna come back stream for a few days and then go right to twitchcon
So i'm only gonna be at twitchcon for like two days
I'm not gonna be there for very long
Saturday is the day that i'm gonna be
At twitchcon for the most amount of time
I bring you candy will you eat it?
I will not eat anything that somebody hands me that I don't know where it came from
I've I have no idea where you got it for all. I know like somebody could have like fucking peed on it. I don't know
Absolutely, not I will not eat any food that anybody hands me
Here here here man. Eat this
Sure
Oh, what what where did you get it?
Oh, uh from a trash can outside
She baited and then I go to the fucking hospital for food poisoning
That's a hard policy, sorry guys
no food
no
No drinks
and everybody gets one
Photo where I don't even make any emotion. I just look in the camera with a stone face
And then if you want like on your phone, i'll fucking like sign it
Just open up like the the iphone thing where you can draw on the picture and i'll sign the photo
I'm gonna make that a thing
How about I do that?
I think that you know what guys that's I think that is new age
You take like a selfie with somebody and then oh, can I get your autograph?
Of course, you can open up on your phone that app and let me just go over it on on the bottom
Don't tell any streamer about that
I don't want any streamers or any youtubers or any actors. That's my thing
But now i'll be at twitchcon for at least
the day on saturday
Somewhere probably saturday afternoon. I'm gonna be all over the place
But thank you to the five dollars. Thank you. Zorro carlos for the five dollars
Uh, they say jeremy need to tell you about an awkward experience. I had yesterday at work
I was working the night shift at dunkin donuts and suddenly a literal bia walks through the door down to every feature
Tattooed gray hair beard dressed like a biker
Now the worst part is when he ordered a donut and said it almost exactly how the biaz said in the meeting of the biaz
I tried so hard not to laugh thinking about it
A real life biaz spotting
Oh and just no no big deal or anything just phylactery lich is going with with with their every stream 69 community subs
Yeah, no, no, not no big deal. Just just every single live stream
I've done in the last like two weeks almost 100 subs from phylactery lich
Holy shit
Still going
Still going you're still going
Holy shit phylactery
I could swim in a bathtub with this many subs
What i'm in pool. I get this is a swimming pool full of subs
No, you it's a lot of subs. You know what i'm trying to say here
It's a lot of subs in the same place
but
But phylactery this is too much money, this is too much money
Thank you so much
But it's too much money
That's fucking insane
BAN HIM
No, that's seriously. Thank you
Oh, I i've said this to you every time that this happens
but
If you can't afford this don't do it
You've given such a ridiculous amount of money if you have like 10 fucking mil in the bank right now then okay
All right. Thank you. This is their college fund
No, keep that money and go to college with it
Don't get why is my voice doing that at this point? I can clearly afford it or I wouldn't have internet
Wait, hold on implying that you can afford it because left over you have enough money to still pay for the internet
Jesus
I can still afford to pay the internet
the entire internet
Now you're a a ridiculous contributor to this stream
Thank you for
Your vat of money
It is just simmering in that pot. It sells diamonds. He's a diamond tycoon
maybe
Whatever it is. Thank you
But we will continue
Zoro carlos with that five dollars with the in real life. Yeah
Yeah, I mean that that's a character in gta essentially
And they made those characters because those those characters those people actually they do exist
They are kind of they they do exist
real bs
A while ago you tweeted saying that you wanted a slug woman is kim that slug
By a while ago. Do you mean like three years ago?
When you say a while ago that makes it sound like I said this like a month ago
It's like four years ago
Yeah, look a while ago you said I guess four years still is and it is a while right technically
That is true
Of course i'm looking for a slug
I don't want to go. I don't want to climb any mountains or ride any bikes
I want to eat a whole bag of baked lays and have the person sitting next to me
Not say anything about it
I want to silently be embarrassed about it and look over and oh no, no, no, that's fine. No, it's fine
He's avoiding the question. I just answered it
I missed this from earlier. I don't know how
But corporal boom gave 55 dollars and 50 cents
So corporal if you're still here, thank you so much for the huge fucking 55 plus dollar bit drop here
This is about four hours ago
What was I doing? I must have been so locked in
Thank you so much though corporal if you're still here
Just say kim is my slug woman
No, but that doesn't
All right. I said it. I just said it but kim isn't active
Kim likes to walk places and no no
What I meant to say in that tweet is i'm looking for somebody that like doesn't give a shit that i'm a slug
Anyways, thank you. Silent serenity for the 250. They say louder. That was during piper
Ridiculous. Thank you door cube for the 250
the glitched audio from the stephen spiritware game is the same noise I get in my ears when I experience
a
Hypnagogic jerk that thing where you're about to fall asleep and your muscles freak out and wake you up
That's terrifying
Because I know the noise you're talking about
Uh, thank you the tickles for 15 dollars. They say imagine a world where germa's games worked
I think we got some pretty good mileage out of east today
Besides the stephen spielberg game crash
They worked pretty well
and
I mean, obviously the piper the audio just not working at all. That's all right
Too bad the rat game didn't work. I know
I know
Unfortunate
That would have been an absolute crowd pleaser. I know it but thanks for the 15 dollars
Thank you
Like four broke today
What was the other one?
I did stephen spielberg director
I did piper
paparazzi
And that was it, right?
There's only three tonight, right?
Am I losing my mind? Did I play other ones?
I don't know. I didn't play any of them
No, not tonight only three
But thank you. Thank you swiggity swanky for the 250 this stream is the most i've laughed all week
But I have heart issues when I strain too much my chest hurts
Maybe that's why you have stomach issues
Be careful. Take care of yourself
Don't strain too much
Uh, no, this is a new problem. I don't know what the hell is wrong with me
Oops, I had like the colonoscopy. I've had a bunch of fucking tests and shit. I don't know. I've no i'm sorry
I just like hit you
And I really didn't mean to
Uh, i've had like stomach and abdomen pain
For like six months
That radiates into my back and I nobody knows what the hell's wrong with me. So
Try still trying to figure that out and it doesn't think I don't think it has anything to do with the colitis
So it's annoying
but um
Yeah
Appendix I don't maybe I don't think so though not where it's not where I get like all my issues
Stop sitting so much. I walk around. I I don't sit that much at all
Contrary to popular belief guys. I don't sit down for a very long time besides this
Besides streaming i'm typically up walking around
Kim and I will go places. We'll go do something. I don't sit that often unless it's right here
And remember I only stream like three times a week
Sometimes like four
But it probably has something to do with it. Maybe a little bit
Because this is a new issue from the last
Probably seven or eight months
Right before I left it was like two months before I moved out of massachusetts when this started happening
I don't know. I've had so many doctors talk to me about it
But whatever you just you know, we we keep going
Keep trying to figure out what the fuck's going on, right?
What you do when you don't stream I imagine you just wait in an empty room until your next stream
I'm just like an android that goes into a closet and like kim turns the button on the back of my neck off
And then a day or two goes by and she turns it back on and sits me down and I just boot up
in a t-pose
God, thank you gray tax for the 10 bucks. I knew the name lasso app
So sounded familiar because that's the name of a dog breed
That originated from tibet
Anyways, love you streams and I hope you're you are loving life and kicking ass
Yeah, i'm i'm having a good time
Things are going pretty well
I really can't complain that much things are going great
Thank you
For the 10 bucks. I love dogs
I really do s10w update slow update. Thanks to the five dollars
Hey, germa just want to donate before the big day. Hope the carnival is a massive success
Uh because I borrowed a lot of money, uh money here
I borrowed a lot of money from the mafia
Combine those two things to give you bits and I need to prove my money was put to good use because if they don't
They'll take my house and my kidneys
Good luck and I hope for the best
You already know what's next peace and love peace and love
Thank you with five dollars slow update
Uh, I can't think of very many things that i've been looking forward to more
at least in the last
I would say in the last five years
As I truly mean this
The carnival stream is that i've been looking forward to this more than anything. I think in the last five years
At least the last three
Why would you borrow five dollars from the mafia?
Yeah, I don't know why you would do that either
Not even live-action germa rumble
I think it's uh, it's different though
Because this is actually live action something something
And plus the live-action rumble was a long fucking time ago
Was it 2014 2015?
That was five almost five fucking years ago
2016 was I thought it was 2015. I don't even know my own channel. Was that 20 that was in 2016
No, how did I make this video?
What in the fuck did I make this video?
Holy shit. It was it was august of 2016 17 18 19
This has been more than three years. That's almost five
What did I say? I said four originally
That's been more than three years. That's a long time
but yeah, I mean I
This is a live event
That is not just a live event. It's a live event that has a ton of participation and a ton of work has gone into it
It's not just hey like for instance. I've always wanted to do like a live wrestling thing
But that would just be like a presentation a live presentation. This is not just a live presentation. This is
A live presentation that is completely and totally dictated by what you guys are going to do
It's going to be total anarchy
We'll see
I'm
I cannot wait to see what you guys do. I cannot wait. What was that like weird cadence there weird, but yeah
We'll see i'm gonna laugh my ass off if I get down there and set everything up
And this this is like a blackout
Here we go, let's start the carnival. Mmm
You would laugh? No, I would go
And by the way i'm looking up into the sky
Like it's not what he's fault. I'm looking up into the sky going which one of you did it?
Who did it?
He's cursing god
Which one of you did it?
Trump whisper
Let me tell you I see
No, that was like eric cartman. That's what you're wrong
No, these guys are fucking pros
These guys are so good. They're incredibly talented. They're really really great at what they do. They're great people
I am insanely lucky
To have been put in contact
With the people at andy mark because holy shit. They are they are they're awesome. They are so fucking awesome
It's such a relief
Trust me when I say
Did you hire an entire circus? Not the whole thing
But thank you slow update
I hope it goes good, too
hunter johnson, thanks for the five dollars. Hey jeremy been watching your streams and videos for a couple of years and
now
Years now and you haven't gone stale. Keep it up
um
I don't I I can't
Do the same thing twice
Now I know that the way that I approach things and the way that I oh, what do I want to do that?
What do I think is funny?
You stay in like the same realm of what you think is funny
But if I don't think something's interesting or if I don't think something is funny, i'm not going to do it and I don't care about it
She doesn't care
I'm talking about putting like time into a project
You've been saying behalf of 10 years now that hasn't gotten old. That's well. That's what I mean. Like I
But we've moved on
I killed all the memes before
I like to try things new things different things
As much as I can right and obviously don't you know, oh i'm never i'm never gonna say the word be ever again
That's not funny. I've never thought it was funny. I can't believe you fucking think this is still funny
No, I do. I do still think that's funny
I do
I don't know. I don't do it all the time
What about speed not that on the other hand?
I'm kidding
I love all my joke children
Even the ones that don't eat their vegetables, but if you don't think i'm stale
That makes me happy because I don't want anybody to you know
I don't want people to come to the stream be like, oh this is like this
Oh stale shitty. Oh german 985. Wow
I remember he's been around for like 10 years. Holy wow in the last few years
Not been very good
Oh, yeah, he really needs to fucking like stop because like holy shit. I don't want anyone to think that
You know, I I want to
I want to be like an entertaining streamer
I don't want to be the guy that you talk about like I remember when he used to be fucking okay
And now he this guy sucks
No, I don't
Everything's still going just fine
Yeah, it's me
Oh wo
I don't want to be he doesn't know
He said it
Uh-oh
Yeah, I don't want to be stale and if I ever feel like I am stale
Then i'm just gonna stop
I'm not gonna do it anymore
If I don't think if i'm not having a good time and if i'm don't think i'm doing something that I think is interesting or fun
I'm not gonna do it anymore. Why would I do it?
Do it for money
I I can't though
I have to want to turn this stream on guys. Like I can't just well, you know, i'll make money if I turn it on
I can be serious
What the fuck am I gonna talk about? What am I gonna do?
Just talk with the vr voice and we'll give the subs
Oh like burping
Yeah, no
No, no i'm not into that
once I had like running the shit I want to do and
If I stop having fun
Then i'm just gonna i'm just gonna move on. You know, that's not gonna I don't think that'll happen anytime soon
We've talked about this before guys. We've talked about this a few times before you guys already know this
You don't need me to tell you this. You know this already
He's already talking about retirement. Yeah, but we're in this world
It's you know, it's a very volatile world in the online kind of twitch youtuber
I don't know. I don't know what's gonna happen. I didn't predict I was gonna be on twitch
I didn't even know I was gonna be making youtube videos
I don't know stream from your retirement house. Maybe
If I can still if I can still have a good time streaming
I'll be 100. What would I do for money if streaming wasn't profitable?
um
I don't know. I figure it out
I have a few backup plans
I figure it out. You'd be a clown veterinarian
Why are you applying that to clowns?
animals
What?
but anyways
That figures up the note it
Um, i'll i'll be i'll be just fine. Don't worry phylactery again
Thanks for the 69 community subs and the 50 that you gave that I missed 15 minutes ago
50 more dollars from phylactery loaded
Jerma imagine if your teeth were flaccid and they only got hard when you were hungry monka s
That just makes me think about the rennan stimpy episode when they had when he has the the nerve endings all through his whole mouth
blah
That's the most uncomfortable fucking episode i've ever seen in my life
of any tv show
Oh, and they're like
Pulling them out. Holy shit. I forgot about how horrible that episode was
Oh my god
Yeah
I don't want to think about that
I loved that show though, but thank you phylactery for the 50 dollars
And all these subs that you gave there. We're about to see a bunch of them right now. Why don't we look at them?
Thank you everybody for subbing. Is it still september? It's still september, right?
I think so. Yeah, it is
Well, it's september is september, right? Okay, at least
Half off something you'd like to see some more serious work from me
That's the plan
Hey, remember we talked about all that stuff about staying interested and wanting to keep my streams fresh and
Make sure I still enjoy what i'm doing and still like doing this and care about it more and more and more that's how
Is to do more and more projects with the right people now
To always have another thing to look forward to
That's the idea kind of a trial run
But thank you to all mew for the 250. Hey germa longtime fan been watching since 2006
Surprised you haven't found me yet. Keep it up haven't found you yet
Surprised you haven't found me yet found you
Where should I be looking?
There you are
Why you haven't found me yet?
He's like under the stairs
That's fucked up
He's on the ceiling
He's tom cruise tethering from the ceiling
But thank you. That's a long fucking time
That is an insane amount of time
That is 12 years
Holy shit
I haven't even been alive that long
Hey c4g, thanks for the 250
uh
If there were two guys on the moon and one killed the other with a rock
Would that be fucked up or what?
Uh, yeah
I think uh, I think killing anybody with a rock is fucked up. I don't I don't know where the context is here
But thank you c4g 250. Thank you silent serenity for the 250
Germa at the risk of sounding like one of those guys have you tried marijuana since you moved to nevada?
I had the realization the other day that it's legal here
And i'm a responsible adult kind of weird when you think about it like that
Uh, yes
I did that. Yeah
Don't don't tell anybody don't take any photos of me doing that
drug addict gambler
He does it before he streams
I'm calling the police. It's legal in nevada. It's
Recreational marijuana is legal in the state of nevada
So my mom told me to turn the stream off
I don't
You know what? Who cares?
What am I gonna tell you? What am I what am I gonna tell you that you don't already know?
I'm calling my mom and telling her how cool you are
That saying that you smoked marijuana is as interesting as saying that you just got out of the dentist
Like is it does it who well who cares?
Hey, I just uh, I just had a crown put in
Okay
No, cool. It does it does it feel better?
Yeah
Yeah, it does
nice
Is there anything else you'd like to share with me?
Yeah, I smoked a joint
Like an hour ago, too
Okay
How did that make you feel?
I felt pretty good
Well, I didn't because I was streaming i've been i've been sitting here. I've been live for like seven hours
We I can't do it right now
I would I don't want to I don't I wouldn't want to I don't
No, I know here here it comes. Here it comes though there
You drink on stream sometimes
Sometimes
Yeah, I drink like one beer sometimes on stream two boxes of wine
and then just like
Go downstairs to the fridge and like eat food and go to bed
You guys know that every time that I drink wine on this stream
I will drink a bunch of wine and then I will just go open the fridge
Give me that
It just eats a bunch of stuff
And then I just go face first into the bed
And just sleep
I mean, I don't look i'm why would I ever get
Like drunk to a point on stream that I would it was like embarrassing. I mean it's happened once or twice
But not that no i'm always i'm totally always with it
I would never drink to complete excess on stream
That's not I without i'm not i wouldn't do that
That doesn't happens a lot. What do you mean that happens a lot?
No, it does not happen. That's happened like once when I did the fucking pretend backflip. I remember that stream
That was a vr stream
There's only been like two or three true times where i've been like shit faced on stream
And it was that eight hour vr stream where I did the backflip
What about the labo stream?
Whatever that's different though
All right, let's get out of here
thank you to
Uh silence surrounding the bill if you if you if it's illegal where you are and you're responsible
be responsible fucking adult and
Do what you want as long as it's legal
Don't be stupid
Then go for it
And that's all I gotta say about that
Have a wonderful rest of the night to see you guys tomorrow. We'll be back at it again with
More I told you this is going to be fmv week
See you tomorrow. We're going to start with fox hunting
Take care
See you soon
Have a wonderful day have a wonderful night because it's late now
See you tomorrow