Okay, welcome to the stream. I hope you all had a good couple last days. My name's Jerma.
If you've never been here before, uh, welcome to the stream. Today we're gonna do some Dreamcast
and by do, I mean, probably finish the Dreamcast. I noticed my voice today, it's very low and
booming. I've been taking my booming voice supplements, I've been taking my vocal
supplements. So now I can do a radio commercial for a jewelry store. Ah, they give real bad diarrhea
though. I wouldn't recommend taking them. Anywho, we got a couple of announcements to make today.
Something that's been for a long time coming. Should have been here a long time ago,
but it's here now. And of course, what I mean is T-shirts! T-shirts! There's only one new one,
but these will be available forever. And I want to give just a quick little sneak peek of what
I am talking about here. So, uh, don't look at that! You're not supposed to see that yet.
So, uh, one of the ideas I had for a shirt, I thought it would be really, really cool,
uh, because I'm such a huge fan of Star Wars, right? So why not make my own Star
Wars shirt? I love Luke Skywalker, I love Darth Vader, so figured I was gonna have my own
version of a Star Wars shirt and here we are. This is the one. It's Darth Vader in front of a
fireplace for Christmas time. You know? Look, you understand? And I think you're gonna, I think
your friends are gonna laugh at this. I didn't make this though. This shirt has nothing to do
with me. I just think you should, like, get it. But this is what I meant by, like, T-shirt.
We're talking about, like, T-shirt day. See? I had nothing to do with any of this. But,
like, you and your friends might think it's funny, so you should, like, maybe get one.
Alright, let's show the real one! Here it is. So halfway through that, I just realized I could
have just been sued by Disney. So I kind of panicked and, uh, and stopped that immediately,
because that, that's not a lawsuit that I actually want. I realized that about halfway
through that joke. So here is what you can buy starting today and, uh, lasting forever.
Here it is. I think I just crashed my OBS. Holy shit. I just crashed OBS because I tried
to load this. Are we still here? Hello? I just overloaded OBS. Well, uh, alright. Anyway,
um, the whole stream just almost went down. I almost just broke my computer.
If you do exclamation point shirts, or if you just go to teespring.com slash store slash
germa985, uh, glue man is back in multiple colors, in multiple cuts, and the night sky is
the new shirt. I wish, I don't know why I just did this. Bear with me for a second while I try
to figure out what the hell that was. I just, uh, there we are, okay. Um, I think I have to,
alright, I'm gonna have to make this my, like, desktop background for some reason.
Why did this have to happen? The night sky is, uh, literally what happens when you look
through a telescope. Really? My computer. I actually can't, I'm just gonna make it my
fucking desktop because, like, this is, I don't know why this won't, this just won't work.
I can't open my file anymore. Oh, that's interesting. Anyways, restart computer. I can.
Where the fuck? Alright, I think my, like, computer just got electrocuted because, like,
I dropped, like, a thousand frames and it said overloading CPU and now I can't open files.
Why? Because I, what the fuck? Alright, well anyways, we're gonna play crazy taxi tonight.
Okay, I'm getting a lot of community subs here. Let me, this really just threw me off.
I have no fucking idea why this happened. I was gonna, like, show the image on screen
and it, my, my computer was electrocuted. Here. Let's just do, fucking, who cares? Fuck this.
Ready? Here we go. Uh, well, let me do this first because I want people to see what it
actually looks like. So this is an old one. This is the glue man shirt. This is what
you can expect. There are multiple colors now, though. There's, like, three or four colors,
so that's really cool. Uh, I don't think it's the exact same t-shirt, though. I believe
they no longer have these, like, American, American apparel doesn't exist anymore, right?
So I think it's next level tees. It's the highest goddamn quality I could possibly fucking
select and that's not even true either, but it was one, it was one of the highest quality
shirts I could buy to have them put on. It's like their premium t-shirt, whatever that
means. But, uh, that's what it looks like. I don't even know what color this is. This is,
like, that navy blue, maybe? All these were made, the, all the designs, both of them were
made by Ashley, so her link is in those descriptions. Name, name lag? Name lag? What's
name lag? Name lag? I didn't know! I didn't, we had it mirrored last time. That's what it
looks like. This is the shirt you're getting. This is, well, this is not the exact shirt,
but it's very close and they're available permanently. These are never, I'm not gonna,
I'm not gonna take these off. The Glueman shirt, the Night Sky shirt, they are both gonna be
available permanently, forever. That's a storefront. I can put other shit on that storefront.
Fucking Disney, don't even look at this shirt. You know, this is not even mine. That was a
joke I made. I want to reiterate that. That was just a comedy piece. Anyways, forever. I'm
not taking them down for any reason. They're always gonna be $20. Just, if you want one,
thank you. I hope you like the way it looks. And now we're gonna play Crazy Taxi and some
more Dreamcast shit. I want to fucking show this on, why can I not open files?
It worked like 35 minutes ago. Can you make hats? I can make a lot of shit in that store.
It's, there's a bunch of random storefronts and accessories and iPhone cases and there's a
lot of, you can do a lot. Please, I'm gonna try, I'm gonna try one last fucking thing
because this is like a big deal. I haven't had a new shirt in like three or four years.
So let me just get this fucking situated because this is fucking dumb. I think I got it. Come on.
Come on. Yeah, I had to do a little bit of, I had to doctor a little bit of shit but I got it.
Okay, let's go over this shirt because I've seen a lot of people asking about what the
hell, what the heck is this? I haven't even seen it yet. There it is. Look at that, finally.
Hey, it only took up like fucking two years. Here is the night sky. This is the new shirt.
Just a father and son exploring the outdoors together, taking a look through the telescope.
Clear, beautiful. This is, at any point where you are right now, this is what you will see
when you look up. It's just, you know, me and my dad. Why can they see the earth?
What are you talking about? I mean, just, yeah. I mean, where are they in this scenario?
You know what I mean? That's the best part. Where are they? What fucking planet are you on?
No, this is father and son looking at the night sky through a telescope.
Okay, no Saturn. No, Saturn wasn't popular enough to be on the shirt. Sorry.
Only the popular planets get to fit on the t-shirt. If you understand, design choice wise,
unpopular planets can't fit on t-shirt. So that's how science works. If the planet's
not popular, they're just fucking delete it. They don't care. Yeah, that means that they're
on one of those planets. And guys, Saturn and Mercury, they could, they could be behind that.
They're behind there somewhere. See the moon? The moon's very large.
Bigger than the sun. So of course that, like, Mercury could probably be behind the moon.
This is just what's available from this National Geographic Photographer's angle.
Why do they need a telescope if the planet's that big? Because you want to make,
you want to see what's on the fucking surface. And how do you know that? We don't know where this
photo could be taken from. What do you want to see the crevices? You want to, like,
what's behind the moon? What's, where are the asteroids? But all jokes aside, this is,
I love this design. I think it's great. I think it'll look good on, on any chest.
It's a lovely, lovely, lovely t-shirt. Yeah, like you guys could be looking through
the telescope. Right? This is, this is potentially two or three different angles
melded together in a beautiful fucking incredible design. Don't you understand? That's you
looking through that scope. Don't you get it? But I have to thank, again, this is Ashley
for the incredible artwork and realizing half the dumb shit that I said to her. That's really,
really fantastic. Thank you so much. It looks great. And you all know what the Glooman
one looks like, but this is the new one. This shirt is only available in black for very obvious
reasons because it's supposed to, the father and son in the telescope are supposed to be
silhouettes. So putting, you know, that wouldn't really look okay on, like, a green shirt.
So black is the only available color here. The site says only available for three days.
Uh, that's, that's not, no way. That's not true. I don't know why it's saying that,
but I have it set to, I have it set to permanently be available. Only available for three days.
Now that's, I have like a storefront. Let me, let me just make sure. So they're printing
in three days. So what, how Teespring works is every three days orders get printed and
shipped out. So I don't know why it says available for three days, but that's just how
they print. So if you order your shirt today, you know, three days from now, all the ones that
were ordered in the last three days are going to print and then it'll start over again.
And it takes probably like a week or so, maybe a little bit more depending on where you live
to get there. But we'll see. Hopefully they turn out good. The last time I used Teespring,
the shirt came out good and I didn't change anything really. So let's hope that they look
as good and wear as good as the Glooman shirts did a few years ago. Anyways, uh,
we're going to move on. If you want to buy one, they're there. And, uh, we're going to move on
and play crazy taxi and move on to like Sega bass fishing and maybe a little bit of a jet
grind radio was the link to the store. If you just do, uh, exclamation point shirts,
it'll pop up. It's a Teespring storefront. You just kind of click on whatever you want.
Uh, I added, I can only make sure I said I added a cut. I added a, another cut for
the Glooman shirt. So there's like a women's tee. There's like a unisex tee. There's a couple of
them. I didn't do it yet for the night sky yet because I figured I'd just let just the t-shirt
be exist for what, like for now, I guess. Oh, this, the shirts have sold out and I'm like,
God, make a dress. I can't do that. But anyways, thank you. It's been a long time coming.
Uh, I know a lot of people have been looking forward to that and so have I.
It's good that it's, uh, finally available. So let's start crazy taxi and, uh, kind of put
a cap on the Dreamcast stuff. Maybe not. I say that, but there's like still Shenmue
and like Shenmue. In my opinion, that's not Dreamcast stuff, though. Shenmue is not like
the Dreamcast stuff because, you know, it's not, it is Dreamcast, but it's not because
it's coming out on PC now. It's Shenmue 3 is coming out in like a few months or something.
Isn't it? Okay. Let me make sure this works. It does. I'm getting my controller.
Seaman. Yeah, I'm still, I know. And I still can play Seaman. I'm going to just load that
up one day for fun. You will see Seaman. I promise. I just kind of got fucked over
in the packaging. Somebody sent me the just disc and no microphone. So that sucked,
but let's go. Thank you for joining me. Joining me. I'm going to turn the lights on in here.
So crazy taxi is a game where you drive around in a taxi and it's fucking crazy.
Best description. I could probably get it. So how do you play this? You just drive people
around, right? They got arcade, original, uh, crazy box. What is crazy box? You can do arcade,
right? That makes the most sense. Arcade play by play, play by arcade rules. Work for three
minutes, work for five minutes. Just go arcade rules. The box, the box, the box. Let me just
remember how to play. Go ahead and pick a car and driver. All right. Let's see.
I'm going to be open shirt. Okay. Let's have some fun.
All right. So how do you drive?
Cable car stop top. It's probably kind of loud, but sorry. Whoa, the,
the analog, the analog is very sensitive. You know, it's also very loud. I'm in 99th place.
978 miles. Um, why did it reverse the controls? Um, right trigger. Why is it doing this?
I, what happened? Oh, right. Okay. I can, I have to set it. I have to set the gear.
Six bucks for the jump. I can't even fucking focus. All right. Get out. I can't drive on
the beach. Why? Hold on a minute. This is important. This shit is loud. I'm going to
turn the music up and the sounds down. This is hurting my brain. Let's go get in. I was
going to go very close, very close. Go get out. That was my practice. That was my practice.
692 bucks for two customers. Are you sure you don't want to register?
I don't want to register. No. Stop popping up every time I log into your website to ask
me if I want to register for updates. No, I don't want push notifications. I don't want you to
email me fucking flyers. No, I only do that again. Excellent. Now I'm ready to get this
going. Let's try to get like a thousand dollars at least. Yep. Same. I'm picking up
the same exact person that I picked up last time. Descent. Get out. Speedy. Speedy. All
right. All right. Go through the chain link fence. All right. This is big money right here.
Yacht harbors. This is 1.2 kilometers. All right. I got to get some air here.
250. Good tip. Four dollars. Good tip. Park. What are you guys doing? Just parking the
road. It's the same like SUV. Yo. Speedy. Who's next? Yellow. Get him. That was a pretty nice
maneuver. That's not a... Can we get out of the car? Whoa. What the fuck? Get out. Made it
over a thousand dollars, right? Good. PC Ford. Alexa. What? Can I pick up more than one
person? I forget. Excuse me. Excuse me. PC Ford. Yeah. Well, here's the thing, though,
guys. Right? This is available. Go. What the fuck are you doing? This is available on Dreamcast,
but the PC port was like six bucks or something, and the actual Dreamcast version
at lower resolution is, I believe, like at least 30 to 40 dollars. It's something like
that. Come on. Look at me. Look. Whoa, whoa, whoa. Over 1600. Come on. Last one. Come on.
Three, two, one. Get out. Ah, that's not gonna be bad. That's what I currently have.
Really? That wasn't good. I thought that was okay. No, what about original? play by
arcade rules in original. Let's do uh, I'm gonna try every person. Fuck off, I want the big money.
This is a $400 affair. $1.50. $2.00. $4.00. Ooh, near miss. A head-on crash got me 50 cents.
Get out! Watch out, out, out, out, out, out, out. All right, I gotta turn him around, right?
I'm thinking, I'm thinking of going down. Down or is it? I think it is this way. I was
thinking I could go up a few jumps to make some more money. Actually, it kind of worked.
I thought I could go off like a jump going down. Apparently not. There's too many sounds. There
are a lot of sounds, you're right. I need two grand. I just don't get in car accidents. I say
you get more tips. Like that. Oh, that would have been... What is under the car? What's
going on? Why am I popping up and down like this? What's wrong with my car?
Fuck you. Right here. All right, I got more than I had last time. This is a quick one. Near crash.
There it is. Gotta drive on the wrong side of the road to make this money.
Nice. That wasn't bad. I immediately picked one up. Okay, good. Turn around. Same deal.
Oncoming traffic. Weave. Ooh! Ooh! Oh, don't ever tell me I've never fucking played this
game before because I haven't. I did like once. There we go. I better get like a class
B license for this. All right, I need something. Come on, get in there. Landing here. I'm gonna
say bang of right. No, left. We park. Oh, look at this jump. Come on. Do I have enough
strength? Apparently. Apparently. All right, we're still fine. Everything's just good.
We're just... We got hit by a fucking train. I don't think this is the way to play through
that. Oh! That wasn't bad. God damn it. This game's too addicting. I might as well do
AAA. Is it too loud? Should I turn it down? Or is it just good enough? Original. I can
do this. Play off by arcade rules. Good. All right, let's do, uh, China. What was
it? 2600 was my best one? I need to get like over three grand. Clean. Let's go.
Stop. Ah! That was a lot of tips though. That was so many dips. That was so many dips.
All right, let's pull this one back. North camp station. Come on, Gina. What the
hell was that? I got plenty of time. Don't worry. I'm gonna get a class B license.
I'm gonna clean this up. We're gonna get it. Over the hill. Nice. Nice. Come on,
I need some more of that. Nice. Come on. More tips. Oh! It's right there. Go through. Go
through. No! Beat the train! At least it's not gonna be very good. Class E gamer. I'm
gonna get at least class B before I change to a different game. Watch this one. Holy shit,
Germ. I didn't think you could do that. Yeah. Dude, I played this game all day,
years ago, and I still play it. And I didn't even know that was a possible jump scenario.
Get in. In. Straight away. It's not straight away. It was that way. Oh! I got it! Anybody in
here? Is that somebody? This game's fucking fun. Still. That was not even good. I can do
better than that. Whoa. Don't crash on me. Don't crash on me. Class C streamer. Don't
worry. I'm not allowed. All right. So who did I like the most? Probably Beedie. I think I made
the most money with Beedie. Go expensive first. Wave Beach. I want at least $200 in tips.
Count it. That's not a tip? How? You really threw me off with that no tip, dude.
Air. Come on. Air. I need air. I did actually turn. How did I go the wrong way?
Are you serious? No. Do it again.
I thought I had the... I thought I cut it the right direction. What the fuck was the arrow doing?
What the hell was that? Come on, man. Jump to car. Good. Ten bucks. Come on. More. More tips.
That was the best I possibly could have done that. Right here. Pizza parlor. This is far
away. Drive. Nice. Good cut. Good cut. You've got a cut than that. Like that one. That was
still a pretty good cut. Right here. Got another person immediately. Big bits. $50.
Holy shit. Miniclips. Thanks for the 50 bucks. They say slow. Wait, wait, wait. Hey,
Jerma, keep up the good work and never stop being speedy. Thank you, Miniclips. Thank you
for the 50 bucks. 5,000 bits. It means a lot. Thank you so much. I'm going to be fast.
It's a shitload of money. All right, Miniclips. I gotta, I gotta, I gotta make at least $50 in tips.
Oh fuck. It's too ridiculous. Jesus. All right. I didn't make $50 in tips. It's okay. Anybody
around here that I can pick up? I need them right now. You. The Millennium Tower. I need
to make three grand at least. But I need to jump. Any jumps around here? Shit! It's all
right. It's okay. Just build up tips. Cut it. Okay. We're good. It's the Millennium Tower
right here. Let's go. Get in. Okay. This is going to take us out. Where the hell am I? How do
I get out of here? What was the last? The highest I've ever had was 26. I did the same
thing last time. Oh fuck. I made it. Okay. I need another fair. Where? There! This way.
All right. Grand Mercury Hotel. Don't do this to me, game. Come on. Get out of my fucking
way. Too many cars. Holy shit. Got it. Somebody else? Is there any other fair? Go! Yes!
Hurry, hurry, hurry. Back to the Millennium Tower. That guy just crashed into me. What a dick.
Millennium Tower. No. Oh fuck. No.
Crazy box. Crazy box. Jump past the K point. Stunt challenge mode.
How do you do this without? What did I do wrong?
Is there like a super mode?
There's a speed boost. How do you do that? Pushing in the sticks.
X, Y. That's the horn. That's going. That's reverse. That's.
Press the gas right when you shift. Okay. There we go. That would save so much time if I did
that in any of the actual game. That would save so much time. Okay. Cool. So that's. You have to
be in reverse and then go into gas. Go into front. Perform crazy drifts to earn a minimum 15 combo
within the time limit. Crazy. So we're learning. We're learning the ropes here. How do you do
a crazy drift? Just hold on the brake? Is there like another combination of buttons I don't know
how to do here? Wait, wait, wait, wait. Okay. How am I doing that? This is so many more
ways to get tips that I wasn't doing. How did I just do that? I think it's hold. Okay. So
it looks like you go into reverse and then immediately into drive while you're turning.
No. No. So you hit both of them at the same time. Okay. So you have to do
reverse and drive at the same time. That's how you do it. All right. So I'll get it this time.
Press start. What do you mean? Like options? Like controls?
That doesn't. Brake horn. Confirm destination. Gear. Drive. Reverse. Yeah. So. I just got baited.
All right. Sorry. I got it. I figured it out. All right. We need.
So I need to get a 15 combo. Shouldn't be too hard. Press start. That was apparently too hard.
Let's give it another go. Ready? Try it again. I think. Let me go faster. Let me see. How long
can I hold it for? Can I like go across the hole? Can I just drift across the whole thing?
I guess it's like five or six that you can actually add it up to.
You can actually control it. Yeah, you can control it while you're turning.
Take all the customers to their destination within the time limit.
Let's go. 109 seconds. Advice is the start button.
You're talking about like at the menu. Not like in game. Why did I just lose time?
What? Oh, you're over here this time. Okay. I gotta get used to that.
It's weird to hit that brake like that. Have to hit both buttons at the same time.
I'm gonna have you. It's A and B together to do that. It's kind of awkward.
What the fuck? Why? 56 seconds. Am I insane? Did that just say 109 seconds?
Oh, it was a minute. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. All right. I mean that's click.
Why not just say 60? So that's one minute and nine seconds.
Count up. 590. Well, I mean it doesn't say why in all three numbers the first one should be large
and the second two should be small. God damn it. I'm trying to. Why do I go faster when you
do a brake? E-brake like that. You like drift and go so fast. Welcome to crazy taxi.
I'm just gonna brake normally. I could get it if I did. I'm gonna do it again. Let's do it again.
It's time to get it. Go, go, go. What the fuck? Oh, why?
You have to. That's annoying. It is. All right. So let me explain something here. You have to
press reverse and drive at the same time. So when you do that, when you take your finger
off, sometimes you're just in reverse. He's making excuses. You can call whatever you want.
I'm just trying to get that down because it's hard to do that.
Oh my god. You have to start that drift to turn around in the middle of the road like 150 feet
away at least. Let me try that. I'm not even gonna do it. Just do it. Just like drop them off
because you got to complete stop. Turn. Shit. No, I'm not gonna get it. Doing it in the wrong
order. It's fucking crazy. That's ridiculous. How do you control that? That's insane. Wrong order?
Like aren't they the same distance away from each other? All right, isn't it all the same
distance? Oh my lord. Wrong order of missions. Let me try something. That's fucking crazy. Oh
my god. How would you ever time that correctly? Get me out of here. Wait, hold on. So you
tell me that I have to do this like Demon's Souls wise? If 3-1 is harder than 1-2. 3-1 is
harder than like 2-2. Oh, I thought this was just kind of... all right. So I like wasn't supposed
to do 3-1 until I knew how to do the other things. It goes down like this. I thought it
was 1-1-2. All right, can't you just call it 1-2-3-4-5-6-7-8-9? What the hell was it supposed to do here?
Run over the flag behind the car within the time limit to execute it. So shift into reverse,
shift into drive to do a crazy drift. There's a flag behind me. Okay, so...
Okay, what? I didn't even need to... no, that was... you want me to drift and then...
I thought there was like a flag behind... All right, I got it. Why does it want me to do the
crazy drift here? Pop all the balloons within the... okay, pop the balloons.
You have to get a crazy dash right after a crazy drift. Crazy dash is... let off the...
let off the accelerator, shift into D, press the accelerator. Let's see. Oh boy, that's hard to
do that. What if I'm already... okay, hold on. What if I'm already in reverse... if I'm
already in drive? That's so confusing. So if you're in reverse, you have to be in reverse.
Totally learn how to do that. You're doing a drift, shift into drive, and then do...
accelerate. But what if I'm not in? That makes no sense to me. So hold on. A crazy dash
is you let off the accelerator and then you have to shift into drive and then press the
accelerator, right? To do a... to do a... no, god damn it. I want to look at the...
You have to shift into reversed and then shift into drive. So but you then... but you
have to shift. So is it just like a practice arena? So hold on. Just set up a macro. That seems
really hard to do, reliably. Shift back into drive after shifting from reverse to drive.
Let off the accelerator. Well, shift into reverse, drive, shift into drive. Okay, well,
I'm just gonna play. I'm just gonna try to do it. What is 2-2? Time limit. You gotta go
into reverse, turn, and then drive. Well, let me just try to do this with my new techniques
that I've learned. All right, that's good. Even that alone is gonna help. No, it's not.
Oh my god! That's not helping at all, actually. The drift just makes you go crazy.
Jesus! I'm just like killing people. Oh, A, B. Oh, that's annoying. Okay, I'm gonna
try for drift. The drift uphill. What a great idea. I mean, that was kind of cool. That should be.
Nope, but I'm in reverse. What the fuck is happening? I've done like exponentially worse
since involving the like advanced techniques. So now I'm in reverse. I don't like that
mechanic. The handbrake should not be reversed. It's completed! Only two dollars
can be driving into a train in the last second pulling away. Holy fuck, that was 20 dollars.
Hold on, I'm gonna try it again.
Somebody mentioned, it probably would be insane to see somebody do like a super expert,
like 3,000 hours in crazy taxi gameplay. That would be pretty insane. I'm only gonna
use the drift. I'm only gonna use those techniques when I need them. For instance,
right there and then be in reverse. I thought those were just tables, like
technique tables on the street. I can't go in that way. This is all wrong.
Really? Let's go. There it is! Come on, get out! 17 bucks! Lot of money, let's go!
That would have been clean if that asshole wasn't in the way. How many cars to do this?
Undrift, too many cars. No! Goddamn drift acceleration! Sorry. God, please.
Turn, turn around! Go for that jump. Get out of my way. It's right here. I need somebody right
now. Somebody, somebody, somebody, somebody, anybody, anyone, anyone, you! Get in! Why?
That's so hard to fucking do that reliably. Like, actually win a game without sitting there.
Jesus Christ. We're gonna see again.
I'll give it a few more attempts before we move on, because we got a lot of other shit to do.
He got worse after he trained. Yeah, because the techniques you have to do are actually
fairly difficult to pull off in a game scenario. Like, those drifts, you get tips,
but you don't complete. You're like, holy fuck, that was a lot of money, but like,
I screwed myself up. I lost like four seconds. Where'd it go? What? Okay, what the fuck is this?
No! Hello? What the fuck is happening? What? Oh my fucking, give me a break. Really?
That was annoying. Let's drop Xbox. He just decided to turn down, he just turned the
control off. That was great. That was really fun. Imagine if I was like at Gwyn in Dark Souls
when that happens. Get out! Get it! I'm gonna go, it's the same person that, where the fuck do
you want me to take you? Every way is the wrong way. Well, this is the right way. Get out!
I'm going, not bad. All right, I gotta just focus on the next couple and just actually
deliver people. Any time. I'm not doing, I'm not delivering nearly as many people
as I was before. That's like half. I don't get it. Let's see if I can get this delivered.
I don't know, unless it's somebody right here. A class D license!
This isn't the right soundtrack. All right, last try. Last try to get above C.
Last attempt. It's clean. Only drip when I need to. I mean, that, not right there. It's okay.
Get out of my car! Get out of my fucking car! Lots of fucking time now. Hit the jump, come on.
Christ. Where the fuck am I going? What the hell? This is far away.
You use car shop. What the fuck? What the hell? No! The fucking arrow just like freaked out.
Oh god damn it. What? I'm not going to make this jump. What the hell was that?
I still, it's okay. Just get, I can build time. Somebody right there. Get out. Whatever,
doesn't matter. Trying to pull off something there, but I couldn't. All right, just drive. Get
there. I fucking lowered that arrow. Just point over here. I gotta get it. This game is so hard.
It's so addicting, but it's so difficult. I can't imagine what a perfect gameplay of
this looks like. Holy shit, it's probably amazing. All right, one more time. Last try
to do this. I'm gonna go with you first. You've ruined it. Retry. Last try. Last retry.
One more retry after this if I fuck it up. One more retry after that. One more retry after this.
One final retry after the last retry. You understand? Go. All right, no fun, no funny
business. Just try to get above a C. I can do it. That's even a little bit funny business
there. It's good. It's okay. Fuck! Don't freak out. Easy. Okay, that's one retry.
That's a, that was a good start. Don't blow it. Good start. Very good.
Exceptional quality. My controller just ripped. I just got possessed. I didn't do that.
I'm gonna use car shop. I know what that is. It's literally right here.
Easiest one I've done all day. Get it. Big Hills Park. All right, get some money. Stupid
fucking Winnipeg. I'll get out of my way. No drifting. Just good driving. That still
qualifies as good driving. Still qualifies as good driving. Get in the car, dummy. Nice.
Just thread the needle. Just go, just go, go, go. Keep going down this way. You can
wrap around. No, he's unraveling. He's unraveling. Oh no. What the fuck is this
traffic? It's over. It's over. I don't want to see the fucking end. I don't care.
God damn. This is so hard. How did I get like 2,800 alls that last time?
No, it's all right. Get out. That was bullshit. Here we go. Ready? One, two, three.
I'm gonna be quiet. Oh my god. I, god. Why? Why? This is how I got all you quarters
for the arcade. You know they stole all your quarters. This is like 75 cents
for one play. Free coins. Really? I take that fucking cash money thing. I need another person.
I'm not gonna make it. No way. No. I'm forever stuck at like $2,000. Forever. What just
happened to the assets? They all just... What's going on? I got it still. Get out of my fucking
car. Where is this? Beach? Fuck off. What is happening? I'm not gonna even get it.
Get out of my fucking car now. Who's right here? Anybody? Forever stuck at like $2,500.
Come on. I have to get it. I have to get it. I can't move on yet. I have to get B.
Six customers though. It's getting better. I got it. I have to do this.
Let's see. Gotta get that right off the bat.
Okay this is the equivalent of me at the arcade. I'm ripping the cord out of the
back where it's plugged into the wall at Dave and Buster's and I'm plugging it back in.
I'm gonna get thrown out. Get it. Come on. This is the one. I almost just ripped the cord
out of the wall. It was close. Got it. This is the one. Get up. Pizza parlor. Let's go.
Didn't even see that guy. That guy didn't even load. I'm in the worst possible position. No.
Use car shop. I know what that is. I gotta get green here. I thought it was a barrel returning.
Fuck you. You fucking bust. Oh my god. Restart it.
The only way you can get like an A or S rank in this game is if you landed here in a
spaceship like 400 years ago and you've been like just you're just wearing like people's skin
and you're just pretending to be a person you've been like jumping around from body to body
you're like oh that was fun being Julius Caesar for a week that was fun let me try let me
try like crazy taxi fucking world record holder that sounds fun and you got your inhuman
reaction getting stabbed like the level of skill required you definitely are just you land
you have this manager you oh you got like the powers you got possessed you got like the gamer
powers here we go let's wrap around get out somebody right here yep got it good
it's right around corner 87 dollars that's such bullshit that fucking goddamn trash can is gonna
stop me
get in decent i got decent time here get out get in come on boost it get out this is the one
fried chicken shack is i think to the left there it is get in my car across the street
get it ah i just think shot that guy with a shotgun my car shotgun that guy that's every
time around don't take that right good call good call good call same thing straight down
straight down green got it you idiot you idiot stop just you fucking dumb idiot game
it went into reverse god damn that's all right i'll get it again this is good
please accelerate oh you idiot i mean not even smart i'm smart not look at that not even
smart game throwing i'm smart this game's not smart you know what i mean out of my way what the
fuck did you just do arrow why did you do that to me what was the point in you doing that
arrow unbelievable truly unbelievable got a new pair right here i don't know where it is
that's 3400 dollars that's 3400 bucks b yes i can yes this game's so good can i get put
okay i'm gonna try to get possessed by a demon i'm not a demon i said i mean alien i mean what
would what was i saying before oh okay now i can do it again i gotta get possessed by like an alien
gamer spirit 89 seconds come on wait out of my way i'm sorry that guy just moved in every
fucking direction i did he's trying to block me he's stripping what the fuck is this pointing
use car shop i know what that is come on to your seats all right back on track let's go out of my
car it's okay it's all right only like two seconds close get close calls here there's a
lot of pretty money right here get out of my car pizza parlor let's go i come back to the
road right here pizza parlor's right here down the road it's all right even if it's
it's okay even if it's normal out get in where you going camping village i have
no idea what the fuck that is this is the one i'm gonna get a i got it we're okay we're at the
points for the two wheels get out i need somebody come on record store you got it when reactions
is it did i get is it my turn did i get possessed all right if i get another one come on
there's somebody right here get in my car come on clothing store it's right down the street
all right i need this guy i'm gonna turn the car around right here back it up straight ahead get it
get it you got it get it get it you got it i need five thousand dollars i can get it
stupid game sucks no it doesn't come on i need somebody else get in the car
3900 it's gonna be a b i could do it i know i can i can do this i can do it don't pick i had
the red was the closest one it's all right i'll get it i'm gonna get a five thousand i got it
this is the last try i got b i already proved that i'm a bee streamer cleaned up no unnecessary
accidents good get out good perfect oh my god what am i stuck on please game what the
fuck was that unfucking believable there were only reds around too that sucked i literally got
stuck on dirt that was absolute bullshit because that was a great first run too
but i drove over dirt sorry okay green i'm not fucking around anymore right there yellow
fucking arrow what the fuck just happened i just teleported to another dimension this is the
wrong way i blame that first that arrow spinning around the fucking circle for no reason i can still
salvage it possible get him no i can't jump any of this it's still possible any greens
there's a green over there we're gonna go light green park i can do it all right speed it up
still green come on yellow right in front of me stop slapping five and pick up another
customer i don't think i want to jump that i don't think i wanted to jump that fuck
i wanted to jump that i think oh no no i wanted to jump that i for some reason thought
that was gonna take me in the wrong direction stuck in b forever it wants to be yeah i just
all right this is the last try before i uninstall the game forever after that one
i'm so close but so far when you come to a complete stop in this game honest to god it
is so hard to start driving again even when you do this bullshit half the time don't
it's all right get up no i didn't want this guy i'm turning around getting that person back
up there i don't want any of these people here let me just get stuck on an object real quick
it's so annoying it's all right relax what the why do you have the handbrake
on the same button that is reverse this one this one this one's a dud god damn it
i forgot this is the one that makes you this is the worst one to pick up because
the arrow just points around the circle the whole time there's nobody even here
oh great they pick up a red i can't restart i'm gonna get trapped here forever i'm never gonna
leave you understand i have to get out of here i'll never leave i'll sit here until i'm
75 years old i'll just get food delivered to my house every day i'll have like a bathroom bag
i gotta get out of here no oh god just how do i stop this stop this i'm so addicted i can't
stop i have to get out just park the car that's not a bad idea all right last one
this is actually the last one no no i have to sit just go go just the last one i'm exhibiting
self-control it's green right in front of me yeah cafeteria come on frame rate what the hell
are you doing that's pretty cool i don't even know where the fuck this is down here
it's all the way down here no no no no oh i hate it oh come on
four fucking walls painful damn it's not over you stupid idiots
just trying to get points and i can't even get up there there's so many cars on this road
this is simpson's hit and run all over again there's one behind me green oh fuck you fuck
you train where is he did he get on the train he got on the fucking train didn't he no
oh fuck you game over he probably wasted 20 dollars in quarters no i probably wasted like
200 dollars in quarters all right we're gonna i love it i love it and hate it at the same time
it's too fun it's too fun i'm sorry guys it's the game's too fun just give me like another
10 minutes no i can i'm gonna win it all back don't you understand that's gonna get
i'm gonna win it all back what the fuck is this place i'm gonna win it all back
just hold on i'm done i swear to god i'm gonna fucking alt f4 after this i can't i can't stay
here let's go why i swear to god you're like three two one mario kart boost dumb dog shit
maneuver excellent for getting here excellent start get out of my car this guy right here
where is he get it why is my frame rate dying so much on this turn here always all right
it didn't it tried to fuck me over but i got it this is it this is the one what am i turning
left i am going over the jump don't you please don't do it time time time okay get in lady come
on what's going good okay okay okay easy good come on yoshi do it dickhead go green straight ahead
yoshi i swear to fucking god why won't you do it when i ask you to right no it's not i got
baited again it's right here all right i need uh i got right here in a record store let's go
three two one yoshi i hate this game good inhuman don't get out i'm gonna get
don't even look at the number just fucking face fucking face is itchy i need an automatic
face itcher fuck he's gonna get out of the car oh you stupid goddamn game stupid face
unbelievable unfucking believable it's going so well and then like a bunch of itchy particles
had to land on my face how dare they when i'm in the middle of a gamer moment getting close
okay marine plaza that's back this way fucking like it's okay as long as i get a 5 000
is all i care about there's nowhere for me to go yeah see look at that arrow look at that
bullshit arrows doing right now come on give me a break i got this i'm gonna get like
fuck it's 7 000 that's gonna be s slow down not me them get out get out of the car so i can get
the green speaking of green yes thank god the tire was still there how many customers have i had
so far i feel like this is ages i think it's the right head move well this is the part where
the arrow doesn't make any sense all right good yellow sniff club is fuck it's all right
okay just get it together sir what sir uh arrow okay get out over seven thousand dollars is what
i'm gonna get here it's gotta be perfect no mistake zero that's not a mistake
oh my god i hate the other people driving on the other fucking side of the road
it's not gonna get it three two one not good enough
6700 dollars fucking people just driving on the other side of the road like how un-fucking
believable by the way that's an s ranking i see it on my achievement i win that's it get me out
i'm done quick get me out quickly quickly what happened no good the game like the game like
fucked up good i fucked it up i just i didn't mean to i got like really loud right there
but i didn't mean to i just skipped the credits i don't then it crashed the computer
that's okay um crazy taxi's still running it says kind of like hopefully this doesn't turn
off obs still live yeah okay uh i did i actually skipped the credits that sucks
i didn't even mean to i got s and that's an s-ranking and that's an s-ranking oh
quiet jeremy there's like a 13 year old that just did that in an arcade like five minutes
ago all right i think i think something's wrong with the computer now because there's
a little box that's floating in the middle of my screen i'm not sure i'm going to be able to load
a game let me see hold on no i guess i guess we're okay that's crazy taxi it's oh awesome
the game's a blast and now we're going to move on to space channel five somehow this is space
channel five uh part two let me just uh make sure it is correctly now that's 12 it's 1280
by 720 no no no no it's gonna be better than that okay looks good audio we're gonna have to
have the sound i mean this is a music game so the music is gonna be up right let me just
change this part two is very hard that's all right just see how long it takes me to fucking
scream at this one i don't want to be that guy though am i like turning into that guy
that's like the older like 30 plus youtuber streamer that just is like this guy i'm not
good at this i don't like this i don't like this game i'm not sure is that happening in
real time here i'm gonna work on that i don't want to be i don't want to turn into like the
old boomer mutant guy i don't want to do that all right let me this is not capturing for
some reason this is very soft settings let me just stereo vibration off lyrics on screen mode
widescreen why is this so low this is very quiet i can't change the settings in here hold on
really i can't put the settings in hold on options play game there's no that's annoying
well at least let you see what i'm looking at uh i'm gonna have to reload the game and
put the audio up because there doesn't seem to be an option here there's like settings
but that doesn't sound stereo there's no volume slider the volume slider already hold on
i'm gonna do this hopefully this works otherwise i'm not sure what the fix it for that is so this
is a hard game isn't this like parapa the rapa audio sound effects that's not that low
that's normal see if that does anything presented by sega uh okay come on now it's very loud
now it's extraordinarily loud
all right well uh i'm gonna hold on i'm almost at the sweet spot another like 10%
down that's probably good that's probably the sweet spot yeah if you're just joining us and
you don't know uh i want to make sure i reiterate it because we had a little
10 20 minutes in the beginning of the stream shirts are now available there is a new shirt
and why don't we just put it on the screen because people probably like wait what the heck's
happening here there is a new shirt and it is this it is the night sky is the name of the shirt
it's currently available it's beautiful it is currently available on teespring
glue man is also back there's a command that's shirts they're 20 each i kind of told myself a
long time ago that i didn't want to ever have like merchandise especially t-shirts be more than
like 20 to 22 23 dollars so they're 20 bucks each teespring premium tee they're really
comfortable they're really nice at least they were i don't know hopefully they come out all
right but that is the shirt the new one let's do space channel five greedy street cheap streamer
uh that's no you're kidding 20 dollars for one of those teespring premium shirts
is the as come on i'm trying to keep them as reasonable as pot as humanly possible
all right that's i think that's the sweet spot let's go play game story mode dance up a solo
storm play as the channel five reporter ooh la la stop the fiendish schemes of the rhythm
rose changing room let's see i don't have okay story let's just do the story let's just see
how we do it uh back in action ooh la la space sympathy a cruise ship soaring above
neo pluto was attacked by a dance troop oh no this is bad this is like you have to press like
a b x y a i don't have that memorized remember we the red dead i need to plug in a play at
playstation 4 controller why why the fuck can't you see you knew this coming all right cool
stream thanks hey welcome to the stream all right i'm gonna stop doing that it's probably
annoying i was trying to match it and i hear the evil dance troop we have to beat them in
advance i'm gonna be so bad at this with the xbox control what does it do makes them dance
what are you doing to all these sims
8 30 am
so this is wait this is this is the sub this is not the dub is this gonna be in japanese
i think this might be in japanese report number one view rating it's just supposed to be invisible
yeah see this must be invisible
bad guys unknown dance troop where are the assets
if hearts run out rescue fails how am i supposed to do this without steam
what was it what the fuck okay can you not do that please is this supposed to look like this
i thought this was just hyper stylized it's not supposed to look like this
oh i thought this is like a cool stylistic okay well that's unfortunate let me just redo it
let me go to the configuration to make sure i didn't activate something weird you know this
it's just the graphics adapter no there's nothing abnormal here you can't you don't
understand japanese you can't see the assets this looks normal why would that's weird why
would some of the assets just not work uh should i like verify the game cache okay i'm
gonna verify integrity of game files because you're missing part one of the game the menu
is supposed to look like that all files successfully validated i think i'm just
it's just not rendering somehow turning off vsync works i just turned it off maybe i'll
check i'll choose like a different adapter maybe i'll choose like nvidia gtx number one or two
let's just try one because i don't know why there's three adapters here when i have one
let me try like 12 1920 by 1080 at 60 hertz maybe that are trying to do anything else
let's just try 60 hertz all right v sync is off everything's off see if it does it
on this adapter is this this yeah this is the steam version of this game hey one of the shirts
gonna be available they are available right now um i okay so i figured out this is putting it on
a different monitor but that's not gonna help that's just what that means zero one and two
okay i don't think this is gonna do anything oh it's still fucked up well uh that was space
channel five part two for some reason that i don't unless there's uh turn down the
resolution i will try doing that i'm gonna turn off uh fxaa the resolution is now at
let's just do i don't know 14 1600 by 900 see what that does the menu is supposed to
look like that oh well why does everybody tell me it wasn't the menu is supposed to
look like that uh a bunch of people told me that was let's try it again i dropped
the resolution turned off v sync i will fix this if it works okay i can just fix it right now who
cares uh hello did it work come on uh don't think of it hell so you're telling me that
the reason why i didn't buy space channel five on the dreamcast is because i know that they
ported it to pc and the port doesn't work well uh we'll maybe try that again later
but for the purposes i'm gonna move on to a different one maybe i'll
we'll come back and try it again
unfortunately that's just kind of how it is turn v-sync is off everything is off all right
let's do uh move on from that one that's too bad i wanted to play that for a while too
so we have uh we have knights what else is in the collection knights is in here sonic
adventure like dx whatever the hell that is sonic adventure dx this one i was told
to play the dreamcast one jet set radio sega bass fishing let's do sega bass fishing
we got all night guys don't worry hopefully that doesn't happen to more than one of these that
would be kind of sad because you know that would be really unfortunate if percentage wise
700 000 games had more working titles than the dreamcast collection on windows
that would be very very sad all right oh we're good with audio let's go i'm trying what do
you i what do you think i'm doing okay here's this see if it works do we have we have assets
oh that's vega that's uh the screen looks a little weird so let's fix that good sega
this is sega bass fishing this is the original best fishing game ever made
game ever made according to some people okay diary let's see sound sound sounds pretty good
background music let's do four three let's see background music test
that's good sound effect test that's good all right fine jesus let's catch some fish what do
you say play game arcade mode original mode arcade mode to play paradise select an area
cape log lodge area enjoy your fishing i don't know how to play select the lure all right
reel and stop move lure move the lure middle deep that's deep sea middle shallow vibration
pencil bait spinner bait let's just do shallow let's do something easy
they're all easy except no we'll do shallow and middle shallow crank select the casting point
can i like turn around
um here's the one here's the one problem with what's going on right now i have no idea how to
play this just assumes i went up to the arcade and put a quarter uh i might have to figure
out do i have to spin i think the line tension has to be somewhere in the green
is it left stick spin around left trigger i don't understand i think we need to go to the
controls menu hook rod control move cast indicator move selection reeling fast lure
selection enter a mode area cancel area selection reeling slow reeling normal uh
okay so really fast this controller is made out of wood so it's a left trigger and right trigger and
how do i actually reel it in though is that what i'm doing
oh he's i have it nice average size good job rank in okay i just looked over
and somebody said you're so bad listen this is a game that's like 20 years old
that i just i have no idea what the controls are i just opened it five minutes ago what i
don't even know how to reel the fish in yet how can how is that possible so that's slow
you wanted a quarter for me okay can i turn the boat how do i okay i'm trying every
direction i can't like move uh i gotta reel it slow keep it like in the yellow i get it
how do i can't turn the boat around okay an average size good job i'm bonus so there's no
i have to do it here this is the only way i can't turn i can't move i can't pull the rod in i
just have to cast somewhere like in front of the dock and it has to be shallow let's get it
oh there's a fish come here that's a huge one come on whoa easy easy easy why let it up let
up let up how do i let up oh he's a big boy come on come on i almost got him get over here
no don't break the line
he's gonna be like 300 pounds
be careful with attention get him get him pull him up yes how much is that one this one's huge
nine pounds pretty good rank in log area cleared go to next area i beat the game area enjoy your
fishing so all right what was with the fire alarm sound all right let's do normal twitch
rod it means twitch tv one reel consistently make move rod to make lore shake
i'm gonna have to do the twitch one this is shallow in the middle select the casting point
how about like here
this is twitch rod you're gonna like twitch
got it whoa slow it down just consistently reel it in don't freak out this is another huge
one i am right get in here whoa what i'm trying to lower it i gotta get you before the time runs
out come on get up here oh he's fighting me so much i can't get it
yeah i put the coin in that was a quarter to see what i got
special uh popper i'm bonus let's change the rod let's go deep reel and stop let's go treat
get it let's get a deep fish let's see here there's a big one right here let's sink to the
bottom come on it's like a catfish come on nobody wants this he does no i'm like it's
reeled up again i can't put it how do you put it down i'm trying to push it down
come on this big one there you go come on come get it get it oh who's too big i'm not gonna
get this in 45 seconds no way get over here no don't break let go let go let go let go
be careful let go let go let go let go
i am lowering the rod it's too big you have to put another quarter in
yeah over here oh don't break it be careful i got i beat it i had to repeat the area
wow record size i think it's 18 pounds 19 pounds record breaking 23 pounds
go to next area inlet area enjoy your fishing i have one second i have zero seconds done
select the lure see here's the thing it's unfair about this arcade game
why you're gonna have the timer go when i'm selecting a broad
so like the casting point and why am i fishing like a nuclear power plant consistently right
come get it get it he wants it come on pick it up somebody get it got it
was a little but careful i got it not that big one second remaining it's okay
okay an average size good job i need to get a huge bonus i'll change the lure
i want to deep reel and stop yeah here's a coin
captain falcon that was literally that was actually captain falcon that like come on
uh we're moving reel and stop we'll do this one come on
no it looks pretty looks pretty big but i don't know if you're big enough for me to want
look at fish hit bonus looks pretty average
not big enough okay an average size
where are the big ones okay let's try over here that it looks like a big silhouette that
that's a huge one down here come on get it you're so huge do it oh this is a big big one
listen over here that slow it down got it pick it up that's definitely at least 20 pounds
this one's huge 10 pounds more than that rank in 16 pounds you got a special lure
inland area cleared i beat them all go to next area what is the next area enjoy your fishing
the secret palace okay this is the end where's the special lure move rod to make a pop sound
are they like the zombie fish floating minnow twitch rod and reel we'll go with the this is
just the top though vibe real consistently constantly yeah like the casting point
yeah look for a ghost bath everybody on the steps come on okay that actually kind of scared
me a little i was like why is there a person down here no fish like silhouettes in the water
and our pondo
let's try over here be around under this bridge where the fire is that's right they're
probably not very many fish in here it's the secret area speaking of big fish there's one
right here big one come on get it a big one close by you can't go and his mouth is not
a ghost fish unfortunately the real is consistently right let up let up let up let up let up let up
i can't let it up a long way to go the rod is as right as i can make it go
you can do it into the boat with you this one is gigantic how big wow record size 19 20
a record breaking size for this leg you've cleared all the areas is this christopher walking
the biggest bass you've caught master that's a pretty good walking please enter your name
and a it's pretty good uh let's see master ranking that was a fun game to waste four
dollars at at uh arcade there's not a lot of other secret areas or anything to do
this i'm not going to skip the credits this game is uh a lot shorter than i thought it was
but it is an arcade game so makes sense dc staff which one of these fishes from the dc
universe but i can't even skip it actually so we have to sit here and watch it presented by
sega 1997 1999 this is 20 years old this has probably been out of the out of the
arcades for like 22 or 23 years thank you for playing thank you you're welcome this game is
older than fortnight game over yeah yes it is all right well play game original mode practice
mode original mode just see new game what is there you can select your fisher somehow
please enter your name this is an amateur tournament i guess it's just a little
different amateur tournament series turn because it's a five state all play for
select the lure select the casting point right in front of the car
oops so there's not much of a difference it's just a tournament
no i don't want the little one in the big one big come here no there's an even bigger one
right here get over here fight it that's fun i got a i got an a um also i missed 50 bucks
from uh it was a five thousand dollar bit donation from juno was so glued and my brain
was only focusing on crazy taxi thank you so much for the 50 bucks uh they say thanks for
the ride germa i appreciate how you ran over 46 people and crashed into 14 cars but i didn't
appreciate when you yelled get out of my car at me the moment we arrived at my stop thank
you again did i get you there on time the answer is yes uh thank you for the 50 dollars
do we just get sonic dx out of the way sonic adventure dx this game is terrible right this
is like an awful terrible dog shit game right am i wrong no wait which which one is bad
isn't there a really bad one this one is the good one oh okay oh six right all right let
hold on let me let me rephrase that let me like go ahead and just make sure i clear the air
here that's the one i was talking about i thought this was sonic adventure oh six
i didn't know i'm sorry i did not i wasn't aware of what i was saying let's play sonic adventure dx
i thought it was oh six let's give it a try this is where all the theme songs came from
didn't this is like the original we have rock music on every sonic game right
and turn the audio down a little let's see how that is
3d sonic has no flow in ages like milk i didn't say it somebody in chat did
are we gonna do a full playthrough i think i don't know i did a full playthrough of crazy taxi
god s ranking that's all you need how long is the game am i gonna and you guys get mad
if i press start and skip the opening cutscene chicago this is where i'm from where's sonic
from that was so loud i'm sorry this is so fucking loud i turned it down i don't care i'm
sorry select a file oh i turned the music down oh stop you can customize various options
sound test no no no no you can listen to how do i turn it down you can customize various options
i'm sorry guys until i can get that fucking figured out i'm gonna piss my pants too
here's if we're gonna do window p break i'll be right back p break there this is loud okay
hello i need to actually go back because i don't think i can yeah i gotta vibration off
yeah i gotta go back and turn it all down again so i'm gonna put the lyrics on and we're
gonna sing it each one of these songs okay background music put it like down here
down here let's see how that works here let's try it again simulated wide screen not cool
that's better select a file i turned it so far down select a file select a file
i was gonna go into my actual select your character no it doesn't matter
absolute bullshit hold on let's see if that helps it does a little a little more
oh look bearable who do you want to play as all right we got amy big e 102 y so i can i can only be
sonic instruction let's get him i'm gonna figure out how to play the game i have no idea what's
how to play as me sonic rotate camera x and b is spin dash a is jump attack maneuver character
yeah i know how to do that hold on i don't want to get loud all right a is jump spin
press a mid jump homing attack directed at the nearest enemy yeah other actions pick up click
down yep throw shake press and hold x e b press and hold x and shake around how to clear the
game it might be tough unless you know everything there's an object other than a capital
mario honesty this is that level the new uh jump city what's it called
oh yeah with subtitle this is happening all right so i shouldn't have punched like
three pedestrians what's up and like drove into a wall now you got like two stars
uh monster it's then your monster
edf earth defense force this is a one-ear bonus you were they had already shot them
oh yeah this could be fun this is the original sonic adventure what did this come after sonic
uh two rings yeah you don't collect all the rings right it's not like coins i haven't
played sonic in a long time the last game i played in sonic was sonic unleashed and i
cried where are you going because i spent a bunch of money on it and i played it for like
four hours and i cried because i didn't have any money with you know nothing fool it's chaos
the god of destruction
i want to sip chaos drink him what would happen huh didn't they try to bring sonic into a new
generation to get everyone into like more involved and care more about sonic they increased his
leg length by like eight percent he has longer legs now tails now what am i gonna do with you
and there's that movie coming out too oh hi so it's the bumpers is the camera which is a
little odd first ever open world ever for the tv's from now on the casino is only open at
night there's a casino in this game how did i not know that don't talk about that travesty
well what did i do
that's correct i know it is i fucking knew it how did i know that what just happened i'm not
kidding i think this may have been on like a playlist i had on a playlist i remember listening
to this song i think it was awesome i don't know why no this is the good one i remember
this one being fairly decent you know if it was good enough for me to put it on a playlist
what the fuck just happened never mind did they fall through the earth
the whale one absolute i don't know i don't matter i missed the thing
it's the only song that was on my playlist if you're curious i didn't put any of the other
nothing else on here characters more annoying sonic or naruto
uh was supposed to kill that guy i've never seen naruto so i have no idea
the only thing i know about naruto is just like bark simpson naruto was voiced by
like a 75 year old man jump as soon as you land on the panel or else you'll fall
what oh sorry dude i'm like seriously like nostalgia is so cool
play as big as soon as possible i need to play as turned down the volume
yeah not bad see sonic long time no see huh i'm just glad you're okay
what happened anyway you're too good of a pilot to just crash like that
that was a test run using a new prototype propulsion system it's got a few this is just
full metal alchemist actors why not just use my plane the tornado it's me otherwise thanks but
you gotta check out my newest power supply
chaos emerald yep i just happened to find one of the seven emeralds during one of my
test flights alphonse and edward this thing's got unlimited power you know so i figured why
not use it to power my plane supercharge you gotta come over to my workshop sonic
i got something i've got that's not a toy it's in the mystic ruins the fastest way is by train
let's go now you can play with tails shadow only available at night when it's become night
so now can i how do i choose tails can i beat tails now welcome to emerald coast
he wants so bad to go to the casino i just want to play sonic blackjack
that's all i want to do take the train to the mystic ruins the train headed for the
mystic ruins will be departing soon okay the train that goes into the casino what an awful
camera i mean i can't really think of a worse camera than this game tails workshop should be
around here somewhere
if it isn't sonic he's not wearing clothes i just realized that it's a giant talking egg
i thought sonic got shorts on the pants the greatest scientific genius in the world
whatever you say egg man actually running around naked 150 miles per hour
now i'm gonna put them to work you're always up to no good now what do you want
i want all of the chaos emeralds better not interfere or else or else what you big loser
or else i'll take them from you by force the hard way three times what about eggman
that's really weird he always uses this same ship every game he makes another one
oh eggman can you just make something else that's not the little circle spaceship thing
that i hit three times it worked i think i have to jump on the i'm assuming homing dash
on the missiles would be what i would do whole systems full power run real fast
yeah land on top whole systems full power
he's not gonna get away with this
this is kind of making me sick i'm sorry it is whole systems full power no you hit me three
times no i actually hit the sector motor takes to kill me hey i'll play with you some other
who's the engineer making these like you gotta have a conversation with whoever is on your dev
team and can we have a device that's not going to take three bumps and explode it has to be
away i don't know what you're using for materials but it has to be something well that
wasn't so hard nice job tail you brought that out there chaos why are you still holding
that you can't you're delivering that to oh no isn't that the same monster i saw the other day
oh yes it's just as the stone tablets predicted
this is the original infinity increases every time i feed him a chaos emerald that's really
true with all seven emeralds in him he'll be invincible and work for me
together dragon ball the original infinity stones though it's ruined i'll build robotnik
yeah no sonica hedgehog is just a wreck where i will rule it all dragon ball isn't that what
bonus let's find another emerald shall we isn't that what they did they made their own version
of dragon ball because they love dragon ball so much that's what he said right sonic you
can't let him get away with this can we no way tails so it's up to us to get the emeralds
before eggman does huh that's why he goes super saiyan he turns into like yellow hair
supersonic well you think they just made that up i mean yeah that is a perfect copy
a nice neva nice nevada theory i almost fucked it up i almost said it wrong can i go
here tails workshop nothing fun can be done in there i wasn't supposed to go that way okay
all right let's go to uh the next area let's have the little workshop should be around here
somewhere i'm gonna go back to tails workshop why we get the gem i don't have like did i not
save the game
okay looks like a key all right well tails where do i put your new what do you put your
like eighth grade science bear trophy over there put it off the cliff that's just water
throw it no no no i'm not gonna throw it off the edge i can't just jump in fall down in
there go in the cave the cave was over here right cave near train that's what i get for not
paying attention to the country just talking about nonsense cave in front of the now go in
let's get a chaos animal what the hell was that why did it stop me it just did it just
stopped me i just i was like a cinder block what the hell was that i didn't even bounce
up like this what happened there i need to get some i need i have no lives left
just walk through this right is it 100 rings there we go am i dead head straight up you
should be able to get out of the tornado time limit or something this looks like it has a
time on panel number one it will take you to panels two and three jump as soon as you
land on a panel or else you'll fall two more good wild all right where do i go from here
it's great isn't a high five that's not correct i almost have a high five no don't jump over what
is this got it let's see official speedrun for this game look at the song the hedgehog
40 rings nice
oh my god this level's full
hold it left stick up simulator yeah but it doesn't mean not fun because right now i'm
pretending that i'm him running really really fun marbles game the marbles marbles with friends
right yes wait there's a streamer that actually likes the song and most people hate this game
yeah not bad the do the train headed for station square will be departing soon
yeah i mean i think came out like 20 years ago it's hard to hate something that came out
this long ago even though maybe it's a little i don't know i can't i don't really have an
opinion i need to go to station square you may find something oh casino time i mean don't
worry right now i'm saying yeah this is kind of cool it's fun it's old but it's interesting
and like don't worry give it like another 30 minutes i'm gonna tell you how this is the worst
game i've ever played there's a place somewhere in the city where you can go down into the sewer
just give it like 30 you'll hear me all right this twinkle park no casino is over here
is it right scene is only open at night how do i get in
is it not technically nighttime three rings you need to play more fishing levels oh it opens the
door okay uh all right sewer if i was a sewer where would i be probably not this way somewhere
on the street out here like a sewer to me super suit what is it now you've got light speed
light speed press and hold the action button to store up power once you have enough power
release the button and you can do the light speed dash oh cool the light speed dash lets
you race toward rings at light speed as long as there's a trail of rings you can go just
about anyway you know that's all the thing i was just trying to do use the light dash
to run along the paths of rings hold the action button and let go when you have enough
power okay do i have enough power you have to actually hold it for a while
and now i can go back and go in that room egg what do i mean egg what i can pick i can pick
that up who the hell was that how did i get in that where was that room where was that
pick this up
oh shit i can steal this i can't steal it i can't place that one
pick up a guy hey don't hey don't use the back door put egg back get egg put egg back
get egg go to back to the casino oh casino it's my time who gives a shit about anything else
the train headed for the mystic ruins will be departing soon cool all right there's the
slot machine there's the poker table they have one casino ten casino casino casino
casinopolis is open so the only way in is the no it's a level right the music is way
too loud i wish there's no solution okay there's no casino open so i'm gonna go
into that room and dash across let me go back doesn't press the button press the button
i thought that they said i can't go in the front door all right this camera is seriously
starting to piss me off i can't even turn the fucking thing around all right let's go
i like this level slot pinball for us ahead these l1 and r1 remove the flipper and match
three pictures in a row and shoot the ball towards the arrow if it's dumped in the garage
you don't have a hundred rings shit i don't have any money pause it your rings i can't activate
any of these i guess okay all right well hold on if it's that well i can't blame sega for
having a 5000 decibel game that they didn't fix and it doesn't matter i just turned down
my audio on windows like my desktop windows audio to 15 listen to this listen to this shit
let's open up sonic all right i have to drop it in three different places now
because now i can't hear anything how's that turn the sound down in the game options well
the funny thing about that is i have to exit the game and restart the game to do that i did
three times pretty much already so i really don't want to exit the game to turn the sound
down all right so what do i go from here cards is card pinball so i can't do any of this
you missed three times however you have less than 100 rings you get dumped in the garage
so i don't know i'm just gonna get dumped in the garage this is like a stack of money
somewhere shower room well i'm robbing the casino apparently i'm just punching machines
that's not okay wash yourself up anymore there's not you know it's not the video game that's going
to make me turn this game off it's a camera i don't mind the game i just would love to see
it at the angle that i want to see that okay so what are you telling me i can just do this
you just go in i thought if you have less than 100 rings you just get dumped in the
garage don't have to use money to make money i'll just get free money what kind of
casino is this is he gonna play for free where are the stakes i can't play like this
give me that other uh target i want that other target if you have to you if you don't make
enough three of a kind now i gotta go through the arrow right i have this game too by the way
i sent it to the garage who's this in the lower right eliot who the fuck is that i'm gonna
hit that other target i have two eliot's all right that's uh got somebody else's card
get the target please all right 96 what did i just go uh
what i get do i have to control this how does it get the bonus what did that do for me i feel
like sonic pinball you're a little too the ball's a little too slow this is very easy
all right the bonus again i kind of don't want to see it though again resident sleeper again
oh i no don't do it again anything else give me a different bonus please stop this
all right now it's stuff what does it am i missing something here okay i ended up back here
but now i just gotta i gotta get that target and we can get out of here control with the
joystick no that's me tilting oh then now i lost because i'm tilting the game knows when you're
cheating all right well now i'm not gonna get dumped in the garage i got my coins
i so badly want that last target but whatever can't have everything you want
okay good nice work so now should i deposit or just leave i got 142 coins all right where's
the exit information how do i leave store your ring in the vault i can deposit as many rings
as you can it may even help show you the way i was just gonna hand them to you i was there's
a chaos emerald right there we just have to do one more stupid game it's a slot pinball all
right this one's cool see there's an actual machine here and it's gonna spin look at that
that's kind of interesting how do i stop it yeah i actually have to stop the rails myself
we just need to get to 400 i thought i was gonna lose that one nope nope not that one either
final eggman oh he takes your money he's got bowser didn't he didn't think you're gonna watch
a guy play pinball bang bang bang two three four five six seven damn it i had a chance
ring ring ring ring got it tails what does that get me amy amy amy no thing for you huh
ring 3k let's get 3000 rings what is that has to be something i just lost that one but it's
fine don't fall down it though there's a lot back there that's good went all the way back
around to the spring get in that spot it didn't go all the way in all right well i did
i just need how many more a couple hundred i have 140 something right so that's two
i'm just gonna get it done right so we don't have to do this again i mean i act like i'm
gonna play through this whole game i'm not what just happened i shucked the machine i
shouldn't have done that why would i do that i'm not gonna beat this whole game tonight
we only can do that with crazy taxi that's the only one i'm allowed to give more than
like two hours to god that game is fucking fun crazy taxi was it was sick what a delight
that game was shining what that's a jackpot that's not now what is with the timer
isn't there crazy taxi too i have to get s ranking in that one too got it you got
to go into the hole with the timer on it kind of easier said than done it's tiny
one is better this isn't actually three of them a lot of tails good got it i see you hit it in
that certain area it the game freezes nothing i got enough but what can i get more what happens
if i get more do you actually get anything if i deposit 500 coins you might get an eggman
oh oh thank god yes i got the sonic head look at how many coins this is wow oh look at this come
on come on i can just say 86 get the 86 83 oh that's so many coins no it's just out of reach
come on damn it all right we get down here i'm gonna max the goddamn game out guys you know
like i gotta say that i did that like holy shit that was lucky okay just don't hit it
up there ever again damn it no get the 42 this really is like the gambling fallacy
just get out just leave the casino it's over you already did it you have so much money
i want to make a thousand dollars tonight no get just leave you're done you did it
let me see it's got another big hit no go home there's so many coins that i didn't get
there look there's no way i'll get an eggman i haven't lost one ball look at how many extra
lives i'm getting because you don't think this is worth it i'm untouchable right now
eight extra lives i'm gonna have like 15 extra lives for when i inevitably turn the it's okay
last ball you could have gotten like 500 rings in the sewer area in two seconds
yeah but there's no shiny pinball slot machine no balls yeah i don't have any i don't have any
balls left shit i need one of those i'm gonna get to 9.99 what happens when you get to the
nine if you get one more does it go to zero yes all right there's 40 there's 42 up there
wait i get it we're fine game doesn't even work the game doesn't even work and i get to
win look at that you didn't think we were getting 9.99 boys and girls we're getting there
okay we're good lightning can't strike twice there i don't think the house always wins yeah
it's not enough 700 coins oh quick deposit in the vault before they know what happened
i'm not just depositing it into their vault all right that's it 851 what's my give my prize
yes not bad got the chaos everyone and i got a new egg well that was fun i blew every cent i
have you really should have left when we had a chance shut up tail you don't know me why would
you hit on a 19 fuck up i thought there was a two in there did you steal it from me what
happened to that emerald we just had house always wins i guess eggman's got one of them
but the other one's safe that guy must be desperate that means his two to r1 and that's
not good come on sonic we need to get busy what the hell is that you see that thing that just
flew by headed for the mystic ruins will be departing soon all right i'm gonna go to the
sewer sewer was down out of the casino it's not bad this game's not bad go get the key
was it in the casino area was there an alley was that actually over here
for the mystic ruins will be departing soon got it okay so pick this up the ice stone looks
like a key maybe i can use it in the mystic ruins so i have to get back on the train let's get
all right where are you i'm gonna get on the train can i like what the hell is that train
the hell the train is going to elevator this elevator i went through the train station
um where's my key okay what are chow raising chow feeding chow how to get fruits small animals
caring for chow breeding chow right how do i get them to hatch is it like oh a little hatching
pod warpole you can go easily to gardens you have previously been to you may bring chow and
eggs with you too throw the eggs throw oh that's an animal come here how do i feed it
jump and throw against the wall i don't know if that's a good idea is that gonna it's not
gonna break is it what you can actually do that that's not what you're supposed to do right
okay well power swim fly run okay that's kind of cool you can name uh oh it's sending it back
you just were born go go get a job another one wait is this the same one how many are there
no this okay well that's an interesting thing chow stadium so you can kind of fight them and
breed them that's interesting what do the gardens do do i have to take one with me
how it works what happened to you all right i'm out there are other gardens all right so uh the
train station right i i go back where's that train i don't even know i ran like by like
three times i think get in what the hell okay so what is this
this is the crystal ring what do i get to do this reduces the time needed to store power
for the light speed dash nice so let's see how let's see what the timer is i can move
around with this on what does that activate is that just the door there's no other cool thing
to do there is he gonna play through the whole game uh no i don't think so we have a couple
other things to get through that i'd want to play this game's fun though it's not it's not a bad
game all right uh i have to go back to the casino alley to get the key even though because
i went into the dumb garden play the whole thing do you guys really want that don't play
the stupid idiot blue rat game i'm not gonna play the whole thing don't worry i just need
to know where the elevator is no not the elevator the train do i have to go out here
up where is the train it's up the stairs no not that way not that way but not that towards the
casino in the chow garden there is the train headed for the mystic ruins will be departing
soon so i have to bring this to the ice center wherever the hell that is in there
i'm assuming it's the giant wall that just broke open uh is it not okay didn't you see a
stone with an ice pattern on it i don't think i did the one guy who said it's not the right way
well i this is the thing i saw when i looked over that's what i saw i saw more than one guy
i saw like wrong way idiot like is he this bad and i'm like that has to be right because
he said that ice when does sonic use a ladder ice cap get the chaos emerald you got it
what is it
tutorial if you're frozen jump a couple of times and you should be able to crack through
okay what's that i don't know so i gotta continuously jump to the icicle and jump
you should be able to jump backwards but don't hold on too long you'll slip right off
uh that's very awkward that's awkward shoot the gun uh did i is that correct
i guess no i have the sonic run super thing don't i what the hell am i doing
i have the thing where i can just run across it these are not even on the same plane
fuck ah whatever let me see what this is an easy way to collect all the coins
easy easy easy wait wait wait wait to look down be careful not to fall off
i think i'm gonna fall off one
whoa straight through go go go go go go go go snowboard level oh cool all right
is there anything else can i just jump or just get away from it i guess this is totally
radical man now the real game starts this is by far the coolest thing in the game so far
jesus it's too fast i'm missing every ring it's okay oops am i closing in enemies
easy i think there's a secret right there i kind of just went right by
it's all right hurry up hurry up tricks i don't have any tricks i can do
did i just get the emerald not bad how many i don't have very many other emeralds to get
how many realistically do i have three two am i not allowed to leave the train headed for
station square will be departing soon all right so uh i'm gonna go to the sewer no big the
cat in the last 15 minutes i'm sorry i don't know what to do the sonic hat i mean his
tails have anything for me to do in here or no just leave play as big the cat go to the lake
uh let me go to the lake sorry i'm not in here what's up knuckles what's his voice like
in this game something bugging you like rafael from ninja turtles right no time for a game
sonic kind of give me the emeralds you have right now just see you take them fight with
knuckles i could kick his ass watch this ready oh no oh no give it your best oh no i would
oh no the chaos emeralds
taking candy from a baby that's a chaos emerald fight fool you made it all too easy
you practically gave them to me hold it right i think we're gonna move on tonight
knuckles don't tell me eggman tricked you again me what about you it's not a bad game we just
we've seen it chaos control right oh no that's shadow these are for you my friend
he transformed again man no one ever cuts us any slack be more careful with some of the most
powerful artifacts in the universe don't put them in your back pocket store them in a safe
inside of a safe with a 25 keypad hash no i can't touch the water i can't touch the oh no
i can just keep doing that i'm gonna assume i'm not supposed to be able to see through this
water here am i correct in that assessment this should be a lot harder i'm not supposed to be
able to see him in the water you are oh i thought it was supposed to be you can see like
the surface level not he's a whole head yeah this is the standing in the water is weird
one more hit all right come together again come on come on i got other games to play
damn it come on i'm trying to missing something here you put your head up put your head up
hello there you go hey i'll play with you some other time this is the game you're playing
jeremy what wait wait what the general consensus everyone's everyone hates this
we just got a new full motion video cut scene it's not bad
when is jet grind radio very soon
all right that's probably a good stopping point
we can't let him get away it's my workshop and we'll take the tornado
yeah you guys go i have some unfinished business to take this is terrible no problem
objectively this is awful but like the video game is not it's not terrible it's not that bad
it's pretty it's pretty decent the game is i think fun sonic's cool so there's nothing
wrong with sonic it's just those cutscenes are just there's not there's nothing to them
all right let's go see big the cat hey look for all the sonic is still around sonic is still
kicking he's still he's doing just fine go to the mystic ruins you might find something
twinkle park uh still only oh id card only okay what was this special for couples right now
okay i remember when this came out and i played that first level i was blown away
because this is like the first time they ever really did anything really like this
you got to give them the credit where it's due it is here's the sewer can i do anything else in
here hmm i guess i just don't know what i'm doing here why do i keep going back to the
sewer i don't know see i because i kind of just ran away isn't there more shit in here to
do didn't somebody say there's like stuff in here oh go back to tail's house i can't take
this yet literally not even one guy said that yeah they did they did they said i could get like
500 rings we were just trying to get you to stop gambling is that really what it was
oh i just got a fucking free egg what do i do with this i don't weigh that enough to be
be kidding me i can't break it all right i'm i'm gonna move on that was sonic the hedgehog
sonic adventure it was a fun game and pretty cool it's it's good i didn't save the game
what it just i didn't save it yeah i did didn't i it's okay all right coming up next we have
knights knights into dreams we want floygan brothers i'm sorry i can't deliver knights is
saturn not dreamcast fake sega gamer that's not true this was poured into dreamcast
there was one on dreamcast is nights gonna open knights was on dream yes it was no you said knights
was on breakfast did i finish resident evil 2 yeah i did well i did uh leon's campaign
no we're not going back to the flagon brothers all right nice 20 by 1080 okay gamepad move start
game acrobat motion drill dash touch dash all right this is made by the same company that
made sonic by the way it's gonna be very loud i'm just warning everybody no it's not i turned
it all down we're good pegi 16 no floygan i'm sorry it's not gonna happen
brand new dreams see sega saturn dreams play the remastered version which was released on
dreamcast they remade it these games are for children why do you play little children's games
this game is enough for children this is the games that you played when you were
when this is what was available this is this is the game that was available to play like
20 years ago doesn't matter how old you were and just wait this is going to be one of the dlc
characters what did i just do all right let's go how do you play what are you supposed to
do in this game i can't play this i have to stop playing this is gonna make me fucking sick
oh this is fun though i need to do to go through different planes nice okay
guys this is a classic you can't be part of the collection so we have to play it
beware oh i did it flying hell's happening i'm actually i think i have an idea
some point an idea i want to see um let's go back let me see the sega saturn
because this is the classic that doesn't i thought you go forward
worse graphics yeah you have to like pick them they steal all your stuff you have to get them
back this looks cooler i prefer it like this actually collect the orbs waterfalls kind of
throws you away i see so you have enough orbs to destroy them you're gonna do it again
time i see this is fun this is cool it's an interesting concept d what is the concept uh
you're in the dream this is what do i have the orbs
not quite music's too loud please turn it up why would you want me to turn it up if it's
too loud not yet let me let me just beat this first level the more that i do is the more
that i think this is actually kind of fun bad guy there is a d more i think i just gotta check
not that many i just did here's the yellow one well that's cool what happened to my view this is
i feel like i'm glitching a game did i do it well this is tricks i'm getting points for tricks
so
somebody just wrote i'm so fucking angry why it's just that we're just flying around i'm so angry
uh finally i get to get the actually this is way worse than the other ones
i feel like i'm drowning right now and i'm desperately trying to get air
holy shit 100 dollars is enough okay nice no no no no not the not is that enough money
i'm saying is that enough of uh nights did i do it uh juno thank you for the hundred
dollars juno 100 i'm so fucking angry all right i did it i win uh you missed my bits earlier but
honestly i want the nice shiny pink badge thank you so much juno sorry i missed your bits
from earlier i should think i think i what is going on i'm gonna boss jesus minus five
i think i should be doing wrapping around hitting her in the stomach
yep right in the stomach i gotta get it right in the jewel three times one that
shit i still i still got it but i got minus five down the hall break her out of this place
hold on what's over here i think i have to break up the door yep that's what has to be done
um 17 seconds to do this wall come here this is the piano this is the piano thing come on break it
what is that snail with a giant mouth that is the weirdest looking monster
oh that's the whole night
it wasn't bad it's cool if you play it you think it's fun but i'm glad you do
i was gonna say dlc for smash brothers but that would have been like kind of interesting to say
like like 30 minutes ago okay it crashed but that's fine i know you've been waiting a long time
so many guys been waiting here for a very long time we're gonna play
jet set radio really it's too bad that space channel five did not work okay jet set radio
it's been a very long time since i played this okay windowed no yeah i think it's good
to go already seems like it is sega this game kicks ass yeah it does it's pretty great
graffiti is art however graffiti is an act of vandalism and is a crime every what
i just got a please don't do graffiti warning
by the way i know one of the town i we're gonna go to shibuya chill i might as well just do
this shibuya show there it is that's correct lesson one skate forward by pushing forward yeah
you teach me something else i know how to skate forward is there anything else i can learn here
just one okay so that's right trigger try doing a little freestyle skating without
bumping into anything all right success how long do i have to do this i think i know how to do that
but can you tell how do i do anything i just know how to play tutorial doesn't want to
tell me how to do anything else we're just gonna have to learn on our own
here we go somewhere in asia there's a city that cannot be found on any map called tokyo
to but everyone just calls it tokyo the two hottest things in the streets of tokyo to
are the punks wearing magnetically driven inline skates powered by newly developed
metrium batteries and jet set radio a pirate radio station manned by the dj professor k that
plays nothing but non-stop hardcore music those street punks have been named rudies
hardcore public music they roam the streets and cover the city with their personal graffiti
claiming that it is their way of expressing themselves to the world however ever since the
metropolitan government and the financial conglomerate the ruca group combined their
efforts to co-found the 21st century project the streets of tokyo to have never been the
same again police crackdowns on the rudies have become more severe and captain onishima
is more anxious than ever to put them behind bars the streets of tokyo to are ready to
explode and that's where you come in hold it you can't go tripping through the streets
so you learn some of the basic no i skipped this i know i can't go through the road runner
try this pull down right trigger and then press jump okay
sweet now try this next run if you pull left trigger the camera will automatically face
forward try this line i currently have an h all right now it's time to get serious
you see something floating over your head pull left trigger to start spraying
spray spray everything right all the opportunities to spray hey while you're grinding
give it a whirl
gum has joined you good not bad i guess i can join you now this is better than the floygan
brothers i think you can keep up with me let's check your qualifications
if you see an arrow use it left to follow it and paint some fat lines jump and spray that
you gotta flick your hand around if you think you're all that try this
grab onto the back of a car you can slide uphill with ease press order left
oh you walk into traffic you can get hurt
your left trigger i have to do all these animations in real life i'm not gonna do that
go back all the way down and spray something down here and that
break that all right well i don't know what the button was to grab a car
walk over to the wall i'm very clearly pushing this car
the music
okay i did i almost missed it but i got it
one last run jump over the rest day grinding down the whole thing up on top of the
all right
i guess you're cool
cool
there's enough bullets can't touch you when you're dashing got it that's
the worst possible advice you can give to anyone like really what
hey out there this is tokyo's very own number one pirate power station
jet set radio over the hood through the streets and right into your brain
we're transmitting our signals straight to you y'all got your antennas on or what
yeah we're riding high in a smooth stream of supersonic sound and i'm your captain and dj
professor k jet set radio
three games are fighting for the Tokyo streets in the west for binton show the city of the
night we got those high tech mania those man machines the noise tags and in the east
from kodani chow the city of the sunset it's that crazy monster mask wearing gang poison
jam and from shibuya chow here we go this is us the city of daylight where's our dance
troublemaker
they were talking about spreading out there or maybe it was the noise
thing trying to send a sister grass through the whole city listen up all you innocent fools out
there officer onishima has got some special order satsu bracelets all ready for you
because a whole road of trouble is heading your way
brought you tea chapter one let's go for real here it comes
yeah you got a internet or having a radio system graffiti it's like they're creating
create your own graffiti create new graffiti let's get a good one let's get i need a different
color
let's go with a swivel and then
let's tag it now no no back back back back can't do chameleon camel camel is fine
how about that bigger all right let's play the fucking game like i can't just
i'm just gonna take too long
yes i'd like to go back
i still have to small ones small they're gonna do like a green square
there
that's hard to control
extra large um god i don't know let's just i'm gonna say we need a bigger let's go red
blood red
good enough
it's a fucking garfield
okay we're gonna go to wherever we can go
graffiti power technique let's go through
the dog and the red arrows and start tagging it my pleasure
i don't have any paint retry no there's no there's no net
all right well i am gonna retry i can't
yeah you have to outrun the police now i remember where this way
the red arrow here yeah there's a couple up there it's like a route mistake right here
how is this wrong
um hello what that was odd
do i need i think that's just that one
the side the sheriff shoots at you
give me that why is the cop why the cop police not going after you
not as a guy if i'm picking up top of the roof come on no no no no
i am doing it in one motion i'm doing it in one motion absolutely
do you have to press triangle i don't think you do
maybe i'm just wrong one up there i guess still
steady don't shoot me don't shoot me that's mine that's mine that's mine
let's see that i'm missing one right here oh shit you're a bad shot but it's all right i
oh that hurts it's like base of our own corner there's one more that i have to get
right here give it away no get off out out out out
out isn't there a way to make them stop i think there is can i say spray
uh whatever it is i have no idea how to do it
got it okay run jesus let's get scratching i'm hijacking the airways and terrorizing you with
tunes because we're gonna throw these dirty streets in the one big dance party just said radio
those cats who ransacked shibuya chou turned out to be the love shockers love broke their hearts
and now they're looking to do some breaking of their own watch out for these psychos
when you see their heart-shaped graffiti around you know someone somewhere is crying
with the uki uki waku waku feeling can the gg save shibuya chou from the trap of love
or is it too late all right let's do it again so here we go love trap hydrate
uh i'll take a break here in a minute go grab a water i gotta get a good line it's all about
the lines in this game
shit you gotta go off and around all right i get it let's go this way
boy this is awkward oh man i'm trying to do this jump and get it
much harder than it looks you can't just go up it's like you want to be off
where's the last one
oh how did i not get that still too far away how are you supposed to you can't it won't you do it
still didn't get it
okay right all right that was painful get me out of here
okay where to up this way that's not the way i want to go
well police are here
what the
really like how why are you not grinding this row wow sure
this game is like fucking freaking me out with this music
all right we're gonna go this way
god did i just actually get run over on the sidewalk who the hell did that
yep you're coming after me
what is going on i'm doing it right now hello
i'm so confused right now
oh where is this taking me i'm gonna climb it like a fucking frog whatever
why did you just grab onto the car why did i really just fall down off a lip
is this me with skates on i don't understand
try this again
no
how is that incorrect i don't understand why that one's incorrect almost every time
and now it's not now it is correct and now i can't even start it
that motion hasn't changed the entire time i've been playing the game
what the fuck
oh shit i gotta make it i gotta go faster across this line here i recently played it
it is very precise i will say doesn't know what i want to do grind this thing
all right there's two did i not pick up paint i thought i had like a bunch of them
so i don't have any paint well that's unfortunate holy shit
i like you can wall ride how do you do that
well nobody told me how to wall ride that wasn't a tutorial i didn't play
horse with one of the tutorial characters and have been telling me how to wall ride
who can't though oh my god
oh my god it's so precise remember this game being this hard
all right can you get off of the rail that is left so i just i just exited the level
not even like a confirmation you just go back to the main menu
it's it i know it says exit but you don't get to like turn me around and put me back
no it is that's how you exit to the main menu
this is headquarters to motorcycle units headquarters to motorcycle units capture
the suspect at all costs
it's like i'm made out of fucking wood
get off just try is there a reason why you guys have to show up
right when i press left trigger on the wall and trash into me you can't
now they come again they don't even try to arrest you they just drive into you
and then they all drive up the cliff and die you got them why did i just read what's
what the fuck are you talking about what does that even mean all right i'm
i can't even i can't concentrate now it's okay but i need more paint
this man this game is very good but it's very very precise and very hard and there's a lot of
you know if you like characters admission fucking wood and you'll love it but no this game is
actually very cool it paved the way for a defining genre of bending genre creating
experience finish it how much more is this that's gonna be at least a million
like leave now you don't get to quit this one i have one who said i was gonna quit
stop sticking a real bad shot no that's not what i wanted to do
i got it you don't need to get the greens yeah but they're extra points
that's the end of the stream boys no it's not the end of the screen
we're not done we might be done with this game
i want to get off of the rail like you stop blowing me to rails
it's like a hat okay when i want to jump on a rail it's like no you know you didn't do
it precise enough when i want to get off a rail no magnet get back get back here get 13
one here lady it's 15 year old me play this game no i've got it took five that was jet
set radio uh it's a good game it's just um it's just very very difficult very precise
and you can't play it like tony hawke you have to pretend you're made out of wood and that your
shoes have glue on them that's how you play it's a good game it's in it's very interesting
go back to floygan he's too salty i'm not salty i'm not it's just i think that has a
lot of learning curve and i don't want to sit there and play that all day it's i'm not mad
at that game it's just i i'm it's it's a it's i i've told you a thousand times it's a very
good game how do i get space channel five to work how did you survive crazy taxi learning
curve but not jet set radio because fast car go fast and there's money involved all right
let me give me a second i'm gonna take one last break we're gonna come back and i'm gonna
i'm gonna try space channel five i'm gonna google this in a minute so i'll figure it out if we can
even play it if not then and we're not going back to floygan brothers i might open crazy
taxi again maybe because i'm addicted i will be right back see if we can get it to work i don't
know if i'm gonna be able to get this to work there's not very much literature on why this
is not working i went into steam discussions and it's like oh yeah i don't know how to get
it to work i'm missing character models i've restarted the game and it's fine like uh
doesn't really help me let me just try opening it again jerma i am here tuber what do you do
buddy what is it yeah yeah you can't see it right now but i'm just seeing if i can
maybe go to the changing room just did not have to load a game i mean she's clearly on
screen let me see her model is in the game see what happens see look ready she's clearly
her character model is here so if the character model is just there why then can we not do it
i'm gonna try it again got it oh my god finally holy shit hold on no don't crash don't
no we've waited so long for this got it let's do it let's crack a fresh one for this one
ah i'm so excited this is my childhood game this is my childhood game
the game's in japanese that's it's too late i don't there's no setting to turn it out of
japanese up up up got it i gotta pay a close attention why is there no prompts on the
screen yes is that the best you got where do you think i got the walk from guys where do
you think i fucking got that one from take a wild guess it's the neverhood actually the
neverhood not from this game use a beam left is left right is right of course it is
of course b when you hear hey okay i love this game now we're going oh bring on the whole
family let's go i'm the winner i'm the winner i'm the winner bring in more space people
space guy dancing to the mo you pay attention quick english setting okay not yet known as the
rhythm rogues you can't get something better than that come on
i got an elephant no i did it i did hey boing we need more hey thanks we did it
what's next we're in the control room it's gonna be hard i'm gonna turn it up too
like i'm the lead dancer it's gonna be hard star okay five what is that hey was it hey
it's dumb i need the other headphone i couldn't hear that
come down get out of here i'm gonna turn the volume up and i'm gonna put it in
what's with the banker no deal what finally
all three of them i'm gonna do d plus
25 spade it said the title 67 percent that's a good d
no secrets all right now i'm gonna put it on english come on no idea wish we knew what he was
saying it was in japanese by default
keep it in japanese now i gotta put it in english
the graphics still hold up pretty well yeah they kind of do
you need english some of the tricks this game can pull are brutal
yeah i'm ready i'm ready to and he's like made out of wood and glue i can't wait to
make like a reference like that and then quit again uh it's not pirate is it in the other
options like the i'm terrified to close the game though hold on let me see let me try opening it
again sorry you just got that loud sound is it in the other menu like the other options
so it is audio voice hey guess what guys it's on voiceover in english is the voiceover
it's not on japanese it's on english what happens if i put it in japanese i'm just
gonna put it on japanese it says it's english let's see this is weird let me just make sure
play game please have a character model yes so it's supposed to be english story mode
two spacebar confirm i mean we have english subtitles now no it is
what language is this any comment mr president english why yes of course good it's in latin
we already saw that now i'm ready
what is that guy made out of tasty cooking rerun will not be broadcast today
all right let's do it i'm ready why is it still low the audio is still low
holy shit i almost just clicked the stop streaming button because i clicked over
here to turn this up give me a break i almost just clicked it it went right over it is that
better perfect great canadian fuck club just came in with 10 community subs thank you so much
thank you this is my brain's gonna melt in half got it an accordia you playing like a grill
what is that it's in a raincoat sega has
i can't talk i can't guys i cannot speak there's gonna be a silent playthrough of this
game there's no way i could speak this i can't talk what i was gonna say is sega has a
shitload of interesting mascots and interesting characters where are they
now keep let that spin around in your brain for like another 30 minutes while i be quiet
i'm ready i gotta get save them before they melt try
i don't remember
i'm too tired for this i think i try to do it the other way
bring it on hey hey hey
i got 36 percent we've reached about a square
it's the hey and the chew and the up and the down and the down and down down left right
chew hey it's an anchorman scenario are we gonna fight each other
down it's not just what hold on a minute wait so it's it's it's different directions not just
down what what direction am i supposed to be going in holy shit what's just the right
direction oh my god
it's insane i can't answer this oh my god this is fucking ridiculous
let's keep going how am i supposed to beat this
i love this game this is fantastic
oh god it's speeding up no not good oh there's more bird they're attacking
they're killing that guy i wonder how insane this game gets me that guitar thing is hard
just because the glow i sometimes it was hard to tell if it was up or down or right
up up and right where like the same thing in my brain and when she's like down down
get it out
i don't know how high you are it's not for me to know i can't fuck up again
here we go
oh this is great
what the hell am i playing uh you came in at a strange time there's a space channel
fight essentially up right chew left chew chew down down da da down to hey hey what wait
what was it up or down what what does it even say
wait what is what is that other what is the vault button what is that huh i'm pressing hey
what the fuck why is it not doing it what the hell i was doing it what
what in the name of god was that i have no i don't know why that happens
i'm using an xbox control yes is that bad
why not dreamcast this is not on dreamcast i have it on pc ready i had it perfect up until
like the guy was just going like hey and it wouldn't work
here we go but i pressed it what the fuck is this thing fucking up on me
i'd be so mad if this xbox control just sucked looks like a turd all right don't fuck it up
here we go dare try to stop us it's gotta be on beat too
left okay what okay hold on a minute i just pressed left twice what happened what ready for a waltz no
oh
oh my god i got a costume i did get a costume
yeah this is space channel five part two this is not the original
no it's a different version the second good job well done do one more love
a blast this is great no the space president i'll exchange the president and the hostages
for 6.6 trillion space dollars meet me at point double x it's like the gdp of almost like
what like 45 different countries like 100 countries come on that's like two universes
here we go the perpetrators have made a demand for ransom i'm ready
trent mill unicycle not another guitar segment i'll die good start so far so good hey june
what what the fuck are you doing what all right something going on with when i hold it
and then hit press it again i don't know why because i'm letting it go and pressing again
it's not that it doesn't register xbox sucks it's pretty much where i need to sell you
here we go come on
sweating down to hit the drum i forgot i was playing a game and i forgot i was
screaming i forgot i was sitting in a chair i forgot where i was i thought i was gonna get
a second it's too much fun you really have to turn off your brain but it's fun
it's another 60 percent what
it's michael jackson that's actually michael jackson
damn so the ransom scoop was a trap back to the station everyone michael jackson is in this
game he actually did voice work for it good job well done wow that probably cost a lot of money
he alone made the budget this game like 30 million dollars i need this space transmitter
to complete my grand plan soon enough none of you will have a thing to worry about
he came to them wow he must have really liked the first one do we get to play with michael
do we actually get to see michael jackson on camera in this level great me and michael let's go
let's see
oops that's a fucking wrong thing that's the wrong button
wait how did i do that wrong what is michael gonna think now
i have wrong order again i got hold on you can't just fuck up yeah i this is so fast
it's amazing how they get from this to tetris effect that's really cool
all right we're the power rangers on board we've reached the inside of the studio
it's just a real disaster where we dropping
i can't wait to see space michael that was somebody said that in chat i didn't
do
where is michael
what right you're not even you're not saying right and left you're going like yeah
it's the first time to introduce that
oh my goodness i thought there was something wrong look at those emotes
good please come up this is gonna be amazing
get out of here this is a trap you look too close to the mic there um michael
you've got to save space like oh
here we go
what why did it take so long why did it make that i cannot remember it now it took too long
to get over here shit right left oh god damn it why up straight shoe right left down
oh man this is gonna be horrible what i pressed it
i like michael in the background chew got it huh come on michael over here on this side
thank you it's our turn now let's go i like the outfit get to play as michael
i want direction from michael we've reached the core of the station yeah he went
is
oh god the president again what are you gonna do now
i try
me god damn no i can't lose
it's on the screen it doesn't matter like it's the it's the beat it's the rhythm it's the
shoes it's the pays
sorry we're right here what are you gonna do now
yeah
dope fucking lord
it's like off beat the off beat oh all right it's gonna be off beat again
come on that's it oh no when you hear oh god
don't hit the president
oh
come on end it is it still reverse it was still in reverse
come on
um
i can't stand a video what was it
dance dance dance okay I'm sorry I can't make any references I can't make any jokes
dance dance dance dance dance dance dance dance dance thanks thanks thanks thanks
nice dance you lala i love this game
Oh
No
Your brain just mixes them together
Scratching my head
You get out of here
It's another one in the bag I think I got this
Shut up
Rock, I don't know why I looked at chat to see what people were saying. You can't do that. Hey, what am I gonna?
What do you guys have to say? Oh cool
Come on come on quick just do it again
Fuck oh my goodness gracious. That was just too many things. Oh
He needs a parry I
Guess maybe playing through them a couple of times
playing through more than twice you can start to memorize things, but
No secrets
What happens face Michael, yeah, that's a really good question
The achievement by the way for that was who
H o o o o for those of you gnomes in the chat that find that to be very interesting
I haven't hit the wall yet. So we're gonna keep going Michael's fine. He's right here
It's a weird level. Good evening, everybody. We heard it through pines broadcast
We see something ahead, what's that the reading on Persian the president points us in favor where level
The film grain is actually hurting my face. It's alright
We got them
The whole cruise here the entire Final Fantasy party memorize the poses
My fucking hands my fucking hands now do it again, I slipped off I slipped off the fucking controller
I've pressed it and it went and my grease covered finger flipped over
What's that the reading on Persian the president points us in this direction
That's not even a real problem. It's time to take a break what I
Just slipped off my controller
Yeah, that is Michael Jackson
Oh
It's the pattern that they come out in oh my fucking Jesus
Okay
The pauses take you out of the beat and make you have to like memorize what you just saw and heard
Five seconds later and it's hard for your brain to do that. That's why it's intentional
For them to put it like that
Michael
Oh
My god, I know I might need a break that person was right that person was right. I need a break
I have no idea what this is
What
That's I gotta do the whole thing good evening everybody we heard it through pines broadcast
Can't skip this either we see something ahead. What's that the reading on Persian the president?
points us in this direction
Come back another time to it. I probably you know, I probably will this game's a lot of fun. Let me try it one more time
This is very very fun game
Play it while you're drunk. That would be the worst mistake ever
No stars lost there. No stars have been lost. This is the hard one
Yeah, I missed it already fuck it up already. Oh, this is hell trying to memorize it in the rail. God damn it
I couldn't get it. I
Thought I was I was paying attention to the last three and then I blew it
Got that one I fucking missed it
Just give me the star I
Blinked and I missed the first one. I actually blinked and I fucking didn't catch the first one
All right, let me pay attention this one it's just all my eyes on screen we go
My fucking lord
No
My god, it's really not that big of a deal
It's just when they go past like an eight or nine sequence like more than seven or eight in a sequence
It's like god you have to like memorize
What?
I press A to do that
The midway point stay tuned that's that's the midway point I got it
Like to do this fan weird keyboard I get it right on
Oh
That's up. I thought that was hey, I thought it was hey, but that's up
It's not it's not be
That's bang not. Hey
Why do you never heard of this I can't sorry both headphones are I can't talk
Why have you never heard of this game?
It's very old. I think it was recently ported, but it's a very old game. It's very good though
I
Thought it was Michael's turn it wasn't Michael's turn that's still hey, that's still the little guy. I thought it was Michael I
Got it, but I press the wrong button now
Space Michael when the guy has the microphone. Is that really the way to work?
Three
Was it hey, or was it to chew what would it was it was it hey
It was that like done done done done done done done done done
Let's do like this
How did I boying that I don't know
Shoot you yeah, that's Michael Jackson. Oh my goodness gracious. It's crazy taxi all over again. Come on. Don't star-lock
Hey shoot go I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready. I'm ready. Do it press the wrong button
Just a little more time you can't change back yet
Okay, Arnold
What huh, I'm it's the guy to get the guy
I just pressed. Hey, I did. Hey, I did up
Hey, so when you don't you shoot the real one or you don't shoot the real one
Are you supposed to shoot the real one? I okay I did I did press. Hey, that's what I did
So the middle one is the one that has to be shot. But how do you get me? Is it up?
Don't shoot the real one
No, I know I understand that like hey is save and choose attack. So you have to save the first two
Shoot the middle one save the next two
Save the real one. We're so far back here
No
No, you shoot the real one again
I might eat to eat the berries and not eat the berries half you guys are saying shoot the real one half
You guys saying save the real one half you guys doing it for fun
So I fuck it up on purpose and the other half are trying to help me. It's very fun
Yes, I'm gonna just figure it out. I didn't do
We'll do it again tomorrow
We're gonna do it again tomorrow, I've been streaming for seven hours of this these dreamcast games
We'll fit wolf. Well, I'm gonna start with that tomorrow to rage quits in one night
What was the oh that Jetset radio doesn't count. I put like 20 minutes in that game
Wasn't him that that's space channel five part two. It's on Steam
It is a port of a dreamcast game and it's very good, but I want to come back fresh tomorrow
I'll play tomorrow. I'm gonna beat it tomorrow. It's gonna be fucking very fun. This game sucks. No
What are you talking about?
What how could you say that they get that game is so charming and fun and interesting
But anyways
We'll pick it up tomorrow. I've been going for seven hours now
After the bits will probably be about eight hours or so eight and a half. So it's getting late
It's like one almost 1 30 a.m. Eastern
Time it's time, you know, you gotta you gotta know when it's time to take a break like that one guy said
It's time to take a break man. I said, yeah, you know what? You're right
Sometimes you just gotta know
Crazy taxi fucking awesome game space to pit channel five amazing game ton of fun
Jet set radio it's hard to learn but with you if you sit down and give it the time necessary
About 10 to 20 hours, maybe 40 hours of time. You'll learn it and it's a very good game
I'm sure you'll enjoy it. These are all in the dreamcast collection
When I'm gonna play seaman when I get it reshipped
Because they got shipped to me with the microphone missing so I couldn't play it so I returned it
And I know another I have to get another one, but that's gonna wrap it up for tonight
I really like want to finish space chin. I'm so like into it right now, but there's only somebody choose instead of
Hayes that you can fuck up before you realize it's time. It's time to go get like food and
Do it again tomorrow. I had a lot of fun as always was a blast. Thanks everybody sticking around
We to move on to the bits. I'll see you guys tomorrow for space channel 5 part 2 and then after that
It's kind of up in the air after that because that was kind of the that was the end of the dreamcast stuff
I'm looking forward to beating space channel
Space channel 5 part 2 part 2 that would be the title of the stream, but as always you guys rock
Thank you so much for sticking around here comes the outro
He rage quit even I didn't rage quit anything. I didn't rage quit. I
I just simply quit the game and put the controller down very very hard and
Air exhaled out of my nose very fast
That's not a rage quit. That is I ended the session of the game
I was playing and I'm gonna come back and do it again tomorrow with a little bit of rage you might say no
No, I wouldn't say that I would say with a slight discomfort level. Hey, is it a rage quit?
That's not a rage quit because I'm gonna I just I'm coming back and playing it tomorrow
Wouldn't a proper rage quit be that I'm not gonna ever play it again and fuck this game
I didn't did you ever hear me say fuck this game. Mm-hmm. I just simply am stopping my session
I'm gonna pick it up tomorrow, but let's uh move back in time here at about seven and a half hours ago
Or seven hours ago at just about see all shirts the shirts the shirts. All right, I forgot to mention again
Shirts are now available
glue man is back
Permanently and the night sky is the new shirt that is back not back. It's here
If you do exclamation point shirts, you will see it. You'll find it. There's a new cut
For the glue man shirt as well. Hope you enjoy them. I hope they turn out very good
Because I love them, I think they're great Ashley did a fantastic job. So
Kudos to Ashley and with that let's go over the bit. So seven hours ago crusty earwax. Thanks for one dollar
Glad to see you're okay. I thought you got arrested. I did not get arrested that didn't happen. Thank you for the one dollar
Thank you Alec for the one dollar. Why does the resolution like like a
2007 Blackberry
Crossed with an Apple 2. Well, this came out before iPhones even existed. So the iPhone has
Apple 2 has
The graphics of the Dreamcast, you know, they copy the Dreamcast 2007 Blackberry
We think they got the idea from but thank you yet went for the one dollar
Fun fact. I'm not actually a professional artist. I just like to draw my free time
This time I have drawn a portrait of you in Shito
Once again, I prefer you just keep the link to the high-res image
Okay, if only I keep the link to the okay, I see I look forward to watching your reaction when you when I wake up
All right, cool. Let's see. I
There's no way that you just draw in your free time. This is just so good that like you like no way
That's unbelievable. I
Just draw on my frizz. It's like some of the most talented artwork I've ever seen
So if you just draw kind of in your free time for fun, you got quite the gift
That's fucking unbelievable
I'm gonna download it and just put it on stream. Let me just get it on the stream
For their wishes, I don't I'm not gonna give the high resolution download link
But it's their request. I'll get it on the screen here. Take a look at this. This is unbelievable
It's like looking into a mirror. Let's see
It's ridiculous
This is extremely high-res
That is truly amazing. Well, thank you so much for this
Look at that face
Even the eyes the eyes are just are perfect. Their eyes are perfect the mouth
How are people this talented?
Remember I told you about the aliens that possess people to like be crazy taxi in like 30 minutes
It'd be the whole thing get s-plus on every single exact everything that works in a lot of different places
I think you got skill. You got talent great work
Absolutely excellent work. Thank you so much for that yen with yen Wen Lin and thank you for the one dollar as well
Thank you some guy for the $15. So funny story. I didn't actually mean to post the Phantom of the Opera Overture twice
In fact, I don't even think it was my intent to post it once
But anyway, here's another video
Thank you for $15 and
Take a closer. Look at that snout
That's Phantom of the Opera again. It's a
Mouse rat thing. I don't know what this is
But it's very clearly Phantom of the Opera
So, thank you some guy for the $15 and the Phantom of the Opera. Hey father frogman. Thanks for the one dollar
Wow, Jeremy great stream. Love grandpa. Everybody loves grandpa. Thank you. Timmy Tim Tim for the one dollar
So how's the comb stream talk to chat stream idea coming along?
The classic comb streams where you just sit in front of the camera and talk or some real comedy German moments
And I'd love to see it become more of a regular thing
Yeah, I've thought about it before but here's the thing about stuff like that, right?
Ah
It's
Everything you've ever seen me do like on like the IRL streams just kind of happened, right?
It wasn't like here I'm gonna plan this and I'm gonna do that and here we go
Yeah, this is the thing. I'm gonna do is a bit today
We kind of just sit there and it just happens. So, I don't know planning out IRL streams in particular
I don't know if I if it's a good idea anymore
I feel like they naturally will just happen when they need to and when they will I
Feel the same way about a lot of different other pieces of content, right?
Stuff just kind of naturally has to happen and putting myself on like a once a week or once every oh, it's the comb stream
Here we go. Here comes the comedy. Like here it comes
That's not gonna really work because that's not how I operate. So just stream yourself sleeping
You can't do that on Twitch you get banned
I mean some of the most fun moments I've ever had on this stream came from things that I didn't even know was
Gonna happen until 10 seconds before they happened. I mean take that as you will I guess but that's sort of how it works
Can't wait for the next funny Friday
Like accidentally being naked. Yeah, like that was a funny plan thing. I was pretend. Everybody knows that but thank you Timmy Tim tan
Thank you c4g for the $1 and they say please give us pins of germa Jax
Teespring does not just do t-shirts anymore. I think I can make
phone cases
Wallets keys. Well, you know you get the idea
socks Pikachu socks
Whale plushies, you know, there's all this plenty of options
So that storefront if you notice if you go to like the store
teespring.com slash stores the germa 985
It's all just there
So any other pieces of merchandise that I want to do through teespring will just go up on that storefront
those shirts aren't coming down things will just be added over time and if it's out of the
Wheelhouse of teespring and it's something else that I want to do then I'll put it somewhere else, right?
But thank you lazy Luke for the $1. I will spend all my money of my bank account for the night sky shirt
Well, I hope you don't spend all your money in your bank account
If you have enough money to buy that shirt and it's something that you want and you think you're gonna wear it
And by all means, but I really don't I really hope you don't clear out your bank account to buy that shirt
It'll be around for a long time. You got plenty of time to do it
Thank you tingy for the $1 Saturn is popular chat will spam germa Saturn now just watch
Well somebody mentioned they might be on Saturn
So that's the ultimate part of that t-shirt because you are Saturn. They're standing on you which is Saturn or mercury depending
Thank you. Ike turtle for the $1. Yo, I got a question about that shirt
Why are you why are we just spying on this family through a telescope?
These are these are questions that I don't have an answer to thank you Todd for the $1
Hey, it's time for some crazy taxi
Thank You demonic cucumber for the $1. Hey, it's Alex
I know the reason why you didn't stream yesterday because you were busy cremating the late Jerma
I guess she toe hasn't appeared because he can't handle the grief. Anyway, Jerma would have made a spill joke by now
Just the heads up
Thank You Marvosh McGally for the $1 petition to make an egg t-shirt next
Also a reminder for chat that this video exists video exists. This is
This is Bergboy puking
Yeah, that's a video on my channel of one of my friends throwing up on camera. He's laughing so hard at a game
That's one of my favorite videos, by the way
This is this is one of my favorite videos on my whole channel
Yeah
It is like house oh
the memories
good old YouTube
2012 burger boy fuking on webcam
So yeah that there it is. I have so much of vivid moments vivid memories of that
Exact video he was laughing. We were laughing so hard
He just threw up. I think he was drinking something out of like a big baby cup, too
I don't know idea who's drinking like booze or something. But anyways, thank you Marvish McGally
demonic cucumber. Thanks for the $1 also
Is the shirt edible?
What shirt the shirt like my shirts they made out of the most premium material you wouldn't want to eat those
Hey Davis, thanks for the two bucks Davis
Dork cube. Thanks for the $1 all these screaming punk singers in extremely dangerous driving reminds me of when
My sister got her license
punk singers
Anything is edible at least once. Well, I mean could you eat that shirt?
You could
It would be incredibly ill-advised
That would be a very bad idea
You would get sick something bad you did you get like a blockage in your attack that you can't you shouldn't do that
Do not do that
It technically is you could
But do not do it. I'm gonna eat it. I didn't tell you to I'm telling you right now. Do not do that
Absolutely, do not consume that shirt wear it run from it. Thank you door cube again for the $1
Fat fart master. Okay, never mind
Thank you Jebediah for the
$10 you ever gonna post on the main channel again. I have no plan to we've gone over it more than a
dozen times at this point
Probably not that channel is gonna stay there. It's never gonna come down but in the current landscape of how
Things work right now on twitch. I don't have time to make a video
I really don't
Streaming I used to make a video once a week
But now instead of making a video that takes me four days to make you know
Four or five days to make it or come up with an idea now. I just stream four days a week
Sometimes less sometimes more and I'm not going to just make a video because I have to if that makes any sense
I'm not going to just be like I got to make a video
I have to because then that's not why I wanted to make a video in the first place
I will never phone in a stream. I will never phone in a video. I just I don't want to that's not why I want to
Do it. So hey, well, you got to make a new video on the main channel. It's like I but I don't
because
Going back and trying to do a video just because I have to do a video
That's not gonna happen. The magic will not be there the it just won't feel fun
It won't be something I'm interested in currently all of my interests right now are on trying to make like live
Stuff and obviously since the move to Vegas
You've already seen a handful of streams that have taken a lot more time to make and like I said once every like 30 to 40
Days, you're gonna see something else. It just depends on exactly what I want to do
But that is the new interest in the new thing that I want to try
I don't know what you could upload that people won't be upset about at this point. Yeah, but there's
There are a million reasons why?
But I've I'm not gonna just do it if I get the urge and it's like something that I want to do and hey
This would be great as a YouTube video
Maybe I'll work on it and try to put it up and now obviously we'd talk about it
But I want to try to transition to more
Experience live experience based content because it's fun and it has to be it's a natural progression, right? Because
You we talked about it literally 20 minutes ago. Not even I
I
Need to be interested. I have to be
It's just not it's not something that I can do. I'm not capable of
Putting a face on and uploading a video because I want to but I'm sorry that a lot of people don't want to hear that
But I don't I'm not gonna like lie to everybody and be like just wait a six more months and there'll be
Jerma Rumble to Jerma Rumble live to is going what is gonna be a live broadcast
Actually on twitch, that's what I want to do
No one's ever done something like that before. No one's ever tried to do something like that. I don't think and
Neither have I that's something I've never tried to attempt before so I've slowly been trying to do more live
Showy type stuff to test the waters to see how possible I think it is the WWE
Yeah, I mean the WWE has like a thousand employee
I'm talking about like eight people with like 20 actors and people maybe with
something with extensions could like vote on who could get eliminated or
Maybe you could vote on who comes in next
stuff like that is what interests me right now and over the few months coming years that I want to try to
Level up to that and right now. It's a lot of meeting people checking out studios
Talking to the right people getting the right position where it's something I could do and so far
I think I'm on the right path. We'll see but hopefully that answers your question
Thank you Peter for the three dollars and 85 cents. I had your stream audio for crazy taxi playing during my drive home
I'll just say that the honking tire screeching and screaming made for a great 4d driving experience. Oh
Jesus I
Make sure the volume is at a level where you're not gonna get confused
Be careful take make sure you're driving safely and you can pay attention to all your surroundings. Oh my god
But thank you Peter
Smelly boy. Thanks for the one dollar. They've redid the entire let it go song from frozen in Kingdom Hearts 3
Only differences Sora Donald and goofy are sitting in the background and it's hilarious. I
Can't play this on stream. I'll go to jail. Oh, by the way
An idea that I had for German Rumble live. You guys might think this is funny because it's pretty relevant
I didn't want to go to jail though
It was gonna just start snowing and this was gonna play and it was Elsa was gonna come out
The snow was gonna just start falling under the ring and Elsa was gonna be like a contestant
Everyone's gonna stop and like look don't worry. I got fucking a million tricks up my sleeve
You don't even know about some of the other ones
That that was like a bad
Not funny version of like 30 other contestants. So don't worry
I got I got an entire German Rumble live two three and four upstairs
But I ain't going to jail so I can't play that whole video. Thank you
Brawler thanks for the five dollars. That is not how you drive a taxi. It is how you do it in crazy taxi
Hey demonic cucumber. Thanks for the one dollar
I'm starting to have serious doubts in my theory that italics is doing the streams now because only Jeremy could come up with
Something as batshit crazy as skin aliens and possession by gamer powers because it must have been in his mad ramblings before he died
There are a few different theories as to how people are so good at video games
theory one alien gamers possession spirits theory two
Highly skilled video game players see the world at point nine eight speed. We've already talked about that one
I'm convinced you just you have that edge
You see the world in like point nine seven not slow enough for it to really have it be a superpower
But slow enough where you have like an edge somebody should test it point now at nine eight is now point nine seven
Point nine seven ratio fighting game players. Yeah
It's like it's like trying to catch a fly
In the air you have to see the world at like point nine six
It's not your humans can't do that unless you have the superpower that lets you slow down time
Permanently by just a tiny bit and then they grab the fly and it's like, oh, you know people can't do that
You must have fucking powers you can train reflexes with practice. You could probably bring it down to like point nine nine
I don't know about point nine eight or nine seven though. Do you see the world at one point?
0.02 probably I
Bet I see the world like point I probably see the world at one point 14
I want to test this theory one day
I want to like clap at the same time or like try to grab something and send and see
What the aren't there apps and games that do this?
There's like a click when the there's a click when it's a green light, right?
Isn't that a game and you can see how fast your reaction is. I have to do that next dream
It's a reaction test. Yeah, we're gonna do that next dream. I can't do it now. Am I I've got gamer fatigue
It won't be an accurate representation of my skills
But anyways, thank you demonic cucumber
Thank you. Just for the one dollar. Hey, Jerem, you're not becoming a mutant boomer who hates everything not yet
At least here's my parting gift. Nobody actually likes this game. Do they?
Kidding. I'm kidding. I love Kingdom Hearts 1 & 2. I'm just kidding. It's a joke guys. It's just a joke
I've loved going to the movie theater and watching
Seven movies in a row and then swinging a sword around for five seconds and then going back in the theater and
Watching like six more movies was it like 16 hours of cutscenes in that game
Metal Gear Solid 4 I think Metal Gear has less cutscene which figure it out. Let's find out
What has more cutscenes across the whole franchise Metal Gear Solid or Kingdom Hearts?
I think Kingdom Hearts 2 has like 14 hours of cutscenes
Metal Gear
Has like a hundred hours of cutscenes Metal Gear Solid 4 has 74 71 minutes. Is that no, it's not real
It's got seven games and then you called me an idiot. How dare you?
Kingdom Hearts 3 actually has a fictional Square Enix anime bullshit game inside the universe of Toy Story
Yeah, but here's the thing like Kingdom Hearts, right?
Kingdom Hearts was a really great idea
Really great games there there there are very good games. They're incredibly detailed. There's a lot to do
There's a lot to see they brought together all the Disney worlds and it was but you could go to Jack Skellington
And then from there you could go to Winnie the Pooh
It was like the biggest Infinity War crossover event in history for video games
It just was and then they came up with the second one and they even added more there was more to do
There's more to see. Oh, that's awesome
Cool, and then the second one and even in the end of the first one they kind of just said hey
instead of it being about like Disney characters and and
You know being like a good person and Kingdom Hearts is a door they went so far off the rails to a point what?
There's so much random shit going on that
It's almost like they have nine movies playing at the same time
Pausing four of them halfway through letting the other five play
pausing those going back and letting the other four play for like two hours and
Then turning them all off the game came out like what 13 14 years later
They were like a bunch of other random games in the middle
There was like a DS like a Gameboy Advance games that were part of the story
They had to like catch people up. It's like there's a lot going on and they're all canon
Wow, but that's what I mean
They got like movies from a decade ago playing in the background for you
Well, you have the current movie playing in front of you
The problem with King of Hearts is they released a shit ton of games on handhelds
But didn't actually tell you they were part of the story
But jokes aside
If you if you like Kingdom Hearts and you were excited for it, then that's great
I'm not that's awesome because let's be real about it
Hey finished the day actually finished their fucking story
They actually did it took them a long time, but they did it they announced it and here it is and it's done
I can name you a couple of companies that have not done that that everybody really wishes they did
Let me know they didn't Kingdom Hearts 3 is not the end
Kingdom wait Kingdom Hearts 3 is not the end of Kingdom Hearts. Oh, don't spoil anything, but hold on wait what?
Well, whatever they
My whole point is completely moot here that just a bit
Yeah, but this done what that's like saying Half-Life 3 never came out, but it didn't but if Half-Life 3 came out
Maybe there would be more Half-Life games like offshoots and Kingdom Hearts 1 2 3 done
That storyline is done. They thought they did it but regardless
I don't want to like rain on anybody's parade for
Liking Kingdom Hearts because I do I thought I think it's good. I played this shit out of those games the first two
I'll probably end up playing the third one
But there's a lot of strange things going on in that series and it's kind of bounces all over the place
to a point where it has gotten to Metal Gear level of
What is that? Who is that? Why is that? And in my opinion, I don't know if you should be making I don't you're making those
Statements during a Disney game. Why is that? Who is that? Where is that?
Donald Duck is Donald Duck is just hanging out in the background. Why I got a Coca-Cola writer. I got a Pepsi
That's not even whatever I need to hydrate
That's not water
But I'll probably play it. I will probably play it
By the way, I just realized what happened there. So
I got a one dollar from Jess who said you're not becoming a mutant boomer who hates everything and you linked
The King that's then I went off on Kingdom Hearts. So you just played me like an absolute fiddle here
That was very well done. Very well done
Thank you
My can't my brain. Thank you phylactery
phylactery for the $15
Dermot, you're so handsome. I have to be careful not to watch your stream and my girlfriend's around take this money
Do you appease your rugged good looks?
Thank you. Appreciate it. Metal Gear story is just as bad. Don't kid yourself chat
Oh Kingdom Hearts story versus Metal Gear story
Which one did you quit halfway through because you went oh, please. Oh
Both of them
Metal Gear is fine until four
Metal Gear 3 is well
I mean you got it at three is then this is then five and then five isn't
the beginning of one and then one is then two and then two is then four and then two actually is
Not even in it's like it's based on a whole nother storyline
Then there's in the middle of five you got the the Michael Jackson
hee-hee
Except it's more of a ha ha
Right. Nah close enough. What a great sound effect by the way
When you smoke that cigar, it's that's I love that part of that game. I love that games a great game
We talk about good games
Look at solid five is good
Anyway, saran wrap. Thanks for the three bucks
It'd be great to see Evo search for Eden on a future stream
It's a childhood favorite of mine and kind of like seventh cross was good
Much love. Thank you saran wraps and I'll type it into Google and I'll see what the hell it is
You're playing Metal Gear Solid 3 for the first time. That is I think that's probably my favorite one
In fact, Metal Gear Solid 3 is probably the only one that I would go back and play again
Is that strange the first two were very
classic
classic pieces of
Cinema right video game cinema, but gameplay wise I think I'd rather go back and play three
More than any of them. Here's think about four. I have not played four
I tried to start for but I just ran out of time ran out of I just I couldn't grab me and I stopped playing it
Four is good, but it's too long for replays
Yeah, I think Metal Gear Solid 3 sits somewhere right in the perfect little place for length gameplay
Storyline cutscenes. I love the boss encounters. I love the but I'm not gonna spoil anything because I don't know who's played it
but the different the
the different does
There's a great. I love I just love that. It's it's got a I can't really say anything, but you know what I'm talking about
Maybe I will go back and play three again a great game
the
The existence of the Cobra unit isn't exactly a spoiler. No
But a couple of those characters you really if somebody was gonna play through to the further the first time ever
I'm not sure you'd want to start saying some of those names
Because you know
Thank you. Hero of trains is for the $1
Hey German longtime fan here
Just want to say that Sonic Adventure DX needs its own stream. It actually has a story as opposed to some of these arcade games
Space Channel 5 has a story and
Michael Jackson's in that one. So I we got to go back and beat that one. They scream their names throughout the game. Oh
I forgot about some of those characters. This is so good
Oh, I could I'm just gushing about Metal Gear Solid 3 but Sonic was a fun game. I didn't not like it
I'm just not into the whole story Sonic
world
Sonic the game I love Sonic the world and Sonic the characters. I really am not it doesn't it doesn't really do much for me
Sonic the video game is phenomenal
But in my opinion, I'm not a big like huge fan of the Sonic world
Dirty Margaret, thanks for the $10. This music is pleasing
I'm not sure what you're referring to but maybe you're talking about the music from crazy taxi
Dork cube. Thanks for the $1
How much of Sonic 06 have you seen because if you haven't seen much I would suggest you play it for a laugh
Well, actually the chat will be laughing. You'll be full of rage trying not to throw the controller at the screen
Sonic 06 I have seen it played I have
Played pieces of it. That's the one where there's the Elsa's in that game, right?
You're in like the weird human world and
There's all those weird cutscenes where you
Yes, so I'm thinking of the right game. I don't remember much. I didn't get very far and
I said I made a lot of people very angry at the beginning of this stream. Oh this game sucks, right Sonic adventure
This is this one is a terrible one and that was I was thinking of 06. So I apologize again for that one
Snoozing copter. Thanks for the $1. Hey pst. Jerma. Did you know that there's an actual casino in Godhand?
Slot machines and blackjack. I'm just the guy with the bits that reminds you to play Godhand until you do it
What have I become do it?
I think I bought Godhand digitally and gave my PlayStation 3 away
I think that's what happened. I have to get it again
Excuse me. Sorry
Mini clips. Thank you mini clips for the $14 and 35 cents. No message nearly $15
Thank you so much and on top of your other huge contributions. Thank you so much mini clips
Dragon zero hexa. Thanks for the $1 place some dirty overwatch League
Overwatch League 2000. I'm not gonna play overwatch
I'm not gonna play overwatch. That's I moved on. I'm glad that people can play that game and enjoy it
I'm glad people can play any game and enjoy it
But I got my time in overwatch. I had my fun in overwatch. I just I've moved on it's not something
I'm probably ever gonna play again
Unless they make me as a character if the next overwatch character is Jerma and it's me and I have a hook
that I can kind of stick it into walls and like throw myself and it's a movement ability and
In my right hand is a three burst shotgun. It goes boom boom boom
boom boom boom
And you have to be pretty close range and then my ultimate would be I turn into a top and other people can
You can these two other people on the team have to throw me
So it's a three-person ultimate kind of I can't use it unless there's two people around me
Boom boom top. There's a Beyblade. Yeah, and I would I would have to cost fifty fucking dollars and every cent
Goes directly to charity. It's the only way I would do it. But thank you to dork cube
For the $1 this just in local streamer expects real gambling games in children's Sonic game
They had a slot machine in there
Inside that pinball machine. There was a slot. It exists. Thank you, bro. Look for the $5, dude you by
Fucking brain, please stop the fever dream Sonic game. It wasn't that bad. It was okay
This is pretty good music in that game. Thank you. Errorless for the $1 Jerma Earth
I'm gonna be rocking that shirt when it comes in for sure
Thank you to no
No, one three four for the multiple bits here and they say go back to fucking Sonic fucking go back to Sonic
I can't and
crazy taxi space channel five those my top picks and
So much so that we're gonna go back and try to finish space channel five tomorrow. But thank you
Sonic was not a bad game. Hey Freudian weapon. Thanks for the $10 Freudian these past few streams have shown me
There's a lot of fun-looking games. I missed out on for Dreamcast
Somebody games a little time
There are a lot. There are too many some would argue which is why how do you have the time?
to watch
fucking 17 hours of cutscenes in Kingdom Hearts 3
That's a whole this the amount of cutscenes in Kingdom Hearts 3 is
The amount of time it takes to play through on an average playthrough of Resident Evil 2 campaign
Who's got the time for that anymore? I know I just slurred those words gamer fatigue. Thank you. Jack the back of the $5
Better watch that coming at you. They do giggle giggle giggle wizard rivet. Thanks for the $1
It's time for slime. Thanks for the $2. Yeah jet-set radio is so good looking and sounds great and is really cool
But is really not that fun to play
But I forgot though. I
My memory is not serving me correctly here. I remember having a ton of fun in jet-grind radio
Was I just young and just didn't care. It was just simpler. It just has a huge learning curve
You just have to get used to it again. Yeah, that's why I
Can't tell you that it was a bad game. I can't I
Made the wood comment, but that was just me being a dick
I hold true to the statement that I think that is a good game just requires a lot of attention
But thank you. Thank you anonymous for the $1. Hey Jerma, it's the animal shelter guy
By the time you read this it will be my birthday
I want to say thanks for having such a great community. I've got a lot of kind words from Chad on the duck stream
Hey, love you, Chad. Oh and for the peeing so often just be happy
It's all you have most people over 70 have had hip replacements. So cheer up. That's true. Sometimes I forget
Thank you ecliptic
For the $2. Hey Jerma, I wanted to say thanks for all that you do your VODs and streams helped me this last year
Relax and pass the time on a long deployment. I'm glad to be back and hopefully I'll be able to catch more of your streams
Thanks so much for what you do
Thank you as well
Welcome back
Hopefully we see your own welcome back almost done here with the bits we have
We had a lot from a lot from not bits, but we had a lot of subs from great Canadian
Thank you came in a couple hours ago. Thank you plasma player for the $1. Just wanted to give a shout out to
Hideki
Naganuma the composer for jet set radio for making awesome music for more than 25 years
He also composed music for jet set radio future and sonic rush
Lethal League blaze ain't nothing like a funky beat is an absolute banger that feels like a jet set radio song
Hold on a minute. They did the music for lethal league this one song
Just the one track. That's really cool though. That's very very cool
Still going 25 years later
That's really awesome. Thank you for the $1 plasma
Hey Garfield the Monday killer. Thanks for the $1 a long time no see Jerma
Unfortunately Garfield has had his bits stolen by swiper the Fox
So it took a while to track him down and take the golf bucks back the punishment has been dulled out properly
He got the Monday treatment
Anyway, that's a pretty wacky video game. You're playing over there Jerma. I remember that one time
I dated a news reporter for a while. That's not a joke. By the way, I dated one she was nice
But she had to move to space
That was a very long and space but I the legend returns Garfield. Thank you the $1 Garfield
Superman thanks for the $1
Hey, Jerma was just wondering if you played any ps2 itoi games because I had
Fun memories playing with them and my stepbrother
He's currently stationed in
Sicily with the Navy as a dental technician and I miss spending time with him
Also, how many siblings do you have and what kind of jobs if you don't mind me asking?
So I have a brother and a sister and for the joke response
I have two brothers and they're very very mean and I don't like them. That's the joke response. But for the real response
I
Mean, I don't know if I want to say I don't know if my I keep my siblings in my family kind of out
of
Everything to do with what I'm doing
So I don't really talk about my family too much
That was the fake dinner. Oh
He hates his family. No a lot of you guys already know this but I keep a lot of stuff in my private life
Just private and that's just kind of how it's gonna stay but I do appreciate the I appreciate the
Inquiry inquiry, right? But yeah, I do have a they're both older older brother older sister. Thank you so much Superman
Dr. Steen. Thanks for the five dollars read scary stories to tell in the dark
On stream in the future. That means bugle bear. I can't I'm not gonna do anything scary
Unless bugle berries on the screen. Tell me your credit card info. Okay, the credit card number is
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 20
expiration
June of
2180 I got a good deal on that one. Hey tingy. Thanks for the one dollar
I found the real reason why you didn't die on the 23rd. It's because your real death was determined during this stream
What if your life is gone, that's what I'm hearing. No, that would imply that I'm gonna live to be driven
I'm not going online and type it in that death that like what are you good?
What what date are you gonna die? I'm not doing that. I did that once and I never I'll never do it again
No way back when I was in high school or something
I'm not doing it. I wouldn't yeah, I wouldn't do it right now. Anyways, why did I do that?
Why would you do that Friday July 4th 2059, okay
What what's what's today's date right now? What year is it right now?
19 29 30 9 40 9 50 9 40 years from now. I'll be
Been like 80
Yeah, hey July 4th 2059. I'll be streaming and I'm gonna get in
Child's hockey pads and a boxing helmet. We'll do it again, and then you guys can sync it up
You know 40 years later
40 plus 30 equals 80. Well, I'm sir. I'm 33 right now and
That means I have like 40 how many more years from like 40 that would be of 73
That's all right
73 equals 80. I'm gonna be fine. Thank you tingy though
Thank you tingy again for one dollar marketing your calendars Chad Jerma's death is February Friday July 4th 2059
How many you got half have you guys wouldn't even probably be here anymore
How many of you guys can reliably say that you could put up with my shit for like another 40 years
What is that for you could?
Can you imagine if I was streaming still 40 years later?
Imagine if you had a subscription to this channel and I'm like, oh, thanks for the subs
Oh you guys that thanks for the 37 year sub
Well, that's that's kind of wild. I'll have a bunch of tears
You know, there's like one month three months six months 12 months 24 month
imagine having like a
25-year sub badge
What the hell would that even be?
Imagine like other streamers I think I think about that
Imagine if like twitch is still going strong
20-30 years from now and some of your favorite streamers are still going
Hey, thank you ice pick 2 1 25 2 for the
18 years in a row
Much love to you. Thanks for sticking around. We have another one coming in from
spaceman 4 4
28 years
What a weird world is gonna be the sub baby goes to college the usernames are gonna get really long. Yeah
Florida is gonna be the streaming capital of the world
Retirement homes are just gonna feed lands
welcome everybody to the
2081 League of Legends world championship today. We have no what this is implying that no one else is ever gonna play video games
Ever again, why is that the implication here?
This people is still gonna be born and be playing games when they're younger
That is what it just won't or will will the old people be on twitch still and the new younger
What was generation Z?
Generation like I don't know XX for whenever they come out. They're gonna be in like holograms
So that will happen. It'll be twitch will just be well the old people are it'll be like reading a newspaper
The day we have and this corner we have
TSM and like all the TSM guys will still be there versus cloud nine
Coming from Sunnydale retirement home to yes. Yeah to yes
Yeah to yes. Yeah, there's like fights in the fucking crowd and the crowd is like 11 people
Four of them have like TSM hats on and fucking shirts. They're like throwing drinks at each other. You shut the fuck up
He's went toppy was supposed to go middle and that's the only reason why he lost the nurse will come over Dave David
What is it? Is your diaper full? Yes, but I'm not moving jealous matches over. Okay, that's okay
That's right. I know what's up water, too
Oh, but the kids will be laughing at us all 11 people are just over 80 all 11 people
You'll have to go to like the archive archive org whatever to go to twitch. There'll be a new thing
Though guys there's gonna you know understand like in in like 25 30 years twitch is not gonna exist. It's gonna be something else
It'll be like going on virtual. It'll be like going on a virtual rollercoasters with celebrities. There won't be any theme parks anymore
you'll just put on like this weird suit and
You'll like you you'll just be able to go to like Disney World online
And like George Clooney will just be there signing autographs on the ride and shit like that
You're gonna be able to walk around. It's gonna be like ready player one. We'll have VR streams
Yeah, but no that would be impossible because how would that ever work? I thought about that before too. It's like
Oh, hey, let's do this thing. We're gonna have everyone's gonna VR headsets on we're all gonna be in the same place
Hey guys, meet me on the Vegas strip. We're gonna go it's gonna be so much fun
I and there's gonna be like 5,000 ghosts just like people
That wouldn't work
What if you have like 10 streamers all streaming like in Hollywood at the same time and you just got like fucking?
40,000 just people like holograms walking around
It's gonna be like weird ghost hangout chat
Imagine trying to go get a coffee going in you with your like hologram IRL stream
Yeah, yeah, can I get a large latte? Um, what about anybody else? Oh, no, there's these 6,000 people in your
900 square foot business and they're all screaming. It's gonna be like private instances like wow dungeons
We have the infrastructure that needs to be there it Elon Musk wants to build underground tunnels
Where you drive your car into them and they like go really fast in a tube
That seems that seems very reasonable compared to like hologram VR chat in a coffee shop
There are already programs to allow VR viewers into your VR games. They just show up as little ghost headsets
they'd be looking like the Pied Piper walking down like
Walking down the street with like 4,000 little rats behind you headsets. Why does we get like a flute out and start dancing?
You could be the giant rat. That's true
But anyways, we're almost done. It's figured we talked about them
Virtual world the virtual reality and where it's going
These are serious topics to talk about on the podcast
What is gonna happen with AI?
That's gonna be weird. A lot of people just kind of you kind of look
Your parents my parents if there is the same type of exponential growth in technology
my parents saw
The invention of the television color TV and they're still alive and
We I'm on twitch right now you can open up your telephone that is in your hand
Press two buttons and somebody will deliver a pizza to your house
They've seen that they saw the Atari. What is gonna be our Atari if technology hasn't plateaued
Which it may have I don't know. That's weird to think about you just don't even know
And it's become so normal the Dreamcast was our Atari. Yeah, but when you're like 70
What are you gonna be saying about fortnight?
Above the opinion that we're gonna we're gonna go too far like think of just Wi-Fi
There are like wireless
There are wireless signals you can go on the internet without a cord
Is that that but we shouldn't be able to do that. That should not be possible, right?
No cords and
Wireless shit that has to be like mutating our DNA like 500 years from now. They're gonna go back
It's gonna be like, oh, yeah, they were doing the wireless. Yeah, they didn't have but they weren't in like the shells
Yeah, see nowadays we you know, you gotta be if you go outside you're in your house
You're gonna be wearing your you're like astronaut shell. How do you send something through a tube without a tube?
I did yeah, I don't get it. So right now they're right now. I'm holding my phone in my hand
I'm gonna type something into it and
An electric zapper shock electric data ray that we can't even see just went through the back of my head through my eyeballs and
mutated my DNA
400 years from now, we're gonna have fins. We're gonna have like fucking flippers on our asses. It's non ionizing
Yeah, and they and they bled George Washington because they thought he had fucking puke in his blood
That's not how electromagnetic waves work
German's ass flippers have not grown in yet. Oh, what the heck man?
What am I gonna get my fins
If only smarter people than you were in charge. I know
If only there were people that were way more capable of breaking any of this down than me
They just don't exist though. That's the problem. That's the that's the worst thing to have to think about
All right. All right. I'm done fucking around. There's too much puke in their blood
Hey, thank you, uh clue the sniper for the one dollar
Deep's one for the one dollar. Mr. Local streamer who has streamed for three plus years. Where are the three year sub badges?
I gotta make them. That's a long time three years in a row. I that's a long time
bless you, uh
Thank you to door cube for the one dollar
I like how you read someone's messages that said you weren't turning into an irritated old man and then immediately shout on kingdom hearts
And questioned whether anybody actually liked the game
But that was just a joke. Look I told you like 90% of everything I say is just like a
Poker it's just like a fire poker
And there's like a joke target that I
It's not i'm just kidding. It's not real
Thank you venus gothic for the ten dollars
No message. Thank you
Dr stein thanks for five dollars. Hey germa got a question for you. Why vegas?
Just curious as to why you chose to move there instead of anywhere else in the entire world such as anartica
Well anartica is too cold
You can't live there
Unless you're on some type of research base from or one of those kind of areas in anartica that are habitable
Some people do I think live there
Uh, but i've touched upon it a few times
Vegas is cheaper than la. I wanted to live in la
It's close to la. It's its own entertainment hub. It's got its own studios. It's got its own movie tv shows tv studio stuff
It's a 24 hour city
So, I mean it's 11 30 right now and i'm about to go get like food
It's late
Late, it's a late person's town. I love kind of the the lights. I think I love I love the town
I love the city in general been here quite a few times in the past
Uh, and and circus circus casino is here. It's one of the lowest reviewed
Casinos on the strip and it's my favorite one. I actually had a conversation with one of my close friends
When we went to vegas together
And we talked about we went to circus circus and we were like, oh this is amazing. I love it here
This is so cool
And then we read all the reviews online how it was like everyone but you know, it's a bit different thought it was a piece of shit
and
We had this long kind of internal conversation with and with each other about like are we the fucking weirdos?
Are we like the people that these reviews are talking about and it was a really real like existential kind of conversation
Like we loved this place. Oh, this is great
And you go read the reviews like I cannot believe how bad this place was
It's like why did we like this place?
But now that those are all the reasons it's 24 hour city. There's a lot to do
There's a lot of entertainment stuff here. It's way cheaper than la by a long shot
It's uh, it's great. I've been absolutely adoring it so far. You shouldn't base your enjoyment on other people's opinions
Oh, I know no, absolutely not
But I guess I I mean this is coming from a guy that liked the venom movie
Right, does that make me a bad guy? Am I a bad guy? I might be no. Yes
Everyone liked the venom movie. No, they didn't
You know, I mean like twitters were like unbelievable. I'm fucking believable
I can't imagine anybody enjoying the venom movie. You have to imagine that they would also be gambling at circus circus
What are these reviews? It said that I was like what the fuck felt personally attacked by it, but thank you
to
Dr. Steen
Vegas is a great place. Vegas is one of those places everybody loves to visit
But people just kind of forget that it exists and they don't want to live there
and the unfortunate truth around it, I guess is that
If you're if you don't want to be
You know for employment opportunities, there's the casinos. There's a lot of restaurants. There's a lot of
entertainment stuff here
and hospitality stuff
hotels restaurants casinos
But other than that that's not at the moment, you know, it's it's it's a growing city
But I love it
I think it was the right call
And those are the end of the bits
Can you imagine enjoying things?
I can't imagine it
See like I remember when I just told you kingdom hearts is a great series
All right, but I hope you love it and I hope you enjoy it. Hope you get a lot out of it
I really mean that
But make another fucking chrono trigger. You should be ashamed of yourselves for not doing that. I'm sorry. All right
I'm sorry, but that's it
We're gonna roll the credits
I got like the weird bug tonight for some reason they made chrono cross
Yes, they did and then they were gonna make a third one and they gave up on it
But thank you all the subs of the resubs. You guys are amazing
Sorry, i'll get to work
Thank you venus gothic for the five dollars germa everything you say on stream is the equivalent of watching someone swing a bat at a
Hornet's nest
No, it's I don't think that's true
That's not true
What did I say this stream that was hitting the hornet's nest? I'm just messing around
I really am just just fucking around. Hope you guys know that sonic adventure. I didn't say that
Liking surface circus. That's a that's a bit true. It's just a prank
Hey dork cube. Thanks for the one dollar
I've come to the realization in the last few years that happiness is sometimes hard to come by
So why bother making fun of someone's tastes if you like venom good? I'm so glad that film added to your happiness
Yeah, I mean look i'm of the opinion that
There is true criticism
There's true
You know if you think this is something I mean at the end of the day stuff costs money
And if you don't think it was worth paying for then of course
Criticism is important very important
but also i'm one of those people that I like to kind of just
Poke fun at even some of my own shit that I think is
You know that I like or that I don't like I think you have to kind of
The mood doesn't have to go as as negative
As a lot of I think a lot of critiques can be
As long as people know that for the most part you're just trying to have a good time
then
All is great
But I agree
There's plenty of things that I think are great that people think are bad or dumb or
And that's fine. That's what makes us different
You know everybody doesn't have to like
The same things fuck I could go for some gravy
The world the world would be a weird place without personal interests and opinions
I agree. It would be uh
Look if everyone didn't have different opinions and different tastes and different points of views and thinking
We would all end up just like squidward in that episode where he gets the can of bread with all the other squid words
Walking in line and going to the squidward grocery store
And it seems great for a little while
But watch that episode and tell me how it goes at the end
canned bread
Wasn't the point of that episode that he was the odd squidward and wasn't like them
and
That is much as he doesn't like spongebob and spongebob causes so many problems. It's still it's it's an interesting person interesting thing
Canned burgers exist. That's really strange
but
Uh, we had one final bit come in from dr. Steen 15 dollars
Thanks for answering the question. I'm going to go to school in new york city
And I love the fact that I can do stuff at night as well
Have a great night
Uh germa enjoy your food spend a hundred dollars on it
You deserve a feast after all the work you do for us keep on doing what you do and we will be there the whole time
Riding every ride you throw us onto
Go get your vr headsets ready and close them because we're going on that roller coaster. Let's go
hundred dollar meal
Uh, i'm not sure i'm gonna do that right now, but thank you so much. Dr. Steen
And finally ike turtle with one dollar. I missed the tony hawk stream a few days ago
But watch the vod and it was good
Have you considered trying out?
Uh, tony hawk underground or thug pro
I thought that's not underground. It's a mod. Oh it is it's a mod for tony hawk's underground, too
It allows you to play pretty much any tony hawk level that's ever been made
Yeah, that's an interesting idea
Because tony hawk 2 is great tony hawk 3 is great
I'm gonna have to type that into google. How often has germa gambled? Is that what he does in between streams?
um
That this is what I do
I just turn all right. See you guys later. I'll see you tomorrow and the stream turns off and I get my code on
And I go to the casino
I don't think I I would run out of money really really quick
If that happened
No, like all things
As long as you control yourself
Moderate yourself every all things in moderation
And you don't do anything insane
then you know if you go to the casino once in a while you can have some fun without being crazy and
have a couple of drinks and
But no, I I do not go to the casino every day
If you go to the casino trying to win money, that's that's not what you're doing. You're doing it. That's not correct
If you go to the casino, you should be going to the casino
to have fun to play
You can go play without doing
$500 blackjack hands it's you can play and have fun. You don't have to do that
But having said that
Uh, I am about 60 to 70 thousand dollars down
So
And I go, uh, I go like five days a week. I'm just kidding. I'm not i'm kidding. That's a joke
so should I start doing five thousand dollar blackjack hands if you have
50 million dollars in your checking account then it don't whatever. I can't tell you what to do
Streamer is encouraging chat to gamble. No, that's not what I said
Don't first of all don't do it unless you're old enough
And only gamble if you know that you're you can control
Potential urges that you'll have in the casino
All casinos are designed in a way to keep you there. They don't have any windows
They're all a mess of of a layout to make sure you get lost
Don't go in there alone going there with a few friends
Because then you get to keep each other honest so you can't just say you can't just sit there and be like
Ah, this is a new slot machine that I want to play just keep going keep going keep going. No, keep going
Somebody can like be like hey man. What are you doing? Ah another
In nine years of vegas. I literally never played a single table game
I went to movies buffets arcades tons of stuff. It had nothing to do with gambling. That's another thing about las vegas
It's not just gambling
There's so much stuff here. There's so many shows. There's some insane movie theaters. They are life lessons
Just don't go overboard with anything that would I would say that about anything
You know just because your car
can drive
Technically over 120 miles per hour on the highway. You're not going to do it
You're gonna go 60
65 whatever the speed you're gonna go like 60 to 70, right just because you can doesn't mean you will or should
Speed limits 80 in nevada. No, it's not nevada
All right. Good night everybody
Last one john horns for one dollar. Just want to let you know how much you mean to us
We genuinely give a fuck about you and hope you have continued success in the future. You earned it
It's it's incredible to hear that that there's that many people that are kind of rooting for me
uh, it floors me every time and
That kind of support pushes me to want to achieve the things that I want to achieve
So thank you so much everybody
Cheers to that. I'll see you guys tomorrow same time around three o'clock pacific
We will finish space channel five part two
And maybe just maybe just a little bit of crazy taxi for old times sake. Don't you know what I mean?
Have a great night guys. See you tomorrow. Take care