Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary and tonight
I'm gonna play as the Engineer. It's been a while since, but I don't even know how long it's been
since a proper engineer gameplay commentary. I have no idea, but it's gonna be using the Frontier
Justice. I've put a couple clips together where this one I get 25 crits in the thing and I go
absolutely insane and the next clip is on offense with I think like 13 or 14 crits, but that's what
I'm showcasing here and it's gonna sit in the background. This is gonna be an update video
on where I've been and what I've been doing and where have you been for like eight days. It's
been like eight days. You don't go away for eight days unless something important's happening, so
let me explain. The reason why I've been gone so long is because I've been working on
some projects on and off of YouTube and the one we're going to talk about today is primarily
the one that's off of YouTube and something that I need to do, something that I want to do,
that I've always really wanted to do with myself, but never really jumped at the opportunity to do
it until now and maybe me talking about it a little bit might pique your interest in you doing
it as well or getting involved in something like this in your area. Volunteer work. Volunteering
primarily for me at an animal shelter. I'm starting today, it is Tuesday, I'm recording
this video, so I'm going to be starting there today as a volunteer at my local animal shelter
to help out with whatever I can, whether that be walking the dogs, playing with the cats, feeding
the animals, maybe helping out a little bit financially in some places. We need five pounds
of this dog food. I'll go get it. We need 20 pounds. We need like two 20 pound bags.
That's what I'm going to start to do with myself for at least a few hours a week and the whole
point of me doing this stemmed from I had this epiphany in the shower. A lot of you guys I know
I told you about how like when I take a dump or when I'm in the shower I think about things
and a lot of you guys might not know. I mean some of you do. I don't even remember if I talked about
it or not. My dog Otto, you haven't seen a whole lot of him and there's no real reason for that.
It's not like oh Otto is in such trouble. He has seizures and he's had a couple of real big ones
that were really really scary scary things where he had to be brought down to the ER.
He's had to go to the vet a bunch of times. We're trying to figure out what's what's wrong.
He's okay though. Like don't get don't take this as there's something really wrong with my dog.
He's fine. He's actually lying down right here next to me. He's okay. But I had this epiphany
where I said man it sucks when you an animal in your house or something that you love you watch
it get sick or you watch it and when we were in the ER I watched dogs come in cats come in they
looked one was like limping it was just like damn man like how do I help that how do I do something
about that like at least personally for me it was something I needed to do and I always thought that
volunteer work I don't have the time for volunteer work. I can't make that time. I just can't do it
but then you then you realize let me look at my schedule here oh today wake up at 11 a.m.
check eat food at 11 30 or to check and play video games for six hours oh yeah that's good
that's busy work that's I've got that and go to sleep I just don't got the time I don't have the
time to do and that's that's where the epiphany came from. I love animals. I love working with
animals. I love talking to people. Why not? Why not give at least like a couple hours a week to
this? I don't know how it's going to go from here. I'm not sure if I'm going to be doing this more
closer to part-time in the future. I really have no idea. This is just a trial period for me guys.
I'm just trying to find more things to do and that's what I was talking about leave it like
throwing it to you guys like do any of you guys volunteer and if you do maybe you could give me
some of your experiences volunteering and maybe some things that I need to know going into
volunteer at an animal shelter or if you're going to volunteer at like your local homeless shelter
or something these are things that I am a total noob at and if you have any information on it I
would love to hear it and I'm sure some other people would love to hear your experiences as
well and we're trying to push positivity here right now guys I guess I'm trying to say if you
have time now I know a lot of people don't have time to volunteer you're working nine to five
every day maybe you have two jobs maybe you're in school you're in college and you just don't
you don't have a whole lot of time you're taking a bunch of classes or something this is not a video
to guilt trip people into volunteering at a anywhere please I really hope nobody takes
this video like that it's mainly just to say in general it'll probably make you feel a lot better
about things it'll probably make you feel more positive I've heard stories that volunteering
is so rewarding when you do it because it just makes you feel so much better about the world
and you're trying to make something happen you're trying to change the world in as small a way as
you might think it is you're still doing it and that's pretty much where I'm going to leave this
video I just want to do a little update on where I've been the last week and what I've been doing
I've also got a couple of secret projects that I'm working on that I really hope you guys enjoy
that's been kind of going through into the pipeline and there's a lot of things I've been
doing on and off YouTube like I said in the beginning this is one of them and yeah just
an update of where I've been and hopefully you guys what am I doing no seriously what the fuck
am I doing right now um anyways guys I'll see you guys all next time uh take care everybody
and think about what I said goodbye