That shit does not want you to know what the fuck was that you all the new players learn and they get used to it.
It's really bad. All right.
I'm live now.
Can somebody confirm in my house Russell?
Oh shit.
We're missing a player.
Yeah, how do you sprint?
Is it autosprint?
You're always moving the full speed as long as you're autoing you slow down.
That's the only way you slow down or someone says we literally don't have our fifth player.
Oh, you're like 12.
Yeah, how do I learn my abilities?
How do I see my bill?
Okay, got it.
Can you press K to read them or just add the F keys?
F1, F2, F3.
All right guys.
Hi, it's me, German985.
Welcome.
I told you about this smite tournament that I'm in.
I'm going to give you just a very quick rundown of what's going to happen here.
So everybody in chat can yell at the other people that come into chat in like 10 minutes
yelling at me as to why I have not like crashed car and laughed about it.
Like we did a couple nights ago.
This is a very important tournament.
This is a hundred thousand dollar smite tournament.
Mizkif is hosting it.
I'm taking this pretty seriously.
I'm going to try as best I can.
No cam.
We're doing I'm in a call.
I got my team here.
I'm a team captain.
He's doing his team.
Yeah, I'm doing my TF2 voice because I have to be able to talk and then tell people where I am.
And yes, I'm in my underwear and playing completely naked because I wasn't ready.
Couldn't take a shower.
It started to kind of early Pacific time.
So I've literally have I've got hardly clothes on.
So just for you to know that.
Okay.
So I'm going to jump back in here.
We have my best friend poke.
You should probably saw from that tweet.
He's what is poke playing?
I guess we just go over it in the roles.
It's me sure for poke no-go Russell and our coaches weekend.
You can I'm sure you probably watching poke stream probably by this point.
All right.
Here we go.
But I yeah, I'm going to be serious.
No cam.
I'm not going to be like, oh, hey, look at me.
I'm a fucking dickhead.
No, this is serious gamer time right now.
This is a hundred thousand dollar tournament.
All right.
You guys get it.
You get it.
This is just my perspective.
If you want to go watch the big stream, that's on ms.
Kiff's channel.
Why don't you stay here?
Okay.
All right.
Look at me.
That's my support character Aries.
All right.
Yes.
And I will be like, you like pulling everyone in with chains.
I am.
I like being.
I like the chains.
I like the whips.
I like all of it.
You know what I'm saying?
Oh, yeah.
All right.
So who all right.
So who's going to play what are we locking in?
Let's lock it in.
I'm support.
I'm Aries.
Okay.
I'm jungle.
I'm Baka Sora.
Okay.
I'm 80 Carrie.
I'm my plea Artemis.
I'm whatever.
I feel like God.
No, I did.
I did.
I'm playing right now.
The only thing is, is when I, when I attack people, the fucking
blood splatters bigger than my forehead.
So like, well, how do I get that off?
Like, yeah.
I'm playing.
You got banned.
Yeah.
It says the owner of this website, high red studios has banned
you temporary from accessing accessing this website.
Refreshing a little bit too much.
Who are you playing?
No Cosmo is a Nami.
What does this do?
It might be the skin.
You have one.
If you do, did you buy a skin?
Did you have a skin on?
Yeah.
This thing see that no, it's crits.
You see it.
I'm going in.
I'll check.
Yeah.
I am not going to lie.
I need drops.
Yeah.
I think it works now.
I drops enabled.
Can I can anybody cry?
Is it a drops actually enabled on my channel at least?
Yeah, they are.
Okay.
You guys drops are enabled.
That would be embarrassing if they weren't.
Oh, you're talking about the numbers on your screen that are
huge.
Yeah.
Can't change that thing.
So now that you mentioned it, I mean double check the numbers.
That shit is fucking huge.
Oh, try now.
You can't jump.
That's awkward.
Yeah, you can you can you can it should be low.
You just can't auto and jump.
Yeah.
No, you can't use abilities and do it at the same time.
Okay.
It's combat scaling.
I think is what you want to turn down.
It's under user interface.
All right.
Yeah, again, for people just coming in now, this is again,
I'm going to make this really clear.
This is a gamer stream.
I've got a team here.
I'm the team captain.
We've been practicing.
Well, we did a little bit last night.
This is $100,000 tournament, no cam, no comedy.
This is not going to be that's not going to be a funny stream.
This is going to be like a we're playing the game trying to
win a hundred thousand goddamn dollars.
Okay, there's a hundred thousand dollars.
You understand I'm not going to like I'm not going to jump
into a tower and talk about like Dunkin Donuts today.
Like this is for $100,000 that not today.
I'm being serious today.
They're only thousand viewers.
That can't be right.
That actually can't be right.
Now.
I only have a thousand viewers right now.
Whatever.
Okay, this is a gamer stream.
But yeah, I'm actually going to try to take it seriously.
We'll have fun.
Don't worry.
Green screen stream is in like two days.
Relax.
True.
Also like what combos well with Ares anything?
Yeah, they both do both of those will be fine.
Artemis like you'll do a lot for the lane as Ares you should
clear and do a lot.
So Artemis will be fine.
And if you want to go for kills, you also do a lot of damage
on Ares.
Okay, so let me just for my brain again speed attack mid lane
then go wherever I want.
Make sure those three minute timers bang, bang, bang.
Make sure blue is dropped for solo every time.
That's I've got that right, right?
Yep.
All right.
Got it.
Yeah, I think I think I understand this character a lot.
This is like a perfect character for me.
That works go if you can like close out of this and I want
you to go in a regular game just so you know where to start
like what to do at the very beginning of the game.
We have time.
Yeah, they said 330 would be when we started so it should
take like one minute.
Okay, so we have good sir three dirty as I'm like three
dirty EST.
Yeah, okay.
So I go to where go to you just go to training and go to
conquest.
I'm not going to buy the burger skin.
I don't even play with that character go to play and then
training.
This is in queue training and then conquest and then do easy
bots.
Just the first one and quick play.
Yeah, it'll start the game up.
These kids are fun sick guys.
I'm going to tell you I'm just going to be really realistic
here.
People will we win the smite tournament?
I think at least one or two people have just installed
the game an hour ago on the team.
I don't I don't think we're going to get to the end will
do probably be okay.
We'll probably do.
All right.
I can't buy the cheeseburger skin.
I don't play with the cheeseburger character.
I believe I believe would you say retirement?
Stream wait, would you say I need to know what you said?
Oh embarrassment stream it.
I'm telling you my I might surprise some people here
because I the last couple days I really talked I took this
pretty seriously.
I was like what character do I want to play?
I want to get familiar with it.
But guys I've played smite for like a thousand hours.
This is obviously like five six seven years ago now, but
whatever.
I think I'll do okay.
And look if I'm if I go 0 and 10 then then I'll buy then
I'll tell a couple of jokes.
Okay, and then we can relax.
I think we've got a good chance.
I really do although not maybe not the first game if we're
playing the top seed first.
So this will be a great indication if we do.
Okay, if we actually beat this team, apparently this is
one of the better teams, right?
You know what I'm saying?
But what I'm saying is essentially is this free points.
I don't think we're going to win the tournament, but I
could be wrong.
I'm just excited to participate should be fun.
It's probably auto.
No, no your two is what you want at the beginning.
Oh, so you want two and then one then three you'll level
your three second.
Just so you have a safety ability to like run away, but
you're going to match your two your one your alt and then
your three.
So just one just curious.
Should I be should I be auto build as Aries or should I
have a specific build?
Realistically, I'll write you out a build right now.
It's trying to help you because I don't know what the
auto builds are building and everything.
So weird why I mean, I was just going to look up a build
so I do appreciate that you also.
Yeah, this game apparently this jungler because I'm a
jungler.
I figured that because we were talking in the in the
before a couple days ago.
It was like, okay, who knows how to play the game?
It's like I do sure for does I think poke said he played
for a little bit Russell said he's played it like years
ago, but I think like me and sure for had the most game
knowledge, right?
So it's like, okay, I so I kind of had to play jungle
even though I'm you know, we're talking we're talking
Little League, right?
If you take the best Little League player in the world,
he's going to get struck out by a Major League Baseball
player.
I'm just that's just a fact.
So right.
That's what we're doing.
What do you mean wrong?
And by the way, they're all these are all gamers in the
practice last night sure for was fucking dominating poke
dominating.
I'm not concerned.
I think we're going to be fine.
It's I'm going to turn out to be the Little League batboy.
I'm not even on the Little League team.
You'll see or whenever you can safely just grab that go
back to your lane.
And then whenever that blue buff respawns you want to do
that every single time.
And I should be just I should just upgrade one three and
then two.
Well, obviously for whenever I can but okay, and then
no-go.
I just type the build in the chat.
It's the same build folks going so you're just going to
do that.
Same thing.
Both the first second third and it doesn't matter about
last hitting.
It gives you extra gold if you all this whole time.
I was like, whatever.
Oh, no, I got a blast it then you don't in this game.
You don't do it like you definitely want to try but you
don't do it like League.
It's not you sit there.
You wait if you just want to power clear the lane as fast
as possible.
I think we're getting a we should be getting in Lobby
soon, right?
Oh, it is a way your autos are a ways.
Yeah, they go through creeps.
And then I'm not my way my my to do.
Yep.
So you'll just auto into it and it should clear very quick.
You're one of the fastest clearing character.
So what are we doing?
Whoa, what happened?
We have 10 minutes.
So they said we were I think you guys are going to be in
a party or in the custom game pretty soon.
Great.
I have not my mom my notifications turned off.
Why would that even happen?
So we should we should get in a party then right?
Okay, let's do that because somebody just tried to like
add me to their fucking party.
And there's some we got it.
We got to go away from that.
I think I have all of your in-game names, but I don't
have Russell.
I don't have you and I don't have no go.
You want to type your in-game names?
I'm watching.
I'm watching Russell Russell, right?
Oops, my mic Russell is literally like down in the game
right now and watching the tutorial.
What'd you say?
You're downloading the game right now and watching a YouTube
tutorial.
How to play smite.
What are you doing?
I've had this game since 2013.
Are you doing man?
Excuse me.
Wait, are you guys waiting for me?
Yeah, just waiting on the video.
Are you watching the in-game embedded YouTube video?
Do they still do that?
Guys?
I don't I don't I want to go on his down.
Are you sure I'm in pokes team or in his party that that was
me super me automatically and then you're gonna want to
turn that off.
If you press look, I think it's Kay.
Are you in game still?
Yeah, press K and see if it says that right there.
And if not, it'll turn off that's auto skill.
You can turn that off.
And then you can close that.
So who are we missing in the party?
He's in a game.
Yeah, I can leave.
I can leave.
I'm gonna leave.
I think they're gonna give us they're gonna give us the
the ID.
I think soon.
Is anyone nervous?
I'm just curious.
I'm not saying I am but I was asking if anyone here.
Oh God, I hear no, I've already accepted.
If we go if we go like oh and 30 because there's a voice
chat in game.
Why don't why are you like unhappy about that?
Sure for because I don't want to hear anyone twice.
Oh, okay.
Well, that's understandable.
I want to hear you guys only once for pure clarity.
Okay.
I just did push the toggle.
So you should hear me twice.
No, I just have the Jabberwockies the Jabberwockies.
Are you talking about stuff?
That's not who I was thinking of.
Tell them to watch your smite video.
I dropped your starter items in there and then your full
build is the one right after.
Each of the volume.
Okay.
All right.
Sounds good.
Should I turn off auto build before we get in the game?
Then?
Yeah, I would you can do it in settings.
I think if anybody wants to know how to play that's a pretty
good tutorials back in like 2012.
If anyone was curious how to play the game.
You have smite Wario's.
Yeah, I bought I bought this back in 2013.
So I probably watched it.
Yeah, it's guides for actually have a guide for Aries if
you want to watch it.
It's probably got some good tips in it.
I'm going to go watch that right now immediately.
It's on your second or first channel.
It's on the first first channel.
It's definitely worth watching.
I'd say it's not something that I wish I deleted but it's
funny deleted.
Oh, yeah.
If you guys aren't in the game by the way, you can press
escape and then go to guides and turn everything you want
off all right there.
Gold Fury is like very guide.
Yeah, do it says guides.
I have an okay.
Let me just with with you guys here.
I have an Aries video, right?
I did like three or four of them didn't I?
Self promo.
I don't give a fuck about that video.
I would delete it right now if I could.
Don't I have?
Yeah, I did.
Did I delete it?
I might have deleted it is just the Anubis one the only
one that's left.
Is it still there?
Oh man, is it still?
Oh, it's there.
Okay, that's funny.
All right, let's go.
Are your abilities at the queue?
No, sorry, it's two two first two first two level your
three of ones and then match your one match your two
your one you're all your three.
Wait, what's the title of the video?
It's this what is it?
Oh, man.
What does it say?
This dude's a beast.
Holy shit.
I was trying so hard Aries God of War.
This dude's a beast.
Might be I hope I hope he watches it and hey by the way,
I'm gonna act like yeah, like did you get anything from
that?
No, like yeah, did you get something from that?
Like I hope you did.
I think I'm kidding.
You know, hopefully you learned something.
Q w e r q w e r.
Yeah, that's like way better for me.
Hold on settings abilities.
You just can't change your w or you won't be able to walk
I was gonna say it's gonna I feel like that's gonna fuck
with you more.
Are you sure you want to switch this no-co?
No, 100% because I played League for a really long time.
All right, man.
I believe you.
You're breaking your no comedy rule.
We're not playing the no comedy serious.
Rule is only for when I'm in the actual game.
I'm not probably not gonna look at chat really much at all.
The no comedy rules only for game moments.
Are y'all getting the battle pass?
I think I bought it already.
I don't know how much even is this in like money?
Wait, how do you battle past trying to think?
It's q w e r is League.
What's 16,000 gems.
I've never had this many gems in my whole life.
This whole game.
Do you feel freaking rich right now?
I just I am like I look up at there and I'm just like I just
I bought the 400 gem bakasura metal skin.
It's like I kind of feel like I need to have one of the crazy
ones.
Does box or have a crazy one?
That's some pretty good skins.
They're not nuts.
The craziest one.
You probably can't buy unless they gave it to you.
This is the one I'm going to be using sick.
Oh, wait, I can play.
Is this the stranger things?
Oh, yeah, special nuts crazy.
You walk around kind of creepy.
I don't but I don't know.
Okay, can I buy this if I've never seen an episode of stranger
things?
Yeah, I mean they just look like little monster things.
This one's cool.
This one's too cool for me though.
I kind of like them.
I missed this bakasura like I told you last night.
Who's the burger?
Well, then play the OG bakasura, bro.
I know.
Is the burger good?
Yeah, he's pretty good.
He's like kind of easy.
Like when you're solo playing you don't really dial up.
You're a support though.
I would anyone know that's the character to goddamn burger.
There's skins like that all the time.
Reminds me of the old was it the old TF2 thing they used to
say if we want to make sure we keep the silhouettes the same.
We want to make sure you can tell who it is from across the
whole map.
I don't want to join a fucking fan club.
Get out.
I just finished watching the germ of it.
I think I'm good on Ares.
You think you're good to go?
Yep, I got this.
I think we're going to win this tournament.
How do you block all notifications from coming up?
IDK.
I don't know because I can't do it.
Apparently is that going to pop up in the games?
Hope not.
No, hope not.
If it does you'll find out the the the death toll transcendence
when demon that's all for me.
Yep, you and that's first second third like that's in order
and fully build the item before you start another item.
How do you have the crazy skins?
So if you are in game and you type in like you can search at
the top transcendence till it'll all be there.
Can I buy death toll?
There we go.
I'm on D&D.
No, you already have a starter.
You only buy one starter item that I'm going to sell and then
sell and do this, right?
So, okay.
This is the other God I would be playing.
Why can't I buy it?
I'm back with them are locked.
Are you in the base?
Yeah, are you clicking on like one of the higher ones like
death's embrace or something instead of no, I'm literally
clicking death's goal.
Should I get this one?
You have the gold you have six with the old.
I have five thousand.
You can't change your starter item.
I sold it because you left the base already.
Yeah, that's why it's because you already left the base.
Are you would buy one?
That's your item for the game.
Would it be weird if in Miz Kiff's smite tournament?
I played as Miz Kiff and just did all the voice spams and
was like annoying.
Does it really matter as long as you don't think it's weird?
You do you man.
Exactly.
It's from let your means be dreams.
Who's Miz Kiff?
I don't know.
I can I got a random DM.
I just didn't know what to say.
I was like, yeah, I've played smite before.
It's not like I begged him in public to make sure I was able
to play today.
Are you trying to make some money?
Yeah, let me know when I got to leave.
What's the first place team win?
I think this is very important.
Okay, each 12k each person.
Yep.
Yeah, 70k for first place.
Wow.
So how do we win?
If you if you buckle up and don't be a problem.
All right, that sounds good then.
Yeah, we wanted the best side of you, man.
No, I am going to be the best.
That's the thing.
Like I genuinely believe I am the best.
Okay, we're fucked.
Oh, this monster has a nice butt.
Dude, this skin is crazy.
Say monster.
You know, I thought you talked about.
What are you talking about me?
Yeah.
No, you want to see what I'm talking about?
Go to the chest.
What imperial?
What a chest imperial chest.
Look at the fourth one.
Where the chest in the store.
Chess Imperial.
Yeah, look for Imperial.
I see it.
I see a similar dog.
The fourth character the siren song.
Chase, is that who you're talking about?
You're saying the siren is hot.
No, turn around.
Wait, it's not me.
You're making it weird.
The longer this takes.
Wait, where is it?
Is it chest?
But are you good?
Where is it in the store?
Nice.
It's just like there.
It's like they drew that.
Yes, you got a nice figure.
I would say.
Well, they don't.
Do I have do I have a do I have 27 chest open?
Sorry, I made this way.
You have a bunch of chest open to you.
I do.
Where are they?
You see the little gift box at the bottom, right?
You press that and you go to chests.
Lobby's up.
Oh shit.
All right.
We're gonna get in the lobby.
So we need who we're missing somebody here.
You're missing me.
Can somebody pull?
How did you get Russell in here?
Hello.
What?
Sorry.
What Russell you're in here.
You're in the party, right?
Yeah, my name is I'm done with Xbox.
Okay.
I mean, I've got an old account after the series s came out.
I mean, that was a phenomenal card is a is a Nami is fucking
sick.
Yeah, that's like a tier five.
That's the highest tier skin.
We got to get no go.
We got to get you in here.
What's your in-game name?
It's no cocoa, but with zeros as the owes.
Okay, we add you for who is a Nami now guys.
Don't forget to buy skin.
You have to make sure that we have nice skins for our characters.
But isn't on me like her skins change like the Queen of the
cards.
They there's different versions of her like what skin you talking
about wait Royal come in my way that you that's me.
Okay, I'm sorry.
All right.
So can I just join with this party now?
Yep.
Okay, if all five of you are there, you'll just go to play and
then go to custom and find their game and I think you need
to know the password.
Yeah, it's in here.
That's actually sick.
Did you see even place my?
Yeah, with rotations around play.
They just make sure I don't show that on screen.
We have no idea how it's all like he plays occasionally.
It's am I am I cool to am I cool to show this screen now?
Is that all right?
There's nothing on here, right?
As long as you don't show them the password.
You're yeah, okay.
How do we not show them the password?
I had died to do it.
We were in a party.
So we got honest with you.
Wait.
Is there a way to turn off like notifications and stuff or
no, I just push go to put on D&D go to your top right click
on your name and go to like friends list and actually go to
friends list bottom, right?
It's like the two people stand next to each other.
Okay, just put yourself on do not disturb.
I have one friend.
Yeah, but as soon as your shit they're gonna fucking spam you.
My voice is junk.
So, okay.
So this is this is the team that we need to be concerned
with right?
That's what you're saying.
It's Mendo, right?
Mendo's team.
Sunny you see you.
I forget Sunny's team.
Okay, that's Artemis build you gave me, right?
Yeah, that is the Artemis.
Yes, sir.
I'm not scared at all.
You should be I have an Artemis video.
No, you don't have an Artemis video.
I looked at all your smite videos.
Yeah, I didn't want to do the stranger things one.
I feel like I'm like look like a default enemy from a random
FPS game.
Yeah, you would it would be cringe.
It's a doom enemy.
But look, okay in the show stranger things.
I'm sure it's a cool and I've never seen it, but I just for
this game with like a bunch of gods fighting each other
and like a bakasura and I feel like this is you kind of a guy
can I unlock the Queen of cards?
Um, you it's all I don't know how many gems they give you
but you gave me 8,000 or is 10,000 really that should be
enough if it's available if you go back to buy all yeah,
if you click on the skin, it should say like this much to
buy everything and you have to buy everything.
Oh what no, it's 9,240.
I don't have enough.
Okay.
I sounds like you need to swipe boy.
I literally am going to minimize my chat at when once
the game starts because I know I'm going to look over there
because I'm going to miss something.
I'm going to miss like I'm going to miss click on something
and I'm going to see a bunch of Omega wells and it's going
to fuck with me.
So I can not gonna look but you get affected that much by
a little bit of Omega lulz.
Oh, yeah, of course I do.
I look over if I have something goes wrong and I see Omega
low like he sucks so bad.
I get affects me.
I can't look at it.
Okay.
What if they all start saying poggers?
He did it instead.
Then I get way too overconfident.
Then you're yeah, exactly.
You're like, oh fuck.
I did a good play.
I got to do something else.
I don't know what I'm going to do and then chat stops blogging.
You're like fuck now.
Very affected by the emotes coming at you.
Yeah, of course.
I can see the Omega lulz in the corner of my eye without even
looking at it.
Yeah, that's what I mean.
What if you saw them spamming?
Oh my God.
It's lacari chasing you through the boreal winter.
Please run and find cover.
He has bad intentions.
I would have no idea what the fuck that meant.
They did me dirty, bro.
I have that emote just shortened.
He chasing.
Yeah, that's too much to type.
Wait, that's an emote.
Yeah, you want to see it.
You can have an emote.
That's that long.
Well, it's like a third part.
Oh, that's insane.
I think my smite crashed.
Oh, oh wait.
So draft that means we are they mirrors in a draft?
Any any devs are watching?
I would like a thousand more gems, please.
They typed it out.
Let me read this real quick.
No, there's no bands.
You're doing draft just because it's an order pick.
Okay, but so but they can still be a mirror in a draft.
Think so.
Yeah, no, there shouldn't be no mirror picks.
That's why the like the orders actually matters.
And when you pick it matters, they can take your shit
or you can take theirs.
Okay, I got it.
I don't think they will.
I think I know what they're going to play.
Yeah, they probably know everything we're doing, dude.
What are they doing?
Dude.
Oh my God.
I got an idea.
What if we do what if we do five Winston's and just fucking
run that the by the point we five Winston's we just all jump
and we all go to like mid tower.
That'd be poggers.
I know they actually can't I don't think so.
Wait, there's a character called Winston.
No people did not like that one.
I looked it up.
Why would they not like that?
I don't know.
Where's Miz Kiff?
I want a personal hello and I want a personal in every team
voice chat him coming in and introducing the event.
Where is he?
Then he would be introducing it right now.
Actually, he's casting it.
Oh, I thought he was a player.
I did too.
He was supposed to play and he's supposed to coach or cast
and then he wasn't going to do anything.
And then I don't know what happened.
So there's no bands.
Are you able to just be in the call with us the whole time?
It's the good thing.
You can't be in the call the entire time.
Yes, this is going to be interesting.
Well, there are no picks.
There's no bands.
There's orders like the like what order you should pick shit.
I bought the bundle.
And I can kind of run you through what they're going to be
doing with their pigs.
So if you guys want to weaken your streaming, right?
Yep.
So if you guys want to watch somebody kind of put the hands
in their head and like kind of look down for how long the
tournament is because that you're going to be like screaming
at us to do something like just you're going to be like,
oh my God, please go that way and we can't hear you.
So we can you want to go watch the disappointment.
It'll be on weekends.
I thought you were I thought you were here holding our hand
the entire time and I thought that's what it was going to be
a first to you.
Oh my God.
This is a whole different like ball game.
I feel like I'm playing a different game right now.
So now you're scared.
No, I'm not scared.
Of course not.
I still do I have time to get the tea.
No, you have no time to do anything.
You have to sit here now.
Who's drinking tea here me?
You a tea guy?
Yeah, I do like tea.
But what type of tea are you drinking matcha?
Wait matcha tea is good.
I actually I actually like matcha tea.
All right.
There you go.
Yeah.
All right.
I like green tea.
I like I don't like Jasmine tea though.
It's a little too much.
Yeah, I'm not a big fan of Jasmine but green teas.
All right.
When I was younger, I used to like a lot of green tea.
Why are we in queue for seven minutes?
It just says that because they're still like announcing teams and shit.
Okay.
Yeah.
So don't be nervous poke like chill bitch.
Damn it is like perfume.
It is like perfume freaking out.
Okay, we're going to get Mendo team.
Leans back with you.
Yep.
Oh no, every time every time I drink green green tea with Jasmine.
I just feel like I'm walking through the perfume section of a Macy's.
I like getting black tea in my boba.
That's good.
Oh, I bought the juicy is a Nami scan.
I'm going fucking deep a 9200 green gems later.
So you swiped?
No, I didn't swipe.
I had some extra epic coins.
So I only had to put nine dollars.
Yeah, dude, they gave me they gave me some some nom noms epic coins
or volt whatever the fuck you want to go in the epic.
Wait, so are we all playing at the same time or is it one team at a time?
I mean two teams at a time.
I'm pretty sure it's round robin.
So you all have to be like there's no way you aren't playing at the same time.
Okay, so are they on the main broadcast?
Are they just going to be jumping around or are they just picking a game in each round?
Guess is they're going to pick a game but they're they're like production.
Dude is from higher from smite.
So I don't know.
He might be a little bit into it.
Oh my god.
Oh my glob.
Why can't we just do like a rock-paper-scissors?
They do these queues 10 minute queue high res.
What the fuck is this 10 minute queue?
Hey, the queue times are completely fine.
And this game is pop.
Wait, what single limb?
That's what my dad say.
So it's not best of three.
It's like wait, we're going to get knocked out right now potentially.
No, you're going to win.
Wait, I thought we were playing everybody once.
No, German.
We're going to knock out the other team right now being trolled.
You have to be getting trolled.
There's no way.
Yeah, if you like it's group stages.
So it has to be where you have to everybody.
Well, if you don't it's just dumb.
Yeah, it would make no sense.
I think what they mean by single limb round Robin is you face everyone
on your group once top to go bottom to leave type thing and losers
bracket if this is going to be a long tournament then, huh?
As long as the strap in.
All right.
I got a pee because I you can't play a tournament with a
I have to there's no way I would be actually wait if you don't
pee though playing under pressure actually makes you play better
sometimes I actually made a video about that belt and then come
back.
Yeah.
So what was your your hypothesis?
Well, my here's my hypothesis inclusion.
I'm drinking a bunch of tea.
So right now I have to pee now and I'm drinking a bunch of tea
or now I have a pee right now.
Do you know that if you have to pee all more often and you pee
like really fast like you know, I know but but but listen listen
to me.
I'm the captain you listen to the captain.
Yes, sir.
If you drink, okay, if you drink too much if you have to pee
and you keep drinking water and shit, then I'm trying to get
in front of the pee.
That's going to have to happen in an hour when we're in the
game and I can't leave you soon.
But if you keep holding it in your balls are going to explode
because pee is sort of the balls.
All right.
I'll be right back.
You already pissing with you.
I will pin.
Okay, I'm pissing there.
I'll be back now.
Just leave the chat open.
Whatever vacation beads and agus annual do I have to buy
those or set those they're free.
So when you start you get one of them level one and then
level 12 you get the other one.
Which one do I get first the purification beads get them
in the exact order not going to lie.
That sounds dirty just beads to get out of my purification
beads.
Do they do they really think this through when they made
that I'm not really a beads guy.
I'm more of a plug kind of guy.
Oh, okay.
Yeah, maybe they should rename it to purification plug.
Yeah, 100% better.
Oh, hi res.
Hello.
They're very quiet real pissing.
Yeah, everyone penis just peeing.
Wait, what the fuck is that slipknot skins available?
Yeah, you know my cousins and sublet slipknot be trolling.
Yeah, no, he's actually one of the main singers.
I don't believe that.
I don't believe it either.
His name is James.
Oh wait.
No, that actually does make sense.
Wait.
No, that actually is his cousin.
Yeah, he's an asshole though.
He doesn't give us never give the family money at all.
It's fucked up.
All my homies.
Hey James, and we all listen to eat.
Now.
What do you guys listen to?
I can't listen to anything.
I got a double all my phone.
You don't be doing it yet.
Yeah, true Russell.
When you got any song man, your last song.
Come on, man, dude.
Listen, I'm not even kidding.
I want to get back in the booth.
Okay, I need to prove myself.
You know, I got something to prove.
I'm like a little baby.
Let's go.
Let's go do this week.
Do you guys do play three games?
By the way, what three you have three matches.
You're gonna we're playing back to back to back against them.
No, no, no once against this team and then Amiros team and
then tech don't seem and then whoever wins the most out of
those goes to finals probably finals or you have like semi
finals or some shit and her has awesome skins.
Fuck looks like you need to swipe a little bit more.
Yeah, no, but I can't get the skins said.
Yeah, what the fuck is my oh got it.
You can't you can't get the fucking funny over there, man.
Yeah, it's hilarious.
Anything you want to share with class?
I don't know why I laughed with my mic open.
That is actually really rude of me guys.
Yeah, and now you have to explain I went into Amarus chat
and I said she sucks and that she's gonna lose and she
insulted me and I thought it was funny.
How did she insult you?
She said what the fuck Russell you did not open up a spine
until this morning, which that is not true.
I don't know why she said that is true actually all week
literally what she said is true.
So I have more hours than you sure for I'm literally a higher
level than you in this game somebody's being toxic.
I have more real life than you children.
Wait, so who's being toxic swallow it on my own terms.
Somebody told me to calm down who's being toxic.
I'm the time the team captain.
I need to know who my team needs to start providing some
order here.
What are you doing fighting who you're not even listening
for and Russell.
Okay.
All right guys.
I didn't tell you I think I'm the best Aries that has ever
stepped foot in this game.
Why is that?
I just like I played today and I'm like, holy hell.
I'm so self dude.
Whoever says let's I'm the captain mates up.
It's not captain at all.
What's that from?
It's from the Caribbean.
No, I'll do it again.
I'll do it one more time.
I got a job.
Yeah, that's not incorrect.
I don't know the most famous line.
No, I'll do it again.
Do the line.
Whoever says that they are the captain is no captain at all.
Why does that sound like fucking?
Oh, that's that's the burning on Connery.
Why does it sound like burning crusade?
That's correct.
King Anduin win says it to thrall.
Guys, we're in.
Here we go.
All right.
Can they see my what I'm picking?
What do we do guys at the top of the screen?
It says no tank.
We have a problem.
Why is he slick is picking I just wild card, dude, just pick
fucking cupid and to freak him out.
Wait, what if they pick can I can we have same legends same
people?
No, no, we're gonna hope they don't.
All right, so it's my so one each or one too.
Am I picking right now?
I think it's me of your hunter.
You guys can trade with each other.
So I would pick the two hunters.
See right now.
Nami right now.
Oh shit.
We lock in lock is a Nami.
Can you lock it in because those are the ones you're worried
about them or you can do the block as well.
Let's go.
What's it too late?
Yeah, I don't know.
It's our ruler guys.
The select things they're gonna pick it.
I've heard of this one step guy.
Oh, we've seen a Freya like any of us give a shit.
We all learned how to play one God like four days ago.
Oh the Freya how to counterpick that four days ago.
How about like 40 minutes ago?
Yeah, you're you're in a little more trouble than I think
everybody else.
If you want to pick is a Nami for me, that'd be like a great
guys.
You don't have to worry.
They're literally just all picking the stuff.
They were one trick and you don't have to worry anymore.
They're just most of your shit is big dirty like what you're
gonna play against by the way short for skin was $100.
I just want to make sure everyone knows.
Yeah, but I got it for free mofoca.
Oh free.
You're good for free.
Hello guys.
I'm getting told ruler into Freya.
Do it as the team captain.
I'd say do it.
Hey, okay.
Thank you.
Why did you pick?
I'm pretty sure Freya is going mid.
I might bug my skin is oh, there you go.
I pick now.
I I cannot see chat anymore.
I'm going to we need to I need to pay attention to over here
guys.
I'm sorry.
You're already referring to them even though you're not looking
at them anymore.
I know just whenever you can you're you have like lots of
extra time.
Yeah, I'm sure.
Why did you why did you have extra time?
They give you extra time in case something like you guys
wait, I'm trying to lock it in.
Oh and nobody locked in got it.
Yeah, you have like a set like time and then they can add
time.
Oh, that's cool.
They didn't want to remake if anybody else like just not
now just your chair is in the wrong settings.
I can Russell.
Hello.
What happened?
It's your game guys.
Am I good?
Hello.
Yeah, we're getting here.
We can hear you.
Are you fucking trolling my my ethernet?
Huh?
What are you doing?
What do you you're still here?
I'm in I'm in I'm in did you guys did your Wi-Fi pick it
up?
Yeah, why is it not letting me pick?
I think you your game doesn't close.
No way.
So so do we have to restart?
Will it just lock it in closing 10 seconds?
It'll close the whole lobby in 10 seconds.
Oh, he already picked Aries though.
Then you're good and he just needs to stay in game.
Oh, he's Aries.
So we're good Aries.
Yeah, you're good.
We have one so I cannot show me that I picked it though.
Just just stay in game.
Just wait for them to tell you Lobby started and then restart
your game.
We got a number one Vicky me that so the Freya and the
shing-10 are in your dual in no kill.
You're against the top character.
It's a balona.
They can disarm you.
I make you not lonely.
Fuck him alone.
Looking at that.
We might have the skin advantage here.
We have to $100 skins.
We're already like swagged on dude when you was your skin
$100.
You see that you see that baby.
Look at that shit.
Watch me transform again.
Dude when you locked that when you lock that is a Nami.
Holy shit.
Do the crowd went crazy when you just locked in the is a Nami
and so I'm just telling you, how do you know?
I can check here.
You can't hear them.
Oh, you can hear him.
We just got two countdowns.
When you guys are in loading screen tell Russell so you can
restart his game.
Wait, we are loading right now.
I'm still watching your stream and you you can't see anything
right?
Like you can loading now.
I'm loading.
Okay.
Good.
Then I'm good.
Then right.
You should be good and I have to win.
Good luck.
Thank you.
This guy's like a Freya one trick.
All right, so you guys you guys know what's going on here
with let's let's let's break this down.
I'm going guys.
Let's let's win.
Who am I?
I have to buy the starting amulet.
Yeah, get the starting item.
Which is beads.
That's my starting item.
Remember guys, let's go to our respective buffs and help each
other win.
Is this Peter Griffin?
I bought the wrong item.
Can I sell it?
I don't get everything back.
If you're in the fountain you can.
I bought desk toll and I bought purification beads.
Just don't leave the fountain.
How do I search?
What are you looking to buy?
Lost Lost
Artifact I think can you can you type in?
Oh shit.
I forgot a relic.
All right, every take a deep breath.
Just get the search bar should be at the top.
Don't know screaming.
Everything's fine.
We didn't even start at the game.
Focus off guys.
What are you doing?
Yes, sir.
All right.
I need here's what here's what I need.
I got short for you and me here at speed.
Yeah, we're here.
We're gonna move over to red.
Wait a minute.
I'm on the wrong side.
Wait, didn't I start?
It's in here now, huh?
You guys have to do the blue thing into the purple thing together.
Yes.
Where are you at?
Start at the blue thing and then move to the purple thing.
You both going to take that.
Yep.
I'm coming.
Which one's blue?
The one you're right beside right now.
All right, you guys ready?
Three two one action.
Camp right here.
I take this.
I have colorblind mode or something.
This is actually green.
I don't know.
Yeah, I'm going to try as hard as I fucking can.
I think you were supposed to take that.
I said that.
What did you take?
Russell doesn't deserve it.
Okay.
Now you try.
Let's fuck shit up.
I guess you can take this.
By the way, I only picked this character because he pukes.
Oh my bad Russell.
That was I'm colorblind as well.
So I guess I have to take it.
Bro, it's fine.
It's brought to the previous leg.
Wait, they're walking up to us.
Help.
We died.
Good luck.
Oh shoot them, bro.
Junglers going left side.
Yeah, Junglers going left.
Listen, I just farm and we win the game.
Yep, true.
Hey, hey, hey, hey, you guys ready?
You guys ready?
Right side.
Let's go.
Let's go some early bullshit.
I'm coming in early gang.
Let's go for it.
Wait, they have minions.
They have minions.
A lot of minutes don't matter.
Don't matter.
Why doesn't?
Okay, I'm here.
Oh, no, they know.
They know.
They know pushing you.
No, they know.
I'm dying.
Taking so much champion damage.
Minion damage.
Shit.
What?
Champagne damage?
You got a Bologna.
She's doing the totem.
I don't like that.
Guys, we're doing fantastic right now.
This is the this is this is how a winning team.
I got your award.
Jebaited.
I got Jebaited.
Junglers on my side.
They switched lanes.
Hey guys, we're okay.
We warmed up now.
Yep.
All right.
How's it has mid look?
I mean, we're just say, you know, a push war.
All right.
Watch this ready.
I'm watching.
Wait, if I'm in the tower ring, do I get less gold?
What was I watching?
No.
Do you want these mid camps?
Holden powers, right?
Maybe.
They're taking it.
We got it.
We got to stop them.
Yes, sir.
Really?
You let the burger take it.
You're scared of a burger.
You damage them.
You damage.
Okay, you be the burger.
How's solo doing right now?
Did they take did they take all my camps?
Probably.
What the fuck?
They're pushing us.
Probably did.
Block it for you.
I'm blocking for you.
I am dead.
Muscle.
Man, I tried to save you.
They went on when they went in on you and I tried to save you.
It's okay.
That's okay that we die though.
That's okay.
Yeah.
We can't lose a slick and want to know what's my beads do again.
It makes it so you can get out of any CC.
Got it.
What's my G do?
You don't have one yet.
That's it.
That's your second relic.
You get that later.
Oh, it looks like something's in my slot.
Yeah, it's like a little a little gem looking thing.
That's not real.
I'm going to get red for you.
It's any help on my side.
I'm mixing right side missing right side missing right side.
All right, I'll come left and after I get this block across over
mid house has mid look.
I'm just pushing him to tower constantly.
He's doing that.
I can't like get through it.
All right, I'm gonna I'm gonna come.
I'm gonna come left side.
We don't rent the windows anymore.
Just saying at all.
Why because like I mean that we're just both underleveled.
You said the balloon is really aggressive.
Yeah, really guys.
All right.
I'm coming.
Yeah, I don't think they know.
I think they're the team might think that I don't know the other
map like other side of the map exists.
I think we'll be all right coming to you guys poke.
I push him out a little getting going here.
They might have words.
Are they getting six gold?
Is it because I'm too close?
Yeah, back up back up.
There they can't.
Oh, yeah, they're at camp near to kill him.
Let's go.
Yeah, let's do it.
Let's do it.
I'm sorry.
Hey, hey, you got a money.
You can't go in earlier.
Yeah, sorry.
Sorry.
Next time.
I was good.
Oh my fucking god.
This balloon is got fucking baloney sandwich.
I'm dead.
Oh, he's pushing us.
He's pushing us.
I wasn't supposed to.
How was it?
What's happening to me?
I just got dunked on around right now.
We just got ganked.
Why did I just get thrown across them?
I'm going right.
No, I'm going left.
I like as all right, just farm.
Just farm farm farm.
We'll be good.
It's all right.
We only have four.
We're good.
I made a carry.
Do they have 80 carry?
Yeah, they free.
I'm so underleveled.
I got a farm so bad.
Yeah, well, I'm stronger.
And I'm older.
No, what the fuck is this thing?
Kill minions.
I'm dying.
My balloon is gone.
Yeah, I'm missing missing left.
Yo, I'm dying to this.
My balloon is basing.
I'm pushing tower.
Yeah, I would just push tower.
I have no gold.
I think we're on tower all game.
Maybe let's just clear these minions quick then.
Oh, she TP?
You want to get on mid camps?
Yes.
They're not there anymore.
Never mind.
Let's go get the red thing.
Purple thing.
Yeah.
I was going to try to help you gank, but it doesn't matter.
It's not up.
Red buff will be there when you get back.
We should get the side thing.
She's going to help.
She's going to do fire totem.
We want to help.
All right.
I have ult.
How you guys doing all right?
We're going to kill mid.
Yeah, let's try to get it.
Poseidon will start.
I mean, let me get, let me get, let me get more kills.
I got, I have to level up.
Yeah, they're outleveling us.
Poseidon is missing.
Or mid's missing, rather.
They're getting the side camp, just saying.
I'm just so desperate for XP right now.
Are those traps?
Oh, yeah.
I can see if we can gank someone or not.
Yeah.
Let's, are they, how far up are they in right side?
Sorry, my bad.
Are they, are they in lane?
Oh, here we go.
Wait, our teammates gone.
Our team, our team's gone.
Focus the Freya, if we can.
Yeah.
Wait, I can, I can push.
I can push.
I'm here.
Let's go.
Pick up, pick up.
Pull, pull, pull.
There it is.
All right.
Bring it back.
Bring, we can, we can bring it back.
We're good.
Good, good, good, good, good.
Oh, beautiful.
One tower, one tower here.
Back up, back to farm, back to farm.
Don't hit, don't hit him under tower.
He's dead.
We know, but you're dead.
The what?
Oh, my health.
Oh, my God.
I gotta wait.
Yeah.
Be careful.
Careful.
They're taking my tower.
No, no, no.
We're good.
You should back poke and try to bug.
Yeah, I'm out.
I'm out.
All right.
Here we go.
Come back, dude.
Easy clap.
Who's their mid?
The void camp's back up.
I got an item.
No, I don't want that fucking thing.
Oh, it's siren.
Oh, I thought I finished it.
Oh, I hear music.
No, that's not good.
What do I buy?
I'm gonna, I'm gonna get blue for you.
Is it is it new me?
I don't want to drop it.
Don't open mine.
Why?
What does your ulti do?
Russell?
I don't know.
That pole was huge, by the way.
That's how we got that killed.
He give you a build in the chat.
You look at all right.
So you you want to?
They're taking all our shit.
Okay, okay, okay.
I'm coming, I'm coming, I'm coming.
Let's get you this buff.
You want protections, right?
You want like who's doing all the damage on their team right now?
The dodgy physical, right?
Belona hurts.
Yeah, I've got physical damage.
Okay, for one poke.
You're not even under tower, bro.
You died because you were fucking dumb in our buff.
You're a reading fucking items.
Sorry.
Hey, whoa, wait, wait, wait, wait, we're in this.
We're in this.
We're good.
We're everything's okay.
I can't push up guys.
We're doing great.
I got buffs up.
Hey, it's only 2v5.
We're good.
I'm afk.
Who's afk?
They're on the right side of them on the right side buff.
Just saying.
Are they over?
Yeah, they're here.
I'm getting out jungled.
I knew I did.
Okay, they have jungler is like the best jungler in like the
tournament so far.
Well, he did start.
I'm hurting this.
I'm going to come.
I'm going to come over there.
I'm coming to gank the balloon.
Yeah, let's let's collapse on left there.
She's too strong.
Honestly, just go somewhere else.
I can't even hurt her.
What if we we I mean, what if we we could collapse on her?
I say let's let's let's just fucking go nuts.
You know what I mean?
They're all here.
They're here here here here.
What's the point of jumping?
Watch out.
What do you mean?
What's the point of jumping?
We could do the fire thing.
Oh, the dodgy writer.
We cannot do the fire giant.
Oh my god is bad.
I do.
Oh my god.
I'm dead.
Fuck.
Oh, I don't know.
I was thinking fuck.
I got I saw red my brain.
I forgot the dodgy was so how overleveled I forgot fuck.
All right.
We're okay.
I have question mark to him.
I got to level up.
We can't we can't why?
Oh, yeah.
Okay.
I'm now dead.
Are we here?
No, we're not.
Yeah, I'm coming over there for the brand.
Maybe as we need help with the we need help.
We need help.
Okay, then we're okay.
No, you're good.
Go on.
I'm I'm here.
Okay.
No, okay.
No money.
I have a lot of money.
That's what it said.
How's it buff over here?
Look, okay.
Grab this.
We've got all these items.
Oh, I'm dead.
Oh shit.
See if I can help.
Oh, you're in trouble.
I was on my own Russell.
I love you, but you gotta be more in front of me.
What I wasn't even near you.
I don't think in Lane next game.
Watch out.
Hey, they're going in here.
Yeah, whip it out.
Careful.
Careful in this jungle over here.
They're all collapsed in mid side.
Can we get a pick off?
They're doing the really right side.
Super right side.
It's three minutes.
That's three minutes right now.
I gotta go farm.
Oh, maybe I might be able to help you here.
I should have got my fucking all.
All right, poke.
I'm with you.
I have no.
Oh, that one's guys one.
Really fuck.
Come on, man.
You got that person though, right?
I'm taking power taking power.
No fuck.
How I could they just got away.
Fuck.
I have no idea what that one person's.
How did I not kill that one person?
What?
Fuck the all four of them were in there.
Okay, we took it.
We got we got left our.
All right, good.
Wait, he's getting XP camp.
Maybe we should get okay.
Let's get XP camp.
It's dead.
Yeah, they got it.
Shit.
We are our lanes missing our lanes missing.
Waiting for an item.
I just can't believe I didn't kill.
They hit like two ticks.
Wait, there's a maximum kill this guy.
You want to kill this guy?
Yeah, go on.
I should have cleaned that up.
I just want I can't hurt them.
I'm just so underleveled.
Fuck if you yeah, if you want to wake up, I'm I'm like,
I can I can farm pretty hard.
The fuck just happened.
Oh, yeah, we can.
We cannot be dying like that.
I'm getting pretty strong.
Yeah, we wait.
This is not over.
Just saying.
Yeah, Fred does a lot of damage.
Now.
She's right here.
Be careful.
We actually might be able to get it.
That means that two or three people are probably right here.
So are they looking at?
No, they're not looking over there.
My money's low.
Let's get this.
Right.
Oh, they're going to try to steal it.
Aren't they?
Oh my God.
No way that ain't happening.
There are thieves.
Thieves is big.
I got the.
Oh, what the fuck?
Yeah, we got to back up.
We got to back up.
I have no idea what this person's alt does.
I thought it would already went past whatever the fuck it does
and then it would win again.
Poke.
Don't die, please.
I'm in lane and fine.
It's faster.
I just do this.
Our towers destroyed.
Which one?
Right side.
Oh, they kill it.
Yeah, we we got to get some of these.
Objectives, I think.
Okay.
Although we don't think it's just far behind.
If we can get to like level 15 to 20 ish.
I think we'll be okay.
We just have to get there.
Okay.
All right.
Yeah, let's back up.
Russell.
I'm here.
Oh my fucking God.
I'm protecting my left hour, but this balona is fucking like.
Dude, what?
Oh, got him.
They're so overleveled.
I gotta get out of here.
I'm coming.
Yeah, this balona is fucking insane.
All right.
We're good.
We won that we actually won that exchange.
Also, you didn't see him coming.
Did you see him coming?
Yes, he's between the traps.
I honestly am with this left and might just like you're behind
me all game.
I'm pretty strong.
I could I might be able to like, oh no team.
Arguments supposed to avoid these.
I think so when you live on your own island until like mid
end game.
I don't know how the pacing works differently in Smina.
Yeah, we're not in bad shape.
We really aren't we can pull this back.
We're only down like 8k gold gold don't matter.
It's it's the clutch time is what matters.
We pick off two or three more people were back.
I'm walking to lane.
Wait, they're pushing.
They're pushing you.
Oh, I'm getting get to I'm dead.
I'm dead.
I'm hooking them in.
I got to go like new.
Collapse collapse collapse.
Very nice.
Just got a god kill.
Just saying.
Good job, man.
Really pulling it back.
This is a clutch plays.
Let's go.
Wait, look, no, no more arguments.
We're good.
We're just going to get our hearts and heads in the game.
And we're good to go.
I need help with this balona.
I'm coming on my left.
We might be able to me though.
Yeah, she's so strong in general.
She's just tanky.
She's tanky.
I can't really touch it.
She's level 15.
I was a good hook.
You can hook people Russell.
Yeah, that's this all to me.
No, no, no, no, no, only my all.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
So like they're missing up.
Usually I also that they can get sucked under tower and then
we do all the damage like we zerg them.
Oh shit.
I mean, I could I could try to fuck around here.
I mean, it's up to you.
Yeah, we should.
I fucking miss my all.
I think we're going to wait.
I'm not with you.
Yeah, I back it up.
Yeah, it's not worth it.
Buff is almost coming up.
Yeah, I know.
I see it.
Hi guys doing right here.
Oh, no, I'm not.
If you guys gonna yeah, it's missing right now.
This character careful.
Careful right side.
I can't move.
I literally can't move.
We should have made.
Yeah, they're all they're all here.
They're all there.
They're all three three right side.
Okay, we guys.
Okay.
Now I understand.
We just got to stop leaving like safe areas.
Oh, that's fucking huge.
Go in, go in, go in.
That's huge.
Absolutely massive.
Big.
Get her.
Collapse, collapse, collapse.
This is huge.
We have surfer ring.
Lose it.
Therefore, this is actually so hot.
I'm not even kidding.
I think we forgot.
All right.
Back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back, back.
All this fucking dodgy.
All right.
That's it.
We're good.
We pulled that back.
That was clutch.
We forgot.
Just pull it back.
Pull it back.
Can you get the dodge?
Yes.
Hey guys, we're good.
We're good.
We've gained back so much ground.
Yeah, good job.
You too.
Oh, I forgot to get the magic shell.
I pushed mid tower as well.
Our team is going to scale like crazy, by the way.
What do I do in this scenario?
I think at this point we have to just kind of be together.
Okay.
All right.
I'm going to actually wait for my Pridwin or whatever it's called.
We have to move as a unit.
I got it.
Fire giant.
Is she scary?
We could try to do Goal Fury.
Very scary.
You want to try to go?
Fire giant Baron.
I feel like we're under leveled still compared to them though.
That's kind of scary.
Yeah, I kind of want to race out of math.
They're going to push race out of math though.
They're pushing race out of math.
How many are in right right now?
We're so under leveled though.
How many are 16?
How many are 13?
Yeah.
Well, he has three kills.
We need camps though, but every time we get near camps.
They just finished Pyro.
Oh shit.
That's scary.
I'm coming over to you.
I'm just trying to get away.
Yeah.
Come to me.
They're all here.
What the fuck is going on on my screen?
Get me the fuck out.
Yeah.
Watch out.
She's on.
She's right in there.
Yeah, I'm just running away.
Wait, should we just push?
Yeah, I would just push the right lane.
Oh, they're coming.
Yeah, they're wrapping up.
Yeah, I think they're coming.
I'm leaving right side.
A lot of coming going on.
You like that?
Yeah.
All right.
You're here.
Wait, I like this guy.
Can you go check it?
Maybe you could solo farm and then I rotate.
I can't I'm so I'm dying every time.
We just all we have to do is make sure we have words on fire.
Giant.
They never do that.
We're fine.
What is God fury?
Gold fury.
It's dragon.
Basically the right thing.
What is this?
It's gone.
Let's fucking push this tower.
Okay, but one is in mid blown is the scariest of their whole team
so far in the dodgy.
Yeah, she hard.
Yeah, you guys be careful.
They're going to collapse.
Yeah, yeah, leave right away.
All right.
Cool.
Oh God, of course.
I'm the slowest one buffers up.
I'm so scared.
They in mid right now.
Yeah, let's go.
Let's go.
I have my own coming coming coming.
She's your ult on the AD carry.
What's the name Freya?
I'm ready.
Go for it.
I got one.
No, I miss my own.
Don't let that dodge you get away.
Let's go.
I got flash.
There it is.
And that's how you bring the goddamn game back.
Let's get gold fury.
Go fury.
Gold fury is gone.
Oh shit.
We can get a fire giant.
Can you think we could do it?
Should we do it?
We got to do something, right?
Yeah.
Well, yeah, let's let's go.
Let's go captain.
This is your kill.
Let's get the pyro guy.
It might be too late now.
Oh, let's push tower.
I don't know.
I don't play this game.
You have guides motherfucker.
Let's just push mid tower.
I should have definitely bought but it's fine.
I don't understand.
Oh my why?
Guys the towers.
How many how many how many?
Of course, bro.
I pull back pull back pull back pull back pull back.
No, not worth it.
They're up.
They're all up.
That's her little lift ability.
Yeah.
If you got money spend it because we brought the game back.
So if you got money spend it.
Good stuff.
Why can't I upgrade my sentinels?
I wanted to be one know why.
Is it is it maxed out?
It's like what is it?
Is that your starter item?
Yeah, you got to wait till level 20.
That's that.
That's the last thing that you're going to upgrade.
Yeah, that's the last item you're going to upgrade.
We're going to scale really well here if we can keep us up.
Wait poke.
Yo.
Oh my god.
I was so close.
Are you saying right side?
Are they going for fire giant?
Let's fight it.
Good.
I see the Bologna.
I'm coming.
We can maybe fire giant.
Stop this guy.
Let's fire giant.
Let's fire giant then.
But there's a lot of me here.
Hold on.
We need tank.
Oh boy.
We've done it.
I would go.
We're not over here.
We're not out here.
All right.
Let's get it.
Oh my god.
I'm going to die for the fucking fire giant.
I got to get out of here.
I'm going to die from fire giant.
I have to leave.
Okay.
We can we can we can.
Well, it's not that we're not strong.
It's this fire.
We need a we need a we need a tank to take that take the hits though.
I'm dumb.
Sorry, but our right side is being pushed.
So I can't yeah, I'm fucking one HP.
It's like hard.
Word beside all of you as long as I'm here.
We took the lead here.
Oh, I almost died.
No, I'm pushing right.
I'm going to come right side.
They're all they might be thinking to do fire.
I'll be there in a second.
Yeah, they have balona to right side.
So they are going to take it.
Yeah, they're taking it.
They're taking it.
Yeah, go go go.
Let's go.
Me and you know, they're doing the fireman sir guy.
Oh, they're doing the fireman sir.
Oh, I shouldn't help you.
Oh, they're doing.
Yeah, you see it now.
I'm gonna go by.
We have them.
What do we do about that?
No, we're not.
We probably 2020 hindsight.
Yeah, let's get it over.
We probably should have killed the fireman sir.
2020 hindsight there.
Gailing hard right now to push right side.
Still have no gold.
How?
They're right here.
Watch mid.
I'm with you brother.
Yeah.
I think they got two or three here.
Yeah, watch it.
Yeah.
Let's back off.
Well, I'm full build right now.
They're all in this right side here.
I wish I had a ward to be honest.
I'm nowhere close to my full build.
Well, if we there's a power site.
It'd be now for me.
It was Primal Fury thing.
Wait, wait, you're no, no, no.
There were people literally just seen over here.
I think they they're gonna do fire.
We could fuck with this.
I think they're doing it right now.
Let's go.
Let's let's fuck with it.
I'm coming.
I'm just I'm just gonna go in there and just just I'm just
gonna just kind of cause it.
I'm behind poke.
Okay, it's already dead.
It's dead.
Shit.
Primal Fury then can we kill the Primal Fury?
They're coming in real hard.
I'm coming coming coming.
We have to play very defensive.
Watch out, we need to form poke, form poke.
I got to leave you.
I just got fucking.
Shit.
Oh, I just flashed into it.
I thought they were on the other side.
Oh no.
Oh, that was fucking big.
That was actually huge.
Oh, damn it.
No, no, they're all they're all low.
I saw.
They can't push because I'm alive.
But okay.
I think they're doing gold period.
I just want you.
I'm trying to feed you sure for like you already full build.
There's no more.
I'm off.
I feel like I don't do damage.
I should have just pulled back.
My nerves are too high.
It's okay.
Right.
And then all right, we we got to start winning team fights.
That's the only way well, we've won every single team fight so
far.
Yeah from from the this part going forward.
I'm just going to stay next to you sure for to be honest.
I'm honest.
I can also like solo push left hard, but I don't TP.
I'm going to let you solo push right side.
Maybe so you can get this book right here.
Whoa.
Why wouldn't do that?
Oh wait that buff.
Okay.
Well phrase somewhere near just saying so watch out but I am
like kind of hidden back here.
When does their fire giant run out?
It's like four minutes, but they have it.
It's a long time.
I mean, they haven't gotten anything from it yet.
Make sure you're buying wards.
Give extra gold.
There are two right side.
They're getting me.
Yeah, I'm getting ganked brother.
It's a tower to the other else down.
They were in the fucking jungle.
They used to be caught out.
Now shit.
They're all here.
Yeah, they're all pushing me hard.
They can't really push if I'm at the tower.
I'm going to try to push mid and just like yeah, we have I'm
not sure what the what the play here is.
We just have to wait until they mess up really.
Damn, you do so much damage.
It's done.
You have a stun.
It's like it's 20.
Yeah, I can board bottom left.
Bottom left.
If I board, you want to kill?
There we go.
No, there's three though.
There's three.
I'm going left side.
I can fight the Deja.
I'm going to wait in the jungle because she's probably going
to dash through.
I'm going to fuck with him guys.
I'm trying to get out my ults up and I flash my ults up and
I flash.
I didn't know the command.
I can help you guys.
I thought she was going to dash in the jungle to get away.
Turn when I'm there.
I got her there already gone.
I thought that she was going to jump into the jungle to get
away from you, but I killed her though.
Okay.
Good.
I was waiting for the escape.
Xp camp up.
Everybody at 20.
Sweetie.
Poke near me and they're doing the obelisk shit too.
Damn it.
They just got objectives right now like hard.
Yeah, we need we need to do objectives.
I think we got to kind of group.
We got to group up at this point.
Yeah, I think we are ready for a team fight.
I think we actually have to like you're so fast.
I know speed buff.
I'm kind of scared to go with you because if I go with you
then I can't leave you like I can get out and I can't they
doing as if it's fire giant back up, but they're not they're
not doing that again.
Are they?
No, it's not up yet.
I mean you can wait for one more item for my powerslake
and then I get a buff right side.
Yeah, I got to complete my last item.
What my buff right side might get killed here.
I'm just going to push left.
It's dead.
Nevermind.
We can hear the sadness.
How long does last?
Okay.
Well, it's their fire buff has been gone.
Yeah, I'm so scared to sit inside jungle.
So I'm just going to chill come push with me.
Okay.
Well right now they're just waiting to gank.
Yeah, I was going to say that's why I feel like we shouldn't
push Freya was left side right there.
So yeah, they're doing the pyromancer.
Oh fuck.
I don't know if Giants up or not because we don't have a ward.
They're all on left side.
I think you notice it's I don't know the timing.
So when these objectives are up usually that if you as long
as you have a word your vision on them, you can see I think
I was muted.
Sorry.
It's fine.
They're all probably just right here.
I think we have to go in we have to we have to we have to go
in going to go in here.
This is a big deal if we can get this.
This is a huge deal.
Oh boy.
All right.
That's big.
That's a big deal.
Big deal.
Did we they won't be able to finish fire.
They can't get fire.
That's right.
So that was a 45.
So it's fine.
I'm almost full build.
I sell dust hole and I make invent and venom or something.
Oh no.
Oh shit.
I have to yeah, I have to upgrade my last title.
You can upgrade it.
Defend left side Phoenix.
They're trying to push Phoenix.
Got it.
Yeah, that that's the last item you upgrade.
What's happening in the races?
Should I do nothing about it?
I mean, that's a catapult.
We just have to deal with that later.
Okay, it destroys their towers.
But I'll be full.
They're they're trying to like she use her all.
She's waiting for the item real quick thing.
Yeah, I'm waiting 10 seconds or so.
Was that her all which I push right?
I push right side alone.
Should I push right?
I'm on a pillar.
That's her all.
Yeah, head right side because we get they're gonna they're all
in the left side.
Hi, four, three, two, one.
Come on.
Wait, I'll come right side.
I guess.
Are there any objectives up that we need to worry about?
We could try gold fire.
Go furious.
Not even worth doing right now.
Everyone's pretty much full.
Well, every fight is going to be around the left side of the
map right now.
Okay.
We just need more than we should just push out.
We should push out right side a little bit and then just maybe
everybody control left.
I'm gonna go to base real quick and get my my Invenom shit.
Yeah, I need to eat some stuff.
Who's that?
They're on the mid.
Freya and someone else actually Freya just went left side
camp or left side jungle.
You need to go left side.
Careful.
Whoever's left.
I'm out.
Could they be on the anything on the left side of the map?
No, right?
To giant.
We need to get close to giant so I can put a ward.
Oh, they're doing it right now.
Shit.
I thought I could put a trap and run.
Oh my God.
I'm stupid.
Oh God.
They're coming.
Play the towers.
Play the tower.
Yeah, I just stay in tower.
What one shot me.
Oh my God.
You got pulled in by her ult.
I'd be pretty strong.
I'm pretty we're pretty strong.
They can't like if they push I'm just going to all because I
can just they have to tower dive against me or else they
can't really push that for a minute.
Yep.
Oh my God.
It's a long countdown.
I got a track and then suck them in.
I'll be honest.
You could you could do it.
You got a good one.
We don't need to force a fight that fire giant.
No, but if I suck them under the tower, that's easy.
When like we just know if they want to push they're all going
to have beads.
I'm imagining they're probably all going to use it.
Yeah.
Left side of the map seen pushed.
Yeah, they're going to split push.
I need to eat some more minions for them.
I need to eat some minions.
All right.
Left is pretty empty for mid right now.
Yeah.
Going back mid.
We should know how long their buff is.
I don't see anybody over here.
Are they still for in mid where they went?
They're probably just serious.
Yeah, only fury.
Are they going to get kill fury?
All right.
Now we got a we got to think about making a move here.
Well, this is whatever it is to just wait until it's off.
Yep, they're going right side.
We can we hyper push left.
Yeah, we could try.
You could try to get tower and left.
How many are they all in right side?
Yeah, they're all right.
Push push push left if you just hold it.
Yeah, I think they're going for a win here.
They're going for win.
They're going to try to end the game.
Okay.
I'm dead.
Yeah, they're trying to end the game right now.
That's that's very old down.
I was just terrified.
I just fucking press that button.
My god, they're doing a lot of damage.
They bet they got it back up though.
They're backing.
I'm pushing this.
Oh God.
Oh no.
Oh, he can do that.
Oh God.
Oh guys.
Wow, they can just tower dive.
They didn't necessarily tower dive.
Yikes.
I'm up in six seconds.
Oh fuck.
I'm dead.
I think this is it.
Yeah, that's a guess for our game.
We'll see if I can clutch out or not.
Hey, hey, hey, listen, listen.
This was this was the team.
This was the team to beat by the way.
That's what we've been told.
So this was the team.
No, he didn't say this was the team to beat.
Oh, he said it was one of the strongest ones.
Oh, I use my beads, but like it didn't work.
It didn't get me out of the swirly.
I use species you can't get out of.
I'm pretty sure I genuinely think my biggest problem is knowing
positioning.
I got caught out so many times early game.
I think we did our warm-up game.
I think we did good though.
I mean, come on.
Wait, I think that was a good.
I think that was a good show.
I think it was a good showing.
We lost the wands up, dude.
Yes, you did.
You did better than I thought you would have to that start.
I get kind of shit on but it's all right.
You guys got to I know it's hard the beat none of you are
beadsing like you use your beads.
So you don't get CC.
So like what is beads?
That's right.
Yeah, you use those do before you get CC.
So like that dude would go up on the bottom thing and change
you.
That's when you would beat so he wouldn't pull you look at
your first player damage.
How much damage did I do?
I do a lot.
I did nothing.
I needed to do more to show up to practice last night.
We would have won.
We had a we had a team practice yesterday and we could have
been on the same thing.
No, I'm just kidding.
Nobody told me dude.
I didn't know you guys were looking at the OTK shows chat.
Okay, I would have expected to DM me on Twitter be like,
yo, dude, we're practicing right now.
I'm like, oh shoot.
Let's go crack.
Do you guys have pings disabled on discord?
Yeah, I have everything disabled on this rely on the most
lazy guy on the team.
Yeah, you know me.
Yeah, I think that that would we did good though.
That was a good that was a good showing.
You guys are we're not doing that.
Your next game should be easier.
You need to win.
I agree and your last game is going to be your you guys need
to step up again.
All right.
Well, yeah started early like the start of the game Russell
takes the green book.
Yeah, I know and then I'll be more aggressive in lane.
Yeah, you need to start your three Russell.
What's my first item?
I should start my three three pots or you all potions.
Yeah, that's all you need is potion and then transcendence.
You'll finish.
It's a morning star is the tier one item, but you'll go transcendence.
I'll type it out again.
Like no, no, I see.
Very cool.
Yeah, then I get transcendence.
Yes, or whatever item that you had.
Yeah, I can see you guys again.
We tried we tried but I needed that warm up though.
They were good team.
We got to be more.
We got to be better about trying to get the objectives to those
just like a fire giant.
Fuck that was fun.
This games fun.
I just got to be better at it.
We pulled that back.
I'm very proud of this team then you can start fucking around.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
Got it.
I'll have a phone call my mom.
Yeah, you got to answer.
Hi mom.
Am I going to play Anubis?
No.
Yeah, I think I'm going to stick to Aries.
I think that's that's the play if we don't think I'm going to
learn anything else.
I retyped out your all's both you and folks will build in that
order.
Got it.
So the next game we're going against is it Emerus team?
I believe so.
I don't know what their full thing is.
Are there bands in the finals?
Yes.
Oh, no.
So you're telling me if they banned my champion.
I have to learn a whole new one.
Yeah.
Well, we have to get to the finals first.
That is going to get but we are going to get to the finals.
I think we're going to get to the finals.
Which mid do you think I should play?
I mean you had like 50,000 player damage.
Yeah.
No, you should definitely do whatever you did.
Do that again.
You were your own team.
I was wondering if there's something that has before pressure.
No, you was you were doing was like a perfect and I don't think
hair would be any different.
You guys should have won the game when you killed everybody
and Russell wasn't right.
Sorry Russell, but you fucked him.
Oh, yeah.
When we got fired there.
Yeah, when the game of it.
Yeah, what happened?
When you were in right and they want to fight you want to do
fire you need you're like your character is be in front of
everybody start every fight be at every fight never be by
yourself.
Yeah.
All right.
That is good to know that is very good to know you should
die first.
You should be like the first one.
Here you can play that.
He has to like stay behind everybody and do not try to do
the fire dragon.
I don't want to play any other character Ares is definitely
the one.
Trust trust.
There's going to be a character he could play that he does
nothing on.
No, no, no, no on Ares.
If you start your three instead of your one, he'll do what
you want to do in lane.
I mean we can trade lanes to can I 80 carry in the lane and
work with no, we're fine.
We just fucked up early.
We got oh, I mean if I'm being completely honest by Artemis
fucking sucked.
Okay, look at the damage and it's true.
Yeah, because I had no one to fucking support me.
Oh, maybe we should change.
Maybe we should do.
I mean, this is support my fucking finger in your ass.
You guys you guys are at each other's throats.
Really like it.
This is nothing compared to what some apex players say to
each other.
Make sure you guys have cool avatars too, because that's
important.
Sure.
I had the skin buff.
I played this game.
Didn't you didn't you not like Uler?
I feel like you were saying I don't like I just didn't like
the third guy.
I played the ninja character.
Okay.
Yeah, I get a fresh start.
I think Uler is too hard.
No, he's not.
He's not hard.
Just was born.
I mean great on Artemis too.
Like you guys made a lot of plays very good job.
Your early game screwed you like really really hard.
I just think I wasn't impactful enough to be honest.
Well, yeah, you have had your first game.
So and that's also how it all works.
You're on an island for the most part.
Did I get an F on my report card weekend?
So pretty much I should just farm like a like a D.
Yeah, I miss some of your plays.
So you did some stuff, right?
Like when you guys traded you and no code kill the guy in left
and no good.
That's fine.
Like you have fires.
That was good.
Okay.
So we basically see doing is trying to alpha your laner
and if you've ever out of them you steal all the camps around
you like the other thing poke if you play Artemis your ultimate
is the same as beats.
They can't CC you or anything.
So yeah, I realize that too late.
Yeah, you could just all same for you.
Your alts will make you CC immune.
Really?
I didn't know that you could just all and then it'll help you
get away to your to make you move faster and you attack faster.
Doesn't remove slows and shit or not.
My yeah, my room is also.
It shouldn't matter once if you're all thing in that anyway,
it'll just you'll be CC immune everything.
Lenses slows and becomes immune to slows.
Yeah, when you want to do fire to you for could have done it.
You just needed whoever was healthiest to pull it.
It's pulling better the most.
All right.
We got a we got a game.
Yeah, you're someone else should have pulled anyone but you
pretty much.
We got a we got a game here.
I did pull it right.
I think you guys reset it.
I was going to be first.
If you guys are like not sure just do whatever is up like
if that pyromancer is up do that instead or do gold just
do something.
It doesn't matter what you're doing as long as you're doing
something.
I'm pulling some of the game you guys good.
Yep ready to go.
Let's go.
Good and ready, baby.
I'm ready.
La de I have listened to what we can have said and I am going
to apply that knowledge to this game same.
I feel like sure for I'm just going to why I'm going to get
super strong.
Why is that?
Why are you on the other team?
No, he can swap.
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait.
How do I swap?
It says I'm in your party.
Yeah, you're in our party.
No, the they'll swap.
Close that close the shit.
You're in right now.
No, go and click at the top of the number.
Click the number at the top the countdown or count up.
Okay.
At the top middle just click on the actual number.
Yes, click on that and then a little like refresh.
Click through a fresh button.
It'll move you.
There you go.
Yes, it turned my game volume up you guys shit on this team
like you should actually just dump through this thing.
You are giving me the confidence that I needed.
That's what we like to hear.
We want to see some five man air results from you.
Yes, you made some nutty plays and do crazy turns was feeling
the nutty plays.
Honestly, I was actually feeling them.
I had the nutty plays, but then I would get caught out and
then I also wouldn't be in front of poke, which is another
problem and I'm going to fix all these problems and it's
really late.
Like you guys are kind of like, what do we do?
You're running around.
You need to put some wards down and you need to make sure
they just don't do fire.
Oh, yeah, fight them.
Yeah, I'm going to try to just this time.
I'm going to try to have a ward at fire giant from like
five 10 minutes forward.
If you get a chance, if you're that deep, put them on their
side of the map on fire.
Yeah, you need one on the fire and the rest just on their
side.
So, you know where they are.
Yeah, also with awards, right?
It says upgrade your word.
Is that when you get the magic shell or what?
That's all great.
Your your relic you can make them better.
So yeah, like late game.
Once you have your full build upgrade, whatever you want.
Okay, so then how do I get more awards?
You just buy them.
They just they're 50 gold and then there's a bigger one.
That's 120.
Oh, okay.
The bigger one is the pink word.
That's invisible in the early game.
Just if you think about it, grab a single 50 gold word.
If you don't just in the late game is where like when you
get when you guys are grouped, like what the fuck do we do?
Where are they on this?
That's when you have to start working.
Yep.
Okay.
And get him out there or usually just ward gold fury and
fire giant and then after that just put it in random spots.
Yeah, that's actually all it needs to do.
Okay, let's go away.
If you get hit.
No, they'll keep taking.
Yeah, if you start a fight, pop them like I can't.
Yes, you can.
Okay.
And then what about my aegis?
Do I press my E plus my aegis?
Basically your aegis you want to use to not take damage.
So like if you everyone's jumping on you or fucking you up,
you want to use that but you cannot use that when you're
cc'd.
I give you your son.
You cannot be Angie basically or whatever you can beads
and then aegis.
Yeah, if you need to or if you just know the damage is about
to come, you can just pop.
That's actually super smart.
And then I can I can but I can't cast abilities not in the
aegis with the beads.
You can you beads.
You're like ready to fuck him up like you pop that just turn
and start fucking wailing on beads is like BKB and the
beads will last a couple seconds.
It's two seconds.
Yep.
Okay, so I said your fly is down.
I don't have any clothes on that's impossible.
Uh-huh.
You're naked.
Oh, right.
I forgot a minute call for everybody.
You didn't you didn't tell us that you were naked.
Is that what we're all supposed to be playing like so we
can play better?
You'll turn on the webcam like team synergy or something.
Stand up.
Look at this team synergy.
They have they all have fucking the sad Pepe face.
Yeah, because that's going to be them when they lost.
Yeah.
Sure for that's a fact.
Shrew for God.
Hold on a sec.
When do we press press play?
Hold on a second guys.
I'm opening up chest so I can get the so I can get this
skin real quick.
You $100 skin.
It's going to be big.
$100 skin or boss keep going.
I just got hold on.
We essential bees.
What's wrong Jerma?
What's wrong team captain?
I did hold on if we if we have time, but it's something
that I captain the team captain has something to potentially
show.
Oh, no team captain can't do it.
You're going to show it, huh?
My girlfriend took a picture of me when I was sitting here.
I got it.
All right.
What do we what's going on here?
I got the skin was banning banning.
Wait, what?
No, it's a little wrong.
Dude, I'm just going to pass ban.
That's what we're doing.
I think they're just passing.
Okay.
Oh my God.
Now we're picking.
No, there's no bands.
Okay.
Can I even show this?
Hey, stay tuned for next game when I when I show a picture
of something funny.
Can I frag out Azul?
I have to sneeze.
I feel like it's just kind of weak because I yeah, I throw
the axe and then I kind of need to be confident in Russell.
I got to focus right now.
I'm okay.
Chats going down.
I'll show it.
I'll show it next game.
You got it.
You got to do what for me?
I can't see chat anymore.
He needs to be confident in you to play.
I am extremely confident that I will play well here because
I just opened up a skin and it's over.
It's GGs.
Same.
You got the cat ears.
No, I got your mind.
That's pokes.
Nevermind.
I got the higher gun Aries meow.
What it was a one in 120 chance of getting it.
Meow.
So their first character they picked is their jungler.
He has an ability that makes him not take any damage and
then he has three damaging abilities that are all just
abilities.
Thanatos.
Thanatos where solo probably young actually.
Okay, that might be Robin a solo Thanatos.
Yep.
Is there a loser bracket?
I don't think so.
So we can't get first anymore.
So he's a win.
We can get out of this is a group.
Basically, we have to come out of this to to minimum.
You need to win the next game.
So be tuned.
Yeah, when it's yeah two and one and then we play semi-finals,
right?
Oh, no, no, it's fun.
I think it should be semis and then finals.
I think I don't know.
Okay, I was in cabs should be in the ADC lane against you
guys.
Your Ares all will bop them if it's be like he beads are
his only way of getting out of it.
My Ares all what sorry will fuck up the amusing cab.
They're second pick.
He doesn't have any way to get out of your all other than
his beats.
Okay, amusing cab.
That's the one with the bees.
You told me about and that's what I'm playing against.
I don't know.
I think you're going to be against the Robin of the first
year.
He's got a route a slow and a leap that slams.
I'm going to piss on him.
Huh?
What?
All right, guys, let's do a little pep talk here.
Let's hear everybody.
Try to do your best.
If you don't do your best then fuck you.
Can you sing the song for me?
Do you want to sing that?
Yeah, sing the song.
Try your best.
Do your best.
The song.
Wait, what happened?
They didn't make a selection.
They were power gaming.
We got to pick quicker than that.
I didn't do it.
Is that lobby still up?
Am I supposed to be seeing a screen right now?
Because I'm not seeing a screen.
And Chovies was an empty planet RuneScape.
We should have an automatic win.
That's unacceptable.
They're power games.
They're wasting everybody's time.
Yeah, give us that dove.
Miss.
Call the miss.
Report him.
We should get a thousand extra gold on our team.
Each.
True.
Dollars.
Is that lobby up or no?
I don't want to show it.
Who's the Ninja Turtle?
I think it's this.
This is a bunch.
Russell, your shit might be fucked.
I think so.
I think you need a reload.
Oh no.
It was actually good that they dodged.
Okay.
Why?
Resetting.
But like he has his numbers stuck and I don't think he was in your lobby.
Like I don't think he could actually see it.
Yeah.
I couldn't see anything.
That's why I wasn't.
Oh shit.
I didn't know you guys were even.
Last thing in disguise.
Oh yeah.
Jeremy last game you went to kill the duo lane.
Hit level two first before you do anything like that.
Okay.
Yeah.
Try and clear your jungle a lot first before gank ruining.
Unless it's like a really obvious game.
Did you know that guy makes videos on this game?
What are you talking to your report?
Huh?
Oh my bad.
I should know my place.
They needed.
Okay.
I mean I I can take some light criticism though, right?
I mean I got it.
I got it.
Very light.
Like I know to not suck.
Just stuff stuff like stuff like oh like this game.
Yeah, how are you good at this?
I can lie.
You're really fucking.
I'm good at every game.
I play.
That is a point and overwatch.
She was a pro at every character too.
Yeah, that's actually it.
Yeah.
Okay.
How do I join?
Oh, I got you.
I'm going to join through poke.
I guess I can you join through poke?
I don't think you can.
I think you need to go.
No, that's why I did last time.
I'm good.
We're good.
Oh, there we go.
I'm in baby.
He has like my icon by the way or new lobby.
All right.
Are we all in here?
Yes.
All right.
I'm joining the new lobby.
Yes.
Enough talk.
Now it's time to chug their beer.
Like are we good to go now?
I think how do we trash talk the other team?
Can they see what we type you guys?
No, you know right now they can.
Yeah.
Oh no, you're talking to party.
Oh, no, that's we're going to lose man.
No, you guys are going to lose.
Oh got it.
Now I can type lol XD match accepted.
Yeah, they'll have bands on go baby.
Just skip the bands for now.
You're my oh, I'll just cheat it.
I say we just cheat it and ban their their champs.
The rabbit up open up their streams ban their champs and keep
it moving.
What do we think in here?
All right.
No, don't ban Baka Sora.
I wanted to pick Baka Sora.
It would have been horrible.
Excuse me.
That'd be so funny if I did that though.
I'd have to play Thanatos.
I know how to play him.
This game needs like a UI upgrade.
It's just like League though.
Yeah, it's ugly.
I think it's hard to do shit quick doing a UI upgrade.
I think for a game that has this many things to look at.
I feel like it's hard.
Yeah, but look at like the bottom when you hover over a
character.
It's like it looks so plain.
I raise it.
If you're listening ready.
Oh, they did it ready.
You got here again.
Yeah.
Wait, is it my turn pick?
Oh, she's banning.
Emery is banning again.
Yeah, we have to pass it back and forth.
Silly guys.
Very very silly.
Low magical damage.
Uh-oh.
I mean the UI definitely has been updated in this game.
Because I remember playing back in like the day, you know,
back when we were all younger.
Oh, we don't have low magic.
We have low magic in the UI.
That's true.
By the way, those of you that are watching the drops are
enabled.
There is a custom.
Not custom a new a is it even new?
I don't know.
There's a skin as a cupid skin.
It's called cupid dreadnought and it is a this if you support
team this team here, you can potentially get that if you
drops are enabled.
So give it a look.
Yeah.
Yeah, we're the best team.
We are number one.
Are you an infomercial salesman?
I'm trying to sell it.
Give me one five second tip on jungle that I didn't do last
game.
I need my farm more.
Okay, farm a lot more.
Okay.
I farm a lot more copy paste this.
Thank you very much.
I see you later.
So they got danisos in the jungle.
I think I don't know whatever.
He's using the misc if skin.
Yeah.
Wait, they all have the same profile picture look like that.
Does that mean he actually plays the game?
We should have done that.
Oh boy.
All right.
I feel like this game is gonna go smoother.
Let's make it happen.
Do I buy five pots?
Wait a minute.
I have extra money.
You buy it.
You shouldn't have extra money eat speed speeds.
That's why fucking music is too loud.
Shut up.
Sure for even looking.
I knew it was you.
I'm like, no, I still have money.
I bought death toll and she knows me in three pots.
You just do that.
I know.
All right.
How do you know heads in the game?
Go to where you need to be.
We got to win this one.
I'm starting three daddy.
I didn't buy my beads poke.
Poke communicate with me.
Remember don't take my camp or else.
I swear to God.
I will run it down mid if you take my camp.
No.
Okay.
All right guys play well play hard.
We got a three Royale.
Yeah, for tonight without character board right now.
Just wiped out Tomato Town.
It's a different game.
Stop singing that.
They're back in now.
I'm so I'm not going to be there in time.
Oh jeez award.
They hit it first.
The game the game is so loud.
Now, oops.
Your game is loud.
No, I turned it up.
I'll turn it down in the game.
I'll turn it down.
Perfect.
All right.
Let's do it.
Oh, I just got stunned.
Very very confident.
I don't know why but I'm feeling so wrong.
They went the wrong way.
Why does it get so loud?
I turned up like a tiny bit.
All right.
Good luck.
They're level two.
Thank you.
We got a bet.
Do we have to back up?
Yeah, I feel like we have to back up because they're level two.
Like the game volume went up like crazy.
Oh, wow.
I'm backing up as you should.
Hey, help me help me help me help me in the jungle in the jungle in the jungle.
Come come come in the jungle.
Oh, I'm coming.
I'm coming coming.
Careful back it up.
Okay.
We could do this little totem thing.
Be careful.
They're going in.
Careful.
I'm good.
We might go to kill here.
Let's punish that we can.
Now back it up back it up back it up back it up back it up back it up.
Not worth it.
Oh my god.
Bro, that ability is nuts.
Not worth it.
My base here.
I know we can start screaming right now.
He's probably like, you're not supposed to be over there.
They're low.
Yep.
I'm oh, I just got stunned out of my out of my three.
I got stunned out of my three.
Okay, let's go.
Let's go back.
We actually back them out of lane.
So that could be good for us.
Left side is MA.
I'm going to get mid buff.
Is there any buff that we can get while they're gone?
Um, I don't think so.
Left side, MA stuff.
Never mind.
He's back.
Perfect.
Buff is down here for one of you guys.
Yeah.
We might actually have an aggressive here.
Oh wait, they do have items, but oh, how you guys doing you guys?
Hey guys, they're getting too though.
They're getting their junglers.
Why have I ward in our jungle as well?
Can we go do our purple thing or their purple thing?
It's on the ground right now for you.
The junglers at their red right now.
My side's going mid.
I think they're going to go fight, fight, fight, fight, fight it.
Mid's going over to you guys.
Yeah, mid's going over to you guys too.
I'm right here.
There's too many.
They're low.
Yeah, we can fight this.
No, I went around.
Oh, careful, careful, careful, careful.
Just get out.
Oh, no.
They're still betting.
There was four.
Oh, no, we're fine.
All right.
That's good.
Our that's good.
Oh shit.
Really?
I'm a hella nervous.
I'm gonna be honest.
Everything's good.
Just back to square one.
I need to board happens the best of us.
All right.
Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick, quick.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Go, go, go, go, go, go.
I don't wait too fucking long. Okay, so I'll just push this
We're gonna take her. Oh nevermind. I'm not a laner went towards jungle. I don't know where he's gonna man a camp is gone
boarding
Okay, go fear your uncle if you're here. All right, what do you want to do? Yep coming?
Run back mine to me. I'm coming as well
We know you're getting right you're getting right
Oh wait my ward got him let's go
That's a big ward right there
Yeah, it's going right right now, right we can't do anything about it because of their jungle, right?
Unless he left he must have left. I
Have ult next level so that's good. Okay. Now we can go right side after I level up here
Think let's do mid camp. Yeah, I'm here. I'm here. I'm sucking them in suck them in my way my way. Let's collapse
We're coming. We're coming. I'm coming. Keep him busy. I'm here
Wrong button. I'm good. Nice. Good shit. Good shit. All right, let's let's steal some shit here
Left is missing
Fight fight fight fight
Dude that Thanos is being big right? Yeah, be careful. It's three kills
Watch out Thanos is in here. Oh fuck. I'm here. I'm here
Shit. Yeah, I think those are getting huge under me and run run run run, you know, I was stuck
Yeah, that Thanatos is getting big we're gonna be careful that Thanatos
Five and oh, he's all the kills in the whole team. Wait, holy fuck. Yeah
We're gonna we got to focus that Thanatos every time it's really strong
I can't kill this Ravana. What the fuck? Hold on buying Thebes
Yeah, just go back I forgot to use health pods I'm here on left side
Is anybody there? I'm just gonna buy a lot of money. I'm coming pokey. Let's get the scorpion
Word I'm gonna work
Mid camps. All right, we got word. You'll stick right side real quick. Actually, I don't think you can I'm gonna try it
Let's just try it. Let's check it out. That is but I took it. I guess I'll go to traps
Wait, wait, there's I'm hiding. Yeah. Yeah, we can always missing. Yeah, it's gone. Oh, wait, we can't kill it
We can't kill it. Can we?
Yeah, we got a couple in it and it was altered mid I got him and it's us is going
Nice. I'm trying then this is going to you guys. He has no although
He's one. He's one. I can no no that's not worth it. I know I know I know I see that is he in the tower?
Collapse collapse collapse. I have no help
I
Just love saying collapse. Why do you like saying collapse? I'll collapse on him. You know, I mean, it's like oh, I know what I'm
Left is going right mid what the hell I didn't press that one
Yeah, he is very very very fed I'll come in left side to kill this guy one three three seven health just letting you know
Then it's us is right side jungle. He's right side jungle. I don't know where he's going. I think he's going towards mid
I gotta go finish my item
What I told you they're all here they're all here oh, I'm here though
Hey, if they want to fight this if they want to fight this
I'm gonna come through the jungle if they push that we don't push. We actually bait them bait them
I can also get rid of this fucking
How they do I think they're genuinely all come under tower yeah if they if they I get it go for it go for it
It's missing
There it is there it is there it is there it is nice job huge huge huge push the tower
Anime music it's sick
All right, we gotta be careful. Don't go too heavy here. We should probably get this tower though, right?
Yeah, but after this we gotta get out of here
You know
Yeah, you know very greedy of us today. Yeah, too greedy out to kill the minions, but that's fine
If you back I back right here. Oh never mind. I'm scared. I'm gonna back around this corner. Oh god
All right looking good. Good job. Keep it up
Beep. I am I'm pretty stacked right now. Well. I can get beads and 40 gold. I'm gonna wait
Okay, we're good. What am I doing here?
My dad we did don't know you're you're gonna now left is missing by the way
It's so it doesn't matter if we do it together, right? No, no, it's all good
Right now, yo, your purple's almost up pokey. Yeah, I'm gonna get I'm gonna get my item first
I just put two words in the same mid. There's four mid
Now big item big item. I think this is a Muslim cop is kind of alone here. I
Just heard then it's us in the mid
Watch out then it's a zone you guys
Just try to get up if he's chill if he's still chasing you
I might be able to jump on top of the XB camp so they couldn't get it. I'm with you. I'm with you
Nice nice work
Watch out watch out. Oh, wait, we beat them. They're so low like they're running already
Let's go, let's go I would be careful we might get there
No, no, there's no one over here
Okay, now be careful
I'm pushing this cuz I have my stun. All right about I would be I wouldn't go too far and they're dead
Good shit
Actually, I'm gonna get some good shit. You know combos crazy
Okay, you can't like check the map like league, right?
Just at the top right all the time. I just heard it then is that they notice again? Oh, let's get this XB
Right here. Wait, what are you doing?
Sorry, no, you're good. Okay, let's get this one. You're gonna get this
Yeah, they're they doing um pyro they're doing the pyramids right now when we can I did they're doing they're doing it right now
They're doing it right now. Let's jump on top of this. I'm my all
Oh
Nice work
Let him go go
Push your lane push your lane maybe
Yeah, we kill oracles and shit, what is that we do that over here, okay, I'm coming I'm going I gotta go reset
Be careful
Missed easy
I'll take whatever you can. Oh, you know take whatever you can. I'm I'm I have enough camps down here
Thank you, I'm digging
Are we gonna be that I feel like a spider just ran across your desk
That's how I feel right now, I that's a good question
Yeah, it's just gives it all money
All right, I'm gonna go I gotta buy something I'm gonna go left I know I should buy something else
I could take this I'm not here. I'm not there then it was just going right side
1300 I took you on left one. I was scared
Okay, I'm here now
I'm gonna I have the word though. Oh
You're not you're getting you're getting teamed up on I'm coming over there. Oh god
Yeah, that's all right, you guys can come to me I can help this is the best I can do after that
I don't know what to do poke. You're running the wrong way though. I know I was dead 100%
Yeah, make them think they're gonna get the kill on you cuz we're all here now. Okay, they're backing out
They know they know. Oh shit right here
Damn sorry, we got
That was a good wipe we can get the kill get that Thanatos get that Thanatos
He gets so much help from yeah, he does
That was a good we did it I was like to exchange that we got three of them, right
See more gold. I might be getting tower. Yeah, that's good. Good. Good. Good
They're all coming up now, though. They're all just responsive
Pretty sure we're stronger than them. So we should start. Yeah, we can start grouping up and doing like gold fury and shit
Yeah, let's try to get a let's try to get go fury right now
Wait, should I I want I want to wait for Pridwin. I I need 75 gold. Should I wait for that?
I'm just gonna I'm gonna wait for my gold
Reds there for you
I need my speed buff and then we can fuck around
Okay, I'm waiting for a lot of gold. Actually that's pressure
the damage
No, they just got oh, they just got it. All right, it's not on my side. Yeah, we need to do
A run poke they're gonna come to you. Hopefully I can make it. Yeah, we're stronger than that. If we just group up we can do objectives
The pyro is gonna be up soon. Yeah, we probably get pyro
Alright, so should I come to you guys to get pyro? Well, it's not up yet. Well, how close?
It's that little little thing
They're all here they're all right right here they're all over here I'm coming careful poke maybe
Uh, okay. Actually you got the 1v1 you can do that
Wait, wait, they need just on pyro. Is it just amc in mid? Can I go can I go to you?
Watch out. They're coming to you. No, go we need pyro rotating. They're rotating from right up. They're right here
They're coming to you
We could actually probably uh, oh move on on these two. If you want to move to me I can bait it
I'm here. I'm here as well. Where's pyro? Is it this guy?
I'm gonna ward it. Yeah, it's that guy
Then i'm gonna keep pushing towers stay on the side we can we can take all the raven is all right
Both here. I'm pushing up. I'm pushing up. I'm coming to you. I'm collapsing. Is pyro up?
No, it's almost up. I'm warding i'm gonna ward deeper
You might be able to like
Let's get pyro. All right, get on pyro. Okay doing doing i'm here. All right, i'm starting
I'm starting
They're coming in they're coming in but we fill it
All right, let's go. Let's get in get in
flash ult
Ulting ulting they're gonna be on me. They're gonna be on me
Rotating over there. Oh tenacious. They're all so low
They're all so low
Yes
Should have done that but
Oh bingo bingo bingo bingo bingo
You guys got them?
They're they're in trouble though
We got over the phoenix though get the tower get that left tower
We can't we can't
but we can but
God and I just feel so alive. You know what I mean?
Are you freaking busting busting right now bro busting busting bro. I kind of I stayed alive there. I pressed my beads. I used my beads
Dude, I had I had two green teas this morning. I'm fucked right now. So you're zuded is what you're telling me
Wait, i'm gonna i'm gonna i'm gonna gank i'm ganking i'm ganking
Oh god wait, you could be dead actually any help. Yeah, i'm here. I'm here with you. That's how i'm talking to you. Oh
I'm only level 13 though. That could be a problem. Oh god. That is i'm pulling him away from you pulling him away from you
Never run. He's in here
I'm right here. I'm right here. Is he in the air? He's gonna try to execute you. Yep
There's three though there's three there
Oh fuck
Damn it. They're they're all here left side
Now the whole team is here how i'm so under leveled shit the whole team's here i'm actually really strong
What am I doing wrong? That makes me so under level
Dude sure for what the fuck
He just literally came and took my last hit it wasn't sure for it was me. I did more than half your damage
Wait, really?
Yes, you guys can keep pushing right? The good news is the good news. Well, I caught her
Hey, I caught I caught her out of place. I told you I was coming. We're in a good spot
Just uh, keep taking objectives
I don't know what to say here
Wait poke. You're really pushing up right side you're saying i'm crazy right now. Russell
It's just that thanatos if that thanatos is their entire kill on he's got all the money
11 and 2
We're just gonna stay on top of that thanatos when you see the thanatos just if we're in a team fight just
In just collapse, you know that that word that we like to use. I don't know. I think in particular
It's the word you really like to use
I need exp. Yeah, that's what we need to get some objectives. I'm strong right now. We should fight
Most of us are really strong. Yeah, we can prep the fire dragon to be honest if they all go right I mean top right
I'm really strong top right's pushing. Yeah top right's pushing like I can push out left. You guys want to go to it right?
Oh right here someone right here in front of me
I'm here
You want me? Uh, there's two. Yeah, there's two there's gonna be more you should back off
Their own gold fury their own gold fury guys
I'm gonna help I can push left then
I can push left if you force something, right?
They're pushing us, right? They're pushing us, right? Okay, then i'm gonna take our easy and I could do phoenix
I'm gonna force them all here. They're on gold fury. Yeah. Yeah, this is gonna be big. I'm gonna take
Oh wait, no, never mind because there's not really much of us you just take their attention as much as you can
Oh, that was pretty big but it's good. We can play we can fight. I pulled one. I pulled one. I pulled athena athena's here
Sure
That's big don't get too greedy though because they have I could flash uh flash root I accidentally jumped
I almost knocked phoenix. I think i'm gonna no
I can't kill phoenix this phoenix regen hp
No, yes. Oh
I almost got it. I almost got it
All right back it up
Just keep on doing what you're doing
Nice is it just one there?
I'm coming towards you
One hp
He also not us
Oh
I almost killed him careful
Oh my god, I almost killed him. I outplayed the fuck out of him, too
Yeah, I thought he was gonna run away with that. Oh, yeah, that's that. He that heal is just so it's crazy
boards me
How many i'm here? I'm i'm behind him. I'm behind them. I'm behind them. I'm gonna keep pushing right
He killed the fanatos. Yeah. Yeah, let's do it
Alting him alting him alting him. He's running on me
There we go
That raven is really strong
Does my magic shell help you guys because I can oh i'm rooting him. I'm rooting her. Oh fuck
Shit stay alive stay alive. Yeah, i'm staying alive. Fuck i'm running away
Jesus
Yeah, he's so tanky we do some penetration items
Yeah, we're gonna push hard left side. Just saying I almost fucking one shot the uh, the yeah, then it was very squishy. Yeah
Oh, that's not good. I mean I can kill the raven. I'm i'm actually fucking him. That was my ulti
I have 2800 gold i'm gonna back
Yeah, if you have more than 2000 gold definitely go back and spend some money
All right. We we gotta start grouping up now
We're gonna start moving as a uh a team
That raven is strong. Let's do objectives when we can
Is uh, is gold fury up or pyro pyro's up I think right?
Yeah
I am farming we need wards by the way
Yeah, shit. That's right. We forgot to get wards. I bought them earlier. I put a couple at bar. Yeah
I bought some earlier and then I just forgot it's all by like two and then
I'll get some after though. All right, i'm ready to fight
Right side's pushed up. No
They just did it. They're right here
They're all right here
Watch mid three mid four mid actually
Yeah coming here are
They're going right
Wait, it didn't work. Never mind. He probably beat I think we could do fire giant maybe
We need like a pick or something first
Or we have to deward us you gotta you gotta back off
There's three mid
All right, i'm gonna get running towards me running towards me ravena
Keep forgetting that that did you a job blue's down here. I feel like we shouldn't push this
They're coming
How many all of them?
We can go deep in their jungle and try and gank them
Unless we can do enough I almost have enough we should run together then we can do fire giant
What if we just sit all on fire giant right now and just wait for them and we don't know where any of them are
You don't know any of them are on the map. They're in mid. They're here. I think we win the trade
We have two 20s. They're right here. Oh, they have two 20s now
I think they know we're going for it. Yeah, they're right beside. Yeah. All right, here we go
Watch out for the the collapse behind us
I'm gonna say let's just show that wait. We shouldn't back off too hard. Should we
No, we're just I mean if you see a fight get the play. Oh right there. They're right at fire giant. Yeah
I mean, I I don't mind going in an ulting. I don't care. Are they going for it?
You do you bro if you see it go for it. I mean they look they're thinking about it
Just like we are
We should just go around honestly. I can buy I could just buy I i'm I have enough to buy like all right
They're all in it
Well, if we if you buy though, don't we just
Can I be a cheeky fucking asshole and go get the phoenix?
Oh, no. All right. I'm away my
I think we just messed up. I gotta go. I gotta finish my uh items. Oh, wait, I gotta get my last item here
How about wards?
Are they gonna get fire giant since we all back? Are we checking it? Someone check fire dragon? No one no one's
They were not yeah
Oh, no, it's because we all like backed off
Shit and we needed to ward it. Fuck
I got wards
We're still all right. I have ward now. Yeah, I think we're ahead by a lot
It's just we just need to i'm saying let's fight it and then I don't know why we went to go buy something
I went to the bike
Yeah, you know, let's let's take an aggressive stance now like literally just like just just if we see somebody just jump on them
Yeah, just jump on top of everybody
You see somebody
Crap on me too on me too on me
Use everything just go sucking him sucking him sucking him. He has to stay
Just fight just fight
Go central leaning wait here. I'm helping you buckle through
I need help with the ravena
We can push him in with the push man, let's go yeah if you guys push me I can push left
Yeah, let's just push with those
Okay, i'll push with you
There's a phoenix on left as well
Yep. Yeah, we have no creeps for it though
Just be careful
All right. Yeah, I think one of us should at least
I almost have my ult up if uh
If we do objectives any objective? Yeah, what's up?
How's everybody how's everybody on money we do gold
I try to run fuck I can cut them off. I'm cutting them off
Is he invisible now? Oh me. Oh me. Oh me. Come to me. Come to me now
I chained him. I chained him got it big baby
No, we win we win I think
Keep it up. Keep fight. Keep fight. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it push phoenix
We can probably end it mid. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, push me push me push me. Oh my god
I think they're bursting me in my relic. I just ate all that I just ate all that though
Oh shit in my pants
I'm chaining them
Sorry, does everybody get him everybody attack him?
He can't kill us all
Oh my fucking god that guy's a trillion health
That's it. That's gonna be time. I still vaulted. I still vaulted. I still vaulted
We gotta get the phoenix we have to get phoenix and that
Yeah, we gotta get out. No
There's only only one's gonna be up. All right, get out get out get out get out get out
No, no, no, they're all gonna be up. I hope we can start screaming into his monitor right now
Then we'll find out
Like no you fucking idiots end the game
I was low. So yeah, I don't think we can I mean I I have 2.4k gold. Yeah
I also think it's kind of at the road, too
Yeah
About to wait for 80 gold
No, we can just push side lanes now. Yeah. Yeah, i'm pushing you win the we win the 5v5
I'm full build finally. Holy fuck
Yeah, I told you I think we could have went really aggressive. Yeah, I was at like 20 percent
That's what I call poke just completely aggressive
All right, we should should we get an objective words on fire giant words on fire giant or we push side lanes
I got i'm gonna i'm gonna board fire giant right now
Well for one right lane's already pushing alone
And uh, I feel like just group up around fire giant. We do pyromancer right now. I can do pyromancer
Oh, wait, somebody's there. Yeah, we're we're okay. Wait, i'm not here yet. I'm not there yet. I'm not there yet
Oh, he's gonna see yeah. Yeah, they're they're right here. You guys are missing. We win the 5v5. Yeah, we do. Yeah
Let's do pyro
We're doing it. Okay. Yeah, I mean it's just like a little guy
He's gonna try to steal it
And they come they come
This could be in it. We should be we should probably engage this. I might just go in on this
Yeah, you do you you're the tank bro. Ready? I'm ready. Come with me. Come with me
I got one. I got one. That's all that matters. That's all that matters. It beats the beats. Oh, fuck they all beat shit. Sorry
I forgot about beats. Sorry. Sorry back it up back it up back it up
Backing up. How long's the beats cool down? I don't have there's lights. I wish I'd move right 200 seconds left
Fire's gonna be up
We could just push left and force the fight because we have phoenix in middle. Oh shit, okay
Oh underneath without us and you're fine
Yeah, we just push this lane. Look and then middle push right now
He's coming up behind him. They're not us in the teams behind him. We're gonna stick together
We gotta help him
I'm one hp bro. I have to yeah, just not worth it. You're good. You're good too long of a death fire giant is up
You want to do fire?
No, we can't do fire without fire
Watch out. Watch out. Watch out back it up to make sure they don't get fire
I got him. I got him. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm gonna boost it baby. Let's go
You're good. You're good
I can probably do fire now. We can do fine. Yeah, let's get it. That's right. That's right. That's right. Let's go
Let's go. Let's do it. Let's do it. Let's do it. Let's do it. Let's do it. Just make sure our tank hits it first
So aries, I got it. Yep. There it is. All right
Yeah, i'm just securing it. Okay. Okay. Okay. It's just a cool down. Yeah, it is
All right. We uh, we're gonna
Stick together and push or how are we feeling?
Maybe we should push right side or something. I'm gonna just left just push left or right
Maybe right's easier because the fire dragon just went down. So yeah, let's get right. You know what i'm saying?
I feel you
We take this now. What about this primal fury? I mean, we could isn't it just gold?
Isn't it? I don't know. We don't need that right now. I mean, that's that's fine. That's fine
Right here one's caught one's pushed
Never mind on me. Oh, they were oh wait. Oh shit. You scared the shit out of me. Am I blocking?
No, you can body block that reduce it right here. I need to push towers
Yeah, I warded yeah, i've just pushed towers you've already like you're saying
Yeah, they're getting ready to engage on right side
I'm here. I'm here
Wait on me that guy's really low. That guy's really low me
Fuck I could flash and fucking ult him, but I don't know if it's worth it
We get this tower for you
They're not they're all pretty low
I i'm coming i'm coming i'm behind you guys
Wait, I could pull them from under tower if they don't if they all don't have their raven is not here. Yeah raven is in mid
They're they're pushing our left we gotta be careful. Well, it's not it's not damage to the minion. It's fine
No, no, no, it's raven. Oh, no raven with me. I don't see him on the map. Oh
oh
We just have to keep sieging. We're fine, which i'm gonna maybe
mid
Yeah, mid phoenix then we can just keep sieging this or someone could split mid and get that phoenix right there. Yeah
Oh, here we go. Here we go. They got poke
No, i'm fine. I'm fine. Oh, yeah, but i'm saying like they did damaged you
I could pull them out
They're coming in they're coming in
Oh, i'm not fine. I'm not fine. I'm pulling up. I'm pulling up. He's on me
I don't know how that character works. Fuck guys. I think we traded a few
Oh my beads, I fucking
Oh, no, your body part could be you dumbass
It's all right. We're good. We're good. We're good. Let's talk about aries. Oh my bad. It's three's ring medusa
Yeah, they they got my they got my beads
Hey, if you have a shitload of money go to the consumable tab and buy one of the three thousand dollar elixirs. Yeah
All right. All right. Three thousand. Yeah, it's three. Okay ward. I guess deep wards
Oh on me one on me. You're by yourself, bro. Oh, fuck me. Okay
Yeah, I have a fire giant's up in like a minute or so
Coming to you
Yeah, i'm just clearing the waves
Yeah, if you have wards put them down there
I'm gonna buy we should prep we should prep for fire for dragon or whatever fire pyromancer
I mean you can look for a game. I don't have ward for pyromancer. Just saying
Oh either we already have one
I need to eat
I gotta stop getting jumped on that's my problem
We should uh, I'm gonna trap the fire giant
Yep, I mean like they're not even paying attention to pyromancer. We should just take this shit, right?
Yeah. Yeah. All right. Let's do it. I'll start it. Oh, i'm not there. Oh, no
They watch it back it up back it up. They might be all here. I'm not there
They might be all here
Shit, I try to eat it
I'm hiding here. Okay, they have ward right here. Are they going in fire?
I mean I can fucking push left
There yeah, i'm gonna force left. Don't don't fight. Don't fight. Let me force left and push this wave
And they have they have to come fight it
Same thing that we did before the ravana's here on me. Oh, no, they're gonna come back to me. Oh, never mind
There's four on me for me
That's pretty wild. We got it. They were so clueless
Our middle tower. Oh shit
We're good. They have to go take left lane. They have to deal with this
Okay, I think you're gonna pull them there russell
I don't I don't want to kill one guy. That's why I should do fire. They should come down. I'm gonna burst this thing
Are they in i'm coming i'm coming they're close they're close
Yeah, they're they're all with this. This is a fire giant fight here. They they want it
And if you ever see an opportunity to go in that's all you yeah, it's too mid right now. I'm here. I'm here
I'm pushing up. I'm just gonna push up
Maybe we wrap around mid. Yeah, let's wrap around mid wrap around mid. Let's get let's kill these guys in mid
Boy, uh, okay because they're they're pushing too far up
Yeah, wait, there's two on me though. I could I could ult them
If you get a pole, where'd you go about the dragon?
Are we giving it up?
There's one. Yeah, we're gonna fight it. Now's the time. Yeah, because one of them split. Maybe we should just
I put a bunch of traps on it. I put a bunch of traps on here. We should fight or the
We should do it. All right
If there's any time I guess we're gonna go for it
Let's go
So secure it secure it secure it go ahead get them
Here we go, let's focus the one that's closest always the one that's closest
Oh fuck. Oh fuck. Oh fuck
Chained them chained. Oh, no, I missed it. I'm I'm one hitting i'm dead. I need to eat somebody
Just left
Oh shit
They're dead for 25 seconds. Yeah, they we have to we have to like win off this to be honest
You can try
I mean i'll take tower damage because I mean watch out for that thanatos
If we can win a team fight right here game's over
If they if they get close i'm ulting if they get close, I think we have to like yeah
Yeah, i'm here. I'm here. We're good
They're not gonna push though
All right, there it is
That's two that's two
Let's go
There you go, buddy
Kill all right kill him. Yeah, just kill this thing kill this thing
Oh, that's it
Get it
Yes, nice job
Nice job good shit
Good fucking alts nice job guys, baby
um
Oh shit my food
food
Yummy easy
Very cool. Hey good job
Oh, I didn't I wanted to see the detail of the match shit. Oops. How do you see it by accident bruh?
Yeah, I clicked back like an idiot. Well, there we go. Hey, at least we won one
You can't say at least we won. Yeah
We're gonna win. What do you mean at least?
I mean at the at the very end of the day. No matter what happens. We won a game
Okay, germ
Always a lot of damage. We did a lot. I think we could win the whole thing
Yeah
Player image wait, I only did 17k
18k player damage. I feel like that's not a lot. I mean compared to 40 and 30
No, but I mean you still did more damage than most the other team
I can see the chat again. Hold on. So i'm not doing my role, correct? Um, I really don't know
Uh coach is he doing all right? Yeah, where's our coach coach? Is he doing all right? Does he need a whipping?
I think coach might be afk
Be right back
I think we just got to be more assertive when we know we're stronger
True
I did do a lot of structure damage
That's good. That's good. Lots of pushing
Yeah, my structure damage was 8 000. You guys were
a thousand
and 200 300
Okay, so that was my role
I didn't do a lot of structure damage or damage in general, but I did
do some stunning
So
Yeah, I think what we also need to do is I also need to combine my alt because my alt is a silence
So if you pull them in and I silence them, they can't shrink it. Yeah
That's actually smart. Holy shit. Yeah
So you want to know how to win the next game?
Yes
uh
Russell be like when you guys are grouping around the fire blink and just fucking just pull your dick out and slap them around
Like just go run at them that heard of anything. Okay. You know what what happened?
Hey that herman miller chair sure is good, isn't it? I'm not I have I have shorts on okay
I've got shorts on I've got shorts on I just i'm i'm a gamer
I'm i'm i'm gaming i'm i'm intensely gaming
I have to pee i'll be back
When you're low he can see you all the time. So that was fucking you even more. Oh
That's how he alts you no matter what. Yep. I gotta pee. I'll be right back. Where's the picture of germa playing naked
You missed it. I put it up already
Where if somebody will show you it's it's it's it's not even a big deal. I'll be right back first pick or not germa germa
I'll be right back. No
Pick shouldn't matter to be honest
Okay, you all are just gonna take whatever you want and they're just gonna do the same thing
He's playing naked you guys are second pick last game in the other games, right?
I feel like we all have to go naked. Yeah, I was gonna say like I feel like we have to take on more clothes
Oh, yeah, when you're in lane make sure you guys use your potions
Like just if you're doing anything just pop them if you're at all low hp, you don't need to be super low
Wait, sorry
What did you say? I zoned out for a second when when you're in lane
Even if you're just a little low like say you're at 80% health, just use your potions. Make sure you're okay
It's okay. I'd rather you waste them than just die. The miss gift skin is so ugly
It's definitely an odd skin
I don't want to be me but it's it's scary as hell looking
Oh, yeah, no, there's no going
Yeah
Um, you know your you when you buy buy the death toll first
Your second item it builds into that transcendence item. It's called morningstar. You want to buy like the tier one of that transcendence
Did I not do that? No, no, no you bought you almost bought nothing which would have fucking screwed you
Really bad
Yeah, so buy the buy the death toll then buy that item then buy your potion and he's part about it
Okay. Okay. No, go ahead. The purification beads shouldn't cost anything. They're free
Okay, so death toll how many potions?
Uh, it should be I think it's four or five
Yeah, it's five
Yeah, buy yeah buy the morningstar and then just buy the you max out five potions and that's fine. You can just buy
No, no, no, no buy death toll
Yeah, death toll
I can second item is called morningstar. It builds into the
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, you the one's a starter and the other one is the tier one of your transcendence item
Are you eating?
Yeah, some garlic
Oh my bad
I did it. I pulled a germa. What'd you say?
I said what am I someone asked what I was eating because I was eating
I was about to tell them but then I hotmicked. Oh, are you eating? Can you tell me now?
Almonds, yeah garlic rosemary almonds interesting
Late game you're super tanky too. You can just run into phoenixes and shit like don't like yeah
That's what I was 10 minutes, but you can take them for a little bit. Yeah. Yeah, that's what I was saying. Um
Whenever we were like chilling at the phoenix like I could tank it a little bit until the minions come well, russell
When you know, we're stronger you can just fucking go into the enemy team
Yeah after 30 minutes to that fire giant
It'll make it so you kill the phoenixes instantly like you just all do it once it'll die
Oh cool. If you have a purple fire giant on your buff bar, you'll just kill everything
You guys see the earn free rewards thing in game, yeah watch ads bro, that's cool. We have to watch ads
Germa's
Germa's thumbnail on twitch. What is it? Probably him butt naked
Your thumbnail
Oh my god, it actually is
Wait, where's this picture go to go to your thumbnail on twitch
Just look at this section. Yeah, look at this my section, huh?
mine
Yes
No, oh, it's just him naked probably right?
Yeah, it's literally just him but
He's talking about if you go to the smite section, you know, there's a preview of the stream. Yeah
Yeah, it's uh, it's a picture of you gaming
You're gaming right now. I haven't shown my shorts. I literally i've have shit i'm have shorts on
I don't know the black box says otherwise. I have I have shorts on
You're gonna have to prove it. You're gonna have to take that black box away or else. I think you're full naked right now
I don't see anything
You missed out. Yeah
I linked it in discord
What I saw I wanted to see fucking all he wants to see is germa cock right now
Okay, that's good
He's got booty. Yeah, that'd have to be big shorts. I'm not wearing baggy shorts. I'm just wearing shorts
I don't know. All i'm saying is that a cute little that's a big sensor bar
Uh, I appreciate the chesticles
end up
Oh shit
Yama, I just leaked nothing. Okay. Thank god
What'd you leak? Oh god, nothing. Oh, I just leaked the password. Oh, well, no, I didn't thank god
Whoo-hoo
How many times are you freaking out man? Wait, who's our coach germa or weekend? I'm the captain but
I don't know. Whatever. What?
Who's the one making the videos the guys?
Oh, no, you're talking about germa from 10 years ago. He was like way smarter than I am
Wait, what happened?
No, because i'm over here asking questions and shit, but I was like, ah, we don't have a coach but this guy
I can just ask him
Yeah, we got a coach
What happened to your intelligence germa? It's me. I'm the coach
I got over 35 years old
So you're regressing
I mean 29 when you get older, man
What's it like at 35?
Yo, go look at the characters right now gods
Yeah, look at look at vanima and look at his third skin. Oh, yeah
That skin is as old as time bro. That is really old, isn't it?
That's the skin everyone used to wear well the thing I kind of had to prove it today because
I always talk about how I don't
I I don't really wear that many clothes when i'm sitting around
Sometimes it'd be a pair of shorts or whatever, right?
And people think i'm full of shit when I say that usually when i'm sitting here streaming
I just I kind of don't really have any clothes on so you're a forever nude. No, no, where are you partial?
Las vegas, man. Oh
It's it's 120 degrees out. Isn't that what ac is for?
Yeah, I have ac but leave your car parked outside right because your tires remote. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah. No
I'm a forever clothed. Wait, why do people believe in team tecton that went over team germa? I don't know
Wait, they've been playing for that long. Yeah tectons. I think only been playing smite for the past week like that's it
They've been playing they've been playing a lot though. Haven't they put them in my lane? Yeah, but tecton
They beat mendo's team the one you guys just lost to they like slaughtered them. Wait, what?
Wait, what you guys are much better now. You're better now that is lose the second game. Are we out? Yes
Okay. Well, i'll see you guys later then
Huh? No, we win. We win. We win. We win. What's with all these quitters on my team, man? No, I don't understand
Sure for it, dude
No, we don't just have sure for we have sure for we have germa we have noko we have russell
We have pokey walls. We have weakened. We're gonna win. I think we got
That is actually all we have. Yeah. Yeah, that is it exactly
So if we lose this then we watch the rest of the tournament. Oh, it's for who to watch not who to win
Oh, never think i'm gonna watch the rest of the tournament. We're gonna win this for who to win
Did they spectate our game once or no? I think what about the slipknot stuff? Yeah, the slipknot stuff is um,
I think this game is gonna be interesting. There's channel though on the stream. Poseidon is a lot of it, right?
If I lose this game, i'm going to apex and soloqueue ranked and getting depression same here. We're not gonna lose
We're not gonna lose. That's the thing. I'm literally the plat gatekeeper
I fell out of pred i'm dog shit. No
I'm perpetually diamond one. No d4 plat one d4 plat one d4 plat one
Apparently they watched the end of your last game too, so they get to see bop
Nice
Should I be the stranger things monster for this one? Are we uh, did it did it when are we starting?
I switch my characters take too much working. Whatever you want bro. Don't let your memes be dreams. No, honestly
No other character better than you should just stay
There's gonna be different animations for the new skins and stuff. Now i'm staying with the metal one. That'll fuck with me
All right, I think we should just win. Yeah. Yeah, we should that sounds like a good idea just win forehead
Okay, so let's do that then I think we have a pretty decent chance
To just win forehead. Okay. Whoa, wait, we're all playing the same characters. Okay
So russia you go in your ultimate is a pull
Yeah, it's like well
It's like you started off and I have to get them in the circle and then like the pool takes like I think
Four seconds or three seconds or something. It's one of the easiest ults in the game to beads
Yeah
That's the biggest problem like I can say i'm gonna pull them
But if they beads it I don't pull them you actually got two double kills because they beads it too early
Yeah, did they really
Yeah, you did. That's kind of sad. Wait, how do how do they beads it too early?
If you if you beads it before it actually pulls it will like it'll still pull them if you beat it like way
Or like it fell
Yeah, the whole thing you're falling off the beads are falling off. Okay interesting
so
You pull and then sure forwards your ulti dragging in a line that does a bunch of damage
Okay over issues right now
I'm just trying to figure out right now
What i'm trying to figure out is a combination kind of like overwatch, right?
We're like zarya hanzo like so you pull and then I ult because my ult does damage and it silences
So they can't beads or anything and then you you dragon. Are you talking to me? Because I zoned out
You need to get your head in the game
What did you say
You don't even remember what you said bro
This is where we go five winstons in the middle, yeah
Okay
What oh boy, what the heck you pull pull I ult he dragons
Yeah, wait if you silence your ult silences, right? Yes my ult silences so I can silence into the
Wait, that means they can't beads right? Yeah, no, they can I think you can still beads when you're silenced
Yeah, that's just stupid. What's the point of silencing?
So you can't use abilities because they're not you you don't use them all together usually like if they get pulled drop your shit
Where they get pulled but you're kind of using them separately to make them beads
So one of your all shit is
Wait, that makes sense. Yeah, you can beads while you're silenced right somebody's saying that
Yeah
The order that you sent me, uh, we can is that the order that I build in? Yes, exactly. Okay. All right
Tyrus servers getting ddos right now
I don't think they're getting ddos. Maybe there's so many people playing right now that I think they they're fixing them. They just reset
Is this normal in spite? Yes
Every night while i'm streaming it up
Every night. Yeah ever since like uh, like coven when everyone started playing like smite's player base double
They I think it's a code problem with their logins and they can't even fix it. Oh spaghetti code. Yep
Because the games don't crash like if i'm in a game i'm fine
I'm not in a booster seat. I'm not in a booster seat in the picture. I have that's a herman miller
Embodied chair and it's fucking phenomenal. Okay
Everyone's saying i'm in a booster seat. No, that's that's i'm in that's a herman miller
Well, we can't tell because there's a giant black box by herman miller
Uh, no, they gave me the chair, but those chairs suck. I like the embody
Those chairs suck
Why are you saying that have you sat in one arm rests their arm rests are doggers
I like the aaron arm rests more than I like the embodies because the aaron has like that cushion that little squishy squishy
I I I think the doesn't I like the the back crank the thing where you go like
And maybe tighter. Yeah. No, I love it. That was asmr spark
No, I love it. I think it's great. Yeah, but can anyone purr?
I don't think anyone's gonna want to do that
I
I'm not sure anybody's gonna want to do those sounds
We should try joining now apparently are we all right? We can do it. Yeah
All right. So we're let's go for it. All right play are you guys ready?
I just chugged some water
What who's uh, I just had an oreo milkshake whose game we trying to be joining. Thanks for the reminder
I think it's tectones if he ever puts it up. What's tectone? Oh, okay. I don't know what I don't know is in game
We're on the broadcast. Oh
Can they hear us? Hi guys. Hi guys. I'm my name is jerma
And he uh, my my friends and the team guys
What the fuck team captain sound confident?
I'm gonna play a little bit safe. Yeah
Where's russell?
Where's that freaking yoked up germa? I saw in the picture
Yoked up. All right. Wait, do you mean like
Never heard that before. Yeah. Yeah, I don't I wouldn't say yoked up. I'd say more
Like cottage cheesed up
I didn't see any drooping
I'm sitting in a chair. Yeah, but you know, like old people have like their skin starts sagging. I got pretty good posture to anything
I'd have to relook
What's wrong with you?
But I don't know where to start deep right now two green teas. I'm too
Are you actually oh my god, see you gotta slow down
I just ate this oreo milkshake. It was delicious
Yeah, now you're gonna get the sugar rush lord knows I need that
Should I get another green tea? Should we go three green teas for three matches? What do you have?
I can get yoked up bro. Try get fucking should I get fucking cheddar cheesed up? Get juiced up, bro
German starts calming everything
How do you fall asleep, uh
Like do you like sleep with the tv on?
Yeah, usually ipad I have an ipad on my chest and I just kind of watch whatever and then fall asleep
Really? Yeah
Let's say when he walks in the room. Just find you like they can wake you up
He has an ipad right in your chest
Yeah, I mean that you think that picture was weird this pictures of me
I'll sleep with just random videos of the shit that we've shown. All right, I think we're good to go
But where where is the match? Are they trying to get you guys to make oh are we making the game?
We're supposed to be second pick so I don't know why you'd be making the game unless I don't see their name
I see I see. I remember this game. It's uh stripping is the host
Okay, so it's stripping is that the same password?
Wait stripping's playing
Yeah, I love stripping stripping's on ticktones too. Yeah, I love stripping too. He dropped the password in the chat. Yeah
All right, we're going to kill him though. Can you read that password out loud for me?
um, yeah, um
Uh, I'm trying to think of something funny to say but I don't I don't want to even be somewhat similar
You know, I guess the password like 12 years ago to like a league of legends tournament that was streamed
yeah, I was like tsm versus clg and I I got in it was like a random like a
Alienware tournament and I got in and they didn't kick me out and I played I I cannot join
I cannot join that game. By the way, did you play for I think clg and I went against tsm. Yeah
No one on clg went like hey, that's not our player bruce
When I do password and hit go
They didn't give a fuck but I just you might need a relog or remake your party remake the party
All right restart the game
There's a black screen here. I'm sorry. I don't forgive you. I do. I hope you did. You're welcome
I just saw the germ of picture
You sleeping to xcc?
What
That's not edited by the way, I actually was watching that
Did you post in the chat? Okay
Wait, wait. Oh my god
That's how exactly how I imagined you would look like
Like what do you mean? Like like sleeping with uh, I guess a computer like a computer like on your on your chest
Is that the juicer? I thought it would fall over though
You just because you stay completely still I get I must I just I just like do like I could do like a corpse
And just don't move. That's kind of weird
I don't know this dude. You love some gambas streams, bro
If you sleep on your if you sleep on your back you get sleep paralysis guys
I excuse me. I love my juicer. Okay, I don't care what he's doing
Good. That's what we like to hear. No wonder you're always juiced up on green tea
Uh, yeah, we can't we we're with i'm stuck in authenticating
Poggers
My games with that
What is that you should play games with the juicer?
I would but
Loaded in busy guy. I'll get it happening. I'll get my guy to talk to my guy
I'm in oh, did you get in? Let's just play five man among us. I'll get my guy
Among us
Six man among us
I would turn my face cam off. We all know I can't do that. Yeah, you can you can be shirtless on stream
Yeah, but I know
What do you mean? No, wait, wait, we do are we doing the last game and among us is that what you said?
Yeah
Six it's five e five among us
The smite actually that's actually the bracket the bracket is among us. That's that's when we start the serious games
Tell them you're the sus guy guys. They they don't care. Does anybody in this call give a shit that i'm the sus guy
Nope
Please uh, I was part of the eight harbingers. So
Nobody nobody cares i'm just saying they made it they made a news article about me for being the one of the best imposters
Literally everyone said I was one of the eight harbingers. I don't know what you're talking about
Yeah, among us did that update and got to double for me. So
Yeah, but 3d among us is coming out soon. So
3d among me
I mean, you know, I just forgot we're doing nothing. Can you get can you get re-invited?
We can't even get in the server
I got in. Oh you got it. Okay. Yeah, I got it
We're doing stuff. I was just chilling. How come vr among us didn't take off. I thought that was way more interesting
Wait then
That was vr chat. Yeah, which is probably better than the game. Who knows? Yeah, it was it was sick
We'll find out. Yeah. I don't know. We were so hot off that last game that we're cooling down here. This is not good
Yeah, they're throwing it's actually good because uh, you know, I feel like I peed so I kind of reset
And now like I feel stronger you played worse after you pee, you know that I'm gonna I fuck
I'm the one who said that fellas fellas. I'm going for three green teas. I'm going fucking crazy
I'm going for it. You're about to pass a stone brother. It's green tea. It's good for you. Don't wish that upon anybody, bro
I bet he puts sugar in it. No, no. No, I actually yeah
Oh sometimes i'm saying no to actually yeah, well because it depends on the day sometimes I just have like matcha powder
Are you gonna lie to us?
Well, sometimes no, please don't say that anymore. I don't want to be that guy anymore
All right, let's see if I can get some of you guys in here. Look at his feet
What was that noise? It was like
That was my sword
All right, are we uh?
Who are we missing here me and poke?
I can't uh poke you have a pending party invite me and russell just get duo
Oh, yeah
That's how do I join your party? I think it's it's it's it's it. Yeah. Yeah, I gotta leave me. I think
Sorry, I joined too early. I prematurely joined
Bye prematurely man. See if we can get in here shit. I need a I need a third green tea now
Royale
There we go
You get it. Are you still joining pokey?
No, I need I need
It says it says you have a pending party invite
How do I see this?
No, I don't know. Can you poop? Yeah. Yeah, I think I want to poop
Oh, no, do you have a bidet?
Pending party invite no code. Do you have a bidet? I don't have a bidet yet. Oh just shut on them
I'll shower. I'll shower too. I was just gonna say because if you just swear to while you're pooping it you poop faster
What?
Why?
Why am I not seeing your invite man? It says you have a pending invite from somebody
Can you like clear your invites or something?
uh
There we go. All right. So now you know, uh
All right, I'm joining join offer. That was weird. It's a black screen. Uh, yeah
It's got to stay that way for a little bit. All right new uh new lobbies up. We're good
We're not good. No, cuz I hear this tournament relies on us right now. We need to stall forever
All right. I'm reading power of god right now. Okay. Um, here we go. Does it work password is
bacon and
Eggs, dude, you're muted. You're not muted
All right, we're in all right. I'm gonna take this opportunity to get maybe one half green tea
I'll be right back. Yeah, half with with sugar sugar spice and everything nice, dude
There's no green tea. He's just taking a massive bong hit. That's the poke method
Jerma smokes bongs
Would you believe it? Okay, everyone muted dude. I always I keep zoning out. I don't know why yeah, because i'm not jerma
Yeah, that's exactly it actually poke. I hate hearing your fucking voice. You're so stupid
And honestly, i'm gonna punch you in your face next time I see you. Is that what you wanted to hear?
You can't even reach me bro taller than your ass. Okay, that was kind of weird
That was actually really rude. Well, he's not here. You're gonna physically hurt me
I'd say you will be hurt. Did I say that? I don't think I said you will be hurt
You said you're gonna punch me dude. You're acting crazy. I'm twitch reporting you partner on partner. That's fucked up
I got you chill chill. Okay, let's do this, baby. I just searched. Yeah
That first character they picked has a bit of alt that sucks you into them
Um, and then two damaging abilities and a root
He's all ranged. It's mad. I mean all those guys i'm good. I'm good. I'm good. I'm here seem like they play smile. I'm good. I'm good
I had to cut my poop short
No, i'm good. Huh? I fucking I'm
Did you still have some inside of you or something?
Yes, I I popped the stream open. I was like, I wonder if we're gonna start soon and I fucking I knew how to pick
Why don't you just that's the type of player we like
Now i'm gonna play insane because I need to poop
Wait, you didn't poop
I like half poop. Hey, honestly man. This is uh, this is a hundred thousand dollar tournament just shit in your pants
You can buy a new fucking pair of pants
That's a good point
Like if if we're in the middle of the last team fight and we might win the tournament you could buy a new rug myself
Who's better here uler or artemis?
I mean, you're better with artemis as well. You don't know that you don't know that you don't know that you're warmed. You're warmed
You don't know that
This guy's turtle heading bro
And there's a turtle on the other team. Ew
Dude, I see
You would genuinely play better if you just let it all go
Is that just me
Like you were saying earlier kali jungle. Yeah, but but that's for peeing for pooping. It's different like you're
You keister that you're not gonna feel good
Is this uh, if we lose how many more games we have?
This is the last one
You win you keep going. I think if you lose you're done, but there's no like website or anything to check
Is uh, I guess anybody out already or two in one win?
I think you go to semis and then the winner that goes to finals
All right, how many teams even are in this tournament? Yeah, is anybody out already or I don't I don't I'm sure somebody is
I think there's four no. Well, if someone's oh and two they have to be out of four. There's two groups of four
And there's four people per group
Yep, so if we come in like fourth or fifth place, that means we get we still we're still um able to get maybe like
three to four dollars each, right?
Oh
What are you just beat is oh and two so they're done and snuffy's team is done
What is baron's
other abilities beside his ult
Uh, his two is a circle and if it hits on you it will heal his team and does damage to you
Is one is like a crisscross line ability that does damage and then his three he throws it out if it hits you
It sticks to you and slows you and then roots you up for a second
Who am I playing against collie?
You're gonna be against that bear in the top guy
Is he what is oh that's which that or you're gonna be against the turtle
One of the other which one's what does he do to bite it? So if the the top guy's a mate or the bottom guy
There and he's a mage. Um, like I said, he suck you in results. He has damaging abilities and he has a root
Um, he doesn't have any movement though. Like he can't like blink away or anything like that
Yeah, the turtle has a dash and if he hits you he can push you
His ultimate will knock you up a bunch of times and then he has a little turtle he can throw you
And he has an ability that will make him glow and if he glows he reflects damage like if you auto him
It'll reflect damage. Oh, so I shouldn't hit him when he glows. Yeah, it also lowers his cooldown. All right
I gotta go. Good luck boys. Good luck
Oh, let's do it. What do you mean? Good luck. We need the luck not him
Well, he has to watch us. Oh, that's true. I think we're gonna we're in a good position here. I think
Why is everyone's like border so cool? I'm nervous because they play the character a lot
That guy has 2016 smite what
I have beta tester bro. Oh, never mind. We're chilling. Yeah
I was actually in the alpha of this game
Is that legit or are you just saying that it's like a legitimately different game now?
This is unfair matchmaking
Yeah, they couldn't change the teams because why don't we just have germa play anubis?
I mean, I I have a diamond level 10 anubis. I'm surprised
So
I've had that that's not I didn't make a joke or anything. What did I say? That was funny. No, I know
it's just
It was diamond level 10 anubis. Like the game would have been over if I was on anubis
I just don't understand why that's a funny joke. That's
That's not it. I wasn't trying to be funny
Sometimes that's the best way to be funny isn't it when you're not even trying to it is mildly funny
Especially since sure for is laughing. It does make me want to laugh
See see sure for does have a contagious laugh. Thank you. I'll let everyone laugh. I'm smiling
Hey, by the way, I went I I practiced yesterday in the afternoon with anubis
And just like oh just in case maybe I might play it didn't know what I had no idea what the setup was going to be
Um, I didn't land one mummify in five games
Oh, it was awful. So I was like, oh shit. Hopefully I don't have to play this character
Well, I guess it worked out
Yeah, wait, he said buy deaths deaths embraces something else that's toll
And transcend death's toll. He has it. He has it in the discord. It's death's toll and morningstar morningstar. That's what it was
Oh, yeah, you and folk have the same build
All right, you guys ready?
my
Relic guys be careful. I'm gonna invade closer to my face
Rosaline actually invading this game. Um rosaline ready to win?
Yeah, mommy
Help me poppy. Yeah puppy
How do you guys like your eggs?
Scramble
Okay, sunny side, but if it has like the egg come stuff on the top
I want it. Oh wait, I think it's like
As we cook perfectly sorry, I only like eggs if it's a wasteful thing
Okay, well over medium is what I like
No, it's about to spawn. Oh my god guys. This is wait. This is a hard team. We're gonna face this hard team
Yeah, but I don't be worried right now. You're taking remember? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
That's what I say. You look really cool
Thank you. Do you like my skin?
And that's all that matters
Yeah, but I wanted to hear it again, I'm not saying again, oh i'm not gonna say it again the morale already, huh pokey
don't care
Wait, where's the oh?
I'm playing there
All right now going through this way this way. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
Wait, we're actually kind of popping off
You just blocked me. I lost I lost a minion. No, we didn't we didn't we're good
Uh, there's like a turtle here. What is this?
Yeah, he's being rude i'm gonna play i'm gonna ward actually
Yeah, I've worked here
Good luck. Thank you
Okay, we're doing damage
Yeah, we need level three then we get repression right side with traps mid's missing right now mid's missing already. Damn. Okay
Okay, that could be
From he went left side. What is this? It's a it's his turtle. I don't know what to do. I warded
I warded deep in the jungle
Yeah, mid's back mid
And they're junglers mid too, huh?
If they're junglers mid that means we're probably good to get dude. I'm killing this thing. I'll kill it for you
Okay
They're like clearing camps together
Is this money thing or no?
Well right side are they still uh in the lane they went right side. They might be ganking, huh?
Yeah, watch yeah watch right side
They're back mid together
Yeah, are they are they just staying in the lane together?
I don't know they keep clearing and then going and farming and then clearing
Push right side
Why have lane minion came to me
We're doing damage though, it's kind of good
Hello, wait governor tip in the morning to you. No, they both gone again. Wait. Wait my ward's missing
Yeah, she's probably getting his room. I'm the ward behind us actually instead of in front. I had to take the kills
I warded on the camp
I don't know. They keep just she just keeps soaking
mid xp
They're going left side mid and jungler going left side. Yep
Do I take a camp maybe?
You do right side right
Careful over there. Yeah, check left side. Be careful. Okay, it's back mid
Yeah, he's nice. That's actually big for us
Yeah, I keep starting the wrong thing if that agni pushes up. I might jump on him
Although agni can get away pretty easily. He needs to get a little
Um, i'm going in
That's all right
Yeah
Yeah, they really are kind of hanging out here together. I'm gonna go buy
Wrong button
making a base
15 ah shit 1550 is what I need not 1500 shit
Do you want me to gank mid with you?
No, i'm back just saying mid and jungler going right side mid and jungler going right side mid and jungler going right side
Wait mid and jungler right side watch
There's an item you can get that lets you tp to towers
All right, let's go
Wait, they're actually just sitting mid. Oh, yeah. Yeah, let's well, let's push this for real quick
They're going left side now. Really? I'm gonna pack
Yeah, mid and jungler left side
mid's mid
I want to do a fight. I don't know
possibly
Okay, i'm down. Yeah, I don't know what their ults do though
I don't know. I don't know how strong they are
I got ult down. There's so many minions. I might miss. Yeah. Yeah, that's fine. Thank you for doing
Yeah, that's what i'm supposed to be doing. I will unfortunately have been pretty inconsistent with it more items more items
Let's be now so we can come back for the the right side
Okay, farm warding mid's going left side
Oh, yep. Okay, two
Uh, they they're not they're not the healthiest. We might be able to get do something here on left. They're coming in on you
Wait
i'm here
We might be able to fight this
Am I better traded I hurt them you got this germa I don't too fast
Russell we push me right side a lot of minions. Wait, can we take the right side?
I need 1500. I don't have enough to do that yet
Wait, I think we have more purple our purple's gonna be up
Yeah, i'm coming to get uh your guys buffs over here
Yeah, I think they're just sticking together
You know
Kind of hard we do that
Oh, wait, I don't know where it is. Never mind. I'm done. We're right here pushed. I'm i'm not there
I have ward up in 22 seconds. I got my ult in 10 seconds. Come with me
Oh, they took that how far up are they they push push pretty far up, huh?
Yeah, mid's going right side really
What are you doing? Yeah, it's right here warding. No, just poking
Okay, uh mid's missing. It's missing. Yeah, he's mid. All right. Sorry left side left side. How you guys doing on right?
good good
All right. I'm gonna try killing mid. Should we not try to like let's try it
I don't know
No, not killed them, but maybe like, I don't know
Fucking if he steps out of that tower i'm going in
All right, trying to bait him a little bit. Yeah, i'm ready. I'm going in
Oh shit, he pushed me. I'm dead
Don't die from the tower. Thank god
He he pushed me in my jungle. Oh my god
Oh shit, i'm dead
I sure just ran fuck. All right
Yeah, my bad. Fuck. I did not see him push
Wait, let's get this xp. I gotta buy
oh
All right, then i'll back too. I had to buy an item that has the stacks on that thingy
I think I was supposed to get it earlier crap
He's gonna do the totem thingy
I'm gonna go for purple then right side. I was trying to eat. Wait, should I not get it with you?
Because I was scared of the hell, but I should have just ran 20 20 hindsight. That was stupid of me
Happens to the best of us
I mean i'm almost here
You can start it. Oh my traps up a trap of right side actually
Agnes going left side
Okay, mid's gone here. I'm here left side's gone left side's gone. Yeah, so agony's going left side
What's in our jungle what's in our jungle I think
Are they going right you got minions on you the agony's been left side
I don't know where he went. Oh, he went back to lane
If you want he could push me if you want to like gank this I could try it. Yeah, I know he'll push me
Wait, wait, wait, they take these agnes missing right now. All right. I'm coming. I'm coming. I'm here
If they push you i'm ulting
All right, i'm ulting i'm ulting i'm pulling him i'm pulling come back come back
Nice good job
You too
Being i'm being right away. All right, I gotta go. Bye
Now you're getting good
Good I didn't die
Huh? I'm not agony's missing
It's good. I didn't die. It's good. Yeah. Oh, yeah, it's good. You didn't die
Okay, I did put these wards down at fire turn or something
They're taking right. I don't think fire giant's gonna be done anytime soon
I'm gonna go for purple buff
Agnes going right side somewhere. Oh, no
I leveled up the wrong wall. Yeah, I wonder where they're still up. No
Right side. Yeah. All right. I gotta go back to farm left side
Hello
Is that what you got? No
I'm gonna get these mid camps. No, no, they're gone. Let's go. Let's go a jungle, right?
Get some control of the map maybe or no
Okay, you can try to do it
There's no push that we can do
I'm boarding deep. Oh, I don't have board yet
All right. There we go. Take this probably dead
You can rotate and push
Yeah, i'm with you brother
We're going mid. We're going mid anyone mid i'm coming mid
He's gonna do fire giant if you want to kill you want to gank right now. He's going he's going fire. Yep
All right. We're coming. We're coming then
He's in the jungle
I hear him this night jungle. I think he's right here
Yeah, he's in there fire
Big
Nice. Oh my
That's what we like to see baby. Let's go. Let's go objective objective objective. We do fire giant or no?
Yeah, we could do fire giant. I think
It's gonna do a lot of damage
Yeah, you can back out whenever it's looking good we get fired
I'm coming. I'm coming. Oh, what the fuck reset? Oh shit. It killed me. No
What the fuck
Oh my god
You guys should have not bailed and just hit it yeah, I I was dead dude, I did I did
Well, did we just lose?
No
I think we just because they didn't get any of the gold they got tower though
That's so fucking funny and now they're getting harpy. Oh god. What the hell it doesn't matter
It's fine
You just we just needed to not leave
It's michael
I think we should have waited for you to get there, too
Yeah, probably I was at like 30% health when it started and I was just dead
It's all right. Hey, hey
We don't go jungle other we're doing good
Yeah, we're doing fine. Everything's good. Everything's good
Just keep winning team fights. Keep keep fucking them up
Yeah, we just need to push out towers poke and then just rotate
Or push out minions in the rotate because then we just we win every fight
Wait, what am I jump shit?
That's so funny team what we we did that was like a fucking warcraft raid don't worry, uh, apparently
That happened to tectone's team as well. So that's so funny
I'm doing right side alone. Where are you? Where are you?
Agnes listen
You gotta call it out when you're going brother, I thought you said right side
He's like left side jungle he just ran on my ward
Have to back up. I don't know if you want to gank. No, this is what it just awarded right here. Excuse me
Oh, no, i'm coming. I see him. I see him. I see him. Oh wait, never mind. He's here. I thought they were with two or three people
Yeah, watch out. Be careful. You don't want to get jumped on
I'm, they're trying to jump on me. That shit fucking hurts. Oh my god. Oh it does
Yeah, cali's mid
Where uh, they pushed up for it all I could I could try to jump on it
They went to your left. Yep, just trying to get the scorpion. We're doing the scorpion. Yeah, he's trying to fucking kill me
I'm gonna come right side
They're being aggro as hell
They're gonna be aggro and we should we should back off. I think they know you're coming. They have minions and everything. So let's back off
Wait, wait, wait, you guys are coming right side, which is we're just gonna check it in
They're coming to you guys. They're coming to you guys. Yeah, they're here
We're here
You got my tower
He's out leveling this shit out of me. Oh shit. I get purple
Can you do it alone or should I help ash right? Yeah, I got it
I'm going to red and i'm gonna push out
Nothing go by
Oh, they're coming. They're coming on you. Yeah, all right coming coming coming
They knew
I don't want to get I don't want to get caught here, but
We can out we probably do this
Is that mid i'm coming i'm coming
I'm here i'm here. Oh, no. Oh, they're all one shot. Oh, no
I wouldn't have killed him anyways if I didn't
Wait, do we win or you backing off? What is that on my ult? Okay
Okay
I only got one on that ult
Yeah, if you got the uh baron, I would have been a kill i'm coming back poke
Yeah, he he just I just couldn't get him. I couldn't kill him
It's okay. Oh, he's jumping on me right now. He I think he ages. That's how we got away. You're alone
But i'm coming. Oh, yeah, the cali egg is
Damaged i'm here here
I can't reach him though
Yeah, I can't reach him. Damn it. He tried it though. You see that
Yeah, you fucked him up the shit
That ward's about to die. I forgot to buy new ones. Oh, they're both low. I i've my ult's up in 25
If they if they don't back, they're purple
I'm warding. Oh
I got him. I'm here. I'm here. Careful. The entire team is gonna go over the union. What is that?
Oh agony's man, we're chilling. Damn it. I should have
They're coming. They're coming
That's why they're pushing that's why they're pushing
Yep, we're good. We're good. We're good
And drop this blue for us good though
If they if they push I have all just saying
I'm gonna get out of these mid camps here. Oh, I have 1800 gold. I'm gonna never mind. They're gone
You're gonna be alone. You're gonna be alone. I'm backing actually. Wait, let's take this right side first. Yeah
Oh, sorry
I'm coming, right?
Wait, we're not there. Yeah, I can I can
Never told you
Uh 1900 2k
The enemy has fully powered their obelisks i've let trebuchet whatever is coming in
They might be doing fire. They might be doing fire. Are they I doubt it. They would need all five to do that
They're on this side though
I can go left side
I mean, yeah
If you run to me, I can help
Hope
I cannot use my abilities
Wait, I can I can we can still fight them right side. Can't we if i'm there? Why can I press g sure for?
Well, they're gone already I thought they might push oh too mid though. I spam g
Fuck man, there's three behind behind behind. I was bearing there too
Yeah, I don't even know but there were three watch out mid watch out mid. Don't don't push don't push
There's a guy coming from right side. Yep
I'm gonna go up. Okay, i'm just gonna push me if I can get there man. They're just doing objectives too
Yeah, yeah, because they're getting kills
Oh behind you. Oh, fuck me. Can you survive? Can you drive? No
No, I should have magic shelled. Fuck. Why did I alt?
Hey, man, there's three right side
All right, we maybe we should start moving as a team now. Yeah, they're kind of catching
They're they kind of passed us on gold pretty hard
All I can we only can really do is push lanes
This is cali by herself almost max. We probably get this cali
She's gone
What is she completely gone?
Find it out. Yeah, she's up here somewhere
I don't have to complete my build
Nobody here in middle, huh?
one's up there on my right side
And there's a kid in the mid
There's two mid
You guys want to try some do something on right side?
Yeah, i'm down. They're just playing passive by the looks of it
Yeah, we just need more wards
Oh shit
I can come to call me
I'm warding like very I'm not I boarded I warded right here
But she's she ran back
We can take right tower
Yeah, they're eight cubes mid
There's like i'm coming i'm coming mid right now
We go mid there's four mid i'll push right i'll push right alone. Okay, i'm behind you
No, she's literally one shot. She's literally one shot. Cali's one. Just get out. There's all five are here
Yeah, i'm out if I stay there
Let's get out
Fuck. Oh, they all went right for me
Oh, what the fuck?
All right
Well, that was just scary. He just tanking the turret like that. They just
They got things like that
What is that? He was thinking that it was a turtle. He was just thinking the fucking are they are they all up there still?
Yeah, they were still here but careful. Okay, they're going back there
barons right here
Ramis three was
You took my buff
What can I drop it? No, it's like red book
We're no problem
It's a reasonable. Sorry
It's all right. I'll do a lot with it. I promise
I believe me
All right, what's left side? Is there anything left side that's up right now?
Um, we could try to do what the pyro is up in a minute
We need to ward it. We need to ward it. Yeah
They're going mid we should do something mid
They're doing they're doing one of the camps in the middle. They're getting ready for pyro careful
I'm trying to get as much xp as I can right now
Can we kill this?
They're definitely setting up for pyro for sure
I don't have a ward right now though
I got a ward up there
There's a ward up there
I'll clear left left. Okay
I'm ulting. I'm ulting. I'm ulting. I'm pulling this guy
We need that we need that
His all makes so he can't die. Well, he has turned to mirror all in that all
So if we don't have a stun or something they can just run
Yeah, they're all hanging out here. No, it was alt for alt. Yeah
I think they I think they want to do pyro
There watch out baron baron baron baron's right here
Coming they're coming in. Oh fuck
22 seconds to my ult
Oh, that sucked. I'm here. I'm here
I could be that I got fucking destroyed
God damn it
Yeah, I tried to flash away
Oh my god, I died so fast
I got picked by the turtle. I couldn't move and I got melted
I don't even know what happened to me
They were getting noob stomped by a kali right now for two weeks and the team was announced like what a week ago cheaters confirmed
Before I don't want to buy
Fuck me
I mean it's it ain't over. I mean we're down we're behind like this before
We did come back we have we still want to get money, yep
They're all level 20 and we're not even close
What we need to do is one win one team fight
Yeah, that's all matter. It's like an hour fun for an hour. We good
Just farm for an hour under towers. You can just enter towers
Yeah, the fire giant really was a was a big a big negative
We lost our momentum after the fire giant
Imagine if we got it farm for an hour
What is this thing?
I didn't buy awards
They're in mid right now
Three minutes take this gold fury
Mid yeah, they kill mid three in mid right now. I'm pushing it. I'm pushing it four in mid right now
They're in the tower right now
We met just four they're all here
Every single person's here. They destroyed the tower
They're coming in. They're coming into the jungle coming to the jungle
I'm here. I'm here. I'm pulling them from the jungle one on me. Fuck it. I'm taking them
I'm died
Holy fuck cali can't die in a roll. So
Holy shit, what's going on fair match making out there?
ggs
Oh, it's not over yet. It's not over. It's not over. I don't know. I'm just i'm just uh
Just saying things
I gotta heal same i'm so close
Once we get even in gold and xp, we have a better team fight than them
Yeah, they're mid gold the gold series is just gold right nice luck. Yeah, we're better
i'm just gonna wait for my item then because
What else am I gonna do at this point?
I got I need eight gold
Collapse kevin
So that's what I just said. We just sit under tower and fucking
We just have to kite them or wait for big air results
Because if you forced too much the colleagues just gonna press r and not that
Russell you're gonna make the game when you play russell
I am going to try my best
Tried to eat that guy, but it didn't work trying to catch up in levels and xp
All right. Let's uh, let's group up somewhere
They're they're they're right here. I'll get the buff here. They're all right here
Oh fuck
I'm like holy shit that her fucking hurts. I'm out. I think we should be trying to run
I
If we die here it's over
I mean I can wave clear fuck they're in mid right now three in mid
I have all
I have good wave clear so they can't push too much. It's gonna be hard for them to get into the phoenix air
They're all going left though. They're probably gonna get that left tower
I'm up in four. I'm with you sure for
Yeah, they're on left
What the fuck they got that siege tower, too
Okay, they all use their fucking
Thing anybody low are they low these beads?
No beads
I could jump on top right now and just say fuck it. Whatever. I'm gonna hit the trebuchet
My ult's up in 42 seconds
Two of them use their their beads
Don't push up too hard because I don't know where they are. I don't need
All right, I got full stack here. It's a lot of them don't have beads anymore. That'll be good for the next fight
Oh, I didn't want that
Are they uh, they're not doing fire turn or anything. They're doing they're doing it go go go go go go go
This is where we do it. Oh, that's bad
Don't die now
We just wait this out then that was the chance I went in like I actually caught some they're also low
I wasn't there
We were all we were all just barely out
Honestly, I'm pretty tall we may have uh, we may have gotten in
It's possible. We would have gotten in and killed somebody but if they killed devire giant we're all
Yeah, which is really fine. Yeah. Yeah
So we just have to play slow again
They're all up here
At least one of them i'm going to buy i'm gonna go buy real quick might as well
Yeah, go finish your bills if you have I think everybody just go buy. Yeah, i'm buying words to finish your bills if you have any
We need a water jungle really bad
You're dead
Oh my god, I am
Yeah
We have to play by the tier threes. Sorry
Yeah, I mean at least my death isn't that bad
No, it is pretty bad
They can yeah, because they're on an initiator
Yeah, okay
I think they're I think they're gonna go for it here
Oh, yeah, they are. Yep. I'm dead. They're just fucking aping me. Yeah
Sorry guys
No, the sander tower sander tower
Yeah, kali's invincible with the owner
Yep, she's a noob stomper
They're hacking
That was so hard
Yeah
I don't think i'm doing enough
I definitely was not
Dude, i'm telling you the odds are stacked against us because otk tournament and they want tectone to win
gg
They had four sumi pros and tectone
Sure, it's an nt. What the heck
I'm kidding. I'm just maybe we get more magic damage. Don't don't we get more magic damage? Oh
That wouldn't have changed anything. I'm magic. They even hired the fire dragon to get I was just dead half the time
the fire giant
Wow, well
Um gg guys, I guess, you know, it was a good try wasn't it? Wait, wait, we're done
Yeah, yeah, we're out. Where's our coach?
He's giving up on us. He doesn't even want to hear from us
I think
Oh tiebreaker
We might have another chance do we have another chance for the for the hundred million dollars
I think the tiebreaker is like the wind speed though, like whoever won the fastest out of all three of you guys
So I don't know who that is
We got noob stomp by kali. I forgot her alt makes her unkillable
Well, you guys like we're actually fragging until you all died to the fire giant. Yeah, that was the turning point that that was like
If we uh, I think we probably would have won the game if we didn't die there
If you had done the fire before like a couple times you guys wouldn't have died to it
It was just because you guys didn't know
That would have been a nuts call. Like you would have just won the game that early, too
Well, what happened was they started without me and then they also ran away. Yeah
I didn't even know
I I was in I died first. I I was in there with 40% health and just died
I tried to jump away with like 10% health and just got instantly killed. That's all right
If we win the tiebreaker, we're still freaking going strong
That would be I need to put can I pick something that hits like hits harder maybe more cc like
Uh, yeah, we can we can give you something else if there's another game
Oh, yeah, true. If there's another game
That baron dude was nuts. He was just bragging me out like just sucking me in and pulling everybody in he was kind of tanky, too
Yeah
Dude that kali was just
Oh, yeah running through us
Yeah, you you forget that it's like oh my god, i'm gonna kill the kali. No, she's invincible for like 10 seconds
Yeah
And even your brain is still just like why why is why won't she die? I'm hurting her they hacked
They were aim locking
and wall hacking
Yeah, so what's the uh,
What's the what's the what's the story now? We're waiting for in the game
The top teams are playing for the championship like the teams are the best records and then I don't know who's playing for second or
Who's playing for third?
Hmm
They're talking about it. I think we just have to wait and see gamers
Well, it's fun at least
Yeah fun
We gotta see you naked
That's true
Yeah, that's a good time
Just blame Russell move on that was definitely my adc's fault
adc's are just
I did throw i'm sorry
Adc's are weak bro. You know how it works. Sorry Russell
No, wait, we we just we just injected steroids and just screamed and we were just going crazy and then just ran
Straight as fast as we could into a brick wall
Yeah, there was a fire giant. It was just like I could fucking do anything
With the hype behind fucking pokes voice too. He was like
I thought we could have done I think I think we can we could have done it but we did it bad
Wait, no, we could have we
Screaming fire giant like we're just doing a fucking ritual and then we just died
I mean, I feel like we all had so much health for a second and then it just went away fire giant hurt. Yeah
Hey, I think we did pretty good for a bunch of people. Hey
How many we haven't played the game in like six or seven years somebody eight years?
Noco you downloaded the game two hours ago
Yeah, I think I think we did pretty good. I think we did pretty damn good. No, he didn't
Yeah, we all did great. Like I think I even outlained like a professional league of legends pro
I think I think we did really good
Then I think we could probably get like third place
I mean russell didn't show up yesterday
Come on I didn't do bad
That's copium. Hey, we're allowed to huff copium. We just group b is wait both groups have three o's and then one twos
Across the board. So wait, are we going to be third place?
I don't know. Do we get money?
We might be second
Bro, we bro we get money
Wait, no, but that's not the bracket is it are we playing to get in the bracket?
I don't get it. I honestly don't understand how this is working
He said whoever loses in the semis, I don't know what the fuck that means. Do we get third?
So how long from now is that?
I don't even know
Wait, do only the top teams from the group play now
They play for the finals like you're playing the final championship game already
But there's I guess a loser's like third place
Oh, I see there's okay 70 years
There's 3030 12 12 12 12 12 12 12 12. Wow. Oh, all right. That's gonna be a shit show to figure out
That's gonna be an absolute shit show
Oh, yeah
Wait, dude, i'm hungry
I need food. I just need to know if we play more or not
Yeah, same because if not i'm going to apex
I thought you were trolling by the way 12 12 12 12 12. Is that troll? Nope. No, it is real
Those are the numbers. There's only one team really dangerous. There's six teams with one two and there's two teams with three. Oh, huh
Oh two teams with three. Oh, okay. Yeah two teams three. Oh, can we just all share a third place like that would be fine, right?
Yeah, wait, that's actually such a good idea. Why doesn't otk just give us all money?
We're just like hey everybody else lost but you did a good job
Yeah, I think isn't it? Isn't that basically what twitch rivals is?
Yeah
Yeah, I think the only thing good thing about this right now is that it's about the rain. It's about the what the rain
It's about to rain. Oh
I love the rain. Oh, could I leave?
We should get paid for being held hostage
Honestly true
I have so much to do guys. I'm very hungry. Wouldn't you have to be a you freaking busy man or something?
Yeah, I mean, I guess we could I guess we could just like host the main stream and
Just go you're gonna end stream in I was honestly just trolling. I have nothing. Well, actually yeah, I do I do
but not like
Pay us pay us now. Oh because they bet I see they bet on our team winning the whole thing
Oh, did they actually well, well he's talking about his yeah twitch channel points. Yeah
I was like damn they really believed in us like that
I was like, no, I feel like I let everybody down
Uh, there is definitely not a chance to win the tournament. So I think that is official, right? Yeah
No
My fight money. I want to say i'm just really happy that I uh, I knew what buff camps were what i'm proud of you
I think I think that was a good one
That was intense. That was fun. Did you get you riled up? I did. I think you guys are done. Yeah, we didn't make it
No
Wait, what place did we end up?
Thank god. Oh man, we're not in the last place. Are we?
Oh, oh, okay
How did they even decide who got thrown out? I think we're all last place for playing smite
I think it was fastest win from our bracket fastest win from the other bracket our freeze
Our fight money
I had a reverse monster gg guys. I mean all that matters that we tried our best, right? I was naked on camera today
Well, you weren't on camera
Someone took a picture of you. I was literally naked
You keep saying you were wearing shorts. Are you lying now? Yes. Wait, but which one is the line guys ggs? Yeah
Thanks for playing
I shall see you guys later. Bye. Bye. Yep. Take it easy
Thanks, uh, thanks we can for trying to help uh, he's already gone man. He's already gone
He's like, I I could have made money on some other things like I could have made 12k bro
You give me that you give me a bunch of fucking chumps. Yeah
That's not like with the losers. All right, did you guys see you later guys? Thanks for playing. All right guys
That was the uh, that was the tournament. I think we played pretty well fire giant shit that we were I think we were just high
You know on our own supply
I think for like I said before a couple people that hadn't really played the game before
And then the rest of the team hadn't really played that much for years. I think we did pretty well
I think that was that was a good showing we could have played a lot better obviously, right?
But whatever it was so fun. It was fun. Yeah, hopefully it was fun to watch
Yeah, sorry. I wasn't really interacting with the chat at all. I'm trying to at least
Be somewhat involved in the the call-outs and stuff. But yeah, I I think that's it. That's pretty much all I had planned
I want to um
I want to just make sure I reiterate
The next stream is going to be uh, the green screen stream, which would be the 30th
I have hundreds of actions i'm going to do in front of the green screen. It should be a fun time
It always is so see ya in front of see at the green screen stream
I don't really have a start time, but it's going to be somewhere in the afternoon pacific
But I want to make sure that i'm ready to go so I don't really have like a hard starting time
Just so i'll let you know at some point in the afternoon june 30th
Uh, congratulations or good luck to whoever is going to win this tournament because I mean it's 100k
It's a lot of money. So good luck. And yeah, I i'm not going to do any really altar or anything
I just was kind of streaming. So there's another perspective good night. Goodbye
I'll probably just i'll probably just raid ms gif. I mean that obviously right that makes sense
Let's raid ms gif so you can see the end of the tournament if you want. Good night. Goodbye much love to you
And i'll see you soon. Thanks for watching guys. See you soon