Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here and Boo. Hello. Playing some smite.
Gonna be a live commentary. Gonna showcase Apollo, the god of music. Now don't ask me why.
Apollo is the god of way more things than just like music. But they kind of have to put that there.
Because there's way too many things he could be. Let's go. Where are we going? Right. Okay.
Oh, but bro. Oh, come on, Cupid. Don't do this to us. Did they want to go right?
Well, Aokwong is mid. What? Are we gonna have like a party over here? What did he say?
I think he's going left. What the hell is he talking about? I don't even know.
I think he wanted to go with this Aokwong. Like I think they might be premade. Yeah.
Or maybe not. I don't even know. I just want to get a piece of cake from the cake slug.
Who's getting this? You take this. Okay. I hope this tornado doesn't just kill him.
Alright. Thank you. Let's do it. You know the speed buff now gives you attack speed as well.
Oh yeah, it does. 10%. Which is why it's better for the physical guys to take it.
Especially for ranged because you can just pop the minions easier. Yeah, they did that a little while ago, right?
Yeah, it was last month or something like that.
So for those of you that have no idea who Apollo is, he's the newest god.
If you're watching... Oh, watch out, Ragney. If you're watching this...
Jeez. What the... Okay. Ragney's scary, level one. Yeah, she is. She's aggressive.
She also doesn't got a whole lot of health now, does she?
She'll probably regenerate back. Does she have any potions? I don't know.
Yeah, she has two health potions.
So what I was saying before, Ragney just tried to smoke me.
Apollo is the newest god. If you're watching this right now and like six other gods have been out by then,
then I apologize, but he's ranged. He's pretty powerful. He's got a lot of utility.
I'll try and give you some speed. It should be okay. I got Creeping Cursed.
Okay. Yeah, he's probably my favorite god at this point. I just love the sounds.
Get out of here. This guy. These guys are super aggressive. They are very aggressive, yes.
She's probably going to take our cooldown, right? Yeah, most probably.
That's our cooldown, Ragney. What the hell? Oh crap. I'm not a man in here.
So I guess try not to stand on our minions because Hades will want to dash you and that'll sting a bit.
It really will. She's going to have her pulse soon. We can do one more anyway before she gets it.
Should have got Hand. I should have got Hand of the Gods. Take those away.
She's looking. Yeah, she's right here. She's right here. She's literally right here.
I don't have my dash yet, but Hades is coming. We might build it.
We can fight Hades. No, she's here. She's here. She's here.
I still don't have my dash yet. I don't know why I got my fear first. I was very stupid over here.
Do you think Ragney's going to come back? Yes, she is. She's ahead of us.
So those of you wondering, when I hit 10 auto attacks, I get to shoot five that are really, really fast.
Just like this. Oh boy, there she is. And I'm silenced.
They're diving. No, they're diving. I'm going to go down.
No, you're good. You're good. Just kill that spider. There you go.
Hades did not ult you. No, he's not five yet. Okay.
Ragney's out of mana. Ooh, you going in? Careful. Oh boy, here she goes.
Oh no, no, no, no. We got a Ragney.
I threw an auto attack on her. Oh no, I tried to hit F4 and I hit F3.
Is that your... Oh, you didn't get back up your ult. God damn it.
One thing about this keyboard I don't like is if I hit any of the F keys, I feel like I'm pressing all of them at the same time.
It's quite annoying. But yeah, I threw an auto attack at her and she just jumped right on top of you right when it happened.
I'm not going to do it yet though. Let me know when you want to go in because I'll pop girdle.
Stay away from the minions. Hades is a piece of crap. Oh, well, you're Hades too. Whoops.
Yeah, but I'm a cool looking Hades. He's just a jump default skin Hades.
That's in the middle. That's only Archon. I'm not too scared of Archon.
What's he going in? What's he doing? Well, he's taking a lot of minion damage for this.
Yeah, he sure is. Ragney's right behind. Nice job. Oh, now she knocked her up.
I'll fear her. Let's kill her. Let's kill her. Yeah, she's not going to get away.
Oh, so much damage. I had to Aegis otherwise she was going to kill me.
I was about five mana away from smacking the ground with my three and I would have killed her.
I just didn't have enough. I was unlucky. Good exchange.
Hades, when he dashed, he went to just go slam on minions, but my fear was ranked up and he couldn't do it.
He just took a bunch of archer damage for it and his dash was down so I might as well ult him.
That's true. God, there's so many minions. So many minions.
How's everyone else doing? Oh, they're doing pretty good. Nine and four.
Alcong's holding up mid. He's two and one. Left lane. Cupid's three now. Yep, it's looking good.
Yeah, it's going to be good. I think cooldown buff is back up if you want to grab that.
Hades isn't really going to... Oh, wait, Ragney. Ragney is on your side.
I'll be fine. I'll dash through her. She must have pulled me out. Yeah, she missed. She missed her pull.
Silly girl. Get out of here. Oh, man, her basic attacks do so much damage.
I've got to get Voidblade. Voidblade is next, for sure.
I don't know if she wants it. I'm ulting as well. Yep, just hanging out, shooting autos.
Got one. Oh, she does so much damage. Oh, no. Oh, she webbed it.
Oh, damn, she's strong. Yeah. Son of a bitch. It's that dark, man.
What is she building? A little bit of life still. She hasn't got three yet, though.
She's probably in the jungle. I bet she's over here somewhere.
Yeah, I just hear her put eggs down. She's at Manor, actually. This is risky, isn't it?
Yeah, this is... Well, here she comes. Oh, she just got it.
Just get away from here. I'm going to... Oh, damn, I'm so dead. I'm so dead.
She's almost dead. My last hope. My last... No, boop. No, no, no.
She's one shot. Yep, she sure is. Hey, Ragney.
Oh, you got... Oh, stupid bugs. They're nearly dead. They're easy to kill.
Hades is coming your way, but he's really low. Yeah. Yeah, shoot him, shoot him.
I think you can kill him. You think I can get him? Yeah.
He can't do much damage to you. Yep. No. He's out of Manor as well.
Just shoot him. Oh, as I say... Oh, damn. He meditated.
Did he really use it? Yeah, at least he blew his meditation.
Yeah, I didn't know he was that low. I thought he was at at least more than half.
I don't know why he chased you. He's never going to out DPS here
if he's got no minions to smash, so I don't know what he was trying to do.
I thought he had way more health than that. Oh, well, that's good.
That's a good exchange. I'll take it. I'll take that, yeah.
I don't mind dying for the killing of the Arachne, at least, let alone the Hades two.
Left lane's still doing really solid 5-0 cupid. Oh, wow, yeah.
It's a long case 2-1. It's looking like a GG, but...
So, Paul's ultimate for people that are like, what the hell was that?
If you know Thor, Thor's ultimate is he goes in the air and you can pick a spot to jump down
and it stuns everybody, right?
Apollo's, you can just ride around in the air forever.
Well, not forever. It drains, what, 50 mana per second?
So, you can stay up in the air for as long as your mana can hold
and then you just land right on top of everybody.
It doesn't stun anyone, though. That's the thing, it does not stun anybody.
It just does like, I think it does a dot, right? If I'm not mistaken.
What, no? Apollo, his dot.
Yeah, his ultimate's kind of weird. It's like taking damage, his ultimate.
Oh, my God, every single person is in mid.
Yeah, that was really unlucky. I was about to smash everyone
and as I went to do it, Arachne silenced me. I couldn't.
Oh, they're not in mid anymore.
Yeah, they're building a Doom Orb.
So, he's got a lot of magic power. He hasn't died yet, either.
Arachne's up by Goldfury.
Is she gonna attack Goldfury? I'll jump on top of her if she is.
I think her, I don't know. I think her spider's hatched.
I think we have wards there, I think.
Yeah, I was gonna say. Oh, she's in lane.
I might. Oh, boy, never mind.
I was gonna say, I might be able to go jump on top of her right now.
I don't know. Maybe. Maybe we could.
Hades ult is done. Mine's up. Yep, let's do it.
Alright, I'm going in the air.
I thought she was gonna come backwards.
Oh, she exploded. She blew up.
Nice one. Yeah, I timed my ultimate.
I thought she was gonna go backwards. I never landed on nobody.
That's okay. At least we got them both.
Yeah, she was really far up with no mana.
And, like, not even have health.
I don't know what she was thinking.
We could grab mana. I think it might be up.
Maybe, maybe not. Let's check.
Nah, okay. No.
I don't think it'll be long.
I reckon she's talking about three minutes ago.
Let's just try to get the tower.
Right. Get that little doily. Little doily.
How are you doing? Oh, wow, you're 6 and 2. Nice.
Got a bunch of kills.
Put a bit of her in the tower, but fear that guy.
Fear me.
Let's just not get pulled by her.
Yeah, she's looking for a pull on me.
Nah, she got me, but it's okay.
Oh, shit, okay.
My bad.
Oh, boy, I'm going down here, for sure.
Oh, get out, boo.
She's just so much damage.
I don't think she actually went back to spawn.
I think she just life drained something.
But, yeah, let's not get pulled in.
Hades will have his ult now.
Arachne, I don't get her.
Loki, Loki, Loki.
Loki right here.
Oh, boy. Oh, my God.
Oh, boy.
Trying to get that hit on that Loki.
Oh, one more hit. Come on.
Oh, bitch, I'm going to die from the bleed.
No, you're not.
I feared her while she was hitting you.
That was very close.
I just get back to spawn before Hades
dashes out the jungle on you.
That was so close.
I'm lucky I had that last shot on
my one. My one's what killed her.
Yeah, well, lucky Hades was in there as well.
Loki kind of just, I don't know,
I thought he would have killed you, to be honest.
I know, so really, what does he build?
What does he get for items? Oh, he's only level 13, that's why.
He's just not, he's just been kind of
underleveled all game.
Left lane kind of sorted him out for us.
He definitely would have killed me.
If he was 15 or 16, oh, man,
I would have died in two hits.
I was just lucky.
I'm going to get physical protection for that Arachne.
I don't get Arachne. She's
super strong and scary.
I am terrified of her, but
she's considered one of the worst gods.
Yeah, that's very odd. Oh, right here, right here. Freya.
Freya's right here. Freya's literally right here.
She's on four. She's not too much of a threat.
She can still do big damage.
I might go in here and try to find her. She was just literally
right here. No, I'd say save it.
Save it for them. We all going to jump on this
Loki? Is that the plan? I think we're about to
show this Loki that he's in the wrong
lane. Alright, here we go.
You're in the wrong part of town, son.
Let's see if I can time this. I was going to say
he's right here. He's in the jungle.
Hello. I see Freya
as well. Oh, he's
over here. He's trying to... What, you don't think we can see
you over here?
Was he going to try and pull it through?
I don't know. That was weird. That was very odd.
This got gold. Arachne
probably just soloed that, to be honest.
As long as we... I got the tower.
I found a dragon.
Geez, you really did. Come on!
It was kind of unnecessary.
Alright, I'm going to get out of here. Oh, boy.
Arachne's right here. Arachne's right here. She's right here.
Yep, they're both right here.
Run.
Get out. Get out. Get out.
Get out. Get out. Get out. Get out.
Get out of here. Get out of here. See if a long guy leaves.
Retreat. I don't know. They might be able to get that.
Oh, no.
He's screwed. He's out of manners.
Oh, look at his health going down.
Yeah.
He's doing an attack buff. Oh, of course you got that.
Get him. Get him.
Oh, good dragon.
Right when he does his ult. Beautiful.
Oh, no.
She's not going to get away. Oh, no.
Freya.
No, I didn't. She's life stealing it.
One more hit.
I missed so many auto attacks.
So many auto attacks were missed right there.
My goodness.
Thank god I could hit my one.
Seriously.
There was a Freya. She could ult you.
Oh, my god. You're right. Run. Run. Run. Run. Run.
That actually makes me run faster, doesn't it?
You dashed and the circle hit me.
So I move faster. It's cool.
Yeah.
It's a good buff.
I really need a void stone, but I can't afford one yet.
Let's go with some.
I want some crit and I want some spree.
And I want some more coffee.
I'm kind of glad the Arachne is doing well, otherwise this would just be a steam roll and the game would have been over a long time ago.
At least I'm making a game of it.
Because his left lane just stumped.
Are you building stacks or anything?
Nope.
I never do. I never do.
Well, Devara's Gloves is pretty amazing.
I don't buy it very often.
It's really cheap.
I only found out the other day.
The one thing I don't like about stack items is
you have to get the stacks.
I like the items that just give you the shit.
You get it.
Are you taking this?
You take it. I've already got max cooldown reduction.
Oh, let's go help.
I'm going up.
One of them's down. Loki's dead.
I'm going after Freya right now.
Oh, my prediction was wrong.
It's alright.
They're so dead.
Goodbye.
Nice.
Yeah, we can do Jhin.
There's Arachne.
In fact, if you get Jhin, I'll knock down midtown and make sure Arachne doesn't come.
Sounds like a plan.
Who's tanking this?
I actually think they're waiting for you.
No, they're not.
Arachne's missing now.
She's next to me, actually.
We should kill this before she gets here.
He's almost dead.
He is almost dead.
I'm going to need help with this Arachne.
That's the one.
Thank you very much.
I was just kind of dueling with it, like dancing while you were doing giant,
then you all just popped out on it.
There it is.
GG.
How'd you do?
Pretty good.
Probably wouldn't have had at least
three or four of those kills if not for your ultimate, but
that's how you do it, right?
Thanks for watching, guys.
That's Apollo, the god of music,
the sun, rain, the stars,
and every other thing in Greek and
Roman mythology. He's Greek, right?
Greek, yeah.
I think he's called Apollo in Greek and Roman.
I'm not sure.
Thanks for watching.
My pleasure.
And see you next time. Take care, everybody.
Goodbye, Smite!