This is a game about insta-killing.
So what you t-
Hey lady, welcome everybody to Rats Insta-Gib.
Here we're gonna show you a couple of quick tips and tutorials and strategies
on how to get the most out of your game.
So as you see here, this is Star here.
Star, go ahead and give yourself a- let people know who you are
and what- how- the way they can find you.
Do you see this, like, toxic cloud of, like, red?
Yeah.
You die in this?
I don't know.
Yeah.
Oh, you can't go in this.
It's like lava, huh?
That's really-
Can't stand still either.
That doesn't count. I'm looking at the lava.
I have to hit you once.
Now we're one-on-one. No.
No, look at the- look at the frags!
Look at the frags. It's first to 15 frags.
Oh, okay. Thanks. Fine.
Seriously, you want to pull that on me?
So you could just, like, kill yourself intentionally?
Yeah, it doesn't add to somebody- nobody killed you.
You killed yourself.
Man.
I mean, now we're talking about just kind of running away with it, I think?
I mean-
That was a stupid spawn.
I mean, yeah.
But I'm bad, so.
I mean, I really think it might be possible to really start running away with this.
I hit you!
Did I hit you?
I don't know, did you?
You're starting to run away with this.
You know, you're talking about really starting to run away with something.
Let's get- let me just- let me 15 to 1 you.
Okay, let's talk some comedy.
You want to talk about comedy?
Whoa, how did you know?
Wait, you told me we were going to talk comedy!
I didn't say stop fighting.
Well, no, you weren't shooting, and you said we're going to talk comedy,
and that's when you- I pay attention to that.
It's all right, I got to lead here.
For the first time.
Am I going to have- come on.
Come on, no.
Come on.
My arm just got stuck in the-
It's like-
You got to pay attention!
You got to know where people are going!
How could I?
All right, I can't let this get out of hand here.
It's like a giant maze, and you could be anywhere.
You could be on the roofs.
Yeah, but that's how you play.
I really thought you didn't see me.
Well, you're bright blue.
I changed the- no, listen.
I changed the colors, and you are the same red as everything.
Well, why would you do that?
Because I didn't know we were going to play on the red map.
Like, I made the enemy red.
That made sense to me.
I couldn't even see you through that fog.
It's called camouflage.
You're an invisible person.
Learn how to camouflage.
Maybe you'll get better.
Shit, that happens every time I click to respawn.
And now you know exactly where I fucking am.
Oh, you can see shadows through the ground.
Okay, but you wouldn't have even looked up here.
I wouldn't.
And that's what's going to cause me all kinds of going to the lava.
Right in the fucking lava.
Thank god that doesn't count for anything.
Yeah, I know.
What a cheater.
Yeah, there we go!
He's doing it!
No, I did it again!
The rock is back in Ohio!
I keep doing that!
I keep telling you exactly where I'm standing.
Fuck me!
Okay, good, good.
I didn't like...
You did it again.
I didn't...
No, I didn't.
You did.
I didn't click.
I can't believe that missed.
Yeah, someone's cheating.
Why don't you believe it?
I've got a hacker on the server.
I'm just going to focus up here.
I hit the fucking pole.
I hit the pole that was right in front of me.
And you're telling me...
Telling me I'm...
God...
Oh, you're losing your lead!
You should have seen that shot from my perspective
because from my perspective,
it looked like I hit you.
All right, I am seriously...
I am ready to go.
Yeah, think you're gonna pull that on me?
You're gonna pull a me on you?
You're gonna pull me on you?
Is that what you're gonna tell me?
I'm not gonna pull me on you.
Oh, where is he?
I don't know.
I don't know where he is.
What the fuck?
You're just sitting behind the goddamn couch like a fucking prick.
I killed myself in the lava and respawned somewhere else.
Wow.
Now that we've warmed up a little bit...
Let's raise the stakes a little bit here.
Let's go ahead and make another bet.
Actually, you know what?
Fuck that.
I lose every bet, so...
You don't want to do that.
You just tell me what you want me to do and then like I'll do it.
I know exactly what you want.
I want you to do.
I've had this written in a notebook for like months, just waiting for another bet.
I want you to wear a silly hat and brush your teeth, but not your teeth, like your nose.
Okay, so just thanks for...
Okay, you did that.
Is it done?
Okay, it's done.
All right, so let's play and here we go.
I'm not spawning.
It is a countdown.
Oh, oh, oh, oh.
Remember, everybody, remember, everybody.
It's the first to 15 frags.
Hey, here we go.
Oh, yeah, I'm just going to be a camper.
See, the whole part about this game is you want to be bunnyhopping everywhere.
This is rat...
This is rat insta-gib.
You really weren't lying.
You really are.
You really were being like a camper back there.
I was doing like all kinds of like insta-gibs and you weren't like even trying.
Where are you?
Oh, hey, I'm all warmed up.
You're trying to exploit warm-up matches and this is why I didn't want it.
Oh, they're starting setting his controls up.
Time to make it look like I'm good.
Good thing you brushed your teeth nose already.
Don't, don't roll out the underdog just yet.
I'm going to be like the 1997 Boston Celtics.
Nobody can be like Gabe the glue man Degrosie.
Okay, where did you spawn?
Up in the little cabinet?
I would have killed you, but you had spawn protection.
I got you anyways.
I think I did.
What do you mean I didn't get you?
This is pixel perfect aiming.
We're talking I spawn in the stupid cat.
The spawns in this are like brutal yet.
I'm very scared at all times.
Those dumb fights where you just get down by the blocks.
What are, what are those?
Oh, it's his comeback.
Oh, he thinks he's going to come out and he's going to eat some spaghettios.
You were behind me.
Were you outside?
I didn't even know you could go outside.
That's not fair.
You cheated and that's not.
Oh, these spawns, man.
I didn't even see you over there.
Dude, talk about spawns.
Are you outside again right now?
We're going to play hide and seek and you're going to find where I spawned.
And this cut the video like 20 minutes ahead because you're not going to do it.
Hold on a second.
I have to you.
Where are you then?
Hide and seek.
I seriously had, you know, I have to come fucking find you.
Yeah.
Are you like underneath here?
What?
You're not like in a cabinet or something.
Hold on.
Maybe are you like, I just heard you shoot.
Okay.
Wait, we're going to play Marco Polo.
Yeah.
So for me to be able to actually find you, shoot your weapon.
We'll say Marco.
That's the rules.
Marco.
Okay.
You're over here.
Marco.
All right.
Even more over here.
I think I.
You spawned behind the bookcase.
Oh my God.
Okay.
Marco.
Again?
Yeah.
I'm Marco.
Marco.
You're on the fucking light.
These spot points are.
You're on the light.
How would I ever know you were up there?
I never would have known that.
You wouldn't.
If you didn't shoot me, we would have been here until the time when it ran out.
Shit.
If I didn't suck.
If only.
See, you didn't think I was going to do that.
You thought I was going to peek around the edge.
Yeah.
You can just call me Eugene.
You can call me me.
Yeah.
I thought there's no way I would miss the stupid spawn behind you shots.
You can just call me mean gene.
Oakland.
Fucking.
I just told you exactly where I was.
I got miss clicking like an idiot.
What?
Yeah.
Right.
I called.
Nice shot.
Got some.
Got some frags going on.
Yeah.
We do have some frags going on.
You on the bookcase.
That's like the third time you spawned in the fucking hide and go seek book.
Where?
What?
Where are you?
Oh.
These.
Oh, you have one frag away from winning.
I can't let you win.
I don't even know where he is.
I know where you are.
I want to get you.
No, you don't.
You.
Fucker.
No.
Well, it's a good thing you brushed your nose already.
Shoot the rat.
The rat.
I really thought that was like for a split second.
I thought that was actually happening.
It was.
What was happening?
I like turned right.
I was like, what the fuck is this thing?
You were like freaking out.
I thought the thing was seriously shooting at us for that.
I thought you were going with the joke, but you just were dumb.
I didn't see you.
How did you hit that?
How did you do that on his head?
Was I on his head?
I spawned behind you, right?
I'm kind of scared to move because there you are.
It's kind of scared to move there.
Watch out.
Kind of scared to move.
It's a very...
I spawned...
Damn it.
Come on.
Right behind you.
Whoops.
I keep doing the German again.
I wasn't doing it before.
What changed?
Yeah.
Doesn't it?
It sucks because you just immediately give away your position.
Immediately.
I luckily hit you right when your spawn protection came.
These spawns are the worst.
I just spawned.
Hey.
Yeah, you did.
How are you?
What do you think?
I just spawned.
I don't even know where you are.
Oh, there you are.
Oh my god.
You had spawn protection and everything.
Hey.
Found you.
You got to turn and look around at all times.
You know what I mean?
Yeah, I got to keep my back turned, spin around, back turned.
Get that spawn protection off of you.
Nope.
Only if you get it off of you.
Got it.
Shit.
I'm fucking.
Oh, yeah.
Yay.
Aye, aye, aye.
Where's he going?
I'm going to check the usual spawn points.
I'm going to find him.
Found him at the usual spawn point.
All right.
I'm going to play.
Look, I'm going to play some PC games.
Damn it.
That would have been cool if I hit you.
Hey, look.
Guess what I did.
Spawned?
Yeah, I spawned.
That kind of startled me.
What?
How do you always know where I'm going to be?
This is try hard time.
You have 14 kills.
Oh, yeah.
I forgot.
It stars like back is against the wall.
My back was up against that wall.
Too hard.
Dude, do you see this aim percentage right here?
42%.
That's pretty good.
Wow.
I got a good spawn.
Well, I think we both have really good spawns.
Because neither of us are moving.
I guess, yeah, neither one.
Dude, at that exact moment, we realized both of us.
And you just were a hair fat.
Come on.
Damn it.
Why did I think you were going to leave the cubby hole?
Why did I think you were going to do that?
I love how this is what this has turned into is when we first spawn,
who is going to be the one to show their face first?
I'm looking.
I shouldn't tell you that I'm looking, but I'm looking.
Where are you?
How have we not seen each other yet?
I don't understand.
I swear I know where you are.
You jumped right over me.
Is that where you spawn?
What?
What are you doing in there?
That's where I spawn.
I keep spawning like behind cabinets.
Oh, come on.
You had spawn protection and shit.
You just like spawn in my line.
I just spawn exactly where you killed me.
Seriously, it is so hard to shoot in that little hole.
Like shooting into there is almost impossible for me to do.
Well, come on with this.
I'm leaving.
Yeah, screw that.
Screw that one.
Where is he?
Where the hell are you?
Of course you're up.
You're in the sink washing the fucking dirty filth off your hands.
This level is brutal.
Oh, come on.
I was doing some jumps.
What do you think I was doing when you shot me in the back
like the Benedict Arnold that you are?
Excuse me.
Do you want to get instagibbed?
Well, let me ask you a question.
This is a serious question.
Would you like to get instagibbed?
Come on.
You were standing still and I just kept aiming like you were going to move.
You're up top on the fucking light again.
You're always like up on a lampshade.
I was on the lampshade.
I would never look up there.
Why would you ever look up there?
I keep thinking the green goo is you sometimes.
Like the green stuff on the wall.
I'm like, oh, that's him.
But you're blue.
Shit, I did it again.
I did it again.
Oh, I'm getting this movement down, though.
I'm getting there.
I see you.
I know where you are.
No, I don't.
I lied to give you a false sense of security.
Damn it.
It's going to be so hard.
It's going to be so hard to hit you between those books.
I couldn't get out.
Jeez.
How come that went through your face?
You're in the rat cage.
You are stuck in the cage.
Jumping around is fun, though.
I will say.
All right.
Okay.
String it together here.
String it together.
I cannot hit anything right now.
It's embarrassing.
And I'm going to...
What are you?
You're going to freak out?
You're going to...
Damn it.
Why did I not know where you were?
I knew exactly where you were.
And for some reason, I was like, yeah, where is he?
I have no idea.
Oh my.
That was...
That's going in the frag movie right there.
That was a shot.
Oh, that's going to go in the rat movie?
Yeah.
I know where you are.
You think you can be silly and sneaky?
You're not going to be sneaky.
You're not going to be sneaky anymore.
How did you hit me?
I was behind the wall.
I turned and I put the crosshair on you
and I clicked the left click.
I wasn't even...
There's no way you could have seen me.
Got to finish this one.
Finish this one clean.
Damn it.
I did it again.
How many times...
I wonder how many times I'm going to say that in this video.
What is making you do that?
I'm clicking to like respawn.
And it's screwing me up.
Okay.
Seriously, like I need to clean this up.
Oh, another frag movie shot.
Fucking shit.
Okay.
You...
Oh, let's go.
I tried to turn that corner.
There's a tear in the ground.
Gotcha.
No, you didn't.
You didn't even get me for a second.
Spawn protection enabled.
That was a shot, Jerma.
If there's anything you should be proud of,
it's that you're leading right now by three points.
That was a shot.
If you'd seen what I did right there.
I'm slowing that one down.
I want to see exactly how much that went right through your body.
Oh.
What the fucking spawner?
You didn't even know where it was.
You didn't even know where I was.
I know where you are now.
Are you going to fool me?
Think you're going to fool me with my I'm on the lamppost bullshit?
Had the same idea as you and it didn't work up.
Jesus.
Why are you kidding?
You're on the die.
You're on the lamppost again.
This game is both really good and so frustrating.
I've got a feeling you're going to spawn like on top of me.
I've been to be careful.
Yeah.
You just like after you kill someone, you need to freaking hide.
Hide.
I know you're going to spawn.
I knew where you were going to spawn because it just it just happened like that.
Sometimes I've hit you just like.
You just end up spawning like up on like the lamp again.
Where are you going to go?
We're going to go find the punching bag.
Is that where you're going to?
No, on the lamp again.
On the lamps again.
How many you spawn up there?
Like five times now.
I just scared.
I could hear you're like I could hear your keyboard clicking because of that.
I heard like.
It's fucking spawn protection.
That was such a nice shot too.
I fucking spawn protected.
Oh fucking.
What can spawn protection?
What are you doing there?
I was I didn't think you were going to look.
You're going to complain about spawn protection.
You're standing still like waiting for my spawn protection to turn off.
Got you right in the back.
Where did you spawn?
Okay, you're right in the spinal cavity.
Okay, now you're dead because I know exactly where you are.
Now you're dead.
Now let's go ahead and close this one up.
Oh, congratulations.
My thanks.