Wait, talk. I don't think people can hear you.
Oh shit, talk. I don't think people can hear you.
And I have one of those too. Oh shit. I don't think people can hear you. Oh shit. I don't think I can do that too. Oh shit. I don't think people hear you.
It didn't do anything.
No, I didn't miss it. I didn't. I'm here. We're here. I know you're here. I'm just, you know, I just, this was my big break.
Xbox and
All right, look hold on I got I got how do I turn this down?
Both of them so much individually and I'm really curious to see what that I'm here
They and how different it might be from pretty much in the wrong place
60 seconds see you don't ever go to the movie with the previews are on
Well, I really need to see the Gemini man trailer like ten more times. I've already seen it
This is the same amount of time when we travel together like how much time was left in boarding
Yeah, you get right on the plane
You get right on the plane
Get to the terminal fucking like two hours early. No you get right on the plane
Yeah, but what about?
Hillary's email
What about the people that don't know that you were gonna stream and come in late and then okay on my stream
We've got a no chatter left behind policy and if you don't start early you're leaving people behind who didn't know
No, they were here. No early
What do you know? How do I do it? What's fun? I'm gonna talk during the cut
I have to meet I have to be able to deafen you during the big reveal of Elden Ring
Okay. Well, you've got you've got 60 seconds to figure out how to do it. All right, let me figure it out
I have to tweet that I'm here. I
Got a tweet. I can tweet my mother that like we're about to get on the plane. Okay. Yeah, I
Got a I got a story for you, by the way
Just I don't know why I was late. I have a lot that I wanted to talk to you about but I don't really have the time
We got the after show. That's what that's for. We sit and we talk about our what our thoughts were
Yeah
Well, not dead silent you can like coffins they make like old man noises
Seats on the plane
Anyways, hi guys. Welcome to e3 shows gonna begin at 55 seconds
Yeah, I got to turn you up this down
Yeah, what do you guys want to hear more?
What if I did it? Okay. All right. I got it. What do you guys want to hear more me and stars hood?
Larry is banter. We're like I want to hear they want to hear
What is the future of gaming with more ways to play than ever before?
We're finally bringing to the home console. Yeah, my dream is generation. Why is my true? Oh fuck. Hold on
I'm gonna disconnect for like five seconds. I'm lagging. There we go
Sorry, I was running. I'm good. I'm good. We're good. Good. Welcome to the e3 conference. I'm here. I'm here. I'm good
I'm good. I'm good. I'm good. Okay
Now if you could follow your own advice and please the movie is starting I want some complete silence. All right
All right. All right. I'm good. I'm good. We're old depth of the trailers. They've worked a long time on creating
Yeah, I can turn this up. What did you want to talk about? I don't have time
There's there is not enough time to get into it. It's like a whole
Shit on the screen get this off the screen. How do I turn this off? How do I get this off?
20 years you click on on the right side. There's a there's a twitch gaming pop-out and like you click on that
That's a not visible
All right
Watch this guy talking everyone around will come together and celebrate what games mean to all of us
But you don't know how to mute me so I'm self-conscious now fuck they've meant even more all right
Stop Todd's talking for being with us today. Thank you for the support. You give us and one another
He thinks we're friends 20 and I wouldn't be here if it wasn't for the friendships
We've had that whole time at Bethesda. We believe video games do one thing better than anything else
They transport us through art and technology
There's real magic when you step into a new world and can make it your own
We've traveled the worlds of Elder Scrolls of fallout and now for the first time in over 25 years
We're creating a new universe
With starfield oh we already knew that hundreds of years in our future. It's a new that did you know that about hope?
Your humanity and yeah, I'm greatest mystery
It's a game we've dreamt of playing and it wasn't till now
Where the technology and the team who's hard it was your first time don't worry about it make that dream a reality
We're excited to finally share our first in-game teaser and something was in game all right
I'm on my phone. Are you what I was just like
Attention all right quiet. I did that during Elden ring. I didn't even realize it was on screen
I just talked over it stop dude am I the guy that has to tell his own friend to shut the fuck up at the movie
No one's there where I'm talking about. He's walking. He's climbing a ladder
Can you visually see this or do you need your ears to hear the ladder clank?
You may as well just be smoking a cigarette next to me like get the put that shit out. They say okay the wonder is
Not that the field of stars is so vast
But that we have measured it
You're part of constellation now part of our family
What you found?
It's the key to unlocking
Everything this is all we've been working towards
I have so many drinks. I don't know which one my drink. We've come to the beginning of humanity. Excuse me
To discover what's out there
Yeah
Yeah, no gameplay no by can I tell you I'm sick. I'm sick of the space shit
Space shit, and we saw this movie already
Space shit is the new zombie shit. It's the new I don't I don't care for space stuff anymore
Okay, so um I mean there's this gigantic vast universe, and you just don't want anything to take place in it
But I it's just like I'm sad honest. I'm sick of seeing the guy the astronaut helmet on I've seen it a thousand times
Water I don't I'm sick of seeing
I did imagine a movie that like every every like five to ten minutes. It's stopped
You get to discuss what you just watch
Well, yeah, I mean how many buzzwords
Somebody
We are committed to forging the next getting Komodo hype right now, what is that?
It's only 50% that's not
50% you guys you gotta spam it gamers rise up not here. Do you spend it in this?
Is the main chat
If you do it in there it counts it's all twitch does not count so today of course they count
This looks bad. We can't even get it to 50% show 30 tight. Yeah, you got to amp it up
If it gets to the top every single they cancel Starfield today is optimized for Xbox series X and S
This is weird to have this on the screen and features
This is I don't know why this should not be on
This is the equivalent of us saying do we just talk over her like they're trying to put something on the screen to entertain you
Well, she just like does like the Naruto filler
Like oh, this is the last like five years of games. We've released. We're gonna tell you that we did this and
You you guys just like play with this toy. We give you for a second, but it's filled. So what happens?
What if she looked over to the left of the screen and was like, oh the height meter filled
That's what I put on the funny hat and like it's like a hat comes down she puts it on
Well logically that can't happen because this is streaming on multiple platforms and only twitch has the meter. Oh shit
This is actually a gameplay. Oh
you know what I mean, I
Thought this was light
It looks so real
Your place talker got to
We can do it movie theater style, hey, dude, did you play stalker?
I tried to like a long time ago and I I didn't have a good computer and it just crashed so I gave up
Yeah, yeah, who is that? Who is that?
John stalker I what I was in the bathroom. What's that guy do?
Character from Metro. Okay. Hey, it's your fucking seat. I got sticky
Sorry, sorry the movie's too loud
This really looks like Metro this game's kind of fun it really was I've heard a lot of good things
I think you would actually like this game. I think I would too
I mean like the whole series
That is you talking I don't know why for some reason
I was looking down at my water and I looked up and I thought that the model he was dancing with did not load in
And they were freaking out behind the scenes
Donald Waller
Mutual sir actually looks kind of look a bit pretty good. Yeah
That's a hush. Oh
One of them is a sushi. Um, I just want to let you know
Can everyone listening know that I've decided so that we can have a totally neutral and our biased review of e3
You're gonna disagree with me on everything. Yeah
This game looks like garbage
It was a typically a slower pace to tactical game and they've got people running around
It's like you German what
Understand you you get into these like
People get it
Oh wait, you know
Roll the tape back
streamer reveal I
Gotta tell you what I did today
You gotta just why you were late. Yes, and it's fucking horrible. Listen to me. This is important
I wish I could pause e3, you know, I mean we got like we got stuff to talk about the movie
So I was in a rush and I fuck this more
It's just left for dead again. We've all played it before
Okay, we've seen this we all already know that dead deep rock galactic is a better game move on
so before I got here, I just got a new deodorant, right and
I grabbed it and but without even thinking I
Just brand new I took the top off the deodorant because I was in a rush got out of the showers
like I gotta get fucking get there gotta get to the movie, right and I ripped the top off and went
And scrape with the plastic shit still on it
Plastic nub on it and I caused like damage to the underarm here. It was like gotta go gotta go
It was horrible I have like a cup there
Took me like five minutes to figure out what I was gonna do. Okay, I took you five minutes
And that's why you were 30 minutes late
Well, I cut my underarm it hurt a lot
It was awful. It hurt a shit load
All right, what are you doing that?
What do I think what I said? I think that
Everyone has wanted a left for dead sequel for like 10 years and no one made it and now that they've made it
it's outdated and other people have done it better and you could really try deep rock galactic if you haven't or
Personal favorite of EDF
No one gives EDF a chance, but they're all gonna play left for dead again
EDF was fun, but EDF I think that people just don't know what to do about multiplayer anymore
It's just like I guess four of you have guns and shoot it people running at you
I would not evolved from like the grab three of your buddies and shoot at people sprinting at you
I don't know. How how do we do that?
Do you like this is what I brought up last time last time they showed the e3 for the first time and you know
Everyone big disarray cuz you got I'm a hard person to agree with. How do you feel about reloading guns?
Personally, where you stand on this? I think it gives a pause for you to have to stretch each other
Make sure that you can it's it's a risk and reward
Okay, so this is why we're good because we're neutrally balanced that I'm gonna disagree with you on everything
Well, we got all these zombies running towards you who wants to stop shooting them
That's why doom was so good and everyone loved doom because you can just jump around and keep shooting them
What is the reload animations and these left-for-dead games are like, okay, shoot you shoot for a second reload for four
Thanks kid. Can you two shut the fuck up back there?
Talking the whole movie next question. Do you think DMCA is real or made up? I think DMCA is made up
Yeah
No, I don't well then explain this how come
No streamers have been banned. I don't know because everyone freaked out
they mute your stream if you have like a portion of this they will mute it and
Now everyone's saying that I don't know. Why are you fucking up my whole worldview?
Well
You're listening to this popular song on your stream right now. Nothing's gonna happen, right?
Well, they have they have like they've suspended people
Who name a big streamer? They've suspended. I don't know. Don't pay attention. Fuck. I'm this is I'm terrible at these
Okay, how did you hear about DMCA claims being an issue?
Um, it's all like a reddit thread that said hey like they're kind of cracking down and then like twitch came out
Didn't twitch come on with thing that said that like that like hey, we're like DMC cracking down who told me that
I swear no, no, dude. I DMCA is but my youtube channel has been fucking strike before but not strike
But like shit has been what does it have to do with your twitch stream? They mute it
They mute it if they hold forces of odd. Are you here's the real question? Are you afraid of DMCA?
I am not afraid of DMCA. I am afraid of having my
Magical voice muted during a goddamn live stream while I'm talking and listening to music
Well, it doesn't happen while you're talking. Yes. It does if this music in the background mutes like 12 minutes of your stream
Yeah, and your VOD which isn't while you're talking. No one watches the VOD. They might do that shit. You never know who knows
Yeah, but on OBS now you can have your VOD save with a different track than the ones that you streamed with
Stop talking. Stop talking. This is very important. That was just Johnny Depp dude. Okay, it is. Okay, you're right
Actually, this is Johnny Depp. Do you remember the first time they showed Sea of Thieves at E3 and we were both like
This is the fucking game. This is the game changer
Trying to watch okay, I guess I'm trying to member over here
Oh, yes, and now one Davey Jones, I
Believe that now is the perfect time to use these cannons
This is perfect
I've never seen a Pirates of the Caribbean movie. Well, but the reason why this is perfect because the latest Johnny Depp
Jack Sparrow shit is like Johnny Depp pretending to be Jack Sparrow. It's it's kind of gotten that far
So now like he's CG so they're even pretending that the actor is a real person too. So if you see the first day where
What's his name? Jeff Goldblum came on to announce Jurassic Park
No, it's worth going back to watch
I swear he came back and did a parody of himself to make fun of everyone who wanted him to do it
It was really great. All right. Wait, what's um, all right Johnny Depp now available
Yeah, should I get Xbox game pass? I feel like it's gonna be worth it at some point soon
Do you have a computer?
Yeah, but that's oh
Okay, do you have I don't know tens of thousands of viewers
Is your purchasing of games that deductible in taxes
I'm times. Yeah, I don't think game pass is really gonna help
Okay, here's the real final question, I'm sorry last one
Are you going to play a game made later than 1980? Oh, this is people in like diapers on the screen
What you kusa is this and why have I not played it yet? I want to play this you you would actually love them
Yeah, I played because zero
I don't know. Why did some why everyone want me to play the first one zero? Why wouldn't I play that one free alpha gameplay?
Are you sick of the yeah, what do you think it's cool?
I'm a huge fan of the in. Um, what was the name of that movie?
district 9
That was a really good
But like cinematic trailer, huh? No. Yeah, I think I think I'm kind of over it. I'm actually kind of let's let's watch
I'll come on. Oh, hi
Let's get the buck chance to the chat. Oh
It's actually it's on the screen. Why are they doing this?
And it's like ruining the trailer for everybody that wants to do not listen to two dickheads talk over it
Yeah, let's see some pot. It's like hey, I'm watching this
I have a confession to make after this trail is over to about how I play battlefield whenever I played it
Okay, I've never killed one person in one game of battlefield. I don't think once
Once no, I just kind of walk around and shoot the like weapon at stuff in the air
Like my assault rifle and stuff at planes and stuff and I pretend like I'm playing
And I just revive people and then I don't ever play the game again. And like I don't and then people stop inviting me to play
I
Mine is actually a little bit similar is I find like a really tall hill and I lay on top of the hill
And I just kind of watch the battle
And every one minute I take a shot and like pretend I'm like sniping and like I feel cool
I don't hit anybody though. So I'm saying I have not killed anyone. So you play battlefield as an idle game
Well, yeah, like me and my friends we do a full squad and all four of us are on different hills
Just looking for other people on hills, but nobody really ever gets a shot in also. Are we still in the previews?
What these are these are games I know but like has this field come on talk yet
Todd was out talking
Well, this is not even Xbox this is Bethesda
Co a group thing. I see I seen this a lot too, but back at you
Yeah, but I feel like a lot
This is what I worry about, you know last day
You're like, hey, let's watch on the last day. You've already seen all these already. I haven't seen anything
I'm waiting for Elgin, right? You have you have not heard that like Psychonauts 2 is a thing. Well, yeah, but I'm
But it's closer to being released
There's three or four new clips in here
It's like it's actually fun, you know, I asked this question every single time this trailer shows
Have you ever played it nope
probably more fun than like
cleaning a dirty fence I
Don't know about that going to this game might have too many buttons for you
You think so? Yeah
We're getting just bang bang, but reveal reveal reveal
This is usually the moment when I say hello and welcome to the Bethesda e3 showcase
We love that we can share this you're not gonna do the Xbox this year and whether you've known Bethesda for 35 years or are just
35 what?
That's when you like pat me on the back and you're like good good job Jeremy. Yep. That's how old you are
I don't know how old you are. I don't know why we're talking what and today bringing ten more titles to game pass for a total of
You know how old you are Jeremy you're three yes, I'm free like the award-winning doom eternal
If you're looking for another reason to play it doom maternal will be optimized if you play doom
That's why you think the reloading is essential this next-gen upgrade will be not every single game has to have no reloads
Because then every game becomes like the zombie game every game becomes the the two choices that you have to make at oh
Which one who lives and who dies right that everybody? I don't want to do that. I want everything to be different
You were just complaining about every game is the same game
When was I complaining about that you said what it was the very beginning exploring every beginning this frame you said
No, I said it and then you agreed. I said man. Oh, what's with all these that left for dead clones, right?
It's a you show four people you said they shoot zombies. No what I said
Was that there's a better version of Left 4 Dead and you should just play the best version of each genre and that is deep
Rock galactic, and it's not even debatable everyone who plays this game knows this this is just true
I forgot our whole conversation already. I have to be honest. I'm just I'm just winging it here
All right, what is this?
Do you think they're ever gonna Diablo 3 this game and they'll come out with Reaper souls
And people it'll be actually kind of fun. I think people are enjoying it that
still play it
but
No one who had the initial impression that they think it's bad is ever gonna go back and like try it again
It would take years for like a whole new generation of people to just forget what it was like when they launched it
People saying it's kind of fun
Yeah, I've honestly not been hearing bad things about it what the launch was, you know
One of the worst I thought you understood what that insignia meant
No power another brotherhood. I said this plan in motion and I am the only one who can stop them people like CBT, too
I'm surprised. That's the kind of comment you would read righteous crusade. Well, it looks like you don't know me very well, do you?
I guess I don't been watching the stream lately. I don't know. Do you talk about CBT often? I might
Know I thought CBT was a time zone when people started spamming it like a year ago. Oh really I think I thought it was
Central British time
Yeah, never mind I'm not joining now
It's a follow I
Would take 30 less trash cans on the screen for this to run at 60 FPS
And everyone else agree that with that
Big agree, but there's the games always actually have that mod. Wait. No, I'm not supposed to be agreeing with you
Oh, I think the the graphical fidelity is worth the loss of frames because I can't see over 24. Anyway
Studio has now surpassed 18 million players and shows no signs of slowing down
Right now still going enjoying the new Blackwood chapter part of the gates of oblivion your long
I feel like the whole Bethesda conference has me been going they're still working on this
This is still a game. They haven't like liquidated this whole franchise. Like that's what I've been saying the whole time
So console enhanced this Tuesday the game would deliver a true native experience. I have heard for the series. No, wait, that's
That's fine. Repeat every single thing you said about fallout 76, but like change the wording to elder scrolls online
This is the mobile one. No, this is not the mobile. Yes. Look. Yeah, this looks like a mobile game. You tell them
No, no, no, I just
Elder scrolls online that was the console one that it was I came on a console right?
That was a big deal. What came out on console? That was a big deal that it came out on console
Right a big deal that an elder scrolls game came out on a console. It's an MMO
It was like an MMO that came out on console again. Are you gonna play any games that have come out after 1980?
Well, why is every question marking me? What am I talking about?
Wasn't wasn't when this when this when this first came out wasn't it on console and that was like, oh my god an MMO on console
No way. Yes. Yeah, it was that was Final Fantasy 14
Remember you're wrong stop
That was Final Fantasy 14. I mean like one guy might have said that I don't know if it was a thing
I thought that's what I thought. That was a big deal. Oh shit. Wait fall guys
Have they added? No, I'm not gonna be mean
This is not fall guys
yeah, if you want to like when you say you don't want to be mean if like a game comes up and you don't like
It but you don't want to be the one to say it
You want you want to just send you like a discord message every time I want to say something mean and you'll just say
No, no, you just ask me. What do you think about this and then I'll say it
Okay, I don't I don't have a filter. Oh, this actually kind of looks fun. This is that my bad game gang beasts
Pretty sure this is like gang beast too. Yeah, is it yeah
This looks like it could be fun kind of fun. Oh shit. This looks really fun
Well, not actually but yeah, it just looks like gangbeast
Actually, it's kind of fun. Hey you play this game
Wait, hold on before I say anything. I want to know what you felt about how you felt about this game
I felt that okay now go what I just want to make sure I was ready
Okay, wait
Why do you need to be ready? Because I just need to be ready. Are you capturing my soul?
I want to let's hear your thoughts. I want to hear my thoughts on Hades
Are that I'm really sick and tired of rogue light games requiring you to lose multiple times claiming that it's because their game is hard
Rather than just that they're gating you from being to
Accessing the things you need to actually win the game from the start
You know, we go back to the back in the day gamers who played fucking binding of Isaac
You could just go beat mom like what's the big deal?
But nowadays Hades is like you got to play for a couple of hours before you can do plus 300% damage and double your health
Sorry, I didn't listen
Essentially that was my game of the year last year. How fucking dare you first of all and second of all was it?
Yeah, I think it's a good game except for the first part where you need to unlock things
Here's here's the better example. I think Hades is encouraging the trend
Have you played the last spell the last spell is a tower defense rogue like but here's the catch
You can't actually build towers until you've lost a few times
You'd be a horrible boss to work for I think
Somebody would come to you with a concept of like a thing that they were making it'd be you'd be like
Nope
redo it and then and then they would they would redo it like a hundred times and
Then you would have already moved on to another project
Well, I feel like I'm giving I feel like I'm giving actual reasons and not just I'm not just telling them
No, try again. I feel like I would I would offer some form of guidance, but then you would have the perfect thing
What's your favorite game of all time?
Diablo 2 we can agree on that. Well, you're not supposed to be agreeing right now
Master Chief is back there
Our goal has always been to bring players together and for the first time we're thrilled to offer our entire
Quiet right now
You said quiet there's halo I know and then you waited 20 seconds instead
Why are we quiet and invite more of you than ever before to become a Spartan hero?
I'm excited to be here with Joseph Staten the creative
What's the last halo you played?
Me and me and Joel
We played on legendary the the remake remaster one for 40 minutes and it's the only time I've ever played it
I watched people play it and I was like
Halo 2 I've never played a halo game
I don't know. It just never grabbed me for some reason. I don't know why
Reloading
Wait, do you reload and halo? Yeah, you do. Of course you do you shoot your battle rifle twice and then you reload
I mean that this is a huge deal, right?
I'm very excited
All right, I was thinking about doing the puke thing I was thinking about going them but I was like I don't want to do
That right now like people trying to watch you know, I like about Master Chief is he kills relentlessly
But also it's clear that he cares
Okay, imagine me like landed on his like head
That's all that's it
That's it
It's too early
So I need it
Hey, you know, you know how cool of a boss I would be
How cool of a boss would you be drama you'd come into my office and it would be like a
Transparent cup that has levels of like up here
There's a there's a line that says don't even think about talking to me
And then when the line is here and the coffees here, it's like maybe listening and then when it's down here the line right here
It's like now's time not now's time for you to talk
That's how you know, I'd be a cool boss
You
Okay, I don't know how to react
On successful deployment my deletion routine was supposed to complete
Good good something stopped your deletion. We need to find that Cortana or a new hollow girl
Just people this is change people are getting furious with us if we stop we don't stop talking right now no gameplay
No, bye. Stop talking. Of course. You can't have a halo game without multiplayer and on Xbox Series X
You'll be able to enjoy infinite's multiplayer action at up to 120 frames per second
Finally, I'm very happy to announce that halo infinite's first free-to-play multiplayer season and infinite story-driven campaign
We launched together this holiday
A new day is this a new generation
This is halo. I just gotta let you know people are sitting at their table right now
And they are contemplating whether to give this restaurant of our stream like a two-star review
Where we're getting there? I was letting you know we all need to be careful here
I just want to let that person know
That they're sitting in a virtual restaurant and the only thing letting them like stopping them from going to a better restaurant
They don't even have to stand up
They just click the special events where it says that under the stream and then like there's a whole bunch of options
You can just change the restaurant you're in. Yeah
Yeah, you said that like a fucking Denny's or something and you just you know what?
I'm really not into this like French toast grilled cheese. They just gave me
That one Applebee's you just teleport into the seat
Yeah, so like they put down the pancakes in front of you at Denny's and you're like how these don't look that good
You just you switch you switch the channel and there's a new tray of food in front of you already
But do you have to pay you would have to pay right?
Not no
No, maybe no
so what's stopping somebody from just going just
What about like the trolls that would just jump from restaurant to restaurant and order everything on the menu and just jump the galaxy?
Jump to the next restaurant
The customer is always right. Oh
right
Don't just run it all capitalism. Why are they talking? I would probably like payload twos multiplayer
I thought is this it always looked really fun to me. Well, it's free to play. So you're definitely gonna try it out, right?
That one looked always the most fun. What about it? Oh, no, just driving the cars around running over people
Oh, you can't do that in three, but it just seems cleaner. It seemed more fun. I've seen three
Shut up. I'm serious over Elden ring, right?
Stop talking. This is my why I'm here
As the Diablo figure wanders, I know there's five dude
game of the year
Must be stopped. It's my fucking like I'm ready
Are you not excited for this? I heard it's very good
Wow, I even have mixed feelings about my game of the year joke. I mean it looks great
It's so close one to one to the actual Diablo 2 that
The bugs that Diablo 2 has that like speedruns use it kept everything even like really weirdly obscure mechanical things
Really? So it's it's like as authentic of a remaster as you could possibly get
Because this is I've I've wanted this for a decade and a half at least
Well, see my only mixed feeling is that I I never stopped playing Diablo 2 so like a graphical update doesn't even
But don't you think this is important to remember here don't you think that
Having a Diablo 2 on the blizzard launcher
Means we'll get interesting updates to the game
No, you don't think they'll add stuff to it like items potentially really doubt they would add things to it
I feel like whenever you add things to a remaster the purists start complaining and then you you're afraid
Even look like even patches though even stuff that like people have been begging for well
That's what I mean is that they have bugs from Diablo 2 are
Remastered to be authentically bugged from like still so if they're not patching that they're not gonna what is happening on this?
I don't know is this is this by the is this me or is this the this is the stream, but he's my brother
And I would die remastered
This is not Diablo, but it just got louder
Why is this this got like 30% louder
My only concern would be able to remastered is that Diablo 2 has a whole bunch of mods, and I hope that
Blizzard doesn't restrict
Mods being able to make be made of the remastered because otherwise
To me do like actual Diablo 2 is still just gonna be better
hmm
Stir shut up stir shut dude this game came out like two years ago. It's the new games and cinematics no gameplay no buy
You
Give a bunch of policies apparently that I didn't know I have a lot of policies no gameplay no buy no chatter left behind
But what if what can we have one trailer where we don't talk just one this one?
Okay, ready is like the fourth time. They've shown this game, but this one. Let's just see if we can do it
But if we're gonna do it why this game?
Okay, okay
Let me ask you a question
When I am dead and Yara is burning, what exactly is your plan whole hands sing songs around the fire
It really was just like
I
Somebody said NBC comedy intro trailer like the music I was gonna say this music is a little oh
You know that they're killing people
Whatever happened in games where we honor the death of the fallen I want to play like crazy back, but you
know this is worse this is like an NBC compilation of all their comedy trailers and like and and and
Michael walks out just like it's happening. It's happening. Is Ubisoft really gonna make light of revolution
This is a lot of fun all right don't talk if I called it from the clouds, I'm gonna keep talking
onto drag knock online
Everybody's a slime rancher devs. Are you shooting me? Oh, I want a real. I want reaction for this one
It's too early for that shit
all right
Slime rancher was all do you play slime rancher?
Yeah, I love that would have been my game of the year if I played it when it was actually relevant
I can like 2017 or something right? Yeah, I think I played it too early
I never played like I loved it
When I played it, but it was very good. I'm actually really excited for that. That's I love that game, so let's see
It's been a while since we have had a real good snowboarding game, right? Oh
steep yes steep, but steep was uh
It was more than snowboarding game. It was a wingsuit game. I guess you could count that though
I get the appeal of snowboarding games and games like this
But I just can't play them because I end up trying to do a backflip for too long and don't land the third back flip
I mean, I get way too overzealous with the tricks on the snowboarding game, and I just fall down every time
You actually get to do that that'd be actually kind of fun if you could be the camera guy I
Okay, right that one down. I'm serious
Writing it down as if they if you can be the camera guy then I'm I need to play that
On my cart, I feel like atomic heart is going to be cyberpunk 2077 without all of the hype
Maybe better
This what is this song is it getting you pumped me kinda
It was 80s Russian pop. What was that? I won. I'm kind of curious about what that was
Hype meter fog meter just filled up 200. I don't have a fog meter
Haven't you made this tweet before where you're like, I'm you're one of those people that say you are sick of games that have pixels in them
Did I I feel like I feel like you've been there
Maybe because I was shocked that you would have one of the lowest forms of opinion. I
Think pixel part if done. Well, I'm pixel art can be I think it's like it has a big range
Yes, it's almost like you can arrange pixels and do like a lot of different things with them
I mean that this this is look this looks gore. This is gorgeous. Let me just say, okay
There's a range in pixel art. I'm very interested quiet write that one down, too
Okay, am I actually I didn't write down the last one. Why didn't I don't even remember what the last one was?
Why didn't you not write it down? I'll write this one down. What was the other one? I don't remember it was a snowboard game
No, it wasn't that was the one I told you to write down was a snowboard game
in the first year of grounded
Millions of players kept busy
With crafting it's a billions of players
Billions
To celebrate everyone at birth getting an account tied to their ID
But not those guys
Why have I never even heard of this
You should probably turn on arachnophobia mode, oh even her blob scares this of us
Or never go home
Oh, honey, I shrunk the kids right. Oh, and it looks like we added achievements to nice
Okay, I'm writing this one down. I
Would say this is what Jerma sees every day
Okay among us to
Enter the sauce guy. All right, so I'm gonna take a screenshot of this so I can pretend like I played it
Is that important so you can prove that I was in a different clothing. I threw up my backs
I just threw my back out. I just literally pulled the muscle my back
I'm worried about you
Like if you move you hurt yourself
Oh, I just pulled a muscle down the left side of my back cuz I've you hurt yourself putting on deodorant
That was stupid do the face
No, I did. I need to drink some more water. I got water right here
Yeah, I know what's happening right now. No gameplay. No, but I
What is it? I don't know. His stories will be it's like this 2d 3d thing is kind of cool looking though
Why am I doing that without eating fucking like
I
Yeah, and I don't know
I don't have a reaction for you
Wait, how did you see that before I did? I thought you were saying and what's your reaction Jeremy?
I didn't know that no, I'm I have the paid for stream that you actually had seconds in advance
Yeah, am I actually like 10 seconds behind?
You could try refreshing like that's better
No, what
There's like binaural audio
Yeah, I feel completely
explicit and I love the government now
That's the shit you listen to when like you really want to go to bed before a big event that you're really really excited for like
The first ever packs being a content creator and you couldn't fucking fall asleep
It was four or five or six a.m
And you had to be up at 11 and you just put on binaural beats in both ears fucking so pissed off that you can't
Go to bed and you just please fucking work so I can be go. I'm like a content creator now
Didn't work. I mean, I wanted I want to throw up question marks, but a lot of people are plus doing you
So I just I'm glad I just turned off the webcam right when I spilled coffee all over me. It just went all over me
You need to live in like in a home. You know what? I mean? I'm fine. Okay
No, I failed another
I'm fine. Yeah, I don't know about this game. I'm kind of bored of games taking place like on earth
You know what? I mean?
Like the entire universe is boring you so I think I'm just gonna be the opposite again
And say like any game that takes place on a planet. It's just I think a little overdone
I think I'm just I think I think we're just too spoiled
And I mean like there's been so many video games in the last two or three decades that all summer been so good
That's just like outer galactic exploration. Yeah, we both hate one because this is a planet in space
So like I'm just I'm over it
Suddenly and for no reason we added combat goons to our game. We needed shooting. I was intrigued until a moment ago
But this is but I we said you talked about this last year constant conflict
It has to be constant conflict
I think I'm being parody
Silhouette because the developers haven't finished the design
Finished the story or finished any gameplay that's actually ready to show in fact, the only thing they have finished
Is the title?
Wait, really? Why?
No gameplay. No, bye. I played the first I played through the whole first one. It was
Okay, it was fun. I mean that we're getting it too. I feel like they there's isn't a DLC that is still making for the first one
Yeah, there are. Yep. They are. That's what I mean. Like it's
It seems pretty this is really close to having a second one. I also feel like
You would probably like flight simulator
You kind of really don't do much
Like a one-button kind of game. What's that supposed to mean? This just seems like the game that you seem to like
like
Like those euro truck simulators to you probably really enjoy
Earth game resident sleeper earth game
Yeah
Constant conflict right? Yeah, these planes are in constant cut they're in competition to get there. Do you see how many there were I
Don't I was I was honestly curious about your opinion and why you would or would not like this and I feel like you just deflected
I would probably like it. I don't not saying I wouldn't when it came out
I just don't think I had a good enough graphics card to be able to play it. Oh
Is this top gun actually might be
Do it do it do me a favor do me a hit pause on your on your hit pause on your stream
No, just do it. Just do it. Just do it, but just please do it ready, right?
Ready pause the pause ready one two three
four five
No, I'm back. You were you were not that far behind me. I was I was it really was
Can we both just press refresh at the same time?
But I'm
Capturing the browser. All right. Let's tell me what you see. So am I
Rain, I see cactuses. I see rocks
grass a car
You see how do you see a car? Oh, I'm pausing for like you're so far behind you are so far
All right. How do I refresh this f5 on all browsers? I'm not I'm not I'm capturing the actual like embedded. Oh
That's what you mean
Yeah, no, then I just pause more
When the splash screen comes up that says like the name of the game like car driver
Atlantic tell me okay
Low latency mode. I do have low latency mode on yeah. All right, so the Jeep just went through the outdoor car wash
Just getting on the road doing things that are gonna get us absolutely arrested pulled over illegal. What else that's the whole trailer
I think I'm behind you now. Wait, hold on. We'll find out
Inside the car both of us. They say both paws on the title
Posing I'm on the title. I'm so far ahead of you. I'm paused on the title. Yeah, I
Go, I don't think pausing will fix it. Wait, wait, no, no, no, just refresh it. I refreshed. I'm good
I can't wait to show you what we've been working on. I'm like live now. I think
Oh your streams live. No, like I think I'm like live like I'm getting the live feed
Whatever I'll just like delay my reaction
largest and most diverse open world ever in a Forza Horizon game
And there is no better car to explore it than the stunning. Oh, what's your opinion on cars?
Um in unparalleled detail, they did look nice in Forza Vista. Thanks to the power. That's a pretty humble opinion for someone who drives a Ferrari
I've invited along some of the team to help you I can do that some of the amazing content that's waiting for you in Forza
Like seriously, that's fucking so annoying
Hey Mike
Hey, what's up Mike and we also have Abraham with us as well. He's one of the talented actors who will be appearing in the game
When you were riding around me fucking sir should have a lot to say about how cool it was and
Now you want to like talk shit. That's fine. You campaign well
You made a bunch of comments about the sun roof and how fucking cool that was I
Mean it was cool. I'm just saying that your opinion on cars is like
You're really not that into them to be a guy in a Ferrari
You know, I don't think you appreciate it
That's a peek at our adventurous campaign but Forza Horizon has always been a game that's best enjoyed with others
Let's go and see what some of our other players are up to
The Xbox series consoles allow us to capture every last detail
What are they up to the individual needles on these cholla cactus?
What is what you told me to wait a second? I'm like waiting for you
Because it was like the e3 we're like people talking
Yeah, cars, but it's like the fake multiplayer like we were talking
This is one of my favorite things about e3 is when you have the like fake gamer moment
Especially when you have people communicating over voice and they say all the things that no one would ever say
Let's watch let's leave Maddie for a moment and head out to the coast and meet Don
Don is already on the move exploring this idyllic seaside town
This is a recreation of Mexico that is honest authentic and filled with love. That's why is there somebody fucking gameplay? Oh
Hey, what's up?
This is a mural by Mexican artist Farid Rueda
Just one of the many beautiful faithful pieces of Mexico. You'll find all over for to horizon five
Like oh, let's check on see what what's dawn up to
Fuck you doing who are you? Why are you in my game?
Using photogrammetry data captured on location atop an active
Mexican volcano the entire world has been recreated at this level of detail. I'm not really feeling this one
It's just another earth game
That I just actually looks good consoles, but I mean the actual graphics
I'm really yeah, I'm very happy that consoles have caught up to what PCs could do like six years ago
Because
Games have been looking good lately cities anywhere in the world
It's a colorful undulating city full of vibrant architecture
Yeah, even has a sprawling network of tunnels and these twisting turning, but it's a box that you buy once every eight years
Is usually under four or five hundred dollars the eliminator
Yeah, but you have to pay for your internet on it separately
Open-world let's head north to the can we mean the horizon so if you want to play online games
Don't you need like a PlayStation plus subscription HDR camera rig captured 24-hour shoots?
Four years if you're paying $15 a month
How much was it?
You have to pay for internet no matter what
Well, why is the internet I'm talking about like a beast computer that can run insane ultra settings is usually more than a thousand
1500 bucks in it
Run like a game on like ultra and have it be the look good. You need like a pretty beefy computer
Not really anymore actually well, okay, you know what I mean, I'm not gonna argue that they aren't more expensive than
It's actually gone a lot cheaper
Knows that bill loves minigames so intelligently prompts Sierra to invite bill and 80 I don't have 1080
With that horizon arcade minigames starting soon all of our players are coming together
For a second I thought these are people
Oh gamer track
Our players now have to work together to find and pop as many as they can
Okay, go up here to the left
You know what I figured out about this
These these people are all streaming the game. That's what I figured out
We're going over to the stage because when you stream a video game
This is an inside information you guys you you have to say everything you fucking doing because you're terrified of dead silence is
Going through the balls incredible. Whoa big turn
You watch out you don't have to though you do though you do you can be comfortable with silence
They're all screaming the game they're all making videos streaming I think they'd be louder
Okay
Yeah
Forza Horizon 5 is the largest most fun
I was gonna make a really specific
Example reference showcase for the X what it's seven like seven years. I'm just gonna let them go
Thank you. When is it gonna end? I'll see you all in this. It's a big deal for a lot of people
Team Xbox is on a mission to bring the joy and community of gaming to everyone on the planet
That's why you the gamer are at the center of everything we do
Today we showed you 30 games
27 of them will be available on Xbox game pass
Now through the end of the year you can look forward to back-to-back
Monthly releases
Landing day one on game pass led by five new titles from Xbox game studios as well as highly
Anticipated games like back for blood 12 minutes and the ascent and as we look ahead to next year
I'm inspired by the creativity of Bethesda and Xbox game studios
We showed you the highly anticipated RPG starfield
Coming exclusively to Xbox
But we all know that some of the industry's best RPG storytellers working on about
They're still making a fable that's not canceled fallout 76. I think so the outer worlds to I mean apparently elder scrolls six
We unveiled the stunning multiplayer mode for the world's most beloved shooter in Halo infinite
Adding to the roster of iconic Xbox shooters
Alongside Wolfenstein years of war perfect dark in doom
We premiered the most everybody said why is he nodding and listening so intently he doesn't even have an xbox
You have vibrant and authentic depiction of me. I don't know in a game. What does Xbox games come to PC?
Ten is hard at work on the next what's the motors also apparently you just love Phil our growing family
Smart guy studios is devoted to advancing the medium. We all love
That camera change was perfect has been here for 20 years and that's because of you
Our team strives to make Xbox a place where you'll find the greatest games the most dedicated
developers and the most passionate community
Together we all make Xbox coming up the best place to play
Before I go
There's one more thing
Take a look at this brand new
Original game from the arcane team at Bethesda the studio that created prey and dishonored
Arcane created something new for them an open world immersive shooter that you can play alone
Or with your friends and like starfield death loop this game will be an xbox
exclusive
the death loop
probably
I'm sorry. I've seen five distinct four distinct characters, but it's about a real
Piper with a sans eye I'm interested
Wait is it a four-player shoot the people running at you game
Redfall Massachusetts behind me. We are witnessing clear signs of cult activity as the locals
I wasn't why somebody does have to be vlogging. I was just here to record a vlog and I accidentally ended up shooting them all
America
It is it's a four-player shoot the people running at you game
No, let's go off to
Somebody says can we mute the Diablo 2 nerd that hates everything
Are you talking about me you're talking about him? I don't know people don't like me you should mute me
Both of you
Yeah, I don't hate everything you see my pog face during slime rancher 2
I'm willing to give arcane studios the benefit of doubt on anything, but like these types of characters. I don't know
They set a certain tone for a game that I don't expect to like and also by the way, no gameplay. No, but
This is oh, it's not gameplay. I don't know why I thought this was gameplay. I was like, oh game. It's worked. Oh
Yes, this gameplay I'm actually really impressed now all in engine footage. This is great
Every game has to have a sniper. I get it. Every game has the rocket launcher and every Bethesda game has to have a little robot
Yeah, and it takes place on earth. I know this no no, that's not Bethesda. That's gearbox. What am I talking about?
Wait, is it there's a little robot in every Bethesda game too. No, I'm thinking of um, what's the game with Peter Dinklage?
The game with Peter Dinklage. Yeah, it's in the game. Yeah when he replaced him because his voice lines were so bad
Destiny. Yeah. Yeah
That's a little remind me that just every time I see like a little robot, dude
The one the first vampire guide looked like the outsider
from
Dishonored I was confused. I thought they were doing like
Like a PlayStation all-stars mashup and that robot was from like some game. I don't know
Destiny's fun though, isn't it? Oh, just nice fun though in it. It is. No, it's I'm serious. Like isn't it?
I played the first one for a little bit. It was fun to shoot stuff
You know for all the people that are that are like, you know, sir, you're annoying. Yeah, destiny 2 is a great game
It was even more annoying that he didn't complain about it
Honestly, I picked the wrong person to stream this conference. But I want something. I want something that's like oh shit
I mean, I asked you if you wanted to so it's my fault
Just hates everything. He's bashes everything. He's one of those BP bashes. He's angry
Some of this stuff does look pretty good. I mean age of it. That's it. Is that a remake?
It is right age of empires. No, actually, I think it is the
The thing that most interested me this entire conference
Was them saying we're still working on a fable and they didn't even show it since when are they working on fable?
I think I think he was just saying that they're like currently working on it
Yeah, but it was like the briefest of name drops of like I am we're working like we what?
Yeah, but how long has it been? Holy shit. We've been here for an hour and a half
Yeah
Wait, what?
How did that go by that my brain that did not process that an hour a half has gone by time goes by fast when you're
Just having lots of fun
That I've been having no fun with you. That's the thing. I've actually hated every second of being this
I think that I think that you're being you're playing coy and you've had so much fun
So what what's what's the what's the big one? I feel like I missed everything
What do you mean you I missed everything the big one they started with starfield
Yeah, but that was an hour and a half ago. So you forgot you missed Elden Ring. No, I'm just kidding
I saw the trailer that looks fucking awesome. Yeah. All right, wait, we gotta talk about elder Elden Ring for a second
Am I to be am I wrong here?
It's it's an open world from software like Dark Souls game like open like complete or is it because don't mean Dark Souls is open
World technically right but like a big open world
Supposedly and you get a horse but why they give you a horse if you didn't have somewhere to go
Why are they making that such a point because all the other Dark Souls games were kind of open world, weren't they?
They've not really they were open in that different paths connected to each other, but they weren't actually open
I can't imagine how crazy they've been an open world Dark Souls kind of game
It has open fields, but it still has some the same dungeons like Dark Souls
I don't know
Well, but here's something really important about about the guy in the call right now the last from software game that came out
He didn't finish but I did
Which one was the last one? It's Kero. Remember you did not beat the last boss in secure. Oh, you were like this game's dumb
I don't want to even complete it. You're
You're bringing up games that are the most likely to make people not like me
Hold on. I guess for this add-up
I'm getting flashbang by the screen being open. So wait
Well, hold on the next one is Square Enix at 12 15. What time is that what that's like?
That's in like 45 minutes from now. Yeah, okay. So we've got a lot to talk about for 45 minutes a huge recap
I actually I don't know if you wanted to keep talking about that
I don't know if I'm interrupting but I know that like I was saying earlier, this is my this is my big break
I don't normally have such
High caliber celebrities on my stream and I'm kind of trying to make it as a journalist
So I actually wrote up a bunch of interview questions for you and it would be an honor if you would allow me
To interview you no. All right. So what did you think about?
What do you what what do you think about me beating secure? Oh before you I didn't beat it at all
So I don't really I don't think anything
Congratulations, nobody said getting the sus guy is pretty big
So what what was in that conference that you thought was that you were interested in?
Babel
All right, you wrote down you know replaced I wrote it down snowboard cameraman I wrote that down
I wrote I don't know why I wrote that down. Why did you write among us? I just
Sweeping the nation. So wait, what was the among us thing was that they they're adding more lobby slots
Wait, so is it okay for you to interview me? I don't want to interview you
I don't what you are you you are interviewing me. You're not a question
I have what would I even ask you like I don't you just asked like three in a row
But this it's we're talking about the games we just
Watched not about like what you had for dinner last night
that was not one of the questions, but you know, um, I like the camera the cameraman snowboard game could be funny because
You know the laugh-out-loud moments of being able to take the camera and watch like you like snow snowboard down
I don't know why it's you it's not gonna be you
It's gonna be somebody else way more interesting than you but like it's gonna be filming somebody like a hilarious other streamer
Going and like crashing and jumping over somebody and stuff. You know, I mean I need I need the
old-person
Recap, I'm like clicking to the stream what you didn't hear what I just said. No, no, I heard what you just said
I'm looking like what games they showed that I miss
Understand because like there was a couple things that seemed interesting, but everything that seemed interesting had no gameplay
Which is kind of typical e3. I'm curious about the arcane
Studios because our game studios has never made a bad game
But I don't know what they were showing because there was no gameplay. It's gonna be like
Shooter four-player, that's very presumptuous of you. It's a
You're jumping to conclusions here, Jerma, even if it's and I feel like you're not being fair to the developers
I always try and give it there. All right, hold on. But what what what did you said arcane studios?
What was the last thing they made?
Prey was the last okay, so they make good games. Yeah, they make prey to make dishonored. Oh, okay
So, yeah, they probably they're probably all right and they're they're making death loop
But I think this would be the actually the first time that they have
Made two games at once because I didn't expect a second game. Also Dark Messiah a very good game
That is a very good game. I'm just kidding. Yeah, but if you want to play the snowboard game, I'll film you. Oh, okay
Yeah, no, okay. No, that's fine. I'll do the snowboarding you do the camera. Yeah, it was just kidding around
Something for blood darkness. I might I would love to see another one of those wouldn't you?
Yeah, I would love any I would like a heroes of might and magic game that
Was the last one they even made they've made a bunch of them
But even you just haven't heard of them because they were not very good. Why are you pretending to play games?
I know that is what I'm doing cuz I don't
I mean, there's 22,000 people here. I have to at least pretend like I fucking know what I'm doing
I have to we have to say I have to sit with like a hand on my to be like
Let me tell you something. That is not why people are here, right?
You know if they wanted to go to Applebee's they just switch the channel you have to be comfortable
Silence sometimes I am comfortable with silence. But did you see that? It was like a dust cloud that just went by the camera
That was crazy. Uh, no, I don't have it open. We want the dump truck. We're here to see you. Oh, thanks
No, thank you. Seriously. Thank you Applebee's Andy. You're looking cute today. You lost weight
I've gained a lot of weight actually like a hundred and sixty
Okay, too much weight. Oh, yeah, I haven't stood up on I haven't stood up on camera for a while
I actually know that's versions of me have how it way that really like okay
Jarvis short jokes, but to hear that you're you gained a ton of weight. You're 160
We're going with this that math doesn't that's weird to me that you could be like, oh, yeah
I'm up a whole bunch. I'm a hundred. That's like nothing
I'm not I'm how short do you have to be for like I've gained a bunch of weight and you to be 160 pounds to be
Like oh, it's not how it's getting bad. I'm five like eight, you know, how tall I am
Why is this such a mystery? Well, that's I'm just saying that's the first time it has actually hit me as like I'm on board with this joke
There is no job. I'm five eight and a hundred and sixty fat guy pounds. Like I need to lose
160 cannot be fat
Seven to five eight and I'm gonna say that range because it depends on what kind of shoes you have on if you have dress shoes
On I become five eight and a half without
You're a dwarf without dress shoes. I'm like five seven and two quarters or something
I have to have dress shoes on my chat, which is scientists very intelligent people
This guy's saying 160 at your height is perfectly healthy
Are you always this down on yourself?
If you have fucking dress shoes on you get a little taller
Wait, how tall are you?
Six two. Yeah, right. What do you mean? Yeah, right? You're like again. You've seen me
Oh six one. You're like six feet on a good day
By the way, who gives a shit about any of this? What did you think about the fucking fable conference?
I think it was really cool that for about one second
They showed a sword and apparently that sword is in fable. Yeah, we can we can we move on to something else?
I mean, this is making me a little nervous talking about how tall I am
What did you see the first conference? Did you see yesterday?
I didn't we could watch yesterday's stuff cuz I haven't seen any of it. No, I've seen that shit
It was fucking cool. Some of the stuff was cool. You really should check it out
Yeah, I was going to wait because you were like, I'm only gonna stream on Sunday and I was like, oh, okay
I'll just like I'll cue it all up for him
And but this is this is what like all the big reveals are like Xbox the Xbox. No, that's when that typically happens
They typically happen on the first day. Let me go take a break. I have to go to the bathroom. Um, yeah, when's the next one?
well, 15
12 15 we got a we have to kill a lot of time here. What are we gonna? What do we do?
I don't know shit. How do I how do we kill like 30 minutes? This is like 45 minutes. I don't know ma'am
What can we even play?
Among us. I'm not playing the minus. I'm not playing wait, you know what? No. No, it's the only time I'd ever play it
It's a bit me and you what are we gonna? I who is the imposter you you killed me
That's how you do it. The reason why I don't play among us and the reason why a lot I I'll give you the reason
I don't I don't know like
10 streamers to be like hey you guys ready to play among us. No, I don't I'm not gonna do that
Well, then you're gonna get involved in the streamer drama. I know like four people
I mean I could ask people on Twitter just ask people on Twitter what I don't like. Okay, here's thing
I don't really want to play though
I don't really like care that much about among us to like hit up a bunch of people and be like hey
I want to play among us today. Can you and can I be in? Oh, yeah, that's another thing
Talk about so I'm gonna I'm gonna be do it. I guess I'm talking about tomorrow
I'm gonna be on
OTK schooled you just making up letters. What? Oh, I'm gonna be I'm gonna be on schooled
It's a it's a like a game show. Oh, check it out. It's a it's a it's gonna be fun
It's a it's a game where you go through 12 grades
You start it like kindergarten you go grade one grade two grade three and if you get three questions wrong, you're eliminated
I hopefully I make it past the second grade. I really I'm very concerned
I've actually been studying like the periodic table and like math and shit cuz I'm stood
It's been like 20 years since I've been in a fucking classroom
Yeah, when you're in school and you're young they don't teach you that you don't actually need to know any of it
I really hope I get this past like the fifth grade or something
I think is that's like okay, right getting to like the sixth grade in a game show at least it's like alright
Seventh and eighth grade science questions are kind of they can be really specific, right? Yeah
I do could you beat yourself, you know, you used to do the uh, what did they call it in school the
The fitness awards and gym every year. Yep. They're gonna make you beat your like your times on the
You can do never tell the story about how I tried to run the mile as fast as I could and I end up like
Puking and they had to put me in a wheelchair and we and I had to go through like the halls in my school
I haven't heard that no, I like I've told that story. Yes. Okay. I'm just making sure I've told it
Okay, I was so desperate. I think you just told it again
I did but like I just so badly wanted to I don't know why I just
Decided I was gonna run the mile and try to get it as fast as I could or do it as best as I could
And I think like six or seven minutes was oh wow
You get your name written down in a book if you go like six or seven minutes
And I was like I'm going for it and then I it was awful
I felt awful. I wasn't really prepared for it. I ended up like puking behind a tree. I couldn't really walk
I was so fucked up that the teacher like the phys ed teacher had put me in a wheelchair and I it was it was just awful
But here's one thing I'm really good at in that shit
You know the one where you sit down and you put your feet against the box and you have to put your arms out
And go help them lean forward
No, no, how far how far on the line you can put when you put your hands on top
You guys know what I'm talking about the sit and reach. Yep. I am
Reekishly good at the sit and reach because I have really long long arms and fingers and
Like a really long body
So I'm able to just like go like this and just I beat everybody's record when I was young
I could do that position the reach I could put my nose on the ground. I can barely reach my knees now
What happened put your nose on the ground wouldn't you know like if you put your feet out in front of you and like lean forward?
Yeah, like I could stretch enough that I could put my face on the floor what yeah
Yeah, what what what's the problem? Oh?
Are you good? Oh, I see where this is going. I see I understand where this is going now
You have sexual comedy
Like what the fuck are you talking about you could seriously lean down you could put your face on the ground
Is that what you're telling me? Yes. No you fucking no way. You know, what are you talking about?
That's what I'm talking about you're telling me while you're sitting if you were Steve Wow back you could lean forward
All the way and have your face touch between your legs and hit the ground
Well, I mean like my body would go forward so like not like not like that close
There's what you're talking about
But yes, like if I leaned and tried to do the like touch your toes I could get my face to the ground
I lived it
Like okay, we gotta move on because I'm gonna get stuck on this
Everything's fine. Everything's fine. I'm just I lived it. Are you jealous? No, I just can't
Understand I can't believe that what you're describing is something that everybody says is impossible
But the stop somehow
You put your face on the ground between your legs
Do you understand like how that's not even you make it doesn't make any sense what you're saying
There's no way you were able to do that this no way you're able to do that this I don't believe it
I I refuse to believe that's possible
You could probably look up a Google like a video right now and react to it live on stream
Like someone stretching and do it like I've seen videos of people doing crazier stuff than that
Okay, do you not like those kinds of videos
I think it's time we take a quick break and get a little bit of water refill some coffee and get prepared for the
What's the next conference is coming up next Square Enix coming up next probably anime games and you know growing up
I was just always told that people like, you know, yeah flexible boys. Oh
My god, I just muted him. I mean I muted him. I I'm on his stream, but he's not on mine
Yes, you are. You're muted on my stream respond to you still. Okay, I'm gonna
Okay, I've got to start screening your comments, okay, go ahead and tell me we've got not true
We thought like at some point you were like, oh, you know what?
I'm gonna put like the actual like 18 plus on the channel and I'm gonna start saying swear words like damn
There is there is a mature audience morning on this channel. Yeah, so why can't I talk about being flexible?
It's it's it's the way you do things. You know what I mean? It's the way you do things
It's the way you it's the way you do it. Okay, so let me ask you this. I'm screening it good
All right, let me know I'm sorry. I'm screening it right now
Say that again if you had to if you absolutely had to I'm screening the rest of this
To be so say that one more time if you had to bleach one part of your body, what would it be?
I'm here. I don't know. But what are you talking about? Like? All right. I'm come. All right. He's muted. He's gone. He's muted
We're gonna I'm gonna take a break. We're gonna go pee. I might grab this more coffee
This is gonna this would be like a five-plus minute break
Okay, like I'm not gonna turn the stream off but like there's nothing gonna be here. What are you you agree with that?
What did you just say? I just said like let's take a five-minute break a five-minute
I'll get like a coffee cuz I mean we got like another like 20 30 minutes
I'm I'm like young and spry enough still that I don't need to get coffee. So I'm I'm still just gonna be here
All right. Well, I don't I just I'm not gonna be here for like at least five minutes. Okay. Well, are you are you muting me?
I just want to make sure that I don't like say anything while you're gone
Okay, just came out of my nose. I gotta go
Alright and turn off your stream too. I don't want you to talk about me. Okay
All right, I'll be right back I'm back in like five minutes
we're gonna do Square Enix and
Hopefully we don't talk about stir being able to lean forward far enough to touch the ground, right? Okay
Well, I will be right back after these okay
I want to say that this was also like second or third grade. So you're making it I okay
Goodbye. Good fucking bye. Goodbye. Goodbye. Goodbye. Goodbye. Goodbye. I'm going I'll bring it back. Goodbye. Oh my god
I'll be back. I thought you were talking about like like now like like recently. Oh my god
I'm out get back. Stop. Stop. Stop it. Stop. I'm out of here. I'm out of here
I'll be back in five minutes. I need to unmute him cuz we didn't talk about this. I thought you were saying
Yes, I was able to do that maneuver and go boy. I got I got that maneuver up there somewhere
I thought you meant like you have that maneuver
It's something that you like developed and be able to able to do when you were younger and it's like something you could still do
I
Specifically said I used to be able to do this and I can't even reach my own knees now
I was I didn't even hear the second part of that sentence. Okay
I think that you just have like a prejudice against me where you expect the things that I say to be things you don't want
To hear and that you don't actually give me the floor to speak
And you don't really consciously accept what I'm talking to you about
I don't know my fucking like
My brain thought that like this is so are you know? All right. Goodbye. I'll be back in five minutes