All right, hello. So what's the deal? How's it look? Are they going to start at 4 30? Okay, so uh
Game awards. Let me make sure I have this stream ready. I saved the game here. So we're good to go
Started 20 minutes early. It starts in 10 minutes. Make the face cam huge. Don't worry
There'll be a nice big face cam for you. Game is saved. Let's get out of here
Close that and let's go back over here
I put water in my hair
I I made I just made myself look like a fucking dickhead
I tried to like do like the thing but now I just look I look like way
Way worse than I did 10 minutes ago. I just needs to dry. I look like fucking dad. I look like dad
You know what I mean? Like this is I put way too much water here and none here
All right. What do you got game award? Show me or is it?
My fucking this hair sucks
All right. All right. All right. All right. All right, we're
Uh, oh, sorry I muted
All right game awards. Here it is. There's the stream. I gotta change my
When you when you order hold on, let me see if I can get this right
When you order a crispy chicken sandwich from mcdonald's you have the most tender juicy crispy chicken sandwich
That's ever been made
You get a free medium fries and soft drink, which is great. I get it right because after all who orders just the sandwich
I think I got pretty close
What are you talking about? Wait, did that not come through?
Why do I have three bug legs on my head here? This is spider on my head
There's a there's a big spider right here and i'm just gonna let him stay
I look like the fucking guy in the crime show that they like put against the wall
Hey, man, where's where's the boss?
Just to fuck up cop like I have that like stupid like i'm the guy that goes against a brick wall by the cop by the detective
Okay, um, here we go mcdonald's crispy chicken sandwich
You see it
I don't want you to see that
All right. Oh
It starts soon. This is actually for the pre-show
Is this for the pre-show?
This is what i'm gonna do. All right show starts soon. How do I get rid of that? I don't I want to get this off screen
I disable this
Bathrobe, I don't have the bathrobe anymore. It's gone. It's been lost. I look really sweaty
Like really sweaty I want to get this extension off info. How do I turn this off? I want to like close this
control
Control what's control plus? How do I do that?
I did control plus
I didn't do anything
How do I get this off?
Oh, there we go. I don't want invisible turn it off. Okay. There we go
Now it should be good to go
Okay, here we go. It's time for the game awards
I'm so excited
You have no idea
I played I think one game that came out in 2021. So my opinion you absolutely should listen to I gotta change the category too
One sec
Starts in eight minutes. We'll talk we'll talk in a second. I could just get stuff ready
Why is this showing up here? Make sure make sure it's on hd
hd, okay good
Just stalling I not stalling. It sounds good
change the category
to
I gotta say i'm streaming the game awards. All right
live from my
apartment
Here you go
and then uh, just just chatting I guess
You guys are gonna love this title. I think
Just turn the stream off
I'm gonna look like it's squirrely
Let's make it seem like I don't know this is happening and like
Somebody would be like dude
Please let me help you. I think this would be like a dude
You look like this is a journal. You're a game journalist now
Let me get the chat in the right spot. I want to be able to see you guys
What do you see what you guys have to say? All right, so
My favorite game that came out this year. Let's see if I can name a game that came out in 2021
resident evil 8
warrior ware for the nintendo switch which I thought was a piece of shit delta rune well delta rune is the did
Did you see that? Hold on
Uh, I should just like get gel and just blaster this down
Pokemon snap if I played that for like an hour
Hitman hitman 3 came out this year. I have to get reminded what even came out
I don't I actually don't remember what came up
I'm gonna turn it up. Is that as long as it goes?
volume mixer
This is up
Uh, this is gonna be loud. Be careful
I'm making a
Warning you i'm warning you right now turn down a little bit because you're good. I'm gonna get it
You're gonna get a window sound
It's gonna be loud turn your volume down. I'm not getting it on my turn your volume down
three two one
Here we go cam works
We look all right
It's too loud. I'll fix it
Okay. So what's your favorite game that came out this year?
What's your favorite game that came out this year my favorite game that came out this year is probably
It's probably resident evil 8. I like that's what that's good. Is that even nominated for anything?
No more heroes 3. Yeah, but that means it's not gonna get nominated. What's even what I'm gonna
I don't even know what the nominees are
I haven't even seen the nominees. I have not looked at one
Nominee for the game awards. I don't even know what's nominated
I'm going in without any knowledge at all
undertale
Oh, that's the one that goes
Orza came out
Boneworks boneworks is like 2019
Is this 20? I know I know like 2020
Okay, I this has to change because I hate it. Wait, it just got more it got evolved
It looks like my my hair looks like a plant that needs water
Like I need to water this head
This actually is gonna be it's gonna distract me over the course of this whole entire broadcast two minutes two minutes
Till we find out who won the nintendo
multiplayer
live streaming
Of the year
Go take a shower and come back. Yeah
Yeah, fuck that
What uh, what if what anybody excited for anything is anybody anybody here excited
I don't know what it is. I don't know
Okay, this music is supposed to be hyping me up right now
But I kind of I kind of feel like i'm at the dentist
Like if your dentist was playing this music it wouldn't it'd be like i'm at the den
I don't really care like this is weird to play at the dentist
In the waiting room like i'm not excited at all for this. I'm not excited at all for the dentist
They are the same place to me right now
Can you imagine if like a dog waiting room had this though?
I would that would be so awesome
Just waiting for your appointment
There's gonna be game announcements
I look like 10 years older with this. No, I gotta it's got it's gone
All right here. Let's go 15 seconds. Let's go
I'm probably gonna have to i'm gonna do cam in and cam out
Welcome to the game awards 2021 first big reveal probably coming up right now
Get yourself strapped in here. What why are we getting why are we getting the adult swim warning game awards pre-show?
It's a show for all you completionists out there that rewards you with exclusive content awards and not to be missed
Or you'll embarrass yourself world premieres. I'm sydney goodman
And as you can see, I am in person at the iconic microsoft
No, it's not for gaming's biggest night
We are live streaming around the real world and in the virtual world thanks to it is a free show with oculus you
I thought it was not
Massive musical performance i'm here. I don't have biggest talent in triple a titles like suicide squad
The matrix awakens and destiny 2
It's a free show one thing this community knows
It's that you don't have to hail from a giant studio to make your mark in gaming
So let's start off with our first world premiere an indie
That is as charming as its hero is cunning. This is tunic
Excite me, let's go
Right, all right, all right
All right
Kind of looks like um, all right one of those gray hairs went my eye
All right. It looks cute. All right
tunic
My eyes just hurt
First award of the evening and I really can't think of a better one to start us off. We want you to be games for negative
This category I don't want negative of what gaming can be i'm not gonna be negative just to be negative
Challenge the player on more than just skill exploring all the corners of the human condition
These are the games that remind us in a medium where you can be anything be good. The audio's fucked up
Here are the nominees of the games for impact award
Why is the audio scuffed and the game award for games for impact goes to
Refresh the stream on my end life is strange true colors
It's the music wait, are you guys being serious?
Thank you so much. Um, I can't believe we won
As devs we work on games for years at a time before we share with the world and by the time we do
The world's often different from when we started the adventure. I have low latency on you true for me
Than with life is strange true colors. It's not just about finishing a game in quarantine
Who could have predicted what kind of an impact a game about human connection would make in 2021?
So from everyone at deck nine and our partners at square enix. Thank you so much
Congratulations
I'll tell you if I ever win one of these for any reason
I'm just gonna fall sprint under the stage grab the award and just keep going
And go out the exit that turns your tv into a gaming console
Now if you haven't heard of amazon, they're a little indie development studio
i'm kidding
Anyway now for a limited time the fire tv game the whole time. I would just be going
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
It would be so cringy people probably fucking hate me controller built for i'm never gonna win an award by the way
Let's be really clear about this gaming bundle. We'll be right back with more
They just saw those eyes and they're like don't ever let that guy in the building
That's like exactly that's exactly what would happen
And win the game award 5g network
Yeah, come check it out. We're gonna party hardy until we can't hardly party and there's gonna be some surprise already hardy on the way
I think one of their names is jack harlow. Yeah, I think one. Yeah, one is gi carlo. Yeah jack harlow
So yeah, so is it still pre-show and uh, we'll be on twitch.tv slash nato. Yeah. See you guys soon
Discover
risk of rain two
risk of rain three
No, they would still make it they would in the middle of developing this
Is here 30% off
Yes
That's why the camera's never on
You're just okay. The reason why the camera's never on is because there are like five to ten frogs full mouth frog burp
Every probably 20 30 minutes. I'm serious. That's why I don't do it. It's better like you probably have seen like on the last couple days
What's this?
Started max level
Well, that's just unfair ain't it?
Instantly unlock all end game modes
Don't even play the game
Just unlock everything get to max level and uninstall
This audio is kind of fucked up
Hey everyone, and yeah, the music sounds like it's coming through like a kazoo whether you're in person or watching the stream
We've pulled reddit's r slash gaming community to see pause and unpause for 2021 the game of the year and the winner
Is resident evil village?
And if you're on tiktok use the hashtag game night today
Well
King of fighters
I can't believe it king of fighters. Are you serious pog?
What
Are you kidding me
I
Actually, this is probably gonna be kind of cool
I remember king of fighters. Oh
And now I need to refresh it martial arts festival. That's kind of that's pretty cool
A fight of tea. Wait, there have been 15 of these games ready for a fight. It's actually been 15
Holy shit
That's insane
Turn off low latency. It'll help
What's this?
That's the um
Are you guys seeing it among us?
I'm gonna just put a really really gross plate of food in front of gordon ramsay. It's that same sound
I remember the cartoba an island dune sea
I remember the guide stone. Oh, no, he's not the guy with the chainsaw
No, I mean the the sound effect I just ran out of water. All right. All right. This looks all right
What is it?
Super mario galaxy odyssey 3
I'm sorry. I'll shut up
Home world 3 what is home world home world have a game fun. Should I play it?
And now I have the honor of announcing the same icon for esports categories the same icon
Here award trophy is the game's logo goes to
simple
Congratulations
Here are your nominees for best esports team
And the game award goes to
not as vincere
I don't really pay them. I don't really watch um that much esports but
Game award goes to
coma relations coma
I watch speedrunners, but not like teams
Here are the nominees and the game award goes to pg. I thought that was golf 2021 league of legends world championship
Congratulations league of legends world championship and congratulations to what's pgl and now we have
Three more world premieres in a row ready for you spanning all different genres and niches. Yes go niches
Niches and to start us off rising from the ashes to take their rightful place as gaming royalty once again
Telltale games is back and better than ever and I cannot wait for you to see
All right
What is it? What do you got telltale? I've heard stories about you
So you've survived the crushing black space batman minecraft
lego edition series
So you don't put up with any bullshit
Dawes is a tack dog
So you don't have any problems killing innards or belters who?
Disagree with the opa
I've heard quite a bit about you kamina drummer. It's hard to tell if it's all true though
Truth is truth
How you deal with it is up to you?
Boss man
I keep hearing this show is really good. People are probably really excited about that
Reggie from a hit show the expanse. I heard it's amazing
I'm thrilled to be exploring this great character further check out that's cool issue of game informer to learn more expanse a telltale series
We all have our reasons for babylon's tower to fall
Not everyone has the power to make it happen
What it's not smite what are you talking about?
I'm kind of interested
Why does it kind of look like ass?
I don't mean the game. I mean, I don't like broadcast because you're watching in 480. I'm definitely not watching in 480
Ludwig's here
What's up, Ludwig?
Ludwig raid
Oh shit, Ludwig
What's going on guys?
All the way from youtube
Thanks for making the uh the jump over here
What's going on guys? We're currently clogging our pants
at the
Wait, why what?
I need to know what that was
Hope you had a good stream. Hope you uh
Had a good time. Whatever you're doing
As you know, everyone here would know Ludwig top five content creators in the world without a doubt
How would I okay? I didn't even catch what that game was
It seemed insane
50 community subs from afric and this is the back of it. That's pretty much amphric
I said your name wrong. What is it?
Thanks to the 50 subs make sure you come through it's going to be all over the horizons 5d network
It's gonna be insane whole network. Wait, what?
So make sure you tune in and hang out with us that way
And now guess what? I have
Two more worlds does that mean that it's gonna be on all of our phones steaming hot fresh from the oven
That I don't know the word's steaming hot to me
Wanders restlessly through the darkness silver light illuminates the land and the mountains
It shows its true
It's an ad showcase. Yeah, it's the game awards they
The whole thing is to premiere new stuff and show ads
It's monster hunter
Monster hunter rise sunbreak. I got the one on the switch and I gave up in 30 minutes because I was sick of doing the tutorial
Like after the third hour of the one on switch I was like, I don't even want to play this anymore
I'm sure it's fun. I promise. I'm not bored. I promise
I promise i'm very excited
Holy shit is that how much is that the 30 pounds fighting come closer and find out what's going on?
Car what the fuck was that?
What the fuck?
This is insane
So what is um, it's john tucker must die. But no, no, no. No, what is it?
Scott pilgrim scott pilgrim nukes the universe. What is it? What's it? What's that game?
Evil dead the game at the game awards and tomorrow on george's winter scott
Scott pilgrim versus the world. Okay, and sabres tim willett's about the game which is coming out next year
And now we've got the world gameplay premiere of another evil game evil west
Which we also announced that actually looked kind of cool game awards. Let's take a look
That was that was like that was all over the place. It looked cool these years
maintenance
vigilance
Of course, all that means nothing when hell's gates start spewing shit everywhere
All right
All right, a lot of particle effects
Again, I will make this statement again
I want less particle effects not more
And they're always neon colored
They're always neon blue neon purple neon green
They have to be bright neon colored
It doesn't need to be bloom inside of your particle effects bloom
I don't I hate the neon particle explosion shit
It drives me nuts. You didn't see that coming. That was cool for more content
Here's a new world premiere from perfect worlds new world
What a new world from here?
A busy week in the art busy may have been an understatement
Evidently your sorrows have been working over time. Oh my game. He plays death
That is truly unprofessional now death. We talked about this try not to lose your temper again
Maybe it's about time your supporters showed you some respect
Okay, well you know what they say if you want things done, right it's best to do them yourself, all right
Oh, yo, this looks pretty great. Actually
Who made this this is the hollow knight devs
Have a nice death. That looked pretty awesome. Actually, i'll be honest. I'm ariel bern the game award
We're watching and hosting a watch party together on nate hill's channel
Yeah, we're gonna be watching on twitch.tv slash nate hill and it's all powered by verizon 5g
Spending the night with some of the biggest stars
And me and ariel so come by and check it out come through
And now I have the pleasure of presenting the game award for best audio design
When your medium relies so heavily on being successful in putting the player inside your story audio design is everything
It's the ultimate hint system an instant mood that either alerts the player to what's coming next or obscures it
It's basically playing god
Here are the nominees for best audio design. Oh wait
I get to be alive for this one and the game award for best audio audio design goes to
Come on. Forza!
Oh my god
That's such a surprise to me
Our audio team throughout the development of forza horizon 5 have just been so passionate about everything that they do
There's this relentless appetite to produce an audio experience of the absolute highest quality this this award
It really does mean the world to us. That's really forza sounds great. The car is so i've just
I'm sorry
What's this actually fucking like very technically incredible game congratulations?
Takeshi furukawa here to tell us more about his latest score. Did you guys know jim carries here?
Jim carries it here somewhere. I'm takashi furukawa
You might have heard my music. I am most known for my BAFTA nominated like no not here
He's he's here years ago. I met with a new and exciting swedish studio
Why are you not there with me their vision for a beautiful side? Why would I be here?
The game centers around a heartfelt relationship with a new sonic movie girl and an adorable creature
I instantly fell in love with the project and it's stunning. Don't call jim carry at 3 a.m
With the original soundtrack i'm working on right now. I hope he does something funny
music
I i'm this is actually really like good music somebody just said jim carrey is smoking hot and like it's kind of throwing me off
It's kind of feels like the music that are on a disneyland ride
You guys have been on soren
Is it sounds like
Which is a compliment by the way, that's not negative
Sounds good
Oh, I was gonna catch it in my mouth planet of lana an off-earth odyssey
All right. All right, is he baked? Well according to my calculations
I can't believe it. We are shouldn't be hitting pretty soon final premiere of our pre-show. I gotta be careful though special game announcement
Something you did not see coming. I gotta be careful. No, i'm just kidding
Persona starting to turn into street fighters
For like dragon ball games
Persona four
What was this one?
There's like two or three adjectives after the game
persona four explosive destructive
intuition
Arena ultimax
What is is that is there already one i'm so confused persona for arena ultimax is it a
It's time for me to hand it off to our main show
It was a ps3 game. I know I know persona is like a beloved franchise
There's a lot of like weird side things that I confuse me
An exciting artist performances by sting and imagined dragons appearances by keanu reeves
Carrie ann moss jim carrey ben schwartz and yes
More world premieres coming up so soon for our main show and I just want to say I hope I didn't remake of a fighting game
That's cool. But you know what?
I'm not gonna apologize because when the best of the best of game development and production has that much to share
I think we all win and when it comes to the game awards more is more, baby
Thank you all for getting stoked with me at the pre-show and congratulations to the winners of our first awards of the night
And that's it for me. Is this stream gonna find my seat the 2021 game awards starts now. I have to be careful dmca again
Here we go
Is live of course it is what am I talking about?
It's from arcane
These pieces I want you to hurt like you hurt me to death
I want you to lose like I lose when I play now. That's not jim carrey, please
A fallen angel you ripped out all my parts
I couldn't care for invention. You made me
Fog the smoke
Some dense gas
Like I told you I feel weird just sitting here on camera just sitting doing nothing. I said this every year
an incredibly talented person
Not this guy. He's not me
I shouldn't even be on screen right now. That was so good
like I
Like all this guy's probably spent like fucking hundreds of thousands of hours crafting the ability to build play like this
on stage
At the peak of his musical talent
Wait, is resident evil 9 gonna get announced today?
I don't belong here right now. That was unbelievable. Actually. It was really really good. That was really good
Why don't we just go ahead and tell her that we're divorcing is not pick him away
Of the free-thinking world is in your hands
It's a resident. I know you've been meeting with her behind my back. I loved resident evil 8. I know people didn't like it
And I sense suffering here spirit
You have to work on it just give up we're never getting out of here. Let's see how special you are
Have been doomed to a great game
It will not be fine. It will be
I guess it's my time to shine. You gave it a six
I did
No, I didn't look into your eye that really I did. Sorry. No way
That's embarrassing because i'm talking about how much I loved it
Stay a team. Enjoy the beach solution was enough
I'm breaking this loop
Welcome to the game awards
2021 now here's your host
Jeff keely
He's like pulled muscle in my chest. I'm serious
We're here all the stupid things to that apparently game awards video games biggest night live in person
Look at all that. That's a lot
Holy shit, that's really decorated sting phenomenal. So honored to have him open our show
That was what could have been from arcane the new netflix series based on league of legends
Thank you so much sting ray chen and the game show was supposed to be really good, isn't it conducted by lauren
I've seen the first two episodes absolutely incredible. Thank you guys
Well, I gotta say it feels so incredible to be back here on stage at microsoft theater
And streaming live to tens of millions of you around the world
This is a night for the fans and you know, the games we love
Are nothing without amazing developers and that's why we do this show to honor the creators of games
So welcome to all of you. I didn't read the harry potter books either and I watched the movies. I'm not gonna play league ever
So good to see everyone
But you know, we gotta be real and we can't ignore the headlines that are out there game creators need to be supported by the companies
That employ them. I think we all agree with that
So let me just say this before we get to any of the news or announcements or awards
We should not and will not tolerate any abuse
Harassment and predatory practices by anyone including our online communities
We all love games and if we want this industry to keep growing we must build an even brighter and more inclusive future
The games we play
And when the games that we love they teach us that we can impact the world around us and tonight
I call on everyone to do their part to build a better safer video game industry
Speak out online
Vote with your time and with your dollars
Empower these world builders who are creating the future of all entertainment
And believe me the future you're about to see
Looks absolutely incredible
All right, we got a lot of good stuff for you. We have so much news to get to
But now to present tonight's first award, please welcome a nominee tonight and the star of far cry six
I thought I was gonna say the star of sonic the hedgehog 2
Wait, really?
Oh shit, that's awesome
I love this guy
Independence allows a game to go a little bit more wild become a bit stranger and the freedom to break boundaries
Demonstrate excellence achieved through great risk here are the nominees for best independent game
All right, people are gonna people are gonna eat each other over this one
Look, I know this sounds weird, but didn't play it. He's repeating itself
Didn't play it
Fuck. I'm what am I even doing here?
Why am I here?
I shouldn't be live for best independent game. Her inscription was very good. I've always been scripted if it was me
kena bridge of spirit
I actually did not play any of these games
All right
If I mean this and I mean it I mean it
I mean it
If I have not played at least three games that are nominated throughout this entire broadcast
I will gift a hundred community subs
Like come on, dude. Are you serious?
I have to have played at least three of these. Um, well, yeah, but it was an amazing journey to get here
Um took a lot of heart with an awesome team a few of them are here today
But just can't say enough about the amazing people we worked with on to make this game and to make the vision come true
Um have to take our partners at sony who kind of believed in us from the very beginning
I don't think I played one three and all the guys at epic who just have been there from the beginning. So
Thank you everyone. And uh, this is a great honor. Oh, I said a hundred subs not add anything to the debt
You said you played one. I know I played resident evil 8
Congratulations guys. All right. Now it's time to look into the future
Two years ago this team announced their game on this very stage now
They're back with the first gameplay reveal when I saw this
I could not believe it was actual gameplay, but it is captured by the team in game this past weekend
So back and get ready. Is it though experience a new level of cinematic immersion?
Okay, we'll see
She said our swords
We will forge new stories to strike the gods that haunt us
All right
Oh, it's this game with the real faces when they were still singing and it was like a real face
Soothe our scars of their siege of our may see them as gods
We will show you eyes behind their eyes
Uncanny valley maxed out
What is that
What was that?
Do you fight this shit? I didn't play the first one
Did I just skip the book and go right to the movie when this comes out?
I hear it senua saw that to win the war we must break this siege break it
With an unshakable truth
Break it than impossible feet
Does this actually gonna be gameplay or is it guys the edible just hit I thought I was in my car
Whoa
I'm just kidding. Relax. It's the eyes. The eyes are just so
expressive
All right, just wait for the letter q to pop up on the screen
And a keyboard style and it being pressed in pressed out pressed in pressed out pressed in pressed out
It's the look at the eyes. It's the eyes
Miss
Miss oh
Knocked down knocked down
Those graphics are crazy. Was it on xbox?
You see
Truly incredible. That's not a cinematic. That's gameplay and that's why we do world premieres because the state of our art
Just keeps getting better. Thanks to ninja theory for that incredible. Oh man
It was gameplay in the sense of it's the gameplay engine not like a full motion video rendered cutscene
Right
That's like a rendered. That's not that's a non rendered full motion cutscene. That's still impressive though. It looks great
Am I gonna play it? Not really
But maybe I will all right. Give us a star wars game. Give us a star wars game. That's
Give us a vr triple a star wars game. I want to have the lights every my hand, please
connect
No, it's not connect
What is it?
All right. It's a tower defense game. Imagine if it was I top down just tower defense game
Star wars eclipse td
Okay. Well, I don't really know exactly what that is, but I saw lightsabers
Although I did play
Yeah, last jedi game no the last game last star wars game star wars eclipse will be the first
Game set in the high republic era of the star wars galaxy and is being created by quantic dream in collaboration with lucasfilm games
And is currently in early development. All right, there are many more game announcements to come
Trust me as well as awards all night
We are partnering with youtube shorts if you have a favorite nominee tonight that doesn't win
Let us know your thoughts by posting a youtube dream
They made the movie game right and head to the youtube gaming twitter handle to find out how to get your very own
Salty consolation gift. All right right now. It's time to meet our first global gaming citizen a program
We started back in 2018 to turn our air over his hitman individuals who are building positive inclusive. Where's hitman around gaming?
Was hitman actually gonna be here
That'd be cool. They announced them. I love hitman
I grew up playing games games was as a little kid as a little a little gay boy
I just want vr star wars so bad different games gave me a place to
Feel safe and to be myself ever since that
One with the joystick in the arcades
It was like you control the tie fighter and then you fight darth vader it was like a big arcade cabinet reference to be inspired
To build up all this drag this insane costume all this makeup all this hair, but feel powerful
Because as a kid, I felt weak. I felt like the outsider
Yeah
Now let's run to the exit when you find people that have similar interests you can be yourself
So close you don't have to be worried about all these things that make you relax guys. Come on special
I gotta turn my switch on it's been a long time
Besides uh, what was the last thing I played on switch? What was the last video game that I actually played?
What was the last video game? I actually played
besides of ports of 20 year old video games those don't count
That just like scared me
Yeah, we've got some stuff on sale, but let's all take a breather while we give away hundreds of free game codes
This is our small way of saying thank you for playing our games for the past 35 years
And we're just getting started yeah, am I high
And much more including stuff that hasn't even leaked I feel like i'm the only one seeing this
We have a project that can use your talents in fact across bethesda and all our studios we're hiring
So consider this your invitation to join us
There's a lot of work to be done. Bethesda are they gonna show um
Are they gonna show
That ended weirdly
What are they codes for? I don't know try them on steam. I would try them on steam
It doesn't work on steam
Maybe it was just a laugh out loud joke
All right, don't tell me what was nominated for game of the year
I don't want you to tell me. I don't want to know
Play for free february 11
Is anybody else just waiting for like an evil villain guy to be just like a normal person
Oh, whoa. Whoa. Whoa, wait a minute. Whoa, that was lost ark
That was lost ark
That was lost ark. I've been waiting for that game for like 25 years that game. I want to play that
I actually really am interested in that that game. What is it out english?
That was a new look at lost ark from amazon games coming in february and speaking of amazon
We're proud to partner with prime gaming. Holy shit. I want to play that you can level up your gaming experience with free
Games including need for speed hot pursuit tails of monkey island and frostbite
That game got announced when my hairline was here and for the games you already own
You can unlock skins i've been waiting for that for a long time league of legends new world apex legends and roblox check
Regularly for new drops and surprises at gaming.amazon.com
Next in the days leading into the game awards
I read the internet with a little bit of fear wondering if some of tonight's big surprises might leak
This one sure didn't it's time. Oh
that no one had on their big non-league
Watch it be something just so
It's gonna be batman
Batman versus superman the experience
You put on a vr helmet your batman. You just get the shit kicked out of you
With haptic feedback all of your chest and shit
Gameplay gameplay any gameplay anything at all besides wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait monolith monolith monolith monolith monolith monolith monolith
Monolith monolith
I am that's that company's fucking awesome
That's a big deal to me I love that studio
Shadow of mordor shadow war
Gotham city imposters
Fear I am actually I want to see more about that game. I'm very excited. I love that studio
For you escape to my little brother's idiot games that one that one that one
Lady demetrius
There it is we got yes, we got one
president evil
We got one
Let's fucking go
That was the scariest walk i've ever done do a line do a line do a line
Thank you, I keep repeating myself an honor to receive this i'm just repeating words standing here in front of you all today
I would like to give a really huge. Thank you to capcom for creating an amazing game full of wonderfully
rich and
known
He is but one
And to rosanna and dj with the workhouse to steve canibaly our amazing cinematics director
I've said this before but i'm gonna say it again because i'm a broken record
You took a chance on me when you hired me for this role and in doing so you have changed my life
Being a part of this game playing this role and becoming a member of this amazing community has changed my life
So thank you so so much
Now that was great. She was great and doesn't even
You nailed it
The my favorite game of the year is gonna sweep we're gonna get a clean sweep of every award
This is not the story you want it to be
Wrestling empire is not nominated
Oh shit, that actually might be my favorite game of the year. You're right
real face game
All right, it's here's the new trend in gaming the we have a real face
Sam lake sam they come all the way over for finland for this. This is so exciting
Alan wake too. It's been a decade fans have been asking you for it
Why is now the right time to bring him back? Well, first of all, didn't alan wake get removed from steam?
It's been raining here in los angeles today
It's on us like fiction fiction leaking out into reality. So, sorry
Didn't get removed from steam because they had like copywritten music in it or something over 10 years
Uh make this streaming of making it we've been iterating on the concept and we know fans have been asking for it
We've been a bit protective. We knew this is gonna be a pretty scary experience
That game was all over that was a cool game that was even with a flashlight, right?
What kind of game are we gonna get for the sequel? Can you tell us something about it?
Yeah, we are breaking new ground here. This is going to be remedy's first ever
survival horror game
Our take on the genre the first game had horror elements to it, but it was an action game
I'm actually more interested in this than I was before the perfect genre to bring together
The story and gameplay closer than ever before because the story horror story
Is at the very heart of this and it's psychological layered deep mystery to dive into
I you know, you are actually pretty that's incredible. I'm interested. I can't wait to see what you're doing with this game
I know you said to me a while ago
This was your dream project and i'm so honored that we got to announce this here at the game awards
So we're gonna hear more next year. I think right? Yes, we you know
Fitting to the theme. Yes, we're gonna go dark. Okay for a while to work on this
We'll be back next year
Sus wake time. Okay to show more. All right summer 2022 more on allen way to play control. I didn't hurt as good
Very exciting. All right. Well now i'd like to welcome a comedian writer and a well-known chili dog enthusiast
It's ben schwarz. Yeah, it's such a carry
He'll be back soon. He'll be there soon
Imagine he like scrunches down into a ball puts his like legs up here with his like butt right here and he starts echoing
And then tries to roll
Fringe or like chad
What do you guys think? Thank you so much for supporting our movie also
Thank you very much for the note about sonic's legs and teeth in our original trailer
I know for real. That's a good note. That's a good note. I'm really happy that worked out
We needed that we really needed that
The good news is you need to go outside our first movie that we got to make a sequel and today. Yes
I go outside all the time. I my vitamin d levels are my blood vitamin d is 38 people at the end
today
I brought with me the trailer to that sequel. I can't actually I I liked that movie. I know
Like the real trailer
This is a blank dvd for effect if this was the real trailer
I feel like we were screwed because there's no computer with a dvd drive anymore
So this would be like troublesome. I've got a 40 blood vitamin d level. We all are about sonic 2 so many
Incredible people are in this movie. We got james marzen tikka sumter. Colleen o'Shaughnessy as tails
Idris elba as knuckles
I want to see this, please
Jim carrey as dr. Robotnik
Now jim has actually sent a very special video over to say hello to all of you and
Please be in the costume in luck because I have the video with me right here
Oh a callback. I'm happy just kidding. This is blank still. Let's roll the video. Jim. What do you say?
Hello everyone and hello ben
I'm sorry. I couldn't be there with you, but I look forward to meeting all of your avatars in the metaverse
Where we can really get to know each other
Hey before you see this exciting new son, he's smoking hot
I'd like to pass on a word of advice that my scottish grandfather gave to me when I was just a boy. He said son
Don't grade it in the grinder
Don't do it son
Don't grade it and the grinder boy
Graded trek five confirmed grade it till the cows come home
But don't grade it and the grinder
And then to drive the point home he put his hands around my neck and he squeezed real hard and he said
Don't do it son
Don't grade it and the grinder are you listening to me boy?
Are you listening?
Inspiring words
Thank you, jim, you know, I think we all need to hear that
Yeah, take it in if you need to it was so weird great. Okay. Here we go
Thank you again for continuing to support the blue blur and it is my honor to present to you the trailer
For sonic the hedgehog 2 enjoy
I think it was the people in the audience going like
You know exactly what i'm talking about quiet
Pretending to be batman blue justice trademark pending you're still just a kid
Trust me there will come a moment when your powers will be needed
But you don't choose that moment that moment chooses you I just got goosebumps. Wait a second. Did you steal that from oprah?
Papa's got a brand new stash
Since i've been gone i've discovered the source of ultimate power
That sounds big it's been on my vision board for years
Not too late tails
Who are you names tails?
Okay, this is what we're gonna do step one light taunting step two. I have no idea
Isn't too bad
Hey aus emeralds face it you're never going to get my power
Do I look like I need your power?
Where are my manners sonic meat knuckles?
Rilling commentary, I can't talk over a trailer most anticipated game is horizon forbidden west from gorilla games
What team is hard at work back home in amsterdam finishing it up for a february release
But i'm grateful they put together this for the fans
They're gonna set up for this one
What was the game? What was the game? What was it? What was the game?
Remember you talked through all the other trailers died. You don't I don't talk through jim carrey. No matter what
That's like talking at church. Are you shitting me?
Constant conflict. Yeah, it is
Oh, that's that's chugging
That's chugging. It's chugging
Wow, that actually looks cool
That last 10 seconds made me want this game. That looked really cool
The gameplay was lagging
It's early
It's early relax
I thought that was her making those sounds
I thought she was going like
I was like, holy shit. Who is this?
There's one thing I wish I could do it was play a musical instrument, but I got these fingers
It don't they don't work. I can't
I got this which never closes and never ceases
This works just fine. These not so much
It's actually not much of an issue. You just need practice
I hold a pencil like this
I don't think practice is going to help me
Wow game awards orchestra. Thank you so much. I am so ready for this game
Thank you so much to lauren and the orchestra and in her first ever performance and trip to the united states
The beautiful julie elvin. Thank you so much julie
Class speaking of music last week
You probably saw everyone posting their spotify wrapped on social media my top writers of 2021 rufus
Sam fender and day glow you can make your spotify wrap now in the app and stick around as we reveal for the first time
Mario rpg ost chrono trigger ost on gaming consoles and 2021 also on the music front some of the music
We've been playing tonight is from sessions diana sessions is riot games project with music made to be safe to stream without fears of copyright issues
Check out sessions dot riot games dot com to download the full album and now it's time for a special and long-awaited announcement
Percussion I can do that. It's just swinging and hitting things
Final fan is this when they're gonna finally reveal the other characters
Cats it's not cats. It's not in this trailer. I'm gonna have a problem
Begin surrender to the darkness embrace it
This is the pc port. Oh, all right
So when is the second there's a second part coming out, right?
What's your name xbox game pass for pc
2021 game awards xbox game pass for pc and youtube
What do we think? You know, it's so effortful. I like that. We animate it. You're welcome
Okay, I understand the impulse to do something big
But what do pc gamers actually want?
Because I don't think it's that video graphics cards new pc games. We have some great ones coming day one
That aren't 400 marked up marketing idea
What if gator tweets out this list more or less leaking it in a cool hip way
I retweet it because I have so many more followers in here. It's done. What's done? Tweet it. It's out there
No, you didn't I don't think you should have proactivity and a crime, man
When people think about xbox game pass they think about console. They don't know we're a pc gaming service. Why not just call it
pc game pass
That's a great idea. Okay, we're going with that
Just like that, you're gonna change the name of the whole thing because of gator who calls himself gator
It's a good name. All we gotta do is ask some top tier streamers to this to really land gator. Yes, what about
100 thieves big fans
Was that's a hundred thieves. Where are the other 97? I get it. That's thank you, man
We'll take it from here brother. We got cameos. We got ideas percolating right next steps to me
Like what about jerva?
I said it. Are we really gonna make I said it for the game awards and you're not gonna wrap in it at all
That meeting
fucking
Get away with that graphics cards need to be cheaper
And I get thrown out this is kind of like saying we're at the the game awards
Yeah, yeah
I just didn't mean to put the webcam on why is the stream in 480? It's not I swear to god. It's 1080
Handy crush
For a second. I thought that was a new mario was like they're gonna just really just announce a new mario like that
That's the golf one that I promised
It's 864p. Yeah, but the stream i'm pulling is 1080
Slime rancher 2 is on day one release for the pc game pass
Are you lying to me right now or is do you mean that hello game words?
My name is martin fos anderson aka mr savage is really bad
If you're if you're stressed what I do for you're trying to play a game and trying to win it
If I was stressed after school, I just wouldn't be able to focus properly and it would just make everything 10 times harder
Together with truth. I have an important message vaping nicotine can increase anxiety symptoms and stress levels
I think it's really important people know the truth about vaping nicotine
Yeah, don't fake what are you doing?
Smoke is bad. Yeah, I what are you doing?
I don't know
Did I tell you guys about the stream that I wanted to do?
Where I was kind of just put on like sunglasses and get in and get in front of the webcam and play fortnight
And just be vaping
and the whole time the webcam would get filled with smoke like it would be you couldn't even see me and the smoker line was
gonna go off
And like a fire like firefighters were gonna come like break the wall behind me and I was gonna still just be playing fortnight
Sorry, um, I'm I'm I just didn't do it present the game award for best action, I guess
And oh shoot. That's so sick
Sorry, sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry
So, you know as a martial arts superhero myself, uh, I know a little thing or two about
action and uh
Oh snap with the plasma sword
What are you watching? Sorry. Sorry. Um, where was I the prompter right?
What's supposed to be watching action is the best when it's kinetic and and fast paced and
And and totally organic to the uh, no you did not master chief
Oh, you didn't watch your stream. Sorry guys. Look you guys know that halo just that person with a phone filming
And it's literally sitting in my living room while I gotta be here
Uh, so he's watching your stream actually playing halo
I'm i'm on stage presenting the game award for best action while watching streamers on twitch
Seemed like a pretty reasonable compromise
Anyway, here are the nominees name drop me name drop me. Let's see it
Stop yelling. Why am I yelling?
Didn't play it
Come on
Didn't play it. Come on
Played this one
That's two
Oh, absolutely that should not be on the list that should absolutely be taken off
That shouldn't be on here. Sorry. Sorry
And the game award for best action game goes to
Returnal
I didn't play this either
Stop doing the pog joke
You know what? I actually agree with you
Because like every time I do that like I hear a snap down here
So I have to stop doing that. You're right. I won't do that anymore. Wow
Thank you. Uh, we are so happy to be here to accept the award
I gotta look up this game on returnal returnal when I first joined house mark
I could tell returnal was a really special game
And it was our amazing team that pulled it off and brought you the game that you played today
What is this? Thank you to the amazing team at house mark in helsinki, finland our incredible codec partners who helped us build returnal
Uh our amazing partners at xdev represented by pedro
And uh, everyone at playstation. We're so grateful. We could build a game like returnal
Uh, but biggest thanks space game go to the players. Thank you for playing and uh, thank you for supporting returnal
It's ps5
Was it good? I mean just literally just one best action game should be good
It's very good. It's a rogue like
Action shooter. Oh shit. Should I try it?
That actually kind of looks cool
Should I play it?
Really good. It can't be all right. Maybe i'll give it a look at the beginning
We landed on mark only on ps5 looked wrong. Oh, okay
I gotta get a ps5 then
Yeah, we wanted to find her good luck. I know
But she was baiting us
Look, can I just like come over your house and just like smell the exhaust of your ps5?
Like can I just like you know what I mean? Like I want to like at least be able to know
She knew we would
Say
No
Nothing just said no
And I just put my hand at the back of the exhaust and feel the heat feel the air
Let's go. Oh, dude. It's like it's hot
No, dude, you can't touch anything in my house
Oh
Yeah, what is going on here?
He's going insane because it's boring
No, it's been some pretty cool reveals actually from the uh, the first mission of the game, which is so cool
And bungee is celebrating their 30th anniversary this year
So, uh, congratulations to bungee and there's a lot of great stuff
All right now it is time to get to another new game announcement
Uh a few months ago a japanese game creator reached out to me and said hey
I want to announce my next game at the game awards and i'm so honored to have this opportunity to present this
Global announcement to all of you. Please enjoy
They're just rolling them out just bang bang bang bang bang, huh? Oh shit something good here. Holy shit
Oh
This one has my attention
Slither head
That's a fun one. It's clear tori Amazon has not abandoned his roots. Uh, thank you again for that very special announcement
Speaking of uh, just that we have another brand new game to announce from a studio
Comprised of many industry veterans check this out. That looked really actiony though
That did not look like a typical runaway and hide kind of game that looked like you were fighting stuff with swords
Wish list them I think I don't think they were available. Oh put the human face on the top
Stranding us in these realms we have searched for a way lost
What about the his the dangerous falls?
You are never gonna get like a huge monster like that with just a huge swinging nutsack. It's never gonna happen
just stop
People of the goal. Where's the book like it's not gonna happen
and the crazy part is
It would be every portal is it's not gonna happen. Stop saying it
Half-life one had it
Like these 500 foot dinosaurs
um
Somebody said it would be a crit
spot
What the fuck dude?
How inappropriate and stupid that would be like no why
I would not want to play that game
Oh
Admit it you'd love to play that
It would be really strange. It would be like wow
They do it just things
This giant dinosaur monster has huge balls excepting game of the dragon age
Now you've got a new studio inflection up in canada
What kind of game do we get here with how would you even react to that?
Yeah, so it's a survival crafting game a shared world idea
So we want to bring players together solo experiences cooperative experiences
Lots of ability to go and explore these amazing fantastical magical realms are going to give players lots of ability to come together
Cooperate lots of opportunity for community building that sort of thing
Well, it looks incredible. I said, I love it. Show me this game. Well, I was like this looks so cool
People and you're pretty far along that's real gameplay footage. So people play it next year. Absolutely
Yeah
So we're going to be nearly accessed next year on pc only and looking forward to inviting players in if you want to see more
Play night and gale.com amazing. All right
Well, thank you for that and now a nice surprise for the game awards and tonight we've got much more coming up
But we're also going to introduce you to our game awards second annual future class
What was I feel like they haven't done any
winners
Like three of our industry you can see the full list at the game awards.com tonight
We're also partnering with google play to have our future class mentor the next generation of women in gaming
Google plays change the game aims to improve female representation a z targetable point group of teenagers
Right now meet one of the new members of our future class
I'm dj 9 and ice cream
I hate me right now and I love it. My focus is primarily joy a vats target
Has the potential to be cynical about everything this game sucks
I hate it and I hate everything what's going on. It's much more enjoyable. What's happening?
A lot of that started when I was in the military finding out that people shot rockets at your plane
It's a reminder that nothing is promised. Do you want to look back on your life?
I thought I was doing that looks on the good because I have the gox lr
Hello world. I'm eric slabek from beat games and i'm thrilled to announce our new music pack collaboration
Lady gaga music pack launches on beat saber tonight. See you all in multiplayer
What do we do? Wait, you guys heard that right?
Yeah, you definitely heard that
I'm sorry, but that first swing hits the desk or the top of a chair or vase
I don't like this what I would call propaganda from the vr industry
With like oh just put the headset on and fucking just go
No, no, no, no, no. No, you have to clear out your entire room. You gotta like take your trash out
You've got to make sure that there's nothing there. It's an empty room or you're gonna get hurt
There's no way you put on goggles and just go for it
Like oh just push the chair over four or five inches. No, excuse me
What is this?
Like if that shit happens if you did what that person did you're gonna you're literally gonna karate chop through your desk like
Wwf style you're gonna go through the table
Is knee golem
Yeah, what?
This is a different style. This looks
What is this the lord of the rings golem?
Is it v is it vr?
Hi game awards. It's miztech final phase vr team just released its latest expansion and walker and to celebrate dude
Fuck are you serious? Wouldn't you want to like like go like this and shit like
That would have been so cool
Where did you get the germ is down bad vr now when you order when using code and walker you get free delivery
Uh half-life alex was worth buying that
I'm sorry like look
Half-life alex is worth a thousand dollars. Okay
We all made that joke 10 years ago. I would pay a thousand dollars for half-life free
I did well I did and so did a lot of you so it came true because that's what we got
pubg2
Is it actually pubg2?
They made cooking simulator game in vr
Sign me up
free to loot free to play
free to play
Wasn't pub wait pubg wasn't free already. Wait, what was pubg not free?
Was it afterwards come join us for the game awards watch it was 40 bucks
I'll see you soon back in the summer of 2019. I visited this shit first time developer at his studio in the united kingdom
He told me his dream was to one day share his game with the world at the game awards
Well, that dream is about to come true. It's free
Kind of late for that. Don't you think like I feel like that should have been like three or four years ago
Well, but most of the battlegrounds games kind of falling off a little bit
Yeah, I mean like fortnight's obviously huge and it will be probably forever
They're really big in china. Oh lf plus l ratio
Something. All right. I I you just unlocked the memory
I have a tweet from like
2016 that somebody ratioed recently and I was like, what are you talking about?
They like they went to like an old tweet and they like ratioed me
I was trying to figure out what the fuck was happening
I got like a notification
I was like because I check my twitter like once a week or something, right?
I'm just scrolling down and I see a tweet that I had like four likes on this tweet from like five years ago
And the person wrote like oh i've ratioed you about the fucker or something
I was like what and they had like more likes than I did
But it's just like that tweet's like seven years old
I made me laugh. I was like, holy shit
I got fucking destroyed wait to play summerville. Thanks to chris olson and the team at jump ship for that one
Next we're gonna head to the stage. I actually like audibly was like that's fucking funny
studio
Yeah, and excuse I need to ask this question. I need to listen to me very important
I know I can't pause the game more. This is live
People are like going back to tweets
From like 2014 and shit and like liking them or like replying to them like they were yesterday
Like oh, uh ursula woman crush wednesday. I wrote that like when I wrote that when I was like nine
Okay, let
I keep getting notifications from tweets from like 10 years ago people just like oh, yeah, i've retweeted that
Holy shit, i'm excited
Shake then take heart it's off to the bakery
Chef's heart maker has a plan the best heart maker in the land
If they're expedient with the ingredients, then he might just lend a hand with that delicious last course
Of the delicious last course
If there's a single meal to help make chalice ring there's a delicious last course
Oh the delicious last course
Of the delicious last course
Searching
Is it actually coming out
Oh, this is big. Come on
Look at the drum set. Yeah, look at the drums announce it. Come on
Yes, all right. I i'm actually gonna shut the fuck up. I'm curious. I'm very excited
cool
This is cute
Nice
I can't wait to play this only thing I actually cared about
Quite a it's quite a wait, but it's really awesome to see they actually got to finish it
That's awesome. I can't wait. We have a date june 30th 2022. It's so exciting the delicious last course
All right
Next up early
You saw the trailer for sonic 2 the movie and now it's time for the little blue guy to give you a glimpse at
His next game also coming in 2022
Next game about alan wick. Oh, yeah
It's gonna be it's gonna be a sonic. Uh, well, it's 3d three-dimensional. That's important to know
I'm gonna hold judgment because they make them do weird shit
I wouldn't be surprised if you got a lab coat and was making potions and shit in like an underground mad scientist laboratory
Sonic and the mad science laboratory. Just make it a sonic game. Come on, please
not a frontiers
Stop making up scenarios to get outraged at
That's the point of a straw man
I build his ass up so I can knock his ass down
Uh
What I got a little job for you, it's just temporary folks here they don't make no never mind who you are
What you done?
Everything's got to be new these days
sensational
Whoa, let the mirrors show you who you are. What's your pitch pal? You want to level?
I'd love to learn anything that you want to teach me
I can read a mark quick. This is an fmv game. Holy shit, please pay good money just to make himself feel better
Heaves his own lives
Don't get hurt and you lie you try to find your way out. I warned you didn't I?
There is no way out
Oh, it's not okay. Never mind
They're already we already knew about this that was the best way i've seen since
That's trending now on to awards business. I am honored to be announcing the best art direction category
These nominees across a broad variety of budgets and genres each found their own path. No gameplay. Nobody visual design
music and animation
Into their own distinct expression of intent and purpose
Uh, you know one franchise, I love the art that looks good though. That looks actually really good
I hope we get a new one of those
Anyhow, here are the nominees for best art direction
I'm just looking for one more
That's just been nominated like four or five times. This is good. I didn't play any of those and the game award for best
Our direction goes to sargonas two. I would be fired a guess death loop
Wait, this is the game that you rewind time and like go fight
Yourself and other people like kill each other going relinding and shit
I should play this
Because last night I made the bet that gear model toro would be giving this award so
I can't give an opinion
I would stick to my to my everybody's looking for like a like a hot take here. I didn't I didn't play this
I don't i've never even seen the trailer when I was studying the 60s era by watching his movie the shape of water
Um scrutinizing the sets the colors the lighting so thanks for your indirect participation
Also, thank you for rewarding or risk talking or patient for visual
Expression or level of craftsmanship
And our attention to details. That's a our players seem to really appreciate isn't it?
Tonight i'm proud ladies and gentlemen, and I think the guys across the the ocean at arken are really proud too
Thanks to them for this fucking what a psycho nuts
Thanks to my long time art buddies damien and jean-luc ding abba kabba. Well, thanks you bro. We did it
I may as well just gotten off the subway and like brought in here and never played a game in my life
A big hug for our families and friends. And lastly, I'd like to dedicate this award to the boss robert altman
Peace amour and french fries. Yes. I lost a bet last night also
I'm genuinely angry. Damn. Really?
What did I say? I was like, I can't give you I'm basically like a guy that just got picked up from like the subway
That's never played a game just like hey you want to go to the game awards like just like eating like players voice category
Uh, sure
Players voice goes to halo infinite
That one came out of three days ago
And the game award goes to
Tales of a rise for best score and music those nominees are
Near replicant say the whole thing jeff say the whole thing
One two, two, two, three, four five five one, two, two, four four five five themselves on who they want to win
I wish he said the whole thing
I got one
I didn't know who got nominated. Well, let's see who was right. Here are the nominees for content creator of the year
and the game award goes to
Dream congratulations dream
Of course not here in person
Here are the nominees for best multiplayer game
And the game award goes to
It takes two
That one's actually good that one's actually really good
Holy shit that one that game's amazing actually
That's three
I am never gonna get nominated. I'm never gonna win a single award presented by verizon
There I talk about how like I might show my dick on stream. No one's going to nominate me for anything
It's never gonna happen. Why are you waiting for it?
It's not gonna happen
Yo, don't be waiting for that
What's good? This is kyleef adams here in full effect rocking
This one we podcast the premier podcast spotlighting people of color in the video game industry
Look at me. Look at me now. I when you have i'm not gonna get nominated for anything
Culture and within the world where you see something that grows you dick of the year
Wrong award show confused you feel upset you feel hurt
There's a different thing that I can do it's a different one
The things right now are very other things are all over the place in lots of different ways. It's scary, man
I mean, it's that's just there's no other way to put it
It is scary to be black in this country today
I'm a black mom
So i'm scared a lot of people in gaming communities just don't want to hear it
We sat down for about two hours or so just kind of ran through our feelings and emotions because it's all
I don't want to bring politics
Well, i'm glad that you can ignore this shit because it's quote unquote politics when there's a lot of people reality
So the show goes up it launches so i would see i'm happy to be your streamer of the year
Hey, you need to check this out. Hey, you need to be paying attention to this
And then one of the big outlets caught it and then it just moved
Let's just speak the 100 true
You know, I'd always wanted to use my voice in a way that felt powerful
Really bring home the conversation about doing a show through a prism of blackness
I think we did the job in a really good way and I think the world and the industry was better for it
When he said ego, what do you say? Oh, I want to read this
Ego andy, what did it say?
That ego andy is trying to to cope with him not winning an award. I don't I really don't care. I don't
I've really just I trust me. It's pubg again
Doesn't care. I don't
I think I need some kind of reward
I think I need some kind of reward to prove that I
Really like just wanted one
With amazon luna, I can play all my favorite games straight from the cloud. That's right
I can play on my fire tv tablet and phone
I thought I did a good job
I thought I did a good job this year
You got a bunch of people are spamming loser loser cry loser
If you just came into the stream, you'd be like, holy shit. What the fuck these people are assholes. These people are total pricks
And now i'm wet
Hope when hope is lost
All right, I kind of
I kind of want to go get a shitload of water and dump it in my eyes
And go fall screen and be crying that I didn't win content creator of the year
Will you guys play along with that for a little while?
Just like boogers like flowing out of my nose
Why would anybody stream them doing that
That's right
Now there's a shitload of other content creators guys that are doing all kinds of cool shit. So don't worry
Although I would have liked to have seen ludwig on that list
She's an actor who stars in the mandalorian and the upcoming series the book of boba fett
Please welcome ming na wen
Also, some of the vtubers have just exploded in growth and popularity. There's there's so many good creators
Our own involvement with the story and its characters to be nominated best narrative award
A great game demands provocative dialogue and a captivating plot
But above all it must exhibit a meaningful involvement with the audience
And also just speaking as the mother of a son who loves gaming
It's nice when there's more to the story than just blowing up
Grenade factories and shouting obscenities at your alligator brides, what if you won worst creator?
That would be actually really funny the nominees for best narrative then like then like the crying on camera
Like I I did a good job this year. Oh, that'd be funny
Piecing together the puzzle it was a spell. I am telling you if it is a spell
How do we break it? I need to find out exactly what happened that night. I can reveal their secrets
You know, I would really like them to do more than one content creator category
streaming youtube
Like it's so huge now
That it's taken over. It's so in the mainstream at this point that I feel like this should be more than like a few categories
It's hard to recognize everybody when you have one category
Keep coping. That's what i'm doing
best narrative wait
Is this an original narrative?
a surprise
There are so many people responsible for making this such a wonderful thing
I want to thank marvel game studios for trusting us with their characters
And for allowing us to make them our own
For our fabulous cast bringing them to life in ways that words on a page can never do
for olivier
Does it takes two on there you bear day up my game director the entire crew who worked on it
And of course my wonderfully wild wacky
immensely talented writers
Thank you for making comedy the game is really good. Yeah, I heard that too not complaining too often when I pushed you
To remember our main themes of grief and to go deeper
Who am I kidding? I know you complained, but thank you for not doing it to me
Thank you everyone this is an honor
I think the the problem that anybody that works on a huge popular franchise license thing
is even if it is really good you have to fight against the sort of
Stigma of being the licensed video game. You're already up against a pretty high wall
But yeah, I heard I actually heard it was pretty good
I'm not gonna play it but I heard it was good
I don't play video games
This kind of reminds me of uh, like wind waker. Can't you float around in wind waker?
You'd be a bird too
i'm interested
That looks cute
What a beautiful game. All right. Now we have something very special the gameplay world premiere trailer for rocksteady's newest title
Suicide squad killed the justice league. We've all been waiting anxiously for them to give us a first look at
It crashed it flipped on your crash they crashed
Kaylee
What the hell you think you're doing?
That footage is strictly classified
My name is director amanda waller
Are you my cringe and since the game awards doesn't care about
Disclosing classified intel listen up. I was being somebody in the audience about task force f
That wasn't me. There's somebody in the audience
Justice league or superman
Rampaging through the streets of metropolis you better not say a word ever to anyone because if you do believe you me
I'll hear that you've all been brawler out. I was like we don't know who that was
Does anyone know who that is? She's gone. Good. All right
Well, I think we've waited long enough to see rocksteady's new game. This is gonna be worth the risk
You guys want to do it?
Let's all watch this together
Think of the justice league I think of wonder woman
superman
Green lantern, you don't want to mess with that one, but you
Barry
You're just the team mascot. Aren't you mate the loser of the league folks?
The fastest man alive. It's
Splash is alive and he's playing for team brainiac
I gave you orders kill the flash. I'll kill you myself
I just hope the joker's in
Why don't you just mail me the bullet i'm the eye in the sky taking point
Is it like multiplayer or you pick a character I don't know
Co-op it's a gun type game. Oh, who are you going to main?
Uh, mr. Furious, uh, either that or the spleen i'm not sure it looks like it could be kind of fun
Is that just from fear? Oh shit
I'm probably not gonna play it. You may have met the character I portray in forespoken
Frey holland
I am so excited to be here to announce a brand new trailer and especially delighted tonight as we will be seeing
Pollyanna's first portrayal of tanta prav for the very first time
She is a ruthless adversary for fray and I hope players get into it looking for a boss fight with this woman at some point
I definitely hope that you're in a boss fight
Thank you. Ella. That's so kind even if it is with fray, especially if it if it's with fray
And now a world premiere trailer for forespoken
I
Stop pretending to be interested. You're not going to play any of these games
You'll be too busy playing like fart simulator
The truth really hurts it does it hurts i'll play elden ring, you know, I will
Hey, dude, you're gonna play destiny pvp tomorrow start banning people that say that for like an hour at least
Oh
You guys are so fucking funny. Seriously
Like this is what I could I like i'm gonna have so much trouble stopping streaming eventually
I you guys are just so funny like
sometimes
Okay, it's some of the shit you guys say so
Oh, I love it
What is this?
Is it if it's a warhammer? I have a very personal
personal
Rudge against warhammer 40k
That's what it is
When dawn of war 2 came out
I was so excited because I thought they were gonna eventually put in the tau because the tau is what I played in the original
dawn of war games, right
They just don't give a shit about the tau
I love that. It's they're awesome
the battle suits the
I'm a tau player. Yeah
And they kept putting in this shit that we've already seen a thousand times like dawn of war 3. Let's do in this one
No tau tau. No, no, no, no, no never again
Tau is in the game. Yeah, they added tau to the game when the shit had like eight concurrent players on steam
It took too long
I love dawn of war. It's like one of my favorite rts franchises
But i'm very curious what this is space marine 2
That's that. All right. That's cool
Put the tau in that game put the tau in this game
Joining me now is tim willis from saber and the star of the game who will play captain titus clive stand and
Tim, what do we just see? Well, i'm just so excited. I can finally talk about this game
You know
We are making space marine 2 a sequel to the iconic, you know warhammer 40k game, you know and at saber
You know, we've uh, we're using the experience that we have we have learned from games like halo quake champions
World war z to really bring this game to life to make it the most intense action game ever
And we've got clive as a space marine. It's awesome
Clive, how does it feel to be in the game? This would be fun. It's a dream
A pretty bleak and grim dream, but anyone's ever seen any of the work i've done. I'm not scared of the darkness
No, it's it's i'm stoked and grateful to be a part of this
I used to play with and paint the space marines when I was a kid with my older brother
So the chance to play one of the most iconic characters in the warhammer 40k universe is is everything to me
So it fits you looks looks good
So we're excited to see more of the game and awesome for you guys to show the gameplay tim clive
Thank you so much for joining us and right now. Here's a brand new look at saints row
Oh
Holy smokes quiet
You have power
You can still kick people in the balls, don't worry everybody shoot guns
What the fuck
Saints row the return of the mcgribbler. I I mean that didn't show time before christmas
Is this fall guys?
Is this still is this still a thing one of the reasons why I stopped playing fall guys is because they were
Like seven games in the whole game. There were like seven maps
Is that have they updated it?
Like all those brand deals
Look at all these licensing deals
What the fuck there's still plenty of show left and why would you want to watch alone?
You could watch with me and ariel powers
Tune into our watch party to see a lot of exclusive interviews and industrial spank takes trust me
You do not want to miss it, but don't take our word for it come to twitch.tv
Powered by verizon 5g come check it out. See you soon
But aren't we like all kind of co-streaming this?
How many people are streaming this right now?
Like this this exact event
It's like thousands this two thousand of us
You and only a few people
Oh, how many people are streaming the game awards? Oh, there's just you and the official game awards channel
They're actually kind of pissed that you're restreaming this
Because nobody gave you permission to do this. It's literally an exclusive event. You fucking asshole turn it off
Hey guys phase rug here and i'm asking you to help me destroy one billion mechs for able gamers charity in the hit new game
Mech arena join me and millions of players in five-on-five mech action for a chance to win insane
Mech action raise money for a good cause and get a shot at driving this real mech
Are you ready to battle i'll see you in the arena
Wait
What the hell?
What's one award is one award enough?
Well, the gold medal was was was i can't say resident evil was resident evil 8 nominated
It's one title enough for game of the year
What about one sponsor?
No way with every win. I don't think it's gonna win but
You know enough is never enough
Welcome back to present our next award. All right awards
You just saw in that wd black piece and tonight you can get 10 off selected wd black products
To celebrate the game awards, please welcome seven-time nba all-star and owner of endemic paul george
Good evening, everyone
Uh, what I love action adventure games for their versatility
All right action adventure. Let's go on a puzzle the next you're lining up headshots
And then suddenly you're being put on a hook by a vampire lady taller than me
This category is like a showcase of what it means to be a video game
Here are the nominees for best action adventure game
Best action adventure games
Is this gonna will this win
metroid dread
You better show the crisp banana gift if it wins game of the year
I it's guaranteed to not win game of the year, by the way. Remember your head is 30% here
For best action adventure game goes to so is all of your heads. It's like what are you talking about?
Oh metroid
People will be happy about that
People believe that people are gonna be very excited
That means I have to play it now for the teams at nintendo and mercury steam who worked on metroid dread
Thank you so much for this award and congratulations to all areas bowser
This is the action adventure category and metroid dread checks off both the action and the adventure box
It's filled with action-packed moments behind every door around every corner and I have to play
A metroid game it introduces us to a massive and mysterious new planet that players can explore and adventure through
It's the result of a true collaboration between nintendo
And mercury steam and I have a few comments that the developers asked me to read on their behalf
We'd like to say a big thank you for this award from the development teams at nintendo and mercury steam
That worked so hard to bring all the metroid fans around the world the experience that they were hoping somebody said
It's like a dmt trip looking at the background in this dangerous yet marvelous journey
To zdr we're so thankful for all the fans for enjoying metroid dread on nintendo switch. Thank you very much
I don't know what a dmt trip is like. I have no idea biggest death trap in all history
And then into its jewels start with dread
Maybe I will and see power
Here we must scrabble for desert power move slowly the day of your revenge will come
This is your inheritance speed is a device of shaitan thus there will always be a desert on iraqis
Dude look at that hand
I'm not bored. I promise
My vengeance this is my doom
dude spice wars
How does that work? You need another edible?
I I did not do anything of the stars of the upcoming tiny tina's wonderlands ashley birch and will arnett
What's this gonna be?
Oh, that's the rheses guy
That's the rheses guy
Yeah, there's no wrong way to eat a rheses. Thank you. Ah, don't listen to them eat it wherever you want
The story in tiny tina's wonderlands. Yeah, and are we talking about the dragon lord yet?
Yes, will plays the dragon lord the essential villain within the wonderlands
Yes
But in a clever twist I turn out to be the underdog hero of the entire realm
And it's really beautiful and it's actually one of the main reasons that I took this role. So
So is this like a borderlands game?
What do you mean no
You play a necromantic overlord and not the good kind
Well, he's a job creator for millions of unemployed individuals. He races the dead man
Yeah, and he gives them stuff to do
Okay
Some of them get to sail
Some for all right, let me be in the audience
A lot of them like I don't know stab things or something
Do you really not know the story of the game that you're sure?
No, you know, you mean the the whimsical adventure from the mind of a 13 year old demolitions
expert yeah who whimsically
Tries to blow up the heroes for 40 levels. Yeah, so if anyone is the central villain here, it's tiny tina
All right, roll the damn trailer
How'd they go
There is a two clap andy the border and that's usually me
a world forged by wonder
And ruled i'm usually the two clap andy that laughs and does that one alone who can with fate
One alone whose story is in their own hands
the
Big maker
That's you heavy, right?
You seek passage
I can aid you
I am this feels like a school assembly adventurer the scary stabby one is fred
The undead fall beneath our senses some real evil vibes this way. I think it's fine
What's wrong with it a beautiful body indeed?
and full
of
power
invincible
Looking bad. How do we win this?
we attack
together
For that so cute idiot. Do you want to fight? I'll give you a fight big boy
Sisters, I believe we have found our champion
Oh, listen to me lip flapping while you could be off adventuring
See you love the cheese curl. I wonder how many guns will be in the game
Please go back to monster rancher
Yeah, and when this is over hold on what game are we playing here i'll see him out here
Put this in the background and play monster rancher guys
When I changed to monster rancher
11 000 of you are gonna leave
I gotta see this through
Last year one indie game won multiple game awards and now they're back in a totally new
Unexpected way. I'm just gonna keep the cam on I keep coming at the wrong time. I'll shrink it
I'll play this one. I
I'll play this one
Pretty fun. All right. Tonight. We have a very special k-pop performance
The south korean developer pearl abyss wanted to thank you for the great response to their recent trailer for their upcoming open world action adventure game
And then i'll smash my vr headset with a hammer music video working with the popular k-pop dance team one million dance studio. Enjoy
Wait, we're gonna dance
All right. All right, let's go
You need to get up don't make me get up don't make me get up
Oh
It's the metaverse I got I got a weird pair of pants on I don't want to see
Why am I standing up? I didn't say I was gonna dance. Why'd you print? Why'd you tell me to stand up?
stand up
I can't go that far
Can't i'm so old. I can't I feel like weird
I can't get up
It's the old fucking 36 year old shake
1200 dollars for a front row seat
Do the orangutan we are wrapping up 2021 with spotify and here for the first time are the top three
Male and female artists as listened to by you on gaming consoles in 2021 top female artists
Doja cat billy eilish and ariana grande top male juice world xxx tenacion and polo g
Later, we will reveal the most listened to spotify songs
This spotify rap thing tonight for best mobile game
Here's a look at two new characters coming december 14th to genshin impact and the first glimpse of the upcoming character
What uh, what's the uh?
What came out this year on ipad
That I actually liked
Why is this guy even streaming this
I'm sorry
If you're new to the stream right now, i'm
I'm i'm apologizing to you directly
Do something funny this sucks
I'm on a goddamn clown
I just say I am to my cpa
Oh, this song's pretty good. Oh, I think this song deserves like 36 year old man shake
And what we have here is the the top five cringiest streamers of the year there was only one nominee
German nine eight five
It's me like going like
Like all the clips are gonna just be all over the place if you like this
This would be the whole wait does people care about this? This is what you would see the king has gone insane
He is a proponent of a theory called animal
Okay, did it work? He's capable of anything this automaton muster
It could do much more than dons like angel of death
Descend it from the heavens and your nominees
For cringiest streamer of the year are
German nine eight five
No, it's not working. Fuck it's not working. It's supposed to be cuts. Why is it not doing it now?
Oh, just link them that clip. Okay, that's approves it
I'm stoked to announce that i'm in metal hell singer a rhythm-based shooter game. Make sure you check it out
We also have incredible metal screamers singers like myself like alissa from arch enemy rated from lamb of god
Check it out my friends. I will see you all in
Okay, those either watch the stream for a long time
You know that when like the webcam I turn it on if I have a sync a desync set up
It will like cut to what's going on. It takes like the last frame. Why is it not doing that?
It's not doing it anymore
That would have been funny. That was a minus two that would have been a plus two thousand. Oh, well can't get them all
obs patched it oh
Somebody said I don't even know why i'm here
Yeah
I have that effect on people
And a cringey a streamer of the year
I sort of like monster engine
Hey, you guys you guys remember this one that I did earlier
I was gonna do that for every single category, but everybody hated it after the second time
So I was like i'm not doing that again. That did not land the first two times. I did it
So I was just like, okay, I didn't I didn't even see any minus twos people didn't even react to it
They were just like that was fucking stupid. I don't i'm not even i'm not even give that a reaction
There's two more what are they are you kidding me?
That one's bad
A new way to play your favorite mobile games on your pc
That was me just fucking around games from your pocket to your desktop and seamlessly pick up where you left off
Google play game that was me fucking around before the stream in 2022. That's okay
You know that is brand new game announcement for the first time. All you guys say you don't like laugh tracks
Then please explain to me why this is on like 60 percent of all short form tiktok videos
It's the new laugh track go somewhere there's always somebody in the background of like all these tiktoks going like
It's the new laugh track you you like laugh tracks apparently we need to learn everything we can
I'm not gonna die not if I have anything to say about it. I gotta get off the camera
Can't be right time to impact one minute
I need you to do the right thing
All right
Okay, it's ready to be to make a tiktok
Here we go fates of the negotiations the interests of the federation and the prospect for peace
May very well depend on it
I i'm not just gonna interrupt
He's back again make some noise for reggie
Uh, no, no, no, no
I'm no joking around
It's not gonna happen. Thank you
Uh, I would not do that in front of reggie jeff said it earlier
Isn't it great to be back live and in person back amongst friends? It's fantastic
This is a wonderful time of the year
the game awards
Our opportunity to celebrate the creators and the players
What is this jeff eighth year something like that?
That's actually pretty cool
So much, you know, we've witnessed so much over these past few years the launch of next generation eight and nine consoles
the mobile revolution
streaming games
vr
ar
And quality free-to-play games
And this category represents another innovation in our industry
This is the award for best ongoing game
It used to be that a game would ship and that would be the game
But today's developers keep players coming back to their beloved titles again and again
By delivering and creating exciting new content
Here are the five nominees for engaging their audiences. I would love year after year
I just want to listen to audio books with him talking best ongoing game. I would every book I would have reggie's voice
I played genshin impact for an hour on my ipad
That game award for the best ongoing game goes to
final fantasy
Yes, I did
People I really like this game if I still played any games I would probably play it
Not fortnight. No, not this time. The category had so many amazing nominees that it's truly
fortunate that we were able to win
Um, there's an incredible team behind final fantasy 14 who pour their hearts into the work
Bringing new and memorable stories and adventures to our fans
From around we're born all the way to endwalker and and beyond so a big thank you to final fantasy 14 team and
I can't wait to see what's going on in the future
And honestly the biggest thanks to our community
They've been our rock and we're so happy that you continue to give us our support. Thank you so much. That's good. Cool
It seems like it deserved it
We got another permit. There's been so many of these
Since the dawn of time we helped the glory of competition
Wasn't always what you'd call friendly
As civilization evolved so did the desire for battle and the drive to be the best
Cities grew and soon everyone wanted a piece of the action
Some for power
Oh, come on
It's like a melee game
Don't mock me. I didn't win. That's fine though. I don't have to win. I don't have to win a content creator here
What the hell is going on?
I mean a lot of people just jump off of buildings in the super mario pose
rumble verse
That was rumble verse coming next year from iron galaxy and epic games and tomorrow
There's a first look gameplay event head to rumble verse.com to sign up
Debut of a sequel to a game awards nominee from a few years ago a plague tale requiem
Under the wide and starry sky
This was requested a bunch of times, but I didn't feel like I was gonna be into it dig the grave
And the with the rats, right?
Hugo i'm right behind you
Glad did I live?
Gladly die laid me down
impossible
This be the verse you crave for me
Come on, you've seen worse than this here. He lies
Where he longed to be is the sailor
home from sea
and the hunter home
from the hill
I feel my mind going I know
Think of your brother we have to carry on i'm serious. I really
I can just just put bloodborne at 60 frames a second and add like a couple of costumes and i'll buy it at 60
But i'll buy it again
Are they ever gonna do that?
I wouldn't even care like it was like oh and we added two dlc costumes like who gives a shit is the game in 60?
FPS 1080 we partnered with grubhub to do something really cool to get your food delivered for the game awards order grubhub using
The code endwalker during the show to get free delivery on all orders of 15 dollars or more and an exclusive final fantasy
14 eat pizza emote for the game and I get some dinner
Celebrated its 30th anniversary and next year dying light to arrives after a long wait
We've got a new look right now at the game's story with this cg trailer
Hold on. I'm the ego narcissist maniac. I just may have to make sure that i'm on camera at least once or a few minutes
It's around my neck what
I was going like this
I was holding my
I've i've i've been strangled i've been strangling myself
during this broadcast
That's for me going like this just sitting here like this
Why have I been choking myself to the stream?
Look at if you guys go back
To some of the webcam stuff from like half an hour ago. My hands are up there
This game comes out in less than two months
I'll be playing this for sure
Oh my
Goodness
What have what have I what am I doing?
It's more it's like something down here. Uh, i'm i'm getting like attacked by like a specter
What like ghost is here like fucking trying to kill me with his bare hands?
There's like marks down here
Keep the horror peep the horror. Yeah
What's going on here?
Stop blaming the ghost
Crossfire the triple a game made a triple a studio made a game about you. What would it be?
Be a horror puzzle
Uh action adventure massive multiplayer game
And you have to yeah, and you have to play with your feet welcome
Is this a foot controller three where there are brand new places to explore and exciting new ways like a ddr pad
It won't work with any other controller by earning battle pass xp beyond battle royale
It's all about playing your way to level up past outfits
Including spider-man
There's also new features to check out get around more quickly and invade enemy fire with new sliding
and swinging
And even set up camps where you and your squad can heal and store items from match to match
I'm watching without sound you look like a virgin weapons and items to help win a victory royale and earn the ultimate prestige
the victory crown
Keep winning and keep the crown. Oh, yeah along with these features
Is all new
Explore sanctuary hidden home of the seven in spider-man's home turf the daily bugle along with many more locations
And with the island's new weather conditions
Anything can happen
In addition to all new gameplay check out the chapter three season one battle pass. Oh, you still think that man the foundation
I don't need your honor. You turn your sound down. That's fine
So what are you waiting for dropping a chapter three and start exploring the new island because you'll never know what you might find
or night
create your vampire
blood
I just paused it
Exactly what i'm doing right now. I just I became aware of what was going on. I'm like
Grabbing and like rubbing like this
Um
Jeremy, excuse me. I have to tie my hands to the chair
Like seriously like both my hands to the chair. Why am I what am I doing?
I'm just like rubbing
And this uh, that actually might be pretty fun
It's been a great year so far for shark mob on their first game blood hunt
They just completed any successful early access and i'm very excited for that too small
I need a big thing blood hunt will be out on ps5 and pc in spring 2022 and we'll be free to play
I don't want to fidget cube. I want to fidget wall
Willy wonka shit
So I can get up and like
You know those the one man band guys meme
Where it's like
I need one of those featuring the composers and songwriters behind all of supergiants cube is too small darren corb and ashley barrett
I don't dmc. Yeah, I think i'm fine
You can't skip on the live stream
Am I allowed to do this I hope so i'm not i've turned it off what are you talking about
Nice fucking forehead i'm looking at like the cream cheese here that I have going here
The stories that I know my back was to the world that was smiling when I turned
I gotta get off. Yeah, I feel like i'm like dad at the concert with your kids
Like my kids are having a great time, but i'm just here and like watching them chaperoning
I'm not saying anything about the music. I'm just saying like my reaction there was like why am I not reacting?
Arcane is good. Yeah, I know
Why am I not singing
We have this many people that hate this band
I don't listen to music, so I don't know
No, I I really don't listen to music
Not that much
If you don't listen to music and you don't play games and what the fuck do you do?
cartography
My spare time wood burning
You work at the cheesecake factory why do you have to answer I have to answer that question
Why are we the cheesecake factory to make the game awards live stream more accessible including an audio descriptive stream
Asl stream with deaf gamers tv on twitch and closed captions. It's important
And now to present the innovation and accessibility award
Please welcome jack septiceye and a member of our future class for 2020 and one of the judges i'm sweating
Yeah select the nominees for accessibility the incredible morgan banker
Jack septiceye appearance. I love jack
To be here tonight
Games are for everyone and this award recognizes the teams that are advancing gameplay features and technology
To make sure games can be accessed and played by all
It's incredible to see the effort developers put into prioritizing people who often go ignored
Sharing their work with as many people as possible
And that's why we love being able to show our gratitude to those who go above and beyond each year
Discovering new and creative methods to encourage that outfit inclusion here are the nominees
Innovation in accessibility presented by chevrolet
Update that will be coming shortly after launch players will be able to enable a sign language interpreter
I just I so badly want to kind of take the edges and go like what not hard but just like enough
500 miles down a treacherous valley in the wake of an invading world
I'm talking about like this like he grabs like the sides and just goes like
I really like that
This award means means so much to our team because
Everyone at playground games is really committed to accessibility so much so that we made it one of our core pillars
for forza horizon
around the world there are about a billion players who have some sort of
Makes I think my brain is too smart for them
And I think it's great that us as developers and as creators can add in accessibility features and options and just open the magic
games to more and more players
It's cars. I a few people
Um, I'd like to thank alan hartman. Why do I think that force is so complicated?
It's driving a car and all of team xbox
When everyone plays we all win
It's three buttons such an important award congratulations guys, all right
Well, joining me now is simon viclan from 10 chambers simon back in 2017
We announced your studio and your first game a gtfo right here at the game awards and we're thrilled to have you back
I understand isn't forcing like a special announcement for everyone
Yes, it was a great opportunity to show off the game and
Was it four years ago? Yeah
Why is he so red because that was a really really stupid thing to say something's about to happen tonight. Yes. Yes indeed
the thing is
We it helped us reach, you know the audience for our
Extreme co-op horror game. Yes, and we thought what better way to announce 1.0
We've been in early access now for two years. What better way to announce 1.0 than to come back
No, i'm not on dope right now surprise announcement is that
Gtfo is out now this very minute. We release it right now. Someone press the button
I am way too red someone's pressing a button right now
And it's out now and there's no better time to get into gtfo
Yeah
Than right now with uh, 25 off and uh, you know the we worked hard to make the game more accessible. Sorry
It's more accessible
And uh anymore lip balm. That's not a bad idea. Let's let's take a look. We've got to take a look at the trailer
Yeah, all right 1.0 gtfo. Thanks so much. Simon. Check it out. How long is this broadcast? It's been three hours already. Holy smokes
Co-op horror shooter this game rocks resource scavenged. I give you one more chance
There's only one
Bring it what it wants or die
It's really good. Hmm really dark, please peep this peep it, please
Monsters wait, why are we here?
Terrible things that we do
To deserve such hell
I just thought of the person that sits at the ball should be a critical hit
We don't have to work together
Or we don't die together
Wow, that looks fun. It actually looks pretty good. I am
Intrigued for sure. So is it that new content or is that just the game is a game that exists?
I go by mike the quad and I stream on twitch
It's really hard military in
When we came back, I was involved in a motorcycle accident trying to figure out how to use a controller without
Having any hand function. What's up everybody that kind of sparked my advocacy
I wholeheartedly believe it kickstarts a patient's rehabilitation
Somebody said are you a new streamer?
I just started
um probably like
2015 i'm fairly new
i'm pretty new
I i'll live for thousands of years. So
It's it's pretty new to me and the kind of my lifespan raid shadow legends. I mean
You pick your champions they're glorious and their shields. Oh they glisten like
Wet otters, but the bad guys they're lovecraftian. They're spooky. They're um, i'm big and then you go to battle and it's like
And finally your foe is vanquished and that satisfaction such a primal feeling
Raid shadow legend free bonus. They they got jeff goldblum
What?
They even got jeff goldblum
I will don't be surprised if joe biden does a raid shadow legends ad like at his next conference
Holy shit, they're everywhere
Oh my goodness
Yes, yeah, we have this new deal
with raid
shadow legends
And it's man. Let me tell you they're paying back half the national debt
for uh me to come up here and
Talk to you about it
whore viz
The raid shadow legends is gonna be on the side of like the of elon musk's fucking space mars rocket
In huge letters, we protect humanity
Whatever the cost in fact the aliens that find us eventually are going to think that the raid shadow legends lore was our actual history
as a species
That will be their history
of us
Yeah, there won't be a bible anymore. It'll be the book of raid shadow legends
And all the characters that are in the game and shit
Aren't aren't there like content creators in raid shadow legends or something?
Stop promoting the game for free guys
Me saying the word raid shadow legends. It's like me promoting water to you. It's like hey, there's water exists on earth
It's already it's everywhere. I can't do it anymore television showtime and 343 industries bring the legendary master chief to life
In the live action halo original series streaming exclusively on paramount plus here is the world premiere
First look trailer what plus paramount plus
What do you mean paramount plus?
You're special. There's another one
In fact, i'm counting on it. We're lost in the dark
but you
Give people hope and I will always be with you
This is our heart. I see this
As a new beginning
Please welcome the chief creative officer from epic games donald mustard
All right
That was crazy. That was amazing
So making games that are original innovative and really push the medium forward
Is not easy at all. It's the culmination of the work and talent of hundreds and hundreds of people and countless hours
And it only happens when there's a clear shared vision
Of what a game can be
These nominees for best game direction represent what's possible when it all comes together
Oh, I want to be on cam for this month best game direction best game direction
You have no idea what's out there. Sure
It would be that right it takes two come on
I have new marks on my face
You lose why am I like a mood ring?
Why am I a fucking mood ring?
All right, i'm like i've just touched my what's going on goes to
death loop all right
It's dehydrated
Dude, I drank this big ass water over the last hour or two. It's like 40 ounces. It's huge
I am not dehydrated
um, yeah, so death loop is my first game as a
game director
and it's also the first game that
sebastian and I are co-creative director for
and
Actually, I don't mean that as a brag
It was terrifying
Terrifying for us terrifying for the team. It looks like you made it a plastic. So
Yeah, I really want to thank the arcane leon team
Um
For you know taking the leap of faith of giving their best work
uh
to uh
you know, um
To make this strange game that no one can sum up in 30 seconds
um
I should play this it was really good
Yeah, and also thank you for to playstation you believed in our vision
uh, thank you to our fans and uh
Actually, I have a lot of people to thank but not a lot of time. Can we make those 30 seconds loop?
a couple of times
That was a good one. That was good. I stopped here but just uh
Uh, that was going to me a small last word for uh, my family in french. So lilia aya
Thank you very much
Now it's time to take a look at some other award winners tonight in the category of best esports game presented by grubhub
Here are the nominees
and the game award goes to
league of legends congratulations
for family lay on my
Webcam it's because my exposure is too high because I have no lights in my room. It takes two
Companies for best fighting game are you aware?
nickelodeon all-star brawl
Guilty gear imagine that one
Next best sim strategy you're the nominees and the game award. I was supposed to play that I forgot it existed age of empires four
nominees for best vr ar game
and the game award goes to
Resident evil 4 does anybody else feel like they are blowing through these your most anticipated game presented by prime gaming
Here again, we'll react to this and the game award goes to
Elden ring for the second year in a row
This is going so fast is a little shy if anyone in the audience has any twin blades or wing spears
Talking to you reggie. I'm gonna ask that you please put those away for now. Let's let's bring them out
Here's a little shy but look everybody. It's it's my pot friend
Come on out pot friend
Great to see you. You should put a bow tie on or something. Come on out pot friend. Don't be shy
uh
Looks like he's got a a note or something. I'm sorry guys
I don't want to see any gameplay or any story. So i'm gonna have to turn around for this one. See
See what this note says. Thanks pot friend
Good evening
Please enjoy my gift a new trailer for elden ring
I don't want to be spoiled another world premiere trailer. Thanks, buddy. Let's check it out
It happened an age ago, but when I recall I see it true on a night of wintry fog
The rune of death was stolen
And the demigods began to fall
Starting with godwin the golden
Queen marika was driven to the brink
The shattering ensued a war that wrought only darkness
The elden ring was broken
But by whom?
And why?
What could the demigods ever hope to win by force?
The conqueror of the stars general
And the blade of mickle and milania the seven these two were the mightiest to remain and locked horns in combat
But there would be no victor
And so we inhabit a fractured world
Awaiting the arrival of the elder
Unless of course
Thou shouldst take the crown
I didn't see anything was it good good just confirming the date the same february
Excellent good to see amazing. I can't wait to step deeper into the world of elden ring
Uh when it does come out in february tonight
We've teamed up with spotify to reveal what you're listening to every day on gaming consoles as part of spotify's wrapped
Rage shadow spotify two songs in 2021 on gaming surfaces here are the top three rap star by polo g
Montero by little nas x and mood by 24k golden featuring ian dior
Congratulations, make sure to make your spotify rap tonight stick around because coming up kiano reeves and carrie and moss reveal the matrix awakens
We debut a brand new next generation game and the game awards orchestra pays tribute to our game of the year nominees
This is gonna be like a five-hour broadcast
Holy smokes
So are we actually at real commercials now? Should I just leave like go full screen break off old timer?
You don't think I know ever break a rule to rule two. Oh, you're one of them. I've got all break off
You know you want to
Well respect this rocket league, but seriously break off
I fell into games and I lived and breathed. Yeah, well, we might play monster rancher. I just never knew that it could be a job
Really depends how long this is
What hold on?
it's
So that means
When did I start streaming 230 raised in malaysia? I came to the uk at age 19
If you're a minority working in video games, when did I start going through life five hours an imposter?
I think that's what made me wish I had somebody to talk to so I decided to create my own mentorship program
Maybe i'll play for like an hour
I don't know. Maybe i'll just come back on what's what's today?
thursday
Last weekend, maybe people just really want to be connected and be a part of a community saturday or sunday
I feel like anybody who wants to make video games. I mean this shit. I got a lot of viewers
So, I mean I might as well bring you over to our what's up everyone. I'm sydney goodman awesome game
Everyone is gonna love
I'll play it. I'm gonna play for an hour or two. I really want to play it
I feel like I want to play this
Wait, I was wondering I was like a sheet. Why is like blood coming out of her? I was like, what the fuck am I watching?
It was dumping stuff on her
I'm not going to switch to i'm not going to play it. I'm just going to open it to get ready
I promise i'm not going to play it. I just want to open it
I'm not playing it. I just make sure it's in the background. I'm not going to put it in the corner either. It's getting ready
Do we play split screen? No, I can't do that. Uh, we have literally 10 minutes
I have to go pee anyways, i'm holding it
Go pee now. Actually, this is a good this is a good time to go pee because the game was just in the background
Is it ads right? All right, i'll be right back
maybe
Hey everyone, my name is out of football my go-to is probably gonna be it takes two. Hi everybody
My pick is psychonauts, too
You're gonna have to give it to ratchet and claim ripped apart a pure joyride of fun from start to finish and that's hard to beat
That was a look at which game of the year nominees youtube creators and fans want to see win later tonight
We'll find out if they are right when we present game of the year
Every year at the game awards
We try to find games that push the medium forward in new and unexpected ways
This game comes from embark studios in sweden a new team of veteran developers
Their first game brings together thrilling multiplayer pve action a next-generation physical sandbox and incredible visuals to create a truly dynamic
Player experience. Here's the reveal complete with real gameplay
I'm back. I'm back. I'm back. I'm here. I'm here here. What'd I miss?
There is no way to hide kings
barons
queens
We give them different names, but they're all the same
killing machines falling from the sky
Okay
this
Is our home
our bastion of resistance
This is where the brave meets the bold. I was in the bathroom. Somebody said why does this person not talk die in the shadows?
We will face our fears
head on
Showtime
I can't resize it unless I can see it. That's just part of the trailer
Fuck what is this? What is this game?
Hey, this kind of looks like a edf with robots
They will never stop coming
Whoa?
All right, somebody write this down
It's called
ARC raiders
That was incredible and now we have two special guests joining us for a very special moment
karyann kiano
Welcome. I'm sure you guys recognize the iconic scene moment, right?
Jeff, thank you. It's good to be here at the game awards
And yes, this is one of the scenes that made the matrix feel so groundbreaking perhaps inspired a few video games, too
True that's true
Impressive. Thanks. Can you still do that? Absolutely not but I can in the unreal engine fog
I believe everyone here is expecting to see something new. So here's a never-before-seen look at the matrix resurrection
Exclusively for the game awards 2021
Let's roll the clip him and jim carrey. You have the same energy tonight
Where are we? Tokyo?
The moving portal makes I love both of these guys by the way portals clean reading our shadows
I don't remember this
We don't have to run to phone booths anymore either
Doors on your right set and setting right? Oh, no, it's all about set
And setting after our first contact went so badly. We thought elements from your past
Might help ease you into the present. Nothing comforts anxiety like
little nostalgia
The matrix resurrections looks awesome and we can't wait to watch it on december 22nd
But getting back to tonight's kind of feel like they got dmca'd midstream kiano. You've been in
Not you're not watching this movie immersive experiences
Uh, did you ever think that one day a game could look as real as being in the matrix?
Absolutely
I mean we are reaching the point of which the line between the physical and virtual worlds
are blurry
And with interactive storytelling reaching stunning levels of fidelity the same exact energy don't even tell me they don't ask
What is a game? What is a movie over 20 years ago? The matrix pushed the boundaries of filmmaking and visual effects
We couldn't have imagined where the state of the art would be today was photorealistic digital humans
In virtual sense in fact if you didn't tell me
Jim carrey could be dressed up as kiano reeves and kiano reeves could have been like dressed up in makeup as jim carrey
Just wouldn't didn't tell anybody
I'm thomas anderson like many of you. I work with computers
But computers are also mirrors reflecting back who and what we are and the choices we make
The worlds we build
You feel got it like riding a bike. Are you serious?
Oh, it's is it not a game. It's just like it's it's just the the spider-man homecoming vr thing
Is it a game? It's playable everything you just saw is running in real time and on real engine 5 on playstation 5
And xbox series x and s it is pretty mind-blowing and now you can download and experience the matrix awakens for yourself for free
Right. Oh, it's really good though entirety. It's available right now. Make sure to play it. It is
Mind-blowing epic is just taking things to another level play it tonight, please as we look to the future
It's now time to celebrate the best games of this year to present game of the year
Please welcome last year's winner of game of the year and best game direction from naughty dog
Neil druckman
Thanks, jeff
Man, it feels awesome to be back here together in person. Congratulations to everyone who managed to release a game this year
Perseverance dedication tonight and passion are inspiring and there's no shortage of that in this room
Now performing music from each of tonight's game of the year nominees once again the game awards orchestra
All right, we're the nominees
ratchet and clank rift apart
Takes two
Uh, I don't have to give 100 community subs
Oh
I don't have to give 100 community subs. All right
Does it count if I played it or does it count if I purchased it or does it kind of I got like a like a
Like I caught on my hand from the box that it came in like I haven't even I haven't even played it
I did play three games. It was resident evil 8
There was two more hitman
And far cry 6 i'm good
Here it is
Far cry 6 resident evil village and you said the other one fuck whatever it was. Why are you aware? Ah
Genshin impact I played like four games
Well, no more heroes didn't get nominated for anything. You said nominated. Yeah far cry 6 got nominated
Genshin impact got now I played genshin impact. Oh, yeah, or at least a few hours
Not on stream
Sorry guys
One hour so what I played it the game kind of actually kind of looks fun
Stay extremely mad. Yeah
You think everything looks fun get an actual opinion
I think I said like three things on the stream looked fun
I said something looked cute. Something looks interesting. So we're being shown like five dozen trailers for new games
Well, i'm gonna of course i'm gonna be like, ah, it looks all right. That's cool
It looks cute
This is so many games
A fitting way to honor the very best of the year
Let's hear it one more time for the game awards orchestra. Oh, I thought they're gonna do it one more time
Encore do it again
I've talked a lot of shit, too
I have and finally congratulations to all of tonight's nominees all pretty incredible games
And the 2021 game of the year is if deathloop doesn't win i'm gonna streak on stream. It takes two
That's actually awesome
That's actually awesome. I'm so happy. I can't I can't what the he already has to say
That's a big plot twist. It is that's a huge deal. That's deja
17, uh
Same fuck the oscar and then now
Actually in a way of the office got fucked because the game awards it's getting way better. So
It's gonna be extremely fast. So I want to thank my uh,
Let me see my my my beautiful team for a fantastic. Yeah, he's awesome. I can't do anything. I deserve it
I want to say also I want to
Give this word to my daughter meo and my soon-to-come daughter zoe
It's so nice to have children. I'm surprised how much you love them
If you don't have children go get them. I mean this is the best thing that can happen
Thank you again. I'm really proud. I'm shaking. Look at me, man
This is like a big big moment for me and neil your big inspiration. Thank you. You know what?
Just like he said what he wanted to say
I was like, uh, this is great. This is huge
That's great, that's good post your thoughts with that's really cool. Let us know who got shorted tonight
Thank you again for watching the game. I want to see what that guy that guy's got like 500 iq genius level shit going on up here
Thank you so much. Have a great holiday season. Good night everybody
Yeah, no good for him. Seriously good for that studio