Let me just put my new copy down. I might sound different too, I might have to change some settings because I had to clean every nozzle, every knob, every single one needed to be cleaned.
Hold on. Let me see, how's that? Is that bad? Good? Worse? Better? Hold on. I mean, we're muted now, but how about now? Can you hear me? How do I sound? Sound okay? Okay.
Well, let me go over why we're starting like an hour and 20 minutes late. Because I dumped an entire 16 ounces of coffee on my desk and all like into my computer and shit.
My computer is underneath my desk to the left. I have a big L shaped desk. It's a beautiful desk. The thing is absolutely wonderful. It's walnut wood.
And I fucking did the thing I promised myself I would never do. And that's dump. And I didn't even take one sip out of it either. I came up here to get ready to stream like, okay, I'm ready to start hit the button to start streaming. Here we go. Like it's time. And I dumped the whole fucking thing.
I tried to put it down on the coaster and it just like, and I it's because my hands were a little wet. And those of you guys that don't let me tell you something about glass. Okay.
Don't fucking use glass. Don't drink out of glass. It's not worth it. If you get even if you could even like one drop of water on your hands, when you grab onto glass, it's it makes the glass 1000 times more slippery.
I don't know why we put liquid in these things. Glasses superpower is getting really hard to hold on to when it's wet.
You ceramic or metal drink out of 10. I'm getting a 10 cup. It's gonna be I'm gonna get a sippy cup. Everyone thinks that that's a joke. No, no, I'm going to get a I'm gonna buy on Amazon. I'm gonna go buy like a child six pack of sippy cups and just have them ready every anytime.
Because this was fucking horrible. I I didn't even react right away because I was gonna cry. I just like dumped it. It was like this. This is a brand new desk and like a new place and not even fucking two months and I dump a fucking full 16 ounces of coffee over
my computer on the bike, my my XLR input, my stream deck, my monitor, my fucking controller, my phone, my computer. It was awful. It was horrible. And I almost cried. But we can hold on to those tears now because we're going to do something today. Stop drinking coffee. How do you stop doing something? Yeah, I can't just stop drinking coffee coffees like my whole life.
Two servings of coffee. It was supposed to last. It was supposed to last me like an hour and a half. Hey, just don't do that. No. All right. I just had to vent. I had to vent to you guys. So let's get started. Today what's going to happen is something different. And this I'll give you a quick story of how this came about. I was going to play Super Smash Brothers today. The World of Light. I guess I'm addicted to it. Oh, I just just stopped playing World of Light. Just stop doing that. I'm addicted to the World of Light. It's it's very fun.
It's really interesting. And I talked about it in the pre stream chat. I was kind of hanging out here. I'm like, oh, yeah, guys, I got an idea. I'm going to play World of Light Smash Brothers. And like, when you say that, that's like, no, it was just like, no, that's like, don't do that. But like, I want to do it. And I probably am. So and somebody mentioned just play Nickelodeon Flash games. And I said, I don't know, maybe you guys want to play like Nickelodeon and Cartoon Network Flash games.
One guy said it. That actually was two guys. And I said, all right, fine, because I want to prove to you guys without even a reasonable doubt that one day you will be the one guy. Everyone thinks that's just like a joke. Now I'm playing Nickelodeon Flash games. And not only that, you guys are going to get to pick which ones I have the extension turned on. That makes it so it shows a percentage of where everyone is clicking on the screen. This is going to be a mess. So it's your guys job to browse.
I'm you can control me. I'm going to go with the highest percentages. You want to test it now. Let's test it. How does it work? All right. Well, it looks like it looks like it's working. Everyone people clicking on the moon. All right. Wow. You guys are really, really coordinated. You're going 87 74% on the moon, huh? Oh, almost had almost had it. 32%, 31%. Holy shit. There's a lot of clicks. Okay, I'm gonna have to like, I'm gonna have to make the clicks. Only one click per person until I stop.
All right. That's enough of that. How do I get this off the screen? Okay, there we go. Also, I need to, uh, I think let me see if I can make this. Yeah, I can. Let's make it. How does that sound? All right, we're gonna try this again. I want to do one more test. Please everybody. If 100% of you guys don't click the moon, the stream is going to end. It needs to be 100%. 100% or the stream ends. I think you guys broke it. What's with the weird half circle there on the bottom?
Make sure this is gone. Yeah, it's on there, right? What are you guys even clicking on down there? That was 100% for it. People are clicking on the extension button. Oh, they're clicking on the moon. But that's not a moon though. Okay. Well, it works. I'm gonna regret this. Oh, fuck Jesus. Hold on. Okay. So, oh, yeah. Yeah. Where do we start here? Okay, you guys, I'll show you. I'll show you.
We'll see where we're gonna start. Let's turn that off. Let's pull this up. Well, it looks like we're already on this one. But hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. There are other options here. Let me just go like this real quick. Okay. I gotta, like, put the tabs on here. Okay. So, here are the tabs. If you guys could go ahead and see where right now we're on. This is Cartoon Network. We have, I'll just go through them all. Here's Nickelodeon. Here is Wild Tangent. Nickelodeon Cartoon Network Mini Clip in Armor Games. Uh, could you guys go ahead and tell
me which tab you'd like me to start on, please? Why are people starting over here? This is
not part of the options. I can't click that. Okay. We got, most of you guys are over
at Armor, but click the ad. Click the X. No. Turn, click the ad. I have to, I can't click
that far left. God damn it. Hold on. I don't want to click the Pokemon ad. No, no. This
is not what we're doing. This is, this is not part of the plan here, guys. Oh my God.
This was not part of this. I'm sorry. He's going to have to buy some shit. Oh, I gave
you this power, but I can't, I don't, I need to get my, my Nintendo Switch is
not even here. I can't, clicking this doesn't matter. You guys have to, you're
not doing this right. Shop. Guy, I'm on like an advertising website. Ad block. Is
this going to like show, hold on a second. This is click continue to visit
pokemoncenter.com or official online shop. The privacy and security policies
differ. Okay. Well, Twitch plays web browser. Continue. Oh, come on. You guys
are supposed to pick a flash game, not make me buy Pokemon. Let's go Eevee. I
just need to make sure it doesn't like show like anything bad. Is this a real
website? If I click it on the socks. I don't know. Okay. Hold on. I might need
to restart this. I'm really going to make me buy these 75% add to cart.
Wait, hold on. All right. I add, I did it. I added to cart. Are you happy? Why is it
still here? No, no, no, no, no. Restart it. Restart it. Restart it. Restart it.
Restart. Okay. Which buys socks? Nope. Is anybody else voting on this? People
are trying to get me to click this again. A hundred of you guys are like,
yeah, do it. Oh no, no, no, no, no. It's 96% says go to cart. Go to cart
says 96%. It's time to go. But I have to like put in, what the fuck? It's broken.
This isn't flash games. Yeah, let me just check out with PayPal. That
sounds like a good idea. Wait, what do you mean 37 more dollars? We need free
shipping? No, we don't need free shipping. Well, all right. 47% want me
to click here. I can click here. That doesn't mean I have to press a
number, guys. It has to be plus one. Well, if I click it, that would mean one, right?
Okay. All right. There you go. Okay. Everybody relax for a second. There's
two in there. You need two socks to make a pair. No, this is four. This is
four. Wait. This is four pairs of snow. This is two. How many pairs? This is four
socks. Okay. Come on back. Oh my fucking god. Well, looks like, all
right, that's $25 to qualify for free shipping. You guys aren't even gonna
let me get the free shipping. You're gonna make me check out right now
without free shipping. You guys gonna make me suffer? Wow. I can't believe it. I
can't believe you guys are gonna make me do this. Okay. There are 30,000
clicks here, by the way. I think I'm gonna call it at 30,000 clicks on
each one. But oh, oh my god. How the fuck are you guys gonna be able to do
this? Is there even a possible way for you to do that? I gotta reset the
clicks here. Yeah. Okay. Hold on. I gotta reset the clicks. Okay. Hold on. Hold on a
second. And, and by the way, now I'm including a one click. One click per
person. So make sure it counts. You want to make sure this counts. One click
per viewer. You understand? Hold on. I'll make it easy for you. Hold on. I
gotta get in close. That's not working. I gotta go even closer than
this. I think that's it. Hold on. Maybe a little bit more. That's gonna be so
hard. Okay. Here we go. Don't start yet. Actually, it actually is pretty accurate.
Oh, not anymore. Make sure you're accurate. Over, over 15 inches. Costumes. Over, uh, how
many we got? We had 1,700 participants. Over 15 inches. All right.
That, that's the, oh Jesus Christ. Okay. Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. I gotta
restart it again. What am I even gonna fucking do with this? No, that's
too far. There we go. Okay. Restart it. Some of these are like 40 bucks. All
right. Hold on. Here we go. We got Pikachu in the running. We got Mr.
Krabs. Uh, it seems to be split between Gardevoir and then, but, but this whale.
This is 26 inches. You motherfuckers down there trying to, trying to make me
spend $250 on fucking Pikachu. That thing is, is big as the, I don't know
what I could do with that. Everyone has voted so far. It's a good thing
you weren't looking at the prices, guys. All right. It looks like it's gonna be a
whale lord by an incredibly large margin. Reset? It's not my fault that you
guys weren't paying attention to what the fuck you were clicking on. Are you
serious? You, you could have looked at the prices. This is on you guys. All
right. Let's get whale lord, okay? Let's make, I don't know, I don't know
what to do here. Reset, please. I'm not gonna reset it. Customer reviews. What
could you possibly review? It's big, it's blue, and, uh, my son sits on it when he
plays Fortnite. Back button. No, it's not where people are clicking. Now we're
doing one per customer here, one per user. When we get to about 1,800 to
2,000 is clicks. And by the way, if you want to participate, if you don't know
what's going on, all you got to do is click the screen. You just got to
activate the button there and then click the screen anywhere you want. This is,
this is Twitch, uh, plays flash games or chooses what flash games I play, but
I forgot that I told them they have absolute power and they decided that
they were, they weren't gonna do it. So, back, back. Well, looks like you
want me to, uh, check it out. Go to cart. We're almost at, we're at 1,500. I don't
think it's, it's kind of an, I don't think it's possible to come back from
that. Turn off ad block. I, I can't, I can't just click ads. This is my, my
computer, I don't want to get a fucking computer ad virus. I don't want to
get like adware. All right, we hit the 1,700. There we are. Okay, we're
gonna restart. My order now qualifies for free shipping. Here we go. No, no,
do not even fucking dare. People are still going up here. All right, I, can I
finally get off this ride? We're at 1,800. I don't think it's possible. I
think it's checking out is what I'm gonna do. Yeah, that's it. I am about
to purchase two pairs of Pikachu socks in a, in a Werelord plush. This is
our Christmas gift to you. All right, all right, all right, all right. Let me,
let me just hold on a second. I need to like, okay, I got that. I will prove, I
will prove that I, I will prove that I bought those. I'm gonna be wearing the
socks on stream and I'm gonna, the, the whale's just gonna be back here
behind me. Okay, so let me go back to where I was. We originally chose, we
were, we were originally here. Okay, welcome back everybody. Let's get this
back on the screen. Welcome back. So I need you guys to pick the, at the top,
the tabs where you'd like to go. We've got wild tangent. We've got,
I can't watch cartoons on this stream. Do you understand? This is the
quickest way for my channel to get banned. What are you even clicking on?
I scroll, scroll up. No, this was, this was supposed to be like here, guys.
Cheater. No, everyone wants me to click the Amazon link and that's gonna go
into my Amazon account and then we're on a fucking shopping website.
No, I'm not gonna spend like five grand on this stream. Get him to
Amazon. Oh my fucking god. Just hold on a second. Let me make sure this is
not gonna, yes, I'm sure I'm, wait, hold on, not sure. I'm not so sure.
I'm not so sure about this. I'm not in control here. Oh, I'm not in
control here. All right. I'm not going to Amazon. I don't want to go to
fucking Amazon, guys. No, we're going where we're supposed to go. I want to
go to Disneyland, go to Reddit. I mean, I could go to Reddit. That
would actually be kind of funny. That would be really, really interesting
actually. We could probably do something pretty fun. No, I'm not
gonna go to like porn. That's not gonna happen, guys. Cool math
games. All right. Let's go, let me go back to where we were
supposed to be, which is here. This is our stream now. I'm not clicking
another ad. Fuck me. No, here's what we're gonna do. I'm gonna pick,
I'm gonna stop this and I'm gonna go here. I'm gonna make it so you guys
can't click on anything else. You know what I mean? Here's how this is
gonna work. Watch this. You ready for this? Yeah, try to
deal with this. Huh? Now you have to click somewhere up here.
Good luck. Yeah, good luck to you. No. Oh my fucking god.
Oh, that doesn't mean I have to click there.
I'm gonna play a flash game like I was supposed to do an hour ago.
Okay, it looks like six percent. Oh my god. No, no.
I'm, what? Pick from here. Here. Here is a better idea.
Oh shit. Whoops. It's like all stretched.
All right. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Now you should be able to see
everything on screen. Hey, look. There you go. All right. You're gonna pick
from, you pick your favorite show, okay? Pick your favorite show in a
second. I'm gonna get it nice and close.
I can't believe I'm buying fucking socks. So I gotta get a little closer
though. Like that. Okay, good luck. Let's actually do this for the
for the first time in about like fucking 30 or 40 minutes.
Oh man, this is close. I don't know which one that is.
Is it six? Oh, that's all in the same circle though.
And oh, it's Courage is currently winning. Okay, I think it's gonna be
Courage. Need to zoom. All right, we're gonna zoom in closer here though
because that's correct. Do it again. Go for it. Courage.
It's Courage! The Cowardly Dog with Courage! The Cowardly Dog Show!
You guys didn't even know Snoopy was on this list. What are you, crazy?
All right, it's Courage! The Cowardly Dog with this 2,000 clicks.
I need to get this back to like normal. All right, Courage! The Cowardly Dog.
But what Courage! The Cowardly Dog? I'm not clicking that, okay?
So I'm sorry. I'm not gonna click the ad. It's already over.
I'm not clicking on it. You're not going back to fucking the Pokemon store.
Why does it only have one game? Yeah, why?
Okay, okay. Fun. I told you guys you were gonna have power and
I can't take it away from you now. We did this already!
I'm turning adblock on after this. You're gonna end up living under a bridge with
nothing but Pikachu socks. All right, let's hold on, hold on,
hold on. Refresh it. Wow! There's a fight going on here
actually. I'm very surprised by this. I might have to enhance. Yeah, I'm
gonna, I'm gonna, we're gonna redo, stop. I gotta redo this. I gotta, I have
to go in and enhance this. This is too close. Holy shit!
Wow! This is unbelievable! It's, I have to enhance it again.
That's too, I have to do, we have to go closer. We have to go even deeper.
I can't even go that deep. It won't even let me.
This is fucking ridiculous. I can't, why does some of you guys want me to
click in the middle? Well, it looks like democracy has won.
Yeah, democracy has won. I'm clicking cancel. Let me just back it up for a
second here though. Hold on. Cancel. Wow! That's kind of
unbelievable, guys. Unbelievable. Watch the latest video.
What happens when I click this though? Am I gonna get, like, an ad?
Oh!
It's only halfway done. Holy shit, the subs.
Okay. All right, that was fucking fun. Okay, it's time to,
darn, this is why, fuck, I just, fucking, this ad is a full minute.
Oh, what the fuck? I, what? Okay, here's,
uh, first of all, hold on. Somebody gave a bunch of subs.
Update your flash. I don't need to. I got the latest version. Don't worry.
Now, let me get the, okay, listen. This is, everyone, this is what you guys
picked. You picked Courage the Cowardly Dog
from Courage the Cowardly Dog Show. This is what everybody clicked on.
I'm making sure that you can't click anything else if you want. Okay, here we
go. Courage the Cowardly Dog Nightmare Vacation.
Evil lava creatures have trapped, uh, Muriel under an island volcano. Help
Courage rescue her. Okay.
Bear skeeble. Arrow keys in space. This is so loud. What? This feels like an
unfinished grid. How do I, why is this game still on
their website? This game probably has, they probably
forgot it existed. People saying go down.
Oh, I wonder. Okay, I'm not, I'm not gonna, I don't, I'm not opening
anything else up. I'm not gonna open up Facebook.
Well, that was fun. Let's go back to the other games we could play.
Games, hopefully that were made in the last 10 to 15 years or clickable, maybe.
A game we're gonna do by show. So let's go like this.
Go like that. There, that looks better.
All right. Ed, Edd, and Eddie, here we come. Why are people clicking on Courage
the Cowardly Dog again? Guys, what are you thinking? You
don't really want me to click that again.
That was a Courage the Cowardly Dog creepypasta. Ed, Edd, and Eddie.
Oh, no. No, it's because I didn't have the thing on.
Hold on, that doesn't count. That doesn't count. I didn't put on the thing where
you can't vote more than once. Here, fine. Guys, can I please start
streaming? Thank you. Thank you everybody.
You know, I am just gonna pull, I'll pull up a Ouija board.
No, that's a bad, that's a biggest mistake I've ever made in my whole
life, is pulling up a fucking Ouija board.
All right, it's, Edd, and Eddie wins. Thank you for participating everybody.
Ooh, and we not only have, we have more than
a few options here. Let me restart it. We've got cul-de-sac smash,
Edd, Edd, and Eddie's candy machine, lunchroom rumble, or
spin stadium. By the way, the title says Nickelodeon. Okay, we've got
cul-de-sac smash. Got pretty good radio, 44 million plays.
Looks like this is gonna be the one. Let's see how it is. Here we go.
Cul-de-sac smash. Okay, instructions. Accelerate.
Well, let's turn it up a little. I can't do this. This music is gonna make
me fucking scream. This is nightmare music. When each
derby to advance to the next locat- I can't even talk, I have to take my
headphones off. When each derby to advance to the
next location earn cash by competing in the derbies
that make repairs and build new go-karts in the shop.
In a collision, the faster go-cart does more damage. Keep an eye on your
damage meter. Okay, choose driver.
Never, that is an option. Okay, looks like we're gonna be
Edd. All right, Edd, to the tournament. This is all
locked anyways, to the garage. Get a dollar for first prize.
Okay, I'm ready. Zippy, pick a go-kart.
All right, that's all I can do. Start the derby.
Here we go.
This is so loud. Oh shit, this is on screen.
Get off the screen. I don't understand what's happening. Is it just bumper
cars? I guess. Rolf is out.
All right, I don't know how much I can take this.
That was fun. All right, okay, uh, that was Edd, Edd, and Eddie. Thanks
for playing Edd and Eddie. Oh, I gotta pee. Let me, can I piss?
I was like rage drinking water. I'm gonna pee. Let me, I'll be right back.
You gotta, you gotta keep like clicking on the screen. All right.
Okay, okay. What'd you guys do? Oh, you guys circled the toilet real well.
All right, let's, let's get away from Cartoon Network, okay? Let's go to,
we're on Miniclip. Or, this is not gonna even work.
Is this actually gonna work? Okay, it is gonna work. But you guys can't
even control this. Okay, we can all play this. You ready?
I gotta think of a question. Hold on. This is only gonna work, guys, if we all
put our fingers on it. So, this should work here. Okay,
let me make this a little bit bigger. All right, that looks all right.
So, the only way a Ouija board works is we all have to hold our hands on
it. So, close that for a second. I have, we have to ask it a
question. So, the question is, um, the question is, what's a good
question to ask? Okay, what, what's, what's my, what is my,
uh, what is my first name? Let's see what it does.
Okay, you guys ready? Gotta put your hand on the Ouija. Put it on there.
No, no, not, not, goodbye, not, not clear.
Which one of you guys is doing this? Who's doing this? What the heck?
Whoa, this is, fuck, what the heck? One of you guys is doing this, right?
Like, one of you guys is touching this, right?
That was fun. All right, pick one of these. I'm just gonna get as many of them as I
can. This is, uh, this is Nickelodeon.
Nickelodeon's hard because the, the website's really not that great.
So, hold on. Let me make this smaller. See, the website kind of sucks.
So, we can't, you guys gotta be really pinpoint on here.
This is gonna take a lot of accuracy and I gotta zoom in because there's no
way you're gonna, there's gonna be any accuracy at all. All right,
I don't know what, what, there's nothing even in these spaces. Okay,
uh, here we go. Why did I know that was what was gonna happen?
I knew that was gonna happen. What does this do? Is this gonna, like, make a fart
noise? If, okay, if this makes a fart noise,
then I'm leaving the website. I don't care how many fun games are on here.
All right, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, wait. This is, okay, so I'm obviously
gonna click it, but this is more important.
Okay, here we go. Please, uh, answer that question, please.
On your screen right now. Will it make a fart noise?
Oh, that's pretty lit. All right, let's, moment of truth.
Uh, that was way more elaborate than just it going like,
that's what I thought it was gonna do. Play, no, I don't want to play,
uh, AccuNator. AccuNator is, but we're just sitting here asking a fake genie
questions about, like, YouTubers. All right, pick again. Oh, no, shit.
No. I'm on, I'm on AccuNator. Whatever.
Do you guys, you guys want to play around with AccuNator? I'm not gonna
say anything. I'm gonna be silent and you guys have to pick.
Why do you guys want to click this stupid fucking thing?
Because it says not to. What did you expect? Yeah, I know, I'm just kidding
around. All right, so let's go, I'll do, let's go to AccuNator.
Give me a second. There's absolutely no way that I'll beat Winnie the Pooh
baseball. Well, I mean, I already did. Uh, okay, so I need to zoom in for
this. You guys are gonna play this, not me. I have nothing to do with
this. I'm just here in control of, I'm just in control of the, uh,
the, the boxes here. Okay, so let me just make sure it is in the right place.
It is, and here you go. So, actually, I'm gonna make this a little bit
bigger, because it kind of has to be, right?
Even bigger than that. Even bigger than that. Hold on.
We don't even need the genie here, do we? He's, like, a pretty big deal,
isn't he? Part of the game. You need to be able
to see the question, though. No, we need him. No, you don't. There.
All right, he's still in it. He's still there. All right, here we go.
Is your character a girl? Oh, this didn't really work.
I'm pretty sure that's a no. Yeah, okay, it works. No, it works. It's
pretty, all right, if I go a little bit, let me go a little bit higher. Hold
on. There. But you guys, you guys can't
read that. You have to wait till I read the question, then.
Because there's no way we're going to be able to put it all on the
screen. All right, that's definitely a no.
So, I'm going to click no. Character's not a girl. Yeah, but if I
read it to you guys, some of you guys are just going to start clicking the
screen. All right, character, no, no, no, wait,
character's not a girl. Is your character
real? Okay, when I say the question, when I say the question is when you guys
can vote. Okay, ready? Is your character real?
But how can you guys all play this together when nobody knows what you're
even voting for? You all have a different character in
your head, so how would this make any sense?
Is your character real? Okay, no. Okay, hold on.
So now, let me read the next question to you. Although you can even see it.
Is your character from a video game? Looks like a majority of you are
clicking on yes. Okay, so the character's from a video game.
Already got plenty of clicks. Okay, so character yes is from a video game.
The next one is, does your character use guns? I just have, I just have
5,000 people in a room. I'm just standing on a stage while I point to
the screen for you guys. All right, character doesn't, I don't
even know who you guys are trying to make.
Don't tell me who it is, because I don't know who you're trying to make. Okay,
character does not use guns. Does your character wear clothes?
Okay, a majority of you are saying yeah. All right,
wears clothes. Does your character wear a hat often?
Yes. Who the fuck are you guys talking about? No, no. Wait, hold on a
minute. This seems pretty split. No, does not
wear a hat. Doesn't wear a hat, has clothes on, is
from a video game. Okay, no. All right.
Does your character have hair? No, that's a majority.
Yeah, everybody's clicking that. Okay, no.
Is your character a skeleton? We almost just got sansed right there.
No, the character is not a skeleton. Yeah, according to you guys.
No. Is your character from a horror game? Who would be
no, not from a horror game. That's a majority no.
Is your character bad? Like a bad guy or what?
Probably. Why somebody you guys putting on? Probably. Seems pretty,
you guys seem pretty torn apart on this one. Answer is no. Okay, does your
character fight? That's overwhelming. Okay, so yes. Does
your character have human skin? Click his nose? No.
Does your character play for the Golden State Warriors?
That's so specific. Probably. No. Is your character an animal?
That's a huge, that's an overwhelming. No one's even clicking anything else
except for his nose. Okay, does your character
live with their brother? Oh, wait a minute. Well, you guys, are you guys
doing Pete and Pete on me here? That's what you're doing. Everyone
collectively, all 5,000, you decided you're gonna make, you're gonna do
Pete and Pete. That's pretty, that's really, really
good idea. Nice work, guys. Oh, no, it's not.
Doesn't live with brother, okay. All right. Is your character short? No.
No, okay. No, the character is not short, so you guys aren't doing like a
laugh out loud, let's pick the streamer guy thing, right?
Is your character involved in a blizzard game? Blizzard?
I don't think this is, I don't know what you guys are doing,
but I don't think, I don't think you guys
are on the right track. No. Do you control your character?
I love, this is so, this is so fun to me.
You guys are collectively trying to play Accunator.
Who knows what the fuck you're gonna, I, here, I don't even know.
Do you, you don't control your character? No.
It's not a video game, hold on, how is that, is your character been in a movie?
Whoa, whoa, wait a minute, this is yes. Is it?
I don't, I don't know what that is. Whoa! You guys have no idea what you're
doing. You guys don't, you're not on the
same page at all. You guys are not on the same page.
That's so even. That is scarily even. Okay, apparently it's no.
No. Your character has, has not been in a movie.
Is your character known for their lips? What does that mean?
I don't even know what that's supposed to mean. Okay, no.
What is this? Okay, no. Is that no? That looks pretty no to me, down here.
I can't tell the split, if there is a split. There might be a split here.
I need to reset and enhance this. Click a little bit lower, guys.
I can't, I don't know what it is. I'm gonna reset it.
Oh shit, it's no. That's a big no. No, no, no.
Okay. Uh, who did you make? He's got even more, I thought it was 20 questions.
What's with the more than 21? Is your character in a team of four?
What? How many questions is he allowed to ask?
No, he's not in a team of four. As many as he needs to.
Okay, not in a team of four. Has my character ever gone on tour?
I don't know what that means. No. Wait, there's a lot of people
that don't know. Yes, no, don't know, probably. You
guys are all over the place. I think we might have to enhance.
Yeah, gonna have to, just for this question, I gotta pull this up a little.
Do it again. Don't know. Well, I don't know.
Oh, you didn't know? Don't know. Why's my B or B screen still on?
Okay. Don't know if he's ever gone on tour.
This next question is, is your character linked with Undertale?
No. Okay, not linked with Undertale. Is your character heavily muscular?
Heavily muscular. Yes. All right, I think I know what you guys are doing now.
I think I know what you guys are doing. This next one is, actually I can
probably shrink this a little bit so you can see the question.
No, it's too hard. All right, can we get Mr. Genie out of here?
Okay, there we go. Is your character from the Fallout
series? Somebody came in and said, oh, you guys are still playing this.
No, it's not from Fallout. We're at question 25.
I think it's Bowler from Clash of Clans. Is this who you guys were doing?
Is this what you were making? Bowler from Clash of Clans.
What were you guys going for? You wanted Glooman.
I mean, that's kind of close. That's actually pretty close.
You're wrong, though. I am wrong. Continue.
That's eerily close, though. That's so funny. Hold on.
Okay, do you speak with your character?
And make sure when you're clicking, make sure your clicks are pinpoint accuracy.
That way we get to keep the Genie on screen.
Okay, do you speak with your character? No, apparently not.
I think he's broken. Well, did he skip like five questions?
What was that? What were we just on? Question like 23?
Is your character from a large family? I don't know.
Probably. No. Don't you need to enhance this?
I might have to enhance this. Looks like it's mostly on no.
That actually makes it a little easier. There we go. Okay.
All right, let's try it again. This looks like don't know.
Nose. The nose has not won. It's don't know.
Okay, don't know. Does your character go pearl diving?
Pearl diving. Is it like a cartoon character that dives for pearls?
That's a lot of don't knows and knows. You guys are trying.
So very hard for this. So very hard. It's either no or don't know.
That's too close to call. That's like a 30-30 split.
That's like 33-33. And some of you guys clicking on the nose
are not participating. I'm gonna say that's don't know.
Or no. Yeah, look at the circle here. Yeah, that's no.
Does your character eat pickles? This doesn't do anything.
Probably? I thought you guys were making glue man.
Why does glue man probably eat pickles? Okay, that's what it is.
Probably. Okay. Is your character an alien?
No, that's a no. Look at that.
I mean, it's split a little bit, but I would say that's a no.
Let me go like... I'm just gonna read the questions for you guys.
We'll keep his nose on screen.
All right. Okay. All right. All right.
All right. Now answer the question.
Okay. All right. So it's no. Is your character an alien?
The character's not an alien.
I have to read this question before anyone clicks anything.
That's why I'm turning it off.
Does your character wear armor?
Really, guys? A hundred percent of you?
No, he doesn't. Don't.
We're on a question. 32.
Is your character from Paw Patrol?
Like three of you guys clicked probably.
No, your character's not from Paw Patrol.
Is your character... What the fuck does this mean?
This is what happens when you go past 30 questions in Akinator, guys.
Is your character your own flesh and blood?
How would it guess your son?
Wow. This is pretty even.
If only one out of every five of you didn't click on the nose,
we'd have a better indicator of what this is.
All right. Do it again.
This time, I want the one out of five of you to answer.
Is your character your own flesh and blood?
Is your character your flesh and blood?
You motherfuckers!
No! What the hell?
Is your character your flesh and blood?
The answer is no.
Okay, good.
This... You guys are so off.
This is not even remotely close to anything.
We're going to get like Gandalf here in like fucking 10 seconds.
Watch.
Okay. Is your character...
Is your character a koala bear?
No, not a koala bear.
He's thinking.
He's thinking real hard.
Is your character from YouTube?
Yes.
All right. Question 35.
Is your character known as a troll?
Is anybody going to click on the actual answer?
Okay. No. Not known as a troll.
What is... Why would this make any...
Does your character...
Does your character have teeth?
We want the nose.
No. It seems like a lot of you guys are saying yes.
Does he have teeth?
All right. Yes.
Oh, boy.
Congratulations, guys.
Is your character a wrestler?
I think you did it.
I think you guys did it.
It only took you nearly 40 questions.
Yes.
And 38 questions.
You got it! I can...
Wow. That happened.
You did it.
You got Glooman.
Congratulations.
He submitted himself.
I love down here.
Copyright IP policy.
What if I was just like,
Oh, no. You know, I don't want him on here.
I don't want him on here.
What?
Whose copyright is this?
Well, there you go.
You did it.
Did you copyright Glooman?
Yes.
What does this do?
Hold on. I want to see what this does.
How come I can't do that?
All right. Well, that was AccuNator.
How about this?
I'm not going to say anything.
I'm going to read you guys
the first three questions
and then you're just on your own.
Well, what is this?
Great. Guest right.
Character already played 882 times.
Last time somebody did this
was in September of this year.
Holy shit.
Let me like fix this.
So this webpage thing is all fucked up.
Hold on.
Keep that.
Why can I not...
There we go.
All right.
So next.
Why did I say September?
Because that was September.
That's the last time it was played.
That's the last time somebody guessed Glooman.
There's an EU date.
What?
Oh, I thought that...
Okay. So it was today, apparently.
All right.
But that's not even today.
It's currently the eighth right now.
That's tomorrow.
Not an EU.
Oh, well.
All right.
Check my clock.
All right. Let's go to...
Let's go back to a Flash game this time.
Okay. How about here?
All right. I'm not doing that
because I don't want to buy any more shit.
Let's go back to the Nickelodeon page.
Close this up.
And this.
Back to Nickelodeon.
Let's make this better on the screen.
All right.
Which Nickelodeon game do you want me to play?
Go play chess.
That would be impossible.
That's not going to be possible.
Do you know how that's not even going to work?
How are you supposed to...
You guys have to select a unit
and then I have to do another poll
and select where the unit goes.
Oh, my Lord.
That's going to be unbearable.
All right. Let's do it.
All right. We're doing SpongeBob Surf Cell.
It's going to be loud.
This is such a tiny screen.
Select game mode.
Well, you guys are not clicking in an accurate manner.
This is seagull.
All right. Looks like we're going to be SpongeBob.
Select a board.
Well, it has to be the ice cream cone.
Who are these characters?
No. I've got to be SpongeBob.
Select chorus.
All right. Looks like we're going here.
Okay.
Easy-peasy. Normal or hard?
Play checkers.
We'll play checkers and we'll play chess.
Hard.
All right. Here we go.
I'm ready.
How to play.
Move in space to jump.
Avoid the break.
This is fucking killing my ears.
Let's go.
I don't get it.
Okay. There we go.
Go up.
It doesn't...
I don't...
This doesn't work.
Okay.
So it's not just up and down on the arrow keys.
Go for the jump.
Nice. I got an achievement.
All right. Let's play checkers.
Let me zoom in so you get a good view of this
and you guys can actually pick.
This is going to be...
Give me a second. This is going to take us.
This is going to take a second to get this the way that I want it.
Let me see if that...
Did that work?
Kind of.
All right. Let me make sure it's good.
Then I'm going to stretch it out.
This is going to be really, really ugly.
But, you know, we kind of have to do what we've got to do here.
Okay. Are you guys ready?
Do you get ready to play checkers?
You want me to mute it?
Why am I muting the sound?
Why would you want me to mute the sound versus bot?
Holy fuck. This is ugly.
Hold on.
This has to be stretched.
Okay.
Make sure you're very accurate.
So the goal here...
The goal here is to make sure the first thing you pick first,
the one that you want to move,
then the next one after that is where you're moving it to.
Okay.
So pick the one that you'd like to move.
Us versus you.
Okay.
Yeah. No, that's a good idea.
All right.
So I think it's...
Is it my move?
So you guys are here.
Okay.
So it's my move.
Okay. Your move.
It has to be consensus.
All right.
It looks like you guys want this one,
is what my understanding is.
All right.
So I'm going to pick...
I'm picking this one up.
Where would you like me to move this one here?
Those are your two choices.
All right.
Once there's a thousand votes,
I think that's the consensus is made.
Okay. My turn.
Your turn.
Remember, you got to pick the one that you want to move.
A thousand votes have been tallied.
All right.
It's going to be this one here.
And where would you like me to move it?
Oh, it can't go anywhere else.
Okay. There you go.
My turn.
Okay.
Sneaky little move you guys are pulling here.
All right.
Which one would you like me to move?
A thousand votes.
You want this one?
Where's it going?
The indecision on the...
Change the title of the stream.
Oh, yeah.
I kind of do, don't I?
All right.
That's it.
It looks like you're going over here.
Big mistake.
I've made my decision.
It's time for you to make yours.
Going...
Ah, all right.
Yeah.
That's a decent play.
And there's only one place where that can go.
My turn.
Pretty decent block.
But, I mean, you really weren't...
You just really weren't...
No, maybe...
Well, hold on there.
Slow down, Jeremy.
Don't go too crazy here.
Go to this one and go to here.
Your move.
Protect the queen.
There is no queen.
All right.
The back...
Your back row here.
Only one place it can go.
I'm going to try to go like that.
If I go here, that stops you.
So I'm going to go from...
If you're going to go there, then I'm going to go...
Hold on.
Not yet.
Wait, wait, wait.
If you jump here, if I go here, that blocks it all.
Okay.
Your move.
Right in the middle?
Only one way to go.
Oh, let this play out for a second.
Hold on.
Thousand votes?
Thousand votes have come in.
Only one place for you to move this.
All right.
Let me think about this.
Have you come over here?
Now, you got me.
You got me in a pretty bad position.
But I might have to lose a...
Not yet.
You're pretty much stuck.
Good luck.
Somebody said, are we winning?
I will...
Okay, here's a confession.
I haven't played checkers in probably...
That would say at least 10 years.
At least.
All right.
Trying to set me up here.
Oh, look at this.
Interesting.
I mean, mandatory jump.
Oh, you're going to make one of the...
All right, go ahead.
Unanimously, my turn.
I have to go this way.
Another mandatory jump.
No, baby!
Would you take a look at this?
Another mandatory jump.
What is happening?
Okay, your turn.
I just wiped the board with you guys.
Come on.
I haven't rode...
I haven't ridden on a bike in like 10 years.
This one?
You don't have to jump.
It says mandatory jump.
You guys can't...
It's on the screen up here.
You guys can't see it.
Okay.
So I can only go in one place.
Liar.
Wait, hold on.
I thought...
See, look.
Look, look, look, look, look.
Look.
Look at this.
You want me to show you?
Mandatory jump.
I have to do this.
See?
Liar.
I can't click anything else.
Look.
I have to do this.
And by the way...
All right, wait, you want me to go?
It seems kind of conflicted though.
Delete the game.
I think it's this one.
It is.
There's only one way you can move.
Yeah, that's a thousand votes almost there.
How do you flip the table?
Click on the top right to surrender.
My turn.
What do I mean?
I got so many pieces.
How about a free king me?
Where to?
Almost a hundred percent are clicking in the top, right?
You guys surrendering?
Is this a surrender?
Surrender.
Hold on.
Let me make sure that that's not what you got.
You guys want me to move this?
You can't move this piece.
That's a surrender.
Thanks for playing.
All right.
Let's play chess now.
Time for chess.
IQ test.
Oh, that's a good one.
Let's see just how smart you guys really are.
Okay.
Let's see what this one is.
I think I have to pay for this.
Yeah, this thing.
I have to pay for this.
I'm looking for a free one.
Free quick IQ test.
I don't know if this is legit.
This has got a bad score.
Okay, hold on.
Test.
All right.
Hold on.
Let me get this back on the screen.
Where is it?
This one, by the way, has a time limit.
So no, this is not going to work.
You guys.
Yeah, this 5,000 people.
Half of you can just Google the answer.
That's not going to work.
No, I'm not even doing this.
Maybe that's what the time limit is for.
Okay, let me get this in the right spot.
So I think I can make this bigger
because this is the only spot where the test is.
Why does this have such bad ratings?
Hold on.
I'll get it right.
Why is this a long ass website?
Come on.
There we go.
Because you have to be able to click the answers.
Let me just see.
Okay, hold on.
Wait.
This is not real.
You got 25 questions here.
By the way, each one of your responses is getting less than like five seconds.
Okay, hold on.
You ready?
Let me just re-get this back where I was.
Okay, you ready?
Starting the test.
When I say go.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
Okay.
Go.
What's the smallest amount?
17 out of 100.
All right.
That's it.
You got 1,000 people.
Next.
17 out of 102.
Next question.
How many states are there in the United States of America?
How many contiguous states?
Okay, five seconds.
50.
Okay.
That's your answer.
What is 0.12 divided by 1?
I'm giving this five seconds because people are gonna do the calculator.
Okay, done.
Vintage and novelty have what meaning?
Similar, unrelated, or opposite?
Okay, going with similar.
Okay.
Next question.
Adam is selling yarn for 4.04 cents a foot.
How many feet can you buy from him for 52 cents?
Okay, I'm clicking this one.
What is the relation between credence and credit?
Similar.
Unrelated.
Whatever.
Which one?
Next.
Sarah bought a dress for $44.50.
A purse for $20.80.
And a t-shirt for $14.95.
What is the total of her purchases, Chad?
This is calculator bullshit, by the way.
I'm giving you guys like a...
Hold on.
That one's a no.
Okay, stop, stop, stop.
Okay, what will the value...
What will be the value if you reduce this fraction to the lowest term?
24 out of 95.
Stop giving them math problems.
We're gonna run out of time.
All right, this one.
Okay.
Arrange these words to form a sentence.
The sentence you arranged is true or false.
Triangle sides has a three.
Let's go.
Okay, reduce and produce have what meaning?
You guys have two minutes.
No, do it again, because it fucked up.
What are you clicking on?
Why does it keep changing?
Okay, identify the next number in this sequence.
41, 29, 35, 23.
Why is this so fucked up?
Is this not even the right spot?
Okay, which of these words are a similar meaning?
Rapidly, exceedingly, hastily, hastily, eventually, swiftly.
I can't even see the test.
But it has to be zoomed in.
Do y'all understand?
Do it again.
Rapidly, exceedingly, hastily, eventually, swiftly.
Which of these three words is a similar meaning?
Okay, rule out the word that doesn't belong here.
Affirmation, designation, approval,
authorization, authorization, or permission, go.
Well, it's not my fault that this thing is fucking timed.
Okay, identify the next number in the sequence.
Wait, wait, wait, don't click yet.
Identify the next number in the sequence.
Oh, you did it.
Why?
Now I take it.
I'm laughing at the fact 75.
Because that's not even remotely accurate.
It says between 75 and 94.
No, you guys are not doing a personality test.
I'm laughing because the worst indicator you could ever have
is 5,000 people all clicking on the screen.
And it's like, you know what, you're kind of below average.
Oh, you think?
That's fucking funny.
All right, let me see what else I want to do here.
Oh, see if I can do it better.
Okay.
I'll try.
I'm going to try to do it.
I'm going to try as hard as I can.
I'm going to be dead fucking silent.
I got to get this in the right place for you guys to see it.
But let's take it again.
Hold on.
All right, so let's start the test here.
I'm going to try as hard as I can.
Damn.
So you guys can see.
All right, I'm ready.
Here you go.
You ready?
Okay.
Is there a bar address for $44.50, a purse of $20?
What's the total purchase?
Is it $80?
Well, you guys already...
What do you get when you round of $907 to the nearest tens place?
Nearest tens place, though.
Well, I mean tens place.
Who's ten?
Where's the...
What do you mean their place?
I don't know where the nearest tens place is.
I don't even know what they sell there.
I don't even know if it's at somebody's house.
What is 40 divided by 2.5?
Round four to the nearest tenth.
Medicine is to curing as this is to cleaning.
The opposite of daunting is...
Out of a selling, you yarn for four cents a foot.
How many feet can you buy for 52 cents?
There we go.
Which of these words...
Which of these words have the same meaning?
Information, brainwash, convince, class.
The same meaning.
Information...
Okay.
Rule out the odd word from the set of rules.
Credit, debt, drought, budget.
Get out of here.
What would you get if you reduce 1435 to the nearest term?
Lowest term.
Meanie, meanie, meanie, meanie, meanie.
Ferguson has eight hats, six shirts, and four pairs of pants.
How many days can he dress up without repeating the same combination?
Do you take...
Eight, six...
Eight shirts, 880 days.
How many bananas will you find in a dozen?
Twelve.
If a person is half a century old, how old are they?
They're 50.
Select all of the quadruped animals from this list.
Dog, hamster, cat, A, B, D.
A, B, D.
A car travels five feet and a half a second.
How far will it go in a minute?
That's five feet and ten feet in a second.
So that's 600 feet.
There are three times the amount of monkeys compared to elephants in a zoo.
If there are 88 monkeys and elephants in total,
how many monkeys are there in the zoo?
What?
There are three times the amount of monkeys compared to elephants in the zoo.
88 monkeys and elephants total.
How many monkeys there in the zoo?
88.
If there are 88 monkeys and elephants total,
how many?
No, it has to be, okay, it has to be that.
Count and bold have similar meanings.
Reduce 75 out of 10, 100 to the simplest form.
Five out of six.
Write 19 divided by 20 as a decimal.
Spire and aspire have neither similar nor opposite.
Clark has 15 nickels.
How many dollars does he have?
Five, 10, 15, 20, 20, 30, 30, 40, 40.
Five, 10, 15, 20, 20, 30, 30, 5, 5, 10, 15, 20, 20, 30, 30, 30, 40, 45,
46, 47, 47, 48, 49, 50, 50.
No.
Five, 10, 15, 20, 20, 25.
Dollar 25.
Where's the dollar 25?
Dollar 20.
Sam is 11 years old.
Ross is twice as old as Sam.
So that means, okay, so when Ross is 50 years old, how old will Sam be?
That's, okay, Ross is twice as old, so that's 22.
So 22 minus, that's 40, 41.
No, it's not, it's 39.
Suppose the first two statements are true.
Is the third one true or false?
Jack greeted Jill.
Jill greeted Joe.
Jack didn't greet Joe.
What?
Jack greeted Jill.
Jill greeted Joe.
I don't know, where are they?
What room are they in?
I don't know if they talk to each other.
Jim makes $8.50 an hour and three dollars extra for cleaning a store.
If you work 36 hours and clean 17 stores, how much money do you make?
36 hours, 36, that's, I got 55 seconds here, hold on.
Jim makes $8.50 an hour and an extra three dollars for cleaning a store.
So that's three times 17.
Three times 17 is 17, three, six, nine, 12, 15, 18, 17, 17, 20, 30, 40.
That's 350, no, 320 dollars.
How many seconds are there in a day?
365 days a year, 52 weeks in a year, 24 hours in a day, 60, 60 seconds,
60 seconds in one minute, 60 minutes in one hour, 60 minutes.
So 60, 60 divided by, there are six, how many 60 seconds are there in a day?
How many seconds are there in a day?
86, 400.
Oh, he could be, he could be gifted.
Design engineer, lawyer, computer programmer, electrical engineer.
Congratulations, you're considered to be of high average to superior intelligence.
This IQ score puts you into the top quarter of intelligence for most professions,
but would only be a little above average for a college professor or a medical doctor.
You know, I have just a little bit on the same level as a medical doctor, it's okay.
All the professions that typically contain work is these sorts of IQ including, yeah, whatever.
What, I said it wrong?
Quarter, quartile, top quartile percent, top squirtle.
Oh, it's going into his head now.
All right, I gotta pee, I'll be right back.
Okay, okey dokey.
So, best flash game site.
I'm not fucking going to a random site that I don't know what it is.
All right, are we supposed to play like flash games?
It's turned into something completely different.
Minesweeper, let me see, do the alignment test.
That's going to take like three hours.
We'll do this and then I'm going to go back to like mini clip.
All right, let me get this on the screen.
How are you ever going to click on these?
There's no way this is possible, we can't play this.
How the fuck are we supposed to play Minesweeper?
It's not going to happen, it just isn't.
I can try.
You got to be really accurate.
Here, here, god.
I don't think this is possible.
No fucking way, okay.
Oh yeah, this is going to work.
This is going to work right in the middle, right here.
All right, now I have to enhance.
How am I going to do this?
Okay, did it break?
No damn, all right, so we got here versus here.
Looks like people want me to go here.
You just, you didn't, we didn't even get to do it one time.
You just clicked right on a bump.
We didn't even get one second.
Okay, I'm going to do it again.
Not even one fucking second of gameplay.
Okay, here we go.
Chess?
Yeah, we'll play chess.
If you guys blow, if you guys fuck it up again,
then we're doing something else.
Why are you doing that?
Why are you just doing this on flag?
No, this is where you want me to click.
How do you flag?
Okay, it's right click.
Flag.
No, you have to click where you want me to click.
Not click where you want me to place a flag.
All right, moving on to chess.
Okay, we're in cool math games and this is chess.
I think we're about to play versus another computer.
Random opponent?
Oh no, this doesn't work.
No, me versus you guys.
Play a friend.
Minutes per side, like three, two.
Increment in seconds.
Who cares?
Choose your color.
I'm just gonna, we'll just do the default ones.
If your friend gave you a, wait, I can't do it.
That's like a friend code.
All right, guys, this is what we're gonna do.
We have to beat a level eight computer.
Are you guys up for the challenge?
I wonder.
Okay, let's get that nice and stretched so you guys can puke.
Level eight and let's just pick, what does this matter?
Let's go start.
Well, that's not correct.
All right, wait, do we have time here?
Is this timed?
All right, you ready?
Pick it.
Where are we starting?
This is the hardest computer in the entire world.
Pretty unanimous, okay?
And where's it going?
Which space?
The first or the second?
I'm zoomed in.
I'm enhanced as much as I can get enhanced here.
Which one is it?
Am I gonna have to do it again?
E3.
I gotta enhance it a little bit.
I can't tell.
You guys don't need the E's or the 3's.
But we need to see the board.
Okay, do it again.
Come on.
Get it right this time, guys.
I know you got it in you.
That's a little more clear.
Make sure you're clicking like in the box, though.
I'm not, I don't know what that is, but I'm not gonna do that.
We're going here.
Okay?
Which one?
Again?
You want to meet and root the pawn again?
Uh, all right.
Hold on.
Now, I'm not going to that website.
Come on, guys.
So we are at almost a thousand participants.
Looks like we're going with this guy here.
Is that the case?
All right.
Where's it going?
Right to the front.
This could take us like four hours.
This isn't Nickelodeon.
I know.
This is not even close to Nickelodeon.
I think it's here.
There's most clicks are here.
All right, which one?
Play Civilization like this?
No way.
Chess on its own is difficult enough.
Speaking of difficult, this isn't too close to call.
Well, no, not anymore.
Play Starcraft.
All right, we're going with this one.
And we can only do one thing, right?
Only one thing is available.
All right.
Now what?
Would you want me to move?
I can't move that horse.
We already lost close the game.
Give us Nickelodeon.
This is too easy.
Twitch Prime, Jarmo.
When are we playing Super Smash Brothers Ultimate, man?
I was going to play it tonight.
All right, we're going from here.
And one or two spaces.
Go for the king.
I can't go that far.
So many people are trying to click the X on the corner.
All right, we're going one step up.
All right.
They brought another horse out.
What's your move, guys?
Which one?
Down here.
Even more people.
Looks like you want to take the horse.
All right.
Where's it going?
From one of three spaces there.
Here we go.
Let's do it.
Are we checkmated right now?
Hold on.
Did I lose?
Where do I take him?
What?
I have to move here.
Okay.
I'm in check again.
What did you guys do?
Where am I taking him?
Oh, so that's it.
That's it.
Game over.
That's checkmate.
That's it.
It's over.
You...
That's checkmate.
That's it.
I lose.
Somebody just said, Jarmo, why are you so bad?
I didn't do anything.
Let's play some mini clip games.
Let me at least do the thing that's in the title.
It's streamer's choice right now.
All right.
Streamer's choice.
The real question is what do I want to play?
Oh, there's so many options.
I need you guys to pick for me.
No, I got it.
I don't need anybody to pick for me.
I'm going right here.
Hopefully this is not loud.
It's going to be though.
I know it is.
All right.
You want to see how to lose like 500 viewers instantly?
Wait, wait, wait.
Let me just do this.
I want to play this one.
Yeah.
Not Nickelodeon.
Not even close to Nickelodeon.
Is there a Nickelodeon baseball show?
All right.
I'm ready.
You have 10 pitches to score as many points as possible.
How do you play?
As the pitcher winds up, a marker appears showing where the ball will pass.
Use the mouse to mouse the aim circle towards the marker.
The closer you are, the straighter you're hit.
OK.
You can control the direction by moving the aim circle relative to the marker.
Hit the ball.
Up aim.
That's up.
Down.
And set the ground ball.
Click the left mouse button to swing.
Land the ball as close as you can to the center for the target.
Oh, god.
Oh, shit.
We're losing viewers.
Get out of here.
It's gone.
I got to hit a home run.
That's a home run.
I'll turn the game off.
Winnie the Pooh baseball.
I tried that before.
I got points on that one.
A lot.
I did already play Winnie the Pooh baseball, though.
You're right.
Oh, fuck.
I crashed it.
No, I didn't.
I just right-clicked accidentally.
Get out.
I need to.
I can't leave until I hit a home run.
I can't.
Get out.
No, no, no.
I'm doing it again.
Okay, let's go.
High scores.
I don't...
No.
Main menu.
Easy.
Fucking get out.
Oh, my god.
I'm never going to do it.
That's gone.
I don't think it's possible to hit a home run.
You can't hit a home run in this game.
Why?
Oh, that's what he says.
And it didn't fucking leave the infield.
I'm out of here.
A ball out of the fucking infield.
Get out of the infield.
I can run?
Oh, my god.
No, get out.
Okay, good, good.
Okay, okay, okay.
We're good.
All right, maybe I'll get those 300 people that left back.
Let chat play balloons.
Tower defense.
You guys want to play balloons?
You play balloons.
Don't...
Normal balloons.
No, how about this?
I want to find one of these that I think is cool.
This one looks cool.
I'm going to do this one first.
This one's called saloon brawl.
I need to move it.
That doesn't sound good.
That sounds really bad, actually.
It sounds like my speakers don't work.
Okay, now let's make it fit the screen.
Saloon brawl.
All right, let's go.
Oh, my god.
Grab, punch, block, grab foes.
This is a pretty good iPad game.
Oh, that guy's got a pizza.
Special attack is ready.
How do I do my special?
Oh, my fucking god.
How do you win this?
Get them all in the water.
What the heck am I doing?
Just throw them all in the water.
This is the stupidest thing ever.
Fortnite Season 7 incoming.
I got to at least beat the first level.
Step on his head.
I win.
Thank god.
It's over.
Is it over?
No, there's one more guy with the fucking pizza.
I did it.
All knocked out.
I win.
Like, that's enough of that.
There's so many things here.
We can still hear it from your mic.
That's how loud that shit is.
I'm going to go to sleep.