Hey, what is going on everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary.
And tonight, gonna be playing as the Demoman, using the Sticky Bomb Launcher, of course,
the half Zatoichi and the lock and load, which has become my default Demoman setup ever since
I got the strange lock and load a few days ago. Now this video, I want to really bring
up something very, very important about the Demoman. I want to give you a couple of tips,
couple of strategies to use, because I've never done a Demoman tip video. I think I
said one or two things, maybe a long time ago about it. But I want to give you some
real strategies, at least with the Sticky Launcher. Because with the lock and load and
with the default grenade launcher, it's kind of spam. You get lucky sometimes with air
shots. You have to time it, you have to lead your targets, that type of thing. But the
Sticky Launcher can be a real pain in the butt for a lot of people. And I'm here to
save the day. Jerma saves the day. Hold on just one second. Excuse me, hold on, what?
You think you're going to be teaching anyone something without me here? Who the hell are
you? I'm the principal of the local school. Oh, okay. I mean, this is a Team Fortress
2 video. I don't think you really, I mean, I don't think you need to be here. It's not
Oh, dear you. I am the school principal. That means what I say goes. And if you don't like
that, then I'm going to give you a math problem to screw with your brain. Stop. 2 plus 2 is
4. 4 plus 4 is 8. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. Okay, I understand. You're the
school principal. And if there's one thing I know about principals, they don't like this
chant. You better not do it. Homework sucks. No, stop. Homework sucks. Stop it. Homework
sucks. Homework sucks. Homework sucks. Homework sucks. He did it. He's gone. Oh, for now.
He's gone for now. And is this even a Team Fortress video anymore? This turned into like
outer space adventures with Jerma. What the hell is going on? Anyways, so demo man sticky
bomb tips. Without that guy here anymore, we can get into this. So the sticky launcher.
So what you want to do with this thing, the most important thing about the sticky launcher
is setting traps for people. And that does not necessarily mean hiding behind a corner
with five stickies on a doorway. When I say sticky trap, I mean real time sticky traps.
Think of a land mine system where you're dropping land mines where you know people are going
to walk. And if somebody's chasing you, especially if it is a pyro, you are going to see this
at least two or three times in this video, a pyro will be chasing me or any close quarters
scout or something like that. Drop the stickies where they are running, kind of like a bread
crumb trail to you. So pretend you're Hansel and Gretel and the person chasing you is the
witch and you're dropping these stickies down. So when they walk over the trail, you can
detonate it and it might not kill them for the first sticky or even the second sticky,
but a lot of times it only takes two or three. And for the most part, people will still chase
you. So definitely check out the bread crumb trail in in quotes. I guess that could be
what it is. But the second technique I want to talk about is one that a lot of people
do anyways, but I want to cover it just because some people still don't do it. It is the blind
fire technique. And that is where if you know there are people around a corner, don't try
and make a trap on the right side or wait for them to come around. Just shoot in a space
across the corner or around the corner where you know people are going to be. Because think
about every single choke point in Team Fortress. There's always going to be a ton of people
around certain corners, especially on payload and especially on control point. So once you
get the knowledge of the maps, definitely use this blind fire technique and that follows
up with another technique. And it's not even really a technique, but still there are people
that don't have this. And I was one of those people that originally I did not have this
enabled. Turn on hit sounds. You go to advanced options. This is also by the way how to turn
on the numbers, the damage numbers. So go to advanced options, turn on play a sound
when an enemy is hit. It's something like that. And the damage numbers as text. You
want both of those, especially the first one. Because what this allows you to do is blind
fire around corners and get the ding sound and know, okay, there's people there. Let
me shoot more and kill four people. And it did take me a long time to turn those on and
I really don't know why. I think I just didn't like change. But this is going to wrap up
the video guys. Thank you so much for watching. I really do appreciate it. Hopefully you got
something out of this. I know there's a bunch more tips I can give, but these are just the
ones that I like to use. These are the ones that help me the most. So yeah, I'll catch
you guys all next time and take care everybody.