Hey, what is happening guys? It is Jerma here with a gameplay commentary. This
time I'm playing as the spy and the loadout for this match is going to be
the big earner the new spy knife from the uber update, the ambassador and the
default vanilla invisibility watch. I told you guys I promised you I'd get an
invisibility watch gameplay that I wasn't just gonna do all dead ringer and
here you go here it is I promised you so I'm gonna deliver on that. Also we are
playing on payload race Hightower which was introduced in the engineer update
and right off the bat here I get two quick stabs I thought for sure I was
gonna be able to get at least three or four people right there but that heavy
has some quick reflexes and puts me down six feet under. That is one of two deaths
that occur during this gameplay and I'll give you my quick assessment on the big
earner the knife that I'm using currently. I don't think it really works
that well with the default invisibility watch or obviously the cloak and dagger
the reason being because when you stab somebody the mechanic of this knife is
when you backstab somebody or when you kill somebody I believe it's when you
kill somebody as well you get 30% cloak and as you'll see right here I backstab
this heavy but I have full cloak anyways it doesn't really matter and there's so
many ammo cases when you're using the default invisibility watch that by the
time you backstab your next victim you're gonna have full cloak anyways and
it's not gonna do you any good you're just losing 25 health. Now with the dead
ringer though this knife is incredible because when you backstab somebody if
you use the dead ringer and you use the Latranja or however you pronounce it
you'll be doing huge benefits to yourself because you'll backstab
somebody and if you turn around and shoot one person you'll have full cloak
to just use it again you are pretty much invincible if you use the dead ringer
the Latranja and this knife. As you just saw I backstab that heavy with not a
whole lot of cloak and I got a lot back but that's pretty much the only time it
happens in this whole gameplay this is great here I get these two snipers with
two great headshots that really helps the team out because now the car can come
through here rather than having them pick off everybody that comes through
this little corridor. So now I'm just trying to patrol the area what you
should be doing as a spy on these types of maps anyways it's kind of your job
just to patrol the area make sure no one's lurking around somewhere that's
the best thing to do on this map especially Hightower so walking around
checking to see where people are where the team is where the other team is it's
kind of your duty as a spy to do these things and I get up behind these guys
trying to pretend like I'm a sniper switch my weapons a couple times I get
behind this heavy medic pair and it's doom doom and gloom for you two special
guest appearance by Satan right there so thank you Satan anyways I saw there was
a demo man there that I couldn't get behind I probably would have fallen off
the cliff if I tried to so I got out of there quickly and this is a great stab
right here this pyro is kind of running sideways and I get him with a little
side stab so thank you for coming mr. pyro carts are looking pretty even right
now so I try to come back up these stairs I'm gonna try and get a couple
more headshots on the snipers that are up here so I think they wised up though
because they're not there so if you're unaware the ambassador is the only other
weapon in the game that can crit with a headshot it's the only other weapon that
can headshot period but that was a pretty big fail right there so I probably
shouldn't have even went for the stab I probably should have just backed off and
went the other direction but that's the only other time I die in the gameplay so
let's see what I can accomplish in the next two or three minutes huh coming out
of the respawn now and I don't understand how this happens you guys
will see I do a direct shot right in this medic's face like it couldn't be
any more perfect and watch this doesn't register not even a hit not even a hit I
got him right in the face to lag compensation for the win huh so anyways
I'm trying to get behind these guys they know him around that medic they both die
from the scout so that was a pretty good part on the scout so now just patrolling
again looking for somebody to kill looking for somebody to maim come back
up here no snipers again I thought for sure they would come back because look
where the cart is that isn't a prime spot for snipers and oh German won't
forgot to hit the spacebar you got to do that when you jump don't forget that
next time so anyways this is kind of how high tower goes in your spy you're gonna
do a lot of walking around and when the carts are even like this in the spots
where they are you're gonna do a lot of moving around a lot of walking around
trying to find somebody thought about going for a shot but I didn't and now
I'm thinking about time to go down here to the cart because nobody's here so I
jump down gonna come over to the staircase here and there's a little spy
I didn't know this before because I'm an idiot and I hurt dirt all the time when
I play spy I did not know that you could jump up these crates and boxes but I
end up doing it missed the stab but get it anyways I come down here there's a
pyro that I try and do a side stab to but I miss and obviously as a spy you
want to run like hell from a pyro that knows you're around jump down here here
we go he's gonna come after me I'm waiting for him boom nice little shot
get the kill oh am I gonna die nope just barely miss bumping into the spy
coming in who was doing the same thing I did trying to get health and some
cloak so now we come up to the cart here I want to try and make this happen
because nobody's pushing it really so me and this pyro get on it and I'm a cart
spy now it's like heavy get down here like where are you going like come over
here and get on the cart but anyways this is now headshot mania right here
there's one don't get the kill it doesn't matter there's two I get the
assist for this though and now here comes another couple headshots on the
snipers finally the snipers ended up coming up to that roost there's one
and do I get the kill and there's a headshot kill right there now our team
is just all pushing the cart I figured that we have this in the bag there's like
four or five here so I take a trip down here I'm not gonna cap it there's no
reason for me to be here I'm gonna try and pick off people that come out of the
spawn and nobody really comes out they all go the other direction so I kind of
went the wrong way but it's alright we still do fine so I come out of this
window trying to find somebody that I can't shoot that guy can't shoot that
guy so I just go over to the right side of the spawn and I end up getting a
heavy he just kind of comes out and he just bang gets him right there that's
gonna be the end of the gameplay guys thank you all so much for watching I
really appreciate all the support you guys give so I'll see you all next time
and take care everybody