So here he is, the man of the hour, the medic. If you haven't seen Meet the Medic already, go see it right now. It's amazing.
The new needle gun is the overdose. 10% less damage done, but your movement speed increases based on the amount of ubercharge you have.
The new medigun is the quick fix. Everyone already knew what this was. It was in beta, just like the detonator.
Faster heal rate, faster ubercharge rate, but you can't overheal anybody.
And your ubercharge is a 300% faster heal and immunity to movement impairing effects.
And this thing, I had to buy this. It just lets you see enemy health.
By the way, sets do absolutely nothing. As you can see, I have the full set of this.
So, the quick fix is kind of an odd duck. I think it's weird because it takes everything you've known about the medic and it flips it upside down.
See, right here I'm healing a bunch of people over and over again and running around, trying to overheal people.
It's just kind of a habit that you have as a medic. You have to lose that when you have the quick fix because you don't have to do this.
The only reason why you do this in the beginning, of course, is to build up an uber.
But it's completely unnecessary in any other situation.
I think the actual ubercharge on this thing, it's just kind of odd. It's trying to be like three or four different things.
You know, with the knockback immunity, the extra heal rate, and I don't know, I just feel like it's trying to be too many things.
If they just got rid of the uber completely and made it, instead of 40%, like 60% better heal, I bet you people would still use it and still love it.
So, speaking of the uber of this gun, why don't we take a look and see what it does?
I actually kind of freak out here. I don't really do it so well. I get kind of lost in what I'm doing.
I keep thinking it's going to be like an ubercharge, but like I said, it's just not.
The heal rate is great, though. As you can tell, I just popped it. It's hard to tell if you popped it or not.
It looks kind of like the Amputator taunt.
And that was it. You just saw it. It was faster heal rate for 10 seconds.
I don't know.
The actual heal rate on this thing is amazing.
As you can see, that scout was at zero health and I brought him all the way up to full in less than pretty much a second.
So the actual heal rate is great. Like I said, the uber is just nothing to me. I'm not a big fan of it.
I probably have to give it some more time. That's probably the problem that I'm having.
But, see right here, the soldier just had no health and now he's at full.
It's just, it's an incredible, it's a good, I want to say raid healer, if anyone knows what I'm talking about when I say raid healer.
That'll throw back to some World of Warcraft players or some LoTRO players or whoever you are.
It's a raid healing gun. Let's put it that way.
Where this thing actually excels is in situations like this, where you have to outheal damage.
See, this soldier probably would have just died right here if it wasn't for the quick fix.
The crit screak and the regular medic gun would have definitely failed in that situation.
So, the other items. First of all, I thought the new melee unlockable for the medic was a hat.
And I was psyched about it. I was like, oh my god, that's an awesome, I hope that's a miscellaneous, that would be so funny.
But it turns out it's a melee weapon and with identical stats as the default bone saw.
But you get to see player's health, enemy's health, and that's a huge bonus.
But I don't know if I'm willing to give up some of the other saws, like the uber saw or the amputator, they're just so good.
It's going to take a little more time using them to find that out.
The sniper got a couple of items in this update. Most notably the Bazar Bargain, the new sniper rifle.
Base charge rate is decreased by 20%. Each scoped headshot decreases the weapon's charge time by I think it's 10%.
A scoped body shot or a missed shot wipes the charge. No new secondary for the sniper this time.
But a new knife, the shashahashashashasha, which essentially is just the equalizer without the speed increase.
So this is what it looks like just at base level. I haven't shot anybody yet.
And see there's a little indicator on the lower right that says heads.
Sort of like the Demoman's Eyelander or the Clyde & Moore.
But here's one headshot here and there's another one I believe right here.
So this is what it looks like with two and it looks pretty normal, maybe a little bit higher.
It looks about the same as it would be with the regular sniper rifle.
To consistently do well with this sniper rifle you have to know what you're doing as a sniper.
They came out with a Sydney Sleeper for the people that couldn't really aim too well.
And then they came out with this which was the pro sniper rifle.
So I'm a very bad sniper so I think I only get a maximum, I think I get three.
So yeah, I can't really demonstrate this too well because I only get three headshots so we'll see what it looks like after three.
I'm pretty sure the max is probably seven or eight. I'm wondering what the max is for the Eyelander.
So as you can see it is pretty much, right there it looks like it's the same as the Sydney Sleeper is now after the buff.
So I'm guessing after four or five headshots in a row you will really start to see this thing shine.
These are just a couple of kills with the new knife.
The new knife like I said is the equalizer which means that you do more damage when you take more damage.
I think it's when you get to half health you do like 25% more damage or something like that.
And we end with the Spy. The Spy got two new items in this update.
The first that he got is a new revolver, it's called the Enforcer.
20% damage done over the regular revolver and a half a second increase in cloak time which we'll talk about in a second.
He got a new knife, the Big Earner, plus 30 cloak on kill, I'm not sure if that means backstab or not.
And 25 less health on wear so you have 100 health as the Spy.
So let's go over the Enforcer, it is the new revolver.
It's 20% more damage and it is a straight upgrade, that's right it's a straight upgrade to the regular revolver if you use the Dead Ringer.
I say that because the Dead Ringer is not affected by the decrease in cloak time.
Only the regular invisibility watch and the cloak and dagger are affected by the decrease in cloak time.
So let's talk about the knife now.
Take a look at my cloak in the lower right and watch this, bang.
This knife is also another one of those straight upgrades over the original.
Mainly because the downside is really not that bad.
You only are taking a 25 health hit, I mean the Kunai is a 65 health hit so you're not losing that much health at all.
So for the purposes of showing you the downside of the revolver I'm going to use the regular cloak.
So you'll see here, I come out here and I get a kill, watch my cloak bar, it's going to fill right up.
And then watch this, that right there, that little half second right there is going to throw you off so bad.
I highly recommend using the Dead Ringer with this set.
Not really the knife but definitely, definitely the revolver portion of the set.
And that is all I have for you guys. I'm sorry that I had to split it up into two videos.
But you don't know how horrible this was to make.
It took a long time. I hope you guys appreciate it.
I hope somebody gets something out of it because I did.
I did. I learned how to tear my hair out of my skull because item servers weren't working and oh my god, I don't even get me started.
But yeah, like, comment, subscribe, do whatever you guys want to do.
I hope you guys enjoy the new items and I'm glad I could bring at least some information to somebody who is on the fence about something.
So thanks again, take care guys, I'll see you next time.