Hi guys, welcome to an Omega Lake stream. You were here earlier, I had to change a few things,
because we have some interesting things going on tonight. There's always something interesting
going on. There's always something, always something different, you know, always something
new going on here. Am I using a webcam, Mike? Am I? Hold on. Hello? Hello? Are we good?
What Mike was that? I don't know what Mike that was. Okay, well, anyways, hi. Welcome to
another edition. Go back. Oh, it was the VR Mike. How is it picking me up from all the way over
here? I have no idea. So let's go over a couple things. I'm not going to tweet this out yet.
I want to make sure that the stream is going to be stable, because I'm currently downloading
hundreds of gigabytes worth of data. And we'll explain it. We'll talk about it.
Somebody just gave speaking of hundreds, thinking of hundreds of gigabytes of data.
Somebody just give $200. That was German's massive dong for two,
$200, 20,000 bits. They're just given they're just given hundreds of dollars.
This this is just still happening right now, by the way, like this is another
hundred dollars just came in 300 bucks. This isn't I don't even know how to react. This is insane
to read. This is 300 bucks right at the beginning from German's massive dong. Well,
he gave it to himself. I didn't. I didn't. But thank you so much for the 300 fucking dollars.
They say I love you, Jeremy. You're the best been watching you since before the TF2
pyromaniac update. That's a long time ago. Thank you so much for your incredibly generous,
insane $300 30,000 bits. Thank you. But for what's going on today,
after that gigantic blast out of money. One night, why don't I tell you myself?
How you doing? Okay, anyways, so let me make sure one thing happens here.
Okay. Am I delayed? I might be. Did it again. Why did you do it again? That that's that's $400.
400 from German's massive dong. Okay, this is where it gets a little weird.
This is another one. They say take all of my money. Take it all. I don't want to take all
your money. I don't want to take all your money. That's 500 bucks. Take it all. Take
it all. I don't look I don't want to take it all. Why am I wearing a little boys t shirt?
This is a I like this shirt. It got stuck. It don't ever dry your shirts. Follow the directions
that are on the tag. Nobody ever does that. Why am I sweating? What is it? Why? How am I
sweating? What are you talking about? I'm not sweating. But German's massive dong give 500
bucks. That's so much money to see drop here in less than five minutes of the stream being
like that. That's $100 a minute. Yeah, that's a $100 a minute. I can't even fucking comprehend
it. That's a that's a thank you. That's a fucking ton of money. He's now Bill Gates,
earning $6,000 an hour. What's your going rate, by the way? We're gonna like think
about hire you for a video or something. Well, 6000 hours a minute. I mean, thick
thick hours. $6,000 a minute. I fucked it up. Whatever. thick hours. Anyways,
let's let me explain what's going on today. Because there is something you did it again. I
won't stop. I don't but that's 70,000 $7,000 a minute $7,000 a minute. Well, you that's
that is that is 600 bucks. That is that isn't that's that's that's a lot. That's a that's
enough. That's a fucking in it. I don't know to do this is insane. I won't stop. I'm a
part of you another 100. You're not going to do the you know, don't like, oh my fucking God,
you gotta ban them. I can't just ban them. This is so much money, dude. Like, I really
hope that you're like comfortable doing this. Make sure you take care of yourself first.
Thank you so much for the $700 fucking dollars. Cry for him. At least cry. I'm not in I'm not
in a crying mood right now. Oh my fucking God. What is happening? Herbert just gave 20
community subs. You guys are raising my rate to like $10,000 an hour. Thank you Herbert
1234. Thank you to derma's massive dong for the 700. Jesus Christ. I don't know to say
you guys are fucking that's this is gonna bet you're gonna see that like five more times.
Invest in yourself quick. God, but let's talk about what's going on today.
Play a game. Look, I just play a game lazy streamer. Hold on. I'm trying to tell you
what's going on. My fucking God. This will be the best stream another 50 bucks for massive
dunk. I don't know that I don't know this. I don't know if this is gonna be a good stream
or a bad stream. This might be a middle of the road stream. This might be a great stream.
I don't know. I can't. That's $750. That's outrageous. What was I saying? Oh yeah.
Today. Today is a day. I was gonna start at the normal time and I was gonna just sit here and
accept $1,000 from someone apparently. Best stream NA. Another 100 bucks. Now I'm financially
obligated to make this the best stream. I hope you can please tell me that you can afford
this. I don't I ran run ads or riot. No, no. Everybody slow down. Slow down. I need to
tell you what we're doing today. I haven't even a chance to tell you what the fuck we're doing.
Another turtle toenail get $50. I need you to play peace bone. I'm here to distract you.
I'm turning off my camera. No, you won't be able to see like the reactions. Okay. So no,
I'm not gonna play ads. Stop it. No, you don't have to give me this much money.
You don't have to. This is this is at the nine. I don't know what to do. This is
more money than I've ever seen in one sitting. I think what the fuck is happening. I just turned
the stream on. I'm like two and a half hours late. I haven't even explained to why I'm late.
$950 from German's massive dong. I'm the money machine. Thank you. Anonymous gave 10
community subs. Quick turn the stream off. I never know. I heard there was a bit party
comfort eagle $55. Guys, this is supposed to be a hangout portion where we waited for
Kraken and Nova. I didn't even tell you about this guy spoiled. I mean, I just spoiled it for you.
I can't even fucking comprehend that I just made like fucking 1200 1500 bucks in like fucking
done in 11 minutes. I said I would give all my money the second the stream started
German's massive dong and you're over $1,000 and I don't know why you do that. I don't
know what to do. This is insane. You don't have to give me all your money. That is
$1,005. No, $1,050, right? I forgot how to stream. I forgot how to stream.
I don't remember how to do this. Okay. So first of all, thanks for the thousand,
$1,000 shut the closet. Okay. No, I can't get up because I have like a fucking weird
pants on and I don't want you to see anything. I swear to God, that's the truth. Five
community subs from loco roco. I haven't been able to even say anything. That's another
1100 bucks. How do I stop? How do I turn it off? I'm turning off bits. How do I turn off this?
I swear to God, I don't know what to do is I'm overwhelmed right now. I'm so overwhelmed.
Who is this guy? Oh, obviously it's it's German's massive dong. But you hold on,
you got to stop though. You've got to stop it at the 1000 bits per inch, right? No,
no, no, no, 10,000 bits. I do already tired. He said it. That's huge. That's like a 10 foot.
No, no, that's not what I meant. I mean, you'd be able to put out fires with that thing.
All right. Okay. Now I'm all fucked up. I don't know. I'm done. Just show us the dog.
Oh my God, dude. 12. I cannot fucking believe that I just got over $1,200 from the same
person. And then other people will cut like this is there. Okay, there you go. That's that's
$1,200 for 12. You do the math. I'm not I'm not one of those streamers. I'm not going to go
there. Okay. Anyways, my God, this is fucking ridiculous. German's massive dog. Thank you
for that. No, no, you didn't just do that. Why are you doing this? What's happening right
now? Why am I going to make this much money right now? I didn't even do anything.
Well, now I'm going to immediately order the wireless vibe set thing. Time to retire.
Holy shit. It's just a dream. Like wake up in my bed. But for real, though, like,
completely unnecessary. But thank you fucking so much for the insane uncountable dog money.
And that Peter P 337 are 100 bucks. He just said party. So fucking much. This is insanity.
Thank you. That's his name. That's the person's name. Anyways, this is what's happening today.
We're gonna hang out. I'm currently downloading a bunch of mods. Let's go over it. Let's go
over the week. We're just gonna hang out. We got like 40 minutes until, like I said,
Kraken Nova and tomato. We're gonna do something. And what that is, I'll tell you
after I collect myself. Yes, I had the title of the stream is already here. I'm off.
Anyways, okay, here we go. Let's get a sip of coffee. Let's fucking ground ourselves here.
Let me ground myself. Let me ground myself with like a clear quartz crystal. That's quartz.
It looks pretty. This is this is quartz. Let me ground myself. What's that supposed to do?
Why do I have that? Because I got Kim a ring the other day. No, no, not what you think.
Not what you're thinking. We just were like, we will. No, listen, I got, it was just
like a fun ring and like it was a crystal ring. And I was like, oh, it looked cool. Listen to me.
All right. Another hundred dollars just came in. No, we're not. Who are characters of these? Have
you ever seen them before? I don't know what these are. My stream is lagging. Too much
money has come in. Just kidding. The love never stops. Thank you, Jermis. Massive dong.
But anyways, another 13 hundred five. Sometimes I think this isn't even real.
You know what I mean? I'm going to wake up in like a week or like a month or something.
And I'm going to be like 14 just in bed. And this is just a wild fucking like 10 year,
15 year long dream. You ever think about that? You are always, this is the, this is the,
this is the point of money where like you went over that, that threshold of like,
that's a lot. And then you went over it again. It's like the bar is here and it's just over
there and I can't, I can't see it anymore. It's 1400 dollars from Jermis massive dong.
I have to say it every time. Buy a ring here. Buy a ring with all my money. It wasn't an
expensive ring. It was just a fun thing for fun. We were looking around at some stores and
stuff. Turtle toenail. Another 50 dollars. Let's not forget about the other people that
have given more than 50 hundred dollars in the first 10. This was supposed to,
we are just kind of hanging out, I guess. My goodness gracious. No stream, just bits.
Been watching you for years. This is my first live stream. Well, welcome. Thanks for hanging
out. Eventually I will tell you what we're doing tonight. I bought her a candy ring. Yeah,
made it a candy. Twerk on stream. Why would I do that? But anyways, so we were going to
play. I got to reset. I can turn the stream off and turn it back on. Hold on. Let me
reset. I got to reset. I have to reset. Okay, we reset. Welcome to the stream, everybody.
No, he did it again. A streamer makes a million dollars doing that. You're not going
to give a million dollars. Do not fucking even think, don't even, I don't know if that's
real. You could be being a fucking weirdo. Though do not give a million dollars. I'm not
very good with money. Don't give it to me. Don't give it to me. It'll never work again.
I make a million dollars tonight and I'm like, well, all right. That was like fun for like
the last 10 years. I'm going to go live on a beach. I'm just going to just permanently
lie down in the sand and have like a beer right here. And I'm going to do it so often
that I'm going to have like a permanent sunburn, vacation beer sunburn here. It's
going to be like a tattoo. I was going to tell you what we were doing today.
What am I supposed to do? Dude, what the fuck are you doing? That's $1,600. What did
you say? You best stream for the rest of your life until you die. I can't stream
anymore. Is this what happens? Is this what happens when you get like too much money?
You're just like, um, so what we're going to, hey, what we're going to do today,
let me tell you, it's really cool stuff that what's going on. Uh, so what we're
doing today is, uh, it's something very cool. We're going to play, listen, so, uh, my,
my mother is coming in. All right. So my mother's coming in next week.
So I'm going to spend the next few days here in rural streaming. So those of you
know that I'm taking a little vacation next week. One bit equals minus one brain cell.
Okay. Give, look, give me, give me a little credit here. So I'm just sitting here in my office,
right? And I'm like, Hey, let me get started with something here. Hold on. Oh, let's get
started. Hey guys, welcome. Somebody opens the door and they have a briefcase. And I don't,
I don't know. I'm just like, Hey, and by the way, this person has a sign on them that says
German has a huge dick. And I'm like, well, hey, huge, all right, what's, what's the
briefcase? What is this? And he like, and he walks out of the room and I open up this
briefcase and there's two grand in here. And it's like, what this, what's in here?
There's $2,000 in here. I'm trying. It's, um, this is fucking ridiculous.
He brings in $1,600 briefcase. Yeah. Okay. He just walks in with it with another
briefcase. Five minutes later, there's another a hundred dollar bill of it.
He does that 16 times and he walks in every time he goes like,
and it's like, yeah, like a German's dick. Oh my God. All right. That they said, this is
another a hundred bucks. Derma, I'm done. Give it money for now. But seriously,
your videos and streams got me through some hard times that I could never gotten
through without you. Just want to say thank you for being used so much. Love a fellow
gamer. That's, that's all you needed to say. Seriously. That's it. You don't have to give
me fucking 1700 bucks, but that's a, that money will be spent on candy. I buy a lot of
chocolates. I buy a lot of Reese's. Uh, but for real, that's so much fucking money.
I, I have nothing else to say besides I am fucking forever grateful that you would
even consider even thinking for a second that some random guy on the internet deserves
almost $2,000 of your money and I can't even fucking comprehend it.
Thank you so much for being part of the community. That's, that's fucking intense,
man. Like I, I really, really hope that you can afford it. Number one. And I'm just glad that
you have fun here. That's all I care about. So I will put that money to good use. You just,
you just yourself pretty much bought like the dunk tank spring. Yeah. There it is. Like
seriously, uh, moving on from that though, I, I'm forever grateful. Thank you. Oh yeah,
that's right. I thought I didn't like talk about that yet. I talked about a little bit
at the end of the stream. Uh, you'll see it whenever someday. But anyways, um, after that
monumental amount of fucking money, what we're doing today. Hey, how are you talking to you?
How you been? He's going to say it. He's finally going to say it. He's going to tell
us what we're doing today is I originally planned. So we were VR last night. I wanted
today to be kind of a chill stream. So around like, I don't know, three o'clock,
I was going to just play, um, what's that video game Western? Call of Juarez, right? We're
going to play Call of Juarez. We're going to play Call of Juarez. But it turned out that,
uh, Criken sent me a message and he said, Hey, we've got some shit going on. If you want
to play, we're going to do like black ops, three zombies modded. And I was like,
all right, that sounds like fun, but they don't start streaming till like 20, 30
minutes from now. So what I kind of had to push the stream back a little bit.
It was like kind of last minute, not even like 24 hours, really 12 hours or so.
So I thought it'd be fun. We're going to do extreme modded black ops three.
There's like 50 mods, Jervis dong is average. Why people are given more.
So before I address the more penis money that came in the dong money that came in,
this is like surgeon income right now. Do you understand? This is like, I should be
performing like a heart surgery. I've lost. Okay, hold on. But listen, so yesterday VR,
I was going to chill a little bit today, but we're going to do another high octane
stream today. Crazy black ops three modded nonsense. It was like a hundred and 200,
300 gigs worth of stuff. I can't, I don't know what the fuck it's going to be. It's
going to be insane. That's happening very soon. We're just going to hang out till then
tomorrow. Carl Juarez might beat the whole game. I don't know. Might not might
give up halfway through. It might be the whole thing Friday. That's right. Going four days in
a row, four days in a row of streams here. Friday after like six o'clock. Cause I have,
I've got an appointment that I have to do. So Friday at like five, six plus o'clock,
just going to turn it off and we're going to hang out and have fun about appointment.
So we're going to do four days in a row because after Friday, I'm going to be gone
for a little under a week. My mother's coming in, you know, got to hang out with my mother.
It's been like seven months, which Carl Juarez gunslinger tried to play it a long time ago
and it just didn't work out, but I will be gone from Saturday ish all the way through
into like potentially Thursday, like Wednesday to Thursday depending. So I'll be gone for
about five days straight. Give or take. I'll let you know. He still hasn't started to
play the game. I have to wait. I have to wait for criken and Nova. They don't start for like
another 20 minutes. So we're just hanging out to begin with. Why is this so laggy?
You see that? It shouldn't be laggy like this. There we go. Okay.
I think we were going to set up a little. I have everything installed now.
Let me just get in there and see if it worked. Dude, they're already playing it.
Imagine if they like, like the lie to me. Imagine they're like, yeah, they get it.
It's like a bunch of, it's a bunch of gigs and I'm like, oh yeah,
gigs and I download all this shit and they just like stop playing without me
and they just pretend I'm like not here, but we had before I'm going to open up the game.
I'm sorry, but I'm kind of stalling and a lot of money came in and
you guys are fucking too much. Thank you. Turtle toenail $50. Stop talking about the
stream. What? Dermis dong is average. Thank you Magellan. Thanks for the $50.
Fine. You got me take my money for real though. Forever grateful for your content
and we'll forever will be. I'm forever grateful for the fact that you're watching and you're
here. So I, you guys have made my literally my dreams of like when I was 12 come true.
So thank you for that. That the counter is all fucked up. It's going to be broken for like
the next 30 minutes. Everything I've ever wanted to do in my life. It's like what I,
what you guys are fulfilling that dream. So I have you to thank for that one.
But let's open it up. Let me get out of here. Let me open up black ops.
I haven't never even played this before guys. I don't even know how to play zombies.
This is, I'm going to be such a piece of crap to stream. I've never played a game of zombies in
my life, but thank you so much again to Dermis massive dong. You are too fucking generous.
All right. Let's open this up. Black ops three might be loud. Hope it's not loud.
Yeah. They're going to have to give me like a crash course in this game.
Cause I have no idea how to play it. Play online multiplayer to warm up.
I think Kraken is in like the streaming channel. I wonder what that means.
Imagine thanking your own dong. I know it's weird. Yeah. But how could I warm up?
No, does anybody play black ops? I thought there was like a joke.
No, I don't. How do I turn off the discord overlay? There we go.
Yeah. Wasn't there a meme before that like only like eight people had this on PC or
something. I hear this. Why would this be coming through my Ben Q monitor? What the fuck?
We saw that you had a Ben Q monitor plugged in. You wanted to come through the non-speakers.
There we go. So let's get this captured. It's a PC game. That sure is. Hey, there we go. Look at
that. Hey, do you want to open the store? Oh, Kraken. There is this Kraken. Hey, Kraken,
Kraken, can you hear me? Kraken. Oh, you can't hear me. Oh no. He has AirPods in. Kraken.
I hope I downloaded all this shit right. It wasn't three. It was way more than three.
Hold on a second. Wait a second. Wait a minute. Hold on. It was like 50.
Why are you just downloading? No, no, I have, I should have them all. I downloaded them. Dude,
it took like two hours to download all these. What was that? It was just fucking.
Maps only show up in zombies. Okay. Okay. Okay. All right. That's the default sound. I'm such
a bad streamer. Is there any way I can make sure that I'm like subscribed to these? Let me see.
It says I'm subscribed to all of them. Should I go? Is Kraken streaming right now?
Yeah, it says I have them all. All right. I think I just panicked for no reason.
The first 35 minutes of the stream. My God. All right. Here we go. Let me get my
settings correct. Should be starting very soon here. Stop giving yourselves a bunch of donations.
Treyarch. I'm surprised I actually have Call of Duty installed.
Re-chat. Re-chat. I'm trying to set up a video game. 2015? Oh, that's right. They make,
they made so many of these that I forget that they come out like every eight months.
Okay. Let's go to, I want to chat. Party privacy. I don't know what the fuck that means.
Oh, where's this? Where's this settings? Oh, oh, that, oh, all right. Is there a settings?
Media options. What, what kind of menu is this? Did enough $50 come in? Multiplayer. All right.
I'm going to, let's get this down a little. Voice volume. It looks good. I can turn this
up. I want to turn, let me, cinematics. Somebody wants to hear that. Subtitles on.
Multiplayer music. Multiplayer dialogue. That's because it's Xbox. Okay. Graphics.
Yeah, this is what I want. Windowed full screen. Yeah. RGB. Field of view. Excuse me.
How dare you make that default at 80. Max frame to second. Sync every frame. That's
not what I want, right? Okay. That's better. Subtitles still off. That's all right.
All right. Extra quality. Stop the bits. No, this is, okay, look, I'll do this.
Those are all late coming in. You can tell the money's just going right to his fucking head.
Game player name. What? What? Full name. I don't want the people's full names.
It's your player name. Oh, okay. All right. I think, I think I'm ready to,
I think I'm ready to go. Should I go in here and just scream at Kraigen?
Turn off motion blur. Oh, yeah, that's right. Off. Disabled. Ambient occlusion. I don't think so.
Dynamic shadow of this. Some of these are dumb, right? Which one of these is the dumb one?
I know there's at least two or three dumb ones. Extra? No, this is dumb. I don't want
any of these to be on it like that high because we're doing fucked up mods. They're
going to run like shit. AO is the dumb one. Oh, okay. All right. Let's see if I fucking
get in here and see what he says. All right. Let's see if we can pull them in.
Hello. Hello. Hey. Hey, how are you? Hey, how are you, man?
This is the, so everyone in here is currently screaming? This is the waiting room. Yeah. I'm
actually about to deafen, but uh. Oh, okay. Cool. Hey, yeah. This is the, this is the place
to be. Yeah. I'm live right now. I'll be back in like, oh, oh, say something, say,
quit, say something, say something. I'm fucking alone. That was tomato, by the way. All right.
So just, it's just me in here. Nope. Don't go into the auto chest room. What? All right. Here
we go. All right. So I said I was streaming and I scared him. All right. So what can I,
what can I do? How do, what do I do? What do I do? I've just set up, I gotta get camera,
put the camera back on. Everyone loves a cam, right? I'm not going to play the campaign.
Spend my COD points? I have 200. What does that get me? What? This is a Captain America
t-shirt, guys. What are you talking about? Home Star Runner. It could be that too.
We're going to get started real soon here. What the fuck? Open a loot crate? No,
because I don't want you guys, wasn't there a thing where if you opened up a loot crate,
somebody else could watch you opening loot crates? Was that this game or was that a
different one? Dong's account is gone? Oh Jesus. Well, I, I, I don't know what to say. I don't
know what to do. I guess we'll just see how that plays out. But I snapped him. No, I didn't.
Well, I don't know what happened to that, but I, I don't have much else to say, you know,
that it was fucking an insane amount of money. Kraken's playing? I'm in the streaming
channel right now with Kraken and he's muted and he's deafened. He's doing an introduction.
That's what I've been doing. This is just the guys. This is the introduction. This is my
43 minute introduction. Fix my sleeve. Where? What? What is wrong with you guys? What? What?
Fix your, what the fuck? Like that is like tiny sleeves. I know this is like a look.
You want to see how you make yourself look like a baby? Ready? Like I got like big
fucking shoulders, right? Kraken sent you the collection, right? Yeah. I got it all
downloaded, all installed. I hope it was 800 gigabytes. I'm going to assume. It was insane.
I couldn't believe it. Every, almost every map in that thing is worth about two gigs a pop.
I don't know why. Dude, it was like, I was telling my chat earlier before he started,
it was like I was taking buckets of water and like dumping them out of a sinking ship.
I had to, I was just uninstalling things as it was going. Yeah. That's I mean, think about
like this. I've had this shit on my computer for probably like the last two weeks when we've been
planning on doing this again. So I've been watching this like tumor on my drive just getting
bigger and bigger. Oh my God. It's going to be insane when it's all removed. Yeah. I mean,
honestly, half the stuff, I never cleaned up this collection from the last time we did it
because we never got through all of it. Yeah. So like there's like, it's like 50% trash and
other 50% like actual levels and about 50% of that is stuff we've already done. So it's actually
just like, all right. So how do I know if I have this installed correctly? Cause it's,
is there with me to like see it? Yeah. If you're on zombies, hang on. I'm logging in
as well. The easiest way is just to like join, like go into the game personally, like
a private zombies level. Okay. So like private game. Yeah. And just grab like Minecraft or
something, man. All right. So like change map. Yeah. Okay. I see like star wars, Minecraft,
just grab one song. Hey, don't look too much. Wait, what the fuck are these? Don't. Hey.
All right. Just grab one. This 70 files here. Hey, all right. Just grab one, launch it up
and see if you like what you see or if at least what did it? Oh my God. All right. I'm
going to try. I'm going to try to launch. You said Minecraft. I'm going to just see
if it launches. Get a Minecraft one. We're probably going to start with monopoly again,
though. Why did your voice do that? Huh? I forgot. It's a, it's a, it's an
Activision game. It just makes everybody's voice a thousand times louder. Doesn't it?
Oh fuck. Wait, did I do that? Was it you? Wait, was it me or you? Hello. Hey. Hey,
there's the guy. How you been? I've been great. How are you? I'm doing great. Sorry.
Wait in here in this room for a bit. Are you okay? No, we're good. We're good.
I'm just hanging out. Just being a weirdo. Yeah. My microphone. Oh God, it does.
Craig, you gotta be careful. It does things. Oh, it boosts your mic. Yep. Oh yeah. I just
watched it. I watched it at normal volume. The second I unmuted to tell you guys that
it didn't boost, it boosted to 100. So I remember. Yeah. Okay. So, uh,
Jermo, would you prefer me to call you Jeremy or Jermo? I don't want to.
You can call me anything you want. Anything you want. All right. As long as it's, it's,
it's makes sense. Germ town. How about that? Yeah, that's good. So I'll get the map. The
map works. Cool. Well, which map? Oh, you guys are testing out one. I just had him,
I just had him pick a random one from the collection because we can assume as long as,
as long as his drive wasn't full when he tried to install it. I mean, we'll see,
because it sounds like you're deleting as I was doing that. I was deleting as I was coming in.
I've been like laying down the tracks. It was like 10 gigs a second. It was like,
I mean, I bang, bang, bang, bang, bang. I was doing a Jerma, but like the issue is that I
didn't go through the collection Kraken from last time to get rid of the stuff that we did
and wouldn't go back to. So it's all just like still. Yeah, it's all just this messy.
At this point, I mean, we forgot most of the shit we did last time. So I'll probably
just like grab like stuff that still looks interesting or shit. And we'll skip the shit
that I know was complete irrevocable garbage, you know, the pseudo voodoo one was never going
to play that. No, yeah, that one was fucked, dude. I couldn't find another one that was like
that. Like that was really their Pokemon that you're better zombies. There's there's nothing
else. No, there's definitely some weird ones. I went, I did like a little,
there's one where you fight against rats and I think you're supposed to be cats. I think
I got that one. OK, there's one like TOS violations in this, like 70.
Well, there's a game of Thrones one because I had to. Oh, yeah. Oh, that's topical, dude.
That's gonna be great. I know exactly who do you think I am? Yeah, we're you know,
we're all about the clickbait here. We're just trying to capitalize on those trends.
Months. Why we're playing this Black Ops 3. I was surprised with Black Ops 3.
Didn't Black Ops like seven come out like last week? Yeah, but this is for some reason,
we're all surprised to manage to con you into joining. Yeah, it was literally like just like
today. It was just like, do you want to do this? And I'm like, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, I'll spend 60 bucks on Black Ops 3. Every other person we messaged to play this
actually like, yeah, everyone else said no. So thank you guys for there's no, you know,
there's no reason for that. You'll have a great time. I'll tell you that much.
Let's see. Well, we'll make it fun. That'll be fun. Have you what? Have you met James,
by the way, over half Xenova? Oh, yeah. Oh, yeah. Hello. Welcome. Sorry, I was muted.
Where's this bit? It's a bit. What happened to you, buddy? What do you mean? Are you on
pain meds or something? This is my voice. I'm fucked up. It's a little weird and loud. No.
Ah, hold on one sec. No, is it? No, it's definitely addressed. Why is it pitched up?
All right. I'm like having to like on the fly change everyone's audio levels.
They're fucking. Yeah, everyone. When you turn on Black Ops, like have your
microphone properties open this whole stream. Oh, yeah. Fun, fun bit. Some of these maps
will crash you not for any of our fault, but just because they're bad. And when that
happens, the game will auto boost your mic to 100 again. So it's like an added fucking
slap in the face. Also, full disclosure to cover my own ass. I personally don't have the time to
vet all these levels. So whatever we see in there is basically the extent of me scrolling
to the comments and seeing if anyone yelled, holy shit, how'd this get on? Yeah. So, yeah.
A button prepared for this one. I'm going to get a little bit of a scene change,
ready for this. Last time wasn't so bad. We played Monopoly. We played Minecraft.
Is it working now? Oh, you're great.
Except for the. Oh, Jesus. What? What's going on, man? What did you do to your mixer?
I don't know. What's wrong with it? You're fucking 13.
This is this is. It started. It's not a bit. What's wrong with my voice? Dude,
I've heard you in real life. This is not your voice. What's it? That laugh was on the fly.
What kind of computer you have hooked up? Yeah. I don't know how that computer works.
Wait, can you guys still hear me? Yes. Oh, my God. It's discord, dude.
I closed discord, but it's still up. It's like a ghost. Oh, God. Yeah.
I don't recognize this person. It's really, it's fucking me up. By the way, I sent you guys
a squad invite, the new Twitch squad. Why don't you do that? Oh, wait. Oh, yeah. Does that work?
Oh, no, no. I tried the other day. Actually, this does it. Let's try it.
So is there there's a squat. Oh, I see invite to the squad.
And then people can, you know, watch all the chats and watch all the perspectives.
And it's meant to be like a big happy family. I just hurt my mouth. How?
You invited me and I clicked on it. It hurt my fucking mouth.
I'm sorry. No, I just like I opened my jaw really fast.
It was too bad because you're excited about the invite or what?
Yeah, I just saw the invite. I like I pogged myself to death.
We can't hear James anymore. So if he's
having the one time with spoon. What the fuck? Hello? Yeah.
How are you still in the call? Is it good? No. What the fuck, dude?
I think it's starting to grow on me, though. Yeah, I kind of like this new James.
It's getting worse. I don't know how to say it.
It's definitely getting worse by the minute. It's getting higher.
Like a high wine. Oh, he's gone. All right.
Hopefully he's fixed it. This is fucking hilarious.
OK, so we get like in a team or something. Yeah, I'm making a lot.
Let's get in it. Let's get in the team. Do you ever play Black Ops 3?
Never. I've never even opened it. I don't even know how to play zombies.
I've never even opened it. Oh, great. All right, cool.
I played like the original Black Ops. I don't think I ever played
until we did this like a couple of months ago.
Yeah, another saw map by that tomato because that was that was inspired.
Yeah, we can grab them. You know how like those people
like didn't respond or they didn't want to do it.
And like I did. I probably should have been one of those people that said no,
because I've never played zombies before in my life.
Oh, God. I know the basics.
Run in a circle and a crowd of people run behind you.
Yeah. Except, yeah, that's it. I figured it out.
Some of the some of these maps also have additional objectives.
Like I think one had us in Minecraft forge a diamond sword,
which would let us progress in the level.
We had one I saw was Black Ops for you where so it's like I guess there's many games.
I don't really know how that's going to work, but this is going to be so odd.
Yeah, no, we don't know what we're getting into.
That's the whole that's the whole point. It's like it's like through let wheel.
Cool. Oh, my God.
I opened up my my Black Ops mod folder and it's this barren wasteland
because the folder is somehow full even though it's not.
Craig, you might have to do the first level without me.
All right. Are we going to invite you?
I do like I'll give you the name of one of them.
OK. Hello. You sound good now.
I'm good. No, no, no.
No, no. Are you serious?
It's you started all right. And then it was like, no.
Yeah. What the fuck is weird?
I was I was told to like deactivate my mic before and that should have fixed it.
This is crazy. Other people have had this before.
I don't know how they fixed it. This is totally intentional.
I can't I can't believe it's not intentional.
Now it's getting a little bit to the length where it can't be intentional.
Any better? Or is it still the same?
There it is. Oh, here.
Yeah. Yeah, you're fixed.
Legit. Yeah.
Yeah, you sound good. Great.
All I did was disable it and re enable it again.
Well, there you go. That's all it takes.
That's why turning it off and turning it back on.
Oh, yeah, dude. That's what I said.
Unplug and plug it back in.
Hot take one bikini bottom.
A spongebob zombies want cheese cube three.
Do you want dead?
Dude, how many fucking maps did you make me download?
There was it took me like two hours to fucking go over.
Yeah. Do you want Cobra Kai?
Do you want farm?
Do you want to see? I told you guys.
Minecraft.
I told everybody that last time I was making it up.
I picked multiple Minecraft levels.
I grabbed a lot because I knew I knew this might happen.
OK, this one's called Minecraft, like the fucking German like nine.
Oh, yeah, try that one.
That looks bad.
I mean, I told you I didn't vet any of these, but sure.
Yeah, let's hope this is good.
Get your get your get your scene change ready for real.
And wait, what do I have to do?
Why do I have to do that?
Do we have to like cut the black screen or something?
I didn't hear you guys.
No, I don't think it's ever going to get to that level.
It probably won't be to us.
I can't imagine any of those.
Like all these levels aren't ones.
These are all ones that people have played and voted for.
And there's titties in it to some extent.
Oh, yeah, you know, but we can't.
What?
I'm not saying there's not titties.
You could get titties in a fucking zombies map.
Dude, these are all modded.
Mod map makers are historically just the strangest people in the world.
Why didn't you just download the fucking titty ones then?
We may have.
You know, it's part of the excitement.
It's like you never know if you're going to get titties or not.
Why did I agree to this?
This could have been playing Call of Juarez right now.
I'm ready.
All right, I'm going to invite you.
Yeah, you guys do the first one without me while I power download the last of these maps
and I'll join for the next one.
So we're going to start.
Do I have you guys on here?
Did you invite on Steam?
Did I make it in?
Let's see.
It says you're not in the game.
Me?
No, not Jerma.
I don't know about...
I don't even see you online, James.
Do I shut you in?
Did I accept that you're in?
No, I'm in the party.
Oh yeah, Jerma's in, Jerma's in.
Okay.
All right, so let me get off camera now because I'm disgustingly ugly.
Oh, don't say that.
All right, wait, hold on.
Is there anything I shouldn't be showing?
Is it like passwords or something?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Okay.
Nope, the chances of anyone stumbling across our lobby is
uh, it's impossible.
These maps have been long hidden from the world.
Long hidden.
Hello?
Hello.
Hey.
Oh, the game like cut my mic out for some reason.
Oh yeah, the game's going to fuck with your mic 100%.
Yeah, if it closes at all,
you're going to need to go back into the properties and fix it.
All right.
If the game closes?
If it closes ever.
If the game even opens and minimizes again,
you're going to want to take a quick look.
I feel like the game just like auto-adjusted your mic
and made you like sound.
Because it did.
What?
It'll do that.
It'll take control of your mic
and it'll make you do things.
It's a parasite.
You think I'm fucking around.
Parasite.
You guys don't understand.
Wait, how do I fix this?
You don't, you just try to live with it.
You've got to go in your mixer
and change it afterwards once you get in.
Yeah.
Oh my god.
Didn't mean to call you a parasite.
Really just fucking made you all like really quiet.
This is, this is like akin to like video game archaeology.
Like we're just, we're digging through the remains
of this old game that no one plays anymore.
And we're finding these little gems from like on area.
This is truly bizarre, dude.
Okay, shift is run.
Left click is shoot.
Right click is melee.
How do you do that?
I've, I don't play any of these.
I'm going to be so lost.
Do we even melee zombies?
I guess you use the knife, right?
Is right click melee?
I don't think that's true.
Right click is aim.
Probably be like what?
F or something?
It should be V or F I think for melee.
Oh my god.
It's easy.
It's like, this was the first zombie game.
So, you know, they all could just kind of copy that.
Play one, play them all.
I like bump you guys up on everything else except for the game.
Yeah, the game messes with your mic.
So it blows us up and then we have to turn each other down.
If I minimize it, will it be fine?
Yeah, it should be.
If you can get to your mixer.
What?
Oh, there you are.
Okay.
I'm going to invite you now, James.
Is F's what the fuck?
I see no F's.
Stop saying F's.
There's no F's.
I don't see any F's.
Y'all crazy.
I think they're saying F for squad.
Oh, did I never?
Hold on.
What a fucking confusing thing then.
Also, Kraken, what the fuck have you done on that fucking RP server, my man?
Oh, I've done some fucked up stuff, dude.
Yeah, I fucking heard last night.
They were telling stories about a crime bus.
Yeah.
You know, like, you guys are like enemy.
You're like public enemy number one on that server.
We are?
I didn't do anything.
I've never committed a crime on that server.
Yes, you are.
Like, you're fucking.
You're like known by everybody.
I think every conversation that I had, they talk about the PP boys and like some
of the shit you guys did.
That's like how I guess I could gather some of the info.
Got that scene switch ready.
I told you.
I'm prepared.
You should accept the squad invite.
Just testing it out.
Make sure it works.
Launch it.
You know what it is?
I don't know.
I don't.
You go to your dashboard and you scroll down.
There should be a squad stream section and you just go to invites and hit accept.
Oh, shit, dude.
This is revolutionary.
Yeah.
Yeah, they were pretty cool implementation.
Nice, dude.
Also, Jerma, dude, I love your fucking VR stuff that you've been doing as of late.
It's a lot of fun.
Thanks.
Some of the shit that you've been your green screen stuff that you're doing the
one night.
I was like, what the fuck is this?
But it was so good.
Yeah.
The community came together and made some absolutely fucking hilarious things.
So all right.
Squad mode, I guess.
I've never I've never done.
Do I get an achievement for that?
Probably, dude.
Put that on your jacket for now.
Like a little patch.
I tried to put it on the next twitch hoodie.
All right.
I send you an invite.
You should be able to join our lobby.
Should I go change right now?
I'll go put my twitch shirt on.
Oh, I got my twitch hoodie right here, too.
Is it on?
Oh, my God.
I threw it on the floor.
I'll pick it up.
Fuck on the floor on the floor.
Oh, you hang it up and you you steam clean that and steam it every day.
I ain't going to go get by.
I don't care.
I don't know.
I just like make them go get that.
I think we're all just being twitch ambassadors right now.
Twitch ambassador.
No, dude.
I'm a stream labs ambassador.
Oh, OK.
Do you have a stream lab or something?
I have no idea.
How do I all tab out of the game to fucking get to your guys' settings
so I can bump you up?
Just go to your like your Windows mixer or go to Discord or click.
I can't even click out of your black ops.
I'm going to like it if you try to leave.
Yeah, I haven't had that problem.
And then you make it windowed mode instead of full screen.
Where's the where's the actual settings for for black ops?
Go to the menu and then graphics from there.
They have windowed borderless window.
So that'll do it.
We could start a map in the meantime to take you there.
There's like fucking in here.
Yeah.
Yeah, it'll take me like a couple more seconds to be ready to go
because my drive lied to me, but I'll be ready to go after like one map.
Yeah, I mean, we can do whatever.
How about this?
You want cracking?
Can you like just teach me how to play black ops?
Yeah, do like a warm up.
Well, we'll start the map.
I'll walk you around.
I'll give I'll teach the ropes.
Yeah.
And then, you know, bring on the horde.
Yeah, of course.
That's what we say when you're a zombie hunt.
You say bring on the horde.
This is Minecraft zombies, Minecraft, but with zombies.
What?
Beta 0.15.
They got a ways to go to release, but I I have faith.
I think they're gonna get there.
Beta 0.1.5.
Let me go ahead and take a cursory check when that map was made for you guys.
Yeah, Minecraft with an EI.
This was released in beta form back in June 14th of 2017.
It was like they didn't get the funding for this one.
They weren't able to finish it up.
One of these is going to be a screamer.
I just know what I'm telling you.
Isn't this nice?
Look, it's like Minecraft, but also a bit of zombies.
It's not a 32 bit texture pack.
Oh, what's that over there?
Hey, wait, are you already playing?
I just fixed my stuff.
What the fuck?
We just started a map.
I'm teaching this boy.
He's never seen his own pistol.
God dang it, dude.
Man, he's a natural.
Look, he's already doing it.
Headshots only.
So actually on the first wave,
you're going to want to use the knife.
It gets you more money.
Oh, that's grenade.
It's a V.
V is the knife.
It's as if somebody shakes your head.
Are you teaching him how to just play like zombies legit?
He's never played zombies in my life.
This is going to be a great first experience.
I mean, like ever.
Custom maps.
Should we clear debris?
What's the clear debris supposed to be?
I think it just opens up more of the map
so we can get more of the items.
But it costs the points to use the points
to buy better guns, basically.
Dude, I swear to God,
I've seen the same map in fucking Gmod.
This is like a conversion or something.
Really?
You'll see that a lot.
Well, this is stupid.
I don't want to play.
I'll see you guys later.
I'm starting to see why everyone said no
when I asked them to play tonight.
Oh, dude.
We were like the last invitees.
We had weaves, really.
Oh, no.
We're at the bottom.
We're at the scraps.
You guys were the Hail Mary
and you both said yes and it's like,
yeah, still on.
Oh, James got in.
Yeah, I joined in progress.
How do I?
What's the melee?
I got to refine that.
That's gross, dude.
Yeah, so we got instakill there,
which meant whenever you hit a zombie,
they die in one hit.
That is true.
Wait, are you teaching me
or are you still teaching German?
I'm just kind of teaching the room.
You know, you can listen or you don't have to.
Which weapon is X?
Who made that?
It should be Q.
Behind you.
OK, we're down.
It's over.
Fucking pistol.
Are you kidding me?
OK, well, I got my controls anyway.
Q is your special three.
Wait, your mic.
I told you, whenever you start the game,
that's like you opened your mouth
and put like the Xbox mic in your mouth,
close your lips around it slowly.
That's like the old Xbox 360 mic,
too, the fucking old quality one.
All right.
So that was pretty bad.
We're going to look for a better one.
That was probably about two gigs.
Do you buy stuff in zombies?
You do, right?
Yeah, you buy more guns
and upgrades to those guns.
Oh, so it's like Counter-Strike.
That's what they got it from.
Yeah, I stole from zombies.
No, no, no.
I'm saying counter-strike.
Yeah, whatever you want to tell yourself, dude.
Zombies was the first.
Candyland.
Wanna play Candyland?
I don't know if I want to play Candyland.
Oh, like the board game?
Yeah, the board game, but it's zombies.
Nice.
There's turkey survival.
That sounds fun.
All right.
Turkey survival?
So here's the thing.
There's clearly meme maps
and then there's potentially good maps
and there's somewhere in the middle.
Don't blow every meme map at once,
trust me, because eventually we'll run out of those.
They're going to get burnt out real quick.
We're going to run out of them.
And then we're just going to be playing cod zombies on stream.
You need to throw out a titty map at some point.
Look, we may have been promising a lot
if we promised titties.
I'm willing to bet there's titties.
I'm willing to lie as much as it takes
to get people in for a session
of cod zombies meme stream.
All right, I'll tell you guys.
Sonic zombies.
McDonald's custom zombies.
McDonald's custom?
Why would you make them McDonald's?
The amount of food brand maps that I found.
Taco Bell 2.0.
The amount of food brand maps I was able to find.
We got KFC in there.
KFC 3.0.
Pick all the food ones.
Do the food ones back to back to back.
Ashley, this one looks good.
And then we have to decide.
You guys have to talk about your favorite
favorite fast food restaurants after we do it.
Yeah, is there a Wendy's one?
There's no, I only see Taco Bell, KFC and McDonald's.
None of them will respond to you on social.
Yeah, Wendy's will though.
Yeah, Wendy's sticks to this shit.
Does anyone want to try Super Mario Halloween?
Just fucking pick one, dude.
Oh my God.
Super Mario Halloween.
This one looks good.
This one looks high quality compared to the others.
Mario Dracula teeth then.
Yeah.
You think there'll be titties in this one?
I hope there's titties in one of these.
Looking to get banned today.
Start without me for one more.
What the fuck?
This might be the long haul, Tomato.
I'm willing to sit out the long haul
to make sure it's actually fucking.
To put it into perspective,
my disk drive was so afraid of downloading the maps
that it actually lied to me
so I wouldn't have to put Call of Duty on my disk.
So when I went on today, it listed all the maps.
But when I went over to my workshop ID thing,
like the actual download page, it just said no space.
So right now, I'm using all 100 megabytes down at once
to blast every mod back onto my game.
That is too many megabytes at the same time.
Damn.
I've actually never seen Steam provide this many megabytes.
I think Gabe feels bad for me
because he's letting him in.
What do you have selected here?
We have Mario Halloween.
Okay.
Let's try to beat this one.
I think we can beat this one.
I've played Mario a couple of times,
so I know my way around the.
We've beat zombie levels on this stream.
We have.
We beat the Star Wars one.
How do you beat it?
We also beat Star Wars.
You have to pay like an absurd amount of money
that no one would ever save in COD Zombies.
And that lets you leave.
Yeah.
There's usually like a little giant.
Oh, nice.
Do they give you like a cutscene at the end?
Sometimes.
Yeah.
The Star Wars one we flew away in the Millennium Falcon.
Press start to play.
You hear that?
Oh, God.
Is that going to do that?
Why does it keep saying it?
It keeps happening.
Is it the Goomba?
I don't know.
Are the Goombas the zombies?
Oh, they're behind us.
Oh, they're just.
They're just zombies, though.
They're not.
They're just regular zombies.
There are some levels that have custom zombies,
like full custom.
This is literally just a fucking plug
for this person's YouTube channel.
I definitely do remember the Halloween Mario one.
Yeah.
Why is Bowser T-posing over there?
There was a good Mario level I picked,
and then there was this one that I picked as like the.
God damn it.
You picked another one.
I picked the wrong one.
Why did we choose to do this again?
Is that even Bowser or is that?
No, that's like one of the.
That's one of the Bowser's kids.
On the left side, the ginormous Bowser.
You're missing the big guy.
Oh, I thought you were talking about like Greco,
whatever his name is.
Greco, the famous Bowser.
It's like Greco, Beco, Deco.
They all have the same name.
And then Iggy.
I bought a new pathway.
What the fuck?
Oh shit.
Oh, you opened the path?
Yeah, I opened the path over here.
All right, cool.
What do we got?
Nothing.
Nothing?
You can hit this block and maybe get something out of it.
What?
Like a power up?
But I stopped to play my game.
That was it.
That was the only audio clip from Mario in this whole map.
Maybe we can get to if we get to Bowser,
we can get to the castle over there and we can we can win.
Somewhere in that collection is a fully modeled Mario 64 castle level.
And you guys picked Bowser T-pose.
All right, how am I supposed to know?
That's not this at all.
Yeah, was there a bullet drop in a bullet drop realistic?
The last time I shot a gun in Call of Duty,
I was like 19.
Here, hit this.
Hit this.
Pick this up.
Hit this?
Was that the times two?
That nukes all of them.
I'm just telling them, you know.
This is an early round, man.
You don't even know these strats.
Yeah, why don't you pick it up?
I'm talking Call of Duty 3, by the way, for those of you in the chat.
19, how?
I'll do it.
Oh, that was good.
That was an audio.
T-posing skeletons?
What does this do?
Let's turn on the power first.
These are not from Mario.
Should I clear one of these?
Sure, why not?
I got news for you, friend.
I just spent a lot of money.
The strangest thing about Call of Duty zombies mod maps is that almost all of them,
even if it's not seasonally, you know, accurate at all,
are either Christmas or Halloween related.
I've seen Christmas levels launched in June on fucking zombies.
Shit, you're not.
Hundreds of them.
It's like almost every single one.
So this is going to have a lot of Christmas levels and Halloween levels.
Is it Garfield?
No, that's the...
Oh, dude, do you hear that?
That was Mario's sound.
Yeah.
It's about how you can buy weapons.
I don't like this.
You're not having fun.
I'm gonna have money.
What is he saying?
The horror.
Oh.
Monopoly.
Because that's when it gets real modded.
Yeah, I'm honestly feeling...
Play Monopoly in zombies?
Like full-on Monopoly?
I'll tell you guys one thing about Monopoly zombies.
Last time me and Kraken tried that one,
I don't even think we made it past Go before we did the whole thing.
We died before going past Go.
I'm sure these guys are better, though, you know?
We've brought together the greatest gaming teams.
Yeah, these are the best.
This is like...
This is like the Mario noises.
This is just a meme.
Somebody just thought this was fun.
And you know what?
They spend a lot of time on it.
You can tell.
Yeah, come on.
Come on, some slack.
That toad is on fire.
I turned the power on.
What did that even do?
It powered up these juice boxes.
Wait, I have the best gun in the game.
I thought I was gonna do something cool with the map.
Like, what the f...
Is the best gun in the game?
I have the Wonder Waffle.
Oh, that is good.
That is the best gun in the whole game?
The best gun in the whole game?
I got it?
Yeah.
We win, dude.
Actually, did we save it?
No, there's no saving it.
Just don't die.
What do you mean don't die?
What about ammo?
Well, you can't get a max ammo for you.
Is there infinite ammo?
What are these fact zombies?
So I'm not gonna use it then.
I'm gonna hold on to it until we have the boss.
They're back here.
Boss.
That T-posing boss is gonna drop down.
There you go.
You got ammo back.
Look at that.
Oh.
There are bosses that are modded into some of these mods, by the way.
Yeah.
It's like actual full sequences in this game.
And Darth Vader knows fucking hype.
But this one, I don't think has a boss.
You keep talking about like cool instances.
I know.
I mean, hey, hey, I'm not here to pick the maps out, all right?
This is an uncurated Kraken version right now.
I'm still redownloading the mods.
I feel like I invited you guys to my party
and like only three people showed up
and then they're all just shitting on the fact
that I don't have any decorations.
You watered down the booze.
I wanted them to last longer, dude.
I know how to show up.
So I want to make sure they had enough.
Look, my plan was originally to fake you guys out
and start the map downloading on Minecraft
and then swap it last second to Kiddyland.
Surprise you guys.
Then I was going to, you know,
then we're going to switch to a nice one after that.
But the whole team has been ruined.
Well, if you didn't tell us, I would have felt for it.
I'm not the host yet because I'm still here.
How long does the zombies game actually take
did you start to finish?
Oh, it depends.
The normal ones don't really have like an end.
So you just fucking keep going.
We beat the original Minecraft one from last time
we played this in like 15.
Can I not kill this guy?
No, it was like 20 to 30.
And the Star Wars one,
I guess it was about an hour and a half.
Star Wars one was a passion project.
Yeah, that was it.
That was it.
That was a trip.
We'll, if we just keep progressing,
we can get further to the end.
And then maybe we can fight Bowser and save Princess Peach.
All I care about is Bowser.
That's it.
I mean, I can't, I'm going to shoot this into his mouth.
I don't know what this means.
Oh, you hear that?
That means there's dogs.
Dogs?
Oh my God.
Here they come.
Hold them off.
Yeah, I can insta-kill these dogs.
Leave it to me.
Yeah, it's actually bad.
My sensitivity up by like two points and it's.
Watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out, watch out.
All right.
All right, guys, my chest.
Tell me we got to wall run this.
Does anyone know how to wall run?
How the fuck do you do that?
Wall run?
Oh, get this animal.
I'm dead.
No, I'm not.
I'm okay.
I think if you just hold space, it'll do it when you jump.
But you have to be sprinting.
I mean, I just completely guess that.
I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it, I'll do it.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Does it work?
Wait, you're still alive.
Hold space.
There's no consequences whatsoever.
So no.
What the fuck?
I don't understand.
How do you do that?
I think you.
Yeah, it's literally telling me.
Oh my God.
How do you fucking jump to the other side?
All right.
There's a guy with yellow eyes chasing me and then he's
hard because he doesn't die in one hit.
Wait, do they all have yellow eyes?
They, they, yeah, they all do.
Oh, there's one behind you.
Never mind.
All right.
I'm going to try this again.
Death machine.
What the fuck do you do?
Oh, no.
All right.
I can get you.
How do I get you?
I found it.
You pick them up.
I'll go.
I'll take care of them.
Did I think, did I just use an item on you?
No, you're good.
I got max ammo.
All right.
Let's try this again.
It's almost like when you don't stick on the second part.
Yeah.
I can do it, dude.
Watch me.
How did you fucking jump?
When do you jump off of this?
Oh, just watch.
Okay.
Look forward and hold A or D while jumping wall to wall.
Really?
Yes.
Keep sprinting.
That's true.
They got it.
Hey, you got to hold.
Oh, okay.
Well, zombies are here now.
Oh, I'm dead.
Somebody save me.
They'll lose the best gun in the whole game.
I got him.
Does everyone have a little more fun?
Yeah.
This is big fun, man.
This is big fun.
And you want another drink?
What should I do?
I have $2,700.
Is that my money?
Where's my money?
Bend it on the juice.
Replace the pistol.
People are screaming at me.
I don't know.
I've never played it before.
We can get a crawler and then we can just keep fucking trying.
Yeah, that's the high level strategy.
Yeah.
Buy the juice.
Yeah, buy the juice.
Is this juice?
You're going to want to get the juggernaut one.
Yeah, get the juggernaut juice.
I don't know.
Was that the juggernaut one?
What brand did I just drink?
It's red.
Yeah, it's red.
I want an off-brand Stamina right there.
Was that an off-brand Stamina drink?
Yeah, that was a store brand right there.
Uh-oh.
I think I found juggernaut.
It's back here by Raccoon Mario.
Replace pistol.
I'm sorry.
Raccoon Mario.
Oh, yeah.
How much is this?
Here we go.
It's like 2,500, I think.
Oh, all right.
Oh, that's 950.
Okay, he just got one of the other best guns in the game right there.
I just watched him on stream get one of the best guns.
What did he get?
What the fuck is this shit?
What?
What did he get?
I don't know.
Let me...
He's got like some dual-wheeled laser beam shit.
GKZ-45 MK3?
No!
I mean, it looks cool.
I am a god.
How do you keep making this fucking jump?
Oh, crack and fell.
Learn to wall run.
Oh, I can't see.
I'm trying, dude.
I actually fucking...
Oh!
No, no, no.
I don't like this gun.
I found the same exact spot.
Whoa, what was that?
I don't know.
It's my new weapon that I locked up.
What? You got a black hole gun?
I got a black hole gun.
Of course, the guy that doesn't know what to do gets it.
Did you just fall?
Just now?
Yeah.
Yeah, I walked right off.
But I got stamina up so I can run forever.
No, I was there.
Oh, really?
I should do that, too.
That was pretty close.
That's actually a good idea.
Are we losing money for doing this?
Oh, baby.
Oh, come on.
Oh, my god.
I'm so bad.
There's only two zombies.
No!
What happened?
Never mind the pain.
Don't kill the zombies,
because then the round goes...
What am I doing wrong?
Don't kill the zombies.
I actually got hurt just now.
I don't know.
Don't hurt that one.
What?
Don't hurt that...
No!
Why?
What's wrong?
It's a new round.
What do you mean it's a new round?
It's all right,
because you got a new guy on the team, hey.
Oh, he's here.
It's me.
I'm here.
Do you know how to wall jump, Tomato?
Oh, now there's 56 of them.
I don't even know how to get to you
if we're going to be real.
Where am I?
Did you not spawn right on us?
No, I spawned like...
I'm pretty close to T-posing cloud turtle,
more than anything.
Oh, look.
Yeah.
Oh, yeah.
I may be making a mistake.
Fuck.
Sorry, guys.
My first ever experience in Cod Zombies
is Mario meme Bowser T-pose map.
I don't have time to understand.
And fucking wall run parkour.
Oh, I keep getting to the end.
I made it.
What the fuck?
I made it to the end.
Oh, what does that do?
Nothing.
There's Wario.
What?
That's it.
Get ready.
I'm about to pull this off in one go.
You guys should hurry up and get over here.
I don't have any guns.
Can you guys Luigi me over there?
What?
Luigi me?
Yeah, just like...
Luigi just does it for you
in Mario 3D world.
Oh, oh.
I don't...
I don't know what you're talking about.
That last one I can't get.
Oh, my God.
We're going to die.
I'm dead.
No.
You're my mirror town.
What?
Keep them off me.
I'm going to get you out of there.
Oh, God.
Can I do it?
Keep him off of me.
Keep the one off of me.
Yeah, we're doing it.
Oh, I don't know what's happening.
I revived.
Please don't make me go back
to that fucking other area.
I got you.
Go back.
Yeah, we're fine.
Why don't you pick me up?
I was trying to get to you.
Two men zombies pushed me out of the way.
I got you.
Don't worry.
German's distracted.
He just ran off.
No, I'm all right.
I'm all right.
There's nine zombies left.
What?
Pick me up.
But I don't want to get killed.
No, not me.
I died.
He's dead.
What?
No.
Wait.
You can die?
Oh, no.
I didn't know you could die.
There's only eight zombies left.
They're getting awfully close.
I didn't know you could actually perma die.
I thought if we all died.
Well, eventually he'll come back.
We'll come back in another black hole.
But he won't have his guns anymore.
I like slow games like pick Ross.
Sudoku.
All right.
I have I'm ready.
I'm ready to like switch over and take over the
the curating duty for this like stream.
Wait.
James is almost at Peach.
Yeah, I'm at Peach, dude.
I see T posing Peach.
How much do you need for that?
I need more money.
How much?
It's 3000.
I have 1700.
You can do it.
I can get the Peach.
I always say if we get to Peach, then we win.
How about that?
What else is called that?
I made it.
Oh, yeah, it was over here, too.
We just need the money.
We don't have enough money to do this.
How much money is it?
It's 3000.
I can make us the money, but I need someone said to shoot
the teddy bears that are hidden.
Oh, I saw one of those hidden teddy bears.
Really?
I just shot one.
What the fuck does that do?
Yeah, just got one.
We can't pull our money together.
No, this isn't a cooperative game.
Oh, man, that last jump is.
I know.
I keep falling there.
I don't know.
That last jump.
The angle.
This is a boss wave incoming.
How can you jump?
This map was just shitty and intriguing enough for you guys
to kill just enough time for my entire download to pretty much finish,
which was very nice of you.
Oh, this is so fun.
So whenever we're sick of this one, we can move on to something.
It's more so whether or not we're going to be sick of you guys trying this jump.
Hurry the fuck up and make it.
Oh, my God.
Why are you waiting for me?
I'm dead.
What?
You're dead?
Yeah, German left me.
But he made it.
Okay, I'm here.
Are you happy?
Jesus.
We got to kill the last four zombies.
They were way back there.
No.
No, there's got to be a way for them to follow us.
Nope.
You got to go back.
I think they come through this blue door.
Don't worry, guys.
I think that mapmaker had the foresight to build that mechanic into this.
Maybe, because you can't do anything with this shit.
If he had the time to make it when I buy a gun, it makes a coin ding sound,
then I'm going to guess there's at least a little bit of thought.
Okay, I need to kill four zombies.
Wait, is that Yoshi looking at Yoshi's own skeleton?
Yeah.
I'll be ready.
That's...
I'm here.
Okay, they're coming.
All right, now I just need to get to you easy.
Where are you?
At the spot that spawn.
Okay, well, here comes another wave.
All right.
I'm here with you, though.
Oh, yeah.
One of us is going to get enough money to get to Peach.
Dogs left.
Are you going to be okay?
It's dogs.
Oh, wait, you went all the way back?
Oh, yeah.
I came back to kill the zombie.
Okay.
You get out of here.
It's all right.
I'll get there.
James, do you have like good like sodas, like juggernaut?
Do you have anything fancy?
Oh, no.
I've got juggernaut and the stamina one.
Okay, then you just stand in front of me and catch all the dog mouths.
All right.
Bad dog.
I just bought a nice gun.
I don't have anything else.
All right.
Where are you?
Here we go.
Let me know if they spawn back here.
Yeah, I got you.
Now, this is that Black Ops co-op gameplay.
I was really seeking out when I conned you all.
They just the dog just went through that blue portal door thing.
Whatever the fuck that is.
I did it.
I'm here.
He did program that shit.
You sold him short.
Oh, yeah.
No, it's coming in.
You good?
It's good.
He's just going to do the jump.
Oh, intense, intense.
Nice, guys.
Nice.
Reload your guns, boys.
I'm like shaking right now.
Black Ops things.
Damn it.
You still don't have enough money to get through to the fucking peach.
Someone's close.
Someone's got to 2,400.
That's me.
Who is?
Yeah, who is?
You have 2,400?
Yeah.
Wow.
I love this.
I love the framing of this.
You see peach desperate for help.
And right above it is a YouTube ad for someone's channel.
Right above that is Mario.
And above that is a castle.
And above that is Bowser juggling boobs, I think.
Oh, I thought you said juggling boobs.
I was like, you guys have been talking about boobs for like 45 minutes.
The boob viewer prompts.
No.
Oh, fuck off.
Cock.
Look at this meta here.
They're trying to tell a story here with this mirror.
I got enough.
James is almost there.
What?
I'll wait until the pack is a little bit more lower down, I guess.
Oh, my God.
What the fuck?
Is that the waffle gun?
Yeah, I kind of can't lose.
Wait, crack.
I'm going to break down.
You're incredibly powerful.
Yeah, I'm dead.
It's all right.
You guys have fun.
I'm going to watch the peach part.
You're going to watch the peach part?
Yeah, I'm a viewer now.
It's cool.
I can come back and get you.
I don't have anything to lose.
I mean, now I'm out of time, I think.
No, I can try.
No, that's not right.
We've made the necessary amount of money.
Okay, I'm watching.
Oh, my God.
Go get peach.
I have a black hole gun, too.
I don't understand how you got every gun in the game.
I kind of just, yeah, I typed in the console.
I am looking forward to what this payoff is going to be.
If there even will be any payoff.
Payoff?
Is there any payoff?
Will there be payoff?
No.
No?
In a mod map of Halloween, Mario, you're shooting a payoff.
No.
Okay, I'm fine.
What the fuck?
What?
Go get peach.
It's time.
4,000.
Wait.
Wait, what?
It should be 3,000.
No, it's 3,000.
The other one is 4,000.
It's 3,000.
You want me to do it?
Yeah, I guess.
I'll get the next one.
Peach.
Oh, the pack of punches here.
What does that do?
5,000.
Wait, upgrade your weapon.
Oh, shoot.
I can upgrade my starter pistol.
This is one of the coolest things you can do in the whole game.
Wait, rescue peach is only 3,000?
No, it's-
No, it's 43,000.
43,000.
No.
The fucking rescue peach.
That means we have to play for like six hours.
I could keep on saving up some more money.
I don't want to do that.
That's like six hours of gameplay.
I just killed everybody in one shot.
I'm going to pack a punch to the starter pistol,
which is a wacky part of the game.
You get the starting pistol.
Hey, that scared the shit out of me.
I don't know why.
I shoot grenades.
Hey, you guys want to give up?
Hey, you know those other like 75 maps?
Yeah, I got like 70 other smooth maps we can shoot if you guys want.
Yeah.
You don't want to rescue peach.
What?
No.
We did not rescue peach.
You know, it's like a to-be-continued scenario.
But we're so close.
You're losing out, man.
I guess you could always see the ending on that dude's YouTube channel.
Oh, you're right.
Dude.
Shout out, you always win.
You always win.
That's not a bad YouTube channel name.
That's a pretty good name.
That was definitely an early like 2000 name.
I can't remember if I downloaded a bunch of his maps
because I thought they all looked like trash garbage or not.
There were definitely a couple people that I went through their entire catalog grabbing
maps because I was like, oh, fuck.
He's like, all right.
So do I make you the you win, you lose.
You always win.
I don't know if you can make me the leader.
Yeah, I don't know either.
Do you want to tell me which map to pick?
Or do you have a?
Yeah, I'll back out and tell you which one to pick next.
Okay, why are you back out?
Because I that way I can know which maps are still downloading for me
and which ones are done.
Okay.
Because there's still a couple of them pushing through.
Let's do you guys want to do a real map?
Do you want to do another shit take?
Because that's what it boils down to.
We could just kind of roll.
What do you consider to be a real map?
There are real decent maps like that Binding of Isaac one is actually a decent map.
Really?
Like stuff like A Christmas Carol, which is a decent map.
Then there's ones like Pokemon Sun Slash Moon, which I can assure you is a shit map.
And Taco Bell, which is shit.
I think one sounds pretty cool.
There's zombies and cars.
Mario Kart Edition where you drive cars.
Oh, so this is going to be a throw up stream.
Yeah.
Yeah, I don't drive car.
I doubt to do after birth.
That one sounds okay.
That one can't fail.
It's Isaac and it's actually got like challenges and like the proper rooms
and you get rewards in the right rooms.
It's all okay.
It's all like that one's a legit.
Okay, cool.
Yeah, let's do it.
Sorry, bless me.
That's not like somebody grabbed you in the back of the head and need you and think
Yeah, that was like, but bang.
Thank you.
Crack it.
We lose somebody.
Sorry.
Oh, there we go.
Oh, you disappeared.
Yeah.
Oh, I can read.
I can join mid game if you guys just start loading.
I'll join while it's loading too much data.
There we go.
There it goes.
After this, we'll do Candyland.
Candyland.
I'd like to do Monopoly again.
Yeah, I'm curious about Monopoly too.
Do you actually play Monopoly?
Do we have to actually place Monopoly?
Or are you asking in the game?
I think you make money by killing the zombies and then you pay to move the dice.
Oh, yeah.
It costs zombie points to move your dice.
It's a mess.
It's like it's rough at the very beginning too because they're going to move.
What the fuck?
What?
Whoa.
They even have the Isaac font and everything.
Dude, I told you.
I picked out some actual mods.
Oh, man, if you go into your graphics,
it changes all the font and like the menus too and everything.
Oh, that's cool.
Nice.
Oh, knife only.
I'm sorry.
Host kick noob.
Not knifeing first round.
I'm trying to help you guys out to get further here.
And I say, fuck you guys.
You guys are idiots.
And you booed me.
Okay, so my eye-catcher actually looks like me.
What the fuck?
It does.
Does that mine look like me?
Knife only.
Okay.
Do we need the music?
We like the music, right?
I think I want to turn it off.
It's all right.
It's quite ominous.
I like it.
Quick revive.
I'm going to open this door.
So do you pick a door to go through?
Or is 2000 going to open this door?
Come forward.
Who's got 2000?
That's crikey.
I will open.
Whoa, there's a chest.
Cool.
It's randomizing.
What did we get?
Nothing.
Nothing here.
There's nothing in that chest.
It's alive.
We need a key, I think.
I think we actually need to get a key.
Hey, and now we wipe and die.
It's happening.
No.
Is it still knife only?
I got a knife.
Now it's only knife only if we have insta-kill.
We all take turns opening doors.
We do have insta-kill.
So if we have insta-kill, it's knife only.
Don't have insta-kill, shoot him.
All right.
Who's opening this one?
Who's the rich one?
It opened up.
How did it open?
Oh, how did it open?
Oh, we got weapon box.
That's good.
How much did this cost money?
Give me the treasure.
Whoa, what the fuck was...
Did you guys see that thing?
There was some sort of goblin monster in the box.
Oh, no.
Hey.
Are we bad?
I think we're bad, gang.
That grenade just saved our lives.
I can do this.
Oh, God.
I can't.
Get us.
I'm trying.
Do whatever it takes.
I have no more ammo.
I have no more...
Yeah, I can crawl with knife.
I'm dying, dude.
I get in this position when I play VR.
All right.
Nice job, guys.
Somebody said fucking noobs.
Keep that thing alive.
Keep it in crawl.
950.
I won't make the new...
Yeah, just keep heading around.
We're good.
Just fucking stop explaining what you're gonna explain.
Yeah, I'm just panicking.
Dude, he's getting closer.
All right.
Buy us all some.
Open another door over here.
Hey, there's rocks over here.
If you...
Oh, God.
Apparently, the blue one, there should be an item in here.
Oh, it's 500.
Fucking do that.
Never mind.
How much is it?
I can't buy another gun.
Dude, I'm gonna get killed by this thing.
I can't...
Hey, hey.
Shoot him.
Should I shoot him?
Help.
I don't know.
Wait, did I kill you?
Get him off, man.
I don't know if I killed you or not.
Just...
No, just get me up.
Don't let that thing come.
Don't let that thing get you.
Please, fuck off.
All right, I'll be over here.
I'll be like the dog food.
I'll leave him for two seconds.
I think I accidentally tinged him.
There's a player over here on the wall that says you can draw it.
And I don't know what the fuck that even...
I'm gonna kill this thing so I get enough money to open this door for us.
And then we're gonna...
I still have a pistol.
Don't do...
Yeah.
There's more.
There's more pathways over here.
Here, I opened it.
2,000.
Oh, the power isn't here.
Power isn't here.
This is 2,000.
Oh, that's 2,000.
I mean, I feel like we need to open up some of the stuff connecting these rooms together.
I have to kill this thing.
It's freaking me out.
I think that works.
Like, I don't know how the fuck this works.
How do you draw this?
Hang on, let me see.
I'm gonna get stuck here.
I'm holding F.
I'm aiming and drawing.
I need money.
Nothing's happening.
Okay.
Yeah.
Nice.
Wow, this is like...
Oh, this is a good room.
Guys, come over here.
Good room?
This is like good shit.
You could like actually do around.
It's a slot machine.
Yeah, I just...
See?
What?
Oh, shit.
What is this?
They'll fucking lock, dude.
What is that?
I don't know.
An item?
Out of order.
You broke it.
It wasn't a weapon.
What did you get?
It was a...
I don't know.
Watch out behind you, guys.
The guy's in here.
Ow.
I think it was a shield part or something that you build.
Oh.
Yeah, there are parts in Black Ops 3, zombies,
like you pick up parts of stuff that you then construct at counters to make,
you know, into gear, I guess.
Did you see this gun on the wall?
Did you figure this thing out?
We have to find Chalk to draw that.
Keep it off him.
I need a weapon.
Present hold to draw Uzi.
Yeah.
I think we need Chalk.
I bet you need Chalk and you actually draw it on the wall.
You don't trace it.
You just need Chalk on the ground.
Oh, right here's the Chalk.
Oh, nice.
It's a gun version of Chalk.
I think we want to defend in this big room.
Yeah.
Why didn't it do it?
Did you drop a coin?
I just picked up Chalk.
Is there a tinted...
People saying tinted rocks, maybe?
It was a blue rock and you still had to buy it.
Yeah.
The fuck?
Double points.
Oh, this is fun.
I picked up the Chalk, but it doesn't let me take out the gun.
I have it in my inventory.
What the fuck?
It shows that I have Chalk.
Let me draw this Uzi.
All right.
Now we knife.
Oh, that's the 5-7 Chalk.
Now we need Chalk specific for the gun.
I'm going to open this door.
Wait, what number?
The number on the bottom left is 6.
Now our power is on.
The gun, the gun called the 5-7.
Oh, what is happening?
I fucked up, I fucked up, I fucked up.
He's in that room locked in.
He went into like a boss fight.
Why are you in a boss room?
I didn't realize this was happening.
The fuck was that?
I'm doing the boss fight without it.
Where are my friends?
Out here.
Watch out.
Run.
What the fuck?
I'm in a bad spot.
Describe it.
They're all here.
All the zombies are here.
Oh shit.
You guys have any ideas?
Hey.
How do I use those axes?
I got a DSLR.
Be known, Kraken,
that I did stay at the other side of the door
in your final moments.
Oh, thank you.
Throw it.
I don't know how to-
Oh my God.
Yeah, you can save me.
I'm going to come get you.
We're going to have to push through.
The music's gotten started now.
It started like the OG-
Yeah, I'm one of them.
Don't let me die.
I think he's going to die.
Oh, look at that no-scope, Jerm.
I saw that.
I'm dead.
Knock you.
Geez, normal grenades.
How the fuck do you throw secondary grenades?
We're going to get you out of this one, Jerma,
but you got to give me a hot sec.
I mean, actually, now I'm looking at it more.
I don't think we're going to get you out of this one.
We should be okay.
I mean, we'll be okay,
but I don't know if I can get to him.
How many more are there?
Oh, we don't even know.
There's a lot left.
Oh, look out behind me.
I'm behind you.
Come on in here.
4,400.
Just get in here.
Come on.
I'm going to die.
I'm running low on ammo, James.
I'm dead.
I'm okay.
I got some.
Nuke, let's go.
Oh, you got rid of the crawler.
Don't!
No!
Wait, I'm alive.
You did it.
Hey, we did it.
Yay.
I don't have any guns, though.
Yeah, we need to get them quick.
Yeah.
That gun's good, man.
That shotgun.
Oh, what's that one?
Oh, what's the teddy bear?
I'm sorry.
Teddy bear means it goes to another location.
It means you don't get to use the box.
Oh, the box moves.
Oh, no.
Oh, there's a sail, too.
No, a fire sail.
We cannot survive in this room.
We got to go.
This one looks okay.
This gun is so bad.
Blue rock.
We got to pay that thing 500 bucks
or it's not going to go anywhere.
All right, I'm going to you guys.
I can open this fancy room.
Oh, in here.
In here, gang.
In here.
Wait, it came back.
It came back.
Thank god.
The box is here, too.
Use this one.
I'll cover you.
Hold for part.
What is that?
I need to touch that thing.
What do I do with that thing?
What?
I don't get to touch the teddy.
What did you do to the box where the box goes?
Teddy, I didn't touch it.
I didn't touch anything.
He took the box.
I didn't press any buttons at all.
What's happening?
I wanted to use that thing.
Are you okay in there?
No.
I got a slot machine part.
The teddy bear is over here.
Whenever I walk up to something to use it,
someone has just been there
and when I try to use it, it's broken.
This slot machine is on fire now.
I'm out of ammo.
Can I make a crawler?
I don't think I can.
Why did you get out of that slot machine?
Because the second I tried to use it, it broke.
The fire still puts them everywhere
if someone's telling me so.
There you go.
You guys okay?
Yeah, but the teddy bear is over here.
I made a crawler.
You're good.
You can explore.
Hold F for part.
Does anyone know what the teddy bear does?
Hang on.
Let me take a look.
If there's a part on the ground,
I found it.
I see it.
See this?
I found the box.
See that?
See that foot?
Yeah, that's the part.
Oh.
When we get a couple of those,
you can put them together on a bench
and you can make a fancy weapon.
It's not four.
Nice.
Max ammo.
Thank you.
Rocks.
Dibs.
No.
No me dibs, please.
Oh my god.
Oh, you have grenades.
Yes.
Oh.
Yeah, nice.
Classic pistol.
Step aside, will ya?
Press F.
I want to go again.
Sorry.
What do you got?
Not bad.
What's in the mystery box?
How about I get like the half-life hand?
Where the fuck are you guys?
I keep seeing that in like some weird-
I keep seeing this fucking crawler over here.
I mean, do you really have to babysit it
or can you like sort of leave it?
It'll die on its own if you leave it.
Oh, will it?
Well, I'll trade off with you.
You go ahead.
I have no money.
All right, what'd you guys do over here?
Tag.
Tag me.
Tag, you're in.
Uh, how do I get in there?
Can I open this door for $750?
Uh, skip that one because I'm on the-
Because I'm on the other side.
Yeah, that takes us back to Swan.
Do you guys need somebody with more money
to fucking open some more shit?
Yeah.
Don't let this thing die.
This one?
What should I open?
I don't know if there's like multiple furs or what,
but there's a key door over by me.
I don't know if you can open it.
Wait, what happened to the zombie?
Okay.
How much is the key door?
I don't know.
It's over here by me.
I'll walk over to it.
But I gotta make sure the zombie doesn't get too far away.
Yeah, there's a key door here.
He's stuck on a rock.
I'm so fucking excited for that.
This one's $2000.
I'm holding in P for that.
Stop looking at him.
There's another $2000 door over here as well.
I guess just don't be careful.
One of the $2000 doors that's blue
leads into the same room we've already opened.
Because it is too much of a distance.
So make sure you don't get that room.
Oh, I see an item room.
It looks like it makes a random...
But we need the chalk for all of these guns.
Seriously?
Yeah.
You need to find the chalk that goes with...
Wait, no.
Press and hold F to pick up AN-94 chalk.
Oh, this is like you get the chalk here
and then you bring it to the room.
Oh shit, okay.
So I'll tell you guys which one this was over here.
We need Uzi's chalk.
I got it.
Yeah, get the Uzi's chalk.
Put that on the wall there.
I'll just be here babysitting the zombie.
That's $1500.
Stop getting me...
You still have to pay for it after that?
What the fuck?
Yeah.
And you gotta pay.
You gotta find it and pay.
That's a good perk that we got back here.
Mule kick.
God.
I like that everyone's getting excited for this map
because the next one's gonna be trash.
Trash.
Garbage.
I want to play Mario Kart.
What's in here?
I picked a lot of Mario maps
because they're almost as plentiful as Halloween and Christmas maps.
Why am I getting vote kicked in my own chat?
What?
Have we gotten most of the doors?
What's this music?
Yeah, do you hear it?
Get closer to the button.
I don't remember this being in Binding of Isaac.
I don't think that's a part of Binding of Isaac at all.
Hey, can I kill this stupid zombie now?
Yeah.
Yeah, we don't have anything else.
Oh, it's this thing.
Mule kick is three guns instead of two.
Oh, okay.
PhD Flopper.
Do you know what that is?
That's the one we need to be the dolphin dive.
Yeah, it blows up.
Okay, I'm gonna hang out in this big square room
if y'all want to join me.
We haven't found Juggernaut, have we?
No.
What about Stamina?
This one makes a cool noise.
I feel like the Stamina one was in that first one with the blue rock
where the slots was with the Uzi.
This map would be good for that.
Guys, I got stuck.
I'm still learning.
I can get you.
I don't even know why I switched guns.
Now, scroll.
I thought I had the shotgun.
I do.
Ow!
S-V-U-A-S.
Chalk.
Just buy my fucking custom random-
Ray gun!
Come on, man.
Whatever.
That means that my arms have never been done.
What was that?
Why is there a nuke right there?
That's like a fucking pentagram.
Hey, I'm standing on a pentagram.
It's rotating around.
Yeah, that's gonna be good.
Was that you doing that?
Check it off.
Uh, maybe.
I'm afraid to get off.
Oh, fuck!
What is that?
I don't know.
Oh, why?
Oh, fuck.
What's with the coordinates?
What the fuck is that?
Yo, there's some-
There's some sort of ghost chasing after me right now.
What the fuck are those things?
Oh, we're on-
Okay, we're on the same page.
They spawned out of there.
All right.
What is up with all the numbers?
Is that the fucking coordinates?
There's money in like-
Break these down!
What are the numbers mean?
As they come out.
This is just a Mega Man password.
Oh my god, what the fuck is that?
What?
Cranking?
Whoa!
Oh, there's like a super one here.
Oh, no.
What is that noise?
All right, I gotcha.
Oh, no!
I have no way out!
Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh!
I'm panicking!
Okay, he's-
Oh, shit.
We did it.
I'm gonna get you out of here.
Thank you.
You're welcome.
We did it.
You know, I always got your back, James.
I forgot about my secondary weapon.
You guys know how to open these yet?
More weapons.
Try hitting it.
Double tap root beer.
Cool.
Hey, can I play?
Can I play on the slot machine?
Yeah.
We'll need one more piece of that.
I'm dead.
Oh, I won!
I won!
Where's the-
Where's the gun thing?
Where's the bomb?
Crawl over here.
How do I unprone?
Crayon, how do I get up?
The same way you prone.
I don't-
All right, what does double tap even mean?
It just means you shoot twice as fast.
Yeah, fast.
Hold still.
God damn it.
Hang on.
I'll get him-
No, you get him all for you.
No!
I got a big gun.
No, they spawn behind me!
No!
I don't know if we can make it to you, man.
You're like-
Uh, we can do it.
We can do it. Let's go.
I'm pretty far.
He's like a mile away.
This grenade.
Four grenades into the chasm next to him.
I'm going for him.
All right.
We're with you.
Oh, they all go down in the chasm.
I need a new gun.
I got insta-kill.
Yeah.
Fuck.
Where's the guns?
All right, let's try to keep a couple of these alive now.
I think we're reaching the end.
Uh, we can spend some time.
PhD flopper.
I don't know what that is, but I got it.
I don't know how to PhD flop in Black Ops 3.
That was something in like Black Ops 1.
Is it like control?
No, not control.
I just don't kill any of the zombies that are still alive.
Maybe is it-
I think I want a different gun.
There's always the random box.
You can slide with C.
I don't know what that is.
Oh shit.
Wow, you can.
Where's the box at?
I got a fucking teddy.
Oh, it's right here now.
Uh, it looks like it changes spots, actually.
All right, I'm going to open this.
I don't even know if this is-
this goes to anything, honestly.
That's like the last zombie.
Wait, what's this?
Oh, god damn it.
What's this death pylon?
Oh, watch out to the earth right right right right right there, zombie!
Requires gold level initialization.
Deadshot Dakiri.
I don't know if you have that
Do you have those words here initialization? I want to open. Oh dr. Nog was in here. This is just hanging out
Oh, it hurts out of the book. Oh, okay. I'm gonna kite him over here. Oh
boy, oh
Yeah, that oh I see cuz that's like the equivalent of that spike room. I get it. I want to replace the shotgun with
The m tar the fuck is all this
How do I do the flop thing before saying okay, I just got another m time what the fuck these are like
Mass-produced these things are bad. That's what I just got. I just got one. Oh, oh good. Oh
Now there goes there. Oh god
What lady a second m tar and then flew away?
Was this the door that you guys said you already unlocked on the other side this blue door here?
That's in this blue room. No, I hang on stay there. That's a team. That's a 2,000
Check I'm gonna go to where as close as I can get to that side and see if it's actually like a space or not
Well, should we kill this guy? No, I got okay. I got a tinted rock over here James
There's no way we've been there before well somebody has enough points to open it. I've spent so many points. I do things
Okay, I'll open it. I'll
I'll take the hit
If any guys know what a vulture aid is is $3,000 and it's right over here. I
Would have spent all my $2,000 plus another thousand
The fuck oh, this is uh, it's like a super gold key room for another 2k and
Then over here we know let you see everything. I
Want to go in the super gold key room? What's that? What's that? You see that see that bottle?
The bottle shoot it. I think I think it's a part, isn't it? So what's the story?
Are we doing a little 11? Oh, how many rounds through these blues? Yeah, you see this right here. Wait, wait
Boys, they spawn random. Uh, see this. Well, I was shot fenders. Oh, it's a secret. Oh
It is a wall, but it's probably a secret wall. We need a grenade step back. Oh
It rolls
I hope
We're gonna wipe and die
They drop grenades and kill themselves and then I
This thing and I was on it when they threw them including my own grenade. I can't jump over this
Why oh my god
Well, you know that was good that was a good second time
I don't know if it's random every game or not. I'm gonna assume no
It fell in the hole. My monkey bomb fell in the hole didn't work
Hey, well black ops 3 is pretty fun game. It's first time I've ever opened it
Yeah worth the 60 bucks in three years. I hope you liked the one good map. We played man cuz
Next is Candyland. It was still 60 bucks
Yep, you think it's ever gonna drop price. No, I thought maybe wait five nights at Freddy's zombies, dude
I totally grabbed that pog dude wants to do was to put five minutes of ready hog, dude
Five nights at Freddy's
Let me see if that one's already for me yet. I
Got Candyland ready for sure. Okay, let's do can't land and then five nights of Fred. Yeah, that'll be ready after that
I think after like that level I'll be caught up
I mean, hey, you gotta give you this game credit. They made itself. They made this game really moddable
For I'm surprised you can put this much stuff in here. Yeah, it's I mean, I think that's I think it's really impressive
It's a shame. They'll probably never let people mod a game this much again. All right. I need more alcohol for this
I'm gonna get it be back
Man, everybody's drinking. I'm not drinking my drink right here. Oh, it's minute. You're not in the lobby
Huh? Oh, yeah, I was gonna join when it was loading because I was making sure still I was ready to
Just press start. I'll join while it's loading
Candyland KJ
We got to play this seriously though. I'm not gonna let you guys ruin the only reason I did this session. Okay
For this map. Yeah, seriously take the board game once like seriously or else I'm gonna be mad
There's a dabbing zombie
Take that slum. He's not joinable. Oh my god. He locked me out. Hey take this seriously
Dabbing zombie on the initial screen. Yeah
They cut out like the fucking oh my god, dude
There's an evil cookie monster here. Wait, that's candy from fucking Donkey Kong party is over here
Hey Kraken, uh, can you invite me again? It's not she letting me in this time. Okay
challenge for you
What the fuck is this?
They're they're crawling over. They could the candy zombies are here already. Whoa
You don't have a knife you pistol
What was that?
It's right here. You can get this for free. Oh
Wow axe, oh, I don't think it's gonna let me in
Really? You have to go back. It says I'm in the lobby and maybe it's just he to throw the retrievers
You guys are ruining candy man
Yeah, totally bugged I can't get it, okay, whoa
That's loud. I
Want to beat this level you guys down?
We can do it most a lot of cookie monsters six kill, please, please
They didn't play candy to land a lot when they're a kid. Oh my game
Can't lose this level or it will yes, I see you found the dark
I didn't actually know it was this one to be fair. I knew eventually we'd find one
So everyone's voice is gonna be loud. Oh, yeah, we should probably mute and fix it
What's wrong we just you know play a play a little bit of danger game
It just happened for me
Oh my god, all right coming in yeah, correct and you can continue to host those since I'm still technically downloading stuff
See if they let's see if my mic explodes, why am I getting the beginning message for black up?
Who said that?
You're so quiet you turn this whole microphone down till I can muted. Oh god. Okay. Is my
How's my mic I'm gonna be very quiet for you guys, you're all right. Yeah, you're right
Yeah, I can't win it really low
Also your party is private. Oh wait, never mind. It's good. I'm in all right. I am in as well this time
All right, how about now?
Good
Just wait a minute how the fuck sin how is James a level five and I'm only a level one
I thought like zombie levels were different
Did you play the normal maps? Yeah, I don't know man. Screw you. I always knew you were
Specifically invite people that wouldn't be better at this game than me and you've been in there. I'll be try hard, dude
You have like different perks and shit and like different bubble gums
Yeah, I know that's how try hard I am
I'm ready for an invite. I'm ready for an e-vite if anyone's gone. You got it
I'm starting to learn to play. I
Have I have fucking I'm pretty sure
Pay to win you have to actually purchase them
Gum on my character like actual like super perks. They had to pay money to get I got them for free
But they cut they technically cost money. That's how try hard. I am
Don't know
Got an in with Activision
Okay, so don't lose this game, right? If we lose we
We crash and we get loud. So
Permadeath, I mean it's not possible to lose candy land is the thing. So this shouldn't be that hard. What do I want for food?
Oh, yeah, can you land? Should we just like to roll the dice get enough you win?
There's no choice. Thank you, sweetheart
So this this map has like the same fucking system as the I don't know
Oh, yeah, that's on the is dabbing, huh? Yeah, that's a dabbing zombie. That one is dabbing also very poorly cut PNG these like yeah
It's all fucked up the old one 1911. All right. I'm ready. We ready. I can't are we
Hi, my name is candy. Oh boy. Do I have a challenge here for you today?
But most importantly remember have fun. Good luck. Thanks candy. That's cookie monster
That's some next level get around. It's candy. Oh candy is the girl next to him. Oh
Her boobs say candy. Come on open. Oh door
All right, what they they they're coming in. What is this voice? Yeah, what the hell was why does my guy have?
Elbows where his ears should be when he looks down his sights. I don't understand this
Promise you guys titties or what? Hey, we deliver. Don't we they go?
Lump me in with you in the way that we can't go through here until we have 1200 bucks
That's a lot. Haha
What is this?
Alright, this is a fucking schizophrenic map, dude. I'm freaking out. I have no
Just make some fucking money's blue guys almost got enough. Who is it? It's probably what James?
I played VR chat last night and like this. I'm doing it again
This is like the same map
Okay, let's let's get a roll. We have three candy sticks. I just did it. What is all right happens now we
I turned on the power. Okay, that's good. That's the power
Wow, I love this game
How do we try to pay more money?
What about this one you guys think this is crazy get ready for monopoly just I was got real
Front door front door under the rainbow the rainbow don't have any recoil these pistols
It's really actually kind of weird. They don't yeah, it's like
any bounce
All right, I got money. Oh you got to okay, so we pick
Okay, I bought the I bought the mp5 and it's neon
Do you guys see this? Yeah. Oh, yeah, that's like I'm missing texture get like a slimer done
All right, I'm gonna buy this one, too. We just gotta keep moving. I
Can make some I'm gonna start fucking piling up behind us. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, this is bad
Coming in blood why is soup talk on my screen?
Dude the pistol whips are still one-hit kill by the way, are they okay? Yeah
Revive I don't know what I should be buying
All right, I'm scared I got an m16 to me. Yeah. Oh man, that's a nice gross
Let's do it
What is that what's on the ground? What is that? Oh
There's like those are not dogs, dude
It's already here are they bunnies it's a bunny a giant bunny look sort of like a frog. Oh, yeah, that's a bunny
bunny frog
They're really floppy
This is a bumping mix I like
The mix how are we stuck right here? What do we need? Oh?
Let me kill this next time it's gonna sell my I could get it. Yeah one more. Oh
Whoa spawning in front of us. How much is it to get out here?
19 long fucking around. I'm out of him. Maybe you're just supposed to buy your way out of this
Hey, you got it. Hell yeah. Yeah. All right, who's gonna buy this one James? I volunteer James
God damn it. You don't bought every single one
You also have three thousand dollars, huh?
You gotta spend your money more quickly. This one's germa. Oh, I was gonna get this. All right, I'll get my wait
Never mind. Oh, I don't think you could have afforded. No boss. Oh, we can't reach yet
It's on the other side
I'll try to get the next one
Well, we almost beat it. Oh, there's a game cube over here. That's fine. That's candy beans
I don't think these zombies can cut across the invisible walls
So they have to go down the whole thing and they can spawn on us though
They can't spot like he's they're cutting across these guys. Those ones are fresh fun. Oh
No, these ones jump over them back
So they can't spawn in front of us, but what is this terrible PNG of blood?
Yeah, it comes your whole scene hit twice because your screen becomes a terrible blood PNG actually one when I went down
It was like all blood. It was like a solid JPEG. I'll get this one speaking of bad PNGs
Look at the seven in the bottom left
I can see the outline of why you the white outline. Oh
We just spawning a whole rounds here over and over again every time we open up a cookie monster is it spawning stuff
We're just getting further in I'll get the next one. Yes, please my money
It's like
Hey works for me, I'm about to win this thing we're feeding their souls to this thing
Where which this this big battery looking thing?
See. Oh, yeah, let these zombies get to this. Oh good. Let me get this
One hours the perks. Yeah, these weird like pylons. I got this man
It's just all they're gonna be so what's going on is that roblox what kind of chicken where something roblox up ahead?
Wrap
Beef chicken we have to keep going
Did I need money, how do we get the one up here? Oh
Which juggernaut is here juggernaut?
juggerpock
What if you get will be delicious?
Okay, there's a watch I meant did I just kill us it's the kill it's the kill no, okay
I thought it was accidentally killed her buddy double points
Everyone knife. Oh
Well
You know, dude, I'm not ready to
Do you hear that what was that? Yeah, I was like looking at discourse. He was making that sound the box
I open the box. What did it do?
It's a song a really weird song
I don't have anything spawn right in front of me. I'm hearing it again. Oh
South Park you
Did south? I'm gonna buy it again
Wow, what's sniper?
I
Remember that part in candyland my favorite board game. Well, they're going to candy mountain
Was that the dudes from this I told you every map is a Christmas map
Christmas
I'm gonna go get this stuff. Hold on
Was that an in-game like actual voice line that somebody says or is that I think that was that was one of the characters
Yeah, everything is modded to me. So I don't know what the I
Guys I'm running back to get ammo, please don't let them kill me that guy's gonna die out there. Oh
Disappear when I got there. I'm back. I don't think he's gonna make it back
Whoa, hey, whoa, this dude. Whoa breach
That's it I'm getting back home
You got a fucking death machine
Yeah, she's just like a sniper. Love it
I'm like, I don't know. I'm counting on my team to keep these fucking zombies. I have a sniper man. There we go
The one place you saw me can't be allowed
I'm following craig and down the way. Wait, is there like an invisible wall stopping me from shooting these guys?
Say for the job
I made him back jug is here. I don't have enough you guys need some money. You're loaded. You should buy our way through
huh
Somebody said wow somebody by the job stretch. Yeah, if you don't have job by job. Yeah, I don't have enough money
After this round whoa, we're gonna wipe and die it's what no, this is way more than it came up the last time
It happens so fast by black ops bye-bye there was like a hundred zombies
Everyone say bye to black black ops
Greg and you are at least like one time is better than everybody here. I'm one time is better
Well, I got my big I thought big machine go to the end that's
I'm not crashed dude. I'm good. All right, you didn't crash. I didn't crash Wow, I did
Everyone but the host usually crashes
I'm stealing host doesn't crash. All right
Everyone and everyone's chat type one if you want five nights at Freddy's type two if you want matrix reloaded type three if you
Want zombie cat tree type four if you want turkey survival?
Type five if you want bikini bottoms zombies that one one saw three final chapter. All right, let's tell him up
Watch your microphones. Oh, no, you guys are gonna get loud again. Yeah, I just caught mine when it boosted
before I talked
It's like the second the game window opens. I will say the saw ones are usually inspired
saw ones
I feel like they were so inspired that I think we forgot already having done this one and just completely
Like forgot about it because I'm pretty sure we did every song
To really to
There's there's burger time zombies v2 also, which I definitely did that one. No, no, it's positive
We did burger time burger version two not version one
Let's see, all right connected online seeing a lot of fives and ones in my jet, okay
Probably more fives than ones. Okay five was
five was
Well, I don't remember but you know, I think I think it was
Which is either bikini bottom spongebob zombies this was bikini bar
Okay, I can't guarantee the how good that one
I can I personally vetted every single one of these levels to make sure they were
The absolute peak of quality that we come to expect from black ops 3 co-op
Seems like they want the spongebob one. That's why you can find if you scroll through the list
You'll find my favorite map cheese cube re cheesed. Yeah cheese
Look good
Actually, I'll tell you what there's a shockingly massive
Like subsection of black ops 3 map makers that are just obsessed with cheese cube
there's like a billion let maps called cheese cube and then like
Colon and then a title. Well, I'm obsessed with cheese cubes. Have you ever had them before they're pretty good. I mean like
Like Swiss cheese cubes. They're unbelievable. I mean, I'm just trying to think of why why that's a black ops 3
Like, you know why I have so much presence there
Maybe there's some kind of in thing with their their community. I
Mean like I'm let me just take a quick trip to the workshop
So why are we getting mine? That's not a joke. Oh, yeah
Me either cheese. I just like the Swiss cheese cubes of it. Well, we're gonna see joke
You guys also want to do the Game of Thrones map before Game of Thrones isn't cool anymore
Yeah, we got like we got like four or five weeks for that
If you want to come back to this game
No, we don't we don't do this more than once every like year
Yeah, I mean it might as well be when was when did we do the last one it was I think it's over. Yeah
So now we're gonna version if you've never seen the Game of Thrones that this is not it. Okay, what's the spongebob?
I'm like, oh yeah
throat spoilers
This is a new version there is also about 20 different spongebob zombies maps that all look the same stuff I just grabbed one
Okay, I don't know if this was the real one, but there are oh, we're under the ocean
We see this huge
Yeah, I mean humans are probably really big to spongebob. Oh, yeah, that's right. He is just like a wow the flying Dutchman
What the fuck?
Taking care of Wow, you get hit markers whenever you shoot one, dude
Whenever you shoot when you get that nice click
Dude I love that. Oh, I found the power. Oh, that's nice
Dude I love that
Mark, is there like a light blue? Are they just different colors just different color?
There's just different popsicle flavors of the flying Dutchman
Why why is this the only level that we played so far I think I think ever that has hit mark
zombies, I
Don't know
nice, dude
My eyes are adjusting to all the green. Yeah and blue
Yeah, hey
What are they doing?
Cheese cube re-cheese friend that one that one will be the finale to them. I'm gonna come behind us, right?
What is that? It's like a zap thing. I got like a lightning. I don't know what that did. It's a bomb
explosion
Does someone want to go visit Larry the lobster, I love Larry, okay
It's too expensive. I don't want to go there. Just Larry. No, I'll do it. Where it's right here
Got all the girl fish around them. Oh my god classic Larry
I mean half those are definitely men fish. I can tell I know my spongebob more. Oh
So satisfying when you hit oh
What is that? I don't know
It's like a heart
music
Whoa? Whoa? Whoa? What? Why you guys want to go see Larry? You like a trail on you me? Yeah
I don't know what that means
Like you're like what's a trail see that see that like cloud
The sort of stench around no no keep that one live for me. I didn't do it. I didn't do it this time
I didn't do it. I mean nice. Come on. I opened the way to Larry, okay
Yeah, I got us to Larry. What is this? Hey, we open this way, too
Yeah, we have two ways to go both sides when I bought it. Oh, there's a golden spatula over here
Dude, look at how much fun all these guys are happy bang bang. Oh need the power for I got the power
I guess it doesn't work for this one over here that guy drops power up
Different power. What's the handcuff power up?
Handcuff
Continuity there's a lore continuity to these maps because there's also a map made by this guy
I think that takes place in rock bottom, you know the place below
Are we traveling there? We're gonna go there after
No, we're gonna play the whole story. We got to get the story. I'm gonna see every episode. Oh, we're almost the Krusty Krab
I'm going in
Krusty Krab
There he is. Mr. Krabs. There he is T posing like always like every other every other model in these
He actually does T pose a lot in the show though. Should I get a new elbows always like out?
Which one of these is worse?
Weapons, I don't even know what I don't know what a good weapon of bad weapon is
Okay
James you're the only one I trust to save me
Where are you?
Way by Krusty Krab
Dutchman number 25 kicked my ass
Yeah, I'm getting some points right now
There's a box over here, yeah, I mean I also need money somehow I'm stuck with 20 bucks right now
What is our objective here? I'm really having a hard time Krusty Krab
Yeah, all right that checks out wait how in the fuck is this the first level you've been asking what's our objective
This is like every zombie
Is you open doors and then move for like I've never thought of like spongebob is like a what is that?
Oh, is everyone slow motion? Yeah
Yeah
All I hear is the clicks dude, I love the silent gun. Yeah, all I hear is the
Holy shit
Why that they're like just in slow again. They're all standing still. Yeah
Yeah, we got like some sort of like
the hourglass power up
Yeah, get whatever you can
We should get like a crawler first or something. Yeah. Oh the ray gun. I I'm gonna go to Krusty Krab screw you guys
wait
Manta man's here that stays until I die, right?
Yeah, when you go down wait, not when you die. It's all over you lose it Squidward
Juggernaut is so good
What was that zombie cat oh fuck I
Got zombie cash and then the fucking box went away guys. Get over here. Get over here quick
I got something to show you. Oh, there's a soul box for tips. Oh god
Taxi over here. I'm here. All right ready watch this
Start Squidward
What we do? Okay, what do we do? I don't know
Maybe oh, that's a car there
What was this for? I just okay and keep going
What the fuck was the point of this dude? I don't know. I don't know and then we go this way
This sucks
Who wants my gun? Oh, I don't want that thing. Oh, there's a
There's another power thing. We got turn on here
Damn, I don't remember this part in spongebob anymore. We need three keys cracking. I found what we need. Okay
It's trying to get to the what a castle
I don't remember there being a castle in spongebob
So each perk also has the power on the side of it to active. Oh, you can trade weapons in this
Oh, there's a golden ice cream. Gold ice cream. Yeah, okay
What what do we do? Oh my god, I got zombie blood for some reason nice
There's a trading bench here if someone has like a good weapon they want trade to someone else
Do you guys want the do you guys have enough for the pack of punch?
Cuz I could open this gate. Yeah, I'll save that for now. We're all bankrupt. You must turn the power off first
Oh, I have no weapon. Is there you see the box anywhere?
Fuck and see the other side of bikini bottom on I'm gonna finish this tax. We're out there. Yeah
What no, where's the juggernaut I ran all the way back here to get all I actually have no idea cuz it looks
Like it's using a different model for this mod
Killing zombies here this box
Wait, wait, don't don't kill him up there kill him near this box. It looks like it's taken this way straining into the box
Whoa, yeah
I'll cover your back. Go get him. I got him three nice two one
Somebody down here. This is the wall. This is the gear check. I don't know
I don't know where the fucking where's the money boxes in here. I don't know where the box
Should we open this door?
Let's just open whatever we see that you can afford because everything else is like 5,000 bucks
I'm gonna find a key for this is power. Look, there's a part. Oh
What does that turn on upster power?
There's some another bottle thing here for electric
I I wouldn't buy anything that none of us recognize like from the like word of it
I oh wait, I know what electric sure is when you reload it does like an electrical like
Circuit that hits everything around you. That's pretty cool. I mean I got two grand. Maybe you get electric cherry
Down some electric cherry through your closed scuba diving visor. I need ammo though
Ammo what's the range on it? I think it's well, I mean if you if you shoot one bullet and then reload it
I think you can see
Yeah, it's like to about where I am right now from you. Oh, wow. All right. Oh, that's a gun
It's pretty good for a guy's getting on. Whoa, that's great gun. I need to get I need to get a wall gun
So I have ammo fuck's sake
There was a gun around here on the wall
We're gonna do we're gonna get together because with the just spawned on the wrong
Yeah, this walls get this wave is gonna be awful
Let's do it by Krusty Krab. Yeah, I'm at Krusty Krab. I'm really sure I don't know where the keys are
Yeah, I've been using any keys. I mean, there's another road by that castle
No, so many hitmarkers amazing
God damn it. I don't know what the fuck I was doing. I was trying to kill everybody. Oh, I
Don't know. It was like the range and I was like, I don't need to do it. Oh my god. What an idiot. I'm
He had the fucking bloodlust in his eyes. I think that happens
Hey, look over there. It's an item go get it. I need it
I
Was to be cash. I thought I could go and like electrocute him and kill them or something
I don't know how much damage it did. It doesn't do enough that you're gonna be killing zombies. Yeah
It's all right, I'm just an idiot
Hey, I mean, hey
It's all about you're getting better
There's a there's a box over here. Oh, I think yeah, there's a box over here. Yeah
Oh fuck the round just started as well. Oh
You guys
I'm behind James. You're here. We just go to this castle. I guess James because we're split
It's just you and me cracking. All right my box
See this road here. We never went down this way. Look here boss. That's where they are. Hey, it's where it's at
everyone get box
What is it? What is it? Any keys? Okay, what's worse? There's only seven or m8 a1. I don't take that
It's a shitty shotgun. What?
Don't take shotgun. I don't take it
Let it melt
That's all I could afford. I think I figured oh behind you behind you
behind who
Everybody
If you want to use it again, I'll cover you if you have enough for I don't
Know
They're coming. Hey guys, I think I know where the keys are
You see that seat right across this barricade here that little box those things eat souls
There's one by the Christmas crap that I was trying to fill up. I bet if we fill it up with
No, oh my god
I love all that. Oh, what happened? We're going down. No, no, no, no, don't say that. Okay
Really need that times two. Oh, I think we're good. Oh, this is awful. Here's my work
Has anyone seen a juggernaut? I don't think
Thing sucks. Yeah, that's
Help you know fucking rocket. I mean rockets are shit. I'm not super thrilled about this thing
Got a lot of ammo for apparently there's a juggernaut by the chum bucket
Might be worth an investigation. Okay
That's the bacon mark chum bucket
Where's the chum? Oh, it's right next to the it's right there. I see it down this room. What the fuck?
Wait, why we need a crawler? Oh, I didn't realize that was
No
Shit, where is it over here? It's up here. We should do this anyways, cuz there's a box here
We need to get souls into I have no way. This is the chum bucket
chum bucket
Juggernaut was near chum bucket somebody said over here. I have no ammo come this way cranking. I'm covering you
Right on me. We know Tommy. Oh, there's anyone has enough money. I do I do
We want to kill stuff by this box. I think that's how we get the keys
handcuffs over there
boots
There we go
I am a god. Oh, I got missile launchers for this. So what about my accuracy rating? Who cares, dude? Just who cares?
You got I think you shot
You head right in my face then a missile hit another dog, baby. There it is
Let's just do again extra power
Extra hits before you go down. All right, just don't kill the car. There's one right there, dude. I'm gonna cut this one
That's a normal one. It's fine. He's never gonna catch me. You guys do you got to how you guys doing on ammo good?
I'm bankrupt. So I need something to do with my time. It's it by new gun cause that ammo
Hey, all right, it looks like I'm the only one with fucking 98 hundred bucks
Yeah, I've been waiting to fucking buy stuff, but you guys keep killing the last one
Go go buy it. I'm going where should I what should I buy?
I mean if you kill this thing, you can actually have enough to both open the pack a punch door and pack a punch
Probably or be close. I could open the gate. It's over here. It's by the gate
I just cast do it do it do it all this cash
Would that would that push you up enough is that would that get you 180 if you like our every hit on this guy
Punch, I don't have enough. It's I'm on
If you shoot this guy like a couple of times in the body then finish him off with a knife
What is this percacola? You can get a percacola over here
That a random perk
dig dig
It's loud it's loud it's loud it's loud it's loud tell me to dig
Hey
He's getting in here. It gives you a random perk on the road. You can dig on the road
You know James. I genuinely think if you shoot this thing like a couple times and knife him you'll get enough for dig
But do I but is there any more progress that we can do with money?
No, no, I think you should buy a good gun. I think it's time to get
You guys seen this dig
Somebody said they dig I see it. I see it's just a skull. I know I've been doing that all the time
It doesn't look like it doesn't do it. No, okay. I did it
Well, I think I'm the only one who got the hang on
I'm gonna run around with the shovel and dig all this stuff. Oh, I got one
I just got one you got a key. So they're in okay. The keys are in the skull part in the skull piles. All right
It's a search around before we kill this last one
Yeah, I don't know about you guys my chest has literally just been quoting spongebob for the last hour
What'd you expect? Also, I mean we've only played for like 20 minutes. So it's sort of weird. They've been going for
It's really like spongebob, dude
Your place is safe haven for their community 2000. I got one key here. So
Squidward
What is the fucking pile look like follow me? It's a weird muddy skull pile like bones and dirt mud
debris
Ah
Am I just follow? Yeah, I'm just following cracking because of me. I got no money and I got no money either pal
We're just kind of walking around
You found one is one yeah, there's a there's a pile here if you want see what it looks like
It looks exactly like a pile of garbage with bones in it. There's a wait
Wait, oh, that's not it
Wait James, we got open this the store over here. See that. Oh
I'm gonna get anything out of that one. Yeah, how many keys we have keys? I
Got one. I'm gonna kill this motherfucker. All right, wait
Cuz I'm getting bored do I want to move on oh you're getting bored
I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die. I'm not kidding. I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die. I
Was locked myself with the boat and I was died it's easy to do that
Well, I don't I didn't see any more places to get keys which makes me believe that it's still that those like soul
Boxes crying I dare you to shoot him
Okay, you did you actually did?
All right now do you need to shoot him?
I still didn't get enough. No, all right guys open this open this
Key, okay. I'm telling you guys the rest of them. We got to kill zombies near these boxes
Those take the souls of the zombies. Oh bad. That's true
All right, I'm pack a punchin max ammo. Oh my god, what the fuck is this?
Are they behind me? Yeah, there was
They're behind you guys well my leg that was the worst
Yeah, I've seen the pop-up before too I got the bridge
They're spawning you all behind us. They're trying to spawn behind
Markers. Oh, oh it gave us a nuke. All right, these things are garbage. We don't need them
We're gonna have to hunt these keys
Creativity and ingenuity. Okay, so there's another way to our right. Yeah, right here. Okay. Oh, there is
Packing pack a punch. Oh shit
Pack a punch M16
Wait, don't kill
Why?
Oops, oops, oops. Why are you this way? Wait, what do you what do you need? I want pack a punch
Pack a punch you need five thousand. You put it back in here. Oh, I only have four thousand
Put in whatever gun you want and it'll like make it a super a super gun. It'll be objectively
Nice. All right. Yeah, I'm gonna try
But then definitely don't die cuz you'll lose that. I will
Be like fail fish is like every five seconds. Yeah, I'm gonna do it and 16 right let's do it
Dude, no, this is giving me some hit markers completed
Completed what I finished the the route taxi. I'm gonna go back to super again. I got a legendary
How do you know that dude? You want to play even press F on this?
trade your pack of
Keys what I want to see if this is possible. All right guys, I'm pretty sure can you put it on there?
Yeah, I can cheese. Yeah, that's bad
So it's a crawler don't kill the crawler this time's a
How do I do it I don't know if we can make it to
Someone's gotta keep them off me. I go for you. Keep them off. There's no spawning here as well behind you
I'm not gonna be able to do it. I mean, there's no one here. I mean there were people
That's why I was to 50% health right away. I got me baby
Alright, so I got the second key crawler right here
I'm okay sure
I wasn't just gonna do that if I didn't know good
The binding of Isaac level I'm not gonna jump off
Here I think we've got a feed the souls to little shiny boxes cuz we've gotten two keys two different ways
I think it's the third way
Pathway that you opened is that it that's it the race. Yeah, all I got all we got from the shiny box
It was here was a nuke
Yeah, but we didn't get anything from the other holes that we dug. So
You don't want to do one more pass through and look around. I'm
Unity here sure nothing else is viable
nothing is double-tabble
double-tap over there by you cracking
I think was bomb stoppers. Oh bomb floppers bomb floppers. That's what I did when I killed us all into Isaac one
I think double-tap was by the beginning was it all the way back there
I'm over here. Now. I'll look for you. It's quick reload around here
Over by me is double-tap German get that
Way, oh, that's a long pretty pretty pretty close to oh, I fucking bought the wrong one
That's a kick in the pants guys. No, I'm not gonna get you'll kick. I'll get something else. I
Just get the random one
Random one is pretty good. If you have enough money to just like
100 of them might as well bang bang. There it is double-tap. Oh my god, that's loud
What?
Is there any paths we somehow miss was that quick reload that I just actually get creek fucking reload what the fuck
All right, we're gonna put our
That's amazing. I don't know. I was trying to see if there was any like paths be missed because we're still
That's okay
Little box that I know I know there's one box that's over here that I had to buy a thing to get to some pretty
That's it one box by the Krusty Krab. I'm gonna get one box that shows that maybe it's one over here
Well, look, I had to literally it's the corner of the map and I had to buy a way to get into it
There's nothing else here. So I figure if anything
Inside the car, what was that?
James what no. Oh, I thought that was a zombie. No buying perks
Okay. Hmm
Electricity electric cherry was good, but I only used it once
Yeah, electric sure is really good when every other perk is stacked with it because you're like reloading faster and moving faster
So you're headed more shit
If we make it through a couple more rounds without going down, we pretty much what is that go?
It's the widow one. I don't even know what the fuck the widow one does
That one gives you a special kind of grenade. Oh
Watch out the guys are still if you just stepped on the crawler
Their cluster grenades, ooh, maybe the race is to get the key
He got one from the race. Oh, they already got one. Okay. Yeah, why is he not aggro bastards confused?
He doesn't know who to go after anyone
Fuck I can get one stock here the boat
I'm a kill. I'm a kill him
No, try to stop me stay away from him try to stop me rip. What the fuck is that one?
Wait, did you get tombstone? It's rip
Yeah, when you die, you're gonna drop a tombstone, which will mean that when you've respawn you can recollect your perks
Nice
Over here guys turn left if there's one thing I know it's call of duty black ops 3 perks and
Their various this is where the shiny box is. Oh
This place already filled up though. No. Oh, this is this
Camp in this corner. Yeah, this is why I've been telling you all along
90 I'll believe me. I
Still don't want to do
How many got a kill
You see those little orbs that go into it those are their souls
My god get your face out of my face
You would think that it has enough by now. Yeah, it's got like a hundred people
Yeah, we gotta wait sir closer, how could you tell when it actually got finished
Disappeared there's a pickup
Boots
Oh, wait, wait, don't don't spam this. Oh, it disappears gone. All right, it's gone. Oh, what'd we get from? Hey
Do you get any items? Oh, it's only something cash. Oh
Behind you behind you we gotta get out of here go to the Christmas crab advantage of the sail
We had a sale apparently there another one get it I didn't pick it up. Sorry. It's yours
Somewhere right? Yeah. Yeah, it's oh and the box here too. I put a lot of work into that box
This box should be ready to go
What is this? I have money to I'm gonna buy
This looks future let it reach the box
It's like nowhere to someone should watch the back just oh, yeah
This way
And then it's it for now. Well, unless there's one maybe like a
No, there's a couple more
Electricity thing now. I'm gonna get this again. I might get it, too
Yeah, there it is
Souls complete reward is in the spawn zone. Yeah
Let's stick together here
This is gonna be it. This is gonna be our key our key out of here
Is this gonna be one key? Oh or it's gonna be three guns
What's three guns? I can't wait for this to be what kills me. What's
The round isn't over yet. Ah
Yeah, there's more people's being over there pack a punch holes. Okay. They're good though. Yeah
These are high tier guns
Alright, we're hiding here today. Let's get that fucking key
They fucking spawn right on top of us. What the fuck we don't have any other options. I
Don't got it somewhere in there. Oh, they're all gonna strike
Wait, there's infinite ammo. I see it. We're gods of a little back up. Okay
I got it. It was Max and the time warp. We're good
We're free with this much ammo in the chamber. How can it be?
There's only behind this again
Nothing fine over towards Kraken because I I'm too strong
Where is the where's the junk dog thing? Oh right there. I'll take a left
Nice you don't you just get a couple of times turned around looked at me
All right, we gotta figure out what this oh, you gotta beat this love there
Or let's think who have you not talked to who who's not giving us a quest
Larry Larry's had Larry's been keeping his mouth. Whoa
Larry the lobster Larry looks like he's pointing at some dude. I just watch you kill a crawler
I just watched you pointing run up and kill my crawler. Are you talking to me? Yeah, I'm talking to you
No, you better not be talking to me because I fucking saw you do it. No one else here
You guys have a crawler over there
Last one just blew up your crawler. No, we don't have one. Oh, okay
There's a running crazed guy over here by me. So leave that guy alive
Drink what is this? I'm gonna pack up. I'm so loud. Oh, it's loud. All right, it's
Holy shit with the pack a puncher. It's like over by the key to it. All right, send it
I have ten thousand points. I'm gonna need more perks
Any more drinks dude fill up on all the perks, dude. I'm uh, I'm on babysit duty right now
I can babysit swap for you. All right
I need to use your comprehensive lore of spongebob to explain where the third key
Where did spongebob and Patrick hide the final key? Yeah, where did they hide the final key?
The key of the STG 44. What do you think I try checking garbage cans?
That's what I thought they look at the garbage cans in this map seem a little bit too high-detail
Just get the box
Davy Jones locker the lid
Okay, everyone's saying the lid. All right, I get it. You know, it's one of my memes what the little
Okay, 47
so you guys do puzzle work, I'll just
Babysit this Dutchman for a while
Light beam, okay
The lid the lid the lid it wasn't everyone's screaming about the lid everyone's young I must be the lid guys
It's unanimously the lid all the lid the lid. I know anything about that
Did they mean like sewer vent like a lid for honestly?
It could be opening the final door because we've opened all the mix it for the one over here. So
All right, dude, what just happened? Well, I was looking I was trying to go towards like the beam of light and oh
Here you just want to come over to me. You distracted my zombie
What is happening? Oh my god, I need a hyper. I think German needs to go over here
It's right here, right?
this
bus bus bus bus bus
I need a weapon. I'm gonna power back
Thanks, right. Does he suck? Huh? Who's he? I mean you could get a better gun. Yeah. Yeah from the box. I
Did not miss a dig site. I'm looking what sort of was sort of past the phase where we settle for
Yeah, that's true
sack three
thing
Looks like a dual wield, which means it shoots pretty fast
Probably good pack a punched. Yeah, let's pack punch this thing. I don't know. Did you guys figure out how to dive yet?
Oh easy easy. You can't afford the pack a punch. I think they needed to open up a debris hole
Yeah back this spawn
I'm just gonna run this way for a sec. I
Don't have enough money. I will in a minute though. It's like just like holding this
No, oh
All right. They're apparently we missed one. Oh, there's the last dig site
Maybe double pack the fist gun you can double pack. I thought they just gave you more ammo fuck
Nothing. No
James does double packing do anything in this or does it just refill your ammo?
Uh, I don't know if they added that in like a later thing
I know all these zombie games merged for me after we need it
This this door right here
You see where I am
Yeah, this is the last one. We haven't open
That just goes back to the beginning. Yeah, but maybe it's okay
I was hoping it's gonna like give us a little shortcut opened all the doors thing
double packing gives special ammo
Dude, what the fuck? Where's spongebob hiding his special treasure?
No, no, we kind of
There's another power switch here. Oh
Racing stripes we exhausted all options
Power switch people are saying I pulled another switch right there. We did the power though. It's by the gate
No, there's more than one power. This one activates only one of the vending machines though
Check that maybe we're missing power on the side of every vending machine is its own power. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, it's true
One over here as well that's already broken
We're mr. Krabs. Don't you can't talk to mr. Krabs?
No, mr. Krabs. Don't talk. He's dead
That's just oh wait shoot all the Aquaman's
I've made man to man man to man
man to man
Alright, I see it. No, that's just a blue
Yeah
Okay
I don't have them. Oh, I had them. Oh shit. Get it. We we did it. What is this press F
50,000
Welcome to my game. I fucking hate you're gonna have to pay another 50,000 to get
What the fuck
50 grand here time
I'll have like a punch stuff. This should be okay. Yeah, just try it once and see how fast it goes up because they're right like if
Standing here. They don't spawn in here. We just
Shoot like crazy. I'll watch I'll watch behind it
See how see if it goes make sure you guys prone
extra accuracy
Yeah, no, this should be super easy if none spawn back here. This should be like like a two-round
Not two rounds not to run I was I was thinking more of like if someone
Yeah, nothing's spawning in here. We're good. So this is one person. I'm gonna shoot every enemy
Just shoot every enemy well, we just cover it. All right covering
What was that? That's a super loud coal emission
Which lets me see Oh vulture lets you see every pickup on the map
So this is just practice for you practice for you almost there. I mean honestly ten percent
Hey, I mean this is this is how you actually wouldn't go up black ops and this is an actual
Yeah
Fun just watching next map is gonna be KFC
So enjoy this
I'll throw a grenade though. It's like bring it out. Actually. Now's a good chance
Chats one for McDonald's two for KFC three for Taco Bell make your decision
Which three separate food maps to do
Somebody can pack a punch again. Okay. I'm seeing a lot of threes in there. I see this blood and glory
That's cool
Now we get a max ammo out of this sir, I'm gonna run out of these
Sorry, man, I'm getting the last couple of my purge come unstoppable
18 only it looks like four more of those. Wait am I saving up now? Yeah, you're saying you got $50,000
Fuck
You're a savior money your money
Well seems just like enough time to run an ad on my channel thanks guys for watching all this I did
He rent like you read like a hundred ads on
I mean so much money no idea work. Did it make you know actually was not
No, I'm not up to warrant all the the unfollows I got so at your own expense
run the ads
It was easily like a quarter of the stream
Career suicide exactly wait. I made it feel that if someone were to gift me a sub I would run an ad so
This is not gonna be worth it you're gonna open that it's gonna just say oh no
It's gonna instantly send us to the gate. It's essentially you pay to game over the key
Yeah, yeah, it's gonna be credit for the easy to channel. I can't wait
15,000
This was an interesting map of straight lines
Roads, I'm gonna run out of ammo. I might have to like pack a punch again
No
You always have to buy that's gonna set us back. Oh, I know I know but like I have nothing
So they're like starting to get to us to well, I'm not firing at them. I'm running out of ammo to actually
You're gonna get to like 42,000. We're gonna all have no ammo. I'm gonna piss a bear bear
How's there not been a max ammo yet Jesus
We're too far away from them. No, there's there's perks popping up. There's drops. It's just not a good
I'm any good ones. All right, I am out of ammo. So fun. I'm running out too
I should pack a punch real quick. No, I don't know don't don't I have 20
No, he should I barely have any animal either in German's peeing man. I we need ammo. No, no, no, no
Not as much it's not as much it's only 2,500
Okay, it actually didn't give me any ammo. It filled up
It gave me an extra perk. I don't know what the fuck that even does for me. But oh
God, when is he coming back?
I don't know, but I need to pack a punch now
Wait, did we get one? Oh, that's a death machine
Weak it's it's weak compared to I pack a punch this thing. It didn't even give me any ammo. We're gonna die here
I have no way of helping
How long is this fucking P
I get he's gonna die
He's dead
There's nothing we can do
Get him up. Maybe you won't notice if you get him up. There's no dude. There's no hammer
Wait, it's a kill. It's a kill. It's a kill. Okay. All right, James kill them all knife him if you have to
fuck
Fucking what is going on man? You guys should get some ammo or something like yeah, right from where?
There's no fucking
I know I know I have an idea
If we take a wall
Item now we can probably switch it to pack a punch. I'm down
You're down. What do you mean? You're down? Oh, what was that sound over here pack a punch?
We need to make one of them a crawler. I have nothing. I'm completely out. I'm dead
No, I'm dead. No, I am completely out of everything that I have in my image
I have all my ammo back
30,000 you guys have to fight your way. Whoa, I'm back. You're not you're down. What do you mean you're back?
I can't pick you up, dude. I know I just oh my god. Oh my god
You're guy you dying and glitching or whatever cost me my life
What just happened? I don't know but I came in a savior dead fucking body and I lost all my first back up
No, it's over. It's all it is over
Ah
All right. We'll just tell him that we got it. We got the money. All right. Tell me tell me one
Don't be missing. Tell me miss ending. Okay. Oh my god. Did we win?
Yeah, it was amazing, dude
Spongebob rolls up in his bikini bottom
It's car and he says Patrick we're gonna go jelly hunting. Do you want to come too?
and then we all got in the car and
The game crashes but game worth it. Yeah
Did you not see it were you were you away I was
Peeing no, I was gone for like a lot. How long was that P do those?
I was a long fuck is a pretty long P we assumed after a while. He just like needed to talk to you stream
You didn't hear me say I'm gonna go pee cuz we know we heard you say you were gonna go pee and then
It was like 20 minutes
He shouldn't come a little okay chat
Oh
Did you get did you lose
No, we won. Oh, we won ask your chat saw it. I they can they can recap what I'm sure there's clips. Yeah, we won
We won. We did it. It's good level
Well, we didn't play Taco Bell Taco Bell was a heavy. Oh, we did it
We did lots of people were asking for Taco Bell next I think
Okay, I still want to do Mario Kart. Oh
Wow, my microphone went up to 160 for suddenly and I got a little
jumpy
Freddy's as well, too. I'm fine with anything. I mean, I was just thinking, you know
I've done for Mario Kart five nights Freddy's or Taco Bell is the lobby up yet or no
No, hang on. Did that count as a good map or a joke awful map?
I would say it's more in the middle. I'd say it wasn't quite good
A little serious about would you guys consider that one a shit because if we do Taco Bell that is a guaranteed to be the worst
You ever played alright. Oh, wait, wait, wait, they lost because I went to go pee and they ran out of ammo
I thought he was gonna sit here and have a farm for like a few minutes
Meet a mutant deaf and what was that sound you were just doing in my ear? Oh now you now you're quiet
Wait, what happened? I don't know. He started making these like gum smacking sounds and like pissed me off
Quiet when I called him gum spacking. Yeah, I was like you wouldn't you'd have to I'll probably do it again
Yeah, it sound like it sound like that. Who thing you did earlier cranking on out work like that gross
I don't know you guys are talking about you know what I'm talking. I was I went to pee
Wait, where am I? What is this? You're in multiplayer
Fuck I get out. You're in the game. Wait, what?
Game cranking I don't want to be here. Where's the exit?
They really don't I mean, I guess I could host snow if you're trapped in the game
Are you guys actually have to buy one of these people or else you can't leave? All right
Why are you hosting or should I you can just host again? It's been fine so far
Plus, I'm not sure if I've ever lost team. Is it up now? It is up now
All right, you want five minutes of Freddy's?
Might be shit
This is also a thing we have to do
Yeah, okay. Let's well bang them out quick. We got uh, oh, yeah, I don't see it the hell let's do
Taco Bell five minutes Freddy's. There's there's Super Mario 64 zombies
Which looks better than the other time we did that and then there's oh there it goes
I want to do
Dude, there's a lot of extra minecraft levels. I think we wrote off minecraft too soon
I got like eight of those
The beginning because people weren't ready, but there's a lot of minecraft in there
There's also Simpsons. There's saw still
Saw is so good. They've must have fucking made a Simpsons level. There is I mean, I got it in the pack
Do you think I missed something? I got no I got everything but I would do almost every page of the fucking
I believe it. I downloaded all of them. It took me two hours
Hey, I mean you can't fault me. I put effort into picking these up
to some extent, okay
Okay, saw three the final chapter. I guarantee you will be good times. I can't guarantee that
I don't think it's even made by the same guy who made the good level. Oh, no really shit when I snuck in
Trap you. Yeah, this might have been my son. No, there's there's saw one
There's saw two there's saw three the final chapter and then there's jigsaw. We're playing soft
There's a lot of chapters. They really love me. There's like 18 saw movies to be fair
One though, right? Yeah, you're right. You're right. Maybe you're right. It might be the you know
They're fresh that one that jigsaw was made in like 2017. So
Probably operating
There is definitely a couple of traps like my own saw sort of traps that I put in this mod pack
Cuz I wasn't I mean, I guess I guess they are officially traps now cuz you're the host
So what's up?
Can I just join off you or the lobbies private or come back? Yeah, you should be in there. I said you're in it
Yeah, yeah for the future
Lack of titties, man. You want tits that bad? I can get one. You want me?
Hang on. I'll get one. I can get one fuck. Yeah. All right, Jesus. Give me like ten sex
There was also a mod that makes everyone Kermit is that your thing too you want me to get you want me to
Pander to James now. Well, I feel like I've experienced that already
Okay, then uh, what the fuck is little do they know this is like, yeah the final chapter
There's like eight more. What am I looking at one of these guys? This guy's maps before killjoy. We play. Oh, you're right
That was candy land. Oh, this is the trap. I fooled you all
Yes, welcome to my dungeon this was a mistake
What is our what was our knife do we
Spam click I don't think we get oh we got a lot of money
We all like this like an actual level guys. So um last chance
This is not like any of the other max we've done. I hey I just
Excuse I I hear jigsaw. Why can't I walk away?
German still serve reason why the lad I can't go up the ladder. I can't I swear to God
Okay, you got you on camera. You came over but I swear to God. I don't believe you. I
Go look back at my go open my font
There he is
Do we who go?
Okay, this saws I wouldn't touch the sauce wait what's gonna happen what's Gavin what's this music? Hey, there's like a shit
There's like a there's something on the wall there. There's a gun crank it check on the glass
Do anything it's like no
No
Dude, I love is there a person in here that we have to save for what we make a choice
I I feel like it would be a puzzle if this thing was moving towards us
I got I got a plan
I'm gonna put my head in this saw and we're gonna see if it activates something when I pour blood into like the
That was it no don't get me up. I'm still in the sauce
All right, we're gonna be able to get you
Can we get him? Yeah, there you go. Oh
Joe did you open that?
glass you shoot it
No, I mean, I've she I've been shooting it but like it doesn't do anything probably gave us
Yeah
What about the I don't the guns nothing to shoot gone on the wall. Yeah, I'll just have the guns. I guess
Oh
Wait, I shot him. I shot his face
Okay
Oh
So it usually gives you at least a few seconds to figure out you want to do
I can't crawl
Four seconds
Everyone died
Zombies in saw drink this it's like a it's like a cola power-up. Ooh what?
You played my game and you fail that's not even a game. This is the guy put like a poison drink here
If he was holding two it would be like a drink the poison game
Man four people really clogs up these halls and saw
Navigating your trap streak. So we have to shoot something in there. Oh
How do you turn on your your your flashlight double tap F, okay
Okay
I
Mean I bet we just have to shoot something dumb. Yeah
All right, light them up
Light up everything the guy with a drink. No wait
We got a new TV
Hello, we're here
This it means you have passed your first
Why does he keep doing damn it keep walking back in the room
Hey
Wait, we have to find out what the game is. This is writing the wall game. All right, the blood shirt like surely doesn't hurt you
Don't touch the blood don't touch the blood
Do you know how to hack no
I don't have anything come over here check it. I won't even know how to hack
I'm not fucking around. No, he does. I need a
We need to learn real quick guys, okay, maybe in that box is the secret tech. What was that?
Alright as soon as you start talking nobody move and let him finish his head because he gets spooked if we're moving too much
He's drunk. Oh
Oh wait, I heard him again. Oh shoot this. Yeah, that's what I was just shooting it not doing anything
Shy guy. Oh, wait a minute. I don't move nobody move
Okay
However, this next challenge will test your ability to adapt to your surroundings
Literally talking to just them
Okay, wait, so you two got to talk to Jigsaw I didn't wait I shot I shot a bear in the fire
And it did something it disappeared. Did you learn how to hack? It said get used to your surroundings
We need Jigsaw's key for this room. I'm okay with your dying if I get to live
There that he decided he was too lazy to write to
Did Jigsaw have a knee brace in the movies?
Yes, you see the last one we got crippled. No, I don't said
Okay on if you stand next to this
Guys, you couldn't hear Jigsaw stand next to the walkie-talkie. Yes. That's when you can hear him
What does he say?
Run past him
His button on the ceiling
He says ass if you keep running past it button on the sale asshole button on the ceiling asshole
Asshole mine's actually not bugging out. I can hear the whole thing
All right test our ability to adapt to our surroundings. I think two two of us have to go in here and die
That doesn't seem I don't think Jigsaw. I mean, I guess he does like was this no die. So what?
Oh, no, no to if I get if I live get to know I'm okay with your sign if I get to live
It has got nothing to do with
His dialogue
Stop I can't get out of the blood. I can't get out of the blood
Okay, we guys we got to adapt to our surroundings. Okay
I'd know not to jump into the pool of blood which means I've adapted to my surroundings
Red is dead
So, what do I do now?
There's that door
Has anyone learned how to hack have we adapted to hacking no hacking over here key
Throw nade into box. Oh
Smart chat. Let's try. Uh-huh. Uh-huh. Okay. What about in here? What about in the fireplace?
Okay, we're gonna need a fireplace
You realized what I get is three
I mean this button surely is a thing. What happened to my arrow pointing at it?
There goes are we not like what if you parkour with these pillars? Yeah, I'm trying to go
Okay
I'm not sure you can
No, maybe not. I mean, maybe there's something you need to interact with it
You can't do it I'm jumping on these
You can definitely parkour these yeah, I mean yeah you could
Oh, and then you eat your box and you get in the box totally jump to this and into the box. Okay. Yeah
All right. You ready guys. There you go
You're in
Come on guys
You
That's you're the one that needs to die. That's what it says. I'm right. I made it it says it on the wall
Okay, all right now pick me up
Now pick me up
Oh
Every time I revive I'm gonna die from these
We gotta be pretty sure yeah come through I'll catch you
Okay, okay
Okay, we just everyone just let me through I'll just get picked up on the other side
Dude, I'll see you go. I'll see you on this. I'm I remind me. Oh, hold on. You know what? Let me go
Craigin
Craigin was that supposed to hit me. Oh
Shit, it wasn't even in the right place. All right, so that way hold on anything on the right side here
There's some stuff over here teddy bear. Yes. Oh wait. We just had you just had it. Oh wait
That's a different one. Oh
Dude do they have juggernaut in there? It looks like it. All right follow me
Help oh, I see
Another parkour. Okay, it's some sort of jump thing. Yeah, you fall and you gotta climb back up. Well, oh
It's just sliding
Why wait they don't move with you? Why you gotta move with it? That's awkward
Oh, this is this is I remember this part and saw five
Remember the park or platform mattress to mattress. Oh that one looks so bad
Is it even gonna make it back in time for me? Where am I going?
There's a door. There's a door. There's a door right there next to you. I can't see it, man
Can you just like swim to it? No, there's I mean
Hang on. Let me see
No, no, no, you cannot
Do it you gotta do it for real
What level was it that this guy made that we played before candy land land?
Okay, maybe it gets you to jump. I mean you gotta give the guy some credit. He really covers every genre with this
Yeah, I think he also made the game
You got it you got a jump you're gonna jump from that one to that
This is never going to have our this is we have no we can totally do this this is
Hey Kraken if you go into if you go into console, can you know?
Can you wall run I just gonna hurt. Oh, yeah wall running. Can you walk on that? That's not a thing on this map
Where's the where's the other what yeah, it's like the timings off
I'm gonna get there if you got
You gotta wait. Oh hard person to completely fall before you even get on the next one or else the
I'm just gonna go. Oh my god. It's like buggy man. It's like
Yeah, it's odd you press forward and sometimes it's very weird. Sometimes you get stuck and then maybe jerk off. I'm host
It's not that bad for me, but
Soon as you get through this
One of I've now I'm too deep in no one though. I want to know how it's next
I want to hear more
It's like you move slower than the thing moves so you have to like preemptive
It's you guys you got a jitter step here if you watch how I do it here it's not the bed
I'm showing you he's like the greatest call duty gamer I've ever seen and then where's the where's the where's the door?
Now I can't now it's got to reset all the way, okay, I'm gonna get it this time
Well, that's gonna be
Give it a minute. It's not gonna be back in time
Thanks, Kraken. I think is it is it I think it might be like client-side because it was reset for me
Check under the water bugs. Oh man. Yeah, I don't even think my connection is good enough to do that
I'm running on like over 120 ping
So I think I just watch
Don't look at that
No, crank it if you actually next to one the tilt a key actually does open the real console
Recognizes no clip as a command. I don't have any cheese to not turn off my fucking flashlight again. Try typing SV cheats
It's not SV though. Is it?
Actually, it recognizes SV
Does the knife make you run it faster in this game? Oh
My god, it activated the platform to all guys take out your knives take out your knives. What does that do? You write faster?
It's just like sir. You can keep up with it. Sorry James. I'm cutting you fucking cut me. I just cut you
Ha I did I can do this. You're almost there. Oh
Hey tomato, what happened to you? I died the poison she drowned
Yeah, the knife definitely makes it easier. All right, go for it
You got it
No, I think it's I think sometimes just get lucky in the platform doesn't fuck you. I'm mine still sitting there. Yeah
Oh
You got it. You got it
There you go, there you go
What's the end goal?
When you reach the middle of that wall, right under the stops right under the P is the is the door
You got to jump at the P. Oh, okay. I see
All right. I might get this I see it now
fuck
Don't too early. Wait, if it's under the P
What's the point of that platform under the like the yellow flag? I think that might be what you need to jump to actually
That goes towards it. Oh, really?
Probably right cuz look look I'll activate it. Let me see if it does anything. Is it moving or I'm dying
Okay, I died. Let's got it. I died
Nice yes, was it taking me it didn't move. Oh
No, I don't even know if that's do it if that's gonna do anything
I thought it would move and it never did or do you have to jump from there into the hey
Crawl crawl up to what it doesn't look like you're losing time
The thing's gonna come back. Come on. Come back. All right, here we go. All right, so the last one doesn't move
It should move I it moved when I was in the wall
Maybe I need to be on it for longer, but I panicked
Maybe it gives you a second to stand on it before it moves cuz you definitely should move broken. I
Love saw
What a jump
Is it in the middle for you the rest of this is the rest of the
All right, you're there look it moves look it is moving right now. Why why is it you know?
God, who started it? I shot it what I shot it. I shot it. Oh
Yeah, oh, maybe someone else has to like do it the rest of the way you guys shoot it yourself
It's like a Mario maker level only one guy was able to do this. It was person that created it
Okay, can someone go up this ladder I'm dying of poison
All right, James you want to do it I'll shoot the thing when you're ready if I can even make it up there now jump
Why I think I'm getting decisively better at the second one though
Fuck I can't even make it to the second one. I know I feel so ready to go. I
Can't get up the fucking ladder
Holy shit imagine how satisfying the call I didn't be though. Oh, I shouldn't I think I can do that
I didn't sprint that time. You got it. You got it. I think I can actually do this
I've been getting better
Does somebody need to shoot it? All right. Yeah. Don't shoot it yet. Do not shoot it yet
We didn't reach it from here. We did it. It's okay. We missed no shoot. Oh
Why is it not moving it's not working now
swim under it oh, yeah, oh I
Shot it before and it worked it was moving
Go go go go. It's not moving. Did we fuck it up? I can't make that jump from here. It's all right
Just stay there. I'm out of ammo. Hold on. I'll come get you
Like move and then I'm not gonna notice I'm gonna fall. I'll start yelling as soon as it starts moving
Wait, are you up there? Oh
There's a lion at the ladder
Yeah, the wonder how the fuck it fog does not know or is there a button maybe that we press them on wait
Try shooting it when I jump like when I'm not touching it. I don't have any more ammo. Hey, yeah, I'm out of ammo, too
No, I was definitely I shot it when I was in the air and it didn't move
What happened there I got stuck on the lip I'm gonna lose my mind here tell him to jump and shoot it
Yeah, if you jump up, that's what I did
I'm out of ammo now. I'm gonna die. You know what? Fuck it. I'm going for it
Matt Matt socks, man, I hate this
We gotta be missing something but I mean, I don't know what we're missing. It feels like wait
Let me I I guess I can cry. I try to create the same circumstances. I was under water and I died
Okay, dude, you can hit the fucking flag the giant leg
Draped red box at corner. Someone said is that what we do shoot that and that starts it
Does anybody have any yes, I'm gonna shoot this. Oh, okay. All right. There we go. That moved it. We figured it out
Wait, what did you do? Shoot the box. You can shoot the box in the corner
I like oh shit. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Oh god. Okay, I'm coming on my god
Okay, this boys I'm gonna pull it off you're like an angel I'm alive
Okay, I'm in position oh my god, he's in position someone shoot it wait, I'll just go get it
I'm just gonna go slash the damn flash. It's ready. Go go. It's like passing. I gotta do it in mid move
That is so hard. You can't get any momentum
Dude, I could do it. But it's like I gotta like that's hard man. That's real hard
If we all have to do that, it's not gonna have no way. Oh
Well, I'm down I can get it. Oh
Wait, I'm afraid
Remember get get at the end of it as far away from doors you can you gonna have to sprint jump into it
Oh
Give me plates off to let's go back
Let's do jigsaw the newest I
Mean like I know I can do this and I feel like this is
It's my light someone next to me. Nope. Nope. Okay
This is like Satan knows just let me die here
Okay, we're going back I'm not gonna let you die no game over wait again
Wait, what?
wait
Pathway underwater. No, there wasn't it's just the reflection
Oh
So, do you want to try more saw levels cuz they're all like this they're all like not actually
Mine didn't crash
I'm good. You're so lucky. They don't have crashes
We have Friday nights at Freddy's 4 in 2 mean 1 game of Thrones. We've game of Thrones KFC KFC
What's wrong with KFC? What did people vote for for the fast-food one that we've got right?
Enable cheap. Oh, I don't know
Someone in check might know and today for school lunch steak. Um, that's what it sounds like. I
Tried to catch it too. I was like on the slider ready
I
Mean, I would I also think we're due for another actual good map
Yeah, saw the finance phrase. I'm not sure if that's the good one, bud
Matter of fact that might be made by one of our favorite
meme creators
Is it killjoy again possibly killjoy?
There's notice I remember having a lot of levels. I will say
Only the five is capitalized in five night at Freddy's so and then there's five
Yeah, I mean I'm can I can that one doesn't have that one didn't have any ratings on it
I had a lot of plays but no one really
So keep in mind that one was it was new. It was made like last week
Which means this is a passionate five nights at Freddy's fan
Really? It loves this game
All right, let's up to you guys offline. What the fuck? So which one of which one are you going to?
You're gonna do a jigsaw
We could do five nights at Freddy's. Oh my god. I remember jigsaw. We did that one. It was steamy garbage or
saw two
Hmm saw two. I don't think we ever did. I remember doing jigsaw one and it was steamy
Alright, let's do let's do saw two just cuz we I think we had fun last saw one. Oh, yeah suddenly wasn't fun. So
What's good until it was
There's like five minutes we just fucking ran into and did like a fucking parkour bit
That was the entirety of the map
All of us were in those different trap plans. Oh god, it changes the same font. It's the same fucking guy
I'm getting heiress. Oh synchronizing game settings away
It's him again kill joy you son of a bitch. He's done it again
How many of your mad mop mops have I put in this thing now kill joy?
Wait, I'm separating your character. Why you know, you're not
Interrupted
I'm like good to go. I just yeah briefly. Oh boy
Actually has zombies
No
Zombies we need a bowie knife. Yeah, there's one right here. We need to be thousand for it
I need more souls for my toilet. Yeah, so on my toilet
Guys, we need to let the zombies in so we can put it in the soul toilet now
Do we actually have a soul toilet? Is it for real? Yeah, check the wall bud. Take. Oh man
We're gonna need souls for this thing. I just picked up an industrial drill from the toilet
Oh
Okay, this is good these are all going into the soul
We have half as much as we need for the bowie knife
So what they're gonna get closer to the toilet time. Oh god. I can't see for shit on this map. Oh
Wait, what just happened?
Oh
Okay, I think we won
G underscore spawn no free entities. All right Game of Thrones
Didn't pay for that one. It's not that it's free
We got a we got a bill. We got a play into that
Pandering, I don't know. I'm trying to find Game of Thrones one. I don't think I see it my list
I need to read down on it. I have dead ship. I have
It's in capital letters
Called Game of Thrones
You won't be able to miss the picture because it says welcome to ice grenades tutorial zombie mod
I think he might have put the wrong map in his game
But I promise guys. It's gonna be good. It looked good. Oh
Yeah, I gotta I gotta reinstall it one
Is that in the pack? It should be in the pack. Yeah, I might have missed though
I'll be right back. Okay, didn't my microphone get fucked up again, or is it okay? No, you're good. No, it's not good. Okay. Oh, man
Yeah, I don't know. It's listed on mine. I guess I can host now. I don't know if I have everyone else
Yeah, I guess you could join on Kraken everyone who doesn't I think that should work out
Okay, then Kraken you just join on me. Okay
Stairway to hell looks good
All of this now this one now this is gonna be a good level I think it takes place in the famous castle black. Oh
Okay. All right, I joined
I know the dog smell. Thank you
Thank you. I'm glad somebody does I've been waiting four and a half months for somebody to say that. Thank you. Awesome
Did you I?
Went back way out. Let's see if James can join
James take my invite. I think you would a okay. Oh, yeah
Hey, I want to go a BRB. I see the lobbies not joinable, huh? It's set for friends only. Oh
Yeah, you're in now. Okay. Yeah, it's a nice for some reason. All right, it says I I mean I can be in the lobby
So I got a picture man. So, yeah, I cannot join up you would you have to invite
These people to drop me. Let's see. Yes. Oh, wait, you might not be hang on
Let me open up the server because I press right now. It's at the friends only
I did join game off of Kraken. It is a loading screen. No, I try that. Let's try this one
Hey, there we go. Hi cool
Perfect
This is gonna be a good one. I know I know I picked at least one good mapping. Guess what?
I thought this one was made by kill small
Is that a good or a bad thing? Well
What do you think I?
have this one does YouTube tutorials for
Call of Duty zombies mod making maps. So, you know, oh
I know you're with you too. You never heard of it, man. I think we should we should break in the black ops 3
YouTube scene, dude. I think we should break into tutorials in general. I don't think enough people do that
All right. I'm gonna grab a beer all ready for James. We can also probably start loading. Ah, I'm not gonna abandon James
Wait, is it we're doing a little beer?
It's getting like another drink sometimes it takes him a while
He's got bad legs, you know
I'm gonna sprint downstairs and grab a water and I'm gonna sprint back up as fast I can I'm gonna get hurt
Should I time you it's gonna be 45 seconds guarantee 45 seconds guarantee
Starting starting 10 seconds after you hear the door close
That's right here. What they have to hear the door close behind me 10 seconds. Okay. I have your back
There may have been some developments on my side, too. I know what developments happened kind of
Sideway eyes. I haven't played on the server
It says the lobbies not joinable what
There are three people in here gang that's what it says. Let me invite you
Let me give you let me give you a personal invite my friend James the head German German. Have you ever tried GTA RP?
No, never
Are you interested? Oh
probably not
Okay
Conversation and I was about as quick as we got rejected inviting people to this stream. Yeah, really? That's what you should have said
You're like, yeah
Hey, you want to do this zombies thing and probably not not really
James can you still not get in it won't let me where let me check. Let me go off the message on steam
Yeah, try that cuz uh now there are enough people in that's something weird going on
I just clicked it. It's not that I don't think it would be fun. You just don't like us. I get it
Yeah, I mean like this is the first thing you've done with us I'm like fucking I know I wouldn't blame after this
What you guys just talking about how you guys are getting like banned from the server you want me to jump in on
No, there's no drama with the admins. All right, we we know the admins. Okay. Look, we're cool with them
It's this is more of a it's a beef. All right their gang vs our gang
Dude, I did something pretty questionable last night that I that chat was my chat was telling me that I could surely get banned for
Okay, I'm not gonna speak for James. I don't know
No, but I figured it out later like someone else on the server said it was like it was all cool. I
Used information that I got from role-playing and I did something dirty. Oh
But it was from role-playing
Okay
Everything my character does is dear. It's great. I'm gonna have to host since James can't join my game
I'm trying to accept your invite. It's just keep saying can't join try it try joining like off of yeah
I go put me or join. I think that's how I did it
Well, I'll be not joinable. What the fuck is it there try it again. There is everywhere errors
Maybe I mean cracking as long as we know that map like appears or something for you that you know
It's labeled as Game of Thrones on the map list
Well, I'm sure that I'm not gonna be able to find it in my own lobby for some reason. It's still not working
I'm gonna host again
Yeah, let's see if you can find it. It's like all caps Game of Thrones
Chad am I blind or is versus thing you subscribe to everything like that. I sent you most recently
I think so, but I have most of it there that one was pretty
That one might have been one of the last ones on that list in the collection
I might have had the same issue as some of people were my
There is it
Okay, I was about GT RP. It's just a bunch of cringy dudes. That's the point man. Oh, dude
They got my number we can all be cringy together. That's right
We're just as cringy in the server as we are IRL cringy
There we go it worked
I'm gonna make that problem James. What's your problem with me steam filters only true friends tomato. What the fuck? All right, let's go
I'm sorry. Are you guys ready for us?
By the way, it says this game thrown spoilers if you've never seen the show don't watch the spoilers
You know, I actually don't know how many spoilers this might have
Pretty good warning if you've seen the first episode you you should probably be good
Yeah, watch just come here all of a sudden
Chad told me to turn on dev mode so I can use cheats and that may have broken some of these maps because I did
You like yours. Why do you listen? Are you cheating? I do even know how to undo that. No breaking stuff. Oh
Wow
White walkers what the go back to castle black
Enable copyright sounds
Fuck you, Chad. What fucking you completely broke your own game. Yes, I hear a song
All right, I can't actually leave I can barely hear it. All right. I'm sorry. I'm crashing. That's not the song
Because I was not playable why did you open a thing called
Online
His chat was like that's how you can know clear friend. They teach you
All right. Sorry guys, I'm chat bad a moat only mode for the next five minutes and I'm playing an ad
That map didn't actually look that bad though, did you see that wall? Yeah, I like the voice acting
I like the voice acting in the wall. They couldn't put the elevator in so they just made it stairs, which is okay
I guess
Dev mode
Mods enable a mode only mode. I don't watch out for you. I don't know how watch out for my mic
Why should I watch out for my watch out?
Loud loud loud
Screamer how come well, I've been talking to screamer yet. That's kind of unfortunate
Yeah, I want to either screen or tits and I got neither
I can find tits and put them in this mod pack. You guys really want that I could look like right now
Hey, it's too quiet. Yeah, now you went too quiet. I
Want to get man, I can take all your accounts out right now if you want to slip it in
Do you guys want me to I can't it's a part of a video game. It's fine
Wait, did I ever tell you guys about my my my like my porn challenge idea? What what is a challenge?
Oh, does that mean?
Okay, all right hear me out
You know how you can have multiple
Screens like, you know, everyone's got multiple monitors, right?
so the idea is we're gonna stream with display capture and one of the monitors that it's off-screen is me playing porn the
entire stream and
You just have to ignore it and have it muted and like
It's just gonna be on the whole time and everyone's gonna know it's there
But as long as it's not on-screen, you can't get in trouble for it, right?
Fucking stuff glitches out first or something and fucking me
It's just like top and just like this this mental game of like watching chat and on the other side of the monitor
We take your heart. Oh, no, we did
I remember we also established the rule that you had to be you had to have a source open for desktop capture on the
Desktop next to it. Yeah
Jason desktop has to have capture. It's playing a
dance with death
The only way I know how to feel alive anymore. Exactly. All right, how are we?
Are we ready to I'd like yeah. Yeah. Yeah, we're just I mean I should I should porn on stream before I got an infraction
And that's it. I didn't get banned. Yes
porn on stream before I
Remember this stretch when you were streaming where it seemed like you had infraction the other day
Yeah, I think that was that was during that time. Yes
It was like a there was like this stretch where you're always like on an infraction or the context to it
Or just like this was a nice porn clip. I saw it wants to watch it
You know that fucking super seducer game
They had yeah
Like like a link in it like when you're dating one of the chicks and she said so it was like a I thought
It was like a fake website or something. Oh, no, and I and I pulled it up and it was real
That was probably the first one ever
I mean, there's no way that wasn't taken by that dates back to like 1996
That's an old one. I got a slap on the wrist for it. All right, you guys can release the mode only mode
Sorry, everybody. You had to be taught a lesson. All right, you guys ever do that to your chats
You're teaching a lesson slap around a little
No, I've never actually heard of my chat. My chat's usually okay. Hey yours is nice cuz you're trained them
Well, I that's my problem. You gotta train them on their puppies. Otherwise they get I make examples
Wait, we're fine with in Game of Thrones finally
Yes
I'm gonna turn up my music
Welcome to ice grenades map like
Looks like the taller is done shots
play copyright here
What it's it's the in play the theme. It's playing the theme. Oh
So fuzz muted. Yeah. All right. Bye guys. Bye budshed
And
The transition
They're coming they have top hats and shit. Just like a
Throne you do not know
The walkers don't care
Dude I loved much a bickering without his fucking clock and gunned down like eight guys in the woods
Bunch of undead bastards
Listen cost 500 huh?
They're coming no matter what you do. I'm dead. I
Can't read the font of any of this
I'm having trouble telling how much I have
Look at the UI on the right the game of Thrones logo. Yeah, I'm having trouble like reading into what I'm working with here. Yeah
Dude I just got John's fucking sword. Wait, what I do I have it when you got ice. No, that's Ned Stark
One claw I got a long claw long claw
Oh my god
Your guns use long claws
Long claws. Oh stop using your guns. It's free. It's right over here. It's free. Yeah. Oh
It is free randomly in this pile. Wow, I feel a sudden change in my momentum
Is that text to speech? Yeah. Yeah
All right. Well, I'm gonna start climbing the wall and by me I mean
Long call doesn't even do that
Explode them. Yeah, they like a flying. Oh, we haven't seen the big battle yet. Maybe it will
Hold on hold on
Oh, no, I think we need to start switching to using guns. Yeah
Oh
God cover me if you still man, even when you're using guns
Open some of the way up. Come on guys up the wall pesky crows. They look evil
They look evil shoot those pesky crows. They look evil
Come on, we gotta go going in slow bow
Walkers remaining 60. I've got 68 hundred
Bingo
I'm glad there's only 60 white walkers in their army
This we lucked out doesn't as bad as I want to say this next one's three thousand. I got it. Oh
My god, big spender boys. Let's go. It's a big map of straight line walls. Oh
They're coming would it be the light bringer? Yes
Is there dragon oh
Oh
We cry I wanted to see them it's so bad. I'm fucking crying
It's this I yeah, I should have done it on the sword. Damn it. That's how you get light bringer
Walkers have top hats on we're gonna have to go say shame on you shame on you
What is this pack a punch thing?
It was a it was a power up. Yeah
well, uh
Shame who wants to clear these dead horses? Oh
Shabe all you charge. Oh
What's censored over there somebody naked?
This is like a sensor over here on how much further is this route. They just don't seem to stop coming
They're behind us
All right, we gotta watch people what's behind us because we are getting
Pack I got a perk pack
Oh, you're trouble for the super laser gun that Jon Snow used to defeat the white walk
Actually, I want there's a lot of money. Yeah, let's use a lot of that money to open up this six six thousand dollar door
Okay, so was only 8,000 on the next one
Dragons
They're gonna be the final boss 8,000 on this one. Oh
At least they can't get up here easily
There's just a hell laser. So wow, it should just blast the theme song
Yeah, just can't hear anyone else that one had a baseball cap on what the fuck
two times ammo I
Got Valerian steel grenades
Right out with me
That's really good there's too much shit in the way they're starting to break
It's gonna disappear I'm sorry I'm trying
I
Will
We did it they all exploded get up get the fuck up. Oh my god
Get through there. Where is 9,000? I could use a refined. I think it's Jerma
Wait, where is he?
I'm up
What? Oh, oh, we're so close to dragons now. We got to open this thing. Yes. Don't got open it
Oh my god
Incredible well, I'm going to get it
Which way the door which is the door what door
There's no indicator
Hold on hold on
Here
Stand right here. Wait, okay. See now I can see it. I wasn't there before I swear to hold the door
They look drowsy. I froze them. My god. This one's ten thousand. Oh my god. I got
There's no ammo up here. Oh
This might be the end of our journey
Make a pound
Make every shot count every single one of them
I've used all of my shots sir. No, if you both not a headshot. Don't take the shot
I feel a sudden change in my momentum. I just I feel like I just felt a sudden change
This cut is so bad
I'm still alive
This next one is 11,000. Oh my god, someone's almost got enough
It's me. It's me. I just need I need a couple more hits. Let's let him go
It's open let's move
Almost to the top guys. This is so my god epic. I think there's one more
Why are there 13 thousands? I'll get it. I'll get it. I'll get it
I think the character I think the fucking character just said ask why it's so expensive
I think they're breaking help help guys. Oh my god. I have 30,000 they came from
You were with us is what happens
I was holding them literally all off
There's too many people down here he left guys start crawling towards us they're breaking in
I can't crawl anymore
Get that one off
Come on James snow, you can do it they're spawning here
And back nice dude, we could totally yeah, we can do this we can do this
So shame that we're about to crash out how the white walk is still dying. They're killing each other
What if we just sit here and let it get to zero they're running they're running off the side of the
Didn't want to live anymore. Hey, no crash. That's it's pretty good
Alright, let's go again
You can actually do this one the amount of times that I try to arrest someone and then a zombie pushes me off of
Them like a fucking asshole
He's getting a little bit wild
We're almost there too. I think the sword I think I got too distracted carrying around the sword
I sacrifice not having a full extra gun to you know, shoot with
My chest talks to do I want to give him a minute long at this dude give them more ads. Yeah
They're blaming me for us losing
Pointing fingers ain't gonna get us over that wall, you know, hold the door Khaleesi, you know
You need to get out to castle black
What should we make of this sooner my mom
Shoutout to Simbo for his support
So cinematic
Maybe we should let them get in here first because then they have a chance to drop the pack of punch and that thing like
Save my ass. That is true
Yeah
Shame shame on you
Well dropped a new bomb, yeah
Sure did. I guess I'll open the first tier unless it's like should we just wait?
Until we're completely like fucked can't do anything. I mean if you open it that's here. They can start spawning behind us, which is
My favorite part favorite part. Oh, there it is
I feel like none of us get quicker by
So wait, you can if you go down you just get right back up
No, it means that we can basically res each other in like a quarter of a second
It means I would have been able to res you
Okay
Pretty much if I had it
Yeah, what?
Well, there's also uh, there's also juggernaut get the top there too. That's kind of what helped me out a little bit
I'm taking damn it. I'm gonna get quicker vibe. I'm gonna get it max. Am I gonna save that?
Did anyone even use any if you're just using melees right now?
No, right, but like right now that I was reminded again. Oh
Enough firecrackers
All mine
I feel a sudden change in my momentum
Can you buy it up here we didn't fit an animal that's I just see red
Can someone buy the uh, I think it's somebody used can you stop blowing into your microphone
Stamos we on dead
Shoot those pesky crows
I love the iron sights on this sword
I was waiting on someone with more money to do it, but I guess I'll have to I open
Well, this is what quick revive us for let me get him
The gods are with us. All right, let's go because everything's starting to flake us
Nice God's be good. Huh James? Why is your sword on fire? I don't know on fire
Looked like it was on fire
whoa
Wow
Dude the Thunder gun in Game of Thrones
Really good for the wall, dude
You got that
Matrix ha ha ha they look drowsy
Ha ha ha they look drowsy. Ha ha ha hee-hee-hoo
Should I buy the next tier?
Whoa the man of war too. All right. I'm good
I'll put I'll be putting all my stuff into the I think we're at 5,000 now. Oh
What the fuck? Oh my god. Look talk about free Thunder gun
That thing is
It's gonna be great. Okay, what happened?
What happened they're coming up they're coming up you can if you have you shoot the crows it goes
Okay, Nick. Whoa, dude Thunder gun on this level is absurd
I'm going by
It's so bad to be stuck at like the end point and like the middle point. Yeah, it really is
We got times to get back time to get those points in lads
Time to get those points in lads. I love this game
It's time to get those points in life
Sudden change in momentum
sudden change in my momentum
And swing faster Wow, who's gonna open? Are you gonna hold for a while?
Hold for a bit. Oh, you wanna hold it? Okay
Looks like it's pretty much whenever James wants to go. He's got double or make it this max ammo here
The gods are with us dude, that's actually so good Thunder gun to clear the lane
Yeah time to get those points in lads there it is again
We get some good yellow line are we not gonna get like, uh, oh wait, this isn't the joke
Yeah, we got to keep pushing up. We might be able to just reach it
Start buying
Crikey, where you going, dude? Oh, we're going up. Okay, we're almost to the end of the wave
We might as well start going up now. All right, who wants to do it?
James gets first. How much further is this route? They just don't seem to stop coming. I'm not buying any new guns
I had like 13,000. We should have saved to get the bigger ones. Yeah, I'll get this one
Come on boys. They're gonna start spawning behind us. We don't get up to this corner. I just opened the next wave
Oh, there you go. What is that? Oh, they're spawning
What is that?
The power-up get it for your sword. Let's just stand here. It didn't do anything to the sword. That's bad
What is fireworks standing like this corner, yeah, let's crouch they can shoot over me
We're gonna nuclear shame on you
Shame on you. Yeah, this is a shitty spot to can't because of those ones spot in the corner
You just open up this next one. I can get it here because like they all spawn
All right. Okay James like right behind you. There's a good the next one
Right behind me. Yeah, they spawn like under you. Let's not get the nice one yet
Let's let's hold it here for a bit for sure far. Yes farm, baby. Does anyone have a juggernaut?
Okay, I think it's one more door this was really good for farming I remember this
I tell we didn't ran out of ammo. That was problem. Yeah, I got thunder gun this time. So forget max ammo down there
So tell me if you see yes, I'll let him come all the way up then or you know as far up as we can
All right there
Yeah, some points for short of an infinite ammo. There you go
That that's pretty cheap at the pulse gun
Things awesome. I don't think anything in the spa. There's another power-ups down here
The hell was that dead gun. Yeah, it's going in the middle now
All right, we want to be want to stay here on a farm what I'm gonna do I
Think we stay here for a little bit longer because we have plenty of ammo right now
As long as we don't stand any further than where James is since that's what the enemies
We're good to like just hang out here. I can clear it if it gets too dangerous in one
Nobody spots behind all right
Besides the more money we make right now the faster we just push straight to the top. That's true
Somebody needs like with 13,000 and like 11,000 for the next one to think yeah
All there's another pack of punch they won't have a gun. Oh, let me thunder gun. Do you hear me? Yeah
Right. Oh god, what was that? It's lagged get it. Yeah, I got it. I'm just trying to get past the zombie
The Zeus cannon wag
That shit's strong. Oh it is
Yeah, I can like clear the entire road with this
There's still bum rushing through. Oh shit. Nothing is insane. Yeah cold like double the ammo, too
I'm running low on ammo. By the way, you still have your sword. Nope. Oh
The sword actually works pretty well. That's a good if you don't have a mo thing. It's great
Wish I kept mine. Oh, I don't miss mine
Don't expect me to like something's getting you out of shit
I'm gonna buy the next thing
Yeah, we you know
any damn old school
Might down on the ground. What the fuck? Yeah, watch these. Oh god. They're spawning right there
Jerker dog
Yeah, get this. Let's cover here. They're up here. They're up here. Oh
God, oh god
Oh boy, the gods. Oh, thank god. Come up. Come up. Come up. Come up. Yep. Follow James. Once you get a juggernaut front
I gotta get my juggernaut. Come on. I cleared it out. All right, I can't go get the juggernaut
10,000. I'll die. I'll die. I'll get it
God, I'm glad I still have it for this thing
We're gonna do it. Keep going up. I can't get it money. Keep going up buddy. Go
All right, we wait here. We camp here. Yep 11,000
I'm gonna save all my closest one to get to it. There's a gun here, too
So if we absolutely need it just so we can buy
I'm putting my thunder gun away for a bit to make some cash. Yes
James tell me if you're getting really low on health. Okay. Yes
Yeah, they're not going to fall. There you go. I'm infinite ammo. I'm gonna go now, baby
All right, save your
Yes, I could get the juggernaut I'm going for it I'm going to protect me I'm gonna get by
It's okay, I'll come with
You got insta kill so you should be all right if it was over if it ever was over. Yep
Beautiful. Thank you
That's up. You guys are standing a little bit ahead of the spawn point. Yeah
I still don't know what the fuck fireworks even does for my sword
I wonder what so where's the end is the next two more after this or what?
It's got to be a cut. It's got to be like pretty much where we were. I think
Push for it time to get those points in lads
Let's get those points in lads those points in lads I
Have like 15 runs left. So we're going through pretty quick right now
What happened here I'll get you up I'll get you up
Wait, what?
Did I get you overzealous? Oh
You gonna need to get juggernaut again now. Oh, fuck me. I do I'm so bad. I'm going for it. No, yeah
That's bad idea, I don't know if it's oh god. Oh god. I get back a little bit
We get it gets one mo gets limo
Help me push for it. We got it. Okay. I'm almost out of thunder gun ammo heads up
I got 12 rounds left. This isn't a lot considering how many I had when we started
Walking away, we should go up an axe and we're going to fall short of ammo. We got it. Well, let's get you
All right, it's everyone good on chugging dog
What's happening this sword is taking a lot what's going on
All right
Why are these doors so expensive I don't know one more one more who has enough I have enough 17 grand there it is
Wait, what the fuck friendly?
They're gonna be coming up here
Yeah, they are coming up here aren't they oh from what direction why guys
Well, what left which means I think at the bottom of the thing alone, uh
Wait, what's taking they went to the bottom? I got to pack my stuff
What's happening? Oh, it's the pack a punch. Oh
Oh fuck. I did not think this through. All right. I don't have enough money for any of this
You guys like it pretty though we should get we should get a crawler out of this out of the 56 left. Yeah
I'm pretty much out of the zoo. Sam. Oh, so I'm not gonna use it much anymore. That's up
All right. How many of us 47?
47 I don't have any spawned by Kraken. It's nice over here. By the way, just saying
I'm definitely totally down with
I don't know a man in us and said basically fuck you guys as you went down the elevator kill the dragon
What what?
Kill the dragon. It is flying pretty close to us right now
All right, we're at like 39 left we should start trying to make a crawler, okay
Are they still down here? I don't have any more nades. Well for so what what the fuck what just happened?
It took my all that happened there was it took my my juggernaut because I
Was happening without yeah, we're watching you
I'm gonna make a crawler out of one of these white walkers
What an unexplainable encounter
Is there any? Oh, there's a max ammo over here a
Free one to manage. I wouldn't take it yet. Actually actually i'm pretty low on zeus cannon. We might as well
That's yeah, that's why I figured you get it. What the fuck just happened now
Coming
Wait laser beams, how do we get through this? I think we have to fight the dragon
Oh
Fire
Oh there we're locked in here don't take that max ammo yet. I'm not it's like a sequence
Watch out craig it behind you don't kill all those zombies gonna start the next wave
No
The seven more
Now at least we have to go is that seven one two three four, but that's like 30
I don't have to pay my hbo subscription. I know how it ends. We already know no
That's not seven
I'm this is i'm
I'm a little bit disappointed that we didn't manage to do a single damage on the dragon
We didn't do one damage on him. We did one damage. I don't see anything on his bar
It looks like we didn't do any damage. It's all right. We'll be okay james
You could probably res me if you ran over to me fast. I think they're flying. They are so fast
This is i believe in you because you're you're faster james take out those six there's only six what's the problem
There's only six left james
Yeah, there's only six left dude. There's only five now
Fucking get them more on top. They just spawn on top. Okay
Why
Why'd you tell me to do that? I'm sorry james. I guess i'll leave now
Let me get up right there after that
Hey, I mean
They made a level about game of thrones. That was pretty good. I mean the dragon trick custom drag model got a hand
Yeah
Like that
Did you hear that at the end? Yeah, it's been
Oh, I thought that was one of you guys. No, that wasn't us. That was the map
No, that was a good map that that wasn't just like t-posing bowser in the corner
Speaking of t-posing bowser, let's do five nights at freddy's next god
That's a jump. That's a jump scare one. Yeah, let's do that. Oh, hell. Yeah
This one actually have jumped to jump schism
This is gonna be a scary one
It might be scary warning you
By the killer s be the killer gonna put a face game off of this one. Yeah, that's right. You should that's true
Yeah, let me get it on
Not for me guys, you know, I don't have i haven't done a face reveal yet. Someone's got a lot of graphics. It's uh
We didn't ask smile
Okay
This one's loading in a lot of uh, yeah vertices what happened polygons. He's got a lot going on
Well, yeah charging out. I got kicked out
You got kicked. I got kicked out. Did you not install this one?
I installed the pack. I mean
Was it in the pack? It should be in the pack, right back. All right. Oh, it's in the pack
What the heck happened?
It still says i'm in your game too. It's still loading for me
I'm not sure how much the dev of this map possibly put in that it should still be loading for me
Hmm. Yeah, i'm wondering that too
How much lore did they jam pack into this? Well, do you think the reason there's no ratings?
Is because it's shit. Well, I knew that is there another five. Yeah, so I warned you
I didn't know was in my solo list. Yeah, my solo list. That means I have it, right? Yeah should be
Okay. Well, then yeah, I have it
Hang on while this is loading because it's obviously still loading the game. I'm gonna take a trip to the actual page. Yeah
Take a five gander nights
five nights
at freddy's zombies
And the first comment I see is where the pack a punch
Okay, that's good. Someone's got in the game
Uh, wait, somebody got in game. What are some of these? Uh, best map i've been waiting for a FNAF map
Uh, does it seem like people are having issues playing it very fun
They say says falcon. I think my loading screen seems to be frozen. Yeah, i'm gonna
I'm gonna force it closed. James. Do you want to launch it on your own and see if it can get into it?
Just if I can get into it if I can if it even works. Yeah, I can do that
Meaty bun yells. Yeah
What if it jumpscares? Yeah, you're gonna get in
All right. So yeah
What? Yeah, I did what lower your volume because it could just it could do the
Oh
I'm gonna get scared
There better not be any jump scares says misty fives
I am in it did work. Oh, you got in. Okay
Yeah, it's not even closing for me so
It actually doesn't even look that bad. So can
Join off. Uh, you should just join off. I'm in a solo game. I'm not even looking online
I guess i'll I can try hosting it again. I mean, I don't know go for it. What the fuck
You're scared. You're scared. I'll let you guys don't tell us don't spoil. Yeah, I won't spoil. Yeah, don't spoil
James excited. Can you get in my log?
Can you get in my log possibly close this it
Oh boy
I almost blue screened I think
All right. I'm gonna try joining up you criken
Okay
Once you're in there. Did you get my invite? Can you uh, I just hit game over now
So it's gotta like load me out of here
I don't know if it worked before when I tried to connect to you
Yeah, I mean we might as well see when there's no one else in my lobby yet
Says join I can join maybe
Are you in a uh in a game right now?
Uh, i'm loading in the menu
You should hear my voice just kind of get super loud any second. No, no, it's already been there. Oh now
Already been there
Well, james still can't join me. So uh
Didn't work. I don't get why we're not friends. What did I do? What about five nights at freddy's man?
We're just not compatible too a good one
Which one was that one five minutes freddy's five?
Cry again, no, it was the one with all of them dude the one with all of them. I was all of them. God damn it
Yeah, there's like an ultimate five nights at freddy's that has all of them
I guess we'll just join kraken again. See if this time. Yeah, again. I'm gonna fix my mic
Press join game see if we get it
I love it when my mic gets all quiet and everyone's like ready to go, you know
Lobby is not joinable. What are you?
Is not joinable
All right, guys, come on come on
All right
now
It's time to spend five nights at freddy's
Be careful to get scared. Give it five minutes at freddy's and then we're switching to monopoly
Oh, you guys are gonna be really excited about this one what I saw it looks like a good one
You know, I thought it was called friday nights at freddy's for about
Two years
What friday nights at freddy's? Yeah, I mean that was like friday fridays friday is pizza night
I was like, yeah, it's a pizza place
I mean that but that wouldn't be wrong
Right. Yeah, I mean you spend what a week there
You'd spend at least one of those days one of them is friday at least one of them is friday
Probably unless you start on a on saturday sunday in which case you'd probably get off right before that's true
You somehow skip the friday
You skip friday
I think we've reached the same spot as last time. Oh my god. I did it again
Yeah
I think
The only way that we make this work is that james hosts we join on james because he's the only one that's confirmed
Had a usable map version of this
How the fuck tricky tricky tricky stuff. Is there anything I need to change?
Uh under the private but kraken does need to kraken needs to release us like yeah
Like spirit so he has to close his game to release us so we don't have to restart
Yeah, you're you're released go go forth prosper I still have the the game up I guess
It'll release us in a moment. I don't know. I'm stuck forever. It's gone
No, trust it trust it
God, I hope they make more board game maps. I don't give a shit about any of this
I just want like not like nazi zombie yahtzee, you know, I like
Yahtzee
I want them to cover everything
It's like rng based where you keep rolling the dice the monopoly one does have rolling. I know that i'm almost positive
You you you pay like 500 bucks and it rolls the dice for you and you
Yahtzee zombies
Not that's pretty good. That's pretty good. How is it not there yet? Somebody that's perfect
Come on someone hop to it. Wait a minute
Let me look it up a friend of mine
Uh recently turned 24 and he said what he did for his birthday is he played yahtzee
That was his that was what that was his activity. That's not bad. Yeah, you know, it's a good night
It's a good game. It's a fun game. You just dice around and shake it up in the container. It makes the cool satisfying noise
Maybe you get them right maybe get them wrong
All right, so well it finally released me from my torment
It released us from
You want to play a game stop dude, I don't leave my mic peaked when I do the bit
You know, that's the thing with the bit is that I turn it down after
All right, james. Let's uh
My should be major
It should be up. I guess if uh, if kraken wants to join in first, I guess he could
No, I think i'll join in because i'm your friend on steam and i'm done. Holy shit. It worked. Look at that
I'm finished with you saying that we're not friends. Are we get in are we are we good?
Do you have james on no, I don't have
The guy
Okay, I have like two people on steam
the rest is like
7 000 notifications from when he's
Turning it down too low like you should remember what it's at. No, it's it's automatic
First it goes full volume and then it goes to 60 and I turn it back up to 90
I'm joining off you kraken. Hopefully you're in there
Oh, he's in
Dude, let's play this five nights at freddy's five nights seven
six
five
Four how the fuck does that make any sense that it would have to be me as host to fucking get it to load up
I don't know all we well
I mean all I know is that you're the only person of the four of us that loaded the map and got in it
You know, okay. Wait, how many of us here has done a five nights at freddy's video razor? I have
I I have was this was this a trap? I put my hand back down. I technically I technically didn't
You technically did I did not i'm the only one I am the only one that this is a new experience for me
I didn't make it. Well, I mean i've seen the game and i've played it on a video. Okay
I I had connections back when five nights at freddy's came out
I got like early access to the second game and the third game. Oh shit
You know that guy the guy that made it. I didn't know the guy that made it
But I knew a guy that knew the guy that made it. So they said luke am I in or crash?
I think it might be crashed
Yeah, I don't think it worked for me. I think i'm i'm probably the problem child
It's waiting for yeah
I mean, it's not letting maybe this is only a single player map because I don't remember there being four other like
Schmucks in five nights at freddy's it also got stuck again for me too. It just says awaiting textures
Maybe this isn't multiplayer. Maybe we have to settle for monopoly
Settle, he said but I gotta turn the webcam off. Sorry guys
Yeah, I mean I could
I did I picked some like actual good spook levels. Oh, yeah
Well, let's do scary like there's zombie dollhouse, which is creepy clowns and shit
I like clowns though. There's cheese pick any game with cheese in the name and that's gonna be scary
simpson zombies
minecraft challenge
Do I have to do I have to reboot the fucking game? Yeah, you have to release this james
Okay, oh alien isolation zombies
That was when I uninstalled because I okay sure it wasn't actually very big that map. It's pretty small
Is it some kind of currency thing?
Oh my god, I actually can't get out of this at all. What the fuck release us. I I
You have to like yeah, I gotta fucking go to task manager. Oops, please release us
Okay. Now counterpoint. What about zombies and cars mario kart edition? Let's do it
That one actually has built-in cars. The cars work. Yeah, the cars work
The cars work working cars. Well, the the cars work, you know, james. Have you released us? It's closed. Yeah, I closed it
All right smooth clarity seconds i'm free there we go
I'm sorry that had to happen to you working. I had the working cars does sound pretty good sounds pretty cool
Yeah, that's the only reason I clicked uh, add it to collection as I saw working cars
I don't even think they had because in call of duty. So yes, that's an instant letter grade up no matter what game it is
Yeah, they they made
features that weren't in
quality black ops
That's impressive
I hope it works zombies and cars
I hope it launches dude. There's gonna be so many lol moments if you can run the zombies and with the cars
Oh my god, it'll be out of the yellow moments. All right
This is the best little little bit of education for you. All right, we call them, uh lpbs. All right
Yeah laughs laughs per bit
So you're gonna want to track your lpbs every time you do a bit
You're gonna want to get counter up every time you see a laugh
You'll know if it was a good bit or not
It's important to report this stuff accurately to our shareholders or else we're gonna get shot down
So, you know keep it
Keep it, you know, keep it written down somewhere, please
I've been i've been keeping track for years
Thanks every joke. Why are the yeah, why what's your what's your top tier? What's the big earner?
What's the big earner? Yeah, uh when I said spi like a few months ago
Spi, yeah, they got they got the biggest lpb radio. Oh, yeah, it was huge
Wow
And for so little, uh effort too. Yeah, I just it's just a simple word is yeah, it's really easy
That's that's great return. Let's uh, let's do a sequel
I don't think we've no I can't corner the single word silly voice audience yet. Criken is the problem. We haven't really gotten
that audience
My chest all need to start making up some words, man
That's they're a lot
They can't have this this guy's poaching our fucking our fucking bits for a second right now
Come to me come to me come to me
Cut him out cut him out
Our stocks are falling
He's crashing us
Oh
How do you turn
Uh turn with your mouse. Oh you turn with your mouse
Dude i'm taking like boosts and shit
Here we go music start and stop right away
Wait, what the fuck? I can't
I'll see you guys at the finish
Music only with the mouse
What? Whoa. Hey, uh, is it there's a there's a wall
The music is on for like very limited amounts of time
Wait, do you have to fight the zombies now? I think we have to get out
Hang on. I'm getting oh I fell through that. Oh, you can't
I think you just ran me over
Wait, we need 5 000 points. No, you can't run them over you can't
Okay, we're like sandwich them
So we have to run them over
Why can I not run them over?
There's insta kill. There's an insta kill
We have to pay the toll. I'm down
How do you die with a car to protect you?
I wasn't in my car double points
Double points imagine getting out of your car
I got I pack a punch my car. I think
Is that pack a punch for everybody? I think everybody got that pack a punch
Kraken mother of god. What happened to you?
I can't get you up because I have a war machine. All right, so i'm gonna do this in here until it's gone
I will die
Pick me up. Get me up. For the love of god ignore him. Help me. Why are you still picking me up?
You're all right
well
James what's up? I'm gonna need a hand. Why do we have these kind of guns?
James is running out the clock so he can win the race man. He's playing a win guys. I can win the race
How do I win the race? Well, I mean first you gotta help us because we gotta pay for the next checkpoint
This is gonna know me up because jim is dead. There's a lot more still spawning here
Well, I mean just come get me anyways
Why were they bullets coming out of these guns how is this a race if we also
Hey get me jim is not gonna make it. I mean what I can't see it didn't work. No, dude. Come on
I'm gone. I died instantly when you left
That's what I meant was that we were both about to kill over
This is not even mario. You're not even a mario kart character. You gotta go behind you
Okay
Look at the png of the mario's in the audience what the fuck
There is a weird with this hive mind like of mario's just
I want to go again. I think we can do that. Let's go. Yeah, let's see if it good
Let's see if this crashes
You know easy days to do on the piano
How is yeah, how easy go up three keys you go down three keys
Go impress your friend do it
If I had a keyboard I could do it
F g h
Hg get a digital one use the digital keyboard
website
Okay. All right. Yeah, i'll get it right now
play it
I'm gonna play right now
Okay, here we go. You have to get to watch my stream though because I can't pull through here
Just turn it out. Just turn it up really loud. I'll hear you. I'm gonna turn up really loud
I'm gonna lean into the mic
Can you hear it?
What wait, what do you mean?
I guess it wasn't a tune. Did you just realize it was wrong? Yeah, it's it's different the tone goes a little
I'm opening the game back up one elaborate one elaborate fucking bit
I thought I thought it was dead and dead dead. Uh, right
Yeah, it's a little different than that
Oh, oh he's lpb farming, right?
He's stealing our shits
I got too excited about all those new all those new comedy people
comedy people
Wait, why am I in your how am I in your lobby? But you're not like actually in a lot
Why are you in my lobby? I thought you were hosting dude. Let's turn on let's turn on black ops 3 multiplayer
Yeah, I got really excited really fast and then sometimes I get a little worked up it's okay. Yeah, you sir. Yeah, that's all right
You know, it's honestly the most jarring thing we could possibly do at this point play an actual call of duty black ops 3 zombie
Level and just see how fucking shit every other one die
Honestly, I can't even go back now at this point
Yeah, yeah, I never started to begin with I can't I think I can do that ever for the no
This is the only experience
it's like imagine
Imagine play imagine all these levels
But they've jam-packed about 20 000 times more needless complexity into zombies like for every actual level
There's like a billion different things you're supposed to do a thousand easter eggs
Every map is supposed to last like four months. It's insane and awful
honestly
And other people that play zombies in it. Yeah haven't some levels they just
They marathon lasted forever
They last forever and some levels might as well be like small cities at this point
You know one of them the what the first one in this game actually is a small city
You have to take a fucking bus to get to spots of it. It's like a it's like transit
It's like it's more chores. It's more chores than taking trams than it is playing the level. Oh my god
Imagine that zombies in time. Oh, we're we're doing this again. Right? Okay, I forgot
So someday german when you're in a conversation with someone at a party and they're like, oh I love nazis played
And you have to think you have to think to yourself
How do I answer this?
If you say yes, he's in mario kart version. How do you how do you relate to it?
You just pretend you'd be like, yeah, I could because I know about the boxes and buying and stuff
I'm first. I'm first. I'm first
No, you're not anymore boy
Dude, I totally screwed you over
Oh, this sounds awful
Why is my engine stuttering like this?
Damn, I was gonna knock you off the road, man
I knew there was a turn coming up. I couldn't do that forever. I love how the music's so temporary
What the fuck? I mean we have to make money
We can't even open this until we make some money
I've I found something. All right, everyone. Let's make some money at the beginning of the level. There's something back here
Oh
Jesus christ, why'd that zombie jump? I knew you were gonna be fine
I mean, we should never be caught because we can run there's so much space to run
Somebody just said this looks like a shitty mobile game
One of like the 4 000 ipad versions of this game how do we get up here? It's the kill
There's the music
And it's gone
Nice now, how much does this cost?
5000 5000. Oh
This is gonna be a bad race too many. Hello
What was that? That it looks like a pack of punch thing, but like
What does it actually do? Oh, it's a streaker
What oh
I'm getting real sick of my music just turning on for the first four beats and then turning off
That's how the member you know that myth about copyright
As long as you only play it for 10 seconds, you're fine
Oh my god
Nintendo's yet to find this they won't find dastardly creator
Is a shrieker it's it's like one of the dragons
Dragons, I don't know what the hell the ticking is the sound of you getting any points watch
No, I don't want any points
Oh it is
Someone can afford to open someone can afford blue guy can do the race blue and the guy from over here actually killing stuff
What we were killing? Oh, you took my car german get out. So i'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry
Hey, hey, this thing's a leash
Oh, what the hell?
Are we good?
James open it. I went backwards and I found a secret. What's secret?
secret, dude
I'm gonna find this guy. It doesn't it doesn't look like there's any like power back here though
So I gotta you gotta open this i'm leasing this nine-year-old bmw
Wait, I can spawn a car. What what's secret? Ah, james open it
What the fuck I don't think you can help anywhere near you guys. Yeah, it's only it's only 480 dollars a month
Did you leave trekking back there? He's he's gonna die. Well, I thought we were all going to
Examine I don't think we're gonna make it. Yes, we both jump over the wall
Oh, oh my god. Oh, we can't uh, no looks like you can't looks like you're hang on. Let me try
All right. Yeah, i'm in i'm in the car
Hey, well that works on my back
Your car don't you leave me don't do you want to stay with your car my car's on the wall if you just stay in the car
I'm sorry. What? Hey, i'm sorry. Why would you leave me? I mean
This is why we're ever gonna be this level because we're all fucking abandoning each other
He owes me a new one well you can have that one but just I got you guys here
There's gotta be there's a way to spawn cars. I think yeah
I'll find where I am. Are you good? You sure? Yeah, you you go
I'll buy a new car. I was about to just go. Ah, wow. Wow. Wow. Wow. Wow wicked loud. I'm so glad
Where am I going? All right. Sure. This is a robbery get out of your car
Okay
Get our p. Oh, what the fuck?
Wait, oh no
Holy shit, they're still born
Yeah
Okay, stop get out of the car, okay have it
I think you just stuck there forever. Where are you? I'm in the middle
Oh god, you are in the middle. What is this? This is what I found. It's that perk machine that gives you the fucking infinite perk
You can get all the perks in the game
Wow, what a map to get every perk in the game. I know
Oh, dude, I got a fucking van you are just stuck in there, huh?
Yep
All right. I want to go in there like what wedge into my back and see if we can like fling me in there
Jump start you over that. Yeah, see if we can like slingshot me in there
Let me get some speed. This is not a good place. Can they get into the car?
Oh, I think i'm getting ripped apart my zombies inside of my car. I think they're in the car
What the fuck wow that looks so much fun
I think my wheel is bugged. I can't turn
Do you get something real there's something do I have like a fucking like fin stuck in my wheel like a plane wing
Or something. Whoa, you just jumped
How'd you do that? I got some sort of I got some sort of wheel. I got some sort of metal shard in my wheel
I paid two thousand bucks for this thing dude. Yeah, there is something stuck here
I don't know. Let me see if I can help you get me off of this thing
I can't there is to kill me how much is a car?
It's like two thousand five hundred. That's it
You gotta like go up to that putt that blinking pipe. Yeah
Don't die d dies
I'm gonna get you in like a second. Okay, it's pretty good. Well, you guys need me to buy dude
I don't know. I'm trying to get all these. All right, keep them off
You guys have fun out there
Yes
Every time giant gun with one hand. I need to get up on this blue part. How the fuck?
Here i'll give you a boost
Can you is that possible? I don't know. I'm trying that these zombies are like steel man. I can't
I think something really are wrong with these cars
Hey guys a hot take this map is awful
Guys, I got better
Oh, wait, hold on i'll get you i'll get you i'll get you do you see I don't know if you know, uh
Jeremy you're not using two hands for that gun
Do you look over here look over here
Yeah, that doesn't that doesn't work
You're not gonna hit very many. That's why you can't hit anything
Now it makes sense. Uh, you're gonna die too
Holy shit, I can't believe you just did that come back for me
I know I know what?
What happened?
No, it was the grenade. It was just a grenade. It's okay
I'm dead
Why dude, it's okay, but there's no zombies. I don't know. I I expected I was cooking a grenade and I was gonna throw
It but I held it. Whoa. Whoa, i'm up here. It was funny. It was just for a joke. That was what it was
Oh, you spawned up there. I knew you did
There's something up there
Hit the power at the end where yeah, i'll get it all the way into on the right side
There's something over there. I mean i'm not compelled to come down there ever again now because I don't think zombies spawn up here
I see him. I'm gonna go by the door that you guys wanted to fucking buy
You can't help me
Oh looks like it looks like the pack of punches up baby
Are you throwing grenades in here? Wait
Maybe if you if you move a car close enough, I can climb into it. Can't you oh, that's that a good idea
James I got bad news turns out you just had to pay money to open up the end of the race
Yeah, you you get to the spot. There's a staircase on the other side. That was odd. Okay. Oh, that's fine
Can you get over here? Yeah
Did you do it? I killed myself. Yeah, I got a pack of punched, uh shotgun because of that
What's up with this car?
Oh, what the fuck is up with this car?
I can hear can I hear you shooting from this far away? Yeah, I got a pack of punch shotgun, man
Of course, it's gonna make a little bit noisy. You know what i'm saying? Help me, please here. Uh, i'll get you
Let's go around. Let's finish this race. I'm good. I'm good. Yeah, you're what's got me. Oh, yeah
You guys want to finish the race?
Uh, yeah, let's like that's how you get over to this side. You need to finish the race
Come on
You should be able to win on zombies
Come on, what's the code here?
What's the i'm gonna die in the car
If you die in the car, that means you're like the worst gamer right like you this it's so easy to get away from
No, i'm talking about if you're driving like straight
No, I've had no disrespect. I really did wait. I want a new car
I'm gonna open up the gateway. You'll be able to go straight through
This is nice
That's a nice car. Yeah, like yeah
So i'll take one of these if only I could drive it
All right, who is it? Who is the need to be in the car with 5 000 points?
You gotta be in the car. All right. Well, I got a cool james boncar. Maybe we should get in this man
You get in what?
It closed the gate I saw that what
Uh, oh you son of a bitch it's pushing me out of the world. I can't
Wait, there's a fox over here, too. What the fuck is all this stuff? Okay
Stop i'm trying to get in too pay the fee. I don't have enough money
You do you not have enough money? No move this car
Why is mario
What
Why is he under there dude, i'm not i'm not feeling good anymore. I don't know what's happening. Uh,
uh
My car has gone vertical. I am
help
James what's up, man? I don't need a hand. I'm walking over of course in the mario lives always at two
This is so stressful. You're you're straight down. I need you to bring her car over here and open the gate
You are straight down
There's something there's some gum stuck in my axle
My back wheel's got a wing stuck in it. I can't where's kraken
I've been dead. Oh you're dead. Oh, okay
I'm afraid if I get out i'm gonna get eaten by zombies. So i'm just gonna stay in the oh
i'm coming
What the fuck is wrong with this car that car is fucked
You're gonna have to get out and push him
You're gonna have to ram me wait, there's fucking zombies here. Oh, I know they want to get me man. You gotta
Oh, no
Look, I think you're wedged in there coming to your left
I need to be in a car as well. You gotta be in a car
I can't get to where you are. Don't ruin mario kart for me get in that fucking car and open this door
Spawn a new one. They're only 2,500
I can't get out of this thing. It's absolutely
Not possible at this point coming
God damn it
hell
Unwedge me
Did everybody else see the mario? I don't think so. Yeah, I saw the mario. Is this car right here?
I was watching you. Oh you saw the mario. Oh, okay. That's why I was laughing
Uh, no, you're never gonna get in there james
It didn't work. If you get too close, it'll eat your money and continue to like oh, oh, oh god
Oh god, are you okay? It's happening. It's happening. I'm going through the wall. I think oh no. Oh, i'm free. I'm good
The zombie's gun now it's almost like they had a they had a big plan for that mario
And it just it just didn't work out so that it's like ah, it's too. I can't delete it. It's too big
I can't yeah, it's like stuck there glitched out. I have to put it underneath. No one will ever see it
James you gotta get in that car
I'm gonna get in this car. Let me know when you do don't touch that thing until i'm there too. I gotta slip through
I can't move this fucking car. Don't don't touch that thing yet. You're gonna leave me
go
Hey juggernaut is here, dude. Oh very cool
I just can't believe it didn't let you in. No, I can make the money easy though. I got pack a punched guns
I just thought like, you know as as a team as friends because everyone else is dead here. I gave back
How did you get a pack a punch good?
Uh the finish line
Oh, that's right. I see you. Hey, hey, I got the money
You got through
One came through
Can you clear can you make sure that place is cleared out for me so I can like run in it's clear
Oh, well, there's a couple that that come through but there's not
There are dogs behind
Doing like a weird what's this walk they don't even want to fight you. Yes
Oh, what the fuck I think you might have forgotten but there's a race that's on right now james
I'm right behind you. Is this beginning of the level?
Oh tree
Oh
Okay. Well, this level is awful. I'm gonna
I'm gonna vote in for taco bell the car that kreiken was just sitting there
What do you guys think?
Because I don't think with this tree here we can finish. I don't think it's possible
So I think you're supposed to get up here you're supposed to probably get the ramp ramp over ramp up here
But I mean like I did the lap technically
Yeah, I guess we did
Oh look up here. It says I fucking hate this map
Oh, well, that's a good enough sign for me. I think it's time to play taco bell
Taco bell mcdonald's or I can see the outside of the map right here. I can see give me a boost
Can you see underneath? Oh, you're pushing me under turn and look underneath if you can
Hold on. They're coming
I can see a better place a better
I want to see it so bad. Give me a boost
I want I think i'm gonna let him take me. I got an idea
Kill me james. I'm not I can't do this with you anymore. Okay, you have zombie blood. They can't see you
Wait, hold on. Can you guys just walk around the tree?
Is this
Go win the race tomato. That was your chance
He's held up
Goodbye james. I'm sorry
Wait, no, it's not it doesn't matter as much if you don't like to feel bad about me
I'm just trying to get out of this world
On a car spawn a car get a car get a car, dude
Oh, i'm bankrupt. I don't have any money for a car. I don't have any money that one
This is my old car. I left this car here. I glitched out up here
This is it
This is the one I kept this one can fly, you know, this is your chance
Wait
That's how I died. Be careful, please
I can see it. Oh, yeah, that that is how two people have died on this map not by the zombies
second lap
How many laps in this lap that's five
Va
No way
That was some pretty good pretty good driving around I need another 5 000 bucks to open the door again
What do you think these like parts do there's random parts on the map, too
I don't know what the fuck this man. I don't know how to explain this to you, but I don't think I care what they do
You're trying to fucking win the race. No, I want to go
I want kraken to close the lobby, but he keeps on telling me to race
There must be a winner I feel like I won. Can we go? Someone has to win
I can't fuck. Oh, wait quick. Look look Mario. Oh
Wait, i'm alive. What am I alive?
Why are we alive? We can win this
What did they just trade his life for ours? We sacrificed him to the giant mario statue
What the fuck now is our time
It's the time to shine. Oh, we're going backwards. They're going the wrong way. I'm gonna get this cold
Brewski and let's go
I think are we going the wrong way?
I think it's the right way
Oh, there's so many what the fuck. Yeah, no way you're gonna get swarmed
They're all treated. I just spit all over myself. Hey, I got insta kill for you guys. Oh, wait
Go into that corner over there
Yeah, yeah, go it's too many watch this
Investigate that corner. It's further over
I mean, I do want to see the mario again. Oh, I see what you're saying
It's well, I i've dropped through further. It's over here. It's over here. It's over here. What is another bar?
Yeah, yeah, yeah, that's that's where there it is. This is this is the lip. This is the lip
Okay, where where is mario's location? All right, I
Is it this this way
Where's the center? The center is that way, right? I'm gonna start spinning around. All right, you just start
Just start spinning around. I'll tell you east. He's east which way which east
I'll put hold him think about east is it could be anybody's east. Why is that actually under there?
How do I capitalize on that and find him in kraken's honor?
It's right. I don't know where east is
It's on the other end of the tunnel there he is
um
What the fuck is everyone else dead? Is it just me? I don't have any money. Can we win the race? Did I win?
Yeah, you won. I don't really want to grind money to do this mario bit. Honestly
I don't think the lpb is gonna
What do you get that mario model? You know what I mean?
Yeah, gmod
Just gmod and you made it
I don't know. You can't like pull data from from like the wii u disc. Oh, yeah, you can totally convert
You can pull like the mario t-post from like
wii u
For sure. Oh
crashing
That means it was a good map
All right. How you guys feeling do I do one more?
I don't want to hold you guys hostage if you're all burnt out from
This chaos we can do another one. I'm good. I'm good. I'm good
All right. Well, there's zombie cat tree, which I kind of want to try and then there's uh, what happened?
When are we doing?
We heard monopoly monopoly so much fun we've never gotten past like the second wave of monopoly, but
I mean, this might be the crew. We might have trained enough
Oh, I think we've trained enough
I can hear him swallowing tomato
Dude get out of my fucking ears
I'm just
I'm just waiting that's the kind of microphone that you can hear the person's mom trying to talk to them
You they're in like the xbox lobby and you hear like
You want this or that? No, I'll take uh, yeah, I want
Yeah, i'll take the chicken
All right
It's not on me. You hear them like smoking you can hear them smoking fucking cigarettes
You guys have been able to hear that before you can you ever hear somebody else in the room?
Smoking cigarettes like not the person that's in the lobby the person like on their couch
Yeah, I swear to god like 20 feet away. Yeah, you just hear like
I can hear it. I swear to god. I've never had that
Monopoly dude, you guys haven't gotten past wave two
It's so hard. Wow
We didn't have enough. I think we're also cracking was that last time we did this
We only had three people and did we have more this was the first one we did last time
You know, how many people did we have when we did it? I think we had three. Yeah, so we were not
Yeah, we were short a guy. We were short a guy and we were not we had no idea what we were doing
So all right. Well, hey what what how about why don't we do taco bell first and and give a two minute time?
You want to warm up the tuck? All right, we'll start with taco bell. Let's start with a three minute time talk about kfc because
All right. I'll be honest. There's there's mcdonald's 1.0. There's taco bell 2.0 and kfc 3.0
All I can say about mcdonald's is definitely the best map, but I think taco bell has the best
You know
Presence taco bell then taco bell was the one that won the vote. Okay. All right deal
Yeah, we don't have to do the whole thing working drive-through. It's just so on the features
Look every time I have taco bell
I'm like
This is going to be the time that I enjoy taco bell and every time I get sick and I wish I didn't have taco bell
What are you ordering?
There's no way you can't enjoy it if it's completely digitalized, you know
What are your favorite things on the menu favorite things on the taco bell menu?
I don't know because i've been sick every time i've had any of those. I would say
Last last time we talked about this everyone got hungry which is crazy. Yeah. Yeah
I mean, you don't want to make me hungry because i'll leave i'll leave. I'm trying to join
I'm trying to join your uh lobby won't let me for some reason
Really? Oh, yeah, i'm posting again. It shouldn't be anything different
I don't even see you playing
Yeah, I keep accepting that I keep accepting that invite but then nothing happens
Is your game offline because i've had some instances. Oh shit you're playing. Yeah
Play online about just quit the game and reload it
Yeah, well, yeah, just hit play online and see if it'll connect you and then maybe
That's weird
Well, I mean, okay
Just checking my files
You guys have a cheesy gody to crunch from taco bell. Oh, no, but I haven't but that sounds so good
Did you say no, it's actually pretty good. Isn't that one of the that's one of the like, uh the stapled items
Yeah
Would it be
Like should I order that right now?
Yeah, you're gonna post mate some taco bell right now. I mean i'm i'm like
fuck
You just said yourself though, like you fucking don't like it. I always regret it. No, don't post
Don't break the rule to yourself. You post mates after so if you're gonna do it
You gotta fucking do it real quick. Yeah, you can't post mates after 12 a.m
After 12 a.m, like the gremlins come out you you'll never get your water. I have totally done it
Every time i've ordered post mates after midnight
It's just like half the thing isn't there or it's like somebody
Somebody picked it up with their hands like threw it in the bag and it's just like a mush at the bottom
Never order post mates after midnight. It's always the worst
Oh, no, okay
Sometimes I have i've had post mates before with half the bag was napkins and then like they forgot four parts of the order
Oh my god, it's just like somebody just it was like a joke somebody like was making a joke
Okay. Okay. Okay. I'm looking i'm looking I can order it. Uh
Uh
Okay, three three of them is a lot three of the combos what are you kidding me?
No, not the full combo. Just the thing. Why don't you get the fucking combos half the half that's garbage in there
Okay, just get the actual is this this is taco belly. You're eating like the why are you all yelling at me?
No, i'm getting mad now. I think it's time to get away my phone. I'm putting away my phone
All right. Wait, i'm hold on. I need to look at the menu here because I can't find on my phone
So just what the fuck is happening in here one time. I throw up
If the cheesy gody to crunch is not on here delete this
I actually see it's my specialties. It's the second one in on specialties. Okay, i'm trying to look what's in it. It's three
289 289 sense let let them decipher what it is. Can you figure out what it is?
Uh beef beef i'm looking at beef looking at some it looks like green
And cheese, uh, I look a little closer
What makes that different? What makes that cheesy gody to crunch the thing that it is? What is it? Oh, there's two
There's two there's two. There's two taco
Yeah gone
And cheese on both
Hold on. We got
This service here sucks, oh my god, it's to kill wow
Get up hard and soft shell within one another that's crazy. That's crazy. It's crazy. You're right
It is crazy and this cheese spread on the soft shell. I'm dead again
Oh my god, I forgot. We're playing a video game. I definitely take money from them to bring up this sort of shit on stream
Every time i'm gonna uh box that's why you think I picked this map and added it to my collection delicious
Okay, that's cheesy gordita taste
The fire sauce
This is there's like a there's like a fiery burning asshole joke in here
If you guys want to see some mellow moments, it's in there
I'm not allowed to talk about that because I they asked me not to I love to talk about burning assholes
Let's take a look. Take a look at me. It's there. Oh, that's pretty funny
That's all you know
relatable
Relatable if I were if I was the map maker I'd put red all over this that's gonna be you in a fucking
couple hours here
What if i'm gonna sleep by then?
No, that's not good. You don't want to sleep with diarrhea in your body
Because then you know, it's in there and you know, you gotta get it out sloshing around
Yeah, whatever gets us out of this whole conversation sounds pretty good get me out
Yeah, get me out. Come on
No, it doesn't it doesn't
He's doing the speed voice guys. Everyone. Listen, it doesn't do that. It's like that's like a joke. It's like a meme
Oh my god
Well, I opened the door you guys
You can go outside and the taco bell if you'd like
Why would I want to leave?
Hey, I got the thunder gun
Oh, that thing's good
Okay, clear them off of me clear them off of me get them off of me
Hey, I don't know if that was
Bro, come on get me out. Hey, did you know that if you eat taco bell like did you get like fucking crabs?
Like that doesn't happen like
I mean like I
I don't remember many times after I had taco bell that I like was incapacitated for like
And did you know that it's like 75 percent fake meat a day's human meat in it, too
They have their menu back here. This is hostile. Wait, wait at the back of the mopping hold them up
No
You got it, that's if you can read the menu closer
All right. I don't think they had the gordita crunch. You guys see this like hostile advertising on the back of the fucking
Is there wait? Why why is this burrito crisp? I mean a massive
Why is it?
It says mcdonald's is coming soon
Coming soon. I mean that map exists. They got empanadas. They've empanadas at the taco bell
Huh?
You fucking serious up
I'll post mace it right now, too. Hi. Well, we're over our three minutes on this map guys. So it's time to wrap up
I'm gonna order these empanadas. I gotta I gotta order food. Hold on. Let me order the food. Are we all gonna order?
2 000
Oh not in real life. All right, i'm actually gonna do it
so
I don't know the hell. Oh shit
I think did it give me this is this hey, do you guys want to see a funny meme?
Let me know well you you better order before the gremlins come up
All right. Well, here's a funny meme if you look at top left
It says 30 customers left
God damn. Oh, i'm physically looking
Yeah, looking instead of zombies. They're implying that the zombies are customers
I get it mexi fries
Hold on a minute. This stuff isn't even real
Wait, why are we still looking at the fucking menu? Yeah, I don't this is I i've been to taco bell a lot of times
Mexi fries mexi fries. No, those are real. I had someone talking about those earlier today in my chat. I saw it
Someone brought up mexi fries. They took them off of the menu. I don't know why
But they actually removed they executed them recently from the menu
I know they had they must exist because someone someone talked about them and there's no way they sell cigars
Look at no
No beef burrito. Look at that. That's a that's a nice cigar
Look at the bottom
Yeah, I see it. Oh
I mean, I think it's legit. I think those two exist. I'm trying to read the menu still quit beeping behind me
All right, we're all here at fucking two o'clock in the morning. You don't have to hold the horn down
50 people behind me trying to punch me all the way down underground
Did you guys ever understand that when people do that shit?
Oh, I definitely don't have time to get you it's like a thousand guys
Oh now I do should I get a cool ranch
Stop squirming. I'm not moving. I haven't even moved at all
Like doing this a little wiggle. Are you what the fuck happened? Oh, you're dead
Yeah. Oh, yeah, i'm dead
Taco time is taco time taco bell
Is that a different company? Wait, is this wait a minute? This is not even taco bell
Could this guy not get the actual taco bell menu? You want to get fucking serious?
Taco time is a different restaurant
They keep grabbing adjacent taco themed restaurant and put it up on his taco bell menu like map
We're shilling for the wrong restaurant buddy
Did you kill them all? Yeah. Oh, there's one customer left
Don't kill them. I need to go underground to explore this map. What's the fiery sauce? What is that called?
Fire sauce. It's not on here. It just says fire sauce hot sauce technically fire
How many mick chickens do you think guys could eat in one sitting if you were really hungry? I'm gonna say six. Uh, 30
Wait 30. Oh, I thought you meant nuggets mick chickens. Oh, yeah, I always like to get nuggets
Make chickens. I could probably do four or five
I eat a lot 30
I eat a lot. You'll be winning competitions
Ask kraken. I eat a lot. He does eat a lot. I eat I eat an abnormal amount
No, wait watermelon
Yeah, the beginning said shoot three watermelons. There's gonna be some joke here
Where you follow that pipe all the way to the end. It might yeah
It might be a joint and that's gonna pump into the restaurant as like the meat or something. You found all teddy bears
Yay, what does that mean? I think i'm gonna jump in this makes fun music hole
Oh
Don't go down there don't
This is a real band I think it's like some 41 I don't want to go to school. I just want to stay at home
Oh
Art careful last one I went in it killed me instantly
Man, we waited just long enough to talk there that we definitely murdered all of our vods. That's pretty cool
I was a good well unified silence
The fuck do I open this saw you land the watermelon. I need the other watermelon to open it
I I love this taco bell map play through
I wish this played in taco bell
No worries guys i'll find this
It's probably up there
It actually to come back to taco bell. This is this is some 41 by the way
Yeah, I have all their albums I just know I know so
No
I do this thing where you know how like you play
You get in the car and you pick up a few people and you get you know
You want them to hear your music that you think is good?
And then you but you're you you know that they're not gonna like this
But like maybe if you put on the best one of the album they'll listen and go
Oh, actually, this is pretty fucking cool. You're like, yeah, it's pretty good. I i'll put on some some 41
I do that to everybody and I put this song on
And I like I just sit there and I hope that they're gonna be like this is pretty good and I like
Validate myself going like yeah, it is fucking kind of good. You know that it fell off recently
Literally now I have like a poster of all of them separately not just the band as a whole
Each individual band member is on the wall
Why are we doing why are we I think this is symbol I think it's symbolic of the song
I want to be relieved. He's doing a bit with the song lyrics
Can we
Look at this little car
Can we all acknowledge how small this car is?
funny strike
I can't hear anyone actually by the way this song. Oh, it's over. All right
It is talking back down turn it back on i'll be right back. Oh my god
Yeah, no, the answer to that was yeah, i'm going done
Why do you guys start us with these embarrassed for you? What are these?
They're like some really bad fucking crossbows. I thought we were leaving
I thought I put something
We need we need enough to get through the other door
Oh
I found a I found a
That'll be the end of my story. Oh
Oh, no
What do you think this so you never found the last watermelon james? No, there's one more left
To get to get the map
Yes, here I go
Oh, fuck
All right. There's three left two left. Okay. They're after me. We're okay
Silence why why do you get an accent when you sing like punk songs?
You know what I mean? I know I like you can honestly sing any lyrics and make it sound like punk song
If you just drag out every fucking consonant every e every a and every oh, yeah. Yeah all the vowels
silence
midnight
zombies crawling in the dark
Well, you said you should know it would be crawling crawling in the dark crawling
Close close a zombie shield by the way if I can get the copyright shit
You're not gonna join the fucking band. Oh, no, it's an original song james. Don't worry
Croiling it's crawling crawling crawling in the
That's like it's so exaggerated
Go croiling
You sound like a friend of them. Oh, they were just
They can't hit me behind the glass
ill, dude
glass
All right, can we get the fuck out of here? I want to leave
Why are we still doing this here? I'm with him. Let's go join yourself. I found it. Wait, hold on
That's just a bag. We need the last one. No, we don't
We have to be one
This is killing me james
Wait, there's only 20 actually it's killing me. It's killing
There really are only like 18 left. Oh, but we gotta get out of here
Oh my goodness. There's one left. I trimmed the pack
Nobody's reviving me
Sitting in the pavement of the driveway where the car's on
Morton goldman from family guy
Oh james, I found it
I got it. They gave us a free perp. Well i'm leaving. Yeah
I found another pack. Yeah, that's about the end of it for me folks. Oh wait
Wait, I can order food for two thousand dollars. I'm sorry. Do it. Do it. Do it
I just I just gave me a times two multiplier
What's happening that's it
Hey guys, hey, you could get something nifty up here right here monopoly something nifty
Blink for 20
Get that double points now tomato in the driveway
Okay, it sounds like you're doing you're doing a joke like hold your nose and scream strain like i'm not holding my nose though
Oh shit
I can't wait to be all bound. I can't wait to be open just now. How the fuck do we
Beat this level
Does that door open? Whoa, you just figured it out. Oh my god. I beat it
Bleach what is it? What is it? Tell us quick get it
What is it? I'm here. Oh, don't bother
You don't need to it's bleached sodium
Garlic oh
63,000 to secure this. Oh my god. Wait, can they not come in here?
63,000 I don't want to wait here
Two hours. I definitely want to enable this level and it's silly joke at the end by paying
This place and i'm gonna be fucking bleached i'm dying. I kill myself. Wait, i'm not dead. Whoa
Looks like it was a delayed fuse
How do I get down there to you guys?
Uh, go back down go down into the sewer, uh through the like road the little garage
The little garage
Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I see it. Yeah. Oh, yeah. Yeah go down in the garage and then turn off take away
Here come down here into the sewer. All right, nice
Watch out watch out
And then we okay that just that just disorientated me. I don't know what that happens
All right, here we go
now in here
For the silly bit fun funny funny funny funny funny funny funny. You can't wait and see it. It's really funny
I'm gonna look at it one more time. Yeah, okay
Yeah, did you see the other did you see the other funny thing that was there too what is it right there
Look on the ingredients the second one second second second last one
cocaine
I'm gonna just keep doing this till we end the level. Yeah, i'm actually i'm the one that ends this level
Yeah, what the fuck are you saying?
Yeah, i'm about to hit the escape button, please i'm really close to the 60 60 000 i'm gonna do it
All right
How do I only have 6100 points did I do anything
I had zero headshots. You guys just kept fucking dying and talking about taco
You guys may as well have just thrown my dead body down the hallway and I would have killed more people
Uh
Well, what do we have left we got well, we actually have a lot left technically if we want to be honest
But there's a lot left kranken we have I don't think we've actually done 50% of the entire pack
I put together from like both streams
damn
Hey, uh
I was using the crossbows the whole time monopoly
monopoly
Monopoly has always seemed pretty good. You know, you guys are gonna love it. There's a lot of you guys toss this one up
There's a lot of visual inspiration on the monopoly here
Guess who it's made by
Is it? No, no, no
Is it my boy
You gotta guess who it is
Uh-oh waiting connection. I can't wait till we get halfway through this and somebody flips the table
Like everyone
It's killjoy
No, who the hell else did you expect to make a board game level? What is this noise?
It's money. Welcome. Well
You guys wanted it my gun like you guys kept asking why is there like a california smog over this
There's like a haze. There's like a smog and stuck here for countless hours
What is he saying the shadow man? We have to free the shadow man from this game so he can live in peace
Don't get too distracted by the lore or else the zombies will get you. This is like a this haze is kind of making me hurt
Well, that's the haze of economic uncertainty. Oh god, I fell off
Don't fall off of the uh board
Okay, so how do we play? How do you even how do you even get to the next?
Uh, whoever's blue just like press f on these guys
Yeah blue me
Yeah
I lied about the intricacies of it. It really just moves like two
It doesn't even fucking what did you land on my third trap my final trap of the evening
It's really just candy land again
I am there's not enough room for us to be here. I'm out of ammo
Well, this is why we only made it two
Welcome to my trap dungeon
Do you at least get to pick like a dude do we get why don't we just play monopoly like actually?
So what are you guys doing tomorrow?
Oh god
We need more money
Someone has enough to get us through. I'm gonna get it. I got it. I think I rolled it. I just fell off
Nice axe. What did you what was that? How'd you do that? Wait, how'd you do that thing? We got a chance
I took a chance. You can hold e. Oh
Nice
Push dice
We're in jail going
No, no, we're just visiting we're just visiting
All right, you know actually this is the farthest we ever gotten i'm gonna go keep going
I wish I had any ammo
Yeah behind us
Oh, oh god, I fell off. Oh guys if you're like screwed you can warp all the way back to the beginning
Max ammo, that's what i'm talking about. Nice work
Fuck. Yeah, who did that?
What we might win? That was fucking awesome. You're the man who fucking picked up that max ammo doomseries
All right, why can't I get this gun
Oh, you got a 50 push
God damn it. I didn't have enough
Yo, so if you're like in danger jump off the board because it'll send you back to the start. I need to buy a gun
Uh buy, uh buy this if you have the money for it buy the uh buy this one. It's good almost
It shoots bullets
Which is pretty much the only quarter I have
Oh my god, oh my god
I'm jumping
I thought that guy just called me a turd
who's uh
Who's the guy with the hat?
Has 20 3000
Someone has 3000 points. I do i've been trapped over here
Give it to me. Give it to me
Uh, oh
What I spent it all. Uh, oh
I have a question for anybody. Why does monopoly matter here?
Uh
What does it matter? Stop stop with that thinking of yours. It's candy land
It's just a monopoly board just just go ahead and help help me kill these fiery catches
These pikachu things this is fucking music again
I'm pushing forward a bit. We're almost to the box. I love that killjoy community chest
He's built a really interesting brand with his mouse
All right, who's gonna open this one?
Fine charge zombies rent
Yeah, put a hotel on there. Yeah, do it when they land on it
I think a better gun. How do I do that?
I think we gotta kill someone somebody just somebody just said that and it was uh,
Oh
I believe you
three parts
I'm down
Oh, are you? Help me
I have no god good gun
Axe ammo
Here it is
Oh my god, it's 9 50 hold f to take a chance. Oh, oh fuck. It wasn't a good chance. Okay
The odds hang on i'm gonna try
Don't touch this spending money
No, it's free, but i'm just making sure that it's safe for everyone. It's not don't touch this thing
I think he uses 10 bucks a pop actually
This is probably my so it doesn't do that's third time
three times a charm
I don't know if my odds are bad or what i'm gonna try to get you try it. I'll get you one
I think this is a kill on touch situation
Why do you guys keep doing that?
Because it seems like it takes some money when you use it, which means it might give you something
Hang on. We got ants to kill. I'm trying one more time
It's possible that you could do this and then hit the mega bonus. It's possible. It gives you something really good
You want to give it a go?
What's this thing?
Why is this thing red? Oh, I think he's the last one
Yeah, all right. Wait, wait for the next wave to start. I think I I think the chance is it's a chance to desync you
From the game i'm warping out
Don't feel stop chancing it dude
I'm like i'm getting this like this pop up on my screen
That shows something yanking out the ethernet cable of my computer and I don't know what's happening to me. What?
I think my internet is breaking down
Zombie shield dude
Lots of zombies
Where did you even where did they come from?
Oh, I think i'm dead. Don't even bother getting me up. I've entered like a twilight zone
Oh, they're moving the dice. Uh, oh, I think what if I dice a little bit? Oh, oh
Oh, no moving again, dude
I got a pass go keep moving. I keep moving it. Whoa
I'm sorry. I failed james. I'm sorry jump off jump up
Wait, what if I jump off?
Jump off
Can I jump off and respond like for you go? Are you here? We'll get you we'll get you like down
I can't I can't go off. Oh, that's it then
All right, it's happening back to you
Oh and too many I respond are you you respond? Okay
Tomatoes gone tomato. I took the chance and the chance was a chance to crash my game and that's what it did
So i'm rejoining now. No one's smoking you
Fuck you. No, it's your fault for not stopping me. You know, I you know, i'm prone to gambling
It's in my personality and you watched you fucking
Yeah
How much is it just push 850 still? Oh god 15 now
Max ammo. Oh my god. I feel overwhelmed. I just gotta dive off. I'm leaving time to do time to do guys times two though
It wasn't worth we're so close on the dice am I going the wrong way here i'm rejoining fuck
Hello
What's that? Who's talking?
You guys welcome welcome to the stream what a god
Wait, i'm on the other side of the dice guys. I gotta get the food
Press the lobby is not joinable. Well guys guys, uh, hope you guys know we're we're so close to like
We have to complete it we have to complete it
Oh, did you pass go? Oh my god
Then what does that mean? What do we what happens now? That means roll it again. You keep good game
You get all these perks
stupid as that sounds
Okay, that sounds very stupid I don't know how that dog killed him did he explode on me
I did it. I got to go
Do we get anything for go? I don't think so
Is there like a button near there that you can do we did it. We finished it
I think this is just parked. Okay, it's 25 000 to escape
Well, that's not a lot
That's what you do this. It's just right back here. We can do this. I'm inviting you
I can't I don't think I can join even if you invite me. I think try I
I literally I have to get my food arm. It's gonna they're gonna drive away with it boy. They're outside
I ordered it. It's there outside. Oh my god. You just got cheesy gody to crunches for like yeah
It's they're waiting for me dude, right? I can't get in. This is a two-man job
Oh hell. All right
Try to defend me guys. I'll be right here. All right, go back as soon as I can
Oh, I jumped off
Oh, it's just me
Oh shit. No, i'm behind you. Oh, thank god. You just you just saved my life right there
Uh, yep
My last ditch effort I dropped a grenade maybe can help well it was uh, it was good. Wait, what's happening?
Oh, they're stuck
Kraken's got uh, the um window thing which means that on hit
Nobody can hit kraken right now
He's safe
He said he's alive
He's gonna be alive for about 10 more seconds until his charge runs out
Hurry up and get it back in here. Get those tacos
We did it
Yeah, I got a bomb you guys bad news. I haven't left yet still what?
Oh, this is bad. This is bad
It wasn't me this time I went brb last day wasn't me this time done five times
Hey, i'm i'm proud of you guys. We've never even made it past round two of the dice rolling
We made it all the way to go. We could have easily did it
We have a there's a technique of just jumping off and restarting at the beginning
Yeah, it's pretty you can see the end game of monopoly
Yeah, I mean and it's oh never mind the game bottom fragging
every time
It's too bad
I picked out a lot of there's a lot of other levels like a lot of clown levels and like creepy alien levels and
simpsons level
Just never get to the
Turkey survival actually had fully modeled turkeys clown
They were the zombies
That's why I picked it
There was one from there was a legacy one from last stream where it didn't have any real purpose behind it
But every zombie was for some reason pseudo voodoo the pokemon
I don't know why it wasn't in there was no description. Why it was just every zombie was pseudo voodoo. It just was
They were just pseudo voodoo
Which was pretty cool
So you guys you guys good to go you want to what's the I mean?
I don't know if I can host because james can't join me
But um, we have to see what the cranky boy wants to do since he's got his fucking gordita crunches
I mean, that's right
Yeah
It's like more of a situation of how much longer you guys want to go because there are plenty of maps the maps will
Go forever. So it's like whenever people pull the plug is when we wrap up because we're not going to run out of stuff to do
It's just more of like
You know
No, okay. It can only take so much
And then we don't come back to this for about a year ish
Are you gonna keep the maps downloaded? Yeah, it's all it's all it's all in one ever expanding
Map pack that I won't prune from the ones that we did
So anyone is interested in doing part three in like nine months
Uh, they can enjoy a 400 gigabyte download
I couldn't believe that seriously like when
He's like, oh, yeah kraken said it's a really big file. I'm like, yeah, whatever of course 10 gigs 20 gigs
Yeah, it took like it was huge. It was like my whole entire ssd
Yeah, it's it's a little gargantuan. I might i'll probably pretty big too
Yeah, the actual base game is like 60 or 70, isn't it? I think it's 90. It's like 89. Well, yeah
Well, that's part of it. I think this was around I think this was
I had to redownload the entire
Mod pack on stream like mine didn't download when we started so I was just quietly redownloading the whole mod pack
It was 150 gigabytes. So god, it's a little bit over double the game scale than at that point
So we're up at 250 ish
That's insane that I can right I mean I went through I got more or less everything that wasn't like completely garbage tier
Like obviously not worth playing
In this already so like honestly all that would be added for another session would be like new stuff and
I don't know how much new stuff that's good. Was the one on the the featured was the the
The fucking game of thrones one. Is that the one that's it looks like the same one that's featured
This one was new game of thrones is the one that's featured. Yeah, that one was brand new
Came out came out on the 14th. Yeah
Yeah
Like they're still updated
There's still new mods being made for this and some of them are honestly like you if you look like
There's actually good maps like there are good zombies maps on this obviously we didn't touch any of the actual good ones
But I made it is black ops 4 or not doesn't have it. Why black ops 3?
Well, I don't know why it's black ops 3. That's like the most
Don't all of them all of them have it but like they have to win. It's just that they don't have moddable
They did yeah, they didn't have the mod tools out right? Yeah, they don't have workshop
Like integration and that's what's made this so, you know
Okay
Did we win? No, we lost. No, we didn't win
oh
You were you were invincible for like 15 seconds held out for one more round after you left and then it went to shit
Remember pokemon sun and moon now. I remember that one. No, it was bad. Yeah. I remember that one now
Well, i'll give you i'll give you my uh, i'm down if you guys want to do any more
I'll be around for a little while
If uh, if we want to I got like we could play like a wind down one
That's like probably decent that I saw that actually intrigued me or we can play more trash garbage like cheese cube recheese
We've got options on both fronts. I will do anything. Whatever you guys i'm good for another one
Your mic is really low quiet
I'm fine to stick around for a little bit longer. It's not like I have anything. Okay cheese
I didn't want to see more. Uh
What do we feel on I I could be either the meme one or
The real one. I got a gordita crunch here with my name on it, but i'm also you know, happy to wait
I don't mind. It's up to you guys
There's a lot here. Let's do two more then. Yeah, okay. Uh, let's do
This one looks like it would be pretty good like actually like a decent map actually good
Sure
It's like a western themed cowboy one. That's an actual map. So
Wanted yeah
So is cheese cube just like a piece of absolute shit
He's assuming I think a lot of cheese cube is inevitably going to be garbage trash like
Go to solo and uh, look at the picture hover a picture under the maps. You can see it on cheese cube
There's a lot of cheese themed maps
All of them are completely garbage and I don't know why a bunch of different people make these maps cheese cube
Because like never the same person is what somebody just said
They don't go out here
That's like the whole mentality of the meme is that you see someone makes a cheese cube map and you say well
It must be good and then you make a cheese cube map. That's also fucking
Trash garbage and then you know the cycle continues. Uh, I don't oh there it is wanted. Okay
Now i'm only talking about like pictures that I saw wanted looked pretty good. Somebody said the cheese maps are challenge maps
I do like cheese
Cheese in the name they're for high level, uh zombies players only
That's us. Well, I'd say that's us. We almost beat monopoly. We almost need monopoly. That's pretty
I'd like I mean, I don't want to toot my own horn, but you know, I will I had about like a go ahead
No, I don't like to do that. Yeah, I had like a 40 headshot ratio
I didn't get I get I didn't give her many kills craig and the lobby is not joinable. Can you invite me again?
Hey, can you not do that to me? Sorry, I invite you
I know you're excited to eat that cheesy gordita crunch. Yeah
You probably oh, it's still not joinable
They're in here. I'm in here
My friend's game gotta tell you I hear that I can smell it I hear
I can smell the cheese in this cheesy gordita crunch a mile away as i'm as i'm picking it up
It's got a pungent odor for sure. Yeah, i'm not gonna do a taco camp guys
I I look i'm like the scum of the earth right now. I'm like
I'm like hiding in a twitch hoodie
I i'm
I'm unkempt and i'm eating a cheesy gordita crunch. This is I don't want you to know me this way
I'm gonna restart my game because it's not letting me in
Fucking sure
I invite everyone to my party. They're texting each other at my party
Bring in front of me. They're showing me the texts. Yeah, that was a text between you know, a private text that you saw
I
Put a happy face, dude
I gotta oh my god. I got a hand
Squeezes this fire sauce
What do you think I am?
No, god wait what happened
Fucking cut off text message didn't receive
I cost my
What the fuck spoilers
please
Dude, our fucking game is gonna crash too
Okay, I didn't mean to
Sorry guys. I wasn't even invited to the lame party. Oh, it's red dead redemption, dude. Look that looks really good. Actually
Holy shit
Dutch
Do the Dutch voice, man
Oh, I have to do it like a fucking monkey. You're the you're the dutch for one of us
I can't do it on command dude. All right
Dutch boys do a dutch voice crack your voice
I can't even join a lobby Arthur
Arthur
Just put too much air in your throat invite me Arthur. I need an invite now Arthur
There's not enough
Mangos are
Oh, this is not good. I invited you. I'm if he's doing good
Uh-oh hasn't been for some reason your lobby currently is like super anti letting me in. I don't know why
We can we can reset it if uh, yeah, I think we might need to do like a hard reset
You're wearing those light up shoes. Yeah, it's just hard not joinable for me those sketchers light ups. Yeah
There's lava in the middle there's lava this place is fucked
I told you guys I picked one good map
One good map see the problem is like now I accidentally sort of uh leak into dutch voice like for the next
Yeah, and then you can't scream tomorrow because your voice. Yeah, and then my voice is fucked for the next day
You do too much dutch you get stuck in dutch. Oh, no, dude when red dead came out online
And we were like playing with it online a bunch
I I genuinely couldn't talk for a week because I just kept like doing dutch voice
For like hours on end every stream
I invite
I try to join and I hope it lets me
One last map Arthur
One last map I didn't realize how late yeah, it is getting kind of late
Yeah, it's just not letting me in your lobby cranking. I don't know what's going on. Oh, no
Where is everybody where you guys all from these days
Well, yeah, maybe I can join james maybe I can join james's
Let me try
Well, I mean you guys what do you mean where i'm from? Yeah, you guys where are you guys? Where are you like?
Where are you all from?
Talking to you, I know where you're from. I'm just saying like where y'all from like we're just waiting in the lobby
I'll start i'll start happening right now from las vegas
Say so wait you want me to say like where i'm from? Yeah, like where you from now? What are you doing? I'm
Down the street from kraken
Are you serious?
Well, it's a long street la's got a lot of
Yeah
All right, the game's not letting me in what an icebreaker. No
No, you guys go on you guys thought I was asking my chat. Hey, where is everybody? Where are you from guys? Let's see
Let me what if I change the map and then change it back
I guess I mean, I don't know why I can't even join like james or like anyone. I can't join on anyone
You already reset restart your game. Yeah, I've restarted it once already
Jeremy you go to uh, any gambling casino anytime recently
What the fuck
Geez i'm, sorry
No, why am I going back?
Yeah, it's not let me in you guys should go ahead
I don't want you guys wait them
Start wait, it's not letting you in at all. It's not letting me in at all. Just go go
No, someone else someone else should host
Should I back out?
It didn't work, uh, it worked when I host I'm just gonna reset me now just restart
Okay. Yeah, I can join james. Okay
I'm just the weird one. Wait, what was the fucking math fifty dollars? It was uh,
Rude i'm
Am scoots fifty dollars jesus i'm from new york. Thanks for not asking
If I turn on that star wars 3am bits midnight bits like from the keyboard and mouse. Thank you so much though
It's very good. Remember when I made two thousand dollars earlier. Yeah, it was fucking insane
It was gonna be honest. Thank you so much for the fifty dollars. I don't like pepsi very much
All right, you don't like pepsi. It's pepsi. Okay
Is it weird? I can't tell if you gave me a glass of pepsi and a glass of coke
I would not be able to identify the difference because I don't really care about soda. They're pretty they're pretty different
I think I just don't I don't feel like I could notice. I just don't
care
brave
Thanks everybody. I was just gonna say brave
Squeeze just take a lemon and juice like a half a lemon squeeze the lemon into your water and just put it like a
Teaspoon of sugar and then stir it up and drink it. Don't don't don't drink so bad. That'd be tea
Are you saying like this is that PSA?
Yeah, that's the you're on the right one if everyone can join james looks like he's
I'm gonna have to force crash steam, but i'm you know, i'll be there in a second. I'm being like fucking crazy
Hey, thanks for the 10 community subs pin
Man 10 community subs. Thank you. I don't think i've ever tried rc cola
How do you guys feel about rc cola?
I've never heard of it because I live out in the middle of fucking nowhere
Is that water with a lemon in it? I think that's more reason that you should probably have heard of
With the lemon in it you didn't squeeze the lemon into it. It's not my thing
So i'm not gonna say i'm not gonna answer that it's not like
for me
Is this like uh like off-brand cola, but I don't like cola
But how do you get more bootleg than cola feel like the mass produce it enough that you know, that's cheaper
Rc cola isn't it like a full dollar per can cheaper or something? Yeah, it's cheaper
But I don't understand why like how do they make it cheaper?
Because when you buy a mac you think like the mac tastes better
That's the reason
It's like a oh a computer. Yeah, it's like this. It's a reason
It's a reason why why are you eating your max dude?
Where's my max like fucking 30 more expensive now i'm thinking about mac and cheese, man
No, I gotta go to eat some food
We're all on very different pages
Am I supposed to be in a lot did I just what happened my shut up i'm trying
I'm late to my own party and everyone's texting insane. We're outside your house
Yeah, yeah, no one's even able to like text one another. We're just waiting. All right lights are all off
Oh, dude, yeah, we should switch to worldlands 2. Oh my god
I'm just gonna i'm just gonna play a regular game of call of duty. I'm just gonna like stomp on you guys
Have you guys played borderline series recently that game was pretty fun. Still I played it recently. It was fun
Yeah, we've been doing like a co-op
Your session did not shut down properly would you like to start in safe mode no
Game sucks game suck. Oh my god. Oh, I have an idea. What if for this round
We all turn our resolution to the lowest possible
Yes, what you would do like you see what I do and I at least turn myself down for ask if I'm allowed still
There's a resolution
He's like a mile away that was just me laughing the fuck
Is
Okay, where was I? All right, everybody join
Exactly what the issue was before invite me then coward what yeah, we get to uh, you can't just join
Uh, i'm joining you right now
I hope at least
Ah, hey, wait, what's yours of mine? What am I supposed to be in yours?
Is
Oh one or more
Wait people have done on the content install. It said oh no, I that's my bad
Wait, what?
Let me let me change. Let me change the map
All right now
But i'm in your game
What is happening? Should I not be here?
I don't think you should be there and I think you're confusing him by being there man
Look, I figure he's the only person I have on steam out of there or else kraken's not gonna know where he is
I'm good. All right. All right. All right
Wait, no, I cannot join you guys
Okay, i'm gonna leave the lobby
Oh, no, you should have pulled the plug after monopoly this is
Now you join me
You join us kraken, okay, okay
Dude I think there's something else in that
I haven't even eaten it yet
Just eat it in one bite everyone will think it's funny
Okay, no don't do that you have to enjoy it
My steam stopped working. Okay. Wait. Wait. Wait. Oh my god. Wait. Wait. Wait. I think i'm joining
Yes, i'm in all right
I can't invite him. I will okay. I'm gonna join off you right now
for you
What's that it's fucking bane
What?
Bane showed up for a second
There it is. What the fuck? All right. Everyone's here. Start it start it start it. Thank god
Look at those marshmallows you're roasting over there. There's a lot of zombies that don't seem to pay mind
Because for the first time ever we're not carrying a weapon to hurt them
Think about it. This looks fun
They want us arthur
Those zombies arthur those zombies out there they want us and they're gonna have us
Oh damn old driskels
Those damn old driskels
Oh god, it's happening
We're in i'm a different character now. Oh shit. No, no, no, no, no, no. No. Oh, okay. We're good
If this game lags anymore, what am I carrying? I'm gonna go back to best buy like turn. Why am I carrying like a pen?
You have a pen I have like a pen in my hand
I have like a steak. Yeah, I have like a steak in my hand. Oh my god. My guy's like the rich one. Look at my rings
Oh, you do have light of sketchers. That's great. Do I have like a do I have like a steak or is this like a knife?
What's this in my hand? No, I got chicken for dinner boys
Oh watch it. Jesus. This map is fucking massive. Dude. I told you I picked one and
Oh, all right guys. Don't say the lava it burns you. Oh god. It does exactly what it looks like
Burn you the box is uh, you can see the box like the light in the air
Is anybody else's computer having some problems here?
What is that?
You're lagging. Yeah, i'm having some like extra computer problems
Oh, is it like mine's okay right now. It's all right now
I mean this game uses a lot. I stuttered there for a second
I think it's the particle effects of the why are you on fire again?
I just wanted to see if I could jump it
Wait, where what are we talking this lava here? You can't jump it
Out. What is this?
There's something here. There's a horse. Oh, there's a light shovel. Yeah
Yeah, don't look at the train. Were you looking at the train cracking? Oh, maybe
Don't look at the train. I think the particles of the engine
Oh
particles of the train
Use your knives wow, they put a lot of effort into like you've come a long way to this one
Yeah, look at all this look at that it's got like custom graphics and art music
And music
Can no one afford getting rid of this shit in the way?
max ammo
I like the custom zombie hats. I mean this whole thing's custom. I don't think as much as it's like base game
See if the gun's a switch
Is it also these random guns? Yeah, I think so
Damn man a real level crossbow. I miss taco though take too long to reload
I'm almost ready to open this thing. How much ammo can I put in this?
Oh a crossbow. Yeah, this is all like custom. These are custom weapons
It's crossbowed original
No, yeah, this is new. I think this one specifically. Yeah, it looks yeah, man. I like that. That's pretty fancy
Oops, there's a gun on this wagon over here as well. It even makes that dinky crossbow sound this thing sucks
Why would anyone ever use this
Okay, i'm gonna open up the road
Got some cash. Come on gang. I opened up the way. It's been a lot of money on this
Whoa?
Oh, man, I sent them more lava. All right, don't let's not kill that one
Oh, there's a couple gum. I can finally pay to win the gums are missing someone stole the gum
gum
Does someone stole all the gum? Oh, man
That's not cool. There used to be gum in this thing. Can we go in this?
Oh, it's 12 50 to open this door 12 50. Hang on. There's some sort of uh eldritch heart that you're
Roped up to the wall. There's a lot of doors that like any of these wait. Does someone open that?
What eldritch heart? Well, i'll go over here by me. There's someone someone roped an eldritch heart. Oh fuck
You think I was joking? No, you're he described it perfectly
Oh, you guys want to take a look at this gross eldritch heart
Oh pickaxe. Oh, man
I want it. I want that
That's a thousand bucks I got it
Yeah, it's a pick and I know how small it is. I'm gonna go play some minecraft. I'll talk to you guys later
What are you gonna do with that thing?
I don't know. Is this the box? Oh, we need another shovel
Whoa
That was the most shocking thing i've all seen
This is a cool map. It's like a creepy cemetery. Oh my god
They got like a look at this real good thing just crowding around a street magician and he did something cool
Kaboom I need 10 points. I could open up the saloon
No, I know you're not supposed to
Oh, yeah there. Oh god that lag. What was that?
Yeah, it's a tiny bit of lag. I opened it come inside and have a drink
And if I do it's open now, I got 23. I sound like jeff goldblum
Who told you that I do your character like your character. Yeah my character
Oh, I was like, I don't know exactly. So I thought you were talking about yourself. Oh, no
I do not sound like jeff goldblum
There's a molotov up here that you can get
jeff goldblum is one of those uh impressions that you can do
jeff goldblum's kind of like owen wilson where you just have to make like a certain like
Cadence and noise over and over again and you are jeff goldblum
Wow, that's the only they're they're pretty similar. They're pretty similar
Yo, this game this mod has completely custom guns for like everything
Yeah, ribiolis. Oh, yeah, that's like I just got it. Look at this thing. Is it good actually? Yeah, it's like
Wow, he's here
What in the fuck can you do anything with this up here? I think jeff goldblum and nick cage sound pretty
Nicholas cage. Whoa, what the hell is happening there? What was that?
Yeah, I actually if you do the owen wilson
Whoa
Oh, wow, this is new to me. Wow
Who am I?
Am I jeff goldblum and am I nick cage or am I owen wilson? I'll give you an I'll give you
Wow
What the fuck how'd they mod is this like from a different black ops or like call of duty game?
I don't think there's a way they modded this at this point
This must have been like from a different call of duty and they like ported it in like the bats and stuff
What other call of duty has fucking bats like the I mean, I don't know. There's a western themed, uh zombies map in one of them
but
I don't think that is this bats behind us bats coming in hot behind us
I need a weapon. I'm too dumb to play this game here. Come to me
Come to me inside the bar. There's a really good one on the stairs over here
Get one on the wall. So you have like actual ammo to get back. This one's pretty good
Oh atomic guns, these bats are like stuck underneath the fucking bottom of this
What is going on with this?
Wait, this is just a regular black ops 3 map. No way
No way. We just played an actual map. That was wait. This is not a modern map
This is not no, this is a mod. This is a mod. I was gonna say this is pretty well done. Okay
Black ops 3 has a call of Cthulhu type map and has bad enemies. Okay, so yeah, I mean, okay
Yeah, the what the enemies make sense reported
That was the map I was talking about the hat that was like a city. Where's that box?
I'm gonna get rid of this crossbow
Box is behind the saloon behind the saloon
Should we start opening more doors like a lot of money? Just look up into the air. I was gonna go
You'll see the light. Oh, right, right
Oh, sorry should I go into the cemetery I can go into the cemetery
Oh a model 1887. It's just this little sibling that your mom makes you take with you
ban that guy for life
Someone's making fun of me. I'm just gonna get banned for life. Your character's actually voiced by Jeff Goldblum
Is my chat shitting out like with me?
Are they shitting with me?
Or no
Oh shit
I'm like lagging all over the place on this map though
I'm gonna go into the jail. I opened the door to the jail
Cool, that's in here
Wow, there's a model 1903 in here. Whoa, I got I got a part for some goop in the cage
Is that what you that was pretty good?
Need to turn the power on that storm down
Hold for part. I got a part two
I opened up this back way
The stables so we want to open up the way to the church. Oh, I found another part
We need a key for the church. Well, those people look that yeah, I don't feel bad. They went to heaven
You need a key
Insta kill I regret picking that up so quick. Oh, I found a shovel. I can go back in. Uh, oh, yeah
There's a bunch. There's one over here James behind the inn
There's so many places to go. I just want here too. Yeah
Where at right here right here?
What is that? Oh
Dude, what the fuck?
Give you a power up
Oh looks like this is where we turn on the power, but we need the key
Dude, I'm really liking this submarine aim. Uh downsides look here
Are you using that gun? Yeah
It's really cool. It's got a good submarine attack, uh, rectangle. I don't know if this is a mod though this gun
Feels like too good to not be like made by a professional leader
Oh
Max ammo
ice
What happened to the crawler? There was a crawler over here. Oh, there it is
There's a crawler over here and he's coming in with me
It's freaking me out. I'm gonna just look a guy close him in here. There's a door
I have another one over here like a slower one if you want to kill that one
All right. I'm gonna
How do we get the gum back? I want to fill up the gobble gum machine how
horses in the bag
We're done. What else do I do?
Like a 2,900 or buy some more doors. I don't know where though. There's a cemetery by the church
Oh shit, I got a big revolver come back around 12 to get gums
Jesus there's no way. This is mod
Oh crack it take a look at this
Where does this does this look like a mod gun to you? It's like a big
Revolver. Well, you're holding it kind of goofy
But yeah, I found out how to turn on the power. I mean, it's like it's all modeled and like so what does the power do?
I think you just turn it on on the side of the house
I just turn a valve there's a valve on the side of the house and I guess maybe that power
Oh, wait, it did it powered it powered the jail. The machine in here is on the phd. Ah
whoops
I'm gonna open the uh, is there any other places we haven't opened? There's a cemetery right here
Yeah, there's keys we need to open the rest
I opened the cemetery. I opened it both ways and there's a bunch of things to dig with the shovel
James what's up? Well, isn't that bad luck digging in a cemetery? No, I do put in
Hold on i'm about to there's a wait. What do you mean do over here dig this? Uh, dig this hole
Dig up this. Uh, i'm a goner. Yeah this person. Okay, this is just
I don't want no part of this. I gotta go around no come back
Oh, oh, but you'll shoot the casket the one that's out
Oh, that's bad luck
We should probably open up the uh, y'all should I uh buy this heart?
Yeah
It's 1500
Buy it activates a trap
Oh it activates a trap and yeah
Wait, what are we waiting for?
I mean, there's just a crawler just to buy up as much as you can
I'm gonna hang out in the salon. Is there a juggernaut anywhere or juggernaut?
No
Oh, I can craft an antler shield here guys. There's a shield where i'm standing. I thought I crafted
A stand a shield
It's a shield. Yeah, it's like, uh, can we you can operate this, um this minigun?
Or is that something that just does it automatically?
You probably gotta pay to do it. You guys want this shield? It's free if you uh walk up and grab it. Yeah
Free stuff, I mean, yeah, uh when you press two you can pull it out and you can push through a whole horde of zombies
It's really strong
Oh, there's a little crawler, huh? We get them
Oh
I did that from across the map
Come over here grab this here. Oh, there's juggernaut right here. What the fuck. Wait, where oh i'm going over there
Now none of us have enough
Where is it? We'll get it in this room. Take this take this down
Crack it take the shield. Oh, it wasn't that far. That was like 2 000 kilometers away. Crack it. Ah
What am I looking at that's like lagging every single time?
Ah
This map is slowly killing my computer
I think it's the train
Whoa, what just exploded that's me
the fly hunter faust
Double points rack them up. I'm getting a juggernaut the whole boy
Oh this gun is
Cross over the middle. Oh, no
Oh shit
Oh, there's another thing here
What is this? It's taco. Someone grab this. Someone grab this. What is it? Grab that. It's a sword
Find strength over through liquor. He's got it
Whoa, look at that swing
What the fuck
Wow
I'm so powerful. That's the real john snows, uh sword
Is it I bet it looks so cool
It did look pretty cool. All right, here we go. Let's see if it looks cool in practice
It looks cool because you're on fire while you're fucking swinging it
It's like always when I go when I come down he's down
Yeah
I'm down. He was he died cool. I died cool though. I was on fire. That was what I wanted to look like
No, I can't nice sword
Actually, no with the power of the shield I can get him
Oh, what the fuck? I don't think I care. I fucking I keep on
It's like one hour
Can you make it
What's up, man?
You got it. I think cranky's got you. Oh, no
I'm sorry. James get me now. Now's your chance. I totally fucked that up
It's all right, you guys just cut the anchor off
Need to buy that juggernaut
Carpenter ill
What's the matter with carpenter?
It ruins the flow of the zombies, man
Oh, oh, I'm concerned about the flow. It ruins the flow of the zombie god. Where'd you find this guy cranking?
Rosen
Uh-oh
Where's the speed cola?
I just want to eat my gordito. Oh
It's gordita you fake fan
I think i'm about to crash out here
No, no
There it is
I haven't gotten a max ammo in a long time. No
Are you all right?
I'm crashing up
Oh like at like hardware not like internet
What? Oh, no
Shit crashed em crashed
I'm down anyway
Well, it was a fucking cold
Not true
Damn i'm like hard stuck in here
Black ops 3 won't even close. Yeah, you might have to go to task manager. Yeah
This game does not crash clean
Dude, this is waski. Thanks for the five community shots. Oh, no
You didn't see that with the five. Thank you so much find this fucking key yet subs
No, I think we're doomed actually. Yeah what?
I'm gonna be honest to be honest. I'm reaching the point where i'm pretty hungry for a gorgia or something similar
I'd be down with you letting me die honestly
No, I can't do that now. Actually. I gotta get you guys up
It's like a hostage situation
This is zombie blood here if you really want to this is this is fun though. This is wild. Yeah
Thanks for joining. Yeah, i'm glad you had a good time. It was uh, right now
Yeah, dude, that's a gordito
So, okay, what do you think while they get them up too?
How is it? Fuck
Let me die don't send me back
Let me die. Let them take me get away from me get away
Help help
No
Welcome back kraken. I'm not gonna be able to go to sleep tonight unless I know how much
James is making me play with him
And I got a bomb too I cleared it for you. Oh, thanks no problem, man
Going man. I'm
No
you know how much
Fucking money
I have like oh my god this fucking guy kraken just closed. Oh wait. He's the host. You can't oh good
Kraken, can you just dm me what you think of the cheesy gordita crunch and I can't go to sleep unless I know
Yo, we got like ghosts after us what the it just stole money from me what you're talking about
Oh my god, these ghosts steal money. They steal your money. They're still like 200 bucks. They steal your fucking money like that
Somebody said i'm horny for taco belt. What does that even mean? Who is it nowadays, you know?
Love that shit
You guys are right over here
No, I want I want this to end
I'm so hungry and now that everyone's eating and talking about fucking taco belts killing me
I don't think i'm gonna die for a while, man
And until then I shall remain slouched back in my chair
audibly like zend out
In my microphone
Kraken get up
No
Get up
Did I just get the key did I get the key? What was that?
I don't know man. I I don't know. It didn't tell me. All right one gordito down
Oh my god, what do you think? What do you think?
Is good, I mean it's good for right now. I'm what do you mean for right now? What does that mean for right now?
Like in the moment i'm like that was great. I'm happy to have another one
I don't know how i'm gonna feel how many did you end up getting how many did you get two?
That was your mistake and now you know why
I think you made a you made a fucking driver come out there for two fucking you should have done three
That was a mistake a really mean mistake. What's
Why are you turning on me so fast?
I mean, I like I I think I made a pretty good recommendation and you like that's a fifty dollars. Yeah
All right. Sorry. Sorry. I was curious about a whole time thing
They were probably just sitting there going this motherfucker giving me fucking too fucking easy good fucking they got paid either way
Like like seven bucks worth of
No, it was like 12 12 bucks. Oh james you dropped this one dropped the key. I just got it. You're welcome
Oh, yes, we're gonna fuck
Uh
Stop cursing. Are you seeing this?
Yeah
It's a portal to the future. Oh, don't worry. It's not open yet
What?
I'm gonna watch i'm gonna open yours. I want to see what's going on. I can't see anything
No, no
He's dead
We can be free cracking. We just have to kill him
No, we have to let him die
Oh, I got you have to get me up you have to
Oh, they got me. I'm sorry james. They knocked me down
But they I think they knocked me down james. He's so far away
You have to worry cranking will get you and me you have to get me. You have to get me
She's a good eater cron. I actually did knock me down. I was trying to get you
I just want to look at an image of it
Nice
I don't have like postmates or things to order food with so I actually have to just think about the taco bell
Cheesy gordita crunch and I don't get to act on that urge
Oh, thanks for the res man
My buddies used to get these urges to go
Fast food, but when you know you get lazy
You'd always it's true. You always end up just going if you don't have food
You don't have the means to get some, you know restaurant near you or something
It was always a bowl of cereal. Fuck suck that that sucks. You know what I mean?
Or a bologna and cheese sandwich. It's just like that's never the same. It sounds like some fucking first world problem
It's never the same. You know what I mean? Like a bowl of cereal
Oh, oh you guys you guys all get to act like that, but that is what i'm gonna do when I go upstairs
I don't have options like
No, it used to be like that i'm going to go upstairs. I'm going to open my fridge
I'm gonna go turkey sounds good. I'm gonna pull out like a slice of turkey right put it in my mouth
And that's my fucking day. All right, because I can't just
I know because here's the situation
Okay, I can't like they had postmates here where I lived for like a day and then the driver was like fuck that shit
And he 180 degree right out of town. He left and since then
I'm out here in the sticks alone. I used to eat a dry ass one slice one slice dry
Dry ass no mayo nothing
It was just a dry sandwich with a piece of bologna and a piece of cheese
And I was like this sucks
When you're deprived options you get like it to honestly like there's no at a certain point
There's no creativity in my meal. Like I just like there's no options
So I might as well just eat the most the most absolute basic shit, you know
That's what it's that's what it comes down to now
And it always you open up the pantry or whatever and you just see it
It's something so basic that you can't you can't even stand it. It's like corn flakes or something
It's just like god did why did why didn't I buy like the s'mores cereal?
Um for this very reason
I mean my situation is that like I only go shopping like once like a week and I end up blowing all the nice stuff
I would have eaten over the course of the first two days and the rest of the fucking week is like
a ramen
Fucking bagel like for like the next five days. Yeah shaking my head the whole time dude
I do the same thing with like drinks
I go get like a carton of orange juice if it's gone in two days
Yeah, uh, this will last me a week and I drink the whole thing in a day
Yep, and like yeah, I know that i'm sitting there because I can't I can't order new stuff
And it's too inconvenient to take the trip back. I'm glad someone finally understands me man. That's that's really what i'm telling you
It feels like all these people from the city, man. They don't
Wait, you guys he just said he was from vegas
He's lying to you
I just was trying to use empathy
A friend
I trusted you
I'm taking my bagels elsewhere
Yeah in vegas I could I could go walk down the street and find like a five-star steak right now. What is it 2 a.m?
All right, I after that I gotta go I gotta eat something I gotta find like some slop to put in my mouth
Well, it's been fun guys. Thank you for humoring us in our uh, yeah, uh, it's pretty fun. No, it's cool
sure
Follow all the channels. Yeah, we're still here
They're all swell. I'm still here
Oh, i'm not muted. Sorry. I thought I muted oops
I was telling it by you like bug you guys are all fucking cool. You know
I heard him say don't follow all their channels
What and then?
I didn't say that did I I think he just said that I definitely heard that. Uh, well
That killed the mood for me. Yeah, like
I didn't say that did I did not
Yeah, that's like it's in this one thing off. Yeah, we're turning it off. All right, i'm not gonna support this behavior
No, not the squad anything about the squad
At least the squad keep the squad together
All right, see you guys have a good night for real
Did I actually said no I did I didn't say don't
Does somebody have a clip?
Squads gone
No, honestly fall that was uber hexa nova. That was kraken and tomato
Please
Give them a follow. They're all hilarious. They're all great. Great dudes
squad morale broken
Uh, so i'll see you tomorrow
We are going to probably play
Kalahoir as tomorrow
Unless something else comes up, maybe I don't know anything could happen
Uh, thank you so much for the thousands of dollars. It's not even a joke
We're gonna go through the bits. We went through a lot of them in the beginning of the stream already
Because there was an actual shit load of them. So
If you're taking off, i'll see you tomorrow
Not gonna start at 6 pm 6 30 tomorrow. It's gonna start at the normal time between like three and four
We'll ever stream with nova. Yeah, I mean anytime that these guys want to play of course
You know, it's just whenever it happens it happens, right?
But uh, let's get the it is getting late. So I want to kind of
It's very late. It's almost four o'clock in the morning eastern. So
i'm gonna turn this off because
And let's go back about uh, six and a half hours ago
So i'll be starting to like three or four
normal time tomorrow
Not like it was today
but
We had the the insane
almost 1800 dollars from
somebody named jeremiah's massive dong
And I yeah, it was fucking out of control. It was a lot of money
I
Not much else to say on that
That's how we started it out freudian weapon gave 250
Regardless of the start time. These streams are always a hoot
Jerma Hartway appreciate you
I appreciate you too
Yeah, I wouldn't have started this late unless there was a reason to push it forward by that much which obviously
Pretty good reason
It's always fun
I might i'm sorry. I wasn't really that great at black ops zombies tonight was the only experience i've ever had
i've never played it
And I don't play call of duty either. So it was still fun
Oh then we had
after the like two grand of insanity
Dork cube gave 250 i'm hiding my bits next to mr. Moneybags donations
They still got through you may have been the worst player i've ever seen
Yeah, but like
I don't even know what any of these guns do
I don't even know what I don't know what the power-ups are
I have no I don't know. How do you uh, literally none of these systems i've never seen
Just shoot gun at monsters is all I know just shoot
Yeah, I didn't do the tutorial i'm talking like the black ops 3 tutorial
Last time I opened a call of duty game was I think modern warfare 3
Well black ops 2 maybe like 10 years ago
I don't know
And nothing has changed. Yeah, but i've been playing zombies. It's like a completely different game mode
Uh, but drosophilia. Thanks with five dollars
They say hi. Hi
So there was so much money earlier
Seriously, it's i'm looking back at him. I'm getting
Getting overwhelmed the second time around. This is thousands of dollars like six hours ago
jesus
Uh comfort eagle 55 dollars heard there was a bit party
Sergil but ten dollars small bit energy
No, that's still a lot of money
Trident jacks. Thanks for the five dollars
Love you jerma happy to see some more custom zombies
Yeah, it was still interesting
But my favorite level was probably the if no, what was my favorite level?
Probably the game of thrones one. That was just cool. It's fun and funny
But thank you tried and jacks. It was a good first ever experience
Uh nicknamed jack. Thanks for the 250 we require ads
Yeah, but I don't have to give them to you. You know, I don't want to give you ads but thank you for the 250
Uh loco roco gave five community subs earlier in the chaos. I think I may have missed them. Thank you
The zali thanks for ten bucks. I might not be an oil tycoon, but I wanted to join
Thank you for the ten bucks
Nebula brand five community subs turtle toenail ten dollars
This is no longer a cod stream. This is now a bit stream. Yeah
Wolfgang ten dollars. Here you go. This is the first time i've ever given bits
And it's wildly appreciated
Thanks for the ten bucks
uh
Zalnag thanks for the five dollars
Just five bucks. Thank you. No message or anything. Just five bucks. Thank you
Uh rogue fort ten dollars. Thanks for the ten bucks
They say my turn dollar signs. Thank you. No one is under any obligation to pay me money and sometimes
like two three fucking grand comes yeah, it's
Thank you for everything. Thanks for the money. Thanks for the support. Thanks for the viewership
Thanks for letting me live my dream. Seriously, like it's fucking unbelievable
I can't even believe i'm having this conversation that that much money is coming through
It's fucking remarkable to me
Thank you
Uh flimflam ten dollars from flimflam
Surely such a massive streamer getting such a massive amount of money
Mainly from one massive dong warrants a massive stream announcement for the near future
Well, I already talked about this is this already this whole this stream paid for the dunk tank stream
That might cost a few thousand dollars at least
So there it is
Depending on how what needs to happen
I sure I probably should hear back from
my source soon on that too, so
You'll get more info later
But thank you flimflam for the ten bucks
Uh an anonymous cheerer. Thanks for the 250
They just say
Anonymous 250. Thank you
Thank you the two dollars and 50 cents. We had germa's dong is average for 15 dollars come in
30 dollars actually
They say 12 inches is average by the way
not so
Thank you great canadian fuck club
Threw their hat into this insane money stream in the beginning
With 10 community subs earlier. Thank you so much
A lot of community subs too in the middle of all this
Swiggy swanky. Thanks for the 250
Germa, I apologize in advance. I haven't watched you in a while and i'm currently starting with the siciro streams
Sorry, I haven't been catching up. What memes have I missed?
It depends on how long
There's a lot
a lot of things
And swiggy swanky again 250
Why are you playing black ops? What year is it and then it's a twitch clip the twitch clip is I believe this is grandpa
So here's an example
Yeah, it's been a long time that's what i'm saying it's been a long time
That may be one of the last times I ever played the game. That was like six years ago
And I didn't even play that that was my that was grandpa
You know
Um, mr. Biffy thanks for the four dollars germa, why does your door look like it's screaming?
It does kind of have like a little like a scream face doesn't it?
But thank you for the four dollars
Thank you thomas win for the five dollars
They say hello jeremy me and my friend made a short film called rumble
Inspired by your characters from the germa universe
Including you abia and trench coat guy and dick dastardly richard from the rat movie
We make this movie for you your excellence. We think you're amazing and hilarious. Anyways, here it is
Rumble, let's take a look here. There's a link to it. This is 20 minutes long
I don't really have time to play this now
This is a full episode of television
It's a long one
I might open with this tomorrow
Because it's very very late
It's like 4 a.m. Eastern. I'd rather
do this when
It's not so so late. This is fucking list. I'm like just i'm not gonna scroll that far
But this looks like it's very well made
Make sure to remind me to do this tomorrow because this is like a full episode of television
It's a full movie. They weren't kidding around
Or you know, you know, you know, you know what friday is like i'm gonna be a chill day where we just
We'll just do it friday
Because tomorrow i'm gonna play a game but friday, we're just gonna do whatever
So remind me on friday that we're gonna watch this
It seems like something good just to do right
What am I playing tomorrow? The plan is to do cauliflower as gunslinger
Unless something else comes up
But i'm, not sure we'll see
Tomorrow is friday. Yeah, but you know what I mean like not tomorrow not friday stream
I mean not uh, not thursday stream friday stream because thursday technically is today, right?
but
Thomas win thanks for the five dollars
And this incredibly but highly produced video
That we're gonna watch on like the chill friday stream
I'm, not sure how long the stream will be on friday, but I did I kind of want to get something out there
We'll do a few fun things
But thank you for audience weapon. Thanks for the 250. I was never crazy about cod
But this stream makes me reconsider looks like fun derma jex
It was it was fun. I feel like it took me like
A couple hours to kind of get into the element in the zone there though
Which just came from vr chat
Not even 24 hours ago
And just dump into like candy land
It was a little overwhelming at first, but it was all
After like a couple hours it started to click and it was a lot of fun
But thank you for audience. It was fun. I would you not like it. It's got candies
Felt like it fizzled at the end
Yeah, I mean that that the one I just was kind of getting tired and you get it was kind of very easy to tell
The good a good like the good four and a half to five hours in the middle there was an absolute blast
Took me like about an hour or two to understand the game mode
And really get a click for it. Then we started having a great time and then I got tired
I thought it was I had a lot of fun
You learned vr chat pretty quick
Well, I mean, that's just kind of walking around and looking at stuff and like talking, you know
uh
Thank you das
Das tech for the ten dollars
Say something about daffy duck
Is something about daffy duck like having sex?
Thank you for the ten dollars
Appreciate it
Uh, pretty support. Thanks the ten dollars run a commercial
You just paid me ten dollars to tell me to run a commercial to make money
What
Here you go. Hey, here's ten dollars. Can you run a commercial? You just paid me to run a commercial
I'll do it at the end. We'll do one. We'll do one 30 second out of the end stream
It's 4 a.m. Here. I just woke up in the morning. Is he still here? Was it a good stream?
It's a fucking great stream
It one of the best
Ads are a meme though. I don't know why
Uh, thank you goldfish vendor for the five dollars
With all the money you got tonight, you can finally get that height enhancement surgery
That's probably like that probably costs like forty five thousand dollars
That's probably like fifty grand
I don't know. I never looked it up. I'm just guessing
I just got here. How was this frame fucking one of the best?
top ten
Hey, thanks for the five dollars though. I don't need to do a height enhancement
Get dr. Scholl's inserts and put them in and i'll go up to five nine
thinking face
You can use that if you want
Uh clauski. Thanks for the five community subs evil fish
Five community subs right now
Five minutes go ten minutes go. Thank you
Lots of community subs and speaking of those subs. Why don't we show them on the screen right now? That sounds like a plan
I just got here. How was the stream? It was pretty awful
I like didn't get zombies at first people were talking about how i'm so dumb and bad at zombies and I was like
Fuck, dude, come on. Fuck
I made a joke and like criken said that wasn't funny shut the fuck up and i'm like fuck and I had to like mute
at one point like I
Peered into nova's dms and he was just like dude
I don't want to fucking hang out with this guy anymore
Like how do we how do we get rid of him but not be like a dick about it?
And I like pretended I didn't see it
No, it was one of the fucking top ten streams of the year
Well, you know, you know, i'm not gonna just watch it and you'll see it was high quality
I don't know about that
But thank you. There was a lot of community subs
Let's show them right now. They're gonna blast by you. Just wait
Let they come
I will see you tomorrow
Like I said, we're gonna do four days in a row
Because if you didn't join us earlier my mother's coming in and i'm gonna spend like about a week with my mother
I'm not going to be streaming for about five straight days
Thanks again as always for watching and thanks again for the fucking like me with like
Hitting a lottery like a scratch ticket at the beginning of the stream. I won like three thousand dollars
in the very beginning
so
That's insane. Thank you
Show mom on stream. I don't my mother doesn't want to be on stream
No, my mom doesn't really want to be on stream
She was on stream once and then she didn't want to do it again
Hey peek a banana. Thanks for the 250. Love you germa. Appreciate every stream say germa heart. Thank you peek a banana
Thanks for coming out come out a lot
So thank you
Mom stream or riot. No, I don't
I'm not gonna do that
She doesn't want to do it three to four p.m. Tomorrow
See you soon
This was very very last second
But i'm glad I did it
And yes, I will show an ad don't worry
Stream is it has it been 24 hours? Yeah, that's right. I did this yesterday, right?
uh for stream legends has it been yeah, it's been 24 hours I stopped at like
Eight o'clock yesterday. So
All right. Here it comes stream legends
I sat through a whole stream for this
Well, there you go. You've been rewarded
and for real, uh
Go check out those other guys streams
All those guys have supported this stream
Uh more than more than a handful of times so
You know with raids and hosts and stuff like that so that
Go give them a follow if you don't know who they were
Although they're pretty
Pretty fucking popular guys
Give them a follow
There go the subs all of you
There are a lot of you know
Take care everybody
Get some sleep if you're around tomorrow, we'll be happy and happy
What time tomorrow but uh, well technically today
Thursday between three and four p.m. Just the normal time
See you tomorrow. Take care. Have a great one