Oh, we have exhausted all our diagnostic machines on this patient. We are still not sure what's wrong. What should we do?
Can't even take a chance. I can't I can't do anything. Just go home. I'm sorry. What's up? What's up?
What the fuck is wrong with this guy? What? Oh my god
No wonder I sent him home. He was like scaring people
Well, you made it weird, I'm sorry you were like hey everybody talk about boobs
That's that's a that's essentially what I guess
Somebody crap their pants again
Who does all right? Let's be completely honest and completely real right here
One of these people just crapped their pants and is still sitting up. Wait, if this guy goes to the bathroom, then it was him
I
Love the unhappy face above his head like he is so destroyed
Wow
Did your guy quit? There's like no doctors in the rooms. Where are the doctors?
Where is my host hospital?
Where are the doctors? Every room is empty
What happened? They all quit at once and made a game company deal with it
They really I have one doctor this one guy is getting a raise
Because he stayed the whole hospital is empty of people
No wonder people are just sitting around crapping their crap in their pants
They didn't like get lost in this giant staff room or no. I made this room
For these son of a bitches, you know, it was at that moment that he said, you know what our boss is incompetent
Can you look at that? Look at this guy right here. This guy has a lot of respect for me
He is in like the research development room
he's working day and night trying to find new cures and
Everybody else over here just like walking around the hospital like looking at people all quit
And yeah employee of the month right there link here. This guy is employee of the month
I need a psychiatrist and there's no psychiatrists here and this person's waiting for a psychiatrist
Oh
They are just pouring in you know what see this didn't happen last time because you had the giant bathrooms
Hold on a minute. I need to make sure people can hear this
Hold on
Where is it?
You're two years old I'm laughing because so many people are going
Oh
My god, can you put another toilet in there?
All the people that were going to the all the people that were crapping and all of you and then the guy that just
Like puked he probably get probably like stinks in here
You lose
She's sitting on the look at the seat the top left seat
She's just like rubbing her feet into the carpet
Stop throwing up over here. Can I please win this match?
These guys I'm in like
It's a chain reaction
Look at this guy. Look at this guy right here. It's just like dude. What are you doing?
Why are you sitting in that ten bucks says this guy throws up? I hope he throws up in the office
Where is that? I have this over here. Go over here and get your tongue fixed
Dreamer, why are you still allowed to own a hospital?
Good question, but I'm hey, what are you doing over here? What is this guy doing over here? I think I'm about to fire this guy
I'm firing this guy
Ruin twist he's just in the corner like that. Don't hope nobody sees me
Hope nobody sees me doing this
You're fired
He is so quick to leave
He really wanted to go home. I haven't seen this before what kind of human liquid is that?