Hello, everyone. Hi. Can you hear me? That's good. I'm coming through the headset. Here I am. Hi. Oh, me. Good afternoon, everybody. I'm back at my normal setup. Weird stuff at the end of the last stream, but it's okay. We're not going to talk too much about like the kind of haunted shit that I was dealing with. That was kind of weird. But maybe one day we'll talk about it. But it was a little odd for me. He's the imposter.
Oh, we took care of that guy. We took care of the real imposter. And it's me. And it always has been. I haven't gone anywhere. But yeah, we're gonna do VR virtual reality one more time. Because it's still set up. And I don't really want to tear the whole thing down before I play a few more of these games. You don't have a pop filter on it. This is the valve VR headset. Well, I'm sorry, I don't have a pop filter on today. No pop filter.
Oh, speaking of audio, I want to talk about this too really quickly. I'm going to bring this up like three times throughout the stream because I feel like it's important. So during the during the replacement stream, the audio got all fucked up a bunch of times, right? That was because we had some connection problems to twitch. And it was like feedbacking back to the stream. It was a weird connection problem. But huge, huge, awesome.
News here, we have the studio recording that is currently on the archive channel. So 90% of those shitty audio problems that you heard randomly through the stream, almost all of them are gone. So we got the actual studio recording. If you want to watch some of those scenes that you may have been kind of
unintelligible. They are available. Because the that VOD on the archive channel, clean audio for the most part, there's still some problems, but it's okay. Stream saved. The director's cut. Yeah, I'm not gonna have no pop filter. So I'm really happy about that. Because I don't know people were talking about they were getting like weird twitch errors on that stream too. And we have the connection problems we had throughout that stream. I'm glad that like 90% of that stream was fine.
But it's pretty much fixed on the VOD. So that's good. What about the POG filter? Oh, there's a shitload of new emotes I put on from VT, VTTV. Yeah, I sound weird because I'm talking I'm holding this headset upside down. It's, I sound it's like you're inside of my mouth right now. It's weird.
Anyways, we are going to get started. The first game on tap for the day.
Game called detective
Roe Hill, detective case files and there's audio popping in my ear.
All right, let me get let me get on here. Not frog detective.
This is probably gonna be really loud. Please tell me if it is.
Hey, what's happening?
You are Andy. It's I know it's gonna this weird pops. I can hear them. That's not me. That's the game. All right, this is VR detective case files. Let's get in here. Are you ready? Are you guys ready for the last VR stream and like at least six months?
Because the whole thing goes into the package that it came in. And I literally put the package into a closet and don't touch it. It is literally dust on it when I take it out. I'm in
Kind of I'm getting like rumbles. All right, my pants are on. Can I see you guys? I can. They are. That sounds like VR. All right, let's go.
Oh, an anonymous skifter can skip five community subs. We went over this. I dealt with a little bit of weird shit in the hotel room. That's fine. I took I took care of it.
You know what I tell you about my favorite part about that last stream was even though I was being haunted.
God, my favorite part of that stream is remember when I was yelling Aaron. Oh, that was my favorite part. That was my absolute favorite part of that entire broadcast. I cannot tell you how much fun it was for me to say Aaron loudly. Oh my God, I loved it.
All right, let's go. New game Crow Hill detective case files.
I use left thumb stick and right thumb stick. Wait, hold on a minute. This is gonna come on a little tighter. You can't you know, you're not doing VR right until it hurts.
You know what I mean? And like, when are we when are we going to get over that part? Right? Oh, it's kind of hard. I can't really see that much. Hey, what do I guy that knows VR really well? What do I do? Oh, well, what you have to do is you have to tighten it till it hurts. Oh, okay.
Yeah, that hurts. Good. Now you can see it's not blurring anymore. All right, left thumb stick and right the teleporting and rotating. Okay. Well, that's walking. Hello, detective. You got some messages. All right. Who's this? Okay.
Who are these people? That's a huge chair. This chair is huge. I can't move it. Hello, you got to all right, pick up the phone.
Miss what the oh, it's a bit this way. Press here to read the message. Okay, let's read. Let's read the message. What does it say?
The case you've been bothering about investigating the area around the Crow Hill mental asylum. Yeah, I just received another complaint. So go ahead and investigate the area.
By the way, according to the latest report, a lady in a hat was spotted, it seems. Be careful.
No, no, not a lady in a hat. Well, I better bring my machine gun. All right, how do I where do I go? How do I get out of here? Press here to read. First, I had to go that way with this like concrete outside. What? Why am I why is my office concrete it in? Oh, gun. Please pick up the gun and torch then keep them in each holster. How do you shoot the gun? There's no bullets in this gun. What was this? There's a
torch? Why is there a torch in the office? Oh, how is that a torch? This is a flashlight. Press the left hand trigger to activate torch. Give me the fucking flashlight. What? How am I turning it on? Is somebody help me here? It's a torch. Press left hand trigger to activate torch. They're talking about this. What the fuck? Why do this? It's left hand? Yeah, I can't pick it up with my left hand. I don't get it. A, B, C, D, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E, E,
press left. Look, I can pick the gun up. Oh, no, this is bad. What's happening? What happened? Wait, what was the start menu open? Okay, wait, I can pick the gay holster. Oh shit. What? Oh my god, I can't have more than one thing. Whatever. Okay, I got it. We're good. I couldn't have more than one thing in my hand. Okay, press to go to the door and press the button. Press a grab. Hold on, my eyes are way too close together. Okay, that's better. All right, let's go.
All right, we're good. What the fuck am I? Oh, am I driving? What's happening? Where am I? How do I drive the car? Oh, shit, it's really bumpy. Dude, this doesn't feel right at all. What's happening? Stand up. Hold on, let's go. Hold on a minute. I'm gonna go over the jump.
What happened? What happened? What happened? What? I just run over. I just run over. What happened? What? I can't see anything. You just messed up my joke. I was gonna go like this. Let's go off the jump.
My joke wasn't even funny. What's happening? I'm like a grandma. Oh, this is it right here. Detective. What was that? I'm so freaked out right now. What the fuck? Should I shot him?
Whoa, this is multiplayer. Why are people spawning in as animals? Press right button, open inventory menu and place this there. Wait, hold on. Put this shit down. Where'd my gun go? Okay, press right button to open inventory. Right button. Oh, my God. What is this? Like fucking a seance. Okay, easy. Gear. This can be used for opening the bunker door.
Why am I taking these? Okay, put this up here in my like Diablo skill tree. Can you guys, is it too loud? Equip the table. All right, I'm ready. Holy shit, that's a nice car. Is it too loud? Okay. If you drop something from inventory and reload the scene, you will still get it. Nice. Good developer. Good dev. I know what I got to do here. What?
Okay, so I got to find the key to that thing. How do I reload? Does that reload? What? Oh, my God. What the fuck? Open the wait. I got it. I got it. I got it. Why can't I pick that up now? All right, I'm ready to shoot the fucking lock.
What? Leave me alone, Siri. All right, here we go. Is there a run? The cat? Why can't I shoot more than once? Tell him. How many bullets do I have to shoot? Excuse me. Excuse me. Why are you still alive? How do I run faster?
What? Teleport turning inventory menu quest. I shot that guy in the face like 10 times. Okay, let's go. I'm gonna try one more time. Okay, quick gun. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah. I'm not done with this game yet.
The area around the crow asylum. I just received another complaint. But go ahead and investigate the area. But by the way, according to the latest report, a lady in a hat was spotted. It seems we good. Be careful. What? What? Hold on.
Drop in some frames. Oh, well, during the game up, it's quiet. That's weird. All right, let me get back into this. That was like one of the most ridiculous five minutes I think ever. I don't even know what was going on. Oh my god, it's so dark in here. It's like it was dark in here. All right, back in. So what am I supposed to just run from that guy? Yes, yes, I just tried to pick the gun up with my real hand. Yes, I did. Did I turn the lights off in this game somehow? What just happened? Did I turn the lights off in this game somehow? What just happened? Did I turn the lights off in this game somehow? What just happened? Did I turn the lights off in this game somehow? What just happened? Did I turn the lights off in this game somehow? What just happened? Did I turn the lights off in this game somehow? What just happened? Did I turn the lights off in this game somehow? What just happened?
I just turned the lights on over there and the lights turned off here. That was pretty weird. All right, let's go. All right, I'm not going to fuck this up now. Let's do it. Wait, we're going to go in the car again, aren't we? All right, car time. Close your eyes because it's like going to make me throw up. Can I go faster at least? Wait, I am driving the car. Is that the moon? What game is this called Crowville? Is there a save? Why are you guys saying audio? Do you have your parking brake on?
Oh, what do I hit? The game is too quiet. Should I turn the game up actually? Is it too loud? You guys are just fucking with me. I feel like Fred Flintstone. Like I'm walking right now. I'm running with the car. Check your blinker. No, it's fine. All right. All right. All right. So now let me figure out what the hell I'm supposed to do here. I got to get the key. But there's like a weird. All right. All right. All right.
Pick up the animals. Pick up the animals. Pick up the animals. Where'd it go? Where'd the clip go? Where's the clip? I just had it. What happened to the clip? Under here probably. What the fuck just happened? What happened to the clip? Is it gone? Wait. Oh my fucking God. I don't even know where the clip is. Under the bench. I just looked under the bench. It's not here. I have to do it without it. It's under there.
Just run. How do I run? Is there a run? Wait, you saw it? How do I run? I have to be able to run, right? Next game, please. Don't just wait. Push in the sticks. All right. I'm just gonna go by and see what happens. Go, go, go, go. Where's the key? Where's the key? He can't hit me if I'm inside of his body. Yeah, he can. I trapped him. I trapped him. How the fuck do you run? All right, we're gonna move on. I'm not doing that again. I'm not doing it again.
That game has potential though. That game had so much potential. You know it does. There's so much potential. I love this game. What should I do? Sweet. Last attempt, I swear to God. Somebody's made a good point. I'm gonna do seated VR and use the teleport. I promise this is the last time I'm gonna try this. I think this game has potential. I'm not going anywhere. Just give me a minute. Seated. Wait, what? Hold on. Wait, what? It was already unseated. All right. Maybe that was what the problem was. Left thumb stick and right thumb stick.
I don't think that's how this works. All right, last try. I'm gonna make sure I have the gun and I'm gonna run. I'm gonna shoot the guy and kill him. Go.
All right, no distractions. Go, go, go.
Oh, no. Not about the guy with the axe, right? We don't care about that guy. I promise this is the last time you're gonna see me do this. Dude.
Go. Okay, we need to see what I'm actually running over. Somebody pay attention, please. All right, what am I hitting? I can't even look out there. Is it a bird?
All right, if it scares me again, I'm gonna gift a hundred community subs. I'm looking. I'm looking. There are the birds. Okay, here come the birds.
Flying. Fuck. I have to give a hundred subs. It's not one of the birds. It's not one of the birds. I've run over somebody on the ground.
All right, no messing around. Everybody relax. Calm down. Just sit down. Some of you guys are standing up and pointing at your monitors screaming obscenities at me, which first of all, offensive.
Second of all, sit down. I'm gonna get it this time. I'll get it this time. Hundred subs, yeah. Okay, I'm ready.
But first, first and foremost. No, don't. I don't want to lose this. I need that. Stop. My underwear is definitely showing right now.
Okay, good. This is ready. Give me the gear. I have to kill the guy over there. He definitely has the key. I have to kill that guy.
Anything in the car? Wait, what's that? I have to kill that guy.
Okay, so I have to. I have to kill this demon. Use the table as a shield. Holy fuck, what a genius. What an absolute gosh darn genius that person is.
Can I save the game? I don't think I can save the game.
All right, let's go motherfucker. I'm ready. Just roll it down the hill. All right, slow down so I gotta get this in the right spot.
This way a little. That way a little. Come on, you bastard. It didn't work. It didn't work. What the fuck, dude?
Where's the key? We're going to move on. That was fun though. It probably gets so much more fun. It's all right. It's all right. It's all right. It's all right.
Changing game. Man. Okay, so we're going to move on to. Let's see where we're going to go. Let's find out. We have to go back to.
I got so many games. Where's the other one that I wanted to play? There's like at least five games. Where are they? What was it called? Shit, I can't see it on my list.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Come on. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Oh, there it is. Four warned. Four warned is the game we're going to play.
This one looks really fun. This is a horror game, apparently. Just to let you know.
Let me capture it. This is a sick game. All right, cool. Let's see. Among Us VR is not out. Four warned. That game was fun. I wish it was funner.
Among Us VR is not out yet. Everybody that says that from here on out is going to get a 600 year ban in goldfish years.
Everybody that says that from here on out is going to get a 600 year ban in goldfish years.
All right. So here we go. So what do I do? Can I see you? I can. Early access. Right. All right. So I got a utility belt. It's kind of dark.
I think I just go out the door, right? All right, let's go.
Thank you for supporting Four Warned with your purchase. The game is currently in early access with new content actually being developed.
To stay up to date on the latest progress and to report any bugs you experience, please join our official Discord.
All entities, even those based on real names, places and events are fictional. This game uses proximity and global voice chat.
Wait, is this a multiplayer game? Connect to the lobby to host? Oh, shit. I don't have any people to play that this...
I thought this was... Oh, it's one to four players. This is just... It's Phasmophobia. Oh, what the fuck?
I didn't know. All right. Save this for the next time we play. All right. Save this for the next time. I'll get some friends.
I wasn't prepared for this. All right. We're pivoting. I want to... Okay. This is a four player game. I'm going to do a VR friends night.
All right. We're going to... What? I expect you to die too? Yeah, I'll try this.
And then we got cooking simulator coming up. This is a seated experience. Oh, shit. Seated experience. You got it. How's this?
Don't stand when you play this. Is that a bad place for the camera? Yeah, whatever. Who cares? You can see me.
All right. This game came out a while ago, but I never played it. So let's give it a try. Classic VR experience here.
All right. Let's go. No save data. This is the game that goes... I expect you to die.
Can you hear me? Don't worry. The briefcase is safe. Do you remember what happened? Your memory is a puzzle game and it's going to be very tricky.
Well, take all the time you need. You're back at headquarters and you're perfectly safe. You'll find a tape on the desk in front of you.
Load the tape into the projector console on your right. Now, I imagine you might recognize that bomb disposal device in front of you.
Oh, yeah. Bomb disposal. Given the wear and tear, it might be the same one. Oh, no. A puzzle game.
Well, I'm sure it still works. Now, let's see. What do I do?
Ah, yes. There it goes. Just a bit further.
Whoa. So realistic. Okay, that scared me. Disarm the bomb.
All right. This is a time bomb. Do I need to spin the wheel? Oh, wait. What? Oh, that was easy.
Wonderful. Yes. Next, the machine should dispense a grenade. Ah, there it is. Where? Let's use it to test out that telekinetic implant of yours.
Oh, no. I love this game. All right, cool. Push thumb stick forward to aim and then grab pick up. Reel it in.
Now, try using your telekinesis to hover the grenade nearby. Press A while holding an object.
Good. Your telekinesis is still working. Oh, I hear that when those things malfunction, it's usually very messy. Okay.
Now to dispose of that grenade. Use your telekinesis to place it inside the blast chamber.
So I go like this and then pick up that remote detonator so you can explode the chamber's contents.
Forward. You hold it. Go like this. Pull it. Forward. Pull. Grab it. Forward. Grab it. Push it forward. Disposal. Forward. Close. Easy.
Press the trigger button to use held objects. Cool hat. Where is it? It's on the table. Oh, that thing.
I expect you to die. For your final test, you will need to dispose of three more explosives hidden around the examination room.
Good luck. I'll give you a list so you know what you're looking for. E-O-D-R-O-Z-N-H-O-J-T-N-C-G-A-C-O-C-Z-N-B-A-E-P-I-B-F-J.
I can't do the rest. All right, disarm the rest of the stuff. Hidden around the room? What? You guys see anything?
Uh, okay. Probably behind all this stuff, right? Oh, hold on. Every movie. Every single movie.
Yeah, I think I'll... Yeah. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. Well, I'll be there at noon. Yeah. Okay. Yeah. No. Tell them I can't be there.
I don't know. Why do they do that in every fucking movie? The person will... The main character will sit there and have like foam coming out of his mouth and just grinding his teeth for an entire scene.
Nobody does that. That was a plus two and I... That was plus two. You just don't get it. You didn't watch movies in the fucking 90s.
All right. Where's like a... Where are these explosives? Can somebody help me? Open up under the clipboard. Gas bomb. Time bombs. Where's this gas bomb?
Oh, there it is. All right. This is definitely a bomb. Not yet. There it is. All right. Got that one. What about over here? This is definitely a bomb. Without a doubt. No, it's not. What about that? What's this?
That's definitely a bomb. Oops. All right. So that was the... That was... I need a gas bomb. Cover over the clipboard. Press A.
Wait. Was I supposed to do this the whole time?
Okay. I don't... I didn't understand. Is it behind me? Oh. Oh. Found it. Did I get it? What's this? Salt? Ranch dressing or something?
There's another... There's another thing here. Where is it? Is there like a cupboard or something I can go into? Where's this last one? Behind here? Oh. Turn the sink on. No. No. Help. Desk drawer. Oh, man. Look at that. Thank you.
Good work, agent. You passed all of the tests with flying colors. All right. Let's go. I'm going to have my epostatic ranch dressing. I'm ready. Don't worry, agent. I've got everything.
This game's going to be fun. This game's going to be fun. I believe so. And I'm sitting down so I can stay here for a while.
Shell Games presents... Oh, here it comes.
I expect you to die. Die. I expect you to die. You'll die.
My personal orchestra.
Hey.
I'm not in a car.
This skull.
I feel like I'm watching a movie with you guys. We're just watching a movie. I'm just sitting here watching.
I could never watch Born in VR. I'm just saying. I'm just telling you. I could never sit here and watch Born on VR. No fucking way. It would never happen.
I don't know how people do that. How do people do this?
I could not.
No! You don't have to ask. This is the first time I've ever...
Wait till the song ends. That was really good. That was a really cool intro. That was at least an eight and a half to nine out of ten.
Okay, so this is the first time I've ever sat just sitting here in VR. I've never done seated VR before, really. I could never do this.
Zoraxis?
Zoraxis? Wait, what is this person's name?
Zoraxis!
Game sucks ass.
I can't break this?
Oh man. Refunded. Refunded immediately.
What's this thing called? Operation...
Protect this guy.
Protect the Prime Minister.
Alright, cool. Report available upon completion. Let's go for it.
Let's get you undercover so we can figure out what Zoraxis is up to.
How do I let go of this machine?
Get my hand off this.
Four days ago. Okay. Oh shit.
I'm gonna fail this. I can't play this game. What do I do?
My instincts were right. This place is crawling with Zoraxis operatives.
Now you're all set up backstage. Maintain your cover as a stagehand until you can find and disable the threat.
Okay.
I managed to snag a ticket to the show, so I'll keep an eye on the Prime Minister.
Let's make this show to remember, people. Okay.
Banner's down.
He's much more grandfatherly than I expected.
Okay, wait, wait, wait. What does it need to look like?
Find out what Zoraxis is up to.
Okay, Banner's... Set the stage.
What happened to that sound designer?
What happened to Jerry?
How far down does this have to go?
Set the stage, everyone. I want an impeccable performance from all of you.
Oh. You up there. Up in the catwalk. Be sure to follow the new instructions I left on your clipboard.
That voice sounds familiar.
What the hell is happening?
Stay on your guard, agent.
How far down does that have to go? Two of this.
Banner's down. All the way?
Okay, Banner's are down. Clock R100G10000.
10000. Excuse me. 10000, please.
Excuse me. 10000, please. How do I do this?
What's going on?
What's happening? What's happening?
I can't... What's wrong with my hand?
What's happening?
Dude, what am I connecting? I'm connected to something.
I can't let go.
No help. You're taking L's.
I understand, but how do I stop being in the grip mode?
I can't touch anything.
Uh. No help. No help.
The ratio.
Like, why...
Let go of whatever you are fucking holding.
What am I holding with this?
What? I'm so confused right now.
What is going on?
I need to restart?
Dude, I can't even hit the restart button.
What happened?
Take the headset off.
Okay, that gave me... That freed up my left hand.
My right hand is still holding onto something.
Like, am I holding this?
Still? What does the game think I'm holding onto?
Slow... Do a flip.
I... Okay.
I literally just gripped for a second and now they're stuck.
I don't know what to do. I don't understand what's going on.
I think I have to restart the game.
Worst VR gamer.
Look, Mom! Look, Mom! Look!
Oh, I thought that I could do about this.
Oh my God, what the... What is happening?
It won't let me do it. I'm about to leave the game.
Okay, don't... Nobody fucking move.
What?
Uh, this game doesn't work.
I'm about to leave it.
I'm gonna... Let me turn the controllers off and on.
Get me out of the game! Get me out! Get me out now!
Wait, what is... Josh, what did you say?
Josh said something.
Game might be tabbed out on the PC.
What? Can you see?
Dude, why can I press the button once and then never again?
Holy shit, what's with these fucking games not working?
Are you sitting under the sensor?
No, it was working for the first, like, 20, 30 minutes.
Let me try to restart it.
Stupid.
Fucking VR.
I'm gonna dropkick this off the roof of my house when I'm done.
Like, am I... Okay, hold on a second.
Yeah, okay, so what... I don't know.
I'm just gonna reload it.
Oh, you know what? Fuck it, we're playing this other game.
That just pissed me off more than anything.
That just pissed me off.
Uh, not playing it anymore.
Well, now my SteamVR just crashed.
Fuck, dude.
Okay, wait. Is it here?
Can anybody see it?
Jesus Christ.
Okay, we're gonna play Furious Seas.
I hope it works.
When are we gonna get out of the tech demo stage of VR?
I know every VR stream is a rant stream, but holy shit.
Like, when did the fucking Vive come out?
Like, 2015 or something? 2016?
Are we ever gonna get out of the fucking demo stage of VR?
Or is there just gonna be permanent demos? Forever.
Alright, let's see. Does this work?
Okay, this is called Furious Seas.
Ooh! How do I shoot it?
Do I have to reload it? Oh, this is gonna be fun.
Okay. Explore.
It's just constantly mad.
Alright, hold on.
Get this fucking chair out of the way.
I'm gonna run into that.
I'm gonna fall over that.
That's where you're gonna get your real laugh out loud moment.
Alright, I can go to the shop?
Switch ammo. Pull the lever for switching ammo.
Okay, cool. So, grab to steer.
Press any button to continue.
Pretty simple. Pretty easy, I think.
Alright, let's go.
Wanted. William Avery.
Why does it think I'm way smaller?
Hit the audio.
Okay, so let's go with you.
Okay. Start a mission. Grab the poster on the table and place it on this board.
Alright, let's go.
Yeah, why is it audio?
And, ladies and gentlemen, your winner
for VR Game of the Year.
Look down. There's a spider on your leg.
When are we gonna get out of... Never mind.
Okay, let's go.
William Avery, the cowardly bastard son of Captain Rue and Location, Yolefin Island.
15,000 gold. I'm ready. Let's go.
I'm ready.
Is that...
I'm not supposed to close your shop.
Where's the boat?
Same rant.
Alright, hold on.
Speed. I can go slower or faster.
Mines. Toss barrels into the water.
Pick up raft.
For power-ups, okay.
Alright, let's go.
Let me play a fucking game.
Am I the lighthouse?
They took everything.
My ship, my money,
even my dead father's ring.
Pillaged by the pirate league called the Crimson Bandits.
Why am I just so wrong?
They took everything.
My ship, my money,
even my dead father's ring.
Why am I just so wrong?
The Crimson Pile.
I had ignored them for far too long.
No longer.
I'm gonna hunt them all down.
One by one, from that singing
Flunky Tales Avery
to their insane leader,
Captain Rue.
I've got nothing left to lose.
Complain stream.
They have so much I can take.
Exactly.
That's what he said, okay?
Furious...
Says.
So where do I go? Where's my ship?
I'm so ready for this.
I have to get rid of that, because that should not be there.
Okay, let's go.
I know, you pull the lever and move up and down to zoom in and out.
Pull the lever, we got mines and shit.
This old sloop was all I was able to beg for to take on the Crimson Bandits.
She's a bit old and smells like cabbage.
Is this supposed to be happening?
Is this okay?
I'm just making sure this is supposed to be happening.
Alright.
Dead ahead.
Those islands are where Tales' supply ships have been spotted.
Wait!
I sink those and I'll get his attention.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I need my...I gotta turn this off.
Or is it?
That's gonna fuck with me.
Alright.
If I ring the right bell, my crew will raise sails and we'll be underway.
Or if I ring the left bell, the sails will be lowered and we'll stop.
Alright, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Alright, we're going too fast.
How do I slow down?
Where are we supposed to go?
I wanna slow down, I don't wanna go this fast.
Oh, we gotta go that way, to the island.
Captain, Tales' supply ships are somewhere close.
I'll need to look around and to find them.
Alright, do I actually get off the boat?
Alright, slow down.
I see an island over there.
I just need to pull the trigger to open fire.
Double shot, loaded!
Don't turn...hold on.
Okay, I can't actually shoot him, right?
Whoa!
Holy shit!
Okay, wait, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
How do I...
So what do we do?
Anybody see anything?
Oh shit, it's a boat!
Get him!
Oh my god, we're gonna hit the island.
Stop, stop, hit the brake, hit the brake, hit the brake, hit the brake!
Oh no!
Okay, wait!
Get him!
We did it!
Nice job, man.
Always a pity when someone messes with your livelihood.
Alright, how do we turn?
Ready to fire!
Alright, go faster.
Tales must have more ships around here somewhere.
Ah, a few more of Tales' ships.
And it looks like one of them is armed.
This job just got more exciting.
This isn't a car, dude.
Wait, what, did we just phase through that?
Alright, go fast, fast, fast!
We gotta be ready, load it!
Oh, I don't have to do that.
I don't have to do that.
Here we go!
Fire up!
Faster!
Faster, you bastards!
I need more ammo!
Got him.
Everybody alright?
Shit, lower.
Got him!
Nice job, boys.
Nice job.
What is it?
I can't see!
A piece of trash hit me in the face!
Where am I going?
What does it say?
Level complete.
Alright.
Bounty.
So now what?
What do I do now?
Oh, I just win.
Alright, cool.
Alright, that was kind of fun.
I'll do another mission.
Nice.
Alright.
Speed.
Ramming.
Bring right bell three times to ram.
No way.
Really?
Are we ready?
Wait.
I want ramming speed.
Uh...
Shit!
Turn!
He's...
Somebody shoot him!
Alright, go!
Oh, there.
Fuck, now.
What?
How is...
How would you get away from that?
Oh, I got gold.
Line it up.
Damn it.
How are you supposed to ram people?
There's only one guy on this boat.
What the fuck?
Oh, get him, get him, get him!
We're fine!
Shit!
Oh, shit!
Fuck, fuck...
Oh!
Get him, get him, get him!
We're fine!
Somebody shoot that thing.
Why can I not ram this guy?
Wait, wait, wait, to the left!
To the left, to the left!
Alright, somebody just climb up on his boat and snap his neck.
It's not gonna be hard.
We don't have to shoot anything.
Wait.
Money.
Oh, this is bad.
Alright, I gotta pick this stuff up.
I gotta heal.
Look at him, almost dead.
I gotta pick this stuff up.
I gotta heal.
Look at him, I'm almost dead.
This game's fun.
Pick up the heal.
Right, straight ahead.
What?
Wait, what, that hurt me?
What do you mean that hurt me?
Oh shit, there he is.
Oh, wait, slow down.
Turn, turn, turn.
Watch it, watch it, watch it, watch it.
Ooh!
Fire, let's go.
We gotta go for the big guy right there,
right in the middle.
Oh, sorry about that.
Ooh, nice hit.
Come on, come on, come on, come on, come on, get him.
Turn, turn, turn, turn, turn, turn, turn, turn,
watch it, watch it, watch it, watch it.
Hey, sir, they're literally right there.
You can put that down.
You don't need to look through your kaleidoscope
to see where they are.
Oh shit, bad.
Oh.
Fire, fire!
Turn, that way.
I think I'm doing okay.
It's a telescope.
It might as well not be anything,
because we can see where they are.
Get him!
Oh, that was not, that was so anti-climactic.
Okay, well, whatever.
Did I shoot my own boat?
Am I shooting our boat?
Nice job.
Excellent job, man.
Turn it.
No!
Only one more, that's it.
Turn, fast.
Ready at full sail, Captain.
No more sails to give.
How have you guys not loaded anymore with double shots?
I don't understand.
How have you guys not done that?
I feel like a shitty asshole manager.
Armed and ready, Captain.
Now why is, how come you didn't do that?
Why is it not like that?
Those should be loaded, ready to go.
Shit, turn, he's gonna shoot us.
All right, here we go.
Line it up.
Fire up!
Yeah!
And we're using that gold anyways.
Nice job.
Captain, Tails, angry.
You know, Tails, cowards make terrible pirates.
So how do I prove that I killed him?
Wait, that's him?
Why is he a dragon?
There's a bastard that attacked my crew.
Wait, what is, what kind of boat is that?
I'll make sure you jack-catch.
That's like an old flying machine from like 1800.
No, wait, I need that, it's like a receipt.
I think I need that, that's a receipt, right?
Like I killed him, so.
Do I need that?
I need health.
Can we load up some new stuff, please?
I'm kind of scared of this guy.
Should I just go straight on?
He's coming straight on.
Let this be our final mission.
Boys, it has been an absolute pleasure
to have served with you all these years.
Boys, it has been!
Fire!
Hey, what?
Oh, we're dead.
Hurry, turn, turn.
There's the bastard.
I'll make sure you jack-catch.
Can you do another note?
Here it is.
Yeah!
Wait, throw barrels out.
Where are the barrels?
Oh shit, how do I throw barrels out?
Turn.
Keep playing, keep playing, mate, keep playing.
Oh, he's dead.
That guy died.
That guy got hit in the head with a cannon
and it just took his head clean off.
Here we go.
Okay, that sounded like an accordion.
That didn't even sound like a harmonica.
He's just going,
ah-roo, ah-roo, ah-roo, ah-roo, ah-roo.
That's not a harmonica.
Was it an accordion?
What was that?
That's not a harmonica, that's an accordion.
Oh, just block him.
He's gonna crash into the island.
Oh, what are you gonna do now, huh?
Where are you gonna go?
Oh shit.
Everybody all right?
We're good?
We're good, we're good, we're good.
No way that hits.
You hit a direct hit.
You gotta be kidding me, dude.
All right.
Damn it.
Shit.
Turn, turn it slow.
Right here, this is it, right here.
Bunch of hits, three, two, one.
Good job.
Ooh.
Oh, I don't like how close they're getting.
Turn.
Here they come, here they come.
Ready?
Are they talking to us?
Watch out for that bomb.
Ah.
Here we go.
It is an accordion.
It's an accordion.
He was seriously using an accordion.
Oh my God.
I feel so validated right now.
Nobody thought that was an accordion.
God damn it.
Why do they have such good shots?
Come on.
Holy shit.
Hit the brake, hit the brake.
He won't.
I've never flown a ship before.
I don't know how to actually do this.
Faster.
Fuck.
Oh my God.
Yes.
Got him.
Hell yeah.
That was intense.
That was fun.
All right, got no more money.
Ship's destroyed.
4,400 bucks now.
What can I do with this?
Very cool.
Now what?
That was a mission I was on.
Do I have to go get another mission?
Upgrade the ship?
This is fucking fun.
Okay.
Cannons, yeah.
Pick up raft for power up, yep.
Move up and down or zoom in and out, yep.
Wait, no, we're still here.
What is this?
If I wanna collect the bounty on Tails' head,
I gotta report back at the mission board.
I just gotta ring the left bell
until I come to a complete stop near the shack.
Here?
Then I'll let them know to open up shop.
Okay.
We gotta go left.
We gotta go back that way.
We actually have to traverse.
Harpy's landing, right?
Right here.
Wait, no, what the hell is this place?
Is this, can I go here?
Is this town?
Am I allowed here?
I think I'm going too fast.
All right.
Can I come out?
Is this where I need to be?
Other side.
Shit.
How do I reverse?
Unfurling sails to half.
Why is there no reverse?
This should be.
Oh my God.
Am I in trouble?
I think, am I actually in trouble for doing that?
All right.
Slow down.
I need to park this thing here.
All right, come on.
Looks like an arms dealer has set up shop here.
Oh, look at this.
I just gotta pull the second cord from the left
to start packing some real firepower.
What can I get for a million and a half dollars worth of gold?
28, 180?
I don't think I would want to bring this up here.
Like, you know.
So I've got, I've got like $40 million worth of gold
and I've noticed you've got a handgun back there.
Wow.
I wonder if you're going to use that on anybody.
Yeah, I mean, I'm just here, just me.
Crew is on the boat back there, but you've got a clean shot.
All right, what do we do?
How do I upgrade?
Hey boys.
What do you think I should buy?
See how much I care about money?
I don't even care.
It's not about how much gold you have.
It's about sending a message.
All right, does this guy like jump on top of me
and tackle me into the water?
What can I buy?
Ooh, what's this?
Harpies landing.
You got it.
All right, I want to buy stuff.
What's this?
Wait, what do I do?
No, come back, come back, come back, come back.
I thought this, oh.
Come to me, shop.
Have a look at me wares.
You can put whatever you wish to buy
in the chest over here.
Actually.
Okay, a thousand of these.
I would like.
Is this like the last hole of the mini golf course?
Where the ball just disappears.
Which by the way, when I was a kid,
that always freaked me out.
Cause you go, where do those balls go?
There's some secret weird underground facility
where those balls go at the end of the mini golf course.
Where do they go?
Into a bucket.
But like, how?
Does somebody have to like climb down a ladder
into like a mine shaft and get those balls?
Where do they go?
Yes, they do.
There's a big bucket under there.
Okay, what am I buying?
Oh, I want, that's 10 of these please.
I would like 20 of these.
Cause my crew is, they're idiots
and they don't know how to load it themselves.
Okay, that's 3000.
I want a bunch of these.
I'm going to do one more mission
cause I think this game is actually really fun.
Look, can you just bring up five?
I don't, why do I have to do individual pieces?
Here.
Solid.
Sir, that's just dehydrated dog poop.
Oi, run lads.
All right, so what is this?
Buy the goat?
Cool.
Oh, I want some of these too.
Hey, it's the best of quality.
The pirate is paying for supplies.
Yeah, this guy would have been dead an hour ago.
Oh no, my gold.
Should I, okay, hold on.
Is there upgrades for the boat?
Oh no, they're, okay, well.
I love the smell of an ocean breeze.
So what do I got?
The ships sailing around these waters
were my old business. 60, 60.
Nice.
I'm looking for a fight
or to collect some extra booty.
Single shot, armed and ready captain.
I might consider taking some of them down.
Where's the lion thing that I bought?
Check the far left.
If I need a better view of my surroundings,
I can always use the magnifying glass
near the bottom corner of the map to zoom in or out.
All right, I gotta go to Harpy's Landing.
That's the mission, right?
We gotta go this way.
All right, let's just, let's show off.
Times 20, what is that?
Letting out sails to half.
What am I looking at here?
Ring the bell three times without letting go.
Letting out sails to half.
What am I doing up here?
Oh my God, I just used one.
Okay, that's what that does.
Why would I be like up there?
Okay, let's keep going.
We gotta go to this Harpy's Landing.
Gonna bang a right.
But you know I'm gonna have to do that to somebody, right?
Walk the deck?
I don't think I can leave this post here.
All right, we're gonna thread the needle right there,
which will take us, we go straight through there
all the way to Harpy's Landing.
Let's open it up.
Go full speed.
Were we already at full speed?
These things didn't go very fast, huh?
How do you make a ship go faster?
And is it possible to have a ship go too fast
where we're going like one to 200 miles per hour?
Okay, if they were like 80 mile per hour gusts at sea
and we had like 30 of those lined up,
would we be going 200 miles per hour,
like holding onto the edges screaming
because our legs are in the air flying up?
What would happen?
All right, we got somebody right here.
Put it in drive.
All right, we're ready, let's go.
Should I try this?
All right, let's ram this guy.
Why is the music just still playing like this?
Here we go, one, two, three.
Got him.
We got 70 binoculars, what are those?
Oh wait, which way are we going?
Turn around, turn around, going the wrong way.
We're gonna go that way.
Well, that was a runtime error.
Okay, well, we're moving on to the next one.
Damn it, that was kind of fun too.
All right, we gotta move on anyways.
All right, coming up next, we're gonna do,
I expect you to die, I'm so mad.
I really wanted to play that.
We're gonna do Cooking Simulator VR.
See how this is.
Not enough ram.
Is it a tuber game?
Well, I played this game a lot a few years ago, come on.
Give me some credit here.
I expect you to die is really good.
Maybe I'm gonna reload it.
It's very loud, make sure I can see you guys.
This is way too loud for me.
I gotta turn this way down.
It's much better.
Louder?
Not louder, why?
Home Depot, what was that laugh?
Oh, Home Depot.
This is kind of ugly.
All right, settings, settings, where are we?
Where are you?
There you are.
Okay, let's do settings, settings.
Graphics, put them on high.
Color grading, bloom, turn that off.
Who wants to have bloom ever?
Yeah, I guess it's staying on.
Oh, movement smooth, rotation smooth.
Head position offset.
Remote grab, sprinkles by shake.
Okay, turn this fucking music off.
Hands position, I think that's fine.
Input, grab, use blender.
Okay, so it's like grab, grab, grab is grab.
Use blender is, crouch is A.
Why would you need to tip toe?
Double click A, pause menu is, what the fuck?
Okay, now hold on, what the hell is that?
These two at the same time, okay.
Remote grab, hold this and press that.
I'm ready, I'm ready.
I can't, okay, I don't know how to play it in VR though.
Let's get, let's do the tutorial.
The game's gonna crash if you don't put it in low.
I got a 3090.
It just heats up VR games until they crash.
What did he say, fuck condoms?
What are you trying, what are you doing?
What, fuck condoms, dude, oh, I hate those.
What?
All right, here we go, pause.
Okay, using a knife,
most products can be sliced into smaller pieces.
Grab a knife, cut four slices of bread.
Is that four?
Whoa, this is cool.
Okay, I got four slices of bread, put them on a plate.
Nice, oh, this is gonna be fun, I love this.
We're gonna be here for a while.
You finished the tutorial.
Very cool, very, very cool.
Oh my God, this is great, I can't wait to play this.
Remote grabbing, press trigger and point your hand
and then grab and go like that.
Nice, okay, turn on the grill.
Turn over the steaks using the, I don't have to do that.
Wait until the steaks are ready.
Holy shit, this is fun, this is actually really good.
Okay, that's cool.
No, you're gonna press all the juices out, don't touch it.
I can't wait, okay, cool.
What do we do with this?
Seasoning, there are three types of seasoning,
liquid, herb, dry, yeah, let's try to add some flavor.
Use five kilograms of salt, three kilograms of thyme,
okay, five kilograms of salt,
this is salt right here, right?
Oops, that's a lot, minus, wait, what?
Oh, cool, okay, how much do you need salt
and then three of thyme, this is thyme right here, right?
I don't know, why is it not listed?
How come it's not listed on here?
Okay, three of cilantro, 10 of clarified butter.
Is this clarified butter?
Oops, oh, 10 milliliters.
Dude, this is actually really fun, I can't wait.
Okay, oh, that's the wrong thing.
I get it, I know how it works.
Liquids shedding, you can pour liquids into the containers
in order to prepare a special mixture.
Try the recipe, take a bottle of honey or olive oil.
Okay, bottle of honey, okay.
Add 100 milliliters or 300, okay, that's fine, well done.
100, okay, that's fine.
Turn on the tap, add water, how much do I need to 200?
All right, cool.
In order to taste the mixture,
put your open hand in the pot and move it to your mouth?
What?
It's 50% honey, 20% water, 18% olive oil.
How would I know that?
Okay, fixing stuff, right?
Take phone, choose repair company.
All right, grab the phone, select, what am I doing?
Wait, what did I do?
Choose repair company, thumb stick, okay.
Wait until the repair is over, all right, cool.
Repair is happening, beautiful, perfect.
You got it, there's the fries.
I'm pretty much ready to go, cool.
Oh, there's like a coffee maker too in this one.
There's a new coffee maker?
No, don't do that, what's this?
PC and mouse, is your personal computer here?
You can manage your work in your kitchen.
Wait, I actually have to grab the mouse?
Oh, this is next level here.
Navigation bar, get through every tab.
All right, restaurant info, manage recipes, yep.
Every available dish, okay.
Perks can do it, skill points, yep.
And decorations, that's actually really intuitive.
All right, I think I'm ready to get started here
in a minute here.
Tablets, okay, the tablet, right, you order food here.
Tap the trigger to continue, yep.
Sorting buttons, very cool.
Find anything you're looking for.
In main sec, there's a list of items to buy.
Tap trigger, cool, yep.
Buy a small pot, small pot, small pot.
Very nice, how much is that?
Okay, spawn, good job, wait, that spawned in my hand?
Okay, I got the pot now, nice.
All right, let's keep going, oh well.
All right, now I, yeah, at this part,
you actually have to pick everything up,
put the bread and stuff in there, you got it.
Take a plate from the stack, okay, got it.
Put one potato and one onion on the plate.
I actually don't know which is which.
Where's an onion?
Is this an onion?
This is technically an onion, right?
Put one salmon on the plate.
Oh shit, okay, where's the salmon?
Oh shit, all right, cool.
All right, these are almost done.
Close the fridge, close the fridge.
Okay, I think I'm ready to go.
Let's get started here.
How do I start the day?
I did that, I did that, is there, I think there's a,
nope, wait, is there something else I need to do?
What's this one?
Oh shit, I have to do this, okay, hold on.
All right, so I need, so this is a trout, salt.
Okay, three cilantro leaves.
This is cilantro, how much?
Three time, that's wrong, okay.
Clarified butter, 10 milliliters.
All right, that's fine.
Why is that not right?
Do I have to get it exact?
Getting it exact is hard in VR.
10, salt, five, okay.
Free of time, okay, that's gonna be so hard to get exact.
It really is.
I did it five times, one, two, three, four, five.
One, two, three, four, five.
I don't, I shook it five times.
Oh fuck you game, what the fuck, oh my God.
One, two, three, four, five.
You saw me do it five times, duh!
Wait, it doesn't care.
Five, cilantro, and then sunflower oil, 15.
Got it, all right, all right, all right, all right,
all right, here we go.
How do I start up the game?
Okay, here we go, career mode.
What do you got, what should I do?
Sandbox or just do career mode?
Career, sandbox, career, career, career.
Sandbox career.
All right, we'll do career, why not?
63 meters between, I don't even know what that means.
Just pops up sometimes, let's go.
All right, here we go, within an hour,
we'll be open for business,
use the time to get ready for work.
What do we have for food here?
All right, what are my recipes?
I don't even know, I gotta go to the computer.
Okay, I've got baked trout, tomato soup,
salmon steak, and boiled potatoes.
Okay, so I need to get trout, what does this have?
This is black pepper, black pepper thyme and dried dill.
Black pepper thyme, dill, horseradish, all right.
Okay, black pepper, thyme, dill, horseradish.
Okay, I gotta get these ready.
Okay, black pepper, thyme, what do I buy?
Okay, I think I have to buy that at the menu.
Oh, here we go, black pepper,
I'm gonna need black pepper, salt.
Just get it all over there.
I gotta have a seasoning area.
All right, we're gonna go,
seasoning area's gonna be right here.
Line it up alphabetically.
Salt, pepper, dandelion, I don't even know what that is.
I have no idea.
What are these?
That's horseradish and peppercorns.
I think I'm pretty much ready.
Should I do it?
Okay, probably by use.
That's time I know what that is,
I don't know what anything else is.
I need a bunch of food, right, I need trout.
What have we got?
Stay open.
Dude, what is with this door?
Where am I?
I need salmon too.
Can I hold more than one thing?
I think I'm almost ready, I need oil as well.
Yeah, plate.
Okay, I'm almost ready.
Let's go.
First order, tomato soup.
I don't even know how to make tomato soup.
Chicken broth, salt, black pepper, what do I do with it?
Boil for 60 seconds, do I even have a pot?
Okay, pot, chicken broth, 700 milliliters.
Okay, chicken broth, get it, 700.
Whoa, okay, it's gonna be a little salty.
Chicken broth, salt, black, god, this is too far away.
Salt, black pepper, both 12.
Got it, okay, stay up.
Okay, cayenne pepper, six tomatoes.
Cayenne pepper, okay, is this boiling?
Oh shit, I need tomatoes, ow, my hands.
I need 960 grams of tomatoes.
How many grams is this?
I don't know, how many grams is this?
How can I tell?
One, two, three, four, five, how many is it?
How many do I have to do?
I need to cut them, no I don't.
You have to, you blend them up, let me see.
I need way more than that.
240, that was five.
How many do I have to put in here?
Taste it, what's in here?
That doesn't help me, that's just percentages.
I need 960 grams.
Dude, what is in this?
I need 120 grams of onions.
Oh shit, it's one.
Okay, you can actually look at it.
I get it, I get it, I get it, I get it,
I know, I know, I know, I know.
It's literally just one.
All right, is it cooking?
How do I cook it?
Is this even fucking working?
Add sour cream, okay, add sour cream.
300 milliliters, are you kidding me?
This is a lot of sour cream.
Okay, blend it.
Is this hot?
The stove isn't on, yes it is, look.
I thought that was blood.
The stove is on.
Look, how do I know when it's done?
Okay, I need a bowl.
No, that's not what I need.
What do I need, right here.
Did I even do it?
This is a little light.
Did it work?
Tomato soup, that wasn't bad.
The temperature was perfect, the technique was all right.
Flavor was on point, too much sour cream though.
All right, we're good.
Trout, all right, trout, 200 grams.
One trout is 200 grams.
All right, get this off.
I need to clean this.
Trout, where are my trouts?
How do you cook this?
Yeah, I need a trout right here.
Season with, this is black pepper and thyme right here.
Thyme is five, good, fuck you.
Dill, five, this is dill, right?
Yeah, beautiful, not bad.
Place it on a baking tray and bake for 90 seconds.
Where's the baking tray?
Right there.
All right, let's go.
90 seconds.
While that's happening, let's do the lemon 80 grams
into one lemon into quarters.
Okay, one lemon into quarters.
How the fuck do you do this?
It doesn't matter, that's fine.
How long has it been?
Oops, okay, make it look nice.
And then finish it off with garnish with parsley leaves.
Six grams.
How much is one of these?
Okay, so I need one, two, what?
I have to actually hold them?
Don't, bingo, serve it up.
That one's not, I don't think that's bad.
That's gonna be good, I think.
What do you think?
Wash your hands.
Look at that shit, that was really good.
Another tomato soup, I still know.
All right, all right, let me not fuck this up this time.
Here we go, ready?
Check this out.
So it's, how many tomatoes?
I don't know how many tomatoes I need.
120 times, so I need one, two, three.
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, is it eight?
It'd be eight, right?
Okay, I need one onion.
And then we do 700 milliliters of chicken broth.
Where's the chicken broth?
I don't have any more left.
I gotta buy it.
Hurry, hurry, hurry, chicken broth and sour cream.
Chicken broth, get it?
Okay, it's open, but it's fine.
Okay, now I need sour cream.
And let's get two of those.
All right, here we go.
700 milliliters.
Shit!
Just calm down.
Salt, pepper, 12 each, okay?
Now it's the cayenne pepper and boil it.
Cayenne pepper, six grams.
Now we put this on the stove
and then we add 150 milliliters of sour cream.
Get it on the stove, let's go.
Here we go, boil it.
60 seconds, come on, I can see it turning.
The colors are getting nice.
It's all, hey, what do they say?
What does Chef say?
It's getting happy.
How can I tell if it's cooked?
Okay, add 150 milliliters of sour cream.
Get it, that's too far.
How much is in there now?
I don't know how much is in there now.
I was gonna guess.
Okay, it's ready.
Into a bowl, 300 milliliters.
Here it is, good.
Bingo, done.
Sorry, I put a little too much in anyways.
This looks like water.
This looks like hot dog water.
Why does it look so thin and shitty?
I don't get it.
Why does it look so thin?
That's not bad though.
I got five stars on that one.
I'm gonna keep that available
because it's gonna happen again, right?
I can get a new recipe?
All right, well, I don't care about that right now.
Salmon steak and boiled potatoes.
Salmon, salmon, tuna.
Wait, does this work?
Salmon steak, okay.
Salt and pepper five and add it to the pan.
Oh shit, I need a pan.
Do I have a pan?
That can stay heated, that's fine.
No, put this in the fridge.
I need a pan, there we go.
Okay, get right there.
Let's go ahead and get the gas on.
Not bad, not bad.
Five and five on this guy here.
Let's go ahead and grab it.
That's so much easier than running across
the whole damn level.
Okay, all right, there it is.
I need a little bit of oil in the pan.
Sunflower oil, 10 milliliters, where's my oil?
Don't fall.
Okay, put the salmon in the oil.
60 seconds, ooh, timer, start it.
How do I start the timer?
One, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine,
10, 11, 12, 13, 14, 15, 16, 17, 18, 19, 20.
21, 22, 23, 24, 25, 26, 29, 30, 31, two, 33, 34, 35, six,
47, 48, 49, 50, this is too long.
All right, it's done, it's done.
Two, all right, my potatoes.
I gotta do my boiled potatoes.
Add to the pot, one, two, three, water, salt,
and potatoes, boiled for 100 foot, water, salt, and potatoes.
Where's my pot?
It's in the fridge, because it has tomato soup in it.
Hold on, I need another pot, what?
I don't want this.
I need a pot, why is a small pot of fucking onion
or whatever that is, what?
Wait, can I fit potatoes in here?
Oh boy, it's not done, it wasn't done.
All right, I need a thousand milliliters of water.
Turn it on, please.
Okay, don't put the salmon in there.
All right, just take it off, take it off, it's done.
It's done, it's done, okay.
Water, salt, 20 grams of salt, okay.
Then we need potatoes, 300 grams of potatoes.
How many grams of these?
Two of these, that's fine, it's all right.
The water's gonna wash them, don't worry.
Fry, boil for 120 seconds.
They're not even covered.
Turn the water off.
No, that's on, that's full blast.
How do I turn off the water?
Is it done?
This just tastes like water.
I didn't forget the salt.
There's a bunch of salt in there.
I think this is done.
Okay, now I need a plate.
That's it, that's literally it.
Do I have to slice them up or no?
Should I slice the potatoes?
What a shitty dinner.
Nothing on the potatoes, just two potatoes?
You gotta put something on there.
There's gotta be something else on there.
Am I doing that right?
Was there a Band-Aid on that one?
Just two boiled potatoes, there's nothing on it?
You gotta put pepper or onion powder,
there's just two boiled potatoes.
All right, where am I?
Where are you?
There you are, okay.
This is the last order for today, okay, cool.
Prepare for tomorrow.
I gotta clean up, this is a disaster.
Turn that off.
How much water has gone in here?
Guys, I can't turn the sink off.
I can't, okay.
Jesus, what's this taste like?
Okay, not bad, clean up for tomorrow.
This is a mess.
I gotta get a new recipe too.
Anything left in here?
There's only one, no, throw this in the trash.
Is this still good?
I think this is still good, just put it back in the fridge.
It's only been out for like three hours,
the bacteria's already started to grow on it, it's fine.
That's okay, right?
Use the, there's a hose?
I got that soup that's still gonna be good
for a day or two, at least.
Nothing's on, right?
How much is in this?
There's still plenty in here.
How much is in here?
Not really anything.
Fuck, just put that right there.
How much is left in this?
There's still some in there.
Yep, we're good.
It doesn't matter.
Still have a lemon that can stay there just fine.
All right, put that over here.
I think I'm ready, I think I'm good to go.
Okay, wait, fire extinguisher?
Wait, tomato, straight tomato.
It can be on the counter, that's fine.
Oh, what about this shit?
How much is left in here?
That's enough, that's fine, put it here.
What do you got in this one?
Some of these are new.
All right, what do we got?
That's brand new.
I think I'm ready.
That wasn't a bad first day.
This is my first time watching somebody
play this seriously.
I mean, I'm trying.
Ooh, walk faster, I want that.
Or, yeah, definitely I wanna be able
to move around faster for sure.
Okay, level up.
Skill points available.
Guests pay 10% more money, best reward,
cheaper kitchen decorations, experience, booze,
what do you think?
Liquids are cheaper, I want that.
Products are cheaper, give me that one too.
Buying recipes is cheaper as well, let's go.
Here we go, bingo.
You're gonna spill some stuff now.
Everybody's just waiting for me to drop shit.
That's like why everybody's here.
You guys are all just sitting on the edge of your seat,
just like, when is he gonna drop the plate
with all the food on it?
All right, let's get an order.
I don't think I'm pretty prepared.
Okay, let me buy a, let's get a new recipe.
What do I, okay, I have 17.
Ooh, what's this thing?
A steak and potatoes?
T-bone steak?
Is it like a cheeseburger?
Oh, hell yeah, how much is this?
Oh, I need 24, all right.
I definitely want the cheeseburger, for sure.
I'm saving up for the cheeseburger.
Yeah, I'm not, I'm just gonna save for the cheeseburger.
I got trout coming, here we go.
You have an order, I know, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Okay, it's the trout, I got that in the fridge.
Okay, trout, Andy.
Okay, and that was pepper, thyme, and dill.
Easy, it's all right.
Pepper, thyme, and dill, five of each.
It's gonna be very, very peppery.
It's gonna be very peppery, Jerry.
All right, baking tray, 90 seconds.
Wow, I have, okay, wait, horseradish.
Oh, I didn't put horseradish on it last time, whatever.
It's already on.
All right, 90 seconds, horseradish right there
after it comes out.
I need the lemon quarters, you got it, and fours, good.
Okay, that's good now, done.
Lemon, got the horseradish over there.
Garnish with parsley leaves, fresh, okay, almost ready.
I wanna hold more than one snip.
I need more, I don't wanna, I need more than one snip.
The gas leak?
Okay, that's definitely done.
It's turned black.
Good, huh?
Damn it, I need a plate, not bad, not bad.
I was just gonna frisbee it over there.
Wait, is my underwear showing?
Okay, stay on, I'm just gonna hold it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, stuff's falling off.
There it is, wait, wait, wait, no, take this fish.
What, are you kidding me?
Why did it not take the fish?
I'm leaving this here.
I'm gonna put this in the microwave.
I'm just gonna reheat this when I need to use it again.
What's gonna happen to this thing?
For five minutes?
Does anybody else get freaked out when something,
a frozen dinner or something or some recipe calls,
especially in a frozen thing,
to microwave this thing for more than five to 10 minutes?
I'm always like, I don't wanna do it for that long.
I feel like there's extra radiation.
I don't like that.
I don't like the microwave really at all.
I don't like what I'm doing, okay.
Take, okay, salmon, salmon, salmon, salmon, salmon.
It's gonna be nice and warmed up for whoever wants it.
Imagine eating a microwaved fish.
It's just, you don't even understand cooking.
You don't even know what, you don't get food at all.
Like this thing just heats stuff up
and that's all you, that's all you know.
You're mutating?
All right, let's get it.
Okay, steak and potatoes or whatever it is.
Thousand milliliters of water.
That was perfect in that.
Okay, get that on here.
Start the process here, salt.
I need the potatoes too, whoops.
60 seconds.
Let's check on this.
Okay, we're actually like coming into like,
apartment or your house or something
and like you have roommate or you're like,
somebody's just sitting there just going like this.
Oh, hey man, hey.
Yeah, I really felt like fish today.
Is that a case where you like are moving shit
out of the way?
You're like moving like people and things out of the way
to like, Mike, Mike, Mike, don't, wait a minute.
Stop, stop, stop.
Like you're like literally shoving stuff out of the way.
Like you're in a fucking drama,
like a horror movie or something.
To like get here to turn this off, right?
He's done?
I just like ruined it.
All right, so this is, oh no, I have to cook this.
So what am I doing?
Oh, it's gonna be fried.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about.
Put a little bit extra oil in there.
60, wait, where's the timer?
How do you start the timer?
Oh my God, okay.
What are you doing?
All right, another few seconds.
I need a plate.
Don't do that.
That wasn't even enough time, what?
Plate, where's the plate?
Here we go, potatoes.
It's a phone.
Oh wait, that's the timer.
That's the timer.
All right, turn it, spin it, spin it, spin it.
That'll have been a tomato's freshness.
Okay, nevermind.
Oh, who wants plain food?
Oh, it smells so good.
Oh, who wants food that's on the table
at every RPG you've ever played?
Oh, me, dude, me.
Tomato soup?
Oh, I got you.
I got you.
Chef Ramsay goes into the kitchen
and finds something he could never believe.
What'd you say?
It's inside the fridge.
When'd you make it?
I don't know.
I don't know, maybe two weeks ago.
Two weeks?
No, come on.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
Dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun,
dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun, dun.
I don't know, I don't know anything.
I don't know anything about food.
I just wasted all that making a stupid joke.
No, what, no.
You put it in the fridge.
Yeah, I mean, I don't know anything about tomatoes.
What's a tomato?
I need a plate, I need a plate right now.
Is that right?
I don't think so.
No, it is, okay.
Wait, I have to heat this up.
It's just ice cold.
No, what are you doing?
I thought I would put the tomatoes on there.
No, oh, you fucking donkey, you idiot.
Do you see what you're doing?
Wait, how about a little garnish?
I need to heat this up.
Whoa, why is it black?
Why is it black?
What?
Oh.
Michael, come here, please.
Yes, chef.
What you served me was motor oil.
Motor oil.
And I'm not talking about that's the consistency,
that's what it was.
I watched you pour it in there.
Valvoline.
Yeah, I don't know how to use a knife, chef.
I have no idea.
Hello?
This is fucking rancid.
Wait, I can play darts?
The fish is done.
Oh, another salmon.
What's this?
What do you think you're serving me here?
What are you out of your fucking mind?
Did you make this?
You made this one right here?
It's just disgusting is what it is.
It's absolutely disgusting.
You see, I'm hip.
I know all the fucking jokes, everybody knows.
All right, I need salmon, salmon, salmon.
Oh, Mr. Ramsey, I've got a special delicious dish for you.
Do you think I would get kicked off immediately
if I was like walking around like this?
Okay, here we go.
I need more potatoes.
Bugs in the pan.
Oh, potatoes, two potatoes and water.
What am I doing?
Oh, let's go.
Salt it up.
Oh yeah, I hate that shit.
I hate that more than anything.
I hate that.
They're like wafting shit.
No, don't do that.
Get away from me with that shit.
It's just weird.
Why do people do that?
I swear to God, people do that.
They pretend.
I know I've talked about this before.
Going like, oh, stop, just go like this.
Just look, it's so gross to me.
I don't know why.
I hate it.
It's a basic, I know, but it's something about it.
I hate everything about it.
What, it's going like this?
What, can I breathe in the vapors and burn my nose?
Yes.
What if you leaned in and got boogers in it?
Yeah, what if I went like this
and my sweat on my hand dropped in?
That argument does not hold any weight for me at all.
I need a plate.
What's he doing?
Oh, what is he doing?
They love my food.
They just do.
Not bad.
Booger?
What is, booger?
Guys, I don't know who you think I am
or what you think is kind of wrong with me,
but there's not just water dripping out of my nose.
Do waters not just, if I lean over something,
I'm not just gonna like, huh?
What are you talking about?
Make a lemon soup.
Oh, that's a good idea.
I'm getting so tangled up.
That's a good idea.
Lemon soup?
Sure.
This is gonna make a lot.
Okay.
Start the boiling process here.
So I need lemons.
Should I cut them up?
What do you think?
Just boil them with the rinds on?
Maybe an onion?
And then mush them up.
I need to stick blend them.
Okay.
Ooh, it's actually turning, that's cool.
I have more?
Wait, what if I like boiled a piece of salmon in there?
Would that be good?
Would that taste good?
That would be kind of interesting.
No, why would I, yeah, salt can go in there.
Salt and pepper.
Looks good.
It looks like it's cooking, hold on.
I'm making baby food.
These are the ingredients on the back
of like a Gerber salmon paste.
Hold it, how many can I put in there?
This is gross.
And I just wasted like $30.
What baby?
What do you mean baby?
Baby, do not, don't feed this to babies.
What?
I don't understand.
Wait, what are you talking about?
What are you talking about?
Babies?
Well, I'm not saying that you feed this to a baby.
I'm just saying like that, like this is like,
you put like a bunch of paste into a jar.
You just grind up a bunch of stuff
and it turns into baby, like peas and carrots and,
I don't know, whatever else is mushrooms.
I don't know what else is in it.
What's in baby food?
Peas, carrots.
What else is in baby food?
Is it just ground up peas?
Hello?
What happened?
Somebody said go into, yeah, let me,
I wanna go to sandbox mode.
I wanna do sandbox mode.
I wanna just, I wanna make like pizzas and shit.
Yeah, we're doing sandbox.
Make a hamburger helper?
I will make hamburger helper for you, I will.
Let's do sandbox.
I just burped, I'm so sorry.
Ooh, new kitchen, hell yeah.
All right, now it's time for me to make you
my famous hamburger helper.
It's very easy to make.
The beef stroganoff is probably my favorite.
I like cheeseburger macaroni, it's pretty good too,
but nah, I don't think it's as good as the stroganoff.
Oh damn.
Okay, what do we got?
Right here, we'll start with,
I just wanna wreck this place.
Okay, what do we got?
First of all, let's get a plate.
If you're gonna have hamburger helper,
you need one of these,
because it's literally just shlop.
It's just shlop.
It's just a big thing of shlop and that's all it is.
Start, get our prep station ready, please.
Okay.
Michael Jackson?
I need to put two on.
I don't wanna be like, okay.
Should I even have gloves?
Oh, you do asparagus too?
Nice.
Dr. Shlop, bacon?
Hold on, I just wanna, I want bacon.
What is this tiny little shit bacon, what?
This is bacon?
This is not bacon.
Holy shit, a banana.
All right, stop messing around.
Burger meat, do they just have ground beef?
We'll make cheeseburger mac.
Need a few of these.
Okay, burger meat, but do they have ground beef?
Goat cheese, disgusting.
Absolutely revolting.
I don't see G, ground beef.
I don't see it.
No, they have hamburger meat, like burger meat,
but I feel like this is a patty.
Probably is, right?
Yeah, can I chop this up?
I can chop this up, right?
Okay, I need like a pound.
And then we'll also do,
oh, there's beef chuck.
Wait, can I grind this up?
Do I have a grinder?
Is this a grinder?
I mean, these chunks are too big.
Can I do it to the patty?
No.
Oh, I can.
Oh, nice, nice, nice, right, right, okay, okay.
Can I chop these up even thinner and finer?
Let me see a knife.
Let me see if I can chop this up.
No.
All right, this is gonna have to do.
There's a lot to do.
Get it in here.
Blend the beef?
Um, no.
No, we're not doing that.
What do I do with this?
This, no, I'm not gonna feed it to the plant.
We're not doing that.
All right, just put these over here
because I'm gonna ground all this up.
We're gonna grind the cheese too.
It'll be nice and melty.
Ooh, all right.
Let's do this real quick.
Oops, that was a mistake.
It's okay.
God damn it.
All right, this is as ground as it's gonna be,
which is fine.
Let's get it all.
There it is.
There is our ground beef.
Let's go ahead and get it over on the stove area here.
Not gonna cook it yet.
Just gonna get it there.
Because we gotta brown that meat first and foremost.
After you brown the meat,
you're gonna add your cheese and sauce and your macaroni,
which we need to get that too.
All right, macaroni.
Which one do I want?
This one here probably is the one that looks the most.
Can I see what it looks like?
Yep, that looks like it's it.
Okay, sounds good.
Prep that over here.
I need a thing to boil this with.
I'll give me that pan right here.
All right, so we're gonna go like this.
How do you turn on one of these fucking stoves?
All right, that's on.
I need water in here.
I mean, technically you don't do that.
You don't cook the pasta cooks in the sauce mix.
Well, we need milk.
This kitchen's too big.
I don't know how people have kitchens like this.
All right, I need milk and water.
Where's milk?
Do I not have milk?
Oh, here it is, okay.
All right, we're gonna do a little bit of this.
Just getting our, we gotta get our station ready.
Okay, where's the pasta?
Where's the sink?
Oh, how are you supposed to use this thing?
A little bit more.
Okay, sounds, don't spill it.
Get that boiling, ow, that hurt.
I'm fine though, don't worry about me.
Okay, so now that's gonna boil.
Let's get the pasta in there.
Put the milk in there too.
That's all that's in this box.
No way, what?
This, that's it?
Well, back to the pantry, I guess.
Are you serious?
I need, where's my device?
Hold on, I didn't wanna buy that.
Okay, I need, good.
I don't need sour cream.
Okay, I need, what do I need?
What did I just say?
Oh yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, pasta.
Pasta, pasta, pasta, pasta, pasta.
That's parsley, miscellaneous.
Firecracker?
Halloween candy?
Stool?
Oh, look at that.
That is not what that looks like.
Then you know it.
Where, where's the, where's the pasta?
Spices, products, right, you would imagine.
I don't see it anywhere.
Where the hell is it?
Oh, I missed it, what is it?
What the hell is it called?
Fussy, foosy, foosy, foosily.
All right, I need like three of these.
All right, let's go.
What a fucking scam.
Do I need more water?
I need more water in here.
Wait, hold on.
Can I scoop it back into there with anything
or do I have to do this whole thing again?
Hold on, let me scrape it out of the bottom of the sink.
Hold on.
Dude, that's so stupid.
Oh my God, just give me another few boxes.
Ah, that's gonna make me puke, by the way.
Jesus, dropping the whole thing in the sink.
You know what sucks?
I've done that before.
I have taken a strainer and poured wet, caught pasta into it
and it was like a little too heavy
and it was a little too hot and I dropped it into the sink.
It's happened before.
It sucks.
All right, let me get back to where I was.
We don't need this much pasta.
I mean, we do because it's hamburger helper.
It's just shlop, that's all it is.
This will be enough.
Yeah, this is more than enough.
Go back to cooking this pasta.
Okay, here we go.
The game does not like this at all.
The game hates that there's that much pasta in there.
Okay, now let's continue.
Get our milk in there.
That's a lot, but it's okay.
Where's our cheese?
Is that gonna melt?
Does the cheese melt in this game?
I don't know, does the cheese melt?
I need another pan, please.
Oh no, it's melting, it is.
Turn it on, dude.
What are you doing?
Turn it on.
That our ground beef
and you just wanna get this to brown.
You just want it to brown a little bit.
Okay, what are you doing?
Is this cooking?
What's going on?
Okay, there we go.
Let that cook for a little longer.
Our pasta and our cheese sauce is here.
I also like to add a little bit of onion.
If you haven't, what's in here?
Some of these pieces need to be moved around
because they're gonna cook.
You gotta mush them up.
You gotta break it up with a fork
or break it up with a utensil.
Some of them are not gonna cook completely evenly,
but that's okay.
They'll finish off in the other pan we're gonna use,
which by the way, I need one.
It's just cook, fucking cook already, cook.
Okay, I need a saucepan.
Just like a deep kind of saucepan.
The game really hates
that there's that much macaroni in there.
Hates it.
Big pot.
Bake tray, blowtorch, bucket.
No, no, no, grill pan.
Is this what I need?
No, I already have one of those.
Paella pan?
Okay, it'll do, it'll work.
It'll do, it'll do.
So we're just gonna set this one here on low.
Don't want it to be too bad.
Is it on?
Okay.
Oh no.
It's okay, it's all right, it's all right, it's all right.
Then we're gonna take our pasta mixture with the cheese sauce
and there's our hamburger helper.
Gotta stir it up a little bit though.
Remember, this is the cheeseburger macaroni version.
We can turn that off and we can get this.
We can scoop this out onto a plate now.
There it is.
Looks pretty good.
If you want to grate a little bit of cheese on top,
that's up to you.
That's completely up to you.
But there it is.
There's our cheeseburger mac.
We need that deep plate here.
Okay.
Oh, this is a two-hander.
And there it is.
There it is.
Mess.
You know what's kind of funny?
I feel like over the course of my life,
I feel like I have seen this exact image.
When if you make a bunch of food
that's really, really kind of a pain in the ass to make
or it gets really messy,
I've left it like this for hours at a time.
I have like spilled, dumped, and gotten it like there
where it's like, I got two servings maybe.
And I just leave that shit until, you know what?
Like I could, but I want to eat.
And then, you know what?
I kind of want to watch TV.
So it just stays there for like two or three hours.
And then eventually, finally, you're like, you know what?
I probably should, they're adhered to the counter.
So it's probably time to take them up.
You know what?
You're like, okay, there's a little bit of give there.
And you clean the counter and everything.
Oh, oh, oh, it smells so good.
Now we're going to make a pot roast.
You good?
Yeah.
Boil it in the cheese water.
What you want to do is you want to brown it a little bit.
Are you going to put the au jus on top?
How do I restart?
I want to restart.
I want to do another one.
Boil it.
Okay.
I want to see what happens if you take a pot roast
and you put it in the microwave for 15 minutes.
What happens?
Is it like a Thanksgiving turkey
that I can put in the microwave?
I hope so.
It is beef chuck.
Okay.
What about like full turkey?
I could make like a hamburger too.
Yeah.
I want to make a burger for you guys.
I want to make my,
I'm going to make you guys two,
two or three of my favorite burgers.
And I'm not kidding.
It's just her Holly laugh.
I just heard her laugh.
What, what, what ha what my burger?
You don't like my burgers?
She pretends to like them.
Okay.
So I'm going to make him three of my favorite hamburgers.
We're going to need that pan.
I have, I have pretty, pretty interesting burgers
that I like.
It's my go-tos.
We'll see how you guys like them.
First of all, we need cheese.
I need lettuce.
Wait, I got a corn on the cob.
Holy shit.
I'll use it for later.
No, I, I know I'm not one of those people
that's going to put an egg on it.
So don't worry.
Okay.
Very nice.
Just need one.
I need like, can I chop up these onions?
I can chop the onions, right?
Couple of onions.
Uh, no, no, no, no.
Wait, how big is this?
All right.
That's huge.
We're going to put that in the microwave as well.
How big is this?
What is, that's weird.
Okay.
Wait, I don't want cabbage.
I want lettuce.
Strawberry, T-bone, thyme twig.
No, no, no.
Where's lettuce?
Is lettuce a spice?
No.
Where the hell is it?
Is lettuce in the game?
I don't think lettuce is in the game.
Put eggs in the microwave.
Is jellyfish an herb?
Miscellaneous?
I don't, where, what would it be?
I don't think it's in the game.
Is cabbage, basil leaf, asparagus, bay leaf,
broccoli, chives, cilantro, cucumber, dill.
I do want to make a few eggs.
I'm just curious of how that worked.
Green bell pepper.
No, it's not here.
Mint, I could probably get mint leaf
and pretend it's lettuce.
All right, it's going to have to be the cabbage.
Yeah.
Unfortunately, it has to be the cabbage
because I can't, there's no lettuce.
No, it's not there.
What about sage leaf?
No, that doesn't look like lettuce.
It kind of does.
I need a lot of it though.
What happens if I chop this?
What is this?
Is it a brain the whole time?
The parsley leaves might look like lettuce.
Yeah, all right, okay, okay.
We're going to get a shitload of parsley leaves
because this looks kind of like lettuce
and that's all I'm looking for is the look.
Okay, that'll look like lettuce on the burger.
That's fine.
Romaine?
No, it's not there.
There's no romaine, man.
Okay, now I need, I need onions.
Okay, onions with mayo, with mayonnaise.
Is mayo in the game?
You don't have mayo?
You got like mustard, olive oil, milk.
There's no mayo?
What?
Just make it.
Okay, I need oil.
What kind of oil is it?
It's olive oil, right?
Olive oil and eggs and just whip it up in vinegar, yeah.
All right, where are those eggs?
These eggs are huge.
Okay, where's the blender?
Over there.
We're going to make our own homemade mayonnaise?
Okay, where's the blender?
Where is it?
Where's the blender top thing?
Do I have to buy it?
This is the German meal.
I think I have to buy it, right?
Blender.
What the fuck is this?
What?
What is it called?
There we go.
Wait, where's the food processor?
Is that it?
Okay, all right.
We need oil, white vinegar.
I don't know how much I'm supposed to use.
And then I need my eggs.
That's going to be disgusting.
How many eggs do you put in?
How do you make mayonnaise?
Look, I'm making my secret patties for you guys.
Oops.
How does this work?
There are shells in here.
You know what?
It doesn't matter.
It's fine.
It'll be fine.
We got our eggs.
I need a few more.
What's happening?
I need more oil.
Shut up.
Okay.
I need a couple more eggs.
Now we need a little bit of a kick.
I'm going to say, let's go to the spice rack.
And what do I want to put in here?
I want to put in some things here.
Pepper, a little bit of garlic.
Oh, yo.
Hold on a second.
Hold on a minute.
Okay.
I want some garlic, garlic.
I want like two things of garlic.
And then I think that that's all right.
Maybe a little bit, maybe a little bit of salt.
Okay.
I think that's going to be fine.
That's easy.
Get this on the food processor and let's begin.
As our fresh mayo.
Let's try it.
Thickness seems pretty good.
That's all right.
That's good.
We've got our mayo.
I can sit right here.
Don't have to do anything else with that.
I think it's stay there for now.
That's considered room temp.
You made paint thinner.
It's mayonnaise.
Just relax.
Why everybody hates mayonnaise so much?
You like eggs.
You like oil.
You like like creaminess.
So what's the problem?
Oh, mayo, gross.
I don't get what the issue is.
What's the issue?
All right.
Let's make, let's cook these burgers up.
I am going to do my first burger.
Very simple.
There's nothing too crazy about it.
I need an onion.
This is my go-to though is a knife.
Thank you.
These onions have to be chopped fairly thin.
And then we have to cook these
because they need to be grilled onions.
They have to be grilled onions.
I like them nice and chopped and thin.
Get away from me.
That's all right.
You get the idea.
Because I can't seem to cut these any more
than I already have.
All right.
You get the idea.
These are our onions.
Let's go ahead and start sweating those out.
Let's go ahead and start sweating those out guys.
Okay.
Let's go ahead and start sweating those out.
Once those are done sweating a little bit,
you just want to let them breathe a little.
Give them a shake.
Once those are ready, we can move on to the next step.
Oh, excellent.
Those are good to go.
Get them off.
Okay.
We've got our grilled onions.
I need a little bit of oil for this pan
so I can get these, one of these burgers going by the way.
Rare.
No.
Medium rare.
We do medium in this house.
This is a medium household.
I don't even know if I'm talking to you.
I probably am not.
I'm a, yeah, I am.
This is, I'm a medium household.
I do not do medium rare.
No, we do not do that here.
Oops.
I need oil.
I just need some olive oil.
Oh, you know what?
Let's go butter.
Yeah.
Hell yeah.
This is making me want a burger now.
Clarified butter.
You have, my God.
You gotta be kidding me, dude.
Oh man.
I want a burger now.
Let's do burgers.
Okay.
That's, that's it.
That's good.
Good, good, good.
Now we're gonna, I'm gonna do, I'm putting in,
I need some, give me that.
No, not the mayonnaise.
I don't want the mayo.
Let's season it really nicely.
It's good.
A little bit of salt too.
And you know, I'm feeling a little weird today.
We're going with, what do we want?
No, no, no, no, no.
I want like, I want, I want like coriander or something.
Right?
So I look, so people think I'm like really smart.
Oh, what do you put on your burgers?
Oh, well, salt, pepper, garlic, a coriander, cumin,
a little bit of thyme.
And oh, this person's really knows what they're doing.
They understand the kitchen very well.
Oh, they know what they're doing.
No, people that say all that shit,
they just put it, you can't even taste it.
Like, oh, well, it's a mixture I use of thyme, rosemary,
cumin, coriander, cilantro.
It's like, they're just saying those things
to make you think that they're like a chef.
You can't even taste any of that shit.
But it's like, it's like, it's mac and cheese, dude.
Like you can't even taste that.
It's like, you're not going to be able to eat.
It's just going to taste like cheese and pasta.
What is this?
What is it?
Catnip?
No, no mint.
I'll do some white pepper and lavash.
Oh yeah, yeah.
How about some lavash, man?
No, I want, I want like onion powder.
Here we go, garlic powder.
I'm a big fan of garlic.
Ooh, I love this shit.
All right, I need salt and then I'm ready to grill.
Ooh, let's use this with salt.
Okay, can you just pretend I put salt on it?
Who cares?
Because like, wait, there it is.
Is this salt or is this like whipped cream?
What is this?
Whatever.
Oh guys, you know what would be so sick right now?
If I put some truffle powder on it.
Nobody eats that stuff.
You eat that when you go to a restaurant.
Yeah, they go, oh, hey, do you want the truffle this?
You want the truffle mac?
You want the truffle fries?
You want the truffle?
You just nod your head and go, okay,
thanks for the four extra dollars
you're gonna charge me for these now.
Are you ready?
It's time to begin the grilling.
Oh, we're not using that.
We're using this.
Three minutes aside.
Sometimes three, after you do three minutes aside,
it's very important that you second guess the shit
out of yourself over and over again.
And you do three minutes aside, then you panic.
And then you squish the fuck out of it
because you're terrified of getting sick.
And then you flip it five more times.
So it ends up being about six minutes aside.
What's wrong with this?
Why is this made out of tofu?
It's not supposed to look like that.
What's wrong with this?
I want a new one.
That's not supposed to look like that.
Salt, pepper, fish eggs, whatever the fuck this was.
And oh, you guys can't forget the garlic powder.
You can't forget the garlic.
Okay, now it's ready.
Now it's ready.
Now what you're looking for is looking for a little sear.
Three minutes aside.
Anybody else sit here while this is happening
and they freak out.
You just go like this.
Oh, I don't know.
I don't know.
And then it starts to smell more than cooked meat.
It starts to get kind of a different smell.
And you're like, I don't know if it's supposed
to smell like that.
It's burning.
And you freak out and flip it in like a minute.
I'm not a noob.
Is this on high?
Perfect.
You only seasoned one side.
All right, now we squish the fuck out of it.
Squish it.
Oh, this looks really good.
What happened?
Why is it white powder all over it now?
Oh, don't forget this.
Don't forget this.
The weeds from your backyard.
Whatever that is.
It's almost ready.
Oh my God, dude.
If you could smell that right now.
Oh my God.
That smells so good.
It's just filling the whole house with it.
Oh man.
Oh my God.
It smells so good, dude.
Are you kidding me?
It's like alien meat.
Mom, are you cooking burgers down there?
That's right, son.
Oh, it smells so good down here.
All right, that's almost done.
We got a perfectly cooked medium patty
with, I don't know, like a cocaine on it.
Sit it right there.
Nice.
It's like, it's okay.
A bird shit on it, but I think it's gonna be fine.
It still will taste good.
What was that?
What was, what was it?
It was just flying.
All right, we got our burger here.
I wanna brush that off.
I don't know what that is.
Oh, don't forget the grilled onions.
Shut up.
I need a burger patty.
Burger, whatever it is.
It's the, you put starch on it?
What?
I put starch, Starch Andy.
I'm going fucking, I'm being weird.
I'll put some corn.
I'm trying to throw it onto the grill.
All right, where, give me that.
Hamburger bun.
Where's burger bun?
Burger bun, AB?
Burger meat, burger bun.
Why is it two tops?
What?
Okay, well, whatever.
It's two tops.
I don't, I didn't know.
I don't know why that happened.
Let's start assembling the burger.
Remember this, I'm not kidding.
This is my favorite burger, or one of them.
We'll go like this, start here, like that.
That gets us to, let me make sure
I look at you the right way.
This is a puke inducing turn.
I'm so sorry.
All right, let's get the onions on there.
These are grilled onions.
Dude, I don't even have any cheese.
What?
All right, you get the idea.
There's the grilled onions.
I need my lettuce, which is, I don't know where it is.
Just turn, this is like, this joke is not funny.
It's just an annoying sound.
All right, where's my lettuce?
It's over here.
This is the pretend lettuce, right?
Shit.
I need to make this over here.
Grilled onions, lettuce.
Can I reach it from here?
You have to pretend this is lettuce.
Grilled onions, lettuce, a little bit of mayo, okay?
Mayo, lettuce, grilled onions, cheese.
I don't think I have any cheese here so far.
A little.
I mean, I'm trying to make it look like it was on there.
And then cheese, just cheddar cheese.
Cheddar cheese is fine, although Swiss would be good too.
So, provolone.
Oh my God, I want a burger so bad now.
I'm gonna get the biggest, dirtiest burger
you've ever seen in your life.
Okay, I need to cut this.
Okay, that's good enough.
This is the burger right here.
Again, let's go over it.
Oh, look at that.
It's cumin, coriander, thyme, rosemary,
baked into the meat, put in beforehand.
It's gotta go into the ground, ground chuck, by the way.
No, it's grilled onions, lettuce, mayo, cheese,
burger patty, medium.
I don't think you need any more than that.
Can I cut it down the middle?
The other one, should I even make the other one?
Seriously, that didn't work.
You get the idea.
All right, the other one, I'm trying to cut it.
The other one is a little different.
The other one is grilled mushrooms, grilled onions,
provolone cheese, and A1 steak sauce.
I just pretend like I made that one for you.
Oh, you can cut it.
Next game, all right, we're gonna move on.
We'll do the next game.
Just start, all right, now it's time for the stream.
You know, the part that everybody thinks is funny.
Here we go, what's he gonna do now?
Oh my God, is he gonna put all this stuff
in the microwave and cause a fire?
I actually wanna do that.
Let's hear it, good.
Will this actually work?
All right, if you put something on top of a microwave,
will it get cooked like radiation style?
It's working.
Would this actually work?
Put the corn in the microwave?
Oh, that's not, that's a good idea.
Where's the corn?
Will it actually, will it pop?
Oh, it's dirty, I gotta get like this,
clean it up a little bit.
All right, that freaks me out with a microwave too.
When you're done and the microwave is,
okay, here's your food is ready,
and the food is ready.
I hate that.
This has to be residual,
like gamma rays in here and shit, right?
I don't, I wanted to sit there for like a good 10 seconds.
No, no.
Residual gamma rays?
I don't know, it's like, it feels weird.
I have talked about this more than a few times.
We always talk about, okay, like 50 years ago,
they thought that smoking cigarettes was healthy, right?
It was like not a big deal.
You know, a hundred years ago,
that every 50 to a hundred years,
we learn something new about humanity
that the next like three or four generations look back
and say, what the fuck were they doing, right?
I believe, I think the microwave is gonna be the thing
that in a hundred years,
people are gonna be looking back and going,
what were they doing?
They were zapping their food with radiation?
What, what?
No, they were not doing that, right?
Like it has to be.
Oh yeah, or plastic.
Yep, plastic could be another one.
Definitely plastic.
Okay, that's good.
This didn't do anything by the way.
I mean, it just turned it like a little orange.
All right, it's baking in the microwave, yay or nay.
What do you say?
Laying raw bacon in the microwave
and hitting the button, yay or nay.
I've seen it done before, not a big fan, not a fan.
Baking it is best.
You know, I used to really like putting it in the pan,
but you can only do a few strips in the pan at a time.
And that's a pain in the ass.
I prefer the taste of strips in the pan versus in the oven,
but you can do a whole pound
of two pounds of bacon in the oven.
It takes so long to cook it in a pan.
Get a griddle, dumb ass.
All right, let's, let's, let's move on.
Let's play another game.
Oh, I just want this.
I want this right now.
Oh wait, I didn't, I forgot to make a fire, okay.
How do I start a fire?
Okay, let's turn everything on, right?
Okay, who wants fried eggshells?
All right, let's get that ready.
Oh, right, okay.
This is gonna, this might be loud.
I would turn your volume down.
This could be awful.
I hate this, I hate this.
I'm not even in, I hate that.
Nothing about that is fucking fun.
Well, that was awful.
Oh, I just see, I just hate that.
I didn't like that.
I feel like I'm like sanitizing my house.
No, you don't understand.
I got, sweeping motions, Jeremy, sweeping motions.
Put your iPad in the microwave.
Open, why is this sealed shut?
I don't like this at all.
I hate this shit.
I hate this kind of shit, I really do.
I'm just opening up those snake cans in front of my face.
How's this doing?
This is just magma.
Is it on fire?
All right, I'm done.
Wait, what is that?
What is this?
This doesn't do anything.
All right, next game.
I'm gonna take a break.
I'm gonna get some water.
I'll be right back.
I have no idea.
My face is probably looks horrible right now.
I'm gonna take a quick break.
I'll be right back.
So now we're gonna play Blair Witch VR.
Said I was gonna play this a few weeks ago.
This is probably the last thing we're gonna do.
So however long I'm gonna do this for.
Somebody said, be careful.
This game is really slow going, but whatever, we'll see.
I do need to untangle my VR.
Very tangled.
All right, we're officially untangled.
I wanna mention this one more time too
because a lot of people are here now.
So if you watched the replacement stream,
the upload on the archive channel
has fixed like 90% of all the audio problems.
So I would say definitely, definitely check it out.
Any of those like weird laggy glitchy moments
have been fixed for the most part.
So I would say, check it out.
It was the studio recording, thank God.
All the lag issues we had are pretty much solved.
Let me untangle this for a second.
Give me one more minute.
Okay, you promised us Among Us.
Among Us VR is not out.
You guys just gaslit me into saying
I was gonna play it next time.
But yeah, I'm really, really, really happy
that at least the studio recording came out perfectly fine.
This is still a few little problems,
but if you wanna watch it again,
those issues should be kind of resolved.
All right, let's go.
Air witch VR, I'm so winded.
I'm gonna play VR.
There's a bunch of bricks on me.
Headset, talking about microwaves being problematic,
but bacon is a carcinogen.
It's a mush of all the worst parts of the pig.
I'm not saying it's one's worse than the other, what?
Plus bacon, look, all cooked meat is a carcinogen, right?
Especially if you grill it.
That delicious black char stuff, that's bad for you.
I mean, am I gonna stop eating that?
No.
Have I reduced the amount of meat that I probably consume?
Probably.
But I mean, come on.
I'm not gonna stop eating char broiled bacon bits.
All right, here we go.
Hey, Jeremy, is lettuce a liquid?
No.
All right, I'm coming back.
Where's my mouse?
Hello?
I don't know if this, where's the audio?
Is there any audio?
Weird.
Oh my God, what?
That scared the shit out of me.
There's just an animal over here.
I just saw movement and it was, okay,
movement type headset, standing mode, free movement.
All right, I feel like
you'll be hearing some kind of sounds here.
Hold on.
Why do we not hear audio?
Hey, there's audio.
Hopefully it's not too, too loud.
Hello?
What happened?
I just had it, what the fuck happened to it?
Fucking VR.
What happened to the audio?
I just had it.
Where's the audio?
It was just here.
Fucking audio.
Like the game window, yeah, I did.
I can't, it was, I just had it.
Yeah, this ass is a carcinogen.
Like one out of every three VR games works.
Okay, let me try reloading it again.
I feel like there's better odds at playing roulette
than actually getting a VR game
to work the way you want it to.
Yeah, the audio's there.
Yeah, I got Blair Witch VR down here in my taskbar.
I clicked it.
It has clicked right now.
It has opened up a second.
Why is there even a second window here?
Yeah, it doesn't wanna pull the audio anymore.
Welcome to fucking hell.
I'm gonna try, I'm gonna restart the game
and see if that does anything.
German, do you know how to work a computer?
Yeah, I want, I hate VR.
I'm literally never playing it again.
I fucking hate this thing.
Let me get back into it.
Let me try to reload the game again.
You can hear the audio now.
I'm just gonna give this headset away to one of you guys.
I'm gonna sign it and I'm gonna write,
don't fucking ever use this.
Don't play this.
Only for decoration only is what I'm gonna write on it.
Okay, so it should be in the window right now.
Oh my God, I can hear the audio.
No, don't.
Oh my fucking God, okay.
I need to full screen the window though.
What the, God damn it.
That, I did the exact same shit last time,
didn't do anything.
Like the planets have to be in the right spot.
The earth has to be the right rotation for VR to work.
All right, what do I do?
Can I pet the dog?
Who's a good dog?
Yes, you're a good dog.
What is it?
Okay, standing mode, free movement, comfort, sir,
that's fine.
Video settings, auto-detect.
Okay, new game.
A blooper team production.
Where are we going?
Welcome to
Burkittsville.
Did I skip?
I'm sorry.
This marks the latest in a series of disappearances
dating back to Nukketsville.
What's with the cops?
What's going on?
Missing.
Peter Shannon.
Peter Shannon, my son, I'm gonna assume maybe.
I think.
Wait, why did this?
Oh my God, don't do that.
It sounds like it's jump-cutting.
Peter.
Okay, imagine getting something in your eye in VR
and it ain't coming out.
Okay, grab your phone.
Free movement, I don't know how to use the phone.
Jess, hey, yeah, it's good to hear from you.
Good to hear from you.
Did you hear about the missing kid?
Missing kid.
Why wouldn't it be?
How do you hang up?
Wait, wait, wait, no, I'm glad I did.
Listen, I'm almost there.
I'll call you later, okay?
So I'm out here at a search party to look for a kid.
Let's go, bullet.
All right, let's go.
What do we got?
It started without us, huh?
Let's take a look, what do we got?
Okay, bullet, let's see.
Oh, we got a note here.
We got a note.
He's been through enough already.
Sorry, Anthony.
First come, first served.
What is this?
I'll call landing once I'm in the forest.
Why would I have this for?
All right, what do you got?
Keep going, all right.
I gotta find this kid.
Some items found during the game
can be stored in your backpack.
Okay, cool.
Oh, that's my backpack.
What is this?
My ID?
What the hell is that?
Wait, did I just take a sofa?
What is this, a tent?
Hey, drop it, drop it, drop that.
Don't touch that, disgusting.
Disgusting.
What was the point of that?
What was the point?
Oh, Mike.
That's some strength.
What was the point of that?
Let me see, what is this?
Looking for the missing kid.
Nine years old.
He's four foot four, weighs 68 pounds, okay.
He was in a green t-shirt.
Donut, cool.
All right, none of this shit matters.
It's just fluff.
Let's go.
What's that?
Knife?
What is this?
You wanna play?
Try grabbing the whistle.
Okay, where's the whistle?
Seek.
Pull it.
What does this do?
Snack?
Stay close to me.
You want a snack?
Come here, boy.
Snack.
Do I have food for him?
Bullet, seek.
What?
Heal.
Stay close.
What the fuck are you talking?
Seek.
Bullet, look around, boy.
That's a really awful way to have that be mapped.
All right, let's go.
You have to blow it?
What are you talking about?
Stay close.
You were wrong.
Let's go find this kid.
Stuff's named gamer posture.
Scary Blair witch.
Be careful.
She's gonna come get you.
In the woods.
Chapter one, into the woods.
Machine gun fire?
The dog better not die.
I know, right?
I don't want that to happen either.
Okay.
Bullet, seek.
I don't know why he keeps doing this.
Bullet.
Stay close.
Do I have to press A or something?
Bullet.
Is it stay close?
It's called landing.
During the game, you can try to communicate
using the walkie talkie, okay?
Walkie talkie.
Okay.
Where's the walkie talkie?
Up here?
Bullet.
That's my whistle.
Come here, boy.
What the fuck?
Where is it?
Bullet.
Ellis to base.
Do you copy?
Joining the search party.
Sir. Is there a sprint?
I'm here to help.
That's all there is to it.
Bullet's with me.
If he catches the scent,
he'll lead us straight to the kid.
Heard he needs some graphics.
Sir.
Sticky keys.
Not this time.
Roger that.
Over and out.
Okay.
Time to get to work.
Oh, he's got something.
What'd you find, Bullet?
Did you find a trace of anything?
What do you got?
What's in here?
Looking for Peter.
Not the search party, buddy.
Oh, look.
Another missing persons thing.
Okay.
So, a night in the woods.
Like old times, huh?
I'm fine.
This will be different.
Yes, this is the Blair Witch.
Ooh.
It's not your goddamn trash can.
What did we find?
What do you got?
Where are you?
Oh.
What do you got?
Something?
Oh my God.
It's something.
I think there's a body in here.
What is it?
What'd you find?
Oh, I thought it was...
Am I gonna see it?
Let me see it.
Baltimore crows.
The Boston Red Sox.
That's Peter's cap.
Good boy.
Okay, I got it.
Sorry.
Can you follow the scent?
All right.
Just follow the scent.
Go with, buddy.
Come here.
What is the game?
What's happening with the game?
Why is the game so dark?
Can you smell?
He's got it.
Okay, hold on.
I need...
Wait, where'd he go?
Bullet.
All right.
Where is it?
Is there a sprint?
There has to be.
Where'd he go?
Bullet, wait up.
Don't go through this tall brush.
What happened?
Excuse me?
Who the hell is he?
I don't...
What just happened to me?
Not now.
I can't call him.
Get a grip, Alice.
I'm not giving up now.
Has somebody shot an arrow at me?
An arrow just went by my head.
What happened?
What's going on?
The sun's so bright.
What?
That was weird.
Prolonged loneliness can affect your mental state.
Prolonged loneliness?
Um, okay.
So we gotta not...
We...
Well, don't run away.
Hold on.
Come back here.
All right, stay close.
Ooh, that's an itchy spot.
Okay, now what?
Where are we going now?
Okay.
I guess we're gonna go this way.
Where is it?
No, I want to answer the phone, not button the person.
Can I call that person back?
Is that...
What is...
Is it a picture?
Oh, come on, really?
Good night, Jerma, and chat.
Stay over here with me.
Well, good night.
Thanks for watching.
Thanks for hanging out.
Oh, a few things to talk about real quick.
I'm gonna be streaming on Saturday and Sunday this week.
Sunday, Ster and I are gonna play Dying Light 2.
Gonna go back to normal,
back to the regularly scheduled programming.
I'm not sure what we're gonna do Saturday,
but we'll figure that out.
That's the plan for this week.
So I'll see you guys on Saturday.
End of the stream, voice?
No, not quite.
Not quite, not until I get scared at least once.
This dog looks like Scooby-Doo.
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa,
whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Every video game, I win.
Why am I yelling?
Every time I play VR,
I just talk so much louder than normal.
Bullet, stay close.
Bullet, stay close to me.
There's a tent over there, Bullet.
There's a tent.
Camp site?
It is.
Oh, no.
Alice, maybe you should...
No, I'm fine.
I'll deal with it.
I just need a little more time.
Why does she have a blurred out face?
What you need is help.
I could've managed.
Alice, I can't do this anymore.
What?
What is it this time?
What, I wasn't smiling enough?
Didn't say I love you for five fucking minutes?
Jesus Christ, Alice.
Do you even hear yourself?
Yeah, I can hear myself just fine.
And I can see the way you look at me.
Like I'm a fucking loser.
You're a sick little puppy for you to look after.
Don't lie, Alice.
Get over yourself, Alice.
Be a man for once.
This is like Silent Hill.
There it is.
I'm getting all this from looking at the camcorder?
I hope you can figure it out, Alice.
I'm trying to help you.
I just can't be around you anymore.
Go ahead, get out.
Leave me the fuck alone.
Jesus.
Incoming call.
What did I do?
What am I doing?
Master, you wanted to see me, sir?
Better yet.
I wanna introduce you to someone.
Bullet, meet your new partner.
He's been through a lot, just like you.
What?
Sir, I can't.
Well, you got something else going on right now.
Is he a puppy?
Just take the damn dog, Alice.
Yes, sir.
It's Otto.
We're already at chapter three?
I feel like this is going way too, wait, chapter three.
Are there 45 chapters in this game?
I'm speed running.
Well, we're inside the tent.
Don't, boy, Jesus.
Oh, no, where is it?
Bullet.
Bullet, where did it go?
Where is it?
Bullet, where'd that just go?
You just had it.
Bullet, where is it?
Shit.
Wait, I don't have to do this again?
Red tapes allow you to manipulate reality.
Wait, what's going on?
Okay, so there was a, something happened here.
I can rewind?
Okay, so what do I do now?
Okay, that's fun.
I need that flashlight.
Thank God, all right.
Thanks a lot, Bullet.
Appreciate it.
What is this?
Paintbrush?
Okay.
Ooh, hamburger helper.
Oh, that looks like a fucking gross omelet.
Some leftovers inside.
Maybe a few days old.
A few days old?
All right, let's go.
I think I have to go over here.
What does this say?
FM 2176, field manual.
Spinning a cushioning game.
First it's witches and curses, now what?
All right, you go first.
Did I get everything?
What's over there?
Ooh, a note, a note.
There's a note on the ground, a note on the ground.
What is it?
No, dog, these are leaves.
Can I start a fire?
Oh, a big juicy double cheeseburger
sounds like it's gonna be perfect.
Don't you agree?
I'm gonna, oh, I can't wait.
Oh, hey, is Lost Ark any good?
Did I play it?
I need some opinions.
I need some outside opinions.
No.
Fuck that.
Why somebody knows?
I, okay, that game got announced.
I remember.
I remember sitting, I think, in a call
with like STIR and MLC Stealth in like 2012 or something.
And it was like, oh wow, this is gonna be so much fun.
It's like a Diablo-esque like MMO.
Then 10 years later, I guess it's like out now somehow.
It came out like four years ago in like Korea or something.
What's going on here?
What do we do about this?
I'm not gonna put my fucking hand in there.
Is that gonna do anything?
Just clasped around me.
What's wrong?
Why is the dog freaking out?
I don't know what's here.
What's wrong?
You guys, okay, so I've never seen
any of the Blair Witch movies.
None of them.
Does the Blair Witch ever come out on screen
and is like, is there like an actual Blair Witch
like old lady that is like walking around
and being like, I'm scared.
Does that happen?
What's that?
Okay.
Where's my flashlight?
What is this?
Can I record?
Hey!
I didn't mean to.
Okay.
Relax.
What even was that?
I need my flashlight.
I would be so bad in a scenario like this.
Everybody be quiet.
There's a monster out there that's gonna kill us.
Hey, hey!
What is it?
What's happening?
I hate when people do that.
I'm supposed to just wear a t-shirt
that's just a white t-shirt with just black print on it
that says free food on it
with an arrow pointing up to my face.
Like flip-flops.
Cause I ain't gonna be able to run around in those.
I can't.
An arrow pointing.
An arrow.
I'm not even gonna say it.
All right.
Come on dog, let's go.
Okay.
In what part of the world are we in?
This is like Jurassic Park leaves.
What looks like that?
And where are we?
How did we end up back here?
Wait, we did a full circle?
Yeah, all right.
Should I put the, should I cook something?
What do I got?
Trash items, wooden dolls, key items.
What should I do?
Should I start like a fire?
I don't understand.
What about in the actual tent?
Should I do the camera?
What?
Why is that happening?
Toy car.
Did it just?
Get it together, Ellis.
Cool.
Probably Peter's.
Maybe both.
What?
Sorry.
You know what to do, buddy.
What?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I need my flashlight.
You'd do great on the forest if you weren't so stubborn.
Where's my flashlight?
There's so much junk in my pack.
Okay.
Where is it?
Where'd it go?
Hold the flashlight in your hand.
Where are you?
Don't go that far.
I'm not fast enough.
Come back.
Back.
I don't know where you're going.
Okay.
Remember, you're lost in the hills.
Huh?
Did I spin around?
Where's the dog?
Did I do a complete U-turn here?
There he is.
Okay, let's go.
It's gotten blue.
Come here, boy.
I want the, I want, no, I want the,
no, stop doing that.
Come here, boy.
I want the camcorder.
Heel.
No, I want the camcorder.
Where's the camcorder on my body?
What is this?
Dude, wait, what the hell?
Where's the camera?
I want to get this on film.
We're doing a whole lot of walking here.
Chapter four.
Each chapter is a paragraph in this book.
The frames are dropping?
I wonder, I don't think it's on my computer.
Maybe the internet's messed up?
How bad is it?
When you take the camera out, they drop.
It's probably some weird problem with the game.
It's not on my computer.
I've got a 3090.
Okay, here we go.
Time to get scared, right?
Chapter five, jump scares.
Chapter six, here comes the monster.
Chapter seven, home.
What is it, boy?
Hey, hey, hey, hey, too far, too far.
Too far.
Splash.
Okay, is this just an elaborate Slenderman?
Because I've gotten two of these.
Okay, I have two notes now.
Is Slenderman going to come show up in the woods?
Dog, dog, I need you.
Bullet.
Okay, stay with me.
Okay, where are we going?
Sorry, I'm shining that in your eyes.
This way?
Don't even think about it, game.
I'm just waiting to see Snape's Patronus just walk by.
Damn it.
Don't touch that.
Don't touch it, right?
Should I touch it?
Wait, use the camera.
She's a reality-shifting camera.
I didn't do anything.
Why?
That was dumb, and I'll tell you why.
The reason why that was stupid
is because that filled up the entire screen.
It didn't like pop out right here.
It wasn't like a little thing
that was right in front of me.
That filled up every square inch of my view.
Somebody actually just flashed my face with a red light.
Come on.
You got scared by cooking simulator.
I don't like gas, okay?
And I'm gonna be very upfront with you right now.
If I had to choose between taking a propane tank
and putting it in an oven
versus running around in the woods with your dog
and touch a tree, I'm picking this one.
I hate condensed compressed gas.
It's one of my biggest fears.
It really is.
I don't like ovens.
I don't like small contained spaces
that are like a foot by a foot
that have all this pressure built up inside of it,
the things ready to blow at any moment's notice.
No.
See, this shit doesn't scare me.
I mean, I would be terrified here.
This doesn't scare me
the way that a compressed gas in a container does.
Is it a person?
Yeah, actually.
You know if anyone's ever done
any construction work out here?
The oven.
Of course, concrete, foundations or trenches.
I know what I'm seeing landing.
Zero idea how ovens work.
I know how an oven works.
I don't like it.
I don't like gas.
Okay, you can't tell me.
I know we all know that it's safe.
We all know that it's fine.
Everything's fine.
But if just pull yourself out of the world for a second
and look down at the world
and think of a propane tank, what's going on in there.
Think of like just a propane tank.
If you stop thinking about like,
oh, it's so safe, it's scientific, right?
It's kind of fucking terrifying.
It's this tank that somehow is holding
like pounds and pounds of pressure inside
that if it decides to, if you heat it up or you pit it
or if it's too much pressure builds up, the thing explodes.
Oh my God, what the hell am I supposed to do about this?
There's only like four combinations this could be.
Locked.
Derma creates a fire and cooks over it.
Yeah, I'm not, fire is fine.
Fire is not trapped inside.
Fire is not trapped inside of a container.
It's like all the warning labels too.
Like fire, you know fire's warning label?
It burns out, be careful.
Propane tanks have this like huge gigantic
like just don't fucking touch it.
Don't go near it.
Look at all the warnings are big red labels all over it.
Be careful, this is gonna explode.
Like fire is just like it's gonna burn
and it's gonna burn, it's gonna hurt you.
It hurts, it's burning.
I don't like it, I don't.
And I know I just described the same warnings
that are on the side of a public pool, right?
Like don't dive.
Watch that, you're gonna break your neck.
Don't do anything crazy, don't do anything stupid.
It's too deep.
I know that like all these warning labels.
I'm just saying.
Are you afraid of humans?
Most of all, empty truck.
Dude, Elden Ring comes out in like 14 days or something,
right, are you kidding me?
What's that?
Toothpaste?
Candy wrapper, really?
Go on, see if you can find something else.
The door just opened.
What do you got?
Don't, you're, this is a ghost in here.
What's that?
Ooh, a tape.
Let's see, is that, it's Peter.
I think I didn't see that.
The me talking?
It's called Lanning.
Ellis to base.
Peter didn't run away, he was kidnapped.
I found a tape.
It shows the man who did it.
Me.
Yeah, those tapes, they make things appear,
but there's no time, Lanning.
We have to find the kid, he's in serious danger.
Ellis, even?
We don't have much choice.
Look, I won't do this.
It sounds like the guy from Trail of Park Boys.
I'll wait for you to catch up.
Oh, Ricky, yeah, you're a fucking idiot.
What's his name?
He was shot in those trenches I saw earlier.
That's what, what's his name?
Come on, boy.
Lahey, yeah.
All right, let's keep going, man, let's go.
Gonna find that kid.
Back here again, okay.
So I gotta do something with the car.
I gotta film the car.
The doors keep opening and closing.
What's that?
What's going on up there?
Did I film the car?
Otto!
What's that?
That's the tree, right?
Hey, can you find some,
can you find some place snake on the phone?
It's hard to, okay.
I love these controllers,
but sometimes it's hard to grip
and press buttons at the same time.
Oh, cool, let's go.
It's so hard to see this.
Did I go through the wall?
This is taking so much to even see this.
I feel like I'm shit-faced right now.
Just leaning in, closing one eye,
looking at the phone.
Like, I feel like I am trashed.
I'm gonna get jump-scared, right?
That's like where this, how this becomes funny.
I can't see.
What a boring stream this is right here.
I can do this on my own, with my own phone, right?
Oh, maybe not any index controllers.
You just fucked up my whole game.
Hope everything's going well.
Call me when you have a minute.
All right, come on.
What do I need to do here?
You bought the index.
The index is the best one.
Now, I don't care how many times they show the commercial
of like the people in the living room
like dancing with their fucking wireless.
No, this is the best one.
And yes, it's a thousand dollars.
Okay, whatever it is.
Nobody has that much fun in VR.
No one does.
It's nice to not have wires though.
I know.
And it's probably awesome, but you know what?
I'm gonna stick with my purchase.
Give me the camera.
What am I supposed to do?
Something to do with the truck, has to be.
Person?
I need to figure out what the combination of that lock is.
You nice butt crack, what?
Millionaire can't afford a Quest 2.
I already bought, guys, I have a, I'm not gonna buy.
PS4 four times.
I have a Vive that is in a box in my closet.
I now own an index.
Do you want me to buy a Quest?
I'm the sucker at that point.
Do you understand?
I'm not gonna buy a like $800 GTA V again.
I'm not gonna buy the, I have it already.
Where is it?
Right here?
Oh, what is it?
What is it?
Where is it?
The video was shot around here somewhere.
Come on, where is it?
Let's see it.
Where?
Wait, lay the tape.
It's right here.
So it's facing this way.
He's going, hey, hey, ballsy move kid.
Right here.
Okay, is there a rock?
Was there a rock?
Just guess the code.
It's gotta be a rock on the ground, right?
It's like, hey, there's a ballsy move, Peter.
Right here.
What is that?
What's happening?
I swear he played something like this before.
Yeah, Outlast.
Brute force, please.
Lay the tape forward.
Buy me a what?
Stop saying Peter and help me with this fucking video game.
Stop, it's half of the chat.
All I see is butt cracking beater.
What, help me.
You guys got over that a year or two ago as well.
It went so fast.
Peter.
Call 911 on your phone?
You need to go back.
Find the rock.
Yep, yep, yep.
Lay the tape.
Tree falls in the forest.
There's Peter.
What's going on?
Okay.
Is he peeing?
If the tree falls and nobody's around, call Peter.
Press right trigger to enter what?
Tree?
Buttcrack Peter is the code.
Press left trigger to enter pregnancy mode.
Okay.
What, like.
Oh yeah dude, just press left trigger.
What would that mode even entail?
What are you talking about?
I'm going to look up the answer.
Why is he so bad at this?
I don't know what the game wants me to do.
I guess I'm going to go this way.
Press A and B.
No, this the tree fell.
We just told you the answer.
Press left trigger.
Do your tummy dance.
Look down at the ground.
Remember the code is in the truck.
Rewind them.
The only way to get out of this is to go back and
try appearing offline.
Use the camera.
The dog might find with the stuff.
Left trigger, press A and B.
Look behind you.
Where is this rock that I pick up?
Why would they show that?
What the hell?
Play the tape while looking down at the ground.
Wait, where'd it go?
Pause it.
What the hell is this game?
All right, find him.
We're moving, we're moving, we're moving, we're moving,
we're moving, we're moving, we're moving.
What'd you got?
Something?
Weren't we already here?
We just, we already did.
We didn't find him at all.
What the hell?
You sniffed the baseball and then you brought us
back to the truck?
Where's the, it didn't fall.
What the hell?
This is gonna make a sick vlog.
Your dog needs more strength.
I beg you, you press left trigger.
The code is in the truck.
Where do you see a code?
I don't see a code.
You just lied to me.
That's all right.
Honk the horn.
Get the truck in the same view with the tape.
The problem is, it's hard to see what's on that tape.
You see, I've got a complaint.
Here's my complaint.
Like I, VR it's kind of hard to see anyways.
It's the, your vision is kind of distorted
in a way anyways.
But like having to look at a video inside of VR,
like it, it's almost impossible to make out
what's going on here.
It's like, it's hard to tell.
What, what even am I watching here?
Like, what is that?
It's hard to even see what that is.
That's a tree falling, but what's underneath that?
What the hell is that?
What is that thing?
It's like a campfire, campsite.
He really does hate VR.
Use the x-ray function.
X-ray on the truck.
I don't see anything here.
I got nothing here.
Use the, can we get a diaper cam?
Give the dog the camera for fuck's sake.
Put the camera down here.
You have to time it right.
Collect all eight, pause it when the tree falls.
I can't even see.
What am I even looking for?
Is that it?
No, it's too thin.
He's doing this on purpose.
I don't even know what I'm supposed to be doing.
Line it up, stop looking at chat and use your tiny brain.
I don't even know what I'm looking at.
I don't know what that is.
Cause I, you see on your screen,
I've got like 480p in both eyes.
And then this is blurred to shit.
What is that?
Is that a bench?
I can't, it's blurred out.
I can't see what this is.
It looks like a hot bench.
It's like a bench that has like fire on it.
That's the truck.
That's not the truck.
Fucking tree is that.
It's from behind the truck.
Guys, I don't think that's the truck.
It's the right side of the truck.
Wouldn't it be showing up at this point though?
Seriously?
It's not the right side of the truck.
I don't think this is where I need to be.
Go back to the baby.
Have you gotten to the dog upgrade?
The chat's going too fast.
You're reaching abandoned.
Give the dog the baseball scent again.
Where is this?
Take a look.
What do you think?
What do you got?
What do you got for us?
Anything?
No?
He doesn't want to do it.
Proceed.
Just, okay, please everybody spam that.
Copy positive, please.
That's the only thing I want to see in the chat.
Cause I need to read it one word at a time.
There's a fallen tree that you saw.
The abandoned, unfortunately.
There's a fallen tree.
Pause the recording.
Reign.
Is it?
I can't.
I'm coming out.
I need to read this.
What does it say?
There's a fallen tree that you saw
at the beginning of the last recording.
Play it and pause the recording
when the tree is still standing.
Unfortunately, you will find out that the bridge
behind the tree has been destroyed.
Thus you have to go back to the starting point.
There's a fallen tree that you saw
at the beginning of the recording.
Play it and pause the recording
when the tree is still standing.
Where's the tree?
You will find an abandoned small gauge train.
What train?
I didn't even see a train?
Okay.
I'm gonna, apparently I'm gonna look for a train.
We're going to go find a train.
Okay.
I'm leaving this goddamn area.
The sound is gone again.
He's in training mode.
Okay.
I'm ready.
Excuse me.
I can't see with my glasses.
The whole thing is pitch black.
Go find the tree.
Oh, sonny.
I don't know if I'm glad it's blurry in VR,
but you know, at least we have one fucking ounce of light.
Ooh, good thing I can see where the tree is.
Find a tree.
I think it could be this one.
Okay.
So it's not this one.
There ain't been no train, guys.
Okay.
There hasn't been a single solitary choo choo train
the whole time we've been playing.
That tree does not fall.
Where is this train?
You'll find an abandoned train.
And where am I supposed to find the...
I'm just gonna do two, one, one, three,
because that's what people said.
I don't even care.
Just hurry up.
Just go.
Tree, not train.
What?
Two, one, one, three.
I'm just fucking putting it in.
Give me this goddamn thing.
Two, one, one, three.
It's open.
Fuck off.
I'm going in here.
We aren't even doing that part.
Now what?
Do I have anything to put in there?
I need like wires or fuses or something.
What?
Was that the real dog?
This dog is so happy.
I didn't do anything for me.
All right.
Where's this train?
Where's the train?
There should have been a hundred trains by now.
That liar.
What do you think about scuba divers and their gear?
It's weird.
I don't know.
It's too much pressure.
Is that the tree?
Is that the tree right there?
I don't think so.
Find the railroad.
I kind of been walking in a circle.
Can I get up there?
I'm back at the goddamn truck again.
I swear to God.
That is, that was the tree.
What do you mean that's the tree?
No, it's not.
Somebody said progressive or state farm.
Get out of here with your corporate bullshit.
This is the tree.
You're telling me this is the tree.
You have to own an air fryer for this part.
What am I looking at?
I don't get it.
Pull it.
Ah.
I don't get it.
Go back to the car and walk straight back from the car.
Go back to the car and go straight back from the car.
You have to prove you own an air fryer.
Aye, aye, aye.
So I'm gonna go back this way from the truck.
Where am I?
Here?
Am I going the right way?
Back of the truck.
I'm going back.
I'm going back before the truck.
Take care now.
Bye bye then.
Now what?
Is this right?
To do a BLJ, that's Mario stuff.
Well, I've already been,
I thought I was writing in a notebook.
I thought that was like, I'm writing in a notepad.
What is this?
Is that, that's it?
That's all that was here?
That can't be, right?
I gotta, it's gotta be here.
Do you even do anything in this entire game?
I don't know.
They implemented this like reality shifting camera.
I kinda just wanted Slender Man to chase me around the woods
with like a machete in his hand.
And now I'm lost again.
There's nothing else here.
Please Among Us VR, I'm begging you.
I'm not, I'm not gonna even say anything.
Where am I even going?
Is this correct?
No, this is just a circle.
Please go out and play Among Us.
That shit's not gonna come out
till probably like June or something, guys.
Focus on the task at hand.
Finding me in this convoluted ass game
where I need to go record a reality shifting camera
to find the tree that falls down.
Focus on the task we have in front of us.
Go back to the car.
You guys want me back at the car now?
Remember this, people are saying
that turn left is a railroad from the truck?
All right, well I'm going back to the truck.
I'm gonna give this two more attempts
before I uninstall this game.
Truck is right here.
It's not this.
Drive out of the woods.
Okay, so here's the truck.
You saying that there's like a railroad
around here somewhere?
Because I went that way and then I went left.
Walk from the back of the truck to the tree
and then turn left.
Didn't I just do that?
I swear to God, I just did that.
You need to vent.
Oh, you're making an Among Us joke.
I'm like, yeah, I kind of do.
Okay, turn left.
Oh yeah, I already went down here, didn't I?
This is where I just was.
There's nowhere else to go, right?
Go left?
Like down, that guy just was over here.
There's a path before that.
Is it this blue shit?
I can't walk up here, can I?
Oh my God, I'm walking up this hill.
Is it this?
Bros, I think I'm about to fucking flip out.
Where am I going?
There's collision in a lot of these places.
I can't walk over here.
It's like walled off.
Path before that?
That's the only place I can go from there.
You're saying back of the truck, forward, left path.
Path potentially before this.
Do I need neon arrow signs to point me where I need to go?
I feel like I really should have probably found this
by now, right?
Like you all don't even understand where to go either.
Okay, so like there's only one way I can go, right?
There's this way and then there's that way.
So I'm gonna go, I guess that way.
You should just give up.
I've been kind of about to.
Everybody gave shit to like Fable 2
when they added the breadcrumb trail
to the bottom of the screen.
But like, let's be real.
What the fuck am I even doing right now?
Like I can't see anything.
How am I supposed to find anything in this game?
There's apparently a bridge with a railroad somewhere
that I was already here.
Return to the, I gotta read this, I gotta read this.
Return to the road connecting the tree and the bunker.
There, play the videotape that you found
and pause it when the ball lies on the ground.
This way, I already did that!
This way it'll appear next to you.
Pick it up and let your companion sniff it.
He'll pick up the trail immediately, follow the dog,
you'll reach an abandoned small gauge train.
There's a, what?
He won't sniff the ball anymore.
I just did that.
He did.
Remember he smelled it?
The game is softlocked now?
Okay, I'm gonna tell the dog to search if that works,
I swear.
Pissed.
I'm gonna be, I'm gonna be pissed
if I have to just tell him to go search.
I'm gonna be pissed.
Are you ready for me to get really mad?
Here we go.
Go back to the truck, okay?
We're at the truck again.
What are you finding?
Find it, go on.
Okay, we're going over here.
If he runs me in a circle, I'm refinding the game.
If we go back to where we just were
and he like barks and lays down
and takes his shit on the ground,
I'm refining the game.
Where is he?
I, okay, I was here before.
This is all the way back.
This is, remember the little, hey!
There, there's a stupid thing.
Okay, I found, oh, there it is.
There it is.
The dog just had to go find it.
I'm walking around like an asshole with six senses
and I got a super powered animal that has 12.
I have to use the super powered dog
that goes and finds everything.
I didn't, okay, all right, fine.
So I'm the asshole, okay?
I'm an asshole.
I talked a lot of shit about the game.
Let's be very clear.
I'm still very upset, but pull out the dumbass webcam
and let's see what happens to this truck.
Okay, now what?
Okay, we can go.
We can just walk through.
You don't understand, it's blurry.
It's blurry, it's dark.
It's not calibrated correctly.
Look, you have to do this like, go.
You find it.
Look around boy, hell.
Maybe we can see.
God damn it.
We were so close.
Go ahead.
I just spent, how long was that?
Like an hour walking in a circle
and I have a dog that I didn't even use.
Fuck.
I saw it on my way here.
I could get there in a few minutes.
God damn it.
Just stay where you are, okay?
I'm walking around like smelling the ball,
like sniffing the trees and shit.
And he just is, he is the thing that I described.
He is the Fable II breadcrumb trail.
I just didn't use it.
That's my fault.
I will take that L.
That's my loss.
But I'm gonna be very honest with you.
Just tell me where to go dog.
Just show me where to go.
No, I'm not gonna ask where I'm supposed to go now.
I know exactly where I need to go.
Follow the dog in the pitch black video game.
And I sound very upset.
You know what you can hear when you're like,
just like really like upset about something?
I can't believe I walked around.
Here's the thing.
Let me tell you, some of you guys,
where was the backseat Andes saying,
tell the dog to seek?
You guys are telling me like,
oh, go to the back of the truck, turn left,
take 10 paces forward, stop, look at your watch,
back up four paces, turn right, look up to the sky.
No, not one of you said, dude, have the dog help me.
Not one single person.
It took an hour and a half.
I can't believe it took that long.
Okay, let's all relax.
Let's chill.
I'm about to, we're doing progression here.
Well, the problem is Jeremy,
you're not facing due Southwest.
No, this can't happen.
You've got to, I need you.
Here, see if you can find something, buddy.
Go tell me where to go, please.
Oh man, this has been a wacky day of VR.
I feel like I've been angry,
like 35% of the time I've been on this stream right now.
That's a record.
You shouldn't have trusted us.
Well, I was trying to trust you guys
because you were trying to help.
You really were.
I don't have a, what do you mean call?
I don't have a signal.
Bullet.
Ellis to base.
Landing, where are you?
So am I.
That's the one.
Hey, don't talk to me like I'm crazy.
Who are you, Emmett?
I don't need your help.
No, it's you who needs me.
Now, I'm the only person in this goddamn forest
who is even remotely close to finding that kid.
You there?
Emmett.
God damn it.
What the fuck?
Hey, who is it?
Who is it?
I'll tell you, Ricky.
I'm gonna be real sure as hell pissed off.
Ah!
What is it?
What happened?
Who is it?
What was that?
Was it the dog just biting?
What the fuck was that?
There's no monster.
It's just like a weird guy
running around on his fucking hind legs.
Holy shit.
Come on, boy.
Let's go.
Watch out.
Watch out for the little gremlin guy.
Is this a truck?
Wait, isn't it?
This is a Jurassic Park truck.
All right, let's go.
Open the fucking door.
What?
What do you mean it's called landing?
Nigga!
What?
Why is this happening?
I don't think this should be happening.
What is happening?
Get in the truck.
Bobby, get in the truck.
Oh my God, what is this thing?
We gotta go, we gotta go, we gotta go.
We gotta go, down here.
Follow me, follow me, come on.
I'm gonna go in that room.
I'm gonna close the door.
Hurry, hurry, hurry, hurry.
Down, down, down, down, down, down, down.
Hey!
Eat shit.
Wait, my dog.
What?
He's not in the room, right?
Oh shit.
Is he here?
I think he's behind this door.
He's right here.
Where is he?
Hey, hey, hey.
I don't know, I thought he was doing the thing
that little kids do when you play hide and seek
when they hide like right behind the door.
Don't do that to me, bullet.
The game just got 100,000 times better.
You tried to take so long to get here.
This is awesome.
Oh my God.
Holy shit in my fucking pants.
Where's that truck?
Jesus, man.
Where's the truck, where's the truck, where's the truck?
Where's the truck, right here, right?
So what the hell's going on?
How do I get out of here?
Yeah, okay, there's something here.
What does it say?
Chapter three, say the light.
The light!
Do I have to shine it on him?
Use the camera?
Where is he?
Okay, all right, okay, just get him on camera.
Get him on camera.
Get his ass on camera, get his ass on camera.
Get him on camera, get him on camera.
I hit it, where is he?
What is he calling me, hello?
The message, but there's no reception.
Think of getting used to things that make no damn sense.
Moving is always better than standing.
Those who don't move have 99% higher chance of dying.
Better start walking.
Okay, all right, now let's get to that truck.
The game now, it just got good, and I'm exhausted now.
I think I wanna play this again.
No, but VR, I can't do any more VR.
Maybe when Among Us comes out.
I gotta go back to other games.
I can't just be VR Andy permanently.
Come here, boy, boy, search.
All right, put the camera away.
Let me at least get to the save point.
Yes, you can.
No, I really can't though.
After I do a VR stream,
for like three days after I do it, I'm like locked up.
Okay, let's get there.
More of this game, please.
Okay, I talked a bunch of shit about this game.
I was unfair.
That little weird super fast gremlin guy
was actually pretty pog, pretty pog.
I was just walking in circles for like 40.
Are there more than like 100 people still watching me?
Considering I walked in a circle
for like 40 minutes straight.
Jesus.
That's it, okay.
The light.
Hey, can I get that?
What is that?
I can't reach that.
All right, okay, that's it.
That's it.
I'm gonna call it here.
There's only 10 viewers.
Yeah, there was 16,000.
There's I think 4,000 people left
in the walk around the forest in a circle part.
All right, so here's what's gonna happen.
I will see you guys on,
I'll see you guys on Saturday.
Saturday, Sunday, this weekend.
Sunday, Ster and I are gonna play Dying Light 2.
Saturday, I don't know, maybe we'll just like hang out.
Maybe I'll do like tier list or something.
Maybe we'll do some just chatting on Saturday.
That's fun.
I had fun.
Unfortunately, some, you know, whatever.
I'm not gonna go on a VR ramp,
but I'll give you a face reveal.
Hold on one sec.
How are we?
All right, I will see you guys.
Thanks for staying up if you stayed up.
The streams coming up here on the weekend
are not gonna be at four.
They're gonna be at two.
2 p.m. Pacific.
We're going back to the 2 p.m. schedule here.
Thanks for watching everybody.
Thanks to all the new subs as well.
And the old ones, as always.
There were 100 gifted subs, oh my God.
Yeah, there's some interesting stuff going on,
especially in like March, April.
Once we get, when I sit down at my desk on Saturday,
we'll go over a bunch of cool stuff.
Baseball's gonna happen probably in March, April.
And I'm really very interested in the,
in Cutie Cinderella's streamer awards.
You guys haven't taken a look at that.
Probably gonna be a really, really cool event.
I think that's happening in March too.
Yeah, Cutie's putting together a show
to do like a streamer awards thing.
There's a bunch of categories, like 28 categories I think.
I voted, I voted.
Yeah, I'll talk, we'll talk more about it this weekend.
I think you can nominate up until through the 13th.
What about the direct tomorrow?
I'm not doing the direct tomorrow.
The Nintendo directs are usually only like an hour long.
100 community subs from,
I don't see 100 community subs, what are you talking about?
I don't see 100 community subs.
I see, I see 10 community subs from fat guy on a bus.
Oh, IOU, right, that's okay, right, right, right.
I see, I apologize, I forgot.
That was like five hours ago.
Hey, thanks fat guy on a bus.
I appreciate the 10 subs though.
All right, I'm gonna do it now.
I'll do, what was it, 100?
Hey, should be seeing them any moment now.
And here it comes, okay.
Oh shit, I have to put all of my information back in.
God damn it.
All right, I need to, I need my like wallet.
Do they go through when the stream is offline?
They do, right?
Yeah, all right, all right.
Stick around, I need to like get my credit card and stuff.
I gotta go find my wallet.
I'm not, no, I swear to God,
it'll be there within five minutes.
Because I like redid some stuff on Twitch.
I have to like put all my info back in.
I used to be saved, but not anymore.
Just run ads right now.
Ad break time, but that's so, okay.
You wanna run ads, fine, let's run a few ads.
Give me a minute, let me close out of a few things.
All right, stick around, I'll be right back.
Give me a minute, hold on.
One sec.
Did it go through?
Go through, what?
Did that go through?
My payment couldn't go through?
Wait, what?
Hold on, wait, what the fuck?
Oh God, give me a second.
What the fuck, hold on.
Did I put my card in wrong?
One sec, dude, I can't do this.
I keep getting, unexpected error has occurred.
What?
Literally scammed, yeah, I can't do it.
I don't know why it won't go through.
He's broke?
That's weird.
I don't know why my card's getting declined.
Okay, so I gotta kind of figure out why that's happening.
Let me try something else, one sec.
I'm gonna try one more time with,
let me try something else, I'll be right back.
Dude, that didn't work either.
I don't, I think, is there something wrong with Twitch?
Cause I can't, I tried two, three different payment methods
now, I think something's wrong.
I have no idea.
We're gonna have to save this and hold on to this, I think,
cause I've tried all the payment methods,
I don't know what's going on.
How convenient.
I've never backed away from a sub, a gift sub,
you all know that.
No, but I mean previously, in previous time.
Hold on to it, next stream, I will do it.
I gotta figure out why all my payment methods
are getting just dropped.
Purchase could not be completed.
I don't understand why.
I don't have like a text or anything from like a bank.
No, nothing, this won't go through.
But we're gonna have to do it next stream.
I gotta figure this out.
Sorry, that was supposed to happen, I just tried.
On Saturday, please remind me.
And we'll see you again.
Take care, everybody.
Have a great rest of your evening.
And see you guys soon.
Now, cause I gotta figure out if that's happening
on other services, I gotta figure that out.
Turn off my VPN, my VPN's not on.
I have turned it off before I tried to do it,
so don't worry.
Remind me on Saturday, I'll see you guys soon.
Take care of yourselves.
Thanks for watching, as always.
And I'll see you again.
Goodnight, guys.