Are you even going to give them five seconds to watch the intro?
No, I can watch. Do you have an intro?
Yeah, I have like little the solar system thing.
Oh.
Do you not have an intro? Do you stream?
I mean, I have a starting soon screen like yours.
I thought you meant like an intro, like an actual like animated like intro
that some people have like.
Oh, no, no.
Like a special thing.
No, I just mean the starting soon screen.
No, I have a fantastic one that would make anyone jealous.
You got a pretty good one, don't you?
Yeah, I do.
I actually I have a streaming question for you.
How long in minutes when you hit the go live button on your OBS, you press the button.
When do you like when does your stream start?
OK, I'm here. I'm talking and now we're going to do the thing.
How many minutes go by?
Wait, wait, wait.
From start of the stream to start of playing the game.
Like you press the start streaming until you talking like you're here.
Until you talk.
Right.
OK, I have this really weird issue where I'll turn on my stream
and the moment my stream goes on, I remember like three or four things that I wanted to do.
Yeah.
And then I do them.
OK.
And they are they are totally unrelated to the stream.
Like I can't even remember what it was.
One day I turned on my stream and I was like, oh, wait, yeah, I got to go get the hammer.
And like, dude, like and I just started like setting up some.
I have no.
Wait, you were setting up like a DIY project.
I don't know.
I can't remember.
I just know that when the stream goes on, I instantly into my brain is like.
Hold on.
Now would be a great time to do this thing you had not thought of in a week.
It's weird how that happens.
Your brain just kind of goes, yeah, do this thing.
There's no other opportunity for you to do it.
So it depends if I'm doing a DIY project.
Or people seem like five minutes Monday.
Monday is tomorrow.
Hey, what's today?
I thought today was Monday.
Today's Monday.
Oh, bro, today's Sunday.
I went to work and everything.
I showed I showed up at the office and nobody was going on clocked in.
Everyone was looking at me.
Yes, we are pretending we're aware we're a little early.
I but we meant Monday in Australia.
I think that we didn't get that point across Monday in Australia.
So sorry, we forgot to add that part to the end of the stream yesterday.
Here's the tangent.
OK, so you go off on your tangent before we get started.
We finished streaming yesterday.
Yeah.
Yesterday was rough.
We were jumping over the lava.
There was a millennia.
There was a lot of issues yesterday, to be honest.
Sure.
I think it was full of issues.
Barely a minute went by after the stream ended and Strippen messaged me on Discord.
He said, yo, great stream, man.
It's really refreshing.
You watch watching.
You suck at ass at a game looking forward to the next one.
Soul crushing.
So today we got to do better and be better.
No, no, no, no, no, no, enjoy it.
So your goal today is to make sure that Strippen does not enjoy the stream.
I want him to be bored out of his fucking mind watching my stream.
I want him to be like, God, he was actually good.
He was just holding back.
But isn't it?
Hold on.
But isn't it more fun?
We just kind of don't care.
Isn't it more fun that way?
Do we?
We don't have a look.
I got really mad last night.
That's how you feel.
Why did you care so much fighting millennia?
Well, because because I hate millennia.
OK, I hate millennia.
There's a difference.
It's the only time during that.
OK, how many randomized streams have we done?
This would be the fourth one.
This would be this would be number four stream number four.
I'm sorry.
But if I roll up and somebody I don't like is there, I'm I'm going to I don't want to.
I don't want to be there.
I want to go somewhere else.
That's what we should have done.
But you went into gamer mode when you walk in the door and you say it's millennia.
We should have been like, oh, well, we can go anywhere else.
But remember, we didn't have the key and the rune.
We got really lucky at the last 20 minutes of stream last night
because we went somewhere else.
We didn't get lucky.
We did what we should have done like hours prior.
Yeah. But all right.
So why did you keep going in the fog door then?
I wanted to beat her.
Right.
Because yeah, it's like, oh, you walked away, dude.
Yeah.
No, it's a strong force.
Do you know how many times I was seriously we were walking in the fog door
and I'm like, let's just fuck this.
Let's do something else.
I mean, I did.
And it doesn't matter.
Yep.
You talked me out of summons.
I would rather abandon ship and go do something else than like
walk into millennia's room with like a squad of guys.
Why?
There's just something wrong there.
You would rather not beat the thing and then beat the thing.
That's so funny.
There's a full circle of weird like this is going to.
I'm thinking of this explanation is worth it.
Okay.
Because I was just talking about it.
Actually, there's this show on Netflix that just came out a couple days ago
called like Physique 100 or something where it's like all of like the top bodybuilders
and like Olympic gold winners in Korea are doing like squid, squid game style,
like strength tests to like find the perfect body.
Like it's a real competition.
What?
Yeah.
So they got like 100 people all super fit and they're doing like just,
you know, like a fitness competition basically, but it's all dubbed.
Also, it's hilariously dubbed.
I was laughing nonstop.
The shit that they say and the voice actors are like so not into it and don't have context.
Hilarious the whole way through.
Okay.
But spoiler alert for the Physique 100.
Spoiler alert.
Wait, wait, wait.
Don't spoil.
Okay.
Before you do this, should I just like mute you?
Because like or leave?
Should I take that in my head?
Because it sounds like kind of I might want to watch this.
So you have to spoil the show.
There's only two episodes out so far.
It's not all out.
All right.
So it's not kind of a minor spoiler.
I thought you meant like, oh, this is like a 10 episode, 20 episodes.
And this is like the last.
No, I'm not going to like the people like the first real competition that matters.
The winners from like the first thing get to like choose who their opponent is.
So they've got 100 people.
And then there's like, you know, a bunch of like super fucking buff guys.
And then there's also women in the competition.
And it's like a wrestling competition basically.
And they can just fucking pick women.
And it's really fucked up.
And my wife is like, why is this allowed?
And then there's one guy that's like, yeah, I'm going to I'm going to I'm going to wrestle that woman.
And everyone's like, what the fuck?
So what I'm saying is you can choose to walk into Melania's room with a squad of goons.
But come on, man, like you really shouldn't be like everyone else.
There has like a level of decency where they didn't go there.
All right.
Well, here they can like fair opponents to look good.
Here's but here's the problem with your argument on this.
Melania is fucking unstoppable.
I beat her in my run.
But the point to your point is Melania will wipe the floor with a hundred of us.
That's not true.
Is it?
You're gonna play guilty gear right now.
Oh, yes.
Let's do guilty gear.
Dude, it could be that could be it could be doesn't matter.
It could be like a bug.
It could be a single insect, a single ant in that room.
If it is an insanely difficult, strong enemy, what do you think we're going to get our ass kicked?
Regardless doesn't matter.
But then you're going to look twice as bad.
If the single ant has the waterfowl move, which doesn't matter.
We we were we were dodging it.
You know, we were we were getting there.
Real life isn't video games.
A single.
Why are summons in the game in all caps?
I understand.
I understand your point.
But when you play Elden Ring, it's not in front of an audience that like,
you know, it's a different scenario.
Like, yeah, would I wrestle with a girl in the mud?
Sure.
But on TV, when I can choose muscular men.
What the fuck is he talking about?
What is he talking about?
What what what is he going on?
What is what is he?
What is happening?
Right.
What is he saying?
You have to see the show.
OK, what is he saying?
So this is this is like directly tied to this show on Netflix.
Yeah.
OK, so we saying is I have to see this show.
Well, yeah.
And then you would agree that you shouldn't mud wrestle with women.
Only muscular men.
I I don't even know what the context of what you're.
I need to see the show at some point.
Yeah.
All right.
Are you ready to fucking smoke a blunt with Placidusix or what?
I don't have that mod.
You said you'd be back Monday.
You're liars.
Well, look, I I was asleep last night and I woke up in the middle of the night
and I had just like I had like laser eyes like I was like, we got to beat it.
I can't wait.
I just was like, hey, sir, you're not doing side content.
We're going or what are we doing?
No, we're just doing what we want.
OK, OK.
I thought the laser eyes meant like we have to continue
fucking smash smashing our head against millennia.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
I never want to go.
If there's a bazooka mod and we can install it and we can just shoot a bazooka at her
and it's like 5000 damage, we'll do that.
OK, I'm sure someone has made that.
All right. You good?
Are we good to get started?
Are you in the game?
Yeah, I'm loading up the game.
I'm loading up the game.
I'm continuing.
You already made that joke.
I made that joke in free stream.
I'm sorry, but it was like it was like not a joke.
There were like 15 people that were there.
He's not joking.
Guys, I use pre stream is kind of like, oh, was this funny?
Because they go, ha ha ha.
And then I'm like, I got it.
I'm going to use that on the stream.
How lame would that be if you went to like a stand up comics like show
and they're doing a show before people get in the room
and then they just do the show again that that's called rehearsal.
Yeah, that's dress rehearsal.
Okay, they do that on like every major television show.
How lame would it be if like you pay all you go to New York City
and they're like doing a like theater and they're doing they've like rehearsed for it.
Can't they just like can't they just come out and do it?
Hey, I've never been to a taping of SNL,
but I'm pretty sure that they do dress rehearsal on SNL before they go live.
So they actually I think they do that on SNL.
So it's all fake.
Sorry.
No, this is it's all fake.
But SNL sucks.
I didn't say I watched it.
You got your thing done?
Yeah, hold on.
My controller not working.
What the heck?
Oh, you might say sorry.
My left bumper is not doing anything.
I can't I can't block.
Plug it in, plug it in, plug it in, unplug it in.
I'm plugging, unplugging.
Yeah, okay.
I just looked at this and at some point in our rage yesterday,
I changed weapons to the pizza cutter.
I'm like, where is my fire sword?
Where did that go?
I'm looking at this going, why do I have this equipped?
And I'm like, wait, that's right.
I've rage respect to fight millennia.
This thing's still fine.
Did you break it?
I don't know.
It's only one button, dude.
SNL is funny.
You and Chad are not as funny and jealous crying.
I haven't watched an episode of SNL in at least five to ten years.
I've never watched one.
You know, I think it's really funny though,
is that like news websites will report on what happened on SNL.
Like it's new.
Really?
Yeah, like SNL's take on like this political situation.
Did you see it last night?
It's like, fuck you.
Do some journalism.
Fuck you.
That's, that's, you know, that's so funny because it's like,
I feel like like reporting on something that was already reported,
that was reported through like a satire kind of website or something.
That kind of happens too, doesn't it?
It's like, don't people eat the onion all the time?
Oh yeah, they do eat the onion.
People do news reports on tweets.
Yeah, I remember the first time I did see like,
they used the tweet and they were talking about it on like a news piece.
And I was like, what the hell is going on?
Nothing that happens on Twitter is real.
It's all made up.
Are you joining?
I didn't know.
I thought you said you were, I thought you're having controller problems.
No, I mean, I'm in the game.
I can live with it.
It's just the block button.
You're not allowed to even actually like block anything in this game.
I mean, millennia would destroy me because I did surgery on a grape, bro.
What?
I'm going to look in my closet for my bonus controller.
Where did I end?
Oh, there you are.
All right, so let's give a recap.
We just got a huge raid from RT.
RT Game, what's up?
What's going on, RT?
Hope everything's going well.
Hope you had a good stream.
RT is awesome.
You don't follow RT.
What are you dumb?
What was RT doing?
What were you doing, RT?
Persona?
Persona 5.
Cool.
Join us in following RT Game.
Wait, what?
This is like a new feature.
You could, wait, what is that?
This is a new feature where you could like,
that's kind of cool.
I didn't know you could do that.
It's cool.
Whoa, that's actually really cool.
Sir, do you like the Persona games?
I feel like you might be one of those Persona fans.
You just call me a fucking weeb?
No, it's supposed to have to be very compelling characters
and gameplay and story.
And it's one of the most celebrated RPG franchises in history.
I can't say that I've played any game
that takes you like 400 hours to beat.
And you could have just said no.
Jermis getting defensive.
Uh-oh.
I just wanted to alienate probably like,
you know, like 50% of the people listening.
I have to, let me be really honest, though.
I have to, let's put all the cards on this table.
I have opened every Persona game that's come to Game Pass.
Game Pass again.
And after like 30 or 40 minutes, I just kind of close it.
Every single one of them.
It's not that I don't like it.
I'm just like...
Yeah, I don't like it.
I can say that.
I'm not on contract with the Persona devs.
I played the fighting game,
Persona 4 Arena, I like that game.
All right.
So here's what's happening.
It's been 15 minutes.
We had our relaxing session.
Oh, so you have a limit of 15.
That's why you asked earlier.
So you could set a limit.
Um, what?
No more, no more talking.
All right.
Listen to me very carefully.
You like literally just brought,
you brought up the topic.
Do you like Arena, like a Persona 4?
And then I got...
You got very angry.
We didn't get, we didn't even get to talk about it really in depth.
And then you cut it off and you're like, fine.
He didn't like it.
So like, we're not talking, we're not talking.
Oh, dude, you can't convince me to like Persona.
That was, that was that scenario.
Dude, bro, you're not going to be able to convince me to like Persona.
I said, hey, do you like the Persona?
I don't like JRPGs, man.
Like, Final Fantasy?
I, I can't.
Yeah, but so, I'm going to keep the conversation going.
Here, new conversation.
If you had to pick any genre of game that you would just be like,
incapable of enjoying.
Yeah.
What is it for you?
Strategy games.
Like, like, stuff like Crusader Kings.
Oh, gosh.
I just couldn't.
Oh, my goodness.
I couldn't play it.
I feel like I used to be like that, even with like StarCraft.
Well, RTS is different, I think.
But like, I mean, like true, like strategy games.
I just, there's just too much for me.
I just, they don't bore me.
They just overwhelm me.
Okay.
So we have the Manor key and we have two runes.
All right, let's go to the Manor.
You want, we can actually...
We can actually go into the room now.
Yeah, let's go to the room.
What's your favorite JRPG?
Uh, Chrono Trigger.
Did you play Chrono Trigger?
Nope.
You should.
You really should.
Everybody should.
Everyone.
That should be required rating to own a console or like a PC.
You should have to do your homework.
You should have to prove that you played it before you get like a console.
It should literally, when you turn, you know, when you turn on your Xbox,
it's like, welcome to Xbox.
Set it up.
What's your name?
And what's your date of birth?
Before that, it should, the Chrono Trigger splash screen intro should lie.
No, no, no.
Like it's just baked into every console.
Like you have, it's like, here it is.
Like Chrono Trigger, the and you have to play through the whole game
before you can even make your account on Xbox.
Even if you've already played it before.
How would you prove that?
I don't know.
It could like ask you a trivia question.
Oh yeah.
But no, you could, you could look it up though.
I mean, somebody said, why are you gatekeeping an entire generation?
We just dropped the new halo and we're so excited for you to try it.
Make sure you guys finish Chrono Trigger soon.
Yeah.
Want to be trying it.
The new Xbox just dropped, but make sure you get,
make sure you start playing Chrono Trigger.
It's going to take you at least 20 to 40 hours.
Now this is no, what is here?
There's nothing here.
Are we still fucked?
Don't we need an invitation or something?
No, no, no, no.
There's a, there's a secret.
Oh, okay.
The secret.
Yep.
See the door in the back.
I just got the Elden Lord helmet.
What is this?
Wait, is there anything?
I don't, I don't remember.
Hold on.
No, I know where it is.
Is there, this is where everybody hangs out,
where you do the, uh, the missions and stuff.
It's like here.
Right now.
Guys, which room is it?
It's the room with the, with the girl.
This one here.
Oh, their room.
Wrong room.
I just want to open both of these.
Oh, their room.
You know what the, the, the thing about Millennia is?
Cause I was, I was remembering last night.
Yeah.
That millennia is in like the secret area
of like the frost world.
Right.
That's hard to get to.
And then she's in the secret or secret Hallig tree
that I don't even remember how you like,
doesn't she have to do some weird shit to get there?
Yeah.
I mean, it's a, it's a, it's an optional secret area.
It is.
Yeah.
And then her whole area sucks.
And then you get down there and then it's like, okay.
Mal, like she deserves to suck.
I, I did not hate the Hallig tree area.
You didn't like, you, you like really didn't like the area.
I didn't, I didn't hate it.
I would watch out though.
I skipped the whole area.
You mean like, like you skipped it as
and you've never played it or you like jumped off
like a ledge and landed like all the way at the bottom or something.
I did that.
Okay.
There was the elevator skip.
So I didn't play most of it.
And then I went back and I was like, you know,
I'm curious what's in the Hallig tree.
Like I want to play it like for real.
And I fucking hated it.
I'm sorry.
I can't hear anything you're saying.
We're just cutting the weeds down.
Ah, this is a big job.
This is going to cost a little extra.
I, uh, I can't, uh, I can't, I can't cast magic
because I can't press my bumper.
What did you do to your controller?
Give me, it's just one button.
Give me a second.
I have like an old Xbox 360 controller.
I got to plug it in old Xbox 360 and not an Xbox one controller.
Oh, no, it has.
Well, I was on an Xbox one controller.
This thing has the fucking the weird cable in the middle
that isn't a USB, but it connects to the cable that I've.
I mean, like you go ahead.
I'm dying to poison.
I, I know where I'm going.
I'm clear.
Okay, don't worry.
It's all good.
Don't worry.
We're good.
How's everybody doing tonight?
Good.
Everybody doing okay?
How you been?
You're okay?
Hope you're doing all right.
Stirr, there's blood on the ground.
So you mentioned before that you don't like JRPGs.
Is there a particular reason as to why?
Is it too slow?
Is it like Stirr wants to go fast?
I'm like walking around my room.
Are you talking to me?
Oh, sorry.
No, no, no.
Keep doing that.
Keep like wireless.
I don't think I have another controller.
I'm going to die.
Well, I really ruined that.
Sorry, chat.
I got his attention and he came back over.
We were trying to we were trying to see if you were going to die.
No, I was just trying to keep you talking.
I figured we would keep you distracted and you just lead the poison river.
You found out that you were walking around your room.
Yeah, so you don't have another controller.
No, I would need the extra part of the cable for the other one.
Is it a case of is it like jammed up or something?
I don't know.
I'm using it as hard as I can.
I'm doing tapping.
It's just my left bumper bumper.
You could block button.
Theoretically, you could make left trigger cast and you could do like left stick.
Could be walk.
Does that sound stupid?
Because there's literally there's not a single reason to crouch in this game.
There's not one single reason to crouch.
You can just rebind in this game, right?
Yeah, like individual buttons.
And if you're going to get rid of crouch versus be able to use your shield,
I think that's the best place to put it.
What about crouch attack?
For some weapons, yeah.
Anything else?
Okay, that was like a that was like a GTA four video we made and like somebody just
got hit by the car.
Okay, so I went to go rebind my controls.
So I rebound like you said to the stick and then I went back up to crouch and it's like,
oh, you have to like change this.
It's red.
So I press left bumper to change it and it worked.
There you go.
Why isn't it working in the game?
Wait, it doesn't work.
It only works on the menu.
Yeah, it will not work in the game.
I think I should like restart my game.
All right, let's let's just like get to a bonfire and then I'm going to restart.
That's that's very weird.
Yeah, that's weird.
All right, this doesn't open.
So what I forget what you end up you go like deeper, don't you or something?
There's like a secret wall somewhere again.
This was another area.
That's like, why would they like hide?
Change wand hands.
Someone's saying, hey, change wand hands.
I have a shield in my hand.
I just switched weapons and it just started like I already had the button down.
I was well, that person should be should be commended for that.
Because I'm going to reinstall Windows.
Just we need to find like a grace to rest up.
Oh, it's over here.
Yeah.
All right, guys, I got to reinstall Windows.
The forums were saying this doesn't happen on Linux because like a Gabe Newell alt account.
Dude, what is that thing?
Chat chat.
What is that chat?
Chat, what is that?
Oh, it's just one of those silent things.
There we go.
Banishing you because I don't think it lets me quit the game until I banish you.
Go ahead.
I restarting and I'm holding up.
I'm holding everything up and it's all my fault that we're late again.
No, that's not true.
Yeah.
In the menu.
I could if we're totally fine.
Oh, just just reset the whole client.
I'm just going to go right back there.
I forget where that is here.
Stir.
You have a great room.
Go to Landale.
We're going to kill fucking right card.
Yeah, we're going to kill right card.
Do you like radishes?
Um, I can't remember.
I feel like I've had pickled radishes as like part of some Korean meal.
No.
And I'm like, okay.
Uh, I actually prefer them.
Just just I don't know if I like washed just are you like is this like a Doug funny moment?
We're going back to that again.
Like you just eat beats like raw.
You just like grab a beat and take a chomp out.
I wish I liked beats.
I wish I liked to eat beats like that.
They're they're unbelievably that is like the most powerful super food in existence is a beat.
But I think they disgusting.
I think they just taste like dirt.
Yeah, I I have no mental association with what a radish tastes like.
Uh, they're kind of they're super crunchy.
And when you bite into them, you get that kind of nasal heat.
They're kind of spicy.
Like you get that up here like in the top of your nose.
I've opened my world.
I can't relate.
You don't want to eat a shitload of them.
Like wasabi.
It's a little less harsh than wasabi.
I would say a lot less harsh than wasabi.
My intestinal parasites.
I'm good.
I I stared death in the eye and I won.
You know, it's really annoying about that conversation yesterday and about how
that whole thing played out.
I had diarrhea this morning and it was just like my dog.
I was just sitting there going fuck that guy.
What the fuck?
It's not fair.
That's what I'm saying.
I got away with it.
I was sitting there just being like, you got to be kidding me.
This guy eats raw pork that's been in a backpack for a day and like, oh,
my tummy is upset this morning.
I was like, what the fuck, man?
Oh, yeah, that's the millennia shortcut.
There it is.
Yeah.
Now the door people were telling us to open for like hours yesterday,
but we didn't have the key to do it.
We didn't have the key to do it.
But now we need to how do we get to right?
We have to do the invitation shit to do right card, don't we?
Here.
There's one way.
If you're an actual god.
No, you can get teleported down there.
This jump.
There's a teleporter that takes you down there.
For one second, for one second, I thought your connection dropped
and that was the last sound you made before you got kicked from the discord.
I thought you were like, ah, like, what the fuck?
Like you were like, ah, and it was like, ah, it froze.
I thought you froze and you were just got booted and you've lagged out.
No, I.
What's the jump?
How do you do it?
You have to get up on top of this thing.
And then you see where that like that ledge up there,
they patch this.
So this is really hard to do, but you can jump from the top of this thing
up to that ledge and then right cards like right up there.
I think VR Josh, that was a great moment.
Stirred tabbed out of a source engine game.
All right.
So you jump from here to up there.
Okay.
But I think you have to like be running on that.
So you have to like run in a circle, which is why.
Bro got it first try.
Where are we going from here?
That's not the hard part.
Oh, now we're to get on top of the metal circle.
And then you have to be able to jump to the ledge.
He's killing it tonight.
Now guide me a little more.
Uh, I forget exactly what you're aiming for, but you need to like land
like on the ledge so you can get up to that high ground.
Oh, yeah, that's that's the chat saying it's almost impossible.
It is possible.
Dude, I we have switched bodies.
I don't fucking just wait, just wait.
I'll get it.
Stripping is eating right now.
Okay.
What is that?
Stripping is eating right now.
Like he's like, I was trying to be better so he wouldn't enjoy me being bad.
And I've jumped off the map twice in like 10 minutes of gameplay.
So right now, Stripping, you tell him, Stripping just took a big bite out of
like a fucking steak and cheese, whatever he's eating.
He's probably just like, he's like laughing and like food just came out of his mouth.
Yeah, we're not going to.
I don't want to sit around and do this jump.
It's you're not getting it.
Is it actually patched up?
It's patched.
It is patched, but it is possible, but it's incredibly incredible.
Okay.
So the number one question is, here's our two options.
Let's go fight Melania.
No, no, no, there are there.
There's a way to get down to that.
No, no, there's a way to get down to Rikard.
You get ported there without having to do anything.
I know it.
I've done it accidentally before.
How do you get down to that room?
The one right before Rikard?
There's a way to get down there.
It's part of a quest.
You can't do the quest.
Okay.
The envelopes.
Okay, let's go kill Melania.
Fine.
All right.
My God, dude.
We're doing this.
We're attempting this one time.
And then we are.
I'm telling you right now.
I am immediately porting to one millennia fight, one millennia fight.
And then we are.
And I'm talking about we are.
I'm porting to outside of Landell.
Yeah, we're gonna go do land.
You understand the terms here, right?
Yeah.
You get the terms?
Yes.
Also, do I have a way to turn in the other?
I got Mogues room.
Do we have the tower so we can go to the top?
I forget which one is Mogues.
Let's head away.
Because I know we have access to one more tower.
Everybody's saying like, how do they not know this?
You guys have to understand.
You have to remember.
There was like an entire human history worth of stuff in this game.
It's like an entire human history with like lore books and like thousands of pieces of documents.
It's a lot.
So we don't remember.
Come on, bring it on.
Okay.
Be careful.
Pretty clean.
Not bad.
Pretty good.
Not good.
A little cautious.
That's why.
Dude, her fight should be in a room with pillars.
Actually, kind of should be.
Actual fight.
Oh, fuck.
That was the worst time.
Just hit her.
Dude, I can't.
Just press the attack button once, dude.
What's the problem?
Dude, you're not allowed to play this video game against this character with a weapon
that's less than like a tenth of a second swing time.
I'm not supposed to come in here with a dagger.
You can't attack Millenia with a weapon that is like a two-handed sprinkler.
You just can't.
If I hit R1, I die.
I die if I hit R1.
Let me hit R1.
Dead.
There's no opportunity, man.
They give you enough opportunity to swing with a katana.
They made that character for katanas only.
Hey, don't you have a moon veil you were going to give me?
I did, didn't I?
Yeah.
Jump attack if it takes too long.
No, you should jump attack.
And don't you have like multiple fully upgraded two-handers?
Because two-hand, like they nerfed it a bit, but dual wielding two-handers
and doing jump attacks on her is actually like pretty good.
And then I have a claw talisman for bonus on jump attack.
Let's do it again.
Okay.
Are we changing anything?
No, I got it.
Want the talisman?
Are you going to give me the moon veil?
I got the jump attack.
Didn't I give you the moon?
Oh, I thought I gave it to you.
Did you?
Yeah.
Wasn't I like, oh, look, look, look.
And you're like, oh, yeah, yeah.
I think I told you not to give it to me.
How come I don't?
Did I sell it?
Oh, no, I have it.
Okay.
Well, it's like not upgraded.
Wait, moon veil has bleed on it?
I think so, yeah.
Why?
That's why it's easy mode.
All right.
I knew it had bleed.
No, let's get out of here.
I'm getting out of here.
How do I get out of here quick?
All right.
I'm just somber five.
I went to Capitol Rampart.
Go.
Do you have a somber five?
Yeah.
No, we're fighting her one more time.
No, no, no.
Do it now.
No.
Get out.
Get me out of here.
All right.
Okay.
We just lost it.
I was like, yeah, fucking this, fucking that.
I'm fucking this, fucking that.
No, no, no.
Get me out of here.
We just need some levels.
No, get me out of here.
It's somber five.
I'll give you a somber five.
Get me out of here.
There's no way.
There's no way we're going to sit there
for like another two hours where I just continue.
Every time we lose, I'm going to pull.
Here's what I'm going to do.
I'm going to say exactly what's going to happen.
I'm going to grab this.
This is coming up here.
And I'm going to talk like this really, really angrily.
Like, I'm very, this is, look at how intent this is.
Somber five.
Somber five, daddy.
Daddy, somber five.
Listen to me.
How many do you just want?
Just one.
Do you have an eight?
An eight and an ancient.
I have an eight.
I do not have an ancient.
Give me the eight.
You've taken all these from me.
I've given you like so much.
Yeah, but these are so much more valuable and you've taken them.
We, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we, we.
Let's go to the road of the manor real quick.
Okay.
Are you doing, are you upgrading Moonville?
Yeah.
No, I don't like this arc.
You don't like this arc?
I've been using a fucking long sword all game.
You have gone through like six weapons.
You upgraded the finger.
You upgraded Giza's wheel.
Hey, where is my finger, by the way?
I want that shit back.
Oh, I'm taking up all the sombers.
This is like the first time.
Hey, hey, I'm getting, I'm getting you your fucking finger.
Wait, wait, everyone relax.
And you can three finger my ass.
No, no.
What's going to happen?
You can do this, but not right now.
And I'll tell you why.
Because you're going to upgrade this.
You're going to, you're going to like do R1, L2, L2.
And you're going to go, all right, let's go fighter again.
No, we're going to go do Lane Doe.
No, you're going to want to take that to Millennia.
I know it.
I don't.
Oh, let's go.
Millennia?
No, I'm fucking, I haven't even upgraded a plus one yet.
Entertain yourself for a moment, dear.
Okay, fine.
I've actually never used Moonville.
It's so good.
It's unbelievably good.
Do you have a nine?
I do not.
Okay, I just need nine in ancient.
It would be max.
I don't even think I'm going to use it till it's max.
I wish I could just slide off.
Why am I doing this?
Okay, I'm just thinking about the good times, man.
I mean, Plastiducic, smoking up blood.
He didn't even fucking answer my call anymore.
I'm going to hang out with this motherfucker.
His weed sucks.
It's got this low quality dog shit weed.
It's so awful Plastiducic's had that fucking good shit.
All right, you ready?
Yeah, I voted to travel.
All right, vote to travel.
I knew he was going to do like L1, L2, L2.
And now he's going to be like, oh, I can beat Millennia by myself.
It's just like Neo.
Want to go give it a try?
No, I don't.
It's going to be really weak unless it's fully upgraded.
My whole build is on some cheesy Glintstone pebble Ash of War gimmick.
Hey, by the way, we're going to have to fight over the next larval tier.
I'm going to do rock, paper, scissors for it.
I thought I had one.
Oh, you do.
I don't know.
You have so much stuff in your inventory.
Do you need a larval?
Yeah, I have one.
Build to hold it.
Nah, for now, because I feel like this is going to be an opportunity
where one of us is going to go.
I hate everything that I'm doing right now.
Spoiler alert.
Those of you that are watching the VOD right now, it's me.
So in like an hour or so, I'll be respecting to something else.
Nice.
I actually really like this zone.
Ooh, that's a lot.
Your favorite Elden Ring zone.
Probably this one.
No, it's Limgrave.
The reason why I like Lindell so much is because you start to realize
that you are so close to getting to the base of the tree.
And once you can see the opening there, it's almost like, wait a second.
Oh, you can go in it like I'm right there the whole time.
The game has been teasing this gigantic tree.
And when you're finally there, it's this moment of holy shit.
I'm here right now.
I'm actually at this place.
It's been a distant thing for potentially tens of hours.
Now it's right here.
That's not in the game.
God from software does not fucking miss except for when they made Millennium.
It is big time.
Where are you?
I don't know.
I had lobster and doot at me.
Oh, you're dead?
Yeah.
Oh, you die.
How come I didn't even hear you die?
Because you were talking about how much you love Elden Ring.
You died.
Yeah, that was crazy.
Who even killed me?
Holy shit.
That was somehow your fault.
Fuck you.
Where are you now?
I went back to where you were.
I was on my way back because there's like a bonfire right
there.
No, I don't think millennia is not that bad.
It just is.
She's not that bad.
She just is.
I'm back into like jumping instead of rolling mode.
Really?
Yeah, my brain needs to reset a little bit.
Yeah, because short-term memory took over yesterday,
but long-term memory took over this morning.
That's interesting how that works.
This lobster is huge.
Please kill it.
It's like one hit.
It's going to shoot me again.
Oh, you are unhappy right now.
It's all right.
I'm glad stripping is happy.
That's the problem.
Stripping is in your head.
See, when you died from that lobster shot right there,
all you could think about was stripping,
just like spitting food out of his mouth,
pointing at the screen and like laughing.
You know what I mean?
Like a full open mouth and like mashed potatoes and shit.
Gravy comes out of his mouth and stuff.
That's what you're seeing.
You need to get stripping out of your head.
I can't.
He's too handsome.
Yeah, that's what's happening right now.
Yeah, he's eating a whole turkey dinner right now.
He's got stuffing and mashed potatoes and cranberry sauce.
I am not going to die again the rest of the stream.
I am activating blood cult initiate.
Oh, dark gamer god mode.
Oh, I grant you my soul.
Not you.
I'm talking to the ancient deep gods.
That seems like a really bad thing to sell your soul for
is to like be good at Elton.
No, it's all games.
Okay.
You wouldn't understand.
So what you're hoping for is you're hoping for like you dodge,
dodge, dodge, stripping, sitting there like,
okay, you know that scene in Lord of the Rings
where like the king is like eating the tomatoes
and shit during the battle?
Like you're just waiting for that moment.
It's cutting to stripping like you're dodging, dodging,
like eating the chicken and shit, stripping his mouth.
What the fuck is this fucking tomato eating noise?
Have you never seen Lord of the Rings?
I don't remember this scene.
Oh, have you not seen Lord of the Rings?
The scene, how do you not remember this?
The other recent prime video Lord of the Rings show
erased all of my memory of Lord of the Rings.
Oh shit, that's a dragon.
All he knows is Neo now.
That's all you have up there is like Neo information.
It's true.
I just, I like go 100% in a thing
and then everything else is just removed from the brain.
How far, how close are you to completing Neo 2?
No idea.
I wonder how close you are.
It feels like I'm getting close.
I decided I wanted to play a little today,
but I decided like if we're going to keep playing Elden Ring,
I'm not doing it, cutting myself off
because it's going to keep,
I don't know, my brain is just going to turn to mush.
True, that's all right.
You could, I mean, hey,
it's not a bad thing to have something you really like
to be able to do whenever you want.
That's not a bad thing.
In fact, I feel like a lot of people might be envious of that
because, oh shit, like, oh, I did this, now what?
I got nothing to do, nothing to play.
I wish there was some better games.
You got something that you're ready just to go right back to.
Yeah, I was getting annoyed when streamers are like,
it's a fucking game drought right now.
There's like no games, there's nothing.
Are you one of those?
Are you one of those like there's no games right now?
Because I don't, you don't seem like you'd be one
because you're willing to go back and play fucking driver in the PS1.
My most played game on stream is House Lipper.
I think, yeah, this is not the right person to ask this.
Okay, but yeah, no, I know what you mean.
Look, there's like 20 years, 30 years, a millennia of video games.
Just pick one.
That didn't work.
Wait, there's a millennia of video games?
Yep.
I stole that from Chad.
It sounds like a Chad comment now you say it.
Anybody that says there's no games,
I don't want to hear it if you haven't played Gex.
You haven't beat Chrono Trigger yet.
It's true.
Yeah, I've never been done.
I like how you're actually experiencing the game still.
This is still cool.
I got so lost in this area for a really long time.
It's, it is very, very easy to get lost here.
I think I have been down there.
I'm just forgetting.
There's a I'm trying to I this is okay.
This is my favorite area.
I still have no idea where the hell I'm going.
Oh, there's an I think there's an elevator in here that takes us.
Yeah, you go down to the kind of courtyard level
and then there's a few ways to go.
I know that when you get to the top,
you jump off the roof and you land on the other roof
and then you skip the area and you see bed curses
that item right there in a regular playthrough.
Saved a little bit of time.
This guy kind of knows where he's at.
This guy is like aware of this.
And that thing's going to be really annoying.
Where even is it?
Oh, I don't know.
Um, this is what is that?
Is that what?
What is this?
A dragon?
Wait, I'm poisoned.
What is what the fuck even is in the building here?
That's a dragon or a gargoyle.
I've anchored it.
Wait, did you jump?
What side did you jump down?
I didn't jump down.
I'm still up here.
I was hitting the wing inside this room.
Oh, come down here.
This guy's actually hard and sucks.
Well, I kind of said I wasn't going to die again.
All right, I'll take care of it.
Oh, yeah, that guy's usually here.
I wonder maybe forever here.
He's that good of a guardsman.
Oh, God.
Is that coming through the wall?
Holy shit.
He just turned this whole area into a virtual boy game.
I've said that before pretty recently.
No repeat jokes.
This is a rehearsal.
Hey, sometimes the good ones get to stay.
You imagine in the like, where was the fire?
Oh, oh, that's where he is.
Oh, my God.
It's got a lot of health.
Yeah.
Can it actually hurt us though?
Oh, he says as my head gets pancake.
Wait, it's up in the air.
I think we're safe from the fire though.
I guess not.
Can you stop saying shit like that?
It's like a Marvel movie.
Oh, man.
It's all right.
Fire can't get us in here.
Whoa, all right.
Burnt me.
What the heck, Star Lord?
Burnt me?
It burnt me.
Oh, burp me, Star Lord.
I like that.
I like that version.
Legendary in here.
Not going to minus two that one.
Get out of here.
Oh, man.
That's, that's unfortunate.
That joke went really well in rehearsal.
Lord Rune.
That's like 30, 40K, right?
Oh, yeah.
I don't have power.
I'm trying to do something.
Get the fuck away from me.
The dragons have blood.
Apparently.
This can I make?
Can I make him bleed?
I wonder.
You should be able to.
At least the fire can't get us in.
Oh, I don't even know what you're swinging at.
But oh, you can't.
You couldn't see it.
No.
Do we we both stack bleed together
if we're both bleeding, right?
I believe that's accurate.
Yes.
I mean, I don't see why not.
I think the dragon is on.
I think the dragon is on the roof.
No.
Where do you go?
There's a lot of guys in this room
and they're all aggroed to the dragon.
They are fighting the dragon.
Oh, shit.
I don't know.
It's a fucking jellyfish.
It's a spell.
He's casting bubble.
Oh, my God.
Dragons.
Dragons almost dead.
How do we get?
We're supposed to go like down
to the courtyard down there.
Yeah, I'm trying to.
I just want to kill the dragon.
Yeah, it's smart.
Nice wicked spot.
Put your head up here, please.
There it is.
Come here.
Why do I need mana?
What?
I didn't just take this took mana.
It's a webinar that I'm pretty sure they all do.
You're hitting it right now.
Oh, yeah, I guess so.
I just see a health bar in the sky
that's like taking.
OK, great job.
We get an item.
Do you think that when dragons die,
they turn to dust like that
because of how much weed they've been smoking with you?
Like all the vapors just come out.
And it was all right.
It was all right.
Oh, he's doing the jump strap.
I didn't get it from here.
You go down.
I don't think this is OK.
But we.
Yeah, hold on.
Great sword.
I got a few things here.
Let me see what these are.
Yeah, that's my first carrion.
I've upgraded carrion staff all game.
My first carrion spell.
I think I have some carrion shit
that you would want if you like.
But you don't.
I mean, we're changing our builds so frequently.
I'm not.
I've been using the same.
I switched once and then I switched back
because I realized that was wrong.
That is the that is more than I have.
OK, Mr.
Like I have upgraded like seven weapons this run.
I have what?
Plus one to plus two in three or four weapons.
I only have two items that are over plus five
and one of them is the finger.
It doesn't count because you stole it from me.
OK, it's one of these things.
Get ready.
Oh, I don't have the heels anymore.
Which is like half the reason I did it.
No, no, no.
This thing is OK.
This isn't OK.
This guy is just it's one of those
centuries or what it's what are they called?
I'll tell you the weapon that you get from these things
are is actually really fun.
Yeah, the dual welding light weapons.
I don't know what's happening.
My screen like froze.
Crucible.
Oh, I can look cool now.
I also got a crucible tree armor.
I got the armor.
You got the helmet.
I'm so much hotter than you.
No, you look like you're going to play Warframe.
You do.
OK, look.
Is she talking to you?
No, she did earlier.
I told her I am already married and I can't be seen with you.
The Lord's runes.
Do I need to use that for anything else?
Or is it just purely an enormous amount of runes?
Uh, wow, that's a lot.
We break 100 K.
Come on.
Can we break 100 K?
Never mind.
It wasn't the magic.
It was an ash of war.
Guys, we didn't break 100 K out here.
There is on one side.
There's usually a tour left.
There's a big scary man.
OK, for one second, I was like, what did the mod do?
And why is this dragon so big?
How what is happening?
But like a meteor landed on my head.
Meteor?
Yeah, I have no idea what that was.
There's usually an ulcerated tree spirit over here somewhere.
Right?
It wasn't this thing, was it?
That was a lot of damage.
Yeah, there's like some big creature under the ground
that's occasionally hitting me inside this building.
OK, well, let's go find it.
Yeah, it's shaking the whole game.
It's a bear behind us.
Oh, there is a bear.
Oh, fuck.
That's a big one.
OK, he wasn't actually stuck.
He was just like pretending.
Oh, where's the bleed?
How many times I got to hit you?
He's this once would be nice.
Oh, you're going to me?
Yeah.
Once what?
Hitting him once.
Oh, he can't come down the hallway.
What is the bleed resistance on this bear?
Holy shit.
I just held this on his like butt for a solid five straight seconds.
I that was he dropped beast blood.
I don't like that.
All right, so we can either go up and going up
brings us to Godfrey's room.
Right.
I prefer Godfrey.
I already have one of these.
Or we can go down into the well
and go down to the what the shunning grounds or whatever it is.
Oh, the sewers down to the tree fingers.
The tree is also looks like kind of sneaking around down.
There is glint stone dragon, glint stone dragon.
Yeah, he's like totally blocking the whole sewer.
It like that's probably the not a good way to go right now.
Dude, dual Omen, dual well, dual Omen, dual Omen, please.
That's not a bad idea.
No, the mashed potatoes just shot out of his mouth.
The mashed potatoes just launched out of stripping's mouth.
God damn it, dude.
Dude, that was like a fucking looney tune episode.
Dude, I would be careful, man.
You stripping right now may have just eaten like a chicken wing
and it's like you may have choked him because that was so funny.
And he only said I don't think he's watching.
I don't think he's going to watch the VOD.
I just I'm not going to bring any of this up.
Dude, you were just you were like one, two, three, just right over the edge.
It was so perfect.
I was like totally spaced out in my head.
Oh, man, I only barely.
That was so perfect.
Well, a little fresh restart, reset my pact.
That has to be the ultimate fall joke.
Your reaction was immediate.
Sombra seven.
I'm not going to say that out loud.
I don't want him to know I have one of these.
It's mine.
I need a nine.
I needed a somber nine and a ancient one.
I'll take another Lord's rune.
An easy 50k.
Oh, another legendary hero's rune.
Oh, boy.
Todd, don't hit him.
No, his name was Carl.
That's the last thing he heard before he died, by the way.
He's been practicing the trombone was me in his ear.
It was just mocking him.
That's so fucked up.
That's a hard.
Yeah, it's a horrible way to go.
I got a remembrance of the regal ancestor.
I'm going to hold on to it.
I got a hero's rune level up.
That's not enough.
I wonder if these souls later.
Do you need some?
I'm 15k more.
I think I am willing to do something for you because I know that it's been a little rough.
Oh, God.
And then like a week later, he comes back with like,
remember that time that I gave you a Lord's rune?
Hey, remember on stream that time I gave you the Lord's rune?
And then he asked me to do something wicked.
Yeah.
Freaked up.
But I mean, I know I'm a little bit higher than you.
I feel like you should have that level up a couple of times.
Okay.
Just trying to do a good thing.
Just worried about what this is going to cost me.
Just don't forget.
Don't forget what I did.
Right?
Yeah, I know you won't.
I'll make sure you don't.
I mean, I think I left my souls from that jump.
I don't even I don't want to think about it.
What level are you after this?
15.
Be so bad.
Don't you start at like level 15?
You're not supposed to be 15 at this point in the game.
I need like 200 souls.
Just kill like one enemy.
You go back and kill Carl again.
Nice.
I got another sacred tear.
That was also a hero's rune.
Was it really?
Maybe you can level up more than once.
Foster tech.
Thank you.
Actually, did I go the wrong way?
You got to go up upstairs.
I opened something.
I don't know.
There was a lever.
I've never played this game before.
I don't know what that does.
Okay, let's go.
We can walk straight up to goad free or to what's this name?
Good free.
Gurd free.
What'd you say?
Gertrude up in the top of the God free.
Well, there's him and then there's the magical mystical man.
Yes, Gertrude.
Careful here.
Will they beat Gertrude first try?
Well, it depends who it is.
It might not be Gertrude.
It might be like it might be like fucking Placidusix again.
I hope it's not something bad because this room is very, very small.
Isn't it?
And we could get absolutely screwed here.
Legendary over there.
I have to get that could be a Lord's room.
Where?
Where that guy's hanging over there.
Watch out.
We got a plant on the tree.
Yeah, we do.
Okay, that's a lot of health.
Wait.
I don't think plants have blood.
Yes, they do.
It's called chlorophyll.
Let's just go.
Please.
I would do not dodge here.
I would just hold you right up.
Nice.
That's dangerous to do up here.
That's a lot of confidence.
Can you imagine staring this down and going?
Yeah, I think I'll do 10 cartwheels in a row down this.
That's not a good idea.
Hold on.
I want to get this item.
Yeah, I want to get it too because my items can be better than your item.
I bet you $100.
Mine is better than yours.
All right, fine.
Whatever item this is like rarity or quality, like just quality.
Just like whatever it is like an opinion.
Mine's way better.
Mine.
No, it's not.
I just got Flame of the Fel God.
Legendary spell.
I got the remembrance of a fucking Godwin.
I kind of want to just do like 90 faith and just do all these wacky ass spells.
I think that still fits with me strong character arc.
If he just throws like raging fireballs, you know what I mean?
He's just like angry.
Me rage.
There's a dragon in here.
No, what dragon is it?
Red.
It's a red dragon, man.
It's the lich dragon.
What the fuck?
I don't know what that is.
Neither do I.
I feel like I said it with a lot of with nervousness.
Oh, for the sacks.
First Elden Lord.
Oh, he has that.
I've never had.
I've never done this fight because I've never played this game before.
This is my first time playing Elden Ring.
Why would they put a dragon in this room?
Miyazaki, you're fucking wild.
I don't know.
It's actually not that big of a deal.
It's like, okay, as long as it doesn't do anything else.
There's just kind of shit everywhere, though.
Oh, God.
It's really it's just kind of a mess.
But as long as we it's not killing us too hard.
That's a lot of damage.
Um, it's on the top row.
Off the top rope.
The Huracan Arana.
He's got like, oh, shit, the music is playing.
I'm going to get down there.
No, my big entrance.
They're going to think I'm such a dork.
Get down here.
This dragon sucks at this game.
We got to like, get in there and get some hits in.
Okay, he's in the dome.
Oh, that he just hit his neck on the top.
You just went like, that probably hurts so bad.
He is he is doing a good job hiding how bad that hurt.
Y'all just keep fighting like it's normal.
That's like a oh, dude, are you all right, man?
Yeah, I'm okay.
I'm all right.
I don't know.
That looks really bad.
No, I'm good.
I'm good.
It's like we do you want to go to like a doctor or something?
It's so hard to see right now.
He is having the reverse problem that we have.
He is complaining on his stream right now.
It's so fucking stupid.
How am I supposed to fight these cases?
Little these little ants in this room.
I can't even fit in here.
This randomizer is so bad.
How are you expected to actually do this?
Look, I can't even fit up here.
Fucking game is so stupid.
Actually, I heard a lot.
I mean, I'm concerned for my life, but I think you got him.
Kind of got me in the corner.
He's dead in three, two, one.
Got it.
Sacred tear.
Finally.
I've been needing one.
Oh, Bordasax just went offline.
Is his offline screens up?
Oh, he'll be back.
Can somebody go into his chat and just be like, I don't know.
We were just like fucking around.
I kind of feel bad though, because he was he's probably pissed.
Hold on.
I'll see if he's I'm in his discord.
I'm going to say like get owned in his discord.
Don't don't be an idiot.
I got 100,000 souls.
Hold on.
Wait, you level in this game?
I totally was just walking away.
I feel like I'm just going endurance, whatever.
You know, in like the hour that we've not been fighting millennia,
I have actually leveled like six or seven times.
You have not?
No, I've leveled like eight times.
All we had to do is like not fight millennia for like a little bit.
I know.
I'm so glad that after that first attempt that I just started,
you could just tell I was already annoyed.
I think it was already it was already going poorly.
And I'm so glad we just pulled the plug.
Get in the bowl.
They're not that Fortisax is going to open my stream
and he's going to think we're like beaming him by like jumping around and shit.
Okay, just play it like just play normally.
Don't like if he's watching, I don't want to be like, I don't know.
He's fucking huge, man.
I mean, if if someone like I don't even this scenario, this joke is weird.
But if someone beat you so bad that you turned off your stream,
would you sit there seizing in anger, open up their stream?
Like like, fuck this, I'm done.
And then then like watch their stream.
You know what?
Probably what you okay.
Look, if you were like fighting and you knew it was like two other streamers
and they were like, oh, yeah, Fortisax, we fucking got your ass.
You know what I mean?
You don't think you'd wait.
You'd watch me like, what the fuck are they saying now?
If what are they saying now?
Defeat it that you turn off your own stream.
I feel like you need to get out of the room.
Like you've already lost.
Yeah, you've already lost.
Do you want more memory slots?
Do I?
Yes.
Do you want like more spell slots?
I know you keep saying I don't use spells.
No, I'm good.
I don't know what happened on my memory slots.
I think when I respect, I lost a lot of them
because I had like two full rows.
I kept getting them.
But now I've got like five slots.
Oh, dude, Fortisax raid.
Seven.
What's up Fortisax?
Thanks for the raid.
I mean, I know what you were just doing.
Appreciate the raid though.
Okay, let's go.
Boss, ignore Fortisax.
All right, so what's in here besides Bogot?
I see.
You know what's in there?
I know it's in there
and you're going to want to equip your Rikard bike.
My Rikard bike?
The pike, the spear that he gives you.
Oh, does that mean that Rikard is in here?
Yeah.
Okay.
I think it only worked for one of us.
So you go in first.
It appears to be his stage two.
It's stage two.
Wait a minute.
Ah, it's the regular cutscene.
Lame.
I just want to hear him say together.
Oh, this is a small arena for him.
Yep, it is very easy.
I don't think I can help.
I need we do this again.
I'm going to have to do more man of flasks.
What is happening?
I don't know.
He's swinging at me.
Shit.
Rones.
Wait, what?
Oh, it's Morgoth talking.
Oh, yeah, that makes sense.
It's like Morgoth went to phase two.
What's that?
Is there a car driving?
Yes.
What is that?
Was there a car?
There's a motorbike on the highway.
Wait, no.
Is that from your room?
No.
What the hell was that?
That was in the game?
No, it was not.
Yes, it was.
I'm going to die.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, wait.
He does this thing.
All right.
He's dead in three, two, one.
Nice.
Yippee.
Yeah.
Two sacred tears and Godric's great run.
Oh, really?
That's pretty sick.
That is sick.
When I was walking up to this for the first time
and just looking at this shit
and I was like, oh, my God, I'm going in the room.
It was like.
Jebaited.
I was like, oh, my God.
What?
You can't get in the urn tree.
Oh, my God.
It would have been funny if this was DLC.
They just didn't do anything with it.
It was like that would not be funny.
That would be actually really infuriating.
And it's paid DLC.
Hello.
Old friend.
I got the animation like she appeared, but she's not here.
You probably I'll just stand up and do it.
Are we supposed to get something important here?
She gave me a cookbook.
I think.
Huh.
Isn't this where she tells you that like she wants to fucking smoke up?
It's the the medallion.
Oh, the medallion.
What do we do?
What medallion?
The rolled medallion to get up.
I have a full one.
You have it.
Yeah.
I got that like really early on on the first day.
I completed the whole medallion.
Thank goodness.
She gave me a member.
Everyone's giving me golden seeds.
She's like here.
I don't know.
All of it.
We all have plenty of these.
Can we go to God Rick's tower so I can get the great rune?
Yes.
I believe it is.
It must be this one.
It's the one in the castle is God Rick, right?
Why can't I travel not travel to a site of grace right now?
Why not?
If I can.
I don't know.
Why can I?
If it's multiple pieces, you have the wrong medallion.
Is it was it multiple pieces?
I'm not sure.
Hold on.
I'm looking what I have buried deep within my inventory.
World medallion operates the grand lift of rolled.
There you go.
I think I might have just thought it was two pieces because it is split in half.
Like the image of it.
I just destroyed it.
I didn't mean to do that.
I sit on it.
I think I just assumed it was pieces.
So I am you got to talk to the corpse.
I did.
But I can't go anywhere.
I have to check the thorns though.
Oh, did you not like talk to the thorns?
Maybe that's what it is.
Technically, I guess.
No, those thorns are lonely.
It's a known bug.
You have to you have to separate.
We have to separate.
I banish me.
Banish me now.
And hey, before you go, drop that larval tear on the ground.
If you would, you can come back to my world and get it.
If you fucking grovel a little bit, the game crashed.
I think it was.
I think my game was probably waiting to crash.
So it was just like, hold on, hold on momentarily.
I'm just going to walk up to the tower.
I don't know if you'd like you get items here too.
Or if you can even come.
Okay, he's going to go.
He's going to go pee.
Okay, you're definitely going to want to mute then
because I'm going to go off on a tangent.
I'm back to me is where he walks away to, you know,
just be as weird as possible.
I am.
I'm good.
I made sure to be very quick.
But wow, you can do that.
You can you sacrificed your bathroom time for me.
Well, I don't know.
I just we didn't stand up for eight hours yesterday.
And I kind of want to make sure every like couple hours,
like I get up.
That's valid and based.
Yeah.
All right.
Somebody says a crazy.
All right, so let me open my game again.
What's better, Bloodborne or Elden Ring?
Elden Ring is probably the best single player experience
I've probably had in a long time.
It's hard to compare them because they're almost what?
Almost full of 10 years apart.
It's difficult to say and it's hard to do that.
I think Elden Ring is I think Elden Ring is probably better,
but it's just newer and there's more shit in it.
It's hard to say.
My Dark Souls 2 argument.
There's just more shit.
It'd be nice if there was more Bloodborne.
Okay, I let me bring this back.
You should be able to see.
Yes, you can.
Okay.
All right.
Can you see?
All right, I'm going to.
Do you have your thing on?
Do I?
Maybe the 30 FPS cap.
Yeah, it's that's probably the only thing holding that back at this point.
I have a feeling deep in my soul,
even for reasons I've told you,
but can't say that they're waiting for something for Bloodborne.
Like like some like Demon's Souls remaster treatment or something.
If they do, if they did the Demon's Souls remake,
you have to assume that Bloodborne will get maybe.
I don't know.
I feel like is it one of those scenarios where
like they coded it to a point where it's like,
well, we kind of can't do anything about this.
It's just this is the game.
I doubt it.
When Demon's Souls got like how good that remaster is
and how old Demon's Souls is.
But Demon's the Demon's Souls remaster
was like a complete 100% remake of the entire game.
It wasn't like a HD texture pack.
I never got to play it because I don't have a PS5.
I neither.
But that was a it was a complete they made the whole game over again.
So it's not like a Dark Souls remastered kind of scenario.
I sure you know what?
When I'm 80 years old and all the lawsuits have caught up with me
and I'm on my deathbed,
I really hope there's more Bloodborne content.
You're just riddled in lawsuits and you're 80.
Isn't there somebody on this bridge usually?
Two giants and at the end of this bridge.
No, it's just a really, really long bridge.
I will go down and say the old hunters is the best DLC
in any from software game.
Okay.
Yeah.
Sure.
All right.
Okay.
Isn't there some weird stuff with one of these?
You go there's a boss like in this.
You go all the way down or something.
Yeah.
You like you travel across one of the bridges
and your whole screen turns black
and you fight like two of the Omen people.
That is what happens.
Right.
Okay.
The ring city was pretty good.
Yeah.
But I think as a whole.
Okay.
Wait, what's the the Bloodborne boss's name
in the clock tower?
You know, you know the one Maria.
Yeah.
Maria is if like millennia wasn't dog shit.
It's like they wanted to do Maria again
because people really liked her
and then they put her in a game
where you can't actually dodge that quickly.
Okay.
Real question.
Real question before I restore the power of the great run.
Yes.
You're in the Elden Ring universe
and you come up here in the two fingers here
and it's this holy dude.
Look how holy this shit is.
You think you would take a bite?
No, because that would be disrespecting
this holy thing
and that would be a complete disrespect
that it would be what do you think you're doing?
You see you see like the the ripped up.
It's kind of like it's kind of like bark like tree.
Get it tree fingers.
Hold on.
Honestly, like I think you just kind of
said something really profound.
Hold on.
It is like tree.
It is like a tree bark.
Yeah, tree fingers.
It's a tree.
Get fatty on the phone immediately.
Okay, where are we going?
We can go.
So we you have the medallion.
Here are your options.
Medallion of rolled.
Yeah.
We can do the weird upside down area.
Okay.
With you know you I have that item.
We can put the time thing and it goes upside down.
You can do that.
Yes.
We could we could go in.
I want to hear option two.
We could go in and and fight.
You know what I mean?
We could do that.
But I mean that that's a possibility.
We could go do the medallion.
Or we can go to the upside down.
Medallion upside down world or and we're not doing that one because it's not.
Okay, upside down vote.
My vote has been in.
You're voting for upside down world.
Yeah.
Okay, so then we have to go to lake facing cliffs and go from there, right?
I think pretty far ride.
That's a pretty far ride.
Oh, we could go down into the shining grounds sewers.
That's where Mog is.
That's great for Mog.
Isn't there a place further up where we can?
That's a fake Mog.
But yeah, what's your question?
I don't know if we have to go this far back.
I don't know.
I'm going to follow you.
Take the wheels.
Somebody's name is gaming dragon Fortisacs.
I think they're trying to tap into that market there.
All right.
So we need to find a way to go like here.
I don't know about you, but I have a lot of Fortisacs.
Trying to figure out what you are saying right now.
We need to go down that way.
What does he mean?
What do you mean?
No, don't even explain it.
You gotta be honest.
I don't really know.
I think it's open to interpretation.
Did I go the wrong?
Like, we're not supposed to go this way.
I'm trying to find like we need to go down there.
How do you get down there?
The edge of the cliff that way.
There's a whole bunch of those things on the wall that you can jump down.
Is there?
Yeah, there's some cliff side of wall jumps there.
Yes.
God.
Listen.
They won't.
They won't leave me alone.
So am I going the wrong way or are you going the wrong way?
I don't even know where you're going.
I'm trying to go down here like to get to where.
Well, I mean, like I would we go this far apart?
We do think so much.
I don't know where you actually are.
All right.
We need to just get back together again.
Helen, we just you've gone too far.
I'm coming.
I thought there was a different way to get down here.
Coming back.
You've gone too far.
It's these like sideways tombstones right here.
I wanted you to think I was jumping off.
Well, that's what you got to do.
I freaked out.
Nice joke.
I freaked.
I didn't I knew I wasn't going to make the second jump.
And I was like, fuck, I have to double jump.
But I don't want to double jump too far because I'll go over the tombstone.
I've done enough of those jokes today.
No.
Well, we can work.
There's a bonfire here if you can't handle those jumps.
I can.
I don't know.
I don't know if you're going to handle these jumps.
Well, I just did something to say.
King me.
OK, so there's actually a lot of random shit we could do here.
We could do this.
I think there's probably there's a jail here, too, isn't there?
Yes.
Do you know what's crazy about our playthrough is that this game is so giant.
We keep talking about how giant and big this game is.
And then it was also like, no, the only thing we get.
The only thing we can do is millennia.
Well, we didn't have the key to the manor.
We didn't have the two great ruins.
We kind of we could go this whole like this whole side path.
We didn't do any of this.
Yeah, but but game progress.
We were just beating our head against the wall trying to do game progress.
I don't know.
We made a lot of progress and we haven't killed her yet.
Yeah, because we came progress because we got the two items.
We needed to keep game progress going.
I don't know why you were convinced that millennia had those two items.
No, it's true.
Sensor him.
Oh, fun.
Enemy.
Fun.
Dung eater puppet.
One hit.
OK, so let's check out this.
There's a down by me left.
There's some ruins.
They might be a boss down underground in the purified ruins.
Just grab in the moon fire.
There's a legendary item here for me.
Not for you.
The teleporter in the chest up here in that tower.
I don't remember where that takes you.
You know what I'm talking about?
I think so.
That's good.
I actually don't have to have two acts of Godfrey's now.
No.
Oh, yes, I look over at chat when I pick up a legendary item
to see how many fog champs there are to determine if I'm going to say,
whoa, what the fuck is awesome?
Whoa, what the fuck?
Margaret's shackle.
What the hell is that at Margaret or Morgoth's fight?
If you use that item, it'll make Morgoth go.
He'll slam into the ground for like five seconds.
Oh, so it's like in a Yasha when you say, sit, boy.
Make it rain.
The answer to that is yes, I think.
So do you think that that implies in the lore that Margaret is actually Isiakide?
I think, I think.
He's not, he's not from here.
Oh, okay.
All right.
I'm killing this.
I hate her.
Oh.
Oh, no.
Can't lock on to her.
Okay, now we're going to go over here.
Is something else for us to look at?
What is over here?
That's just, I can't get out of my head now.
I just keep thinking about it.
Isn't there something here?
I'm really busting the lore down.
I just see it from a different angle.
What else is here?
Irma, why do you look like that?
You know, people, people ask that and it's just like, I don't know, dude,
my skin and muscle and sinew up here formed a person's face.
I don't know.
Sounds like something an alien would say.
Bro.
We got the Mariner.
It's the Crucible Knight down here.
What are the Mariners usually drop that you need?
What's their thing?
Deathroot, I think.
I think they're one of the sources of Deathroot.
Sounds right, dude.
Dude, screw you.
You stink at this game.
Distractive.
He is distracted.
Why is my weapon not equipped?
What a great enemy.
Three lumps of flesh.
Let's fucking go.
Larval tear.
Oh, cool.
You don't need mine anymore.
You mooch.
Are you feeling okay?
Yes.
I thought of you today.
Spiked practice.
In my Uber, the song What If God Was One Of Us was playing.
And I never heard this lyric before, but it says a slob like one of us.
Yeah, it's.
What if God was one of us?
Just a slob like one of us.
I got the letter from Volcano Manor.
I don't know if that was something we needed.
I don't think so.
I have enough to level up, I think.
I need one of those.
I need to go back, look at remembrances,
and I got to make a lot of decisions.
Did you ever talk to the finger maiden next to the two fingers?
Yes.
Okay, because she does sell a bunch of stuff.
Yes, she does.
She sold some pretty good things to me.
I kind of want to go to the upside down.
Yeah.
No, I'm going to disconnect you.
I'm going to go get the waypoint.
You go do your thing.
All right, all right.
Just boot me because I've got a major decision I have to make here.
I have banished you.
I'll see you in an hour.
Chat.
I can't see.
I don't know why I'm doing that today.
I don't know.
But anyways, I'm going to make this decision one more time.
I need to have the final build.
And I genuinely don't know what that is.
I could dual weld the omen cleavers.
God damn it.
You know what?
I'm just to make him feel better.
Just hit me a few times.
Oh, man.
Almost got me.
Oh, I did a lot of damage, but sorry.
You're doing good, though.
You're doing pretty good.
Watch it.
Oh, how'd you do that move?
You're pretty good at this game.
All right.
There's no more no more jokes.
No more joking around.
No more jokes.
You got to pick your belt.
You got to pick your belt and see if you're going to dual weld.
Two big hands jumping claw attacks.
I know it's really pretty good.
It's really good.
But are you a big enough man to do it?
That's the question.
The question is, what am I going to do?
Are you thick enough and tight enough?
I missed it.
Missed it.
All right.
What a shitty thing.
What?
Oh, you're going to have a recusant finger or a gold scarab.
I don't know what you're doing, but it doesn't sound like you're respecting.
I'm I took I have a remembrance and I'm just checking to see what they are.
And it's not remembrance weapon randomization.
It's any item randomization.
Yeah.
The gold scarab, though, is this something that is I feel like that.
How good is that?
I should just take the scarab.
But it's a talisman, right?
It's 20% more.
Is it more or additional because the more multipliers and not, you know what I'm saying?
Holy shit.
Somebody just called you a POE player.
I am.
Is that why you said that?
That is why I said that.
It's very important if it's more or not.
You got to know that gaming.
All right.
What the heck am I going to do?
Let me look.
It's going to run around and pick up bonfires.
I'm going to do a poll because I want Chad to decide.
We have three lights, inferno, crozier.
This is just a straight up just strength weapon.
Big hammer.
We also have I'm not going to put that on the list.
You'll pick it and it'll ruin my game.
We have the double Omen killer swing dual weld double Omen killer.
We've got acts of Godfrey, the acts of Godfrey make you
You hear anything in music playing?
Two big knives is funny, but also the acts of Godfrey.
This could be funny too because I'll keep mispronouncing the name.
I'm going to say like, oh, acts of goat fry and everyone's going to laugh.
That's funny.
I'll mispronounce it a few times.
I can't alt tab because it might crash the game.
So what's what is it up?
Dude, Godfrey one.
Oh, shit.
Cool.
What about the God Slayer colossal sword?
You mean this thing that's like a deck strength.
They I don't know.
It's the best sword.
Dual welding is up.
Okay.
So that's what we're doing.
Double Omen wins double Omen killers.
Oh, shit.
All right.
Okay, stir.
Let me get your opinion.
Yeah, your opinion is worth 5% of the vote that that honestly in the grand scheme of
things is not much.
That actually is it close.
It's pretty close.
Double Omen killer dual welding strong guy.
If you do that, I'm going to vote against it.
Like I want you to do that, but I'm going to vote against it if you keep saying dual welding.
Like dual wielding great Omen killer cleaver acts of Godfrey.
Who the fuck is Godfrey?
It's funny.
Oh, Godfrey, Godfrey, Godfrey.
Okay.
Yeah.
And what's special about that axe?
I said it kind of funnily.
That's it.
That's the reason you want to use it.
Or the big red hammer.
Oh, the charge one.
Yes.
That one's kind of fun.
I think practically the Omen killers is going to be the strongest one.
Okay, done.
And I think when you fight millennia with jump attacks with those,
you'll be happy to stick her face in the mud.
Oh, wow.
These look like two turkey legs.
All right.
So are these somber?
I hope they're not.
It's not.
Oh shit.
I have to do it to both of them.
Oh, no.
I've picked up a couple of sombers, but I need regular.
Oh, then I can look and see what I got.
Dude, I will trade you like all of my sombers because I'm not going to be using them anymore.
You just have them all.
If I can have all of yours.
Dude, you are ruining the economy right now.
How many of these do I need?
I need a lot of these.
I was going to buy 200 of them.
I have one ancient.
Okay.
How many of these do I need?
I need 24 of these.
Jesus.
And I could potentially upgrade it for you because I only need one of each.
And I need 24 of these.
Right.
I mean, no.
Wait, stop, stop, stop.
What?
I need 12 of each.
Why did you say 24?
A bunch of you said 24.
24 for both.
That's what I mean.
24 was correct.
Yeah, I was right.
Why is everybody yelling at me?
It's 12 per weapon.
Yeah, what are you guys talking about?
I had it right.
Here we go.
Yeah, you should let me upgrade those.
So I need smithing stone threes now.
I explained this early on.
This is like the one randomizer cheeto thing is that there's an option in the randomizer
to only need one stone per upgrade.
And he has it and I don't.
Because I've played randomizer before and it was just looking for stones for eight hours
and it was not fun.
What's the highest scaling thing that I have here?
Fire, flaming strike, flaming the red mains, wild strikes and flame of roar.
Oh, because yeah, I see what you're saying.
Well, I just wasted like 30,000 souls for no reason.
So you could get these just to like plus 25 each.
Yeah, if you have like I just need one of each stone per upgrade.
So when it costs you six stones, it would cost me one.
Shit.
Okay, so I need so I could do one.
Do you have any smithing stone threes?
I have like, yeah.
We're not going to get in a position where this is going to completely screw me over
and I'm not going to be able to take them.
What about the finger?
I have a plus 10 somber weapon.
Is that is that okay?
Honestly, I have no idea.
I would assume so, but.
So if I I don't want to get this wrong.
Because last time this all look, I got a plus 10 magma worm scale sword.
That's okay, because I'm fine.
Okay, I'm going to give you these both these weapons stir.
Please get them both to plus 25.
If you could.
Okay, I only have one ancient.
Or just get one that would be the main hand.
I can get them pretty high.
Yeah.
Okay, I duplicated my Eldenbeast remembrance.
So I'm going to use all my souls on your new company that you're launching
called Dual Welding Omen Killers.
I thought you told me never to use that.
I thought you said, no, don't do that anymore.
I don't think you can stop.
People are freaking out.
They're saying don't you're going to lose them again.
What's the real thing here?
Oh, do you have a plus 25?
I double I double duplicated my Eldenbeast remembrance.
I'm a double duper.
This is good.
I need a lot of endurance.
Go to at least 50 strength.
Is that okay?
50.
It was 12 decks.
Put these on.
That should be okay.
Do 26 endurance.
20 endurance?
No way.
I think this is fine.
All right.
We're in a good spot.
Now I just need to upgrade these and I'm going to be
I'm going to be an absolute slaughter.
Let me see what it looks like when I swing it.
Oh my goodness.
Yes.
All right.
This is worth it now for sure.
Make sure the jump attack thing is on.
Apparently it didn't double duper.
I need more talisman slots.
Try higher poise armor if I have any.
Still in medium.
Man, I am making so much progress right now.
I'm glad.
It's actually good to hear.
I am glad to hear that.
I am untethered.
That's heavy though.
Look at me.
All right, sir.
I am I'm ready for me to come to your world
for you to drop a plus 25 on the ground for me to see
if I can pick that plus 25 up off the ground
and then for you to then take my items
upgrade them to plus 25 and then give them back
or at least 24.
All right.
You look nasty.
Yep.
Why don't you go to bird feeder on your head?
What's up, dude?
Okay.
I am dropping you my only good weapon
that I've been using all game to prove that you can see it.
To prove that I can pick it up off the ground.
And then you're not going to give it back.
I need some collateral.
Just put it on the ground.
There it is.
Can you see it?
You don't need to pick it up.
I can pick it up plus 25 magic long sword.
There it is.
And I'm using it.
Oh, oh, right.
Okay.
So now very cool.
I am very happy about this time to destroy the rest of this game.
I had a plus 10 scale sword.
Now we're going to see what happens when I get the real shit.
Ashes of war are applied to this item.
It's a lot.
Wait, is this okay?
Can you just give me my item back?
Prep.
All right.
Okay.
So you're giving me your this is scary.
I kind of don't like this.
You're taking the only thing I have to make you just took the only thing I have.
That's true.
Okay.
Here you go.
There's one and here's the other one.
Cool.
Okay.
I banish you.
Let's go to tried.
Won't let me doing that thing again.
Try again, try again, try again.
I cannot wait back alley deals for sword upgrades.
You look like one of those street performers that paint themselves
silver and stand around all day.
Uh, do you have a smithing eight?
I'm going to need those.
I don't.
I have smithing six is the highest I have.
Oh, let me, let me complete that thought.
Like, hold on.
I got them to 16 and 18, but I am out of, um, smithing stone six.
Oh, I have those.
Just drop all the smithing stones.
You have a past six.
All of them or just singles.
I only have up to six that plus plus 18 plus that's fine.
Do you understand what we're doing and why I need them?
Just drop them.
I only have sixes though.
Drop them then you told me you needed plus sevens.
I, you, I, I'm upgrading two weapons.
I needed a lot there.
There's every smithing stone I own.
I do feel like this is some kind of a scam.
Like you're going to be like, oh, thanks.
And you're going to pick those all up and disconnect.
And we're never going to talk ever again.
Well, uh, I got them both to 19 and we need sevens.
Just pick all those up because you probably need them eventually.
For some reason.
Yeah.
When you switch builds again, streamer beats Elden ring only using the kick.
There they are.
There's your items.
We got them.
Get them.
Get them quick.
You're about to cry.
I know they do spawn.
Oh shit.
That actually could happen.
How am I?
268 plus 232 and it's a double.
Do you have the claw talisman for jump attacks?
I do, but I'm not going to use it.
Because you're scared.
No, because I want the extra ruins for now.
He's scared.
What a fucking baby.
Shut up.
I'm not scared of the jump attack.
Eat it.
You're it.
Shut up stupid.
I'm not scared of your idiot.
All right, I'm ready to play the video game.
That's fantastic news for people who like watching you play video games.
So let's go back to I'm imagining I'm going to follow you to put the artist shack
and then we're going to go into the upside down world.
Oh, no, I can.
I think you think you can accept the votes places you haven't been.
I cannot.
I have to go to the artist shack.
Wasn't there a way we did this before?
You totally joined me in a place you hadn't been to before.
I think it's because I.
Oh, because we were disconnected and you never.
Oh, you were there and I just connected to you.
Well, then you we have to go from the artist shack is right there.
Is that is it not right there?
No, you got to go down the hill.
We got to go to Academy gate town and then go up the hill.
Fight millennia, fight millennia.
Who?
I'm not fighting millennia until these are both plus 20.
I told her to lose my number and she cried.
All right, let's go.
I've got my final build.
You look really cool.
Where your cape is like fluttering.
You look pretty cool, too.
The way your smirk goes up on one side of your face
to reveal your deep level of confidence that you have.
Let me I want this now.
So I want it now.
That's you.
That's you, man.
All right, won't go.
How much for a golden goose?
No, they're not for sale.
OK, but how much?
All right.
Here we are.
Let's do the upside down level.
Having some trouble kind of.
My health bar is girthy.
Yeah, I actually like doubled my health from when we were fighting millennia.
Did you or where are you?
All right.
You want to turn this upside down or you want to clear it first?
Do you there's not even a boss here.
Is there a reason to I don't think so.
There are items.
Yeah, but they're like not good items.
Then we're like we're pretty like so huge that we don't even need them.
We are pretty beefy at this stage.
I'm not going to find the axe of Godfrey and go and then restart my whole character.
Oh, hey, check it out, man.
But you wish you were this cool.
Yeah, that's my great rune.
Yeah, I can do it, too.
You have one.
Kind of weird that you would lie.
My power is your power.
I'm the one who passed it down to you.
This isn't upside down verse.
Do you need you need the elevator to go up to go on the upside down area?
It's fucking.
This is the normal way.
Why is this normal?
Come down.
Come, come.
Why is it right side up?
Now you have to go.
Wait, do we go through that window?
We go through that window.
Yeah, something's wrong.
You need the hourglass.
We just put it on there.
I think I took the hourglass off.
You I think you took it off.
You I think you put it on and then I took it off.
Wait, why did you take it off?
I don't know.
Come down here.
You walked up to the thing after I did that and you picked it up.
Yeah.
Why did you do that?
I didn't realize that you did it because I didn't think that you had it.
It's going back upside down again.
OK, I put it back on.
OK, it's back up.
It's yeah.
All right.
But then it flipped everyone.
They all died.
Yeah, it just killed everybody.
This guy's still here, though.
I loved I loved this area on my first playthrough.
When that guy's down, they're just casting.
Oh, that's right.
It's so awful.
I loved it.
Watch out.
There's a giant gargle.
I got to hit this.
Watch out for the gargle.
All right, we should go around.
I think the gargoyle is going to fall off.
I would say we should probably should bait the gargoyle to attack.
So it falls straight down.
It's good to me.
OK, I'm just going to continue this way.
And it can't even like fit over here.
Um, it's like three, two, one.
You're going to die.
What are you doing?
I'm kind of in trouble.
He's still alive down there.
How is he still alive?
OK, well, there'll be a problem in about five minutes.
Holy shit, there's a thousand damage.
This is so overwhelming.
How is this guy still alive?
He just stabbed himself in the chest.
Wow, I guess he wins.
I got Erd Tree Heal.
He just stabbed himself through the heart.
I got Erd Tree Heal if you want it.
I'd expect off the healing.
That's a big drop.
We're fine.
One problem, though, is we have an issue in a minute.
Once we get down a little further.
Items.
You're blocking me.
You said, oh, items.
I turned to look.
Oh, it's the people that fell when you turned it.
Dang.
Items up here?
Yeah.
Yeah, he landed in an unfortunate spot.
Yes, he did.
I thought I was going to kill him.
He's full health.
He's dumb.
In it.
Twilight shots.
I feel like he's just going to baseball swing one of us off this ledge.
I guess as ready as we're going to be.
Who goes first?
Oh, God, you got you guys.
What?
Oh, we went down.
You touched the thing.
Well, why do I spill?
He's going to be still.
Wait, can we crush him?
Wait, what?
Oh, fuck.
He's not coming down, right?
He's dead.
Is he dead?
How do I make this go back up?
You can't step on him again?
No.
Is there a lever?
Can you pull something?
Hold on.
I don't think so.
Let me see.
Well, shit.
Maybe.
Is there no lever up?
There's no lever.
I don't think.
There's a bonfire outside, though.
Yeah, what happens if you reset the area and you touched it?
Like if you die down there.
Oh, no.
I'm sorry.
I just did.
I just there's a cut scene now.
I forget what the heck is down here.
This is how you go over to the other part of the tower.
The howling tree?
No, this is the thing.
The one where you were talking about where you get invaded.
So what?
Yeah, if I step on this, I think the elevator might just be there for you.
Let's see.
Oh, I spawned here with you.
Oh, I see.
Cut scene teleport me.
Wow.
So am I just dumping strength?
Dumping strength or jump into health?
Get health to like 50 first.
Yeah.
Should I get strength to?
What's your health at?
What's the vigor?
Uh, 40.
What's your strength at?
50.
Yeah, I'll get it.
I'll get this to 50 and then just dump everything.
Growing boy.
Look at how strong I am.
You're really.
Oh, my God.
Yeah, I'm a I'm a Flintstone kid.
Yeah, you can walk.
You're gonna bug out the cut scene.
Watch out snail on the road.
Oh, my minus.
Oh, Gen Z doesn't get that one, dude.
Oh, that's true.
Is this doesn't it happen here?
This is not where it happens.
I believe so.
On the other side of the door.
And I hope it's some really weird enemies.
But if you crouch, they can't see you.
It was the snail.
You said crouching was useless.
Wait, it was the snail.
Did we just run by that?
Stupid.
The snail was the boss.
It didn't go into the cut scene, though.
Do you have to kill the snail to activate it?
This elevator takes so long, though.
Oh, but oh, we're on great run.
You got another great run.
Yeah, I'm loaded.
OK, so we jump here.
Go back and we kill the snail.
We go back and we kill the snail.
It's just I want to support to wait.
What do you think?
What's going through your head?
We got to kill a snail.
It's bugged again.
I tried.
No, he doesn't deserve it.
This is not the right tower.
You're thinking of a different bridge.
Yeah, I think we just have this tower now.
OK, then where are we going next?
Well, we were going up this path.
There's still an urn tree.
We could do the snow zone.
Use your medallion and get up there.
We could do some more.
Where do you do that?
We have to go through the capital
and go down that road.
And we go up the lift and go to the snow zone.
The snail is supposed to be a noble.
Oh, that's right.
Yeah.
No, that is where one of the nobles is.
Go to the bridge.
The snail is going to have boss loot.
Oh, fucking.
Boss loot, boss loot, boss loot, boss loot, boss loot, boss loot.
We can also apparently go to Radon's tower,
which I think we have a portal to.
What major thing have we not done besides the snow zone?
We're pretty we're close.
We're close to being able to beat the game.
We never went down to Moog.
We didn't do Moog.
But do we really want to do Moog?
I forget where you were.
You even enter that area.
The Caelid's tower is Radon.
Oh, my God.
It really was.
What?
OK.
There's so many items.
Hold on.
I just got.
What was that?
Man, that guy was loaded.
I got another piece of the Curseful Knight.
Holy shit.
Now I look pretty cool.
OK, so, yeah, we can either go up the lift.
We can do.
Do we have any blue keys?
We could do one of the teleporters.
What are those keys called?
They're like a blue stone sword or something.
They have a special name.
I have one.
I have imbued sword key.
Which one of those is unsealed?
Yeah, that is a unsealed sending gate.
I know one of them takes you to the sewers, right?
One goes to a random spot in Nocaran.
One goes to Faramazula and one goes to.
Yeah, I don't know.
The last one goes.
It's far away in firm.
It's like in the distance, though.
It's not the actual zone.
Oh, oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, it's that.
It's the tutorial zone where you go.
We fight that sentry thing, the scion, whatever it is.
OK, let's just go there.
And we none of us remember which one goes where.
So let's just use one.
Cool.
I mean, I'm down for that.
Whoops.
I voted Ronnie's rise.
That's not that's not correct.
It's down here at the four Belfry.
Vote rejected because I vote the wrong place.
There we go.
I have the hiccups.
Do something, dude, for like a strawberry strawberry strawberry strawberry strawberry strawberry.
Bet you don't have many more for like a month.
Every time I started my stream, I got hiccups.
It was uncanny.
Like stream start hiccups weird.
All right.
So which one do you want to do?
That's one on the left.
I don't remember which one this one is.
There's one that's awful.
And it literally is just a tiny little part of knock Ron.
That's one crystal night and it's awful.
Yeah, I think that's the one to our left right now
because I remember fighting that guy a lot.
I think I had to go back through that portal every time.
We didn't do the Lake of Rod.
No, that's another underground area we haven't been to.
Oh, it's the chapel.
It's a chapel.
Oh, your host.
You can see it.
You get to have the you get to see the movie before I do.
Yeah, I'm in the movie theater already.
What was this in the very beginning?
Um, I I was like a berserker.
Ah, it was.
I'm just I'm just spamming L1.
Okay, we're good.
It's a bunch of items.
Okay.
So I got I got Twiggy cracked here.
That sounds like the name of some fucked up YouTube channel.
Uh, we go back into the church, right?
Isn't this a way to get up and walk around and look around, right?
And I don't think there's anything else here.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Come over here.
I remember this up in here.
They say, um, there's a spot.
Did you have you?
Did you ever come back here?
Yeah, there's a spot up here.
I think on the ledge where you have to jump from it.
I think that kind of hurt my feelings.
I think we actually can get up in the church, though.
Yeah, but there's no reason to.
Who cares?
But there's items, this random stuff.
It could be a Lord's rune.
You don't know.
Oh, my God.
Who cares?
I do.
Now, how do you get to the road route from the Capitol?
Like you go, you just there's a what?
Wait, why is she?
Why is she alive?
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Oh, yeah.
Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah.
There's an is let me just see if it's a legendary.
Oh, is it?
I don't know.
It's in a chest.
It could be a legendary.
She's like the mushrooms growing out of her fucking head.
Yes, I know.
I know.
But look, letter from volcano manner.
That's why you come up here.
That's why you explore.
Now we can do right card.
I have that.
I mentioned it earlier and I said, I don't remember.
I got letter from volcano manner.
I don't know if we needed that or not.
Oh, it was like an hour ago.
Well, let's.
OK, you did write card.
That wasn't right card.
Now, that wasn't the real right card.
OK, so you want to write card, then we could give her letters and shit.
Yeah, let's see what's down there might as well.
We're going to hit a point here very soon where we're going to unlock the giant area.
We're going to do the giant and then we can just end the game.
You need the thing to burn in the bowl.
I think you need like an ember or something.
I think you just need.
I think you just need a certain millennia.
I think you just need her up there.
You sit at the bonfire up in the big crucible thing.
I don't think you need an item.
All right.
And then the letter over.
Join.
Thank you.
OK, so now we have to go do an invasion, right?
Wait, we're going to get a different item every time we do this.
There may be some flaws to the plan.
I have two of them.
I have I have I lay the idol and I have great horn to drag off.
I don't know the words you're saying.
Go into your where the letter is because there's three letters.
Who are you?
What does your letter say?
The letter you have the assassination missions are optional for right card.
I can't find it.
But so then how do we get down to right card if we have?
I thought you did those three and they're like, oh, yes, you can go talk to our lord.
I have the red letter.
I don't know how I it's past millennia.
Juno Haslow, Knight of Blood.
All right.
So wait, I have the other two.
There's only three, right?
Well, then also that enemy is going to be randomized.
Oh, yeah, that's true.
Let's make our way up the road route.
Let's make our way.
All right.
East East Capitol Rampart or Capitol Rampart.
Which one of these?
I think you have to do the Avenue balcony and then run down the road.
I think you're right.
Yes.
No, you're right.
Because you open you open the door and you walk through.
Just kill millennia forehead.
Who?
Check your your physique tears.
Feels OK, man.
Chat just wants you guys to get mad at millennia.
Yeah.
You guys want us to go there and get stuck for four hours.
And like us make a bunch of cartoon sound effects.
And me to bite my mic stand and like smash my face to my microphone.
Yeah. And don't like bite my lips so hard that my lip bleeds a little bit.
That way.
Do we have to like jump off the edge over here?
Probably is a is a path that has it's the path that has the urge tree avatar on it.
Yeah, this is it's coming.
Are you sure it's not going to come with me?
I'll come with me.
No, come on.
No, come with me.
I think you can jump down.
Yeah.
No, come with me.
Yeah, I guess I'm doing I'll look in a minute once you get to a better spot.
Other way.
Well, what you make a decision here.
Oh, I didn't see you actually followed me.
Now you use your run speed ninjutsu.
We just have to go to the big door at the end, right?
Yes. So Andy, I like that was you need did you need somersmithing stone sevens?
I don't know what I need.
What is that?
What is this is the this is the wrong door.
Oh, it's another dragon.
This dragon so badly wants to get over.
No, no, it's this one because then we go up and wrap around.
This is like this.
Yeah, that's it.
I think now.
Yeah, this is definitely it.
OK, smash, smash, watch out.
Watch out.
We got a bleeder.
You know what one of my favorite sound effects is in all video games?
I don't.
It was when ever you got a double dunk from that like it was like a crit sound.
It was like it was the best sound effect in gaming.
And if you got more than one, if you did twice in a row, you'd be like,
something weird about seeing my wife type in all caps based,
like the streams have been having an effect on her
because she wouldn't have said that like a week ago.
Based.
What's wrong?
Now she just says, oh, with a crying face.
Now, I don't know.
She's in trouble.
And then she says, make it rain.
I make it rain.
It's just to get out of any conversation.
Make it rain.
I thought you died your hair.
What?
Don't kill him.
He's a musician.
All right.
I won't.
I bounced.
Kill him.
He's a musician.
All right.
Play us a song then.
Play us a song.
Oh, that's a hit.
Help.
What?
It's a magician.
Hold on.
Let me get the double dunk.
Nope.
Hey, play us up.
Roxanne.
You know, Roxanne.
Can you do that one?
Oh, that was pretty good.
No, please.
What's the highest minus a chatter can give you?
Like if they do a plus two or minus two,
when have you done something so awful
that they're allowed to be like minus 10?
It doesn't count.
It's it was it's either good or bad.
It's not like super good or super bad.
It's just it was that good or bad.
That's it.
Oh, mega dung beetle.
I don't know.
I don't want to kill this.
Oh, but you'll kill the musician.
The guy's just out there playing for tips.
No, there's no plus one or minus one.
It's always two.
Why is it always two?
I don't know because it's supposed to be
the amount of minutes to add or subtract.
Do you even know the lore?
I don't.
That's why I'm asking.
It's Alex and I.
We played Kane and Lynch.
This is the bridge, by the way.
Oh, let's do it.
I always honestly thought that plus two minus two.
Wait, where does this one this bridge?
I always thought plus two minus two was a Sims reference
because when you like your Sim has an interaction
that they do or don't like,
but you can get like the minus two.
Like, I don't I don't like what he's saying.
No, it was italics.
And I did a stream one time where we were like,
let's try to beat Kane and Lynch in one sitting.
The game is like three and a half hours
or four and a half hours long.
It's a very short game because it's the second one.
And we set up this thing.
Well, wait a minute.
What if we gave it a time limit for us
where we had to beat the game in two hours or something
or three hours.
But every time we made a good joke,
chat could add two minutes to the timer
or they could subtract two minutes from the timer.
Right. Okay.
So depending on how funny we were,
we got to have more time to beat the game.
And it actually turned out to be we we ended up
at the last cut scene of the game,
I think with less than two or three minutes left.
That's a plus two.
I liked it better when I thought it was The Sims.
I'm just sorry pretending as that.
Yeah. And we eventually,
once we had less than 20 minutes left,
we started getting kind of desperate
and the jokes were awful.
And we were losing time.
Is it a hidden room here?
Yeah, there is.
I did see it.
It was down at the bottom.
I don't think I've ever been in that hidden room.
I'd like to make it a point that when we come back,
we go to that hidden room.
This might break both of our games.
I don't think so.
It's just the Four Lords fight from Dark Souls 1.
Is it a dog?
Is it a single dog?
It's a dead guy.
It's a dead guy?
Why was it?
I don't know.
I've just been waiting for someone to fight me so long.
I died.
El Misbegotten Crusader.
And I got Hora Lou's Earth Shatter.
Earth Shaker.
Man.
What weapon is he holding?
Oh, they're usually two?
Yeah.
There's the dead guy in this guy.
That weapon is so cool looking.
That weapon is...
What weapon is that thing?
That's like the Elden Beast Remembrance.
Holy shit.
That thing is so fucking cool.
That's the coolest weapon in the game.
I've never seen that.
Isn't that the one that shoots like a gigantic super...
What the fuck?
I want this.
Hope he drops it.
It's the Golden Order Greatsword.
That thing is so cool.
Oh, time for Terma to change builds.
No.
That thing is awesome.
Scales great with Faith.
You have it in your inventory, bro.
I don't have it.
No, I don't.
You have to look now.
I don't.
I'm telling you, that sword is very distinct looking.
I do not have it in my inventory.
I have the Glintstone Chris.
Oh, you got Chris?
No, I don't have this weapon.
You guys are full of shit.
No.
I'm going to level up.
It's the Faith version of the Moonlit Greatsword.
So I'll give you a cool build.
Moonlit Greatsword one hand.
Golden Order Greatsword on the other hand.
Sun.
Moon.
Oh, that's pretty cool.
The sun and moon conjoined.
Bat Chest me all you want.
That's what I'm doing on my next playthrough.
The Eclipse build.
Yeah, and I would wear really dark armor.
So it's like the sun and the moon eclipsing into each other.
Come on.
Do you identify as the darkness or the light?
Bro, you would need to be level 200 to even attempt that.
That's all right.
Mog's Greatrun.
I also got Mog's Greatrun.
Weird.
I think they're just here.
Oh, wait a minute.
Because you also had the thing?
No, I didn't.
Dude, I think they're just up here.
You can just pick them up.
Wasn't that the great rune that you heal when you hit things?
Yeah, but are you understanding that I think we could have just
come to two of these towers and gotten these?
I think you can just pick them up off the ground.
I think the randomizer just puts them here because I didn't have that.
I had the unborn one.
Well, yeah, that's millennials.
What does Mog's do?
Something about blood.
Blessing of blood.
Yeah, I don't know.
All right.
Are you ready to go to the Forbidden Lands?
No, I want it to go down that elevator.
So yeah, Forbidden Lands.
And then I want to go in the elevator and do the secret room.
Yeah, I'll do the blast in a second.
I'm going to mark these because I know we'll forget.
Okay.
You're gonna tell a joke?
I think I saw it on the right when we were going up.
I think because we missed.
Oh, it's right there.
They're right in front of us.
Straight forward.
You see it?
You look up.
Yeah.
Okay.
We're going in there.
I forget what's in here.
I've never been in here.
Five dragon hearts?
How many of these do I have?
Yo, bruh.
Yo, I have 11 dragon hearts.
I could probably just go buy up the whole store.
Let's go to, you know, there's the dragon heart place on the first island.
And that like near the starter area.
Yeah.
Let's go there.
Okay.
We need to it's right over here.
It's like down on the beach.
The entrance.
I think we just go to the first step, right?
Because it's right here.
Yeah.
Do the one in Caleb.
The bigger one is in Caleb.
We've been there.
Yeah, we've already been there.
And it sold a lot of good things.
So I'm assuming this one will also sell good things.
This one will be different too, right?
Yeah.
It's doing that thing.
Really is doing that thing.
We haven't had like crashes today or a lot of disconnecting.
It's been better.
Just the voting to warp sometimes.
This is the best mod.
This really is.
It's just so good.
I just can't.
I can't believe.
I can't believe it's just, you know what I mean?
I can't believe I know what you mean.
Are you drinking pickle juice?
No.
We never killed this slob right in the beginning.
When are you going to do a face reveal?
What if I just went like there's a clay coming off
and like I pulled my nose down.
Clay, clay.
And it was I was a different face under here.
It's the same face.
Just kind of very slightly different.
Oh, this is the rock one.
I can't lock on again.
All right.
Would you laugh if one of the best items in the whole game dropped right here?
And you could have had it at the very beginning.
I would laugh.
A crystal tear.
I don't even.
Strength, not crystal tear.
What are my opinions on Pilk?
Jesus.
I read that too fast.
Other way.
Friend.
Other way, friend.
Traveling to the beach.
This is our beach episode.
The beach episode.
Oh, there's one of the invisible squigglies.
Can you still do your magma jump?
I cannot, but sorry.
I mean, you should still have that in your inventory.
I don't think I don't have any faith to use it though.
Most of these are very simple.
Just some of them are just annoying.
I'll get it right here.
That was so close.
Like that was literally a frame.
Yeah, there we go.
All right.
Crash.
So how do we get over there?
We need to go this way.
It's like a weird teleporter or something, isn't it?
No.
Oh, you know, you can just walk.
You can just walk.
There's a cave that goes under.
You got to go in the cave and battle the dwellers of the deep.
Oh, the buck cave.
Yeah, that's true.
Yeah.
Amadeus is in there.
Big hand boss.
Just hanging out over here.
There's a merchant up here.
I'm going to go see if he's got any cool items.
I would, you know, it'd be more disappointing to see if this guy actually was selling like
something ridiculous.
Yeah.
I mean, he does sell smithing stone 456 for me.
I think I was going to buy like a million of these.
Rose and needle.
What is this thing?
That's a fun weapon.
I think it's a rapier that like shoots a ice projectile.
I'm going to buy it and I'm going to buy a hundred and four of these.
Of what?
I have like little poison things now.
Hold on.
Okay, that sounds really cool.
That sounds incredible.
They scale with strength.
I'm going to kill him while you're talking.
Don't.
This guy has awesome shit for me.
Don't do it.
Why?
Oh, yeah, I can take the better the bell bearing.
Why do you want to?
Why do you want to kill these guys?
What's wrong with you?
I don't.
I just want to go in the cave.
It's holding you up.
I know, but I need to put this on my bar because now I have
I have like 200 fucking poison like darts.
I got 200 poison snowballs.
Oh, watch out.
It's pretty dark down here.
Now all merchants are hostile.
Okay.
That's like that's cute.
They think they think they can take us.
All right.
What do I got here?
Boys charged attacks.
What?
This guy's on the ground dying and he's like, oh, they're going to kill me.
I'm like, here have a golden sewing needle.
Does that make this better?
I kind of don't want to take anything off.
Good.
Now you stop complaining.
I think I'm all right now.
Don't I have the needle?
I gave it to him.
Oh, okay.
Okay.
I mean, it's kind of embarrassing.
There's like a really low level zone for him to be dying in.
All right.
Test these to see if this is worth be spending like 20,000 souls.
Don't kill the guy over there.
What the hell?
This is like a fucking mess.
I don't know what just happened.
A swift glint stone shard.
I know I don't do magic, but that's pretty good one.
What the fuck?
Where are they?
Oh, shit trio.
That's kind of funny because there's normally like a bunch of guys here.
These guys are so parryable by the way.
Mr. Perry.
Yeah.
I don't have like my weapon doesn't really hurt them.
Oh, I don't I don't have a parry shield.
The other one's just like spinning in the corner.
She gave me scarlet rot.
Yep.
Please hold.
Break.
Do the noise.
Oh, you mean that?
Yeah, I don't know how I hurt them.
It's pretty much you have to parry them or use one.
That's what I mean.
I don't put on a parry shield, but now this one is unparryable.
It's kind of like a you like this is like where your character art starts to shine.
I'm doing pretty well.
I think you can hurt them now.
I think once like they get like broken up or something.
Yeah.
Oh, commoners headband.
Sombra ancient dragon smithing stone.
Oh, I got an ant skull shield.
That's kind of weird.
Ant skull plate.
Look at this thing.
No, look at this thing.
Look at where this is.
No, no.
Come here where I'm trying to go to the dragon temple.
I won't look at it.
I won't look.
Don't exit.
They put that there to trick you like having blinked in a while.
Give it a try.
Okay.
Great stars.
Ooh, don't kill it.
Dude, come on.
I don't think we could have walked by.
He could jump over his legs.
Isn't there an invasion here too?
Yeah, maybe.
I didn't.
Oh, no.
All right.
Hey guys, mind if I invade you?
That's like my favorite animal in Elden Ring.
Why did I do that?
Yeah, it's kind of suck.
Elden stars.
Great heal.
I mean, I feel like I should just get it.
I don't buy like 11 of these.
Buy everything.
You can sell Jerma anything.
Just put it in front of him.
I mean, this is the only place you can spend this currency.
I have 11 of them and I can't spend it anywhere else.
So might as well get it.
You make a good point.
I forgot that they're like selling these based on like made up currency.
It is just a made up currency.
It's not runes.
It's just dragon hearts, which I have a ton of.
And there's only six items in the game.
I have 11 hearts.
I have a four or at least four or five surplus of hearts.
I have one.
OK, so we're going to the we're going to the.
This area is too blue.
I wish they would redo it.
Hey, how do you go down to?
You know, we're all like the scarlet rot swamp is.
Yes.
Where is that entrance?
It's underground.
It's part of the quest line for Ronnie.
And from my understanding, you need to go there from not wrong.
Almost just walked off the edge looking at chat in my fault.
I don't know why I'm following you.
I know where I'm going.
Where are you going?
We should get that.
We got to get the map.
I know where I'm going.
That old man had it coming.
Jesus, I make like a jump scare noise for you.
No, it's just kind of right in my face.
Like when he attacked, it was like, um, uh,
I think that's like the you are going to get knocked off your horse sound.
The first mark of death.
Oh, I think that's the thing to do the boss with via, isn't it?
I think I have that.
My cat was telling me we could do that earlier.
And then I said, cool, we did some else.
Don't even do this to me.
Oh, that's right.
These things, these dumb beetles don't give anything.
Uh, boss man.
Yeah, so there's usually a, um, some of those, um,
I get the wave, you spin it around.
They look like a gargoyle.
Now, what a fool I am.
I hit him in his elbow, but he has elbow guards on.
That was actually really dumb.
Oops.
You want to end it?
Go for it.
And twist.
God, I'm so freaking cool.
Oh my God.
72,000.
Very good.
Map fragment is right here.
Up over this.
Let us gamble.
There's no time to gamble when we just destroy it really quickly.
It's like a little map.
I need to level up.
Is 45 enough?
I should have do 50.
45 is not enough.
Do what they say.
Is, isn't there a, is the, what's the cap for, um, for vigor?
Is it 60?
Oh, that's right.
I keep forgetting.
I thought it was, I keep thinking that's 40.
Do what they say.
I did.
Come on.
60 is the true cap.
Who do you think is going to be in the Giants area?
Uh, how could I possibly know the answer to that question?
I think it's going to be an ulcerated tree spirit.
You say that for every single one.
And one of these times it's going to be right.
Oh, he knew, he knew.
It's Radon.
I'm going to say Radon every time because we still haven't seen him.
That's right.
It could be Radon.
If it is Radon, that's actually not good.
It's going to be a super scaled Radon.
This guy's covering his face because of how ugly he is.
Oh, he ruined it.
Oh, yeah.
Our clothing is different.
His head's like a mushroom fungus for me.
His head is still covered in mine too.
Oh wait, he goes, let chaos take the world.
This guy's messed up.
I say we take him out.
Hold on.
May chaos take.
There it is.
He said it.
Okay.
Is there a maybe a boss down here?
Where is it?
I don't know.
Oh, smithing stone seven.
Yes.
That means you can upgrade one of these.
Here's the hole.
Open it, peasant.
What's in here?
Come on.
What is it?
Smithing stone seven.
Somber smithing stone nine.
I need that.
You want it?
Yeah.
I can even.
Somber smithing stone nine is on the ground.
That's fantastic news.
I don't know what killed him, but he died.
Kill chaos guy.
Oh, you picked on the two Elden Lord wannabes.
The two you picked on the wrong.
You're out.
You are.
Let's go.
Let's just get this leave.
He's going to hit me.
I'll be back when I become Hokage.
You need to kill the.
Get out of the way.
Okay.
All right.
There's a dungeon down there, but there's also.
Do we have to do that awful, awful village where you run away?
It's hopefully it's random enemies.
But that's a isn't that how you get to the pallet tree?
Yeah, we ain't doing that.
I don't know if it's random enemies.
They're not.
Wait, if they're invisible still, they might.
It was randomly invisible enemies that could be even worse.
I don't know if it could be any worse than something like insta backstabbing you.
Yeah, it's true.
That's true.
They're not invisible.
You get like machine gun archers that are all on the roof.
Why would I get Botox?
Why would I get Botox for any reason?
I don't know.
It's called when you get out of the shower.
Moisturize your god damn face.
Do you moisturize when you get out?
Do you moisturize your face?
Immediately.
Right.
Do you know?
Do you actually?
I'm an avid moisturizer these days.
You very much.
Dry as heck out here.
Oh, and you're in Vegas, which I think you've been lying about, to be honest.
I just don't live here.
Yeah, I was just thinking yesterday about how...
I live in Kansas.
I was like, oh, yeah, like E3.
No, not E3.
Evo was coming.
I was like, yeah, I want to go out to Vegas.
And then I'm like, wait, I'm going to realize German doesn't actually live out there.
And he's been lying.
He's like in Europe.
That seems like something you would do.
Awfully quiet.
A couple items.
All right, dude, I keep getting spitting stone sevens.
The game knows what I want.
Well, if I was in EU, I think that all the EU viewers right now are like, nah,
nah, that's fucking not happening.
Because it's like 4 a.m. every time I turn the stream on.
That would be really strange.
I think stone seven again.
Smithing stone seven again.
Dude.
What's the odds of that actually happening, though?
What's the odds that actually happening?
That's pretty low.
Watch out, we got a bong boy.
Oh, stung beetle.
Founding Reign of Stars, mate.
Do you want to try it?
I have it already.
Founding Reign of Stars.
Yo, I also got it from that.
What are the odds of that?
Where'd you go?
Yeah, yeah.
We're going to have to do a starlight kid.
We're going to do a crap session.
A craft.
I can like upgrade my moon veil and I think I can upgrade one of your swords.
I thought you were like, hey, man, we got to really do like a crap session.
We're going to have the craps table.
I come down to Vegas.
We hit up the craps, man.
I can talk to millennial.
You can talk to millennia.
Mm hmm.
She's rent free in your head.
I've said I forgot.
No.
Yeah, you want to go to upgrade your weapon?
You just want to keep going.
Let's go through.
Let's get past the giant.
Because then once we beat giant and we burn the tree,
we kind of can decide when we want to end our playthrough.
You know what I mean?
Because after the giant, it's like, all right, what else do you really want to do?
Because we can then go right to the ear tree.
I think you just want to burn a bowl.
Hey, left or right, man?
I want the map fragment.
That would be so awful.
It's too nice, man, on horseback coming our way.
Imagine getting hit in both of your ears at the same time.
With two big ass weapons.
What is that?
I can imagine.
I've been clapped.
Have you been clapped?
Why is that on the ground?
Oh, wait, this is where you fight one of the invaders.
I can't get off the horse.
Isn't this where you fight one of the manor people?
You fight somebody from the manor here, don't you?
I don't know.
Well, I'm asking Chad.
Yeah, I have his letter.
Am I the invader?
Oh.
Watch out.
Wait, what?
Wait, hey.
Not cool.
Behind you.
I wasn't ready.
Why am I fat rolling?
I've been working with him the whole time.
Just to get you on stream, to get you here.
So we can finally, once and for all, prove to Strippin
that you're not a fucking gamer.
Strippin, let's go.
Strippin, what are you doing?
Get out of here.
I don't even know what I'm swinging at.
I feel like you still want to kill me.
Well, fine.
Fuck you.
I'll bring my own friend.
Oh, I can't.
Fuck you.
Hey, try to get a parry.
Try to get a parry.
I tried.
Ready?
It teleported me out already.
What did we even get from that?
A funny moment where we could fight each other for a minute.
Or even in the same game anymore.
I don't know.
I think that actually did break the co-op.
Because you were an invader.
Oh, I know.
Yeah.
It was for fun.
It was a funny stream moment.
And nobody won.
Actually, I think I can level up.
Wait, isn't there a...
Okay, while you rejoin, I have a quick pee-pee time.
Okay.
Okay, I think I'm stuck in limbo here.
I have to restart.
All right, yeah, we'll just do another pee break.
We'll be right back.
I'm going to restart.
Uh-oh.
I'm not really sure what to do about this.
I think I'm still in his game.
I'm ready to die.
There we go.
Wait, but am I still in his game?
No, I can't even touch the bonfires.
I have to alt-F4.
Wait.
Why?
What happened?
I'm going to lose 50,000 souls.
But I have to...
I can't even quit the game.
I have to alt-F4.
Separation missed?
I don't think I can...
I just tried to banish you if you were...
Oh, there we go.
Okay.
I think I'm good.
No.
Yeah, I got to re...
Wait.
Hold on.
I've opened my world.
I think I closed it by accident.
I think that's going to work now.
Yes.
Okay.
All right.
Did you pee?
Yeah.
All right.
It was great.
I did, too.
Did you want to buy a castle in Scotland
and we could live there together?
No.
Okay.
Oh, I got items from him dying.
We got the jump over there.
I don't know where the jumpy go.
Isn't there a bonfire right here?
Yeah.
Let's just get on our horses
right along the countryside.
Don't get me wrong.
I bet I've never been to Scotland.
Sounds...
It sounds beautiful.
It sounds like an incredible place.
But...
It's me that's the problem.
I just...
I don't know.
I feel like a bot.
No, there's no bot.
It's just like, I don't know.
I don't really know Scotland.
I like...
It feels like you're really trying to justify
not buying a castle in Scotland,
but like you...
I mean like...
I don't know.
I got to be so nice about it.
Like, no, I don't want to live
in a castle in Scotland.
Okay?
There you go.
That's the whole statement.
I don't need any more statements.
I thought that star...
Where did you go?
I was freaking out.
Oh, so we got to kill it.
Wait, what is...
I don't...
This jellyfish is underage?
What?
What are you looking at?
There's a jellyfish here
and it's like talking.
You don't see it?
No.
This gel...
No, but your chat's question marking.
The jellyfish was like...
You said when we were 14,
we'd go visit the stars.
There's an underage jellyfish here.
Not making shit up.
Don't you have to...
Wait.
Okay.
Wait, this is...
You have to give the...
Are you killing?
You...
It's gone.
That's...
I'm just saying
you killed the jellyfish
and I think that that's worse
than if you killed the turtle.
Like, I think your chat
probably is freaking out right now.
You can't prove that I killed it
because you couldn't even see it.
Pork brain.
Yeah, that's raw pork brain,
I think.
All right.
Let's keep going.
Let's get out of here.
Man, I am patient zero.
You're going to hear about me on the news.
Yeah, this is going to be...
This is going to be like a huge Reddit thread.
Like, wait, why would he have done that?
Would he eat pork
that was in a backpack for a day?
That's where COVID came from.
Was it a bet?
Why did he do that?
That seems insane to me.
It's Mithingstone 7 again.
Not me.
And then there'll be like buried down
in the thread.
There'll be somebody like,
I don't understand what the big deal is.
I've eaten that before
and I felt fucking fine.
It's got like minus 200 fucking downvotes.
I love scrolling to the bottom
and showing like seeing
the like controversial takes.
I love it.
Who?
Oh, okay.
You just hooted him?
He just looked a little lost.
Hey, Sturd, do you want to know
about my playthrough lore for me?
Your playthrough lore?
Yeah.
I first tried this boss
when I was probably 20
to 30 levels too early finding it.
I never found this boss.
Praise me.
There's like you fight one of these
in a basement somewhere.
Yeah.
I kept seeing people on streams fight it
and I was like, where the fuck is this?
I still don't know.
This is like an ice dragon out here, right?
Okay.
For a second, I thought I thought
all of his clothes just came off.
They kind of did.
That was fun.
I thought I got away.
You thought wrong.
I was just mashing L1.
I just didn't want to even fight this thing.
So you're like bored of Elden Ring.
You want to stop.
We're not playing tomorrow.
Can we just please go straight to Elden Beast?
Can we just end this already?
No, that's not what I said.
Yeah, I don't even want to fight this.
I'm just gonna let him kill me
because I like don't even want to fight this.
I'm just like so over this.
Dude, why are you blinding me?
Cowardly tactics.
Dude, you got the mod
that every time you get hit it does that
to like fuck with you.
He's gonna kill me.
You're good.
Would you smoke a blunt
with the godskin apostle?
No, no, no way.
This is the type you smoke a blunt
with this motherfucker
and they start like talking about wacky shit.
Like, hey, do you think that we should like ever,
you know, like, like,
I think we're gonna live on the moon.
It's like, I don't think,
I don't know about that.
Yeah, when they sign people up
to go live on the moon,
I'll be the first one.
I love that you're quoting
a real conversation that we had with the one we did.
Don't remember.
We had like a taxi driver.
I mean, we're leaving Seattle
from like past west.
This is a real thing.
This is a real bit, dude.
Hey, I got an ancient,
ancient dragon smithing stone, by the way.
You were looking for one of those.
This guy was talking about
sending all of the prisoners
from earth to the moon to colonize it,
just like Australia.
We were in a 30 minute conversation
with this guy.
What?
I don't remember any of this.
What the fuck?
He's no, we didn't smoke a blunt
with our taxi driver.
No, no, no, no.
He's just years ago.
I don't know.
Where are you sure it was you?
I don't know who else would be there with me.
Can you set it a bonfire?
Like enough time has gone by
that you don't think that guy's crazy anymore.
You came up with that idea.
I'm like, wait, what?
What's weird about that?
I was describing it
as if it was very weird
because I didn't want to smoke a blunt
with the godskin apostle
because he was going to start talking
about weird shit like that.
I was describing how it was weird.
Okay.
Where's there's bonfire?
I don't know.
It was the godskin apostle.
I don't know where I am.
Yeah.
And it's like somebody cut us off
and he did like they got in front of us
and they were like four cars in front of us
and he did like the fucking weird
gumby snake move went out of his window
and went in front of the guy's car
and gave the double middle finger to him.
Like in his windshield, like in front of him.
Then he went, he came back in the window
and he was like, sorry about that.
It's weird.
You don't remember any of this until now.
Yeah.
It's weird that I didn't remember that
till right now.
You just want to watch me run around on a horse?
You should live on the moon.
No, I'm serious.
It's like I need direction.
Yeah, we should definitely go live on the moon.
Yeah, dude, we should.
I'm serious about this.
Okay.
I can't look at my map.
I have to wait till
am I going to just show up where I died?
I see one.
Jerma, you would definitely want to go move to a castle
on the moon with stir
and you guys would make it rain
and you'd be able to, like a boss,
be able to do where is that we're going with this?
Every day in our content castle.
It's every day, bro.
I wouldn't want to live in a content castle
because you know what would happen?
One of us would be loud
and it would just bounce off of every wall in the castle
and it would be un-fucking-bearable.
You'd hear yourself for a week.
It would just be like,
it'd be like, I can't fucking stand it.
All these like stone walls, whatever the hell it is.
Okay.
I need to, where are you?
At the bonfire.
I went across the bridge to the bonfire.
Where the fuck are you?
Find a warfare.
I need my souls though.
It was like 140,000.
There was a lot of souls.
I'll bet you teleported anyway.
Well, I think it's closed.
Whatever.
Would you smoke a blunt with Peter Griffin?
You asking?
I mean, I'm just bringing it up.
Somebody brought it up.
Okay.
I mean, well, hold on.
Is Peter Griffin in my house?
Like, is it like, okay, we're like hanging out at my place?
Because the answer is no.
Because Peter will probably be like,
oh yeah, so I can like stay here now.
I'll be here for like a few weeks.
Like, no.
Uh-oh.
Where did you go?
I'm trying to like show you where your souls are.
Stay here overnight.
You gotta go.
My souls are by that urn tree.
Yes.
Across the bridge.
You have to go across the bridge.
Are you checking out?
Peter, you can...
No, I'm fine.
Peter, you can stay on the futon tonight,
but then like you gotta get the fuck out of here.
Why is the godskin apostle back?
Is he?
Yeah.
I don't see him.
You don't see the apostle?
No.
I see you dealing damage to invisible nothing.
This is weird.
All right, well, get your runes.
And then we're going to go somewhere else.
All right, let's get out of here quick.
I'm not saying I couldn't handle it.
I just don't want to handle it.
You don't want to handle Peter Griffin.
Yeah, two weeks later, he's in his underwear with a 12-pack on your front.
That's what I mean.
And then he would like request really specific snacks, right?
And he'd be like, god damn it, Peter Griffin family guy shit.
He'd be like, hey, remember those slim jims that were spicy back in the 90s?
You gotta go find me some of those.
And it's like, oh, he's making a reference to something old.
Wow.
That's something you would never do.
Yeah.
Can you even go make maybe some clam chowder?
Peter, that takes all day.
No, he's crashing at our castle in Scotland.
OK, we need to go.
I need to sit down on the bonfire.
I think we went backwards.
I don't.
I'm lost.
This is definitely backwards.
We need to go.
We were.
All right, let me let me go spend these, please.
Sit down.
Let me spend it.
We did a full circle.
Well, we were talking that happened.
Well, let's let's teleport to the ancient snow valley,
worm runes or some teleport somewhere where it's it's right here.
Teleporting the loading screen would take longer for us just to walk here.
I didn't know it was right here.
Come on, man.
Wait, hold on a second.
Wait, what?
Hold on.
Wait, it's underneath us.
Oh, turns out it wasn't right here.
Someone's got an egg face, egg face.
The correct way to go is I forget the correct way to go.
There's a mogul like where's the big crucible thing?
That's the direction we need to go that way.
I think.
Wait, isn't there a teleporter here?
There's a teleporter down somewhere like right around here, isn't there?
I don't remember.
It definitely is not here.
Okay, we got to go that way that way.
I found the big cup.
Follow me.
I am going to you.
Yep.
There's the big yes, commander.
You're the smoke of one with Homer.
No, I'd rather smoke a blunt with Marge like Marge would be way chiller.
I just got half health.
Where did this guy come from?
What was he following us?
He's invisible to me.
This is all you.
Never mind.
He got full health again.
All right, we got to let's we got to go.
Can we make this jump?
No way.
All the way around.
I'm going down.
No, no, no, no, don't.
I can't.
I'm already committed.
You've committed already.
Are you serious, dude?
There's no way back up.
What do you mean?
You went can't fucking jump up a cliff.
We need to go that way.
Tell me where I need to go again.
You're going to find my hands in your jaw.
In like, yeah.
What do you?
Yeah, like I'm going to put my hand in your mouth.
Is he going the wrong way?
He's not going the right way, is he?
I don't know.
He's going the right way.
We just went in circles for like 20 minutes.
I just figured anywhere else.
I'm going to fucking die trying to do what you just did.
There's a there's a thing up here.
You can teleport to me if you dare.
Let me prove that I can do this.
Yeah, and then this is the giant frozen lake
and you go across and then the dragon's like.
Well, thanks to you, I lost like 4000 viewers, by the way,
because of shit like that because because of me.
Oh, well, guess what?
They all came over here.
You're doing like Peter Griffin impression traders because of you.
All right.
Thank God I can level up.
Can somebody help me?
Why can I?
Why did I lose access to leveling?
I don't know.
That doesn't sound right.
Maybe stuff still messed up for when you were an invader.
I think I think my game is a little messed up.
Delete it.
I have I cannot level up, so I'm just going to restart.
I'm going to restart the game.
I'm banishing.
Yeah, you know what?
No, don't even I'm just going to quit.
I'm going to exit.
I can't even exit the game.
It's been a problem ever since.
OK, all right.
Did you banish?
Yeah, all right.
For some reason, it doesn't let you exit the game if you're in co-op.
It really doesn't like the fact that I was an invader.
I think it broke it.
There it is.
OK, let me.
Why am I just leveling up?
OK, can you put the thing down again?
All right.
Come on, I need to get to 58.
Come on.
Dude, you have star muted.
I wouldn't be surprised.
He's got to learn that he has to his behavior has to improve.
Wait in line.
I am not you're not muted.
I'm just trying to level up in case it happens again.
Is your thing?
I'm using maybe it's messed up because it's not Monday
and we were supposed to play on Monday.
Shit.
That's right.
All right.
Is your thing down?
Yeah.
Let's see what the dragon is.
I don't know if we can find it.
I don't because normally this area would turn into like a mist.
I think we have to actually walk over here.
Hit him.
Hit him again.
Keep hitting him.
It is the dragon.
I think it's just the ice dragon going to fight it.
Guess we have to.
Maybe it's a different dragon.
I can't see anything.
Is this the right one?
Dula?
No.
Oh, I do love mercy on the poor boss.
I got stuff growing on them.
Oh, what?
Oh, we fell down.
Oh, very cool.
Damn.
That's another hundred and twenty five K.
You're for a storm.
What a thematically appropriate.
I didn't bring the drop.
We could definitely be millennia.
Maybe I actually have three times the HP I did when we were trying it.
I want my swords to be leveled up another once two or three times.
I want to get them to at least plus 20 before we do that.
OK, so earlier when I said let's go do some like leveling up
because we've got a whole bunch of Smith's stones and you said no.
Was that so that we wouldn't have to fight millennia?
No.
Right after that, I was like, no, you know what?
Let's get out of here.
You got another ancient.
I have two ancient dragon spinning stones.
Do you want me just to give them to you?
Sure.
I'll be your stone master.
Remember to level up.
We just got a lot of room.
And make sure you grab those.
There's two omega items on the ground.
Yeah, I don't want them.
Molina is picking them up.
I'm afraid to sit down because I don't want them to disappear.
Pick them up.
I didn't concern me.
You can put them back down.
I thought you crashed.
And I thought it was going to make you move or something.
Okay.
I got them.
Oh, there's a there's a what the heck?
There's a jail right here.
Let's do it.
Might as well.
In it.
Where is it?
I think up the hill a little bit.
It's normally the pro tag is in here.
In it.
What the hell was that?
Oh, my God.
Assassin.
Well, we just got collateral.
There's your sniper still here.
No, he's gone.
That was that was surprising.
My cat loves watching you.
That's cute.
All right.
The chain.
That guy was big and strong and his muscles were bulging out of his freaking skin.
We're going to go up this way.
There is a bonfire up here.
I thought there was a jail here.
I don't see it.
Are you looking?
I looked.
Do you have eyes?
I mean, I skimmed it.
I scanned it.
Oh, that's right.
There's this place here.
Somebody said we technically did the final assassination mission.
So we should be able to turn that in and just go right to right card.
If you want to be technical about it.
I think stone eight.
OK, I've been waiting for this the whole game is up here.
I can finally get rivers of blood and play my real build.
Forgot about right card.
Yeah.
We did, too.
Don't look down.
All right.
If it's radan, I owe you 20 bucks.
If it's also rated three spirit, you owe me 50 bucks.
OK.
I'm that confident.
And if it's general grievous.
It's general grievous.
Yeah.
There'll be ones back there.
Then we both.
See, I was trying to say grievous, but general grievous is a POE guy.
Oh, you covered for me.
Aaron, here's your cool.
Let me be clear.
All right.
This is not.
The way.
No, it's not.
I was just looking.
I was just taking a peek.
Oh, tarnish mine.
Your peepee is too small.
And they're laying there.
You must grow two inches.
I can see it was bonfire.
Tony said, dude, the vibes are rotten right now.
Are they?
Sorry, I don't think so.
I don't know.
I don't think the vibes are rotten.
It's not this way.
But this way, there's I see like a tree.
Oh, actually worth.
Oh, dude.
It was a good thing.
I went to that tree.
Why?
I actually got for real carrying greatsword this time.
Like, for real.
Not a joke.
Actual carrying greatsword.
You're fucking with me.
What?
No, I'm not.
You got it.
Yeah, dude.
No, you're screwing with me right now.
You're lying.
There's no way you got carrying greatsword.
That's something that you would lie about because that's so unbelievable.
I don't know if I believe you.
We're doing a bit.
Yes.
Oh, Lord, Lord, this guy's got two fingers.
This hand has got two fingers, dude.
He does with the Giants, like cutting their fingers off or something.
And he's got he's got he's got tree stuff growing out of his arm.
He's a tree.
Giants are trees.
Their hands are their brains and stirs right all along.
But why would they why would they be cutting their fingers off?
I wonder.
They aren't.
They are missing a lot of arms.
They're missing the three fingers, aren't they?
Like the bad ones, right?
Yeah, they're missing the bad boys.
Huh, that actually is interesting.
Maybe they're trying to commune with the greater will.
Yeah, maybe that's interesting.
You just unlock some new vibes from me here.
Wow, I saved the vibe.
All right, you ready?
Let's do it.
Yes, am I?
And by the chain.
But let's do it.
We need to go a completely different direction.
But there's an item over here.
No, it's not.
Stinky item.
No, it's right here.
Vibes have been restored.
Yeah, a little.
Oh, yeah, that's right.
It's a little spot right here.
OK, here we go.
What is the boss?
It's through here.
What is it?
We're done.
Do we let let them bet?
Will we go in?
I'll let them bet.
Vote or die.
It's going to be a boat guy.
That would be funny.
We haven't seen a lot of boat guys.
No, our bosses cannot spawn again.
So Melania is in that manor spot permanently.
Same thing with Eldenbeast.
Alaketh, that's right.
That could be bad.
Got a big skull down here.
Guy's looking kind of dead.
All in.
Don't.
Oh, OK, some people are going all in.
This is 20 million channel points.
They're saying we're going to do it.
I'll hold up.
I'm predicting.
Are you voting?
Yeah, you got like two seconds.
I missed it.
OK, here we go.
What is it?
It's Horoloo.
The fire version.
It's phase two Horoloo.
It's the grab hat.
He's going to grab you.
Just run away from him for a second.
He's trying to grab me.
Oh, shit.
He got me.
He just powerbombed me.
Take aggro.
This is actually a pretty funny fight to be on a horse.
I don't even know if he can grab you off your horse.
I think he can.
Let's horse this guy down.
Uh-oh.
Star.
He's going to get you.
This is actually fucking scary.
I feel like I'm playing a horror game.
Why did you just go in?
Why did you do that?
Because it was under the snow and I thought there was a snow buffer.
Oh, no.
So when people are like, my points, they're going to do it.
I think we are.
I can't lock onto him anymore.
So that's not helping.
This white asshole is riding around these horses.
This is so unfair.
He couldn't grab me.
He should have, but he could not.
What the fuck?
I can't lock onto him, dude.
Neither can I.
Oh, shit.
He's doing it.
I'm under the ground.
Oh, he's got me.
He's he's beard.
He's teleported.
He is having trouble.
He's like a hologram.
Oh, we're going to get really cocky here, I think.
And it's going to be a downfall.
Holy shit.
Wow.
I didn't think I would hit me that high up.
Who would program that hitbox?
Fuck hockey.
I just can't lock onto this shit.
Oh, fuck.
All right.
Just hit him one time.
One time.
Hit him one time.
Well, can you?
Sorry, doubters.
It's too bad I didn't get my vote in.
Wait a minute.
There's a no.
Wait, don't pay it out yet.
Don't pay it out yet.
They paid it out.
They scammed everyone.
This is dude.
Is this a mega scam?
Uh oh.
I skipped.
Look, I transformed into a wolf.
That's that would be so lame.
All right.
Look at how scary I am.
Sorry.
I've always acted this wolf.
Oh my god.
That feels a lot of damage.
I have no more healing.
Hey, we got really cocky.
Oh shit.
This is actually kind of bad.
You have to win or you scammed everyone.
You have to win.
I've got some warming stones down.
At least I can't throw more than that far.
Why are you doing like Homer Simpson yells?
Sorry.
Oh shit.
Don't do it.
Sir, it's going to be up to you.
I'm going to be able to hit him one or two more times.
You're going to have to for the guild or something for the guild.
Scam did not happen.
Scam averted.
Sword key for the teleporter.
Oh, nice.
And some battle bearings.
All right.
Let's go smoke a bowl.
Let's go.
I can't.
I can't get on my horse.
I can't either.
That could have gone really, really wrong if that was not that dog.
I think you get you get like canceled.
I think if we didn't kill that.
Like scamming everybody out of channel.
I don't think you recover from that.
All right.
So we're going to burn the tree.
I'm going to go take a pee break because I didn't go when you did.
I'm going to get I'm going to refill my little drink here.
And I'm going to do like a grab a snack.
Okay.
As well.
And then we can assess what we want to do because we've got our Missoula.
Did you walk into the bowl when you played?
You just you just walk into the center.
I don't remember.
No, I don't think so.
I did because it doesn't even look that far down.
And there's like a thing in the middle.
I fell.
I just walked straight in.
Maybe I did.
You did.
I think I remember you saying to me that you also did it back.
I probably did.
All right.
You should probably just do this because I'm imagining your host.
You should just do it.
Yeah.
I mean, like I am the chosen one.
So I don't mean to like be that guy.
But what do I do?
You say, yes, I'd like to burn the tree.
She won't talk to me.
I think as you sat down first, you like took her.
You won't talk to me either.
I think there is an item we need.
I was saying earlier, I think there's like a burn the bush kind of like joint.
We have to do something.
I think we have to do it solo.
Okay.
Yeah.
Just kick me out.
Kick me out.
Go do some actually wait before you kick me out.
I'm going to give you a couple of things.
And I would appreciate it in this time when we're going to bathroom, coming back.
I appreciate if you take all these stones, please shove them up my ass like a baseball.
I would say you probably shouldn't do that.
But I don't know how many you need.
You would need.
So how many plus sevens do you need?
Three.
Just give them all to me, man.
I don't know.
And then I have a couple of plus eights.
Here you go.
So then I would appreciate it if you were to take these and go upgrade the absolute
hell out of them.
I would really appreciate it.
That's a lot.
That's a lot of stones.
Dude, if you guys thought we were pumping that damage,
wait until you see us when we come back from the short break.
See you when we come back from the break.
See you in a minute.
Hello.
Hey, I got some super crunchy pretzels.
I made some naan bread.
And apparently I like let the cut scene play for burning it.
And I put music on and my chat saying it was like an AMV and everything fits so perfectly.
Like scene changes had song changes.
They're like so baffled.
They want me to go back and watch it.
I might be in some trouble here.
No, no, no, I'm all right.
I thought I had mine.
Oh, the IRS doesn't know yet.
You're crunching right in your mic, man.
No, I am.
I'm like pretty far back.
It's pretty loud.
Is it loud?
I'm like, dude, can you hear how far away I am?
You sound a little echoey, but it is like you're crunching right in the mic.
What?
I am like across the room.
I have long observed the lands between.
This world is in undead.
You're a bad boy.
You've been a bad, bad boy.
I'm just sitting back watching Elden Ring and just like crunching on something.
Oh, I was supposed to go upgrade your weapons.
Yeah, you're supposed to do that.
Well, I'm in Faramundana and I got to get a bonfire.
I was.
Hold on.
I would I would say you should go do it, too.
But like I have your weapons.
Yeah, go do that and then go go to Armazilla.
What?
Stop doing it.
I got hit.
That was that was a hit noise.
That was me reacting to getting hit.
Wait, what happened?
Huh?
Oh, I was I'm just I'm just eating.
I I there is an earthquake in my head right now when I chew.
I can't hear anything you're saying.
Is it really that bad?
It sounds like you're eating like a human hand with how many bones are crunching.
Like, dude, this is awful.
Oh, my God.
Drywall tastes a little different today.
It might be about it might be about that time.
It might be about that time.
Sample it.
Let me change your channel to like mukbang.
Ready or awfully quiet.
I don't.
Delicious.
What?
I don't know, man.
I don't know what you're doing.
I don't know what you're on about.
OK, I want another one.
So bad.
All right.
I am at Armazilla.
I'm imagining we should get the first bonfire.
Get the first bonfire and I got both of your swords to plus 25, dude.
You know what that means?
I didn't even want that item.
That means we have to go fight Melania.
Say it.
I know that's what you want to say.
That means we have to go fight Melania.
Where even is the first bonfire?
You got to go past the first group of enemies and it's on the left.
What the fuck was that?
Why did I go?
I'm holding forward.
Why did I go back dodge?
What?
I'm holding forward and going like this.
Why did he go like this?
That's very cringe streamer.
It was.
That was annoying.
OK, I'm ready.
So you want let's go fight Melania.
Go beat Melania first try because we have an insane amount of abilities now.
We have a ton of health.
Should be able to.
Any damage we can probably mitigate it pretty well.
I feel you.
Would you date phase one Melania or phase two?
I hate this character.
Sorry.
OK, we're actually going to go fighter.
OK, I'm ready to join your game.
I forget what waypoint it is now because we can do the other the easier shortcut.
You overclock your gaming system.
I did not.
My room is hot enough already.
I'm opening my world to wanderers.
Thank you.
Going to get the rot.
If you date Melania, you get the rot.
All right, give me my weapons.
I threw them in the fucking volcano.
You're out.
And I win.
They would.
The ref would call the match.
Oh, yeah.
Let's see.
Re 21 301.
Make sure you put some preserving blouses on your hot bar.
You're going to need them.
Look at these.
All right.
Let me do this real quick.
Oh, I'm just going to dump strength.
Need a little bit more.
Oh, you get away from me.
What are you doing that for?
Okay.
He's becoming stronger.
I now am so unbelievably strong.
Are you ready?
Yeah.
Let's go beat Melania.
If we lose, it's because you killed that musician.
To be clear.
Let us bet.
Let them bet.
And how many?
I don't know.
Five.
Five attempts or ten?
In three.
I think we got it in three.
Oh, I don't know if I bet on that.
Well, you're going to get killed by the water foul thing.
You're going to get killed by the water dance thing.
No, shut up.
And then you're going to go.
No, no, no.
We're going to have to restart.
Okay.
That's going to be you in a second.
You're going to get killed.
No, it's not.
You're the you're bad.
You're bad.
I forgot to upgrade my moon veil.
Fuck.
See, it's already an issue.
Well, I was upgrading your things and I got distracted.
I'm probably not even going to use it.
Okay.
Let's go upgrade moon veil.
I it's going to do the thing again where it's not going to lose.
They're so overleveled, but everything scales.
If we lose to her, then we have to do a full playthrough in Genshin Impact.
No, no, dude.
I'm not.
I don't want to agree to that.
That's just like I have nothing against that game.
I just don't.
We lose to her.
Then we have to get to like Masters and League of Legends.
What is what is that's going to take years?
That's going to take months.
I'm sorry.
I just love this joke.
I don't want to play either of them.
I don't I don't either.
Like I've not again.
Should impact is probably pretty fun.
I don't know.
I don't want to play it for like the next six months.
We both have to eat an Arby's euro if we lose.
My moon does plus 10.
Let's go back.
What the fuck are you doing?
Wait, that's weird.
I don't I don't know who upgraded that.
I didn't because I wouldn't want to like upgrade a moon veil.
What it's doing that thing again.
If we don't we don't do it in 10 tries.
We have to both eat an Arby's euro.
I honestly think we'll get it in like three.
You're underestimating how incredibly.
I'm just trying to get like believers to give the doubters money.
Yeah, I don't know if it already passed.
Okay, German beat this game.
I beat this game.
I'm an accomplished gamer.
I shit my pants to win a quick play game in Overwatch.
Like I'm a born again gamer.
Be careful how many times you say that though,
because I feel like that's like your legacy.
If you continue to say that it is that's that.
That turns into legacy if that's continued to be kind of spoken of.
I don't know.
It's fine.
It's it's in my I think it's in my channel information.
Is it really?
It might be.
I'd have to double check.
That's actually really funny.
I'm actually kind of envious that you shit your pants and put it in your bio
because that's I feel like that's actually really funny.
It's the kind of guy I am.
I'll do it.
All right, let's let's go.
Let's do it when when when I'm stuck.
It's fine.
She's on me.
And yeah, I just have I have too much health.
She can't touch me.
I'm untouchable.
Oh, run.
It's coming to you.
Dodged.
You are nothing to me, Blania.
Oh, get pillared.
Dumb shit.
Oh, she's busted.
She's busted.
What the fuck just happened in my game?
I don't I was waiting for you to hit her.
I told I told you, dude.
I got fucking told you.
I got Morgoth's great run.
Same.
You didn't believe in three.
We were just so fucking weak is the same thing as Placidusix.
I should not have been fighting her yet.
Yeah, I mean.
Fuck.
Nice.
You earned a moment from German 985.
Time to claim.
Yeah, dude.
I'm sorry, like being so fucked up, but you want to, you know, roaming up one time.
What?
I'm celibate, dude.
Let me just say something real quick.
Yeah, if you want to do that, I guess that sounds like fun.
But just maybe don't talk so much shit next time.
Who are you?
Who are you talking to?
Melania was fucking calling me.
What?
My chat asks and I ask, is Jerma's brand weed now?
Only for this one jokey dumb thing where like we're rolling blunts with Placidusix and shit.
Like, like just for like the last couple of days.
I don't know.
You've changed.
Wait, did you miss the point?
Did you miss the fact that that was Melania calling me being like, hey, let's like,
let's like fucking squash the beef and like, I missed a lot of something
because it looked like you were like praying at the altar.
Like you walked up to the altar and you just started talking to yourself.
Like you could hear God's voice.
You guys don't get it.
Jerma has reefer madness.
We're worried about you.
Are we are we ready?
Yes.
Go kill right card.
I think it's going to be a radon.
You think it's going to be a putrid slob.
I think we have not seen a putrid slob in a while.
Putrid slob.
Did you end up making a character in the myriad?
Yeah.
I mean like the revolting.
What was it?
Like the putrid disgusting slob or something.
Oh my God.
I didn't.
The great putrid slob, I think is all it is.
He was charging that up.
He so badly wanted to do that move to us.
He's just like, I'm.
Bro, come on.
I'm inside of the bear.
Millennia.
I sleep.
Giant bear.
I awaken for the meme.
This guy shooting crossbows.
There's a dog.
Do you remember when these dogs would like multi hit you like 16 times
and you'd instantly die?
You're dead.
I got knocked off by the bear.
I'm relating to that content right now.
I'm not going to even reset it.
I'm just going to come over to where you are.
I have one of those things.
Did you kill a bear?
Now?
No, help.
I died.
It's scary.
He's just roaring at you.
Nice kill.
You're welcome.
Yeah, we're going to put that head up above my fireplace.
Ooh.
Okay.
Let everyone know.
Rycon.
I hope whoever it is, they still get the voice lines.
Like how Margaret was saying shit earlier.
I would have imagined that's the case.
Wait, did you ask me what's like your top favorite thing
you would ever want to do or something?
What was at some point where you were like,
hey, what's like the number one thing you want to do?
Want to do.
Like just like in general.
I've never asked that, but sure you can continue.
Okay.
You know those lava places where you get like,
you can take like the poker and like poke the gooey lava
and it kind of just get places in the world.
I want to go there.
Eventually.
You want to poke if you could do anything,
you want to poke lava.
I think like going to one of those lava sites,
whatever they are.
And they're called volcanoes.
Yeah, but like there's a safe specific place
where there's some kind of running down like kind of like this
and you can kind of just go look at it and like poke it and stuff.
Okay.
Don't act like don't act like half of you
didn't have not watched the YouTube videos
where people doing that.
It's like, whoa, cool.
It's like scientific and don't bat-chest it.
I will fucking end my stream.
Don't hurt this guy.
He just grown like that hurt him to do that.
Oh, I see.
You're picking on him.
That sucked.
Awful.
And yet he persists.
Play something else.
Not very good.
Holy shit.
He gets to live.
I don't want to talk about it either.
I'm I'm a math.
So you instantly kill the jar enemies,
but you'll leave the horn guy alone.
What you like the jar.
I didn't I didn't know that was it.
You never said like do not kill the jar.
Didn't need to be said.
Oh, okay.
Don't kill the rat.
You you kill your rat with a little rabies
and it has like a puss on it.
Sure.
Can you do this in real life?
What?
You know.
Can I fight a bear in real life?
He's not even a fan of Elden Ring.
What?
Dude, go go poke some lava, dude.
Don't act like that wouldn't be fun, please.
I think it'd be more fun to roast marshmallows over it.
It'd be fun just to kind of just do it is
I think just be like experience like a like oh,
oh my god, that was brutal.
That woman in a wheelchair.
What?
She can't walk.
Wait, she was in a wheelchair.
She should be.
But I was like, what do you do?
This isn't like Troll Knight sword.
Bro, you are fucked.
All right.
We're almost there.
I have low healing.
If this is a tough enemy and you're poised up.
Leave quick.
Jesus Christ.
I think you died.
I died.
My screen faded to black and then it pulled me back
and I was like, nah, dude, you're actually dead.
I have the grace.
I don't know if that matters.
I think we can warp to it.
Dude, I had 700,000 souls on me a lot.
Can you start a vote and you do it?
Yep.
Yeah.
Don't skip the cut scene.
We won't.
We start has been wanting to hear this guy talk for the last four streams.
I love this guy.
Is it going to be convenient if the rapture happens soon
and then you can get a volcano in Las Vegas
and then you could just do it there?
Why does the rapture have to happen?
All right.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
They need to vote.
Oh, I'm just saying, would it be easier to wait for the rapture?
It would be easier just to take a vacation
than wait for humanity to end, I think, as the question you're asking.
Are you going to go on this vacation in the next year?
I don't know.
Do you think the world is going?
Do you think the rapture is going to happen in the next 12 months?
Probably.
Like, probably.
I'd say two years.
Actually, you know what?
I mean, this could be.
Let's start planning a vacation.
All right.
There's not very many nonbelievers, so.
I'm a blind samurai.
Let's go.
It's it's phase one.
It's Godfrey.
I can't enter.
I think you're in the cut scene that I've been wanting to watch.
There is no cut scene.
Godfrey Devouring Serpent.
It's a serpent that only likes to eat Godfrey's.
He's had one meal.
He's eaten once and it was enough.
Then the family found out that like, oh, they only eat Godfrey's.
Let's call our new son Godfrey.
He's probably got two phases.
Keep in mind.
That's true.
Quick.
Big smash.
That was so incredibly loud.
Actually was.
I wasn't going to say anything, but it was.
That was like you eating.
That was a big crunch.
This is a reenactment.
Oh, shit.
Oh, my God.
I'm just I'm just perma hit.
All I hear is, oh, oh, oh, my name is lagging to fucking shit, too.
It's really hard to dodge this when he's not doing them at you.
It actually is.
Oh, oh, oh, stir going down.
Okay.
Is there a phase two?
Please, mad soldier.
I'm out of healing.
Oh, together we shall be family or something.
I can't remember.
I'm watching the cut scene.
Who could it be, though?
For Dan, if it's for Dan, then we paid out a lot of money to the nonbelievers.
God looks like you.
You would talk over the exact moment where he says together.
It's oh, actually, this might suck.
It's margot.
Maybe not.
I think it'll be all right.
But doesn't Margot have a phase two?
Are we going to get like the phase two inception?
I'm like, that's what you mean.
Watch it on YouTube.
Oh, oh, oh, oh, fucking tomato at him.
He so badly wants you to die.
I have no help.
Oh, oh, he's got me.
Good thing I healed right there.
Epic.
believers let's go there's just four golden seeds I don't know what is with
my seed that I get all the seeds I'm guessing right there oh by the way rest
we come back see what happens when we come back here oh no oh dude you're
right yeah I'm excited I think we actually have to leave and then come
back yeah Joe I just got a moment so do you think that because of this scene
here that it will be some like right card will be in the DLC I don't know I
don't think there is DLC you just don't think that's gonna happen I think they
were gonna make deal if we just sold him another game I don't know give the
dancers you can move him move who you just were moving his head I can't see
them keep doing that walk wait stand right where I stand with just walk with
me is there an edge come over to me stay like go go exactly where I am and walk
forward you're kind of running in place you're moving his head around okay we
just take him with us really put him to a fire okay so should I give this give
the dancer I've never seen this what does this do so you can't see this at
all nope so what if I just kill her oh god that's worse than if you killed the
musician that's all you the jellyfish maybe it's better if I do it cuz I can't
even oh no tennis night it's one of these like skeleton people by the way
hands are you would see him are you attacking this I know I can't see and
it's just you it's kind of a discount bodyguard Wow I got a glass shard worth
it all right maybe if we reset it will you see it hmm you sat down and I heard
her start talking but I can't see her yeah you try I mean I don't think we
have to do anything here no we don't hmm all right so we can go to Farrah
Missoula and do Farrah Missoula go from Maleketh that sounds great what if yeah
and hear me out sure what if we did it tomorrow and not do it tomorrow but
tomorrow is gonna be the day that we were gonna do it it was but when it
became when we decided that hey today we're doing it instead I made a specific
plan tomorrow without me well cuz we did we did it today you didn't ask for
permission if you could do it tomorrow I'm sorry you do you want you gotta go
we go I'm just it's I just feel like my general health and well-being all right
okay so then yeah then let's let's call it then let's call it if you general we
don't wanna wait this is the way so that that was a that was like oh hey
you having fun like what else we doing today that was your version of that I
think right like oh yeah this game Ember yeah it's like really fun but like hey
what else is going on that was that was your version of that no that was my
version of like we could just play tomorrow but now that playing tomorrow's
off the table because you took it away all right but like are you feeling all
right are you okay like we can stop right now if we stop playing I would
like eat a real meal and then I would honestly play Neo so it's fine are you
gonna stream Neo no god no no god no all right they'll tell me that I missed a
key pulse and I'll just it'll send me over the edge he wants to play Neo I
what you know explain you he wants to play a neo so bad all right well then
hello wait wait I have a proposition proposition for you okay proposition if
you want to play let's let's just go beat the game that will not take us
very long but then that means we're never playing again my what I wanted to
do is play tomorrow and what you're suggesting is to go beat the game so we
never have to play it again I mean that's not necessarily true it's just
when would you want to play again like if we're not playing tomorrow like we're
not playing tomorrow when would you like to play like another weekend thing like
Saturday and that's a long time that's kind of a long time like you just want
it we can go in the Elden tree now can we I mean we could we could just pick it
up again at some point and just in the next few days or something we don't have
to play it anymore we could just stop for now and just in like I don't know a
few days and like we don't have to wait till the weekend well I thought we had
to go through like the destroyed Landell we do when does that happen I think we
have to kill Malika who is inferno let's do Farrah Missoula man but they they
want it I I let me make this really really clear I am willing to play again
some other time in the next big this week or something if you really if you
want to get food and like just leave that's all good no I'm fine okay I'm
fine I'm just very you know like very sad you just did the the Neo case is on
your desk and you keep like looking at it I thought I wasn't gonna play Neo
until we beat Elden Ring because I don't want to mess up my brain again so then
okay so the next time we play this just let's beat this let's complete it so
then it's a complete arc and then we're good to go and we do whatever you can
just go back to playing a yo and whatever and then we're never gonna talk
again I'm and I'm already in the best timeline right now let's go to
Farrah Missoula I just don't know what he wants I'm saying what I want I'm saying
let's go to Farrah Missoula I'm going to do I'm going every art must be finite
remember that I do I do remember that that's true that's why I ate that pork
he just wants to spend more time with you German well I didn't want to stop
playing he wanted to call it which makes complete been perfectly understand I
only wanted to call it because I thought we were playing tomorrow oh okay we're
not playing tomorrow we are not playing tomorrow then I need my fucking fix I
need my fill so what's gonna happen here then there's a boss is a dragon here I
guess nothing that's it I think it's a dog it's like a little dog what is that
that's sad yeah well you know what they say you got everything has to end watch
dogs staff I've never seen that before wait what's like watch dogs no I saw
watch dogs Legion the other day like a day or two it goes on sale for like
twelve dollars and I was like too expensive that's too expensive that's
that's a bit much I streamed watch dogs Legion on launch um I never even played
it I was it I was an un un $12 it was an unbelievably miserable experience it
was the game was just like just crashed every if I felt like every like 30 40
minutes I was hard-locking it was so bad
somber smithing stone 9 were you looking for these work we're fully
upgraded yeah no sadge don't say that let me just have to go kill Majula what's
his name Malaka you really do like Dark Souls 2 I don't remember what that word
is that's the town that jewel is the town in Dark Souls I don't I don't know
where I conjured that from that was like mr. Finster moment there is a boss with
the double god skin somewhere down here right we got assassin in the room
invisible assassin in the room watch your butt watch your back ah he's
murdering you he's got a lot of help oh shit scream there's a new adversary I'm
being good kind of murderers like Dexter oh wait we talked about our
favorite areas it might actually be this place this is a very cool spot big
tornado big or not though that sounds I got one guide why do you want destined
death childish because everything's finite and we have to end the run
so we're like speedrunning to elven beast god are you fucking my bungles
can we just run he's just dreaming of neo 2 hey he's invisible man all right
well let's go then the way being I don't know where we go I forget I why am I
following you I should not be following you we need to go oh good one you got
like this this aura of rushing on me now well I mean games over I'm gonna sit
down sorry okay that works I'm at the bonfire I'm coming who's gonna be our
godskin duo how about that well it is an apple will it be a duo is a good
question I think you think it'll be a duo I don't our valiant gargoyle wasn't
it was not yeah I don't think it will it seems like it'll put it like pairs
duos together randomly I mean I'm honestly just waiting for Dan it's one
of the only people we haven't seen I yeah uh-huh yeah that's one of the only
people well major bosses I mean who's a major boss we haven't seen yet
Cornelius we saw him oh yeah I was early on
Radegon that's right we haven't seen Radegon we haven't seen real Mog we
haven't seen Radegon we haven't seen we're Dan why do you say Mog like but
then you say Mog I say Mog like yes hey sorry enemy we're like it we're like we
have to like end the Elven ring your time oh I just got huge chills chills
okay can you do the skip I don't know practice it for a few hours but I don't
know if I maybe I have tried it once or twice
oh you mean this thing where you go you go you got a back step your vibes are
off you don't have to do it let's go I'm just fucking rolled off the edge I've
only picked up smithing stone sevens blaster so you're gonna rent out a
studio for the scream stream or you're going to like just do it at home I don't
whatever you said all right this is it where are they oh it's this guy this
this I did not like this guy and I did not like millennia this guy is my
millennia really I think we'll be all right we're pretty level I think he's
lower HP probably but like this guy she's why do I feel like half the bosses
we fought had this music I feel like it was the only music we've heard this is
the Elden ring boss music for all we are concerned this guy's attacks are just
totally random at least millennia goes up in the air and lets you know she's
gonna do some bullshit this guy's just like constantly spinning in circles and
summoning guys and there's frostbite everywhere and you can't see your screen
that's like a thousand particle effects and he's got the boys with him not
anymore what is he even doing right now what is he doing
it's a big what is the big circle splash and then he goes down and you have an
opportunity to hit him well did you yes look at her honestly how is this guy
not Elden fucking Lord it doesn't want it horror Lou is a naked guy he seems to
be doing this move a lot though would you would you do any other move maybe
well at least it doesn't heal when he hits you they should why me I'm out of
we got it don't worry I'm here I'm here thanks big bro see nothing bad yeah well
millennia was actually easier it's a lot of souls holy shit actually can do it
again and do it a couple more times actually can't I 60 strength do it oh
yeah let's go oh yeah yeah okay cool wrong door where my my souls in here no
I got out yeah we got a bell free key another one is this the wrong way too
there's like three doors in this room you we go up no you're wrong no no no no
no this door no no this door don't we go we go up around we go into this door
then you get the bonfire right next to the bonfire this way that way there's a
lot of people die on those stairs this way that way this way that way this is
the wrong way I was listening to you your first mistake when he said it last
honestly stir is scarier than Jerma scarier reading I'm just reading what
they said what have I done that's scary I don't know I think it's cuz the shit
your pants story well I think that they're having trouble getting over that
this is not the right way this is just like regular Zula there that's the guy
that it's the other door other other door it's his vibes they're just
off about his vibes are off and then we can go yeah kind of we don't do we go
around here we have to go up around to without bridges to go to where hold on
dude he's we're getting doored right now this isn't it we picked that's where we
came and picked the three wrong doors we back to the boss room we picked the one
we this literally four doors we picked three wrong doors I believe it's this
we just went down this one okay then the other the one across across across
across he's just like in neo right now stir is just more unfiltered that's true
Jerma thinks the things like he's thinking about killing you but he won't
say it so he's more dangerous because he's more unpredictable don't through
that don't true him do not give him any more power than he then he deserves for
everything he says there's like four things he didn't say and they're
sadistic you gonna fight this crap or am I gonna do all the fucking work stir is
right just wait that way just wait that way hey big boy he's gonna fall he's
gonna fall and we're gonna laugh in his fucking face he's gonna scream at us and
we're gonna fall backwards
I thought you were going down
hey do this IRL yo outplayed fortnight login I don't know why he's he's into
fortnight did you actually no wait a minute hold on you did play fortnight
you played the original fortnight I you played the real fortnight I played so
much fortnight before the battle royale came out that there was noticeable
damage to my twitch channel yeah and then the battle royale came out after I
had said while playing regular for tonight well this game would make a
good battle royale I played it one time dude you could have been on the ground
floor of fortnight you could you could have like a hundred million viewers
right now like concurrent coda Wow hey you still did pretty good though you
still did fucking really good actually did really good at what you had you
night just in general on twitch man look on for on fortnight no I'm just saying
you didn't have to do fortnight you did other shit that was cool and you it was
good yeah but the fortnight arc if that's what we're talking about you could
have this the darkest days you could have been on the ground level of the
BR fortnight arc would you go his shout hold me rather than pushed me it's
all right that's okay but rest because we're pretty low I just heard you
scream I heard you scream mother fucker I mean that really that really hit hard
that he shouted at me and it's suction cup me shouldn't happen I was like on
the I would play everything perfectly some beautiful all I'm saying is to go
back mm-hmm fortnight save the world that's that good shit back for blood
that's that doggie doo-dooed stupid stupid dumb shit sir where am I going
everyone everyone got excited for that so he says I'm a doo doo it's like the
same game there's left for that to excuse me
leopard it too was actually fucking incredible I'm saying yeah I'm talking
shit about back for blood we're going the right way Oh back for blood from the
developers of evolve oh yeah okay okay I'll try that game fucking three-head
oh that's so funny watch out he's what the fuck you just pull me down you just
pull me down just pull me over this just pull me over that's the perfect enemy to
be there where's the where's the bonfire up here oh I don't remember I hope mad
soldier is in the Eldon beast room I really do make you so happy Roy I love
that guy fucking back for blood bite it's my favorite fucking game I don't
even like know what you're doing but it's funny just imagining someone
excited for black back from one dude I fucking love that guy you're extra silly
today you really are teleport no I'm all right I'm here I mean it doesn't look
like you're here it looks like you're pretty far I'm I've made it down I'm
coming here just that that British accent where are you I'm at the neck
nearest that's you drop down here that was a good that was a good grunt oh like
I couldn't even replicate oh that's right then this is where the lightning
dragon oh yeah oh I remember now oh yes oh yes oh dear oh yeah oh yeah
Wow Frogger killed himself oh yes oh yes is it the same dragon I think this is
scripted I think is just shooting the shit out of the dragons not even here
yeah it's it wouldn't even be loaded in yet it's it's like scripted laser beams
Wow Wow that's my favorite okay guy the last like year or so really has felt
like everyone all at once made the like four-player co-op game it really a lot
of them it feels like something that happens in waves do you remember all the
seemed like everybody was making a VR game everybody was making the League of
Legends kind of you know pop down game there's been like five years from now
there's gonna be like six Elden Ring likes come out because everyone got like
all do this game so good let's make one all at the same time I like that kind of
started happening like a lot I mean they made a Star Wars game that was like a
souls like I think which one did I fall in order is a souls like I guess I mean
it is I never played it but it seemed that way it is 100% a souls like they're
just called action RPGs dude no I you cannot tell me that fallen order is not
supposed to be a souls like come on it is oh you want to um you want to just go
check and see if it's if it was down here yeah can we even activate it this
is I think so you just lay down in it get the bonfire first though for sure you
just have to lie down that's good just have to lie down and let it happen where
is the bonfire we miss it I don't know if there's like an elevator around here
oh it's right here on the elevator all right I'll send it back for you no I'm
good I'm nice like that I'll set it back for you that play secure oh I did I
completed secure oh I beat the whole thing true ending and that game was a
living hell oh on that note you're asking like secure over near or was
harder right I feel like there's some people in chat like to case you stop
bringing up but like you did ask no I did the game is harder than secure oh
for sure why do they all come in here they all heard you these are people in
chat that were very mad that you just said that yeah I know no no but people
Neo being harder was I think the general consensus when you brought it up or five
yeah and and I can confirm I was like yeah this was uh was the safe place to
drop wait is if I gotta go down just jump dude no go down the hero is the
easiest from software game secure is easier than Elden ring I don't think so
I feel like secure oh punishes you way more than Elden ring does if you miss a
couple of those parries you can just get caught and just you dead it's over we
have to go I think we have to cross yeah it's like you I'm seriously just jumped
right there I'm doing the fucking hard one you didn't you did the one on the
left it was easy I thought there was like a whole different area of where you
did I where do you drop down where is it your chat says wrong way guys yeah do
the hard one but going up nice thanks back by the bonfire wait is it no no no
no no no wait is it over here where is it I feel like it was way I feel it was
right here it's not just right here I thought it was where that dragon spawns
you fight the dragon on that letter letter ledger writer what writer where
did you go where so go you're invisible I'm invisible you're hiding I didn't
seek okay there's there's a tiny little ledge oh you got it I lose these souls
you owe me say I'm getting a little bit more tired and I'm getting it's I'm
hitting like the weird threshold yeah yeah I think you hit the weird I think
you've been on the weird threshold for four days I've been pretty tired slept
till like I would have slept a lot today I don't think I ever would have got up
if I didn't have to go somewhere I think I just would have been in bed for a week
I don't know something like something weird with my stomach I don't know what
it is or why you ever been check for worms nah I don't see why I would all
right let's lie down so we said yeah I was yeah you ever check for worms no
what oh it's him it's regular market dragon lord
market this time but your own boy whoa that's a lot of damage didn't even say
the line make sure you eat all your supper tarnished can you imagine can
you imagine that's what he said I'm sorry minus two I don't think it was a
minus two actually everyone yeah I agree with chat I have to be part of the chat
you just like think for yourself yeah sometimes we're gonna get so many souls
do three I remember yeah it was like 300k I got the Hallig tree medallions but
like we're just gonna speed run to the tree so it doesn't really matter we
could always do it again maybe you never know like all things all art has to be
finite yeah our next run could be with the Simpsons mod that's true all right
60 strength and now I should just dump it all into bigger endurance right all
right we have to port out of here so let's port back to the dragon temple
transept what a guild use better nude mod next time what makes it better than
the other what makes it better it's true this feels like we went backwards like
two bonfires from where we were supposed to be then let's go to the altar the
temple where is it I don't remember great bridge beside the great bridge
sounds right that sounds good oh yeah we're gonna get we're Dan one of these
times and it's going to be a disaster we're Dan's gonna be in the Elden
beast room I'm just gonna try to prepare myself in the Elden beast room it's
gonna be radan and we're not gonna be able to have a horse or anything it's
gonna be awful so just fight them draw your blade what if it just is Maleketh
we haven't even seen him yet it's Maleketh it's actually just
Maleketh it's Maleketh man no it's not it's fucking mug we this is this this
is probably real bog mock where did you learn Spanish got for the blood could
not make up his mind on who to attack here it comes all right you got to heal
through this no wait I don't do it you skip get him get him get him we're
unstoppable now don't let him do it just kill him before you can do it hey oh
he's got the fire poker you want uh-oh new build now I don't want a backseat
mode but like why doesn't he just count to like five just keep doing it well he
might not have enough mana probably takes a lot of energy to do that move
count to five seven one two three is a phase two gonna be fucking radan it's
Loretta Loretta to every phase two I used most of my heels just kind of
fucking around why I don't know I just figured we were gonna be alright and we
were rolling yes a little your jump attack does so much damage yep how am I
a lowly kitsune Fox girl gonna compete with your raw strength cuz I'm gonna die
fuck oh one hit yeah we are in a roll right now we're actually on a roll hey
wait hold on wait one guy the one guy said apparently low energy makes stir
horny thinking that Fox girls are cute is weird I just am one there's a
difference I'm not horny what is he just gonna throw that out there just
gonna throw that out there was he what are you what is he saying they're
fucking animal people they're not real what is he I don't even know what he's
saying I wasn't paying that much attention to what he was saying I was
trying to focus on the fight what's happening with someone was accusing me
uh-huh of some heinous heinous stuff okay and I just had to I had to correct
you know set the record straight oh wait who is gonna be good who is gonna be
Gideon ah we could role play he could be Gideon I Gideon school and I'll play
um Nefeli I don't want that potion I'm a strong warrior girl I need to level up
how much is it 70 80 come on you are fucking weird you are weird I'm sorry can
I have a rune I just need wine I literally need like a thousand okay sure
and by the way we need to look our best so fuck armor and shit wear your best we
need to be best we need to be best dressed for this best dress where your
best get up so that we can look better than Gideon this is just the this is it
man it's not there's like more this is it man this is the this is the big one
what are you wearing here I don't know what I got I don't have a lot to work
with nothing matches I'm gonna be in my closet for like an hour you look like a
gigachad that chin you look like a little kid that just bought the game and
it's like I like all these things I have a back belly button dude my cape is it's
like chrome you look so cool I have the all-knowing armor I'm gonna dress up as
him no I don't like that wait what about like wait I kind of like this well you
get more options cuz you have like more you can wear more it's true it's not
fair I'm keeping my water I want to redo okay let's go you're happy if I
pants on hi this is fine wait wait I mean you're wearing sandals you don't
have pants on and you're wearing sandals this is fucking this is good look at
this shit I'm fucking ready
sleigh sleigh sleigh hello we know you can't go on the horse tears were
streaming down my face at this part you were crying because you because you got
lost you didn't know where to go I was just like just so fucked up it was so
bad like you know when you when you cry a ton it's like I can't breathe like like
my nose you know that like you did this dragon here Oh that Gideon that's not
supposed to be Gideon right you know when you cry a lot it's like no it I I
haven't been crying has never happened to me we're going the wrong way what you
get on your horse can't there's like a weird we can jump so no it is it is this
way come on back here come on it's gonna be a putrid tree avatar he's
stressed he's like wait don't go up there please listen to logic we've
suffered enough oh listen to logic he's like stop oh it's Maleketh oh people
are still people are still voting I wonder if that's gonna change well
Gideon always has like no HP right isn't he like die really quickly maybe the
Maleketh does a ton of damage though yeah but like not to me if we like we
were cool in high school so I have like the Lord debuff that's your locked here
we go I mean they're not but okay Maleketh lay your weapons down we will
do it with diplomacy beat his ass now Maleketh the all-knowing oh fuck Maleketh
is actually really strong double swing okay I'm taking it seriously now I
wasn't before I'm unlocking my true power are you yeah we're okay he does a
lot of damage though that's it that's that's what he's saying on his stream
you killed you yeah I think you can do it I think you're that I think you're
that good oh yeah Wow we did whoa did we win this account did he die what
happened does that count he jumped off the map is he dead how do we how do we
score that we score that correct he's not dead the foggates here what dude he
disappeared and I fucking insta died what did I die oh yeah I do have the
Maleketh item what do I have to use that like what does it matter he did he burn
me I he on my screen earned you yeah that was so weird he just disappeared and
then I died it was the death burn stir how would you how would you score that
that doesn't does that is that just a refund or is that like we lost he's not
actually dead we lost because if we can enter here and he's still alive then we
didn't kill him fuck fuck we didn't win we lost let's just make sure he's
actually hold on let's just open it up we lost I'm sorry believers but him in
this area where he can jump off yeah let him just jump okay he really he really
did not want to attack you apparently okay fucking two seconds dude well I
mean you just watch oh shit I was trying to bait him over the edge I was trying
to bait him over the edge I was trying to get him to jump that's stupid what
if we did stealth what do you mean what if we like like we just stealth in
because we know where he is and we backstab him no what we need to just
stand over here let's just fight him over here but like you have to actually
fight no no stay right here just stay right here he's gonna do right now he's
gonna jump over he's gonna fuck it up he's gonna jump over it right now okay
there he goes he's gonna do a weird side jump but he's gonna go right down I don't
know why he fell off like his normal arena has places he can jump off he's
so pissed over over here actually not a bad space place for him to be oh he
almost did it he actually almost did it how does he know oh here he goes there
he goes he's dead see you later he does the jumps on the pillars and it's like
he tried to jump to another pillar that didn't exist it just did a wily coyote
straight down nice I saw bullshit there shouldn't be ring outs okay there is
still an opportunity for this to go really wrong and if it's radan is there's
only two more opportunities praying for a mad soldier he'll be on the horse too
won't he that's gonna be a disaster yeah just wait it's gonna be so
anticlimactic we're gonna get to we're gonna get an urn tree avatar and then an
urn tree avatar that's kind of I really want it to just be like just said you
want to become the Elden Lord here's the one snail on the bridge there is that
snail boss now we already beat that yeah anybody voting right now you there is an
equal chance here for it to be radan and we can't beat this for six hours or
snail and it's free I remember this one should be two phases as well yep radan
is easy not in the area we're about to go to also when you say that statement
remember that we're both bad also very true it cleaned this one all right that's
her in we can should we take a peek or should we just walk in I just walk in
okay go I got it first oh he's huge what a valiant gargoyle first Eldon Lord
Wow they give out Eldon Lord to people wearing diapers there is Eldon Lord
anybody can be Eldon Lord apparently doesn't even know we're here backstab
him let's do I let's do stealth when you jump I'm gonna unleash my katana ready
one two three I'm dead holy shit what I don't wait dude look at your health oh
my god I'm poisoned why did we get so annihilated oh shit he is oh my god
we just were talking so shit I took so much damage so quickly I was trying I
almost menued car go I'm trying I'm trying to cure the poison and that's all
I'm focused on I gotta stop does he have Godfrey's axe no no I think you can do
it for the guild you're doing a lot of damage a swing I have to clear this
poison you're good oh no oh no oh no you they can't be too and what do you mean
valiant gargoyle first Eldon Lord valiant gargoyle twin blade that's not
correct oh okay they're sharing the title it's gonna be three boss
I think you could are you could be the older Lord usually this is gonna be
pretty rough I don't think it's impossible but if don't say it but if
we're Dan is phase two I gotta say I'm impressed the lore lines up seamless
co-op but we're gonna be joint Eldon Lords accurate like yeah Eldon Lords are
always couples apparently it's like a it's weird it's in the lore I mean it's
my hand we run back up there did you not spawn here well why don't I wait why am
I spawned a little bit did I not touch the bonfire you might not have title
makes it better dumb do my bed chamber I'm already walking okay okay well as
long as you don't insta die I mean it wasn't it was just in fact hold on I
don't even have any poison policies I don't if we really really focus the if
we do a big big focus on the first one damage damage damage I think we're
right like before he moved we just you know he just did a lot of damage yeah
all right let's go for it let's go bucko oh okay and let's sync it up again give
this guy the business show him why he's washed up ready one two three okay when
he hits half health yeah if we can both fight one that would be ideal he's gonna
co-op us which is cheating all right here he comes no oh shit poison oh shit
poison I'm poisoned I'm fighting the other one I have aggro you just focus on
him holy fuck my guy is the tornado dude I just don't know the move set he's
fucking destroying me fuck I cannot believe you are still fucking fighting
that one guy I can't Adam hey how about you take the aggro next time that
poison does so much damage it's unbelievable you can't be fuck you fuck
you dude hey he does this like huge jump backwards I'm so slow okay tragic we
need to switch I need the slower guy I don't think the other one's slower yes
okay well I want to kill the one and then I'll come help you and then when I
help you your chats gonna be like wow Jerma so good I mean it's not that I
was doing poorly it's just he did he would do a move and then he would jump
backwards a hundred feet and he's a chase after him put on better armor oh
you know what wait put a put a anti-poison on your hotbar I don't have
any loser use a rune arc also a good idea I don't think I even have anything
equipped Craig blade ash of war we'll see I think we're all right just
depends on what's after this there we go that fucking poison is such shit
completely freezing well I'm gonna grab the other one I didn't get the stab
double poison spray bro fine spring I don't think it's coming to you
oh that's a double hit shit he's moving around so boy said all right who's next
who's next yeah who's next it's all right this is not horrible this is the
phase one bit all right oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh oh you fuck oh it's
alright just play safe nice damn I got a bunch of keys same palace key I don't
know what that all that's for yeah well here it is time for mad soldier we're
done true mad soldier we're done could be I mean it could be radical but then
beast it could be I really do hope it's soldier of Godric if it's soldier of
Godric that's a great thing let the whole let them vote a lot of votes going
on I'm voting are you voting okay I'm getting in on this remember this is a
two-phase fight yeah but I think this is an easy W I don't know I'm all in well
you all in channel point I'm I am all in on no I know although wait let me put a
fucking rune on the way I can't do that from here can I you're all in on no sir
I'm in on yes of course I'm a believer do you just did you just see how fast we
killed dirt dirt towel guy the blanket blanket man whatever his name is your
hurt towel man he's got like he's wrapped in like a I don't know man there's
a lot of nose this is nose are taken over well done hey this we've been
playing this this is all right what we're doing right now this is all for
this story was a there's an absolute pleasure my blankie you ready is the
vote still going we close it 20 seconds make sure you got really good armor make
sure you're good to go I don't want any of this shit I'm not I don't want any
of that they make sure my bar is good I'll see I'll keep those just in case
right you know I'm going I'm going I'm putting I'm putting all my shit on the
bar we're talking steak everything we found the whole game just just just you
don't just take everything yeah just take everything just eat everything I
don't know oh the like boost physical attack item is really strong yeah I'm
eating that are we good George eat we're eating just eat everything just go eat
off the fuck out of yourself okay all right are you ready yeah I think I'm
good who is it it's Cobra Kai it's a flash thing I can't see look out it's
us wait which one is you dude is this you which one's you wait is it you or
is it me it's you on my screen it's you on my screen it's probably sinking for us
then we were already in here the golden rule sucks yeah well this world is shit
who made the world this way no I want to be Eldon Lord no I want to be Eldon
Lord okay man so now what I'm eating yep oh shit it's the ancestral spirit this
sucks oh my god he does a lot of damage yeah no a lot like actually like an
unbelievable about he scaled to be the Eldon beast fuck just like the Eldon
beast you're gonna run oh right in the head he's gonna heal wait wait there's
no animals in here no there's no animals I think this is the the like lesser
version by the way yeah cuz it's all like bloody get over here well he's going
wild oh stop me off imagine voting no yeah I would put my hand through my
moderate but the music too is perfect stop doing that this really just wants
the string to keep going oh god damn it he's so like wiggly by the way from
person who gets the last hit is the Eldon Lord so it works oh he's so far
away I got robbed yes my yes my lord that's my first rule put on these
cat ears it's rubber touches it damn it you just he he gets to make all the
rules now you put on the cat ears I was born for this that's the worst day for
doubters you had a pretty good chance I'll be honest we're Dan still in the
mix radigan still in the my voice is just gone screaming for like six hours
yeah even say a lot of weird stuff maybe a dragon to a dragon in that first area
would have been pretty terrible what ending did we even get Dongita we didn't
do anything put the head in the cup bowing me like I don't know
became that vote must have been like more than 50% assuming we would lose
between now it was it was 26 million versus 31 million 31 was no a lot of
people lost points right there that's 31 million points gone from whoever had
him mimic tear it's like that's probably underneath soldier of Godric that
secret ending what wait what oh we died that's that's half a million souls gone
by the way unfortunate oh that's not good all right I was gonna change the
world I became Eldon Lord and then I accidentally no clipped through the earth
all that power I know what to do with it let's respect our bill one last time you
know actually know we can do can we actually go and do the via boss as well
I guess right I guess now do PvP PvP for true Eldon Lord I don't know how we how
do we would we even fight each other same way that we did it accidentally
before okay don't don't we have like a third party my guy doing I don't know
are you controlling him your character no no I pressed be be held and I just
started walking at her but then I missed because you like walked in front
of her I wanted to be held let me be held no let me in here please let me in
here it's weird I didn't do anything okay we're missing the item oh my god
when you hit her she bursts broken in this mod owned all right well then you
got what you want it we don't have to play anymore hey it's not what I said
it's over forever hey it's not goodbye it's I'll see you in a few years maybe
alright 2025 is there anything you want to clean up where you want to go how do
you feel now I mean we can't really just go backwards after you kill the
mimic to your Eldon Lord that's true the only thing we would find was radan
wherever radan was or ratagon which is probably no cron if we went to go fight
Moog I feel like that would be radon and probably if it was like both of them
because it seemed to be putting the strong bosses and strong boss places
true that's the true ending fight well that was really fun that was actually a
really good time a pleasure all good things all all art must be finite yeah
let Nexon publish Elden Ring online is that's fun that was the seamless co-op
seamless co-op works pretty flawlessly we the only problems we had were very
very just minor basic very very easy to fix problems like oh my game crashed
once every few hours or something it's really not a big deal there were really
like none today too and it was really smooth as mod makers give round of
applause without without the person made this mod we can't do seamless co-op like
this it goes for anybody yeah all joke ending yeah it was perfect
all right dude hey what do you have to do it like we could do whatever you want
to play something I don't know we'll figure something out if we place them
again we'll always figure something out always yeah literally always good night
yeah take care see you later Esther do neo 2 co-op I don't think I want to play
neo 2 I don't think it's for me they're never gonna talk again hey that's not
true we literally just played that firefighter game like two weeks ago yeah
that's fun the next time I'll see you will be let's see here probably Wednesday
or Thursday we're gonna do another chill stream there's a few games that they
just want to relax and play so keep an eye on the sauce at the latest Thursday
and then we'll probably do something this weekend to do house flipper
randomizer yeah the mod it was just randomizer and seamless co-op and we've
got about the typing test don't worry we'll do it we'll do it there has to be
here for it though but that's it there was a game completion figured we
probably had an opportunity to beat it tonight so there it is see you guys
later have a great rest of your weekend it's probably over but have a good
early week you can do ace attorney yeah eight we'll do ace attorney on one of
the chill nights that we do I'll go back to sorcery I will we're gonna have to do
a recap for those that weren't there you should play Pentamon I tried it maybe
I'll try it again yeah have a great night like connect for right I gotta talk to
it Alex Alex and I was supposed to play that man of a Dan game but the devil in
me or whatever it was you're gonna recreate any old videos oh that's right
the hitman freelancer mode I want to do that yeah expect that this week to maybe
this coming weekend yeah I'll see you Wednesday or Thursday take care bring
some water have a serving of vegetables if you haven't all your mother you know
what to do see you guys soon bye bye