This one goes out to all you watching the video right now.
We're playing The Sims 3, baby, here we go!
What will I do?
The choices, they're true.
I'm not sure, but I want some time to maybe think about.
Maybe I'll build a house.
Maybe I'll make some food.
I don't know, but it's time to begin The Sims.
Maybe we'll have some-
Oh, shit!
Don't pick-
Oh, God.
This is why you don't move your hands around when you sing a song.
I knocked over the fucking lamp that was on his desk.
Okay, let's take a look here.
Uh, I do not want this biker jacket.
Oh, by the way, for those of you who are interested,
this is exactly what I look like in real life.
Uh, I don't want this like jazz club waiter shirt.
Get rid of this fucking thing.
What else we got here?
We got like the snow vest.
We got, um, that weird looking thing.
We got Christopher Robin from Winnie the Pooh.
No, fuck that.
No, thank you.
What else we got here?
Business man?
I think I could put the business-
Oh, my God.
This is perfect!
The smoking jacket with the green.
I wear this shit every single day.
I don't even wear pants.
Okay, so you can't have just underwear.
That's bullshit.
But anyways, let's make my name here.
Grandpa and last name.
What is my last name?
Yonko?
Yombo?
I do something like that.
Hey, Jeremy!
What is that?
What's our last name?
What?
What's your last name?
Why do you want to know?
Well, just say it.
My last name's different.
You're on mom's side, so-
I don't even know what my fucking first name is.
Now let's do it.
Let's move into an empty lot.
And I'm going to build my dream house.
It's going to be so much fun.
Loading up the screen.
There he is.
There I am.
Grandpa.
So let's do the build tool here.
Got to make my absolute dream home.
That will rival the celebrities of the world.
So let's go here.
We need some walls.
And I think I'm going to go up this left here.
Start with this little hallway.
Let's start here.
Go all the freaking way.
Go all the way up here.
Up to stiff.
There you have $2,300.
Holy shit.
Build this over this way.
Make sure it's all the way to the right.
Okay.
That looks good.
Bring it all the way down like this.
There's my little room here.
What else do I need?
Oh.
Coming down this way.
Yes.
Yes, I did it.
This is a dream house.
Okay, let's do it.
Build the furniture now.
Let's put in-
Obviously, I want to-
Where's the toilets?
I need toilets.
Here they are.
Make sure we have at least a few of these.
Because I don't like to walk.
Because my legs are really not that great.
So I want at least, let's just say like seven or eight toilets in the house.
So wherever I am, I can always just sit down and take a shit if I need to.
And that'll be Dandy and Randy.
Now we need a-
What else is in a house?
Bed is lined up the way I want it.
Got my fridge.
Now I just need a TV.
Okay, let's put the stand here so I can watch my murder mysteries.
Click on the TV.
This TV looks pretty good.
Make sure it's lined up with the bed.
And it is.
My fridge is all set.
And I think that's it.
That's good.
This house is fucking great.
I wish I could live in this house for real.
It's got everything I could ever need.
Get over there.
Go see your new house.
Why am I talking to a mailbox?
I'm not that stupid.
And apparently I have a stick up my ass by the way I'm running.
Yes, I love the bed.
We are agreeing on that together.
As one.
So what am I going to do?
What TV show am I going to watch first?
Maybe Murder, She Wrote?
What?
Why am I?
What is this?
Why am I just fucking puke?
Oh, so I just made Sherma.
He's on the left.
Jeremy is my grandson.
He's...
I think that looks just like him, but...
He's apparently being a real asshole.
There's nothing I can do about this.
Besides, tell him this is my house.
You're under my rules.
And you need to learn to be respectful.
And now he's pissing his pants.
I don't know why that's happening.
There's a toilet literally one inch to his left.
Okay.
You know, I made way too many of these lights.
I probably should turn some of these off or delete them or something.
How do you turn that off?
Yes, go do it.
I'm supposed to be cooking dinner right now on the stove.
Please turn the damn light off.
Where's Sherma?
Can he turn it off?
Oh good, I think he's going to do it right now.
Go turn that off and we'll get going here.
You don't have to be...
Oh, no.
Oh, there's a fire.
There's a fire.
Somebody put that fire out.
Don't just stand there looking at it, you fucking idiot.
Put your fire out.
Use the fire extinguisher or call the goddamn police.
Oh, he's running now.
Yeah, go ahead and run, you coward.
Where is he going?
Where are you running to?
Where do you think you're going to go?
It's a small fire.
Grandpa will take care of this one.
I got this one.
Don't worry.
Extinguish the flames.
Who is that?
Who is this guy that just came to the house?
Who are all these people coming to the houses?
What the fuck is going on?
Yeah, I'm so glad you guys all ran over here to just scream at my fire.
Like, thank you.
Will somebody call the police?
Is that going to be a thing?
Can somebody do that, please?
Oh my god.
It's the fire spreading now.
Yeah, whatever.
Well, that's going to wrap up this video.
My whole freaking house is burning down and nothing I can really do about it.
But if you liked this video, then click on that like button
and show Grandpa some support, baby.
And that's going to be it.
So I'll see you all later.
And bye.
I'll tell you the next time I play this game,
I'm going to have your goddamn fire extinguisher ready to go.
And not only that, I'm going to have a fucking phone next time
so I can call the police and my friends and stuff.
You'll see next time it's going to be a lot different.
I will make sure of that.