Hey, what is happening everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and guys, I'm in a great mood today.
It is beautiful outside. You know those days where you just look outside and you say,
my god, it is a great world we live in. It's one of those days today, guys.
Hopefully you're having a good day too, but this is going to be an Engineer Widowmaker only stipulation match.
And I know it's been kind of a long time. It's been maybe a month since that last spy stipulation.
And I do apologize, but I've been trying to work on other projects, trying to get a new Enlighten done.
And expect that Enlighten in the next probably three or four days. I'm still working on it, trying to get it as good as I can possibly make it.
So expect that soon. Now this video, this particular video, as I said, Engineer Widowmaker only, that means no buildings, no pistol, no sentries, no nothing.
It's only point and shoot with the Widowmaker. Now that on paper might sound kind of bad, but think about it like this.
When you build buildings, you're using metal. When you upgrade buildings, you're using metal.
When you do anything with any of your buildings, you're using a substantial amount of metal.
This setup allows you to use 100% of your metal and ammo, whatever you want to call it, for shooting people.
Now this is not totally recommended that you do this all the time, because obviously this is just a stipulation match.
This is not something you should be doing every time you play Engineer, because you would really irritate your team.
Your team would just be like, where's the dispensers and the teleporters? What the hell?
And you kind of have to defend yourself by going, I don't know. But every now and then it is totally worth doing this.
And like I was going to say before, it takes you out of the Engineer mindset. There's no nest you have to protect.
There's no dispenser that your teammates are going to need at level 3. You're just a powerhouse Engi.
And that can be a problem when you face a couple of different classes, like the Scout or the Heavy.
And I say those two things for very good reasons. The Heavy, of course, if you run at a Heavy with a shotgun,
I'm going to get you just dead. You're instantly going to die.
There's no way a Heavy won't kill you with this setup unless you get behind them or you catch them somehow off guard.
That's the only real way that's going to happen.
And I say Scout for the second reason, because they're jumping around all over the place,
and it can be tough to get those shots on a Scout, especially with the shotgun.
And it makes it even worse when you don't have a Mini Sentry backing you up shooting them.
So now I want to briefly talk about the stipulation series in general and what I plan on doing with it,
where I plan on going, because before this, I tried to get a Sniper, No Scope only, and Jurati,
which means I could throw the Jurati on somebody and obviously get the Mini Crits with the No Scope.
I tried doing that in so many places. I tried so many times to do that, and it really just wasn't happening.
I'm still going to try and get it. I am determined to get that stipulation, because I think it's a really good idea,
a really funny idea. And another one somebody sent me a long time ago, Soda Popper and Pistol with the Scout.
And I can only use the Pistol to shoot, and I can use the Mini Crits.
So bring up the Soda Popper, run around a little bit, get the Mini Crits, switch to the Pistol.
I think that's a great idea.
But the reason why I'm talking about this right now is because these things are kind of difficult to get good gameplays on.
So expect the stipulation series to be maybe once a month now rather than once every week or once every couple weeks,
because it is pretty difficult to get some of these gameplays.
Speaking of the gameplay, it's coming to a close right now. I think, pretty sure I second frag or top frag.
I'm actually not sure. I don't remember, but I know I'm there.
So in the title of this video, you're probably looking at it and going,
wait, wait, wait, he's revealing something? What's he revealing? He's got an item? He's going to show us the stuff?
That is absolutely right. I'm going to finally... I've been talking about it for so long now,
but here are the prototype items for the Heavy.
As you can see, it is a baby Heavy.
So we got the bonnet. We have the diaper.
And there's going to be a secret item that this guy, DJ Thed, he's going to be working on.
That's the guy who's been doing it. He'll be in the description, his link.
He's a really talented guy, really nice guy. And he's actually really young, too.
For the talent he shows and for the stuff he's doing, he's a pretty young guy.
So it's interesting to see that. Really cool to see that.
But here you go. This is the baby diaper heavy thing that I've been talking about for like four months.
And so this is my call to you guys.
What do you think this set should be called?
Should this be called the Big Baby?
Should it be called the Fat Heavy Diaper Bastard?
I'm leaving it up to you guys.
I want to pick the coolest name for this set.
So drop that into the comments section of this video and I will pick the best one.
And that's what's going to be the name of this set.
So it's not on the workshop right now. I really want to state that.
This is not on the Steam Workshop right now. These are prototype items.
They are not final.
So I will give you guys the link so you can finally see the finished versions sometime at a later date.
But I had to show you. I couldn't hold it anymore.
So this is going to be the end of the video, guys.
Thank you so much for watching. I really do appreciate it.
And I'll see you all soon. Take care, everybody.