Ooh, Deltarune. I got my Deltarune hat on, my Deltarune shirt on, my Deltarune clothes on, my Deltarune everything.
I've got my Deltarune plushies back here. I'm wearing a Star Wars t-shirt. Uh, never mind. I got a tweet. I'll be right back.
How you doing? See you in a minute. Okay. So I want to make this really clear.
This is going to be, uh, for those of you that haven't played Deltarune chapter one, uh, this is gonna be a spoiler free playthrough.
I can respect the people that haven't done it yet. All names will be censored.
All text will be censored. And anytime there's a major, major event on the screen, I'm going to cut to, uh, to auto.
So I'm just, I want to, you know, make sure you guys understand.
Now I'm ready to go. I did run up here though. I'm a little winded.
I always open up. So I'm on my phone. I'll just take a look at the, uh,
the clock app.
And the second hand is on the six.
And it's just going around and I know that it's almost two.
And I go, oh fuck, I got to get up in that room.
And turn the stream on before the second hand hits the 12 up there.
I almost made it.
Very close.
You know, your house has two floors.
Five.
What are you talking about? It takes me about four minutes to run up and down the stairs.
No, I don't live in a five story house. I would never want to live in a five story house.
Have I talked about my like anxiety with living in a big house or a bigger place? It's scary. I hate it.
The bigger your house is,
the more places for a murderer to come in and like hide in your eighth bedroom
while you're brushing your teeth in bedroom two.
And you might not even fucking hear them come in. Nope. No, thanks.
I want to be able to be completely aware
of every single space in my place of residence.
If somebody's scratching at the door
20 feet away, I want to be able to fucking hear it.
I'm not going to be in living room four
and not know what's going on in living room two.
Paranoid. That's fine. That's all right.
Just set up baby monitors everywhere.
I don't know. I don't want to play five nights at Freddy's in my own house.
No, I don't want to do that.
That's when fucking chicken's gonna jump out of my face. I don't want to do that.
No, I want to be very aware of my surroundings at all times.
Live in a four by four house.
Aren't you scared of ovens too?
I'm not scared of ovens.
I'm scared of how ovens operate.
It's weird.
Something about it just freaks me out. I don't know why.
The fact that there is a box in your house
that heats up to hundreds of degrees
with gas.
It's just I don't know if something about it irrationally is uncomfortable to me.
I don't know why.
That's a recycled bit.
No, no, these are not recycled bits.
Hey, I can recycle a bit
when there's way more people that are here than last time I talked about the oven routine, okay?
Two years ago when I talked about my fear of ovens
like 4000 of you weren't here. So I get to do it again.
Every additional viewer that's added to this stream I get to redo a joke because that person hasn't heard it yet.
That was a few months ago.
Never mind.
Oops.
You're environmentally conscious with your jokes.
I gotta I gotta keep my joke carbon footprint down.
That was definitely more than a few months ago. I don't know. I have no idea.
I wonder how many words I've said on stream and on YouTube.
How many actually single words have I spoken?
You have to be talking about like tens of millions hundreds of millions of words that have been spoken into a microphone.
I can't keep track of them all of everything I've ever said.
How am I supposed to do that?
The oven routine is a recycled bit.
Yeah, since the oven routine I have said
745 million words.
Think about that.
Really think think about that for a second.
Important.
Somebody has to count it. I don't I hope nobody does do that. That's way that's way too much work for something.
So that is not important at all.
You see half of your words are filler.
Yeah, because I have so much to say that I need my brain has to catch up for a second.
My left hemisphere and my right hemisphere are the tortoise and the hare.
And they're both they're both competing at the same time.
Like one of them runs real fast and the other one takes like 20 minutes to get there.
Play the game. It's been seven minutes. We'll just I'm
Get out of here.
Play the game. I'm gonna play the game. I'm I'm excited about this one.
Impatient Andy.
Yeah, just we'll just chill. We're just hanging out.
Vod watchers skip.
Well, that's the that's the privilege of being a Vod watcher versus a live viewer.
A Vod watcher right now was able to go like this.
I put oven pipe.
Okay, so we're gonna play Deltarune now. Uh, we're gonna start the game now.
But you guys are here live.
You have to you have to put up with me in real time.
So I'm sorry, but that's just the way it is.
I've been waiting for this. Yeah, I've I'm excited. I did my refresher course.
I remember everything pretty much.
I've seen everything I need to see.
I am refreshed for Deltarune chapter two, by the way, this is chapter two.
So if you don't know what this is, I don't know if you want to be here, but maybe you do.
You say wait, what is it?
You say one to seven words per second.
So that's six thousand one hundred and twenty words per hour.
Okay.
So for six hundred so six thousand one hundred and twenty words an hour.
times
like five hours.
Talking about like what? Thirty to forty thousand words, uh said.
On stream per stream times one thousand.
Is like three hundred and fifty million words or something. I don't know. Somebody will figure it out.
I say way more than one or two set. No way. I say way more than that.
All right, you guys ready for Deltarune chapter two?
You know, i'm fucked up now. Now i'm going to try to say more words a second to like bump my
score.
Where's my audio? Where's my audio?
All right, so I played this on different computers. So I on my
streaming setup is not I don't have the old files.
I'll just pretend like it's the same file.
But I heard I've I've everything I said you don't have to be playing in the same file. It's fine.
He's muted.
How does this work? Where's my audio? Oh shit. That's why.
He didn't kill.
Wait, hold on. Make sure everyone who cares? You're episode two. I can say it. Okay.
Why am I so concerned about saying this?
This is you're here at episode two.
I have to imply that you've seen episode one or played episode one, right?
Like what am I talking about? And this has been out for a week.
I'm always the last person on Twitch to play these games. The new ones that come out.
So I didn't play I didn't beat Jevil on this save file.
Oh, well.
I mean I if you didn't if you don't know I'm I'm one of I think of of six people on Twitch.
Or maybe six people in the world
that beat Jevil on their first try. First try. No bullshit. Did it first try with nothing. No bullshit.
I'm one of six people on in I think in North America.
From my understanding.
Stream is ruined.
No spoilers.
All right, let's go. Let's go. I'm ready.
Let me start.
What was my name in the last save file? I don't remember and can anyone look it up?
What was my name?
I made this was my name.
That's such an old joke though. That's so old.
It's been three years and we're gonna really go back to like three years ago comedy on Twitch.
Hey, on emos. Thanks for the 20 subs. Appreciate it. 20 community subs.
Recycled joke. All right. I'm just gonna whatever. It doesn't really matter.
I'm using a controller too. I know. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. So shut up.
Everybody relax. I'm using a controller. I know I just like everyone just fucking spit out their dinner. Relax.
Joke recycler Andy. Okay. How about I'm just gonna do my name. Whatever. Who cares?
Is this your name? Yes.
All right, here we go. So last thing remember
Chris ripped the fucking heart out put the heart in the cage took a knife out and we went holy smokes
What's gonna happen to chapter two? Let's find out youtuber voice
Chris, honey, are you awake?
Wait, is that uh a knife? No
Wait, what Chris? Did you eat all the pie? It is your knife in this empty tin. Is it not?
Oh, I see. Huh? Oh Chris brightness. Oh wait, you're right. This is from the sims
I
Do you want to know how fucking lazy of a quote content creator? Oh content creator
I haven't opened obs in eight days
You don't understand like do you you get it? I'm sure you guys get it, right?
Uh, all right. Well, that's fixed looks good. What do you do? Yeah, i'm a content creator. Yeah content creator
Influencer. Oh nice. So you must be like really active
Well, yeah, I mean I opened the program a week of more than a week a week and a half ago
I played the sims 3 with some mods and then fuck it
I just didn't even open it ever again until the next time 20 minutes before I had to stream next
Oh, man. Okay, you're a content creator. Yeah. Okay. Oh chris
Am I going to have to lock the oven again?
I don't want you to touch the oven because I don't like the oven well hurry out of bed. It's time for school
Yeah, so the last
Chapter you go to school sit down
You with one of your classmates?
Yeah, ends up getting and you end up going into a portal in the clause in the supply closet
And then you have to fight the dark prince at the in the dark portal and everything
And then you come back and okay good. We get it play the game
No, i'm gonna milk this for like seven hours because it's i've been waiting for this
It's five dollars in your brother's drawer take it. I mean it's five dollars. It's five dollars
I'll put ten back in a week. That's the play. It's a bird cage when the door is closed
There's no escape on the computer's desktop is a folder called epic games stuff poorly drawn design for a game
Seems the last boss is a creature with giant rainbow wings. It doesn't seem like this game ever saw the light of day
Is this a unreleased game fortnight? There's no time to read books just generally. Yeah
That's like really that's a good point
How to draw dragons is at the bottom of the drawer the purple character on the cover is dressed
Immodestly, your brother will never return this book doors locked. Oh, by the way
I gotta say this really really importantly the backseat policy on this stream is as follows
If I
Request help specifically if I request help if I say I don't know what the fuck i'm doing somebody help me
You're free to spam whatever you want in the chat that has anything to do with what I asked
If you say a spoiler of this game
In the chat room you are going to get just nuked by the mods if there's like a put a spoiler chat gone
And you're gone too and you're never coming back. Uh, so where the fuck do I go?
What do I where do I go? I have no idea what the fuck i'm doing. Where do I go from here?
I'm in one of those fucking woods today. Yes. I am. Good luck. It's a landline phone, but you are already have a cell phone
Okay, it's the tv. It looks like it's plugged in but it's dusty the crack stream. It might be
It's chariel the beloved living room chair. Well, shall we go to school? Right? Yeah, chris. There you are
Even suzy showed up before you
Hey chris if I knew you were gonna be late
I would have I wouldn't have showed up on time
Suzy, please don't kick your desk
Treat school property like you treat people. Okay next time i'll aim for the vitals
And that's not it's not what I and in any case good morning class
We have a lot to go over today
First we're starting the reading from page 142
Any volunteers?
Um, I I guess I could read the
Ah trouble yourself. Not noelle
I will valiantly take this blow of humiliation
Uh, that's okay. I I can
Page 142
It was the best of times. It was the worst of times
Times are pretty good times are pretty bad
Mediocre times iffy times so so times listening to this your eyes begin to close automatically
Three voices omega l band that guy for a week listen to this
It's going to close
Have a nice day everyone and please remember your group projects. Oh, um chris. Are you okay? You were um sleeping all class
Don't worry. I i'm not mad just concerned
Usually you only sleep through the start good luck in the and rest well tonight. Okay slept through class
How many voices you got?
That's always such a stupid thing
Oh, yeah, how how how many can you do and i'm not trying to do them, right?
Oh, you think i'm so bad at that. Uh, what do you what do you have? I don't know
I don't i'm not doing the thing you're doing. I'm a fucking doctor dude
You're an e-clown and you have three voices when you come in for a checkup at the doctor's appointment
I don't stick the thing up your nose and then tell you to leave and then say you have nose hairs
I got i've got like 10 things I can diagnose on you. Actually they do
Wait, i'm supposed to be the reverse. Fuck. I fucked it up
Specialists are doctors that like there's a nose doctor, right? And all he does is look at your nose
I said it completely backwards. It was completely backwards. I meant it the other way. I've ruined everything
I actually meant to say it the other way if there's a nose doctor that looks only at your nose
So if the if you only do the nose doctor routine, it's fine
So if I can do one two three voices really good, that's fine because I can do them really good
I fucked up the whole routine. I you didn't lose sleep over it
Did you lost sleep from being susie's partner actually my sleep quality increased who is he talking to you?
Uh, what should I which one should I do the first one actually my sleep quality increased
I'm gonna say lost sleep from i'll do the actually my sleep my sleep quality increased. Oh chris. That's um good. I think
maybe you were just
Staying up late talking to asriel online again
Oh, wait, you can't do that, right? I hope the internet gets fixed soon. The internet doesn't work
I don't want to revert into my primal form. Oh, wait, okay
What does that mean? Well, look who it is the school zombie. He was sleeping like a corpse all class
What's the matter a trouble going to betty by last night?
Me too chris like I could sleep after yesterday
Just waiting for today felt like years. Did all that stuff really happen?
Lancer ralcy everyone. Are they are they uh, you've been wondering the same thing, right?
Come on already. So do we just go back into the supply? Where's the portal show up moment of truth?
Everything we've been waiting for is just behind this
We uh open this and there's nothing inside
Well, uh, we still be
Throw it. Let's just open it already. Um
susie
Yeah
Well, hey
What what the hell are you doing here? Um, so sorry to bother you but um, I
well, I just
Birdley and I were going to the library to do some research for our group projects and
If it's okay. Um, would you uh, would you want to come too?
Oh chris, you can come too. I mean, uh, I mean
like uh busy with um
Help me. What would you what do I do?
Hang out alone in the closet. We were doing crime
Uh, both of these. Okay. Um, i'm gonna say we were doing I don't i'm gonna say we're doing crime
You know just uh committing crimes
He's gonna do some crimes and go to jail
forever
It sucks
That's funny
What? Oh, well, that sounds uh, just have fun you two i'll be at the library
If you could bring her by later, it would mean a lot to me chris. What the hell was that?
Why would noelle ask me to do homework with her?
That's wish much. Does she want to fail? Wait a second. Wait a second
Did you notice how nervous she was and like blushing and stuff or she don't think that she uh,
She's onto our secret identities, you know this dark world stuff. Uh, damn. We gotta keep this under wraps chris
This is our thing, you know, anyway enough waiting already, right?
Let's go. So let's just hear
still here
Cool. All right
And ladies and gentlemen, welcome to delta rune chapter two. I'm your host for this festivities germa 985
I'm looking forward to it. Hey chris, uh, you really want to walk everywhere so slowly? I know you're kind of
Taking it in but you can run, you know, you remembered something about the b button. Oh, all right. When he said shut up, man
What's the over under of me ruining the delta rune and undertale for half the people here?
I hope it's not that high because I love this franchise just like you just like you here. We are chris suzy
It's been ever so long
Yeah, yeah, it's been what a day. Oh, that is short, isn't it?
It's just that i've never had friends before
So i've never waited so long to see them again either fine
I guess we'll try not to let you die of loneliness. I bet lancer wants to see us too, right?
Hey, where is that?
Where is the lancer? Where's everybody? Don't worry not suzy. You'll see them in a moment
Just wait here. All right
Aaron, okay. Hey, this better not be some kind of prank or something first. I have something to ask you
I need you to return to the light world
And go to the old classroom to the east of the closet doors
Inside gather everything on the ground and bring it back here. Could you go to the light world?
Wait, I just got here and I just not listen. Wait, this is a point
You look upon the castle you first saw yesterday. You're filled with the power of immediate nostalgia. Hey
file saved
Cool. All right. So should I just listen?
Okay, go to the east of the closet door and pick up stuff. I'm just gonna do it. Whatever. I'm gonna listen
Are you level two? I don't know
Okay east of the closet door
door is locked
Shit
I live on the west coast of the united states guys. I don't know it's yeah
It's I know listen
I told you I got the two hemispheres
Like the tortoise is the one that processes information and the hair is the one that makes all the stupid fucking voices you hear every day
Right all like the dumb things that I say is the hair running as fast as he can
The tortoise needs like extra time to even process what's happening on the screen. They're constantly in
Conflict with each other. They got the junk off the floor or doesn't do a giant dusty ball
What's in here managed to cram everything into the closet even the rug
Rockboard door is locked. What am I talking about? Well, you weren't here
Okay
That person was when you if you get people that saying what are you talking about weren't here 10 minutes ago
You can't jump halfway into like infinity war and ask who thanos is
Hey chris, so where is everyone?
There is
Guess who's back clowns
Lancer, I don't remember the voices I did but i'll i'll try
Hey chris, don't know what you did. But hell yeah
Everyone's here
But what happened to lancer's castle?
all gone
gone
Right when chris sealed the fountain that dark world disappeared
And turned back into a normal classroom
Where's lancer gonna live now?
Don't worry, susie
We'll conquer ralsleys ralsleys ralsleys. I can't say this word in this place ralses
castle is our own
ralsleys
As you bring dark world denizens back here
Power of our fountain will transform this town more and more
From now on the enemies we spare
Will be recruited to our town
So let's keep sparing enemies. Okay?
Anyhow, why don't we all have a look around
We can head north towards the castle. I have a special surprise to show you there
Not if I surprised myself first
Last one there is a fresh and fragrant egg
Come on chris. You're gonna let him beat us
Beat us. I thought you were racing
Yeah, I want to be the egg
It's funny the castle town is transformed for the power of friendship. You're filled with the power of friendship based architecture
Fruits fruits now, okay
It's a manual read a topic crudes. I'm curious if you spare or pacify enough enemies of the same type. They will be recruited
Recruits will appear in your town
Wonder what happens if you get them all you can check the area's recruit status at save points certain bosses are excluded
Okay, interesting. Can I go on the cafe?
Mama amoeba I wanted to run the bakery but someone is already working there
A cafe that serves pastries. What a disgrace
What sort of humiliating thing will happen next
Check recruits a real dust bunny known to play dirty, but loves to play clean dislikes vacuums likes dusty places
Do these people join the party?
Are these the enemies from last chapter? Yeah, but so I can place
Oh, they just hang out here. That's cool place. Okay
All right, who do I want? I kind of like rudin
Uh, I definitely like rabic
Block sir, okay on man level three house comment level three. Oh, it doesn't matter. Okay, and uh, I like jigsaw
Yeah, I like this group. We talked to them. Looks like it wants to be dabbed with rubbing alcohol. I'm an aide, please
Everything tastes better with a normally shaped body
Hey boss, i'll have a dark candy star fate. So they're gonna hang out here. What are your thoughts on the mario movie?
Uh, it'll have a it'll have a it'll have an 81 on rotten tomatoes
Uh, all right. Well the bakery. Oh, wait, this is um, wasn't it? Wasn't this? Yeah, this is the bad guy, but he wasn't
uh thou hast transplanted us to thine castle town and truly a magnificent town of castles at art
But oh, hmm, something art flattens its field
Couldest thou guys perhaps?
Bringe an evil ruler or something party dojo. Wait, I didn't even go in here. Oh, wait
I'm gonna be the welcome to top bakery our special chefs spin baked goods at the top of their class
For you seems like hath he likes this place. He hopes you'll like it too. I go in the party dojo
We can oh cool. All right, this is cool
It's a bed for three people or one three-headed person
Wow, our house is a dojo makes me want to fight
Can't we go to sleep?
He looks like fighting wasn't in the cards for us. Lucky for you. Just hope you don't meet my friends
Finally a dojo people that are normal shaped. I will train myself with the tournament. Hey boss boss
Hey, i'm so glad to have a nice boss. I could shed a tear
But I won't i'm on the job. I'll cry at home with the kids boss. You're so strong
But there's always time to learn the next step after tutorials is training
So me and the boys got you together a dojo complete our battle challenges and get some fabulous prizes
Meanwhile, you might get a little bit tougher. We're gonna make you the strongest boss
Learn how to spare like a champ jigsaw joe
Joe gray's challenge one or clover rematch jigsaw joe joe's life savings boss
Okay
You can act and spare on the same turn if you know chris's act will give an enemy 100 mercy
Spare them on the same turn with suzy or ralsei
Jigsaw joe jigs in okay
So this is chris
Uh, we're gonna do jigsaw joe
uh act
jigsaw joe
shave
Jigsaw joe jigs in okay, and then
spare jigsaw joe
Okay, and then what about you magic or should I try spare?
See what happens you shave jigsaw joe's stubble
Suzy spared jigsaw joe
Rousey spared jigsaw joe. Oh boss, you're sparing me
Wait a second. I got something else to remind you of
boss
It works the same with making an enemy tired
If an act will make an enemy tired use ralsei's pacify right away
Of course pacify is magic. So you'll need tp
Spend a turn defending to gain tp if you have to boss
Okay, looks like you could use a bedtime story. So we're uh
we're gonna do act or
Jigsaw joe sleepy story
Jigsaw joe looks like you could use a bedtime story and then we're gonna do um pacify right? Oh, wait. No
Everybody no back up back up back up back
bend
Defend oh, no, no bend defend
um pacify wait
Oh, no, you're gonna okay sleepy. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I mean you can't yeah. I don't we don't need tp to do that
Oh, it's an act. Okay. I thought we needed tp for some reason
All right came she came tired and then ralsei cast pacify and you're done
You managed to spare enemies right away battles will go a lot faster. Okay. Here's your reward my entire life savings
One dollar. All right, let's see. Should I do another one raise challenge one get 100 tp without getting hit
Uh, these are like challenges. We're gonna do this later. I'm battles master. Ask me about battles
Raising hitbox nothing. I think I remember a lot of this stuff grazing is if a projectile comes really close
But doesn't touch you you get like something for it right tp or something
It's whole
We failed to hit our funding goal. I will not talk about our whole
Okay, what thoughts aren't always as they appear?
The bigger they are the less to fear you'll only get hurt a little inside take your pride and learn the size
Everybody said you're gonna get 12 hours out of this at your pace
i'm not like
I'm i'm one of them i'm doing what I want when shots aim directly try to move slow
Yeah, because if it almost hits you, yeah
Move it bit by bit. You'll gain tp. That's what it is. I'm taking i'm gonna take my time. I'm i'm excited for this
I love undertale. That was a great series. It's a really cool game
So and I like delta runes the first chapter so i'm going to enjoy the second chapter
That means i'm not going to a a a a a a a to get through this as fast as I can
I'm going to talk to townspeople. I'm sorry. That's how it is. But just a block with a shop. What's in here?
Welcome travelers
Andy that's a heel dark burger
amber card armor defensive charm spooky sword
Okay, cool. Let's talk. So we're now in the castle town
Well now it makes no difference to me as long as I stay in my shop these walls won't change
You don't have your jevil item
No, I don't well
In a way, I suppose it's just a little bit amusing to see you again. I'm sure you three will have an interesting journey
Me i'll just be here offering the same old junk
As you find stronger treasure, i'm sure you'll have a little reason to return here
If you have some time i'll offer you a biscuit and a hint
Have a hint the little prince has something to show you in his castle
Well, now are you going to turn down a royal invitation?
He again
Okay
Cool. Talk to you. I talk to you. Oh wow has transplanted this to the thine castle town. I already talked to you already
Oh, it's quite a wonderful town. Really. Thank you. So why am I alone here a bit of self-reflection? I suppose
I do realize I was quite a coward before
So I wanted to say well
I still am
My cards I cannot handle society but now i'll be living at the top of this cliff
When i'm ready to meet society again, I will be back
Thank you. Thank you for the wonderful home. I will not use it. There's a hole in the wall. There's nothing inside
What about this side? I love this character this character right here. I want to recruit this person. Mr
Society left didn't he? Hmm. I reckon I knew this would happen. It's not a no fault of yours
Yeah, i'll be back one day without trees
I must gain nutrients by eating clothes such as the way of the worm looks like the clothes are nibbled take a bite
Yes, you put your mouth against the mannequin's cheek
chris
Don't bother it tastes awful
And sushi did it too
I like being like this
Don't tell anybody
This seems to be locked may never open again. Oh, this is okay. I know what that is. That's my favorite character
All right, I explored the town a little bit save it. Let's go continue on
Dragged out playthrough of delta rune chapter two. Look i'm gonna screw up a few times. Whatever i'll learn
We'll do we'll just get back in the swing of things here. All right, here we go
This is a bit scary moving to a new place. But as a ball
There's nothing to sphere except sphere itself. I missed the bakery. I tried to go
I thought I tried to go in the bakery and I go in there
Yeah, I i'm gonna have i'm gonna have to get very upset with chat here for a second
If I said that if we just saw the ball character and I said there's nothing to sphere but sphere itself
Half of you would want me to turn the stream off. That's not fair. Oh, I am chef lancer
Try my delicious hand-formed cookies
They're free here for a price. What's the price zero dollars?
I'll take a cookie. I now pronounce you cookie and wife
Lancer cookie was added to your items. Well, well
Welcome to top bakery. I am this bakery smith malias
I do not know what any of these strange tools are for
Using my skills. I can fuse items to create new ones
XS
Ed double dark burger the dd but the double dark
Bouncing bunker burger. Okay. This is two dark burgers to make a double d burger two amber cards is a silver card
All right, so I just gotta go. Let's just let's go. I'm ready. XS
Your body is a weapon too. You must take care of it from time to time. Haha
Sorry
Haha, I can do better
Haha, let's feel my technique
There you go. Somehow everyone's hp was restored. Well, well, don't you feel better after a nice massage?
Ah, it hurts. I'm gonna do it again
Lancer cookie is what one already took a cookie
Wait, i'm still regenerating from the last one. I don't know why he's talking like that
But it's what is that's what i've decided he was gonna talk like. Okay, let's go. You can't fix germa
All right, so let's go prince rousey. I will keep your hat aracked until you need it
That's a cool character too. You want to show off your huge house, huh?
Now what I want to show you is upstairs
Oh, I nearly forgot. This is where I cook cook everything in a giant witch's pot
You're pronouncing rousey wrong. What is it? You mean it phonetically in the chat
rousely rousely rousy ral rat rat rail say ral say
Ral say of course cauldron cooking is very convenient here chris suzy have a cake
Hmm a little thick on the frosting that was for sharing
Anyone was free to make an interception. That's true second floor living quarters. Okay. Well, let's not do that yet
Doors locked. Okay, come on over here. What's this bottom floor living quarters for bad guys?
Wait, it's violently protecting the jail. We're still behind bars for some reason, but it's okay
We
Grown to love this hellish place where we dress as animals. We decided to dress as kings. It's cultural
exchange
disgusting
And they're not even big crazy burps either that's the most embarrassing
You know how many times i've actually squelched those and you haven't heard them at all if they were like
People would be like, holy shit, bro, but there's like little mouse burps like oh hold on
Uh
No, mr. King the the lighteners returned everyone here safely if you're willing to reconsider then
Living a kingdom ruled by you
lighteners little patsy
Staying in this cell is far less humiliating
Now if you'll excuse me a giant hamster wheel is getting cold
By the way, is my son happy like you care you were gonna throw him off a cliff
All right, your prejudice made my bluff too effective. I see
Besides even if I threw me would just bounce
my son is
Bouncy little pumpkin. Oh cute. We have nothing to discuss. All right, go upstairs
And what do you buy? I want to show you is up here. I have a surprise for you two
I made rooms for you in the castle
Rooms so you can stay here whenever you want
Uh, i'd be happy if this place could be like a second home to you
Place that you can go
No matter what's happening outside
Well, we'll take a look
Uh, please tell me i get the rocko's modern life door
That better be my room
Susie, this is your room
Um, I tried to make it something you'd like
You can put anything else you want in here, too
I really hope you like it
My own room, huh? I guess that's pretty cool
My own room like this
How long did it uh
Take you to do all this?
Well eric since I last saw you two I am
Ow
It's pushed me in my mouth. You pushed me in my mouth. I'm bleeding
And you're a real weenie. You know that
I think she likes it chris
Jealous, I got the cool room. Look chris
What does my room look like?
Cool spike bed now I can stab myself during the night
Finally some convenience
Damn, there's everything in here
Iron cones chalk
Moss jars of salsa pieces of ice
Black crumbs from the toaster jaw breakers
Oh and like actual food too the clothes draw full of spiky and dangerous clothing
All the clothes are ripping each other up into shreds
Hell, yeah jealous chris
Susie you didn't get to read the manual so I put it over here for you
Cool. I'll read it before bed. That'll put me to sleep
Let's go
I want to see my room
It's your bed feels incredibly soft like sleeping on a dream
It's a stand for your manual. I thought you might want to keep it here in case you want to read it
This is the manual
Okay, it's a shelf all sorts of keepsakes could be but there might be hidden items here
It's a wardrobe full of all sorts of different clothes
Wear whatever you want nice. I think that deserves a coffee chug
Cool. This is lancer's room lancer. You aren't gonna believe how sick my room is
The room is sick is yours. Whoa, I want to see
I'll keep digging holes until I reach your room
It's got a door, you know
Door wow peach boy you went all out
Wow, it's better than I remember
I even have my own bed now. I don't have to sleep in a hole anymore. I thought you already had a bed
No, that was for the bike
The hole made recreationally is goofy change his voice change. No more goofy. Don't do goofy anymore
I have to change
You know, is it not canonically in your head? It's not like a kind of low but goofy kind of voice. We hate this voice
Is it as bad?
It's terrible
Lancer is a child. Oh, right. Okay. Let me see what I can do. I love that. My floor is full of holes
Better. Hey ralsei, what's up here? Oh just more rooms. I'm renovating
So is your room up there?
Uh, yes, I still haven't dusted it though. Yeah, like we need to see your nerdy glasses collection
Anyway, well didn't you say what you wanted to show me was upstairs?
Sorry work in progress
But and that was I want to show you something upstairs. Oh is that that's what you want to do
Okay, feel free to explore the town until you're ready to leave
We're gonna leave now right chris. You are upstairs. Oh, you want to show me the rooms imagine how rude that would be
Oh, I want to show you guys something upstairs. Okay, cool. So here are your rooms
This is your room. I spent like two months doing all this shit
I hired the construction team you all here on separate rooms. Oh, yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yep
So what did you want to show us up here? That's fucking so rude
Uh, the fucking cool rooms I made all three of you
Yeah, right. It was cool
I don't know why I thought it was gonna be an item or something. I was like, I don't know
I think i've explored enough
Get the gist of what's going on here. It's time to leave wait chris. We're leaving but we just got here
Yeah, I don't want to go do our group project
Oh, you two have homework
uh, well
susie
Chris you'll have to do it right away school's important
I banish you from this kingdom until you start your project
Fine, i'll do it geez
susie
Don't worry. I'll go and help you too
You know what lancer perhaps you shouldn't oops wrong voice too late kind boy friendship form
The answer was added to your key items, but where'd you go?
Don't worry. I just entered your inventory
I'll just be hanging out in chris's pocket. I don't know what that means, but okay
Fear not. I too shall assist
Uh, we're good
Oh quiet. We as a team are good
Roxels became a key item even though no one wanted that
All right. I know already. Let's get going. Good luck today chris. See you soon. See you soon
Well, damn guess we gotta do our project
sigh
At least we got lancer right answer. Where are you?
Because you skipped out after all, huh?
So what what should we where should we do this?
The library
Oh, well, all right. So when we go to the like that the dark world, right?
That's the only place they were allowed to exist
They don't exist here in like the other world
Okay
Maybe they do
All of junk and cards
Yeah, I don't have anything stat. Oh, no, I don't have anything
Okay, interesting
We're gonna go to the library
But not quite yet. The locker is locked the locker is locked
The locks locker is locked
The lockers locks locker is locked computer wallpaper is updated the buff embracing heroes are now edited to be four inches apart
This dialogue about proper distancing at the school dance. You wonder if your mother had some influence on this change
It's a bunch of roses looks like motivational quotes from various literature. Try your best
Astral wolf even in your darkest hour that one seems to be from a video game you ran the water fountain
It's lukewarm
Locker it's locked. Oh i'm wear this this used to be your brother's locker
This used to be your brother's locker locker. It's locked. Okay
Oh, wait a minute. What's all this?
Miss toriel is written in cursive on the dry erase board seems like it hasn't been erased in a very long time
You uncapped the scented green marker. It's almost dry, but that gives it a refined aged apple bouquet
The poster of several basic shapes circle oval square paper dose to chadron kids book
Some of them used to be yours marker sniffer. It's an orange
It's unknown if it's safe for teachers to eat this groan of the gods it grows higher. Is this hubris?
Okay, cool. What's on the computer? Computer wallpaper is updated. Uh, wait, wait, wait, wait
Do it again. Do it again. I missed it picture of your brother and you playing video games
Your brother is using the knockoff controller. Yeah, that was me
Mm-hmm, but here's the one thing about that knockoff controller that us little brothers in the chat will remember
Uh, some of those had a turbo feature and uh, yeah
Being able to shoot whatever the weapon I was shooting at five million miles a second while my brother was kind of annoyed by it
Turned out okay to me turn the turbo on hold x turn the turbo on hold y
Yep
It was a little switch on the front or back of the controller, right? Hold on. Are you ready for the sadie?
Hawkman's dance at this dance all the chaperones wear giant hawk heads and screech at any students that make contact while dancing
Okay, let's go. I check everything. I know this is how I play rpgs
There's so much to see the band practice
This is this is what it sounds like right before a band starts to play
Well, okay am I was just directing traffic as normal when a little dog drove one of these toy cars
Into the middle of the street and started doing donuts in the chaos all the cars in town got jammed up
Thankfully, no one was hurt but ordinary citizens like you got to get out of here
I've got some heavy lifting to do every time I see that face
I have to do a different I have to get a little weird don't interrupt me when i'm lifting
I heard a dog was doing donuts so I sped over here
But I just learned donuts is actually the name of a special attack for cars
Is my life stuck in a loop of doughy disappointment graphics moving at a snail's pace?
I love snails today get any better looks like a car looks like a car. Well, I can't go anywhere. All right, we're here
School god damn project
Looks god damn crazy about them
Hey chris, where the hell is everybody?
Something seems kind of off
Screw it. Let's just go play space pinball in the computer lab. Wait, it's another one of these
huh
It's like the inside of the closet chris. You don't think this could be
Another dark world. Well
I guess this means we can't start our project
Unless you know chris if there's a dark fountain in there
You can seal it
It'll turn back into the computer lab, right?
So what's it gonna be chris?
Let's go. Let's go. We can just use the computer in my house
I mean this one's the that's the boring answer. Let's go. Let's do I have to say it
Let's say it the way like loud
Okay, do you want me to say it like 12 year old xbox live loud?
Or 36 year old man loud which one?
Okay, 12 12 i'm seeing a lot of it
All right
Let's go
Yeah, let's just drop the act
Our last adventure was great, right?
I couldn't stop thinking about having another
I don't know what's in there, but
Can't live if we don't find out right?
Come on chris
So is this gonna be the same place or is it gonna be like a different?
Multiverse or something. I wonder
This is new
This is new. So what the heck's going on here?
Oh shit
Wait inspect
Inspect that this the wires the wires
You're right
Hey
All right. I get it. Let's plug anything in
Oh shit
Ow, oh there they are again. Everyone was
Everyone else has been
Save us. She's going to
Somebody help me
Somebody please
Susie
Cool that you're here. Just uh, like get out of here before it's too late
Noelle
Fuck that
Hell of a study session
Who the hell are you?
I am known as serial number q5u for ex7 yy2 e9l
But you foolish children may call me
queen
Like you're gonna call you queen
Q five three, I don't know queen
Well, look queen. We're not children
Teens are merely big children and adults are even bigger children
Doesn't that make you a child too then?
No, I am a computer smart
computer
Well, thank you for the stimuli, but I must leave now. Goodbye
Hey, where are you going? Why'd you capture noelle?
Oh, I would have captured you too, but I ran out of cages
Why the capturing?
So that she may become my willing peon
In my quest for world domination
Also, maybe I will make her face into a robot one. I who knows I could
Wait, why?
Seems cool
Well, forget it, dude
Nobody's turning anyone's face into a robot
Could that be a statement of animus dissension?
Huh?
You want to fight loser?
Yes. Yes already. Yes
Oh, then bye
Wait, what? Wait a second
I have no time for such frivolities
And would kick your ass in a second
Perhaps someone else could entertain you
Enjoy your assimilation
We're wires swung in
Okay, they're tired. They're already tired
so
and I do
Row wire jiggle jiggle might try to pull the wire off the head
Row what toss christophe free wire? Yeah
What the fuck press y to throw an aim for the weak point? Oh, I can get them both
The wire greatly loosened. Okay, cool
That's 50. All right, almost there
All right. Oh, I was gonna say don't act like I don't know what to do
All right, let's do it again
Okay, uh throw wire. Let's try this again
So are they ready?
That's 50 percent, right?
All right spare
You're ready to go
And can we spare them both? Probably not. No
No, we can only spare them just one
Spare the where wire recruit. Oh, I've recruited right right right suzy spared where wire but its name wasn't yellow
Try using x
Oh shit
Yeah god gamer alert
Those you that by the way, I have to really make this really really really important note to everybody here
I'm bad at a lot of things very bad
Um, you put me in like call of duty whatever i'm gonna get like fucking zero and 20 during the game, right?
I sometimes I get lost. I don't know east from west
But you watch this shit and after this fucking stream. I want to hear you talk about how I what I can and cannot do
Okay
Good. I want to hear what do you think? I can and cannot do after this
After the well after this part
He can't reach the cookie jar fucking ban that guy
See what are you talking about?
Oh my god. All right. That's that was
I'm fine. I'm just not gonna hit
All right act let's go
Oh my god
I just okay. I'm not throwing i'm not tilted. I just it's weird. It's different
Okay. Now i'm fucked up now. You got me fucked up. You got me fucked up you do
This is why you never call a home run. I don't know how people did that shit
Like when babe ruth used to like get his ass up to the plate and like hold the bat up
It's just like holy shit, dude. What if you just strike out right now? You look like a dickhead
I'll get it right now
imagine calling a home run and the pitcher like
Just strikes you out in three pitches
That probably happened to all the time. There was no there was no television to see that
And how come people don't do that anymore don't you think it'd be funny?
It would be all over sports center
All right. I'm not gonna stop fucking around spare
You won got 188
D dollars
Nice fighting again after so long now, let's go catch up to the queen
Or not wait they calm down
I just used my pacify spell to put them into sleep mode
Rousey you're here. I felt a dark presence and hurried over it seems that a new dark fountain has appeared
Rousey they got noelle
Damn, what was she thinking messing in our dark world? We don't do something. She might be
Hurry not suzy. All we have to do is seal the fountain
Yeah, yeah, yeah, you'd be mad about another adventure right come on chris
No
What's this
What's going on? Do I have to touch those touch them?
I thought I thought it was like a guitar hero game. Whatever. What do I do?
Am I doing this right?
Whoa
The green field extends before you and in the distance the city shines brightly
You're filled with the power of a new adventure
Very cool
very cool
Cyber world
Turn it up
Uh, it's already pretty loud, isn't it?
How's that? I'll turn up the music stuff
Very cool. All right. Nice
Whoa, okay
Where wire is swung in? Okay. So now we have
Can um can rousey do anything?
Rousey has magic
pacify right
It's very tired foe. All right
Are they already tired? They already are tired, aren't they?
I believe they are but whatever we're gonna go for it. Just depend. Shit
All right, same deal
and then you
Uh, we're gonna pacify
you
Shit, sorry
Rousey cast pacify
Just one that's fine easy
Well, I can just pass what can I pass by?
What is it? How much how much uh pp is it 16? Yeah, whatever we're good
pacify
Big with a wire, but I like doing the aim, uh downsides
Oh treasure chest
You opened the treasure chest inside was a glow wrist low wrist was added to your armors. Ooh
cuteness
Amber card thin square charm that sticks to you increases defense. What about what's a glow wrist? Who should have the defense probably chris
Everyone else just has that wait white ribbon
Crinkly hair ribbon that slightly increases your defense. Is amber card better? No
That is so behind compared to the stream refresh really
All right, I don't want to miss anything
Does that let's go this way i'm gonna go all the way to what's that queen rules
That's living five minutes in the past
Whoa. All right. Well now what?
What do I have to do?
I have to match the oh, hold on
I don't I don't get it
Oh, yeah, I do. Okay. I thought I had to collect them with different characters
All right. Well, here we go. Here comes a good good. You know what it is. Oh
Fuck I get this but I don't get it somehow at the same time
Certain characters have to touch them because they're different. They're different colored look. Oh chris. It's a free
Edible cyberpedia
I'll add an entry
I'll see you brought an article about losing recruits. Would you like to read it?
Sure
From now on defeating enemies with violence will make them lost
Lost enemies can't become recruits ever again
The bonds you break may make you stronger
And so if you kill people they're gone
I'm gonna try to spare as many people as I can
Lighteners
I haven't seen many of you recently
If you didn't know an evil ruler is taking over this world
I don't really like politics. So I have no opinion on this
If you tried it too, oh, I said something
I've missed that we will have no choice but to cross swords
I'm gonna say it again. If you try to talk to me about politics, we will have no choice but to cross swords
Oh shit
caskeys
Crossed your path
All right, what we got?
uh
Check petting soft voice or roar
check check
and
Rude buster. No check and defend. I don't want to swing the sword
Okay, here we go. Uh
Pacify I can't do that eel prayer. All right, we're gonna defend
This stray cat is in need of some management
Meow meow meow
Okay, so needs management
So how about um
soft voice
Roar. All right, we're gonna roar
Who's each roared the enemies became tired. Oh shit. Here we go
Who's king of the jungle now?
It's just a cat
Yeah
All right. Let's uh, we can't spare
But we can act
Let's do another roar
That's a burping
All right pacify
Does he roar the enemies became tired again rousy cast pacify?
Yeah, yeah, yeah
Tired um, maybe I should pet. All right. What if I pet you pet ask it liked that
And then pacify. Okay
He won
We didn't have to hurt anything. I gotta check up here
Leave no stone untouched
Recently something called internet is having an outage
Some say it was the secret to queen's know-how
Since then it seems like she's become quite extreme
Unturned not untouched
Become my willing peon and I will free you
All you have to do is hit yes on the peon release form
scared
Oh, have you never signed a form before?
No, it's everything else. That's scary
Please abort your sadness protocol
I told you being a peon will be cool
newell suzy chris
Don't worry. We won't let your face get roboticized
That's something they're gonna do
Oh, whoops, I I thought you knew that
Dear that was supposed to be a surprise
Oh well
Wait, it is quite troubling a peon must be willing to assist me in world domination
If only she had follow peons to encourage her
So
so like
you guys
Hey
Are you like
Doing anything right now?
We aren't gonna help you
understood mind-changing protocol
necessitated
giant arcade game
I shall humiliate you at a simple children's diversion
With your self-esteem eradicated
There will be no choice but to serve me
The hell i've never played this one before
Chris it's quite good at games chris is quite good at games aren't they?
Oh, yeah chris forgot you were a nerd show her
Oh, fuck i'm not ready
It's hard to perform in front of people when you're not ready
Oh chris congratulations on losing horribly
I advanced my internal clock to when i've already won
Also, happy birthday suzy happy birthday
It's not my birthday
Okay, you tried to use the arcade machine
You weren't tall or strong enough to use the controls
That's why self-esteem eradication complete
Running laughing protocol
Uh, it's okay chris, uh, i'm short too
Chris wait
I have an idea
Chris if we can combine our powers then
Look, i'll show you what i've been practicing
Magical stool form are
Jesus
Okay
Now we're talking. All right chris leave it to me. Uh-huh. Everybody get over here so I can stand on them
Put your arms out
Our beast form s
Move your arms and i'll move them with you
Let's go
Oh my fucking god incredible
Your transformation is combining all your weak points
Self-esteem crushing efficiency 300 and rising
Commence virtual combat
Wait, we're gonna play like street fighter
round one fight
What the hell press a or b if you dare
Shut up
Just punch out. I'm so good to punch out. You've no idea
All right, should I let him win?
Should I let uh, is this is this pacifist if I do it in a video game?
Oh duck. Oh shit. I don't have to do it more than once
I'm so good to punch out. You've no idea
Yeah, I thought you could beat us. Why that was actually quite amusing
New life forms have exceeded my expectations
I will offer you a new exceedingly benevolent compromise
assimilated into my cyber army
And there is only a 50% chance. I will reprogram your face
Please select your choice
perish in the chill of absolute destruction
or
Flourish under the warm bosom of my hellish rain
Wait, we we can be just join the bad guys. What do I do?
Isn't but isn't perish fight. I wonder if it's should I just do this?
I think this is oh, let's fight. I let's I don't want to fight
Let's go for it
uh
blism
It means titty
We know what it means. We aren't helping you
Understood preference setting set to perish
Come on, let's go after her
Game is wrecked you're filled with the power of video game violence
I want to go back to the city, but the way is blocked
I'm no country boy. Let me out of cyber field
I heard there's a rebel team resisting queen
So far all I found are overpriced bagels
yo
snicker
It's hard work being queen's minion ain't it?
Why don't you take a break and grab a snack?
Grab a snickers
And I I gotta talk about this really quickly
um
So, you know like that like it snickers, right? It's like, oh, yeah, is he hungry? You need a snickers
I can't remember the last time I got hungry and wanted to eat a fucking candy bar
Why do they do that ad campaign? I don't understand
Old material don't care
You said this before I don't care
I'm I don't get hungry and want to oh, you know what? Let me go to a convenience store and get go to the candy aisle
And who carries around a king-size snickers in their
purse or pocket or something nobody does that
I i'm not going to eat that
Do you carry around a full bar snickers in your pocket?
They always seem to have one on them
Thank god somebody had a full king-size snickers in their pocket
What?
Why don't you take a break and grab a snack?
ultra cd cd
bagels only 400 each
It's the peanuts
Why don't you eat peanuts then?
Peanuts are easier to carry
They can fit in a little bag. They're dry
You just eat peanuts
You don't need to eat the chocolate nougat and what other junk they put in there
Just have trail mix in your pocket. Why would you eat a snickers when you're hungry?
All right, uh, how much money i've 500 to buy one of these
It's a bagel
I have five i'm gonna buy it
As you're doing business with you
Have a snickers
cd bagel was added to your items
Want to buy a bagel only 80 dollars?
Okay, hello
It's 400
Got it
Want to buy 400 bagels
80 dollars
Oh shit
Yes
You were crushed under the weight of 400 bagels and defeated instantly. Wait, what?
Not really. You just can't carry that man
One bagel 80 dollars 400 bagels 80 dollars
I'll take one bagel, please. Can I have one two?
You're selling them
Oh, I got scammed. Whoops
What is it? What are they?
Oh shit
Bagel with a reflective inside makes music with each bite. Oh god. Damn it. I did get scammed
Oh, that game looked fun. Let me be the stool next
We tried to call on the cell phone
I missed an area
What the fuck was that? It's nothing but garbage noise
Cuisine is so unrefined out here in the
sticks
Mr. Room. Oh shit
What's this guy? I can't tell you how many of these i've cleaned up
Not so bad
I like cleaning
All right, so I missed a door where I didn't miss anything
What's he talking about?
Oh up this way
Okay apple
Chris, I think you should handle this puzzle
apple a
b
e
a a p
a p
I'm I want to say it so bad
I'm gonna say it so bad
I had to do it. I'm sorry. What that was like not even a bad meme. What are you talking about? It's funny
I liked it. What's wrong with it?
Looks like you got past newbert's force field
Newbert doesn't know how that force field got there
It's newbert's force field
I surprise have newberts treasure
Newbert doesn't know what's inside newbert will give it to you
I love newbert
You open the treasure chest inside was fiber scarf fiber scarf was added to your weapons
fiber scarf for
Uh
you
Okay
Ooh a scarf made of soft microfiber balances attack and magic
That's pretty good
pretty good
Anything else to say newbert that's newbert's treasure
Remember you're just borrowing it forever. I like that guy. Okay. Well, what do you have to say?
Recently something called internet is having oh, yeah the internet
By the way, so the queen's been using the internet too much and and now she's gone crazy or something. The internet is down
All right, so i'm gonna let me go down
Down or up i'm going down first. She lost the internet
Can't go this way. It looks like I get dumped out this way
Hey, what up?
Is this a slide?
I'm the hacker. I'm going after the blue check marks
Find three in the cyber field ahead and i'll join your city
You just look like the kind of folks who have a cool city
According to cyber you found zero blue check marks out of three
Zero not bad for a beginner
Your check quest is only beginning
Okay, please go to find three blue check marks
like here
We'll go down from here
stupid
Hey
All right, we're good
Uh, they're they're not tired yet
No, so we're gonna do soft voice
And you're gonna defend
Rousey talked in a soft voice to the enemies
There there. It's okay little kitty
That worked
Ask his image
Eight bits. All right, let's spare
Spare three to five four to five
You won. I love this song. This song's great
ooh
You open the treasure chest inside was below wrist lovers was added to your arm is nice
All right. So who who has you have a glow wrist?
You could have two glow wrists on
But we're gonna give you one to everybody if we can
What's going on here
Seems to be stuck
Can I help?
I don't think I can help
If you don't finish this today, you're gonna finish it tomorrow. Yes
Plan was if this didn't take me too long
I was going to play the umbrella game
But if i'm just kind of pacing myself through the game, we'll do it tomorrow
All right, this is locked up. It appears to be some kind of force field
god
Vero vicaron
Vero vir Vero
Vero virocon
Okay
What are those check?
Take care check and
Uh, Vero virocon this sick virus needs affordable health care
I'm the fifa. I'm the chill
Okay
sweating suspiciously
All right act take care x or take care. I will take care x
Everyone treated the enemy with tender loving care. All the enemies felt great
I think this is contagious
Okay, it looks healthy
Is that it?
is
Sweet am I gonna play the outer wilds expansion? Oh, yeah, that's right
Agree to all. Oh shit. This is another puzzle. You do it
uh
Agree
Okay, a agree
uh
re
So how do I do this agree to all?
Diver brain i've been 30 seconds. It's a puzzle. Let me do it
agree
Oh, I know
To shit how do I do this a's?
Okay, wait, hold on
Okay
I win. I win. I win
You typed agree to all
Thank you for agreeing to this p on release form
Now you are all legally my minions and I can use your likeness for funny statues
But we just don't do what you say
In that case, I would be forced to use another guy probably
I better get started on that then
Okay, but i'm still going to use your likeness
What did I get for that? Where's my trinket?
Can I get a trinket?
Where's my trinkets? I didn't get anything for that
What I disagree to all
Well shit, I want to recruit you got a check mark
Oh
Oh, okay, I see
Oh fuck that hurt. Oh, no, he didn't yet. Yes, I did
No, oh no, he didn't
All right, so four out of four
You won
So what is it? I got four to four. All right. Well, what if I go up here?
There's a hole in the area. I did not explore. So
How's this work?
Yeah, good luck figuring out which ride to take
It's right ride is the right one
Uh the analog i'm using i'm using a controller
Oh, i'm gonna get i'm using an analog controller. It's weird
It gets that kind of stuck. I got it. Just everyone relax
Yep
Oh a blue check mark. How can only one of them be right?
They're testing every one of them
Oh shit. No, I wanted the other one
It's probably a chest
Wait, what I don't
Is this progression?
That other one goes up
I'm going this way
Oh, we're getting backseated. Uh, oh
Didn't do it right. He didn't do it right. Ah
G
g s fell for rare burr
This is gonna be fucking all day g
Okay
g i a
S was s from here s
f e l
f e b
What's above me?
f
f e
Okay, hold on
g i a
f e l
Fuck
No, wait, I have to go this way. Wait, I can go. Let me try this way
b i a
Oh my god
s f e l
I think I had it right the first time
f e b
I can't there's another g
There's only two g's on the one that's there's only two possible entries
f e l
f e b
r e h
h b e r
Fuck fuck fuck
Hold on g
F e b r e h
Oh my god, there was a b I thought I don't know why my brain thought that was an eight
Oh, I got it. Thank you. Uh, thank you
So that's three check marks. Let's go turn it in
Found three check marks elite. I will now live in your city
Maybe our cyber path will cyber cross once more in queen's mansion
In the meantime, let me show you the power up of the blue check marks
Wow, you made fireworks
Oh pretty
Beautiful. You got verified on twitter
Very nice. I just wanted to make a cool demo scene for you now that I finished this I can show up all sorts of places
Okay
Very nice
Well, thanks. All right this one this place. I didn't go
I didn't go up here
I feel like I didn't go somewhere over here, too
Oh, can I go up from there?
It appears to be some kind of force field. No
I don't want to fight you. Oh wait, I gotta go up from there and then progression is the one on the left
All right one on the right
Okay
Okay, I don't like that. He's gonna drop something on me. We're gonna drop the cages on us. I told you this is gonna be wild
You guys want a tip?
Always stand in the middle. Whoops. I didn't do my own tip
There's more this is bigger. Oh shit
dead end
All right. What's the deal twerp?
Who's a twerp a name sweet? Oh like sweet like sweets
Don't tell me you haven't heard of the sweet captain cakes
Doesn't ring a bell
I guess our acts still a bit underground
Sweet captain cakes. Not only are we cyberfield's best musical trio
We're also the last resistance against a big bad queen and all her crew
That starts with you
What we're fighting the queen too
No, uh captain saw you help her kidnap some girl
Hey, hey, hey cap
We won't let anyone lay a finger on the mademoiselles
Except us that's not the point captain
It's like half the point 60 55. We're rebels not players
We're rebels that play we don't play we don't play
That's it
Okay
Get over here. Okay. I don't who's this
Okay. Okay. Are we players?
I'm a cd player
Wait, they're getting away
Sweet chill there'll be other bad guys. No, this is our chance
Are you ready? Let's fight
Okay
Yeah, play some battle music
Sweet captain cakes blocks your way
Okay, not dancing
All right, sweet kk and captain
Not currently dancing i'm gonna have to say let's go with sweet. Let's do a check
Maybe just start dancing. All right, let's do dance x
Everyone danced with sweet. They're totally lost in the groove
Hey, I love this song ring-a-ding-dong
Isn't this mix?
shway
After if we can get them all to dance we can win
All right. So that is a swede's dancing
Let's just do the same thing. Let's do
Hey kates dance
Everyone dance with kk. They're totally lost in the group
All right. All right. All right. All right. All right dance dance. Everybody dance. Hey, I love this song
I'm gonna watch over the baseballs up top. All right sweet snapped out of the dance. Oh, oh shit
Wait, wait, I can't dance with bad guys
All right, so we have to do
Just the regular dance
Because then yeah
No, not rude damage
Shit because once somebody has it the other one breaks out. Let's see what happens if I do the regular dance you dance
So we got lost in the groove
Dance dance dance do they pay the venue fee?
Okay, it snapped out of it. Wait, I can't dance with bad guys. I've got my next dance moves. Okay, so nobody's dancing
Shit
All right
Maybe making one of them dance will make the other ones dance. Let's try that
Let's do the cap
dance extreme
Everyone dance with cap and they're totally lost in the group
Wait, you want to see my move?
Hey, is this really working?
maybe if chris, um
Maybe if we tried ballroom dancing instead
Hey, why the hell do we need chris to act?
Because that's um chris's unique talent
so
You think i'm too stupid to dance by myself?
Susie learned s action. She can act from her magic menu. Okay
Susie, I don't think you should
Happy feet dumbass
Susie made rousey learn our action even though he didn't want to
Oh, it's charlie brown dance
I'm sorry chris
Okay, so now they can actually do it
So sweet dance
magic
s action
dance
And then magic r action dance. There we are. Okay
Everybody's dancing now. Everyone is dancing
Battle one
All right feel the beat watch my moves dance dance
Hey losers wrap it up battles over
over
In other type words we lost
Does that mean we can be friends?
kk, no
Fighting is not really my style. Anyways, yeah because you're a coward
I mean, it was fun dancing but sweet. Don't worry
I think our dancing beat them beat them. Yeah all mercy like
See when we danced with them it convinced them. We're cool
Now they're on our side
Yes
Hey you three welcome to the good side
We are the good side. Just go with it. Let's rendezvous at our junk shop
We jam the door shut but we'll kick it open
All right, everybody let's go
Very cool. Very cool
I gotta watch out probably. Yep. Well, why are they still doing this? We're friends
Oh, no, we're fine. Oh the hacker is hacking the fireworks
I'm not gonna run through this i'm gonna wait
It's cute. Jerma says very cool. Like he's trying to placate a giant beast
what
What oh very cool. Very cool
Very cool
What what's that tweet that that thing that somebody said before like a year or two ago?
This stream is just me. It's as if i'm talking to like a room full of just angry chimpanzees
That at the turn of a moment could just lash out and try to attack and kill me. What is it? What was it?
That's like this whole stream or something. It's like i'm trying desperately to like calm a bunch of like angry chimpanzees
What was it? What was it called? Somebody's got it somewhere
I want the I want the whole paragraph
Snarl
That's pretty much it. Just keep standing there
Hey, somebody pull up a two-year-old tweet right now
Oh, no links are banned right forever if we go
Oh here it is. Okay. Jerma talks to his chat like they're apes with a very loose grasp on human language
And if he fails they will rip him to shreds
Jerma talks to his chat like they're apes with a very loose grasp of human language
That's so funny
All right, is this the shop? It's a lone door frame, but for some reason you can't see through it
Oh, here's the shop. I heard this unassuming store is the rebel base, but I realized I don't really know how I would help them
It's uh, i'm sitting here going
Okay, guys. Look at me. Look at me
Okay, so I was at the store yesterday and uh, I got it I got a dunkin donuts large iced coffee
Oh
And dude, i'm telling you it was fucking gross. It was the grossest coffee i've ever had in my life. It was disgusting
I don't I don't know where um, I don't know why I can't see the thing on the screen
I have no idea where it is
I'm not gonna do that though. I don't know where it is. I'm not gonna do it. I'm gonna move on
I i'm gonna move on. I don't i'm not gonna do it. I don't know where it is on the screen. I can't see it
Uh, so i'm just gonna be done
All right, i'm going back. I'll go back. I'll go back. I don't know. Where is it? Where is it?
Okay, I I can't see it I have no idea where the fuck it is
Um, but you guys have fucking gaslighting the shit out of me
Stop i'm not I don't care. I'm not gonna do it. All right, i'll do it right now. I'll do it
Tearing apart
No, I told you I was gonna go back. I couldn't see what you were looking at
Get off me. There's so many of you. Hold on. Uh, this is important
Oh, hey guys
Hey, you ever you ever pick up the phone and somebody it's it's a wrong number and you say oh hey wrong number
Hey, uh screw you buddy
You know what I mean? Like that's plus two
I wonder if your neighbors can hear you monkey laugh track. Yo, what's up? Hey
My neighbors, why is this person doing this for more than 10 seconds?
That's way too long to do a monkey like chimpanzee impression
Right, that's way too long. I did it for like two or three straight minutes
That's I got my I got my laugh track ready
No, hold on. It's got to be better. Like you guys got to get if we got this is gonna be accurate
So we got two that are fine, right?
All right, so that that one's a good one
So we'll we have to have a really really like
a really like angry one
That's good and this one now that's bad this one is good
No, no, no, I got better this is good
So now if I see a bunch of minus twos, I know what to press and I see a lot of plus twos
I know what to press
And this is if you don't like if you don't think it's funny
Okay, play the game. All right. Yeah. Yeah, we got okay. All right, right, right. It's monkey friday. That's enough
Okay, let's go
Okay about yourselves
I'm sweet. The ladies call me captain kk
We used to work the sound in this town
Until queen came around
Kk is short for cakes
She made music against the law unless you make a song she likes
But the only junk she enjoys are reverse disc tracks where the vocalist puts themselves down and praises the queen
Or noise music
But even if queenie tries to put a limiter on us
You can't stop the music
Hear that we'll just go underground crash boom bang
That's why we made this junk shop. We'll fund our musical rebellion
Can we make noise music too?
Okay performance you want to see what we got?
Can you handle this hold on to your antennas?
How is that how is that?
That was good all our songs are only four seconds long
Okay, a queen wasn't always so harsh
No, she was she just got worse somehow
It wasn't until that dark fountain showed up she started going into overdrive
Night this night that fountain that
Like what does that night even have going for it that I can't that I don't come on gwen
zoomer tiktok musicians
But like I said, she wasn't always so bad. She used to give me sweets for being so sweet
Oh, I never got candy
He kept calling her a hot mama cap
Yeah, is that wrong? She looks like a mom and tends to overheat
KK help me out here. Oh, what do you think me?
I like candy
Yeah, you're right. KK. We got to focus on what's important if the band fights we'll get out of tune
And we have any lemon drops
Junk work our main gig is making scrap into machines. Our clients are sometimes a bit off key though
They smell off key, too
Like some little weird guy
He wanted us to sneak into queen's mansion
We're just rebels. We don't want to get in trouble
Recently, we got a real high class client
A man of taste he had a way with words. I couldn't even understand him
I blew my voice out doing the fucking chimpanzee shit
Like I it's gone
I'm only two hours in
Now all we got to do is follow the blueprints, right? It'll be our big time break
Yeah, haha. It's gonna break apart big time
Uh, I need some I need some water. All right, so now we can buy
CD bagel you gotta make it cheaper than that. What the hell?
Mecha saber. All right. I have a question. This is a backseat question for all you guys
um
If i'm gonna try to just do the kind of passive just run
Did I even buy the weapons? Is there even a reason to buy them?
If I don't plan on swinging the sword once
There's no point, right?
Okay, well I
Should probably buy a couple of things here
Buy it because I only let's buy no
Goodbye i'm gonna buy another one. All right. All right. All right. All right. What can I sell?
Sell pocket items. You got nothing sell armor
Sell the amber cards, right?
Because I don't need these
Don't sell them. Should I sell? Oh, no. No. Okay. I did this like a okay sell weapons. No sell items
You can craft. Okay. Yeah. Yeah, you're right
all right, uh
Cool
Thanks guys. See ya spell ya
There is a terrific noise coming from the building nearby. You're filled with the power of noise music
I have full hp. Yeah, I do
Whoa?
I should fight these guys because I want to have a recruit five and five, right? Oh wait. Hold on
smorgasbord two
All right, so we need to
Uh, you're already tired. So i'm just gonna pacify you
So we might as well
like you
We're gonna do a roar on you
and then we're gonna do a
Wait, oh shit. I hit the wrong button. All right roar
on
Oh, whoa, whoa, whoa
our action
bare wire
Wait, no. Fuck. I wanted to pacify. Wait. Why? Oh, no. No, no. No, i'm stupid
Okay, listen up a little bit. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep
Sorry, I like screamed out all my energy
I you know, I can't honestly let's think of like like chimpanzees in the fucking wild
Holy shit, how how are you not sleeping 20 hours a day?
Just like screaming. I I would i'm ready to go sleep
Okay, so we're chris i'm gonna act
Everybody's tired
So we're gonna go ahead
We're gonna go ahead and we're gonna go ahead and we're gonna jiggle the wire
Then we're gonna go ahead
And s action u
Oh, i'm so dumb. Okay s action standard. No, no, no, no, no just defend
And then you're going to do pacify on anybody probably you
I can't imagine screaming for like
15 straight hours
Okay, so that means now let's do
I just defend
I mean they're gonna I mean as well might as well
So once they're tired
My brain is is flogged right now. Can I just keep doing that until?
Like can I let's for instance, can I just like keep jiggle jiggle and then not necessarily pacify. Will that take it off?
No, okay. So they have to be pacified
Once they're tired, they just stay tired
I got the three check marks. Yeah, I did
They can only be spared of a yellow
Yes
Tension bit
That is items tension bit
Raises tp by 32 percent in a battle. Okay
Um, I need to do something if I can do it i'm gonna try to controls
Yes
Confirm is going to be
All right cancel the need to change this to be
menu x
That's fine. Uh, I I don't want it to be
I'm I keep pressing the wrong button
That's like confirm in my brain
Is where that is on the xbox controller?
Actually insane. No, i'm not like be like b to my brain is where a is
on the xbox controller
B on the xbox controller is a in my brain because of super nintendo
So everyone bullying
Okay
I don't know
Down sit down
Shall I help you save?
No, I shan't I haven't the faintest idea what that is
That feels way better. Yeah, now I actually can play the game
Correctly did I miss anything?
What's your opinion on chili dogs?
Yeah
Not really. I can't touch this thing. It's too much. It's too messy. I like the flavor
Why do I say bombs?
Oh if they hit that they they explode
Yes. Oh what?
Revive mint nice any more of those they have to hit the arrow has to hit it key nice. What else is up here?
Wait
Then was it something down here?
I didn't that just opened the ability to go up or was there like something over here
Why does this sound like a mario party song?
It's kind of mario party like isn't it?
Oh, come on move
All right. I gotta I gotta do arrow keys
Jesus
63 I can do better than that go back or the d-pad
You've had actually probably worked to 63. That's not good
Hey, what the hell are these things?
Looks like if we ride them
They might bring us over to the fountain
Really and let's get on I have just getting just flashbacks
Of that stupid ass fucking battle toads level that was impossible without a game a game tracker game genie
Remember that dumb level where you had to ride the thing and it was impossible you crashed into everything
Enough you okay. Hold on. Excuse me enough you foolish children
I have been merciful to you thus far, but now it's time for
Your unwillful imprisonment capture drop the capturing capsules
Uh, you missed
That was not a miss. It was a tactical calibration
Are you gonna try it again?
No, I only have like four cages
Okay, wait
I have a small plot twist for you
come forward my
eon
Um, sorry, I just couldn't say no
No, well
Hi, suzy. Um, how are you?
Uh, okay, I guess
Was everybody writing laughing my ass off?
Laugh mlmao. What are you doing that? You're um roller coasters. Um, I I like it
Uh yours, too
Thanks
Okay, this isn't working bring in the next guy
Fear not my beloved noelle
This valiant warrior of brave intelligence
Will be your knight and glow in the dark armor
Birdley you asked birdley to be on your team. I did not ask him. I did not ask him. I did not ask him
That's lord birdley to you simpleton
And soon super lord birdley
The hell does that mean?
I have no damn clue
Just go with it
You see thanks to our wondrous queen
We will soon rule the world
And this and i'll turn this land of fools into smartopia
a true
Scientocracy where the geniuses of the world
Can bathe freely in pools of fresh fruit and ambrosia
by the way
This is something to think about
Ambrosia is supposed to be like the thing that gods ate
right
Oh, they they and they sipped on ambrosia
Why did that turn into like a disgusting fucking dessert?
That ambrosia
Is gross
That's what we say ambrosia is what is it's like chunks of marshmallow and like potato salad
This is what the gods apparently ate
No, what that sucks. What a shitty fucking dessert
It's because you're immortal
No, what is okay? I'm serious like i've had ambrosia like once and I was like this like sucks
What is actually in it? It's
Yeah, this stuff is fucking gross like macaroni salad and like fruit salad combined. There's like was it mayonnaise in this
Oh the absolute the fruit the delectable of the gods
Of course
What would be in it besides?
fruit salad
and
gross cheap
Marshmallow cubes
Ah, yes. Yes, bring me. Yes peon. Bring me my ambrosia
I'll take that whipped cream out of the can
Mini marshmallows and fruits
It's as if
a three-year-old
Sat down and made their own recipe
Bring it to me on a platter on silver
Why is ambrosia? Yeah, okay
Thank you, thank you, thank you, thank you he's immortal
Oh
No, it's fucking what that's not like the death dessert of the gods the dessert of the gods is baklava. I'm telling you right now
That's what ambrosia is ambrosia was baklava. Okay
Look it up. It had to be fucking our ambrosia. No, it's either chocolate ice cream or it's baklava pick one
No longer held back by protozoans like you
And the key to that is us noelle and I
Our power the light nerds
The light nerds
Oh, no queen said light nerds
I actually did
Thirdly queen's just manipulating you
That's what she said you'd say to me
I actually did that
now chris
Must admit I feel pity for you
Unlike susie. I always saw some potential in you
Join our side and I might let you scrub our royal toilet
Don't say it so incredulously
Well, if you're dead set on proving your inferiority
Allow me to assist you
birdley rides in
we got
Check bump bump x check
defend defend birdley go use your roller coaster cars to play bump of chicken
Chris I get why you're getting in my way. You're jealous. Aren't you?
Okay, birdley gives the secret sign but queen is busy with a coloring book
All right, so let's bump bump x everyone rides coaster
The whole gang will attempt to bump into birdley's car
Chris you're tired of being the class number three gazing distantly at noelle and I's
fruited figures
Birdley shows queen his card collection queen escaped successfully
Uh, what's gonna keep doing this?
Bump into birdley's car
So rather than ever studying
You didn't list susie to take us down
Oh, they have little pieces come out interesting birdley shows queen his card collection queen escaped successfully
All right, is it 36 percent mercy?
I'm just gonna keep doing it
Chris you are truly depraved playing in the mud with the class hellion
I have so much magic right now
All right. I should probably heal
All right, chris you just normal bump
Susie I would like for you to bump
birdley
But ralcy I would like for you to use
magic
on
Susie chris. I am a kind and brave hero if you come to our side you may be slightly less distant number three
slightly
a plus
What the fuck is going on in this game?
Are they talking about studying in class that we're in?
This is weird. I want answers
Uh, let's go for another super bomb. My car is breaking
Pools, this is smart smoke. It means my car is getting stronger
Go ahead bump me you bump barons. I'll show you bumper cars. It's a game of intellect not skill
All right birdley's coaster car thing looks sick
Not quite. Uh, all right. I need to heal
regular bump
And heal yourself
Partake chris the sufferer of punishment
Uh car thing looks sick
96 percent now, okay
You didn't play tsa
No, I didn't
So you're right
Uh, let's just let's knock the car down
my coaster
it's
Oh what that's not fair?
My queen my queen save me
In a minute, dear. Hello everyone. I have some news updates
you see
This roller coaster
It's not actually finished yet
What does that mean?
a pain
Looks like this trash saved us
Come on. Oh who's king of the trash pile now?
Good reflexes there good reflexes very good reflexes
Susie are you all right?
It's nothing I just
Oh, ow
Sure, you don't want me to look
Look at what i'm fine
What are you doing feel better
Feel better after you just came up and I acting the acting
Um, it doesn't feel worse, I guess how do you do that anyway?
And healing thingy
Oh healing magic. It's simple. Uh
Susie anyone can do it. I could even teach you if you're interested
Ask me again when it's like blood explosion magic
But if you wanted I guess I could learn it and you wouldn't you know have to annoy me with it anymore
uh
Sure susie
Next time we have a break
Just go already chris
There's like an oscar the grouch in here
You dug through the trash and found a dark candy our candy was added to your items. Nice
It's a trash bag that looks like an eggplant. I was gonna say cash register
Okay
Oh, i'm trying to figure out got it
Oh boy. Oh boy. I'm trashy
Is it all about adjusting your inventory?
Trash cans like me can hold all sorts of things
Just like your storage if you get more than 12 items
Uh, yeah, not now, dude
It's sort of an emotional moment
Oh, oh, that's okay
Oh hell is that newbert over there?
Oh newbert's here. Sorry trash can guy
This is an eggplant. I'm newbert. Everybody loves me. That's why I live in this trash
No time for this guy
All right, so should I go up?
It's a lone door frame, but for some reason you can't see through it
That's my man. That's my man newbert
By the way chris, I just remembered although you can only carry 12 items around
Your storage will hold any extra items you pick up. Yeah
You can access it where you check recruits
Enemies you spare get recruited to our town remember
It's a pretty useful information
It is there's a fork in the path chris it seems like it might be advantageous
If we split up
Who do you want to go with?
Uh, well rousy has the heel so i'm gonna go with rousy
that's i'm just
Basing this on how I feel
With i'm i'm gonna go with rousy because I suzy does not have a heel right now
And i'm going with rousy. That's my decision. That's what i've decided
If anybody wants to call me cringe like I just saw five people said cringe
That's fine
I'm apparently i'm cringe. I'm going with rousy. Hey, why does chris get to choose all the time?
Rousy you're going with me
Uh crap
Okay, i'm gonna explain the joke. I didn't do the joke. I'm gonna explain it though
Sit down sit down sit down not yet
um
I was gonna just do like a fart sound like
And then go man
I've been holding that in for like three hours. Thank god i'm alone
I
Somebody liked it somebody liked that somebody thought that was funny
I'm clearing that we're not doing that again the rest of stream
I just cleared it
I that that voice is not happening anymore. We're done
I cleared it. I cleared it from the xlr
All right, hold on. What can I do anything else? Oh shit. I can go this way. What's that?
somebody's trash house
The door is locked
Is that just is that trashy's house? I would assume probably is don't look sad
You're never alone. You got new bird
You can hold a lot more in your storage, you know, oh, but you won't be able to use it during battle
Check it and make sure you have what you need
It's what I wanted to see what I already said. Why are you saying shush? Don't shush me. Welcome to
the
City
I just thought they were just back there. You have neither fluffy boys nor mean girls with you now
Reluctantly you are filled with the power from the cat sign
I heard the roller coasters are undergoing maintenance. That's a pain because it's our only form of public transit
Welcome to cyber city pedestrians need to press the switch to cross traffic
About how mad would you be?
You're in a car and you still sort of like just press the button
And the the walk sign happened everybody stopped and they just don't move and then they press it again
By the way, can somebody correct me here? I need to know this
I've been told like three different things about how that system works
Does that actually do anything? I've been told that when you press the the button it actually is just a placebo
It doesn't actually do anything
Is that accurate?
Some of them do
Some of them some do nothing
It depends depends on the city
So I have it
Just to give the pedestrian something to do to make it feel like they're doing something. It's a placebo effect
It depends on where but most actually do something
I've heard conflicting information over the years
Oh god, this is um
donkey kong country
The donkey don't come country. We have to jump and hit the lights and keep the lights on
Whatever it is the stop thing
Oh
Oh nice
That level was brutal. It really was it was horrible
What are we cleaning up for you ask?
We don't know a parade perhaps
possibly
Hey, how bad am I peas?
I have to switch out this thing. I think
When I say like oh like a peter
A peter piper picked a pick of pickled peppers, right?
It's it kind of sucks, right?
You get are you getting the uh the pops?
Because I feel like sometimes it happens. Is it good?
I swear to god. I feel like it happens a lot. I think I have to get a new pop filter
A large event is going to happen in the streets later. We were told to make room for something big
We're trashed
dug through the trash
Found twenty dollars
Only dark dollars was added to your money hole
They're making room for your ass
Good one. Whoa pop-ups popped up
I kind of want to kill the pop-ups
All right pop-up, uh click or block click. I'm gonna click the pop-up
You unconsciously clicked on an ad for a video about making knives out of spaghetti
That made another one click here click here click click
Oh, that sucks
Up up is preening its weird rubbery flesh
All right block
It's why repeatedly block the ads
Walk 10 ads happy
Oh now I can see
Okay
It's there
It's easy with no ads
Now click it again. No
I don't want to click the ad again. I clicked it once
cd bagel nice
Okay, what are you doing here?
Who are you and what are you doing here? Chris? What are you?
Oh, no. Hell, sweetie
Don't let her find me
No, well, sweetie darling, honey. Where are you?
We're a team now remember
You still have to be my willing minion
Chris
It appears
Our comrades have pressed the escape key on us
So it has come to this
In order to find our teams
We must form an uneasy truce
Queen my splendid queen. Where are you?
Oh, no, don't let him fight me
Ah chris not the life form I was looking for
Hmm, where's the rest of the c plus squad?
Don't tell me you've got abandoned
Ha ha ha ha ha ha that's what you get for trusting susie
Uh, huh?
well
fiend
They're just
They're just busy retro gaming somewhere
I bet they're waiting for me on the player select screen
Listening to strangely groovy music
Uh, so it's come to this
In order to find our respective teams
It appears we must form an uneasy truce
He said you could double truces
Huh? Did you hear something?
No, it's just the sounds of the city
Oh, okay
Well, i'll be ahead don't be late
First as part of our truce better one keep distracting birdly and find a well
Oh, you see
Birdly he's
Okay, there's nothing wrong with him. He's just annoying
Toodles yes, I um if it's okay
Don't even refer another truce
No triple truces
Yeah, we can we can have another truce. I think yeah, like it's gonna be triple truces. No triple truces
But no, that's no i'm saying of course. Thanks chris. I will join the party. What is the sugar form?
So um any idea where susie is?
Well, i'm just asking it's a normal question
I don't know. I have no idea where susie is
Is that what's that? What's that? What's this? What's this? Um, um mouse
Sorry chris, could you deal with them?
Maybe you can get them in the other mouse hole
Annoying mouse room. Okay. Well I
Do they come out they bounce?
Hold on. How do they bounce?
All right, so we gotta go like this
All right, you say I know I know I did
What does that do? Not quite i'm gonna move it over here. Yep
Uh, thank you
Mice will rotate 90 degrees when they collide with the block. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah, I figured it out
Why have I already recruited all these?
Well, what does noel do?
What's going on? What are we doing?
I mean, what are you telling me to do act?
Can someone please explain what's going on?
Boy, is this your first time in a battle?
Uh, well, yes
Oh boy
You and viril viril cone explained how battles work to noel. Oh, I get it
It's kind of like dragon blazers and if we're nice to you we can win through mercy
Yeah
And the way I have to do that is
Dressing up in a weird costume
Yeah
You and noel showed the enemy tender loving care
Nice
Ah spare
Okay, bye. What am I buying?
This is a new enemy
Ambulances beeped towards you
hospitality
Well acted warmly towards ambulance
Needles aren't scary medicine's important. You know, this girl's so sweet. Let's give her free bullets
Okay, what the fuck
Making siren noises with its mouth
You won. All right, so we go. Let's check this guy out. This is good. We are adison. All we do is advertise
This is an advertisement too
Advertisements not only 9.99
Don't like advertisements block ads for only 9.99 change your mind bring them back for only 9.99
I'm just gonna run an ad
But I don't want to like delete a third of the audience here
Don't like advertisements block ads. Oh same thing
Wait up or should I go right?
Go right first
Go up first
Whoa?
Susie she's right there
I can't get the courage to say anything
Who's that person? She's with anyway, it's kind of like
Oh, they're looking over here. Let's go
How can they get to have fun at the carnival?
Watch out for the cars
stop what
What?
Hey
Hey, hey
We did it
Can't even cross the street without getting my ass kicked. I love this city
Because everyone else got plugged. They're a lot more agreeable
It's nice
plugged
Jesus your cousin from boston
Why did you say that?
Now you got me all fucked up. Why did you say that?
Your cousin from boston
Uh, can I do
What can I even do to you? Well offered a cold compress
Yeah, i'm home free
I love those commercials really just made it seem like everybody from boston just carries around a six pack
everywhere
Even to the fucking doctor
Just a six pack in your hand
In the waiting room and in the doctor's office and shit
Oh can't do it quite yet
Don't they?
cousin
Of the green monster. Yeah
Jermis from vegas now. He doesn't count anymore
What?
What do you mean?
Is it advertisement for a giant ferris wheel?
Gosh, that's amazing makes the one at the festival look like a toy
I wonder if suzy would want to
Uh
Gosh, who am I kidding?
I will ride with you
No, I think she would
I think suzy I think suzy would
Really? You really think so? Yeah, I think so
I'm coming from suzy expert chris
Hey chris, how'd you become the suzy expert?
Oh
Two young beings together on a school night
But I interest you in some brand new dating shoes
Huh? No, you've got it. Totally wrong chris and I are just um friends
This has been my neighbor forever. We've been through so much. Sometimes it feels like we know each other better than anyone
It's somehow it's hard to say. We're exactly friends
I
I mean
we're
That's I don't know. We're friends
Yep, that's right. We're friends. We're friends. It's surprisingly nice just hearing. Yeah, we're just friends friends
Ah, you two don't look together
Uh, can I interest you in some brand new divorcing shoes?
Yeah, that's it. Yeah look
Where do I how do I look?
Who is this guy? Hey
Any way to deal with crushing existential dread?
Asking for a friend
Friend that looks and sounds exactly like me
You're talking about me
All right, that's best that's best joke of the game so far without a doubt that was definitely the best routine so far
No, leave me alone
What do I get to kind of move I go down. Oh I go down. Oh
Hey
Looks like you need to hold it down. Yeah, can you stand over here?
You keep standing on this one
I'll stand on this one
And now you come over here
Nice teamwork
Yeah
It was nice teamwork
The game lost in the craftsmanship of the boxes
Oh, it's the queen. She's right over there
Can you distract her somehow?
Oh
You're here
Sorry chris while i've been looking for noelle. I've had like four of these all ages appropriate glasses of pure battery acid
Don't worry, that was my throwing glass it's safe
Look chris
crisscross applesauce
Now that we are truces. I feel like we are on the same
mathematical wavelength
And you get me chris
You do not do
You do not do crazy things like have opinions or scream when I capture you
Or tell me horrible plans for smart boy theme park
I just cannot compute it
Why everyone else is so ungrateful?
I learned that from master shake. Whoops. That was my extra dangerous glass
chris
I just want to make everyone smile
And if I become an evil villain to accomplish that
Is that bad?
It's okay
You do not have to answer
You would be wrong
But chris while we're still truces
Maybe we could make the most of it
We could play that game again. Wasn't that fun chris?
Just you and me
Having a good time
No one else to get in the way
Queen i've been looking everywhere to show you this a monument to our greatness together
oh
um
I I oh oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, how do I put this?
very
uh
smart
So smart you are I love tolerating you
I knew you'd be an omen such perfect taste
Very cool statues. I did. Ah, I don't know you had uh nipples
I will soon in our ideal world
Chris feel free to admire our artisanship
Queen and I have plans to consider
Oh, yes. Oh good looking forward to that
Hmm. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Let's go, uh burglary
Keep going. I'm right behind you
Procedurally lowering the volume of my body
Sorry chris. I must opt tab out of here
Wow cool face
Cool face looks like my disguise worked
It's silly looking but it beats hiding
Let's get going chris. Look, it's you. Oh
oh
I can't see anything. Haha
Yes, i'll try not to wear it unless I have to
Okay, let's go for a reel this time. What is this?
That's a big laugh. That's like a fuck
You chris, can you stop looking at this?
You became lost in the craftsmanship
Why do we have to look at it twice?
Because there's so much to look at here
chris
It's a work of art
What part are you looking at?
If I say I like it, will you stop looking at it?
Isn't this thing just the best?
The statue seems to suck bad
chris
There's no reason to look at this
There's no reason to look at this anymore. There's no reason
Oh, it's our friends
Energetic music wafts from the boxes
Filled with the power of musical bagels
What'll it be chief?
Oh, I hope you didn't hear that
I think the music was covering it but like a frog sound came out of my mouth because I
You know what I mean? I internally burped
What'll it be chief? I got cd bagels 80 dollars pop
Uh, let's just talk
Who is that? Uh mademoiselle leave her alone cap
Nice radio antenna you got there. Those are antlers cap
Huh? I oh
Let's play her a song
I was waiting
How's it hanging? We're making some extra money by selling in the city
We gotta make those bucks somehow
Gotta buy new gear gotta get new kicks. I want to be a car
Good thinking kk gotta have a way to get around honk honk
You like the big statue building it sucked took a lot of scrap
The other job we did was way better. It was big
It's gonna blow your mind. It was big
I don't think I need any items, but that's all I have is bagels
Okay, i'm gonna buy
I'm gonna buy two bagels
Because I don't think I have a heel right? I feel like there's probably a boss coming on here
Yeah, what kind of bagels do you like?
Uh, I like everything bagels
One problem with everything bagels though is you are going to have to clean your counter
Doesn't matter how careful you are doesn't matter what you use for a plate or a thing to hold it
um
little like
Bird seed is gonna be all over your entire counter and it's a pain absolute ass
You take a bite out of an everything bagel
It's like being at the beach like sand just gets in your underwear
It's worth it
Welcome to cyber shoes too free samples. Would you like one?
Sure
You got a small shoe with a toothpick through it
I like that
Wait, can I get another free sample? That means I have two shoes
Please i'm begging you. These voices are cringe
What do you want me to do?
This is the hottest tea shop hot hot hot 50% off
For a hundred dollars choose your own flavor. Sure
Okay, choose your own flavor
me
Okay, here you go
Chris tea was added to your items
What?
It's own flavored tea. The flavor just says chris
Okay, here you go
The well tea was added to your items
All right. I'm running a room
I'm lancer
Oh, thanks for the free sample. I couldn't eat another bite
All right, wait
I don't want to fight you. I don't want to fight you don't hey what they're already tired
Stop doing fucking boston guy thing
Wait, so how do I do this if I don't have um pacified?
Oh noelle can do it. Okay
Sleep missed spare tired. Okay, I see
Oh, it's all good
I think I can actually spare
This should work
Oh, I thought it was gonna be yellow. The first one was yellow
I did that only one time. Why was it not yellow this time?
Fuck and now you're no, you're not. All right, but whatever sleep miss. I just
Oh, it's I thought they were in front of me not above me
Otis tea shop. Okay. Yeah, let's go over to the right. No, but if you don't choose a flavor who will
Sleep miss will spare. Oh, oh
It's a mannequin with a dress on it clothing store sale sale. We're selling this for 75% off only 300 dark dollars
Great doing business with you
It was added to your armors
Where is it? It's your armors
I don't see it. Where is it? Oh mannequin
It's a mannequin with the clothes permanently. Oh
You fucking asshole
Bye. Bye. Bye. We're sold out
Whatever. Oh shit. All right. Wait, how do I get over there up? Oh god
Okay
Whoa
Oh no
Oh
All right. Here we go. Ready? Three two one go
Oh looks like another electric wall. This hole has a switch inside. Oh shit. It's the eyes are gonna be horrible
That's something inside
What do you think? It's a hole for mice to enter into
Left right. Wait a minute. Oh goodness
Okay. Well
I didn't even what are you doing?
They're gonna come out
Why are they how do they get him to come out?
Oh down. Okay. Sorry. My iced coffee is okay. Listen
Listen, my iced coffee is huge
It's here right in front of my monitor on the bottom right side of my monitor and it's fucking enormous
And it's covering that text
Okay, I get it
This is like a 32 ounce tall starbucks cup
It's gigantic
Fuck what do I do?
Can't move. Oh god. I killed them
Okay, so they have to go. Oh fuck. All right. So wait a minute. I gotta get the first part right
It's not right. It's not right
All right. That's not right
Not right
That's right. Okay
Huh? The force field's still up. Why?
We missed something. Hello
Oh
Here again
Garbage, you're gonna get scared over it. I can't believe you made those mice do that
Huh? I guess the landing on the switch turned off the force field
Let's go
Not yet
Um, what am I doing? I mean I looked at chat and chat said you need to go down and i'm cheating
Oh, well what?
I said no back seating. What are you guys doing?
I saw somebody in chat said you have to go down
What did you do?
Fuck well that yeah, they they made me do this. I didn't do it
Okay, here we go
Oh
All right. I got it
Go
Go why I want to go down. What the fuck go down
Oh my god, go
Go
Hurry up
Okay, so what the what I don't understand what am I doing down here? Why did I do this?
Go further down
What?
More down here
What are you guys talking about? You have to do it on the yellow side. Oh
Pulling my hair. I'll leave your hair in it's fine
What the fuck dude?
Yeah, I keep getting stuck on shit
This is fucking hard, man. This is hard. I keep getting stuck
Oh, there it is
No, there's blockages I it's like a maze. Okay, wait
It's like left right left down. I don't you have to go. It's like weird this this blockage is down there
Oh my fucking god, I don't get it
one two
Oh, I think I got it. Come on you got it. Why do I do all this for?
Okay
Wait
Oh, that's what I came down here for. It's a dumpster. Seems like there's a pillow inside
Okay, the room between there is a room between
That was not worth it
Not really. No
It was worth it. I mean it was kind of worth it. Oh fuck. I have to get back up
Can I go down even more just go left? Huh? I found them. Whoa
Why did they look so pleased? What is it? Is it in storage?
Now it was worth it. Yeah. All right
powers
act
Heal. No, what is it?
Leave this room again and enter it
Look at your title. Those are all the title
What does it say?
Delta ruins second chapter
What it sucks?
right well
remember
I haven't I don't I didn't like remember much of the shit from the first time I played this I played three years ago
And I don't know what happens in this game. So I can't make like a funny title to reference the game because it's been a while
Yeah, I did a refresher course, but I didn't have any funny material to put here
Is it I think that's okay, I think it's fine
What what's wrong with it? Is there like a typo?
Delta ruins second chapter
That's not
What do you mean the title?
in game termo
what
In-game title. What are you talking about?
Just ignore them. Okay, I don't get it
I don't get it
I don't understand
In I don't have an injury what your character class is now moss finder
um
Okay
Citizen's duty to properly rotate and release mice using the traffic signs engage and disengage. Okay. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah
cheese free cheese
Chris you aren't going to touch that cheese. Are you?
I'm going to touch the cheese
You rub the cheese down like a beloved pet
suddenly
Oh
boss blocked the way
I love boss
trap all
That ball shit. I want it tired of being pushed around
I was just thinking about overly elaborate machines
All right, let's get it
shit
You think you're the big change?
but the enemy
one to three
You won do I get the cheese?
I never want to see cheese ever again
Cheese was destroyed in the heat of battle feels like you lost sight of what was important
Yeah, wait, there's a chest over here
Chris
Oh if you touch the cheese
It's like operation
I'm glad I did this though because I want to I want to recruit three
Left right left right this way that way this way that way
Is there a mouse on the screen? Oh, okay. I get it. That's all right
nice
fair
Create a three
Oh fuck it was like you lost sight of what was important. Damn it
This feels too easy just to get it, right?
You open the chest. It was a cd bagel. I sure I probably should eat one of these
Yeah, i'm gonna eat one
Use a cd bagel
dear the dead end
one of these
I
Switch didn't seem to work
Uh, the platform's falling help me
Come on. I'll
Oh, sorry chris. So you just saved me. Didn't you? My god, this one's falling too. Ah
Yeah, who the fuck is this?
Ah chris stuck on this puzzle. I see
I thought I heard no one calling for help
But I get that sound I get what that sound was now. Okay, I can't
The brain must I can't read both you just you read it
Talk on a puzzle just like this one
He's but a powerless dough without my help
I love
I love mu
Mo
I love mo
I love mu mouse
I love mouse
You love mouses
I love mouse. How did you
How did you solve that?
Even a broken clock is right once a day
And chris if anyone asks
I solved the puzzle
Not fair for you to get extra credit for a fluke
Get it, but no one think otherwise, especially susie
You know, she just uh lord it over me gosh
You know, I don't think i'm afraid of mice anymore. Actually, I think they might be kind of cute
Let's keep going the well is now immune to mice
That's good
Let me go to storage for a second. All right
I have a dog dollar
Revive me it heals a fallen ally to max hp. Okay
Can I just store these t's
Dog doll a dollar with a certain dog on it. Its value decreases each
two
Okay. Um, what do I do with this thing?
I'm gonna keep the t's
You dug through the trash and found 20 dollars you dug through the trash and found 80 dollars
Oh
Pop up and mouse appeared
Well cheered rightly
Mouse I don't like the mouse. I'll tell you why the mouse is the one that's hitting me the most
It's just the spiders from binding of isaac
Something about that movement pattern. They'll like move pause move pause move pause move. Nope
I hate it
It follows you I know
It repeats your movements
Does cd bagel actually i'm gonna eat one
Now what? Oh
Well, what are you doing with chris?
I um
We have a truce
A truce with chris
That's impossible
That would be double truces
Sorry, not my dearest noelle
I know what you really want to say
you do
Going along with all this
You feel forced, don't you?
That's why you're not with queen right now
Birdley you get it
Yes, I do
Chris is forcing you to be on their side
kidnapper
Chris our truce is over
Well, this may hurt
Help you wait just listen you
Birdley blocks the way
All right, what we got birdley, uh play smart. Let's check birdley for fun and defend
Usually only gets this mad when you play games together
Chris I get it your head's gotten big from solving that puzzle by dumb luck
Oh, this is tricky. Okay. Okay. I gotta figure it to get the pattern out
All right, let's do uh
play dumb
Play dumb play dumb and I need to heal
I shook
You looked acted like you were an idiot next to birdley's genius
Oh chris a shame. I must have eaten so lowly birdley liked that
fuck
Well tried to talk to birdley
Uh birdley i'm glad you're trying to help me
I need to thank me dearest noelle
Accidentally complimented
Guess what chris I have one or two more things you'll never have behold comrades
All right, I need to
play smart
You encourage noelle to use her mind her magic increased birdley found her smarts appealing
It's right chris unlike you. I have a loving team behind me
I'll never be just fighting alone
Nobody said please kill birdley
Um, like hold on. I'm
No, I can't
Shit, all right act
I gotta get rid of these guys
So i'm gonna heal her and she's gonna do the mist
Sleepest
Goodbye, my allies are gone. They're probably just helping queen search for me
shut
Birdley crushes his smart scouter out of frustration
Play smart encourage noelle to use her mind her magic increased birdley found her smarts appealing
Summon more guys. I don't need to do that. Just wait the original ones are gonna come back any minute now
There you go. All right again
Almost there. Why are you hitting me? Don't worry. It's part of my calculations
Shit in my pants, come on
All right. How would he out now? I gotta check
Holy halberd grant me strength
All right. Let me see spare you're at 76. All right, let's do that one more time play smart
You encourage noelle to use her mind
Acted smart partake chris zephyr of punishment
Yeah
92. All right. I just have to do that one more time. So i'm gonna heal and she's gonna yeah
Seedy bagel myself
And then have her do her thing and action standard now. We should be at 100 time to uh do pacify
No, I don't need to
Damn it
Birdley, are you okay?
Chris, maybe we should have gone easier on him
Oh easier
The only one going easy mode was me
You look exhausted
I'm only tired of holding back my true power
Ah, no, well, it'd be too simple to save you now
Chris go ahead and train your strength values
Try hard and maybe someday you'll be a worthy rival
Sometimes I can't believe how cool I am
He would just listen after defeating birdley a certain scent hangs in the air
You're filled with the power of chicken nuggets. What he smells like chicken nuggets
Now I want that now. That's what I want
Interesting. All right, are they all gonna move or?
Kind of concerned about this. No, we're good
Noelle honey, where are you?
Oh, no, here she comes
Well, come home. I made you a battery ass and pie
Oh chris perfect timing
Have you seen
All my luxurious queen
Oh my circuits chris skin in the car
My queen, where are you?
I've made you a gamer's delight
She's not here
Gamer's delight that was close
chris
Who is your friend?
My face recognition software does not compute them
And yet something about them seems
Cool robotic even
Chris we must drive to find noelle
Everyone get in the car
Chris press directional buttons to steer
Chris don't hit the cars
So much traffic, isn't it? Wonderful
Lightners love traffic. They look it up all the time. Poor noelle. I can't look I can't read that
Stop everything
Chris get the banana
Why?
potassium
stuff everything
Here comes a crossing to get ready to stop
Like can I?
Oh my circuits. It's a traffic jam
A dog must have wandered in the road again
Chris be a dear and go press the walk button
It's just over on the other side of the road
Um, i'll go too
No
You must stay
Hmm
Until you hear all of my mixtape
Oh, okay
Chris hurry up, please
Next up is my cd of vintage hard disk noises
Chris, please hurry
Buy queen clean the most popular cleaning flavors
Queen clean made of 100 acid. Hey
every
it's
me
Everybody's favorite number one rated salesman 1997
Ha ha ha
Whoa, if it isn't, uh
Lightner, hey
Looks like you're all alone on a late night
All your friends abandoned you for the slime
You are sales gone down the drain the drain
Living in a goddamn garbage can
Well, I've got a special deal for lonely hearts like you
If you've lost control of your life
Then you just gotta grab it by the silly strings
Oh, why be the little sponge who hates a tough one in a nine life?
When you could be a big shot
Big shot a big shot
That's right. How's your chance to be a big shot?
And I have jet
the thing
you need
that's
Hyperlink blocked
You want it? You want it?
No, you want it? Well, I have I got a deal for you
All you have to do is show me
Your heart-shaped object
You're a lightner. Are you a lighter?
You've got the light. Why don't you uh, what is anybody sure to be sure to be sure up?
Don't want to be a big shot. Okay, check spamton. He wants to make a deal
But don't give him your money
French mick clover
There's nothing wrong with having a nice splurge every once in a while
Don't make a deal
Deal. Hey, hey, hey, I've never seen a heart-shaped object like that before
My eyes are burning like dvds of any movie and app, right?
I have a very special deal for you kid
Tell me more
Not interested
Wrong answer wrong wrong wrong wrong try again
Meet local singles straight from my
There's nothing wrong there's nothing wrong
Shit, oh I didn't come into this prepared at all. Did I uh, oh get big and win wild prizes
So what do I do here act?
What'd it say? Congratulations. You are the 100th visitor click here to die
Okay, let's make a deal
Kid in business. You need to say you're interested. All right, tell me more. That's the attitude you little slime
Feels like this only come once in a your ant size rapidly shrinking life
Get big and win
Spant and flash is an award-losing smile
Heal deal
What?
Oh, I can do deal again deal
Believe it or I used to be a big shot the biggest shot, but now I need a little generosity
Didn't say don't give him money
It said don't give him money
That's right. And I don't mean money
I'm a salesman. I was never in it for the money
enlarge yourself
Okay smells like what's he at?
40 percent
All right deal
I was only ever in it for the
freedom
Make your own deals to call your own shots
And sometimes in the morning a little
Hyperlink rocked again sounds good doesn't it kid don't you want to be just like your old pal spampton?
Take the deal
I don't think I don't think I would know i'm gonna take the deal
Now that's what i'm talking about. You got guts kid. That's discomfort and abdominal pain in my guts
And they can win wild prizes
Oh, all right. I get it. What is he at 60? I gotta heal
If I heal deal I heal 60 deal and heal 60. Let's do it
Don't worry kid
I will give you deal insurance only for low low price of a thousand kromer an awesome price an absolutely terrifying price
Which is so low everyone. Oh everyone I know is dead
I'm not gonna buy the insurance
But you don't have enough wacky stacks
Kid you're killing me
Please stop killing me. I will give you another deal
press f1 for help
Congratulations, you are the
what
All right, he's at 80 percent
All right deal
Don't worry kids. I'm an honest man
I just need your account details and the number on the back of the card and you can enjoy a thousand feet over
I refuse
What you don't need it
That's a real big shot move kid. You're like me
Yes, we know what we want. Don't we?
Wild prizes hot single 100 customer and most of all
Will you take the final deal remember this is up to you I won't force you
I'll take the deal
And a deal's a deal
Where's your doing business with you kid?
Oh, he took 24 dollars now on to the next step
I'll be waiting at my homemade store front site
In the trash area close the repairs
Come alone and don't forget to like and subscribe for
He's in the trash house. Yeah, he's in the trash house. We gotta go to the trash house now, don't we?
It's a dumpster. It looks like there's a pillow inside the poster is torn revealing a faded one underneath
Big shot autos take a ride around town and our special the rest is cut off. Should I go there now?
I'm assuming i'll get access to like the actual hub world again, right? I loved that guy. That guy was awesome
Oh, right. I was I forgot about this
Get it first. We have to drive to find noel
Turn on the high beams
When she sees the queen's signal she will come running
Why?
Need to find noel so badly
What are you saying? The city is dangerous
Imagine poor noel clipping into a wall somewhere
wasting away from potassium deficiency
You're actually worried about her. It would be if I wasn't going to find her
uh, but
Why her?
Wait, let me guess is it because she's weak enough to make it and you can make me and make the person into a peon
No, just the opposite
It's because she's strong. What? Huh?
Let's stop the car. What's wrong with it?
um
I was just concerned because it hadn't exploded yet
Looks like we'll have to split up on foot
She's such a
weirdo
Chris if you see noel tell her my knowledge of her preferences is absolute and if she needs proof
Use this queen's mixtape was thrown into your key items
Toodles for you somehow. I feel like we're almost out of here
Let's go chris check on lancer. Hey, thanks for the tape. I was hungry push my tummy to hear a cool song. That's it
Nice gosh, that was close. Wasn't it chris?
This strange world this big city. It's so wild. It kind of makes my head spin looks like another puzzle
Maybe if I go down here
okay
e e
E e I said the city makes my head spin
I didn't mean in a bad way, you know
I was wanting to go someplace new, you know
E e c and des always told me she'd take me
Somewhere like this
Somewhere with shining lights e e c
e
C why don't you miss exploring chris back when the four of us were kids?
Gosh, remember that night. We explored the forest behind the graveyard. He's
December
I know we never found anything interesting back there. I mostly remember crying because I was scared
december
For some reason I feel nostalgic thinking about it
Yes
Yes wiping away my tears with the warm sleeves that smell like cinnamon
I guess I didn't mind being scared if it meant someone would comfort me
December chris is the only one who knows how weird I am. It's not fair. You know
Everyone knows how weird you are
December we got deals the ball throwing game prizes are seated under the counter
Ball throwing game prizes are seated under the counter. It's a ball throwing game prizes are seated under the counter, right?
bottom
All throwing games. Does this matter?
Does placement of this stuff matter? I feel like it kind of I feel like it does why?
Oh, no, she's coming back
I'll hide in that stall
Hey, check this out
Sweet right
Where's my prize?
Oh, um
here
Nice
Wait, I actually don't want this
Nobody does
How was that
Uh suzy, you're not supposed to attack people with it
Oh, yeah, watch me chris. There you are
Chris check out my new attack plus two healing you felt slightly healed
How's that meet the new healing master chris?
Oh, yes, she is a real master at it chris
God teaching you sarcasm was a mistake
Hey
Oh chris, what's that you have there? Is that a gift for someone?
Give to birdly
Give to noelle give to ralcy give to suzy give to birdly. Who do I want to give this to?
I think I want to give this to birdly chris. Have you seen?
Chris we took a break from trucing for one second and you're already back with suzy should have expected this
You couldn't keep up with my puzzle solving skills
Uh-huh
plush of
me with nipples
Um, I guess i'll forgive you for now. See you chris. All right. Why the hell did you give it to birdly?
Why did you give it to birdly? What unexpected kindness?
Let's just get the hell out of here. Wait
noelle
What the hell were you doing in there? That's cheating. I um, um, um
Glad you're okay though
Since that stupid queen took you I was kind of worried. Yeah, I don't thump thump. That's the foot tap. Wait
Aren't you on their side?
Huh?
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait
Uh, I I
Chris help me. She is our enemy now. We have a truce
That's right. We have a truce
Chris said I could be on your team
Oh really?
Well, if chris said so I guess didn't really want to kill you anyway
So get in line already. Oh, okay chris also said I should be behind suzy
Uh, well chris said so
Let's go
Guess i'll join too, but only for this room
Yeah
Our party is complete. That's funny. Oh save point. Um, I should probably go pee
Yeah, let's go. All right. Let me take a break
I'm gonna get some water
And we'll take a quick brb. I'll be back in like two or three minutes. I'm back
But I am crunching on some almonds
Good gamer snack
So give me one second
Yeah, i'm gonna go out on a limb here and say that just like roasted almonds like salted roasted almonds
That's the best gamer snack. It's quick
You don't need to eat very many of them
peanuts too, but especially almonds
They're calorie dense
They're nutrient dense
Very crunchy. They're very crunchy as you can tell
That was larry. I was just doing larry david
They're very crunchy very crunchy
All right, let's go chat monkey mode engage. All right, should I go up? All right
status report update
Those of you that have played this
How many more hours from now?
Until I've received the completion of chapter two's completion
Okay
About two to three hours at this pace about three or four hours. Okay
Okay, you're exactly halfway through
Really?
About two or three. Okay
Okay
so
Well, here's what's probably gonna happen
We're gonna go for a little longer
Probably like another hour i'd say
and then tomorrow
We're gonna open with this i'm gonna complete it and then we'll move on to the umbrella game
Cuz I don't I don't want like blow through this
You know what I mean? I don't want to just like
Do a seven hour stream and like eight hour stream blow throughs and just forget it tomorrow
You also have to do the secret boss i'll try
All right, so we'll go for like another hour. Let's go
I take the stairs of the teacups. What's the point of that? Wait, I know. Um to turn up that force field
Just stay standing on this switch
Huh?
Well, see you later
Wait, what?
Okay
The treasure of air where three are one place one to three
Perhaps it means we all have to enter one teacup
I don't like doing it but it works
Okay, you're eating a tuna melt
I wish
For a split second
And I mean like one full second I could snap my fingers and just be you for one second
Right when you take a bite
Like you bite down. I mean i'm you now i'm not you. I just I you know what I mean god
I just want to be you for one second
It's like I want to eat that delicious fucking tuna milk
Okay, you want to possess some no I
Wait, what happened? Did it work?
Why are you so high? No, I what are you talking about?
Well, do we have tuna haters in the chat right here?
Like a tuna fish a tuna fish sandwich
We don't right?
There's nothing in here
All for nothing. Tuna is good. Just don't take too long. Okay, wait
Do more silence
Tuna is amazing
Well, let me rephrase that I like tuna
I hold on. Sorry. Let me redo that
I like
tuna
but
It has to be cooked all the way through i'm talking tuna from the can
Let me show you my ultimate healing move
Get hit
avoid
Lucy told you to avoid getting hit by the ambulances. Okay. I smell like ice proful
isopropyl alcohol
It was amazing from the can
Yeah, that's how I like it like that. You take it out of the can
You mush it up with a fork
You get it to I don't know this might sound gross, but it's not
You get it to a paste consistency slightly chunky. Don't go too crazy. So it's not like like baby puke. You know what I mean?
Hat food. Yeah, what's okay? Sure
So, um, why are you all writing a teacup together?
Nuclear bunker andy
No, you have no idea going to school
opening up my lunch
and I had
Tuna sandwich in there. That was a big deal
It's like wait mom. What's in there? What's the sandwich?
Usually it would be just like bologna and american cheese, right? Oh man. What if it was tuna fish?
We were eating that day
It was amazing if that was in there
I would eat it so fast
too fast
We were eating fast that day
Wait, where'd they all go? Oh, wait, isn't the hacker do this?
You're being invaded
Wait, I don't want to pop the balloons
No, I want to keep the balloons
Oh no
cheese
All right. Can I get all three of them?
Uh, we'll do that. All right being pushed around
Spare well now let's actually act
crap all
spare
Shit. All right. I got you
Gamble time i'm doing a scratch off ticket if I win money i'll give subs
Let's bet how much I'll win if you get it right you get 30 of when I win
um
Here's what's gonna happen. You are going to scratch off. Let's say that there's eight slots
Eight slots, right?
You're gonna win on every single one of them. You're gonna win on all eight. You're gonna match eight of your numbers
You're gonna be freaking out
And you're gonna go to the bottom to see what you won and it's gonna be two dollars for each slot
Now that's the worst
But you know this time this time. Here's what I want to hope happens
Hope this time you get one just instant win. You don't have to match any numbers or anything
Don't have to match
And it's like a hundred thousand dollars
Hope that happens to you
And I don't want you to give me any of it goals in the chat
What's up job?
What's going on?
I just what you just you don't have to like you're just watching. He's just hanging out
Hey, I hope you win a hundred thousand. I might let me do it. Do I like the game? Yeah
I think it's really good
It's really fun. Really funny. How the fuck are you doing?
You're gonna hang out sometime. We still have like the the first
Um part of the second half of the tutorial
In halo infinite, so
I mean, I mean if you're around
I I don't like this spiders and finding vasik are the worst
There we go
Hey
Susie
The hell you blaming me for you made the trap what?
Oh, it tricked me. I don't like this one. I'm very hard at this one
She ate the cheese. This is the time that you played halo on impossible difficulty and hated it. Yes
The only time i've ever played halo in my life
We played it on impossible
And we didn't even make it out of the tutorial
And I never played it again and I hate the series
That's so fucked up
Oh, wait a second. Where's noelle?
Sorry, I just never seen fireworks up close before
Fuck you for that. What?
Those bullets what you scared?
Uh, um, I guess so. Maybe that's uh, why I couldn't stop watching
Fuck you for doing that zero to catch mice
Okay, so how do we you put the mice in the hole?
Ah, okay. I get it
Wait, I need a mouse
Where do I get a mouse?
Oh, okay. You have to let him go
What do I think about the final smash dlc fighter? I don't even know who it is
Wait, I don't think they even announced it yet. Are they announcing it like next week 20 more?
Maybe if we um split up the world. I wonder who it's gonna be obviously honestly
because
This is the last smash character ever right?
I don't know. Are they gonna make another smash brothers? They kind of can't
If they make another smash brothers, they can't who they're gonna add for characters like mr clean
How are they gonna do this again make a prediction? I'm gonna make a prediction. Um, yeah
Unless they start adding serial mascots. There's no way there's gonna be another smash brothers. I'm gonna say because okay
They're either gonna do one of two things. The first thing they're gonna do is they're gonna do some
Incredibly iconic video game character that is not there yet
Like I don't know
Like the doom guy, right?
I saw that floating around before and that would make a little bit sense like oh doom like gaming history, right?
but what they probably are gonna do it's probably gonna be crash bandicoot because
That would be the ultimate
nintendo
microsoft
Collaboration between every third party. It's probably gonna be crash bandicoot. It probably will
It's like playstation sony sega
Microsoft i'll tell you. Oh, all right. All right. Here's a prediction. I'll make that will make me really upset
It better not be a fire emblem character, right?
That would be like you can't do that for the final character if it wasn't gonna be crash bandicoot or so. I don't know
I
Shinkuro Miyamoto
Can I say like that? I don't know that might that would be actually that could happen. It's not gonna be waluigi
No that that that unless it was it april 1st. Hope they put mario in phoenix, right?
I don't know if phoenix right is gonna be the last character
I'm trying to think of anybody else that I think would actually be in the final slot
I know i'm sorry. I'll play the game play again. I'll give me one more second crash bandicoot doom guy
Shigeru Miyamoto
Or i'll give you one like the top four
um
Fucking ronald mcdonald
I don't know. That'd be awesome
I would okay. Let me ask you would you be upset?
If ronald mcdonald was the last character. No, you'd be you'd be so happy everybody would go crazy
I've said this before but I tell you where they really messed up is not putting scrooge mcduck in the game because that was
A classic nintendo game. He has a move set that makes perfect sense. He's got the pogo. He's got the gems
He's got the golf swing
It was a mistake to not put him in there and you already have disney bullshit in the game with the
Wait, do they have disney bullshit in the game? Is there disney bullshit in the game? Fuck. It's gonna be sora
No, it's not nobody cares about kingdom hearts right now. That should have been like a year ago
No, it's not gonna be sora now. Okay. I would have agreed with sora if this was like
Like early 2020. Nope too late rayman would be cool
All right, i'll release the mice susie will break the balloons when they reach the top
Chrono from chrono trigger. No, oh, they don't give a shit about that franchise
Susie will break the balloons when they reach the top and chris you catch them
Okay, they picked the characters in november 2019. Oh, that's you know, that's right
That's actually correct. It really might be sora
But don't you think you would do that?
Not as the last character
All right, hold on
Because honestly if you had okay the final character
Of the dlc
Should be banjo kazooie
Right unless you got somebody better than that. Think about it
Who have they put in the game so far that has like a huge impact on all of video games?
Is that i'm very bad at this
I'm saying like who could it be possibly that's that's more
Ridiculous than banjo minecraft steve. Yeah
But then who would the final person be it's not gonna be sora
If it was gonna be sora sora would have been announced where banjo was announced and banjo would be the last character
You see what i'm saying?
Because kingdom hearts 3 was relevant back then not now
Master chief, I don't know about that. Oh, yeah, take that you stupid mice. I'm seeing you enjoy puzzles susie
They aren't awful if you do them like that
Not bad. Well, that was kind of smart. Maybe a tetris block. Yeah
I mean nobody really thought that piranha plant was gonna be in the game
But that kind of just came out of nowhere. Can I?
Okay, let's i gotta pay attention to the game, but you have my thoughts crash bandicoot doom guy. Shigeru Miyamoto
uh
a regular nintendo nes where the controllers are your arms
and like two
Nes light guns are your legs. There's also I don't know maybe a possibility
Need one
He's so high
Oh
Look, we're finally close to the fountain
It's queen's mansion
Oh, what why did we come here?
Chris you brought noelle right to me
I knew our truce was the best
But unfortunately, that means truces are over
Noelle get over here
but I
Noelle I will only say it one time
Infinitely get over here. Get over here. Get over here. Get over here. Get over here. Get over here. Get over here
I noelle are you hesitating?
Let me if then this for you
how about if
You don't listen then a certain bird might take a ride in the acid river
birdly
That's right. He was just with us
We must have captured him and we weren't looking
I'm sorry chris suzy. I
I wish I could have stayed with you longer
I can't let birdly get hurt, you know
Don't be sad noelle, honey
All that remains is the final step
A splendorous queen. There you are
Sorry, I thought I saw you in a used game store and
Oh noelle, are you okay? You look a little funny. Okay plan b
Yep, jerd, huh?
What are you doing?
I see now her will must be unleashed by force
Perhaps if I make her face into a robot one
You said you wouldn't do that if I
Variable lying set to true we were going to be smart together. That's not fair understood
fairness activated
Hey, the thing I calibrated those cages. You said I could trust you
What do you know? How do I know I could trust you? You said you were a gamer
Birdly I only play mobile games
One of you is going to help me with my plan
And it's going to be noelle
The rest of you go to your rooms
I only play mobile games not a real gamer. What are you going to do with me?
Damn
You're still here. I only made four cages
I literally don't know
How do you like your new room units
As you can see they are perfectly suited to your interests which I gleaned from your internet search results
I estimate you will have no desire to leave
Please tantalize yourself with your surroundings and wait patiently while I dominate the world toodles
Chris hey, can you hear me? It's like there's some way to communicate between rooms
Convenient, isn't it? I really thought of everything
Shut up
Anyway, let's think of some way to get out of here
Rousey you got any bright ideas?
Uh, hey, where the hell's rousey?
Damn, that's soft yet tender screaming
Chris that's gotta be him
Quick, we gotta think of some way to get out anything you smuggled in that might help us lancer
Should I take the lancer cookie?
Maybe he'll come out and help. Oh, it's me lancer release me and I will release you
Miss me
Because I missed you
Lancer that you I thought you ditched us
No, I love ditches, but I never did you
I was simply relaxing in Chris's spacious pants. Oh
Oh pocket
Yes, and I saw it. Oh
pants then various items
A wild mom puts you in some shock cages. Uh, yeah, we're trapped. So, uh
Hey, wait, did you see us on the roller coaster?
Yes, it was amazing. My first coaster ride ever
I love getting nauseous with friends
Hey, you should probably uh free us
Oh right. Yes
You can always rely on friendly me
I almost swallowed. I must have choked on my own saliva to make you free
I have no idea how to use this
Request new item for room. That sounds good
I think before I shovel
What do you let's say? Uh
quantity overload
All right work
Let's go blue person whose name I know
Jelly in the shape of various knives from search query sharpest kitchen knife. Yo
It's a calendar with college vacations circled
from search query
summer vacation college when
juggler's book on juggling and other tricks from search query how to use magic
It's two pixelated toriel's playing the piano from search video game piano tutorial
Get out of here
It's a vhs explaining how to install video game piano from search query video game piano tutorial use the communication device
Yes, you put your whole head inside and honked
Chris what the hell are you doing trying to fit your head? Okay. Yeah, me too
Hey, we don't have time for this. It's dozens and dozens of bath bombs from search query diy bath bomb. All right, let's go
Chris. Hey
Man lancer, you're the best
Come on. Noel and rousey are waiting
Yes
Let's put the pedal on the metal
What
Hey lancer, are you okay? I i'm fine. I'm just very cold
Hey, what the hell I
Are you okay, dude? Here? Let me help you. Thanks. Sure. See but I
It's not strong enough. Quick chris. Let's find rousey. Maybe he can heal him. Wait, wait
You two aren't going to leave without me. Are you? Uh, yeah, we are
But no, well my damsel in distress. She must be
In distress, I I cannot help with it
Okay, fine. Come with us. Shut up the nameplate reads
Burgly, I mean birdly peek inside. Yes
But you saw surprised you sort of nameplate reads caddy's room peek inside. Sure
Wallpapered with the pink cat ad from the city. It's animated too nameplate reads
Jockington's room peek inside beautiful. Is there a save point? You've escaped from your second personalized room of the day
You're filled with the power of vacation homes
This is an ideal stopping point just so you know, the final act of the chapter kind of starts here. Oh, okay
um
Okay
This is like we're going to like the final like hour or two
ban that guy
Um, hold on just a minute because
Oh, it's all the shovels
Seems like the room is overflowing with shovels and you don't have anything to dig through them with
Who said that?
Whoa, it's a copy of an online skateboarding game from search query cool skateboarding game online
somewhat glitched out hologram
from the search query
uh
Accidental smash on the keyboard. Susie's talktube thing looks a bit bigger for her larger head an egg
Painted egg. It's warm
from can harboil eggs hatch
Vacuum powered book from search query losers. This library sucks. Can I go in any of the rooms?
You respected the gamer's code. No screen peeking. You can smell the glittery cat food from here. Anyways
Uh, let's know
You feel like noelle would enjoy this more
Asriel's room peek inside. Yes
You opened the door with your eyes closed. You saw nothing for the feeling. You wouldn't learn anything. It was like a puzzle
think uh
Think you can do it chris
On your skinless boneless thighs everyone. I'll think of a solution
Chris just ignore him. I'll just be over here where I can't hear you
Now be here away from your iq debuffing aura
These dark bulbs will cast a bright shadow on the ground
Why are you doing a castle griffin state voice? I don't know because he's like i'm a hero. I'm a champion
He's like larping. So that's why
Fill in the space with dark to unlock the way
All right. See you tomorrow. Oh fuck. I can't leave
Ah chris still stumped by this simple diversion. That'll put your neurons back in the crayon box chris
I can already feel the solution welling up in my brain cavity
That's what I will say now go
Uh, I saved it back there
Yeah, all right if this is a good stopping point then this is a good stopping point i'm gonna i'm streaming tomorrow
But I would we're doing two days this weekend. So don't worry. This is a good point. Yeah, this is all right
So tomorrow might be a little longer than
Maybe because if this is only like another two hours, maybe
three hours
less
Than the umbrella game. Yeah, I think that makes sense
Because I think there's like two is there's like two or three hours in the umbrella game left
And there's like two hours left in this
So that's a
Should be like a five to six hour stream tomorrow
You have about two hours to completion if you do the secret area. Yeah, then that that makes sense then
Because I want time tomorrow to be able to well not time tomorrow. I want
Um, I want to have enough content tomorrow because I don't know if the umbrella game has more than an hour or two
Two hours pepe left for like three hours to be honest
Yeah, but I think we'll be okay
Depends on how long you take on some of the bosses. Yeah
And look tomorrow we can go a little long tomorrow. It's fine
I wanted to make sure I started it and got to a point where we could do it again tomorrow
Okay, and look I look if we if the next if it takes four or five hours to do tomorrow
Then whatever i'll play that that'll be it. I don't want to rush through this. That's the problem
I want to like take a time to like
Actually take in the information and stuff because before I don't know if you guys remember
If a game was like seven to eight hours before like seven ish hours
I would just blow through the whole thing in one stream sometimes
And then just be done with it and then just like okay, that's it. See you later
Um, I really want to like process this shit
It's like i've been waiting for this game to come out for a while
I don't just want to like just inhale like eight hours of a gamer session and just forget the whole game
I need my turtle half to process the game
Yeah, we'll see you tomorrow. Uh start at the same time two o'clock pacific
We'll finish this and if there's time we'll finish the umbrella game. Have a great rest of your evening
We're not done yet because i'm gonna go like this. Thanks for the subs. Appreciate it everybody. Thank you
Very much appreciated a little shorter than usual, but you know these days I don't really have a timer
But I do want each stream to be at least four to five hours. Maybe we go a little long tomorrow
Any grotto beast thing when grotto beast we will be talking very very deeply about grotto beasts
I'm hoping very deeply and I mean very deeply about a month from now. You'll be hearing a lot about it. I would say
Because I really want to make sure that it's possible to get it out for this year's like holiday season
What we're trying to do see if we hit that target grotto beast tournament prize pool
Philosophical grotto beast discussion with professor germa
Wait, what is grotto beast? You don't even need to know until I tell you
Probably three or four weeks from now
But I think before that you'll probably hear about a few things
Especially considering well, you know, why don't we just yeah, you know, maybe tomorrow or the night, you know
No, no, no, I I don't want to let me talk to people today and tonight and tomorrow
And make sure I get you some correct information
So maybe we'll talk about some stuff tomorrow. So now that you said that it's going to be another three months
Well, I mean technically it might probably is going to be three months before you can see it
Because that's what I want to have it you be able to get it
I don't have a release date for it. All I know is I want to be able to have it
Accessible before the end of december. That's what I want if it's possible. We'll see if not, then it'll come probably shortly after that
hope
Oh
Oh, that's a tip of the hats
So if you didn't know
Uh, actually a lot of people that probably are new to the channel don't really know that much about
me maybe
more than the last few years
Uh, but there was the team fortress 2 community
Did a charity event every year well tip of the hats
and
Uh, I would participate in it
As of probably i'd say like a few years ago
And I think they're doing their final one
this
The next couple of days, I think
So go, uh, definitely go support them
All the the old tf2 guys
I think they've moved on too. I think they're doing like valorant stuff now and
Um, they're all really really good people. So
Uh, we're gonna raid them
But this is the final one go support it go say hello
And I will see you guys tomorrow
Well, they're ending right now. All right, hold this for tomorrow. Hold this for tomorrow. It just ended. Oh shit
shit
All right, I think they're going tomorrow. They'll be back tomorrow. All right
We'll get them tomorrow
Hold hold till tomorrow
We're going there tomorrow
bad timing andy
But honestly like okay, so tomorrow before I go live they're gonna be live before I am
I'm certain of it probably around like 11 a.m. Um
I think they're gonna be live tomorrow somewhere around 11 to 12
Central time maybe
So they'll be live before I am so go support them before you you know
Do you want to stay then stay there?
So now all right, but we'll see if we can catch them tomorrow. Well now I got where we're gonna go
Who's streaming right now?
Uh, who's live?
Oh shit, I just broke my chair
Hold on. I was like leaning too far
What the fuck?
Okay
Uh, we're gonna let's go say hi to kraken
I actually I think I actually did break the chair. How did I fucking do this? Do I have to go get another chair?
I haven't really um
How do I fuck this up?
No, we're not delaying tomorrow because of that
Uh go say hi to kraken if you don't know kraken was
A huge part of the dollhouse stream. I know you a few weeks ago. We did the um
behind the scenes show
but
Go say hello
Playing minecraft. What are you doing minecraft kraken?
Building a spooky sky carnival. Holy shit
Uh go say hi
I'll see you guys tomorrow
More chapter two of i almost said undertale, but that's not true
Take care of yourselves. See you soon
Bye. Good night
See you later