I am back.
So this is a fast-paced moving shooter.
This is not a controller game, right?
What about viewfinder?
Yeah, that's true.
I already got it open though.
It's a Guggerda game.
I, I like Guggerda games.
All right, let me make sure this is good to go.
Should be.
Capture this.
I need to capture a game.
I would like to capture a game.
That'd be great.
How high should my sensitivity be?
Dude.
All right.
It looks good.
Let's go.
Is there a cutscene?
Probably.
Did I just skip the cutscene?
I didn't mean to.
Should have known it was going to end this way.
Did I skip the cutscene?
God's sick sense of humor or something.
People like me don't get second chances.
If I did, I swear.
I can't believe there are 10 Winnie the Pooh movies.
I'm so mad about that because I've never won the million in that game.
I'm just never going to be allowed to.
I'm just never going to be allowed to get it.
I shook my head the whole time I was peeing.
There's no way.
I swear I was just in the middle of something.
Remember a thing though.
Where the heck am I?
Do I know these people?
That's what's going to happen in about five seconds.
Neons rejoice for you've arrived in glorious heaven.
What?
We are the believers agents of God.
Okay, can one of the mods change the title?
Because that does not make sense for neon white.
And you dead mortals are what we refer to as neons sinners.
The goddess judged most unfavorably.
Okay.
Wait, am I meant to be in hell?
But fret not for we have granted you an opportunity for salvation in
our annual competition.
The 10 days keep it during these 10 days you neons will use your
villainous talents to annihilate the demons invading our Holy Land.
Okay, I think I can handle that.
This is for real.
Hey, guess what?
You died and God thinks you suck.
Go kill some crap.
That's me.
You will each receive a soul card containing a weapon.
I'm that character.
Tana soul card.
Soul card with a melee slash attack.
It cannot be discarded.
Attach note reads according to our records fights.
Ideal weapon is a totally sick Samurai sword.
The most competent Demon Slayer will receive the ultimate reward.
That's me.
I'm very own place in what the fuck?
No, I want to be that character.
That's not like you at all.
You don't you don't act like that guy did.
That's me.
You can be the other one.
You can be like this like boss character or something.
But first some housekeeping.
That's me.
Aeon white do not forget you are here in heaven as guests.
These masks don't mean an explosive that we won't hesitate to
detonate if you step out of line.
And I guess I'm going to please refrain from removing them.
Unless of course you'd prefer to go out in flames.
Yeesh.
I guess lowly sinner shouldn't expect red carpet treatment.
But heaven kind of seems like a racket and yet forgiveness
strangely compelling to me like every inch of my body is calling
out for it.
It's almost painful voice act along.
That's that's what we're doing.
Who exactly did I used to be?
Now then go forth catch your boat at the glassport and kill
every demon you find will be counting.
All right, demons soul cards.
No sweat memories might be hazy, but I don't need a tutorial
on how to kick ass.
They are going to do a tutorial, right?
Love tutorials.
Okay, movement.
Sure.
W S A D it's W A S D use me way way way too hard.
Way too much.
I'm going to go with 30 and then how's the FOV should I be
a hundred or too much is 95.
All right, find out a little too low.
Looks really cool.
They like point 40.
Okay, what am I looking at here?
Is there a double jump?
There's a glide.
Oh, this is very pretty.
I have ammo for this.
Oh, now what?
Oh, you can walk in this jumping to your bunny hopping.
Is it be hopping?
Not really music's too loud.
I got you.
That's all right.
I think that's a little bit better.
You did it.
You got a bronze medal bronze medal unlock insight level
one unlock for this level gifts findable.
Okay, press restart.
Wait, you can just quick restart.
Okay, that's a quick restart.
There are seven demons.
Terrify card fires like a machine gun.
Swap cards with Q.
I think I want to change that to a different button, but start
like this.
There's sprint or anything or am I just always sprinting?
Oh, what's next?
I level to nice TF to aim.
I was at an insult.
Okay, I get it.
That's pretty fast.
I'll take it.
Your voice is annoying.
You should mute your mic must have been a real hardcore.
It's me yellow.
You're annoying.
How's that sound?
It has been a minute.
Neon yellow.
This guy even with a mask on I recognize him from earlier.
Tell I know him just vaguely.
That's me.
Holy crap.
You got the freaking anime sword.
I thought for sure you'd get one of those little guns like
the oh should have to turn the page.
Sorry.
Everyone's waiting.
What's it called like gnomes use?
Gnomes.
I know you're a badass.
Hell doesn't idiot like this seem to remember me perfectly.
I'm not gonna skip all the dialogue.
But no, we need I'm gonna know what's going on.
Okay, man.
No, for real.
We rolled together for years, bro.
Got off to some crazy stuff.
You're my sass game, man.
The darkness to my light.
You know, I saved your life once took a bullet for you, dude.
Really?
Nah, I'm just messing.
I'm not skipping.
I'm not skipping anything.
Yeah.
All right.
Seriously, dude, we should team up just like old times.
Then I can save you for real from those like demon freaks
or something.
Yeah.
Appreciate the offer.
But no, thanks.
I work alone.
Don't shush shush.
Don't shush me.
Don't tweet at me.
Like my favorite line from a from a TV show.
It could be one of my favorite lines.
Don't shush me.
Don't tweet me.
Just there's so much going on in that sentence.
I love it.
Sure.
Good meeting you.
Let's go.
This is a pistol.
This card ability triggers a second jump right midair.
How do I discard a card?
Oh, can I have another one of those?
Do I only have to have one bullet for it to work?
Oh, I see.
Okay, you have to collect them.
Whoa, that's okay.
I get it now.
Cool.
Cleared it.
Oh shit.
He's playing a real game.
It's a good.
It's it.
Yeah.
Yes.
Is this as fast as I can go?
I'm assuming.
Yes.
Didn't even break a sweat.
No, I can go even faster than that.
Technically.
No, not even close.
Rank up.
I ironically like this game.
I mean the game seems fun.
Jump on a balloon demon to kill it and bounce into the air.
And with a double jump, that would be pretty cool.
Oh, I blew it.
Here we go.
I got to save this.
Oh, there's still a demon left.
Oh shit.
Okay.
Hold on.
I need to I don't like you being the button to press.
I want to be like mouse for like a little too.
All right.
This game is fun.
Oh, just one more try.
Just one more try.
It really hits you with that one more try.
There we go.
Yeah, gold medal.
Gold medal.
Yeah.
Gift collectible.
This is just the tutorial.
Okay, is that the alt girl I saw from earlier?
Hey, mind letting go of my shirt.
There was this huge demon chasing after me.
Where?
Where is it?
Looks like I lost it.
It was wrong music.
You'd protect me if it came back though, right?
No, sorry.
I got a boat to catch.
You're on your own kid.
You know how I feel about being called kid white.
I actually don't remember amnesia side effect of dying.
It seems to voice Andy.
Seriously, really good.
Aren't they?
I got this one.
I've got this one on lockdown.
You know what I mean?
I'll find me somebody that could do this better than me.
You won't be able to find it.
You're not.
I don't think so.
I've lost some memories too.
Like I can't even remember how to use a gun which makes this
whole situation extra scary.
You will bury.
No, no, no.
Bugleberry is more like this.
You'd like to know where the bugleberry voice comes from.
It's very easy to tell you although maybe it should be sort
of a mystery and tell you everything.
Yes.
Yes, the inspiration for bugleberry's voice is none other
than our favorite cartoon character Captain Crunch.
My cabin crunch cereal.
A little bit of inspiration there.
I think there's a lower bomb right there.
It's a few.
It's a few different people.
It's a few different people but bugleberry is like 33%
Captain Crunch.
I don't know.
I should probably get going.
You wouldn't really abandon a cute girl like me, would you?
I know you don't remember but you were once a great teacher.
Mr.
White I I was well, okay.
Fine.
I can spare a second.
I guess you want to bend your knees a bit arms extended not
locked.
Is this good?
Yeah, but keep it steady.
You should use both hands and fill any open spaces on the
grip with your fingers.
There's something kind of exhilarating about this, huh?
Mr.
White.
I'm just looking through the chat and just seeing just the
people the people that are not they're not even participating
in the chat.
Cold hard metal in my hands that hint of danger.
Like you made you probably the game is probably muted.
You probably have no video on you just talking about what
you had for dinner today.
Anyway, like this.
Holy crap.
Are you sure you forgot?
I was so much fun.
Thanks white.
I owe you big.
Well, you know, it's like you said I'm a great teacher.
Just did the thing with space.
It's violet.
Don't go forgetting this time.
Neon violet.
Violet, huh?
Here girl shoot.
All right, it's time.
Let's uh-huh.
Purify bombs destroy red breakable walls.
So did I do that right?
This work.
Oh great groups of enemies.
It takes about a second.
Not bad.
Am I grandma keeps that?
No, I think we I think we've answered enough my grandmother
asked this question questions for it to last us a few years.
I think stand near the so you can like rocket jump to give
you forward momentum to I'm imagining.
Yes.
Yeah, Captain Crunch sounds nothing like bugleberry.
Well, that's why I said it was inspiration.
It wasn't necessarily a one-to-one impression.
Is there a boss at the end of this again?
I didn't mean it didn't want to do that.
I must have missed it.
Yeah.
Yeah, I'm just getting started.
The bronze medal.
Nineteen demons.
Okay.
Well, I'm fine.
What the hell?
Oh, it's health.
That's how we use the environment bronze bronze is the best no
expectations.
You're not in you're not in second place because in second place
you would feel like damn.
I wish it was first place easy.
You just get awarded for being cool, but there's no pressure
of second place.
You wish you were first is no pressure first place.
Give me bronze all day behind you.
I do that again.
Somebody and the channel.
I don't know if mods can do that or not, but demons zero red
a hundred and the channel if it happens again long time no
see white neon red nice heard from before this girl is you
staring quick say something cool white that is massive
rifle want to taste that's okay.
Seriously, please don't point that thing at me.
Would you realize that this is the least effective way for
you to get me here because barrels very long and the target
here is now very small.
So now if I go I dodge my shoulder grab the barrel push
it over then we're this is this is a problem for you now relax.
I just like to see you sweat.
Okay, John.
In that case you should watch me wipe the floor with demons
sometime.
Yeah, I've seen a lifetime of that kind of thing.
You know, this is actually the first time I've seen you here
in the competition.
I mean makes me wonder do you think this will end for us the
way it did in life?
See, I'd love to answer that but I woke up with no memories
of life.
Not that I don't recognize you.
It's just the details are fuzzy so far though.
I feel the strongest connection to you.
Damn it white.
Why would you say something so lame to a girl how bizarre?
I've never heard of a neon with such an affliction.
Messing with me.
Are you I have no reason to lie to you.
Is that so?
Can't believe God himself decided to bless me with the
thing.
I love most a completely clueless boy.
This isn't fun for me, you know.
Well, it is for me.
We could have been lovers in life and you'd be none the
wiser lovers.
I could know every last one of your measurements.
Be serious here.
You've got a long boat right ahead.
Maybe you could fill me in on the details of my character
or even your relationship to me.
I don't know why honestly, it's probably easier this way
for both of us.
What are you going?
All aboard the ship.
I thought that was us for a second.
Strugglers will be returned to oblivion.
Yes, don't think I made it this far last time.
This really is my first roadie.
What happens if I press half bad?
Looks like that's what happens.
Bad for a dead guy, huh?
I feel like we missed something really important.
I thought it was going to be fast-forward and it was going to be
like, I thought it was going to be funny, but exactly what I
expected.
Why am I so disappointed?
Want to walk to the Believer's Sermon together?
I want to fight, I want to fight demons.
Yo, bro, you made it.
Kick a lot of demon ass.
Yes.
Like it was nothing.
I'm telling you bro, with our like combined powers, those
demons are donezo.
Wait, do we play together?
Do we switch characters?
Oh snap, Violet, is that you?
This is crazy.
It's like the gang's all here.
I'm sorry.
Do I know you?
Are we all mutuals here?
Yeah, man.
Violet was our crew's littlest badass.
Like this one time I read her diary and she had written this
crazy fanfic about her and the bot.
What happened to this guy?
Oh, that was the I'm done.
Okay.
Let me tell you something here.
So that was the I'm done talking.
My dialogue cuts off here.
There is a hyphen.
Somebody needs to interrupt me.
What happens a lot of the time is the person will say the
line with the hyphen there and they'll stop.
So to be like, oh you and me.
Oh yeah, and you get cut off now.
So how you do that and you make that work a little better
is you just hold the hold it at the end.
Are you hold that last line?
Like we were supposed to be going to the grocery.
Oh, then I'll give me that opportunity to cut me off.
No one cares.
This is an acting class out of where the where the hell did
you think you were?
This is like a live streamer.
I play video games.
No, I'm teaching you acting skills.
I don't know what you think this is.
They may be freaks, but
all right, cool.
Welcome to Central Heaven.
It is an honor for your kind to bask in its beauty.
But remember this is no place you guys it's it's fine.
Chill out.
You are here as demon exterminators and demon exterminators
alone population always spirals out of control this time of
year.
It's onerous work, but the possibility of redemption is
well worth the effort.
Is it not and on that note we'd like to introduce last
year's winner of the 10 defending his crown is the vicious
Hulk.
We don't even know who neon green is neon green is going
to be and now it's like all of a sudden.
No, no, don't skip don't skip with this guy.
I love neon green.
Don't skip please.
Why does it feel like he's staring directly at me?
Why do I feel so angry greens demons slaying prowess has
been unrivaled for years, but surely there exists a neon
green among you all who can compete don't skip don't
skip what is happen?
Who are you?
You should play scorn.
I already did.
It was a fun time church is dismissed episode 2 killer
inside.
I'm ready to kill some demons and days until judgment.
Depart for your current assignment lay past assignments.
Let's go to the beach.
Enjoy the view of the beach.
I hate how perfect this beach looks feel like I should toss
something in there next time.
I'm gonna throw all right report to Heaven Central Authority
next thing to do talk to Gabby.
Hey, I'm here for my assignment.
You will get new assignments from mr.
Mikey.
I'm his secretary and let me talk to him.
Mikey a cat to just let me read the script.
This doesn't have to be difficult unless you'd like that.
Mr.
White proceed all Neons must achieve a minimum neon rank
in order to be granted a new assignment.
What's a neon rank your neon rank is determined by the
number of gold or ace medals you have earned in prior
missions.
I won't be getting any of these more gold or aces means
a better rank.
Let's see.
My neon rank is this that good.
Like an a-plus.
I'm sorry.
You'll need to achieve.
Mr.
White Mr.
White.
Mr.
White increase my neon rank has to visit the job archive
at Heaven's Gate earn gold or ace medals.
Got it.
I'll be right back.
All right.
Let's go get some metal.
If three more neon ranks, I think I have to go here,
right?
Depart for your sign is a job archive.
Oh, where do I where do I get a new mission?
Did I not get it?
I'm ready for my next mission.
Oh, Mr.
White it says here you just visit the job.
Oh, I'll be right back.
You guys make me skip the dialogue so fast.
Okay.
Wait, I didn't do good enough.
Is that what it's telling me?
So I have to do I have to go way faster.
This is a speedrunning game.
You're going so slow.
Am I I was 27.
That's a gold medal.
He's got it.
93, right?
Doing fine.
I was just going around.
I what did I get on this one?
Okay bronze.
I need to do this in 13 seconds.
Great startup.
See if I can make that gap.
That's a that's a platinum.
See anyone beat that?
All right.
I get it.
Pretty sure I just got to 93.
This was silver, but I can do it in 19, right?
Let's do it.
I forgot.
I have to actually kill the stuff.
That was fucking messy.
I hold on there.
Another one down.
It's pretty cool.
It is.
Yeah, this is fun.
I'm enjoying it.
Okay.
Next mission time and days until judgment.
Let's go get new assignment.
Well, look at that.
Your neon rank is sufficient to move on to a new assignment.
Sounds are very really good.
Yeah, they're heavenly delight ticket.
How fun ticket granted to top-performing neon is good for one heavenly delight.
Is it the heavenly delight kiosk in the cathedral to redeem an experience beyond
your wildest dream?
One moment while I check on mr.
Mikey schedule.
Have a seat in about four hours for hours.
Why no, there's got to be somebody I can speak with soon.
I'll look into that for you.
And when will that be about four out?
All right.
This is ridiculous.
I'm going.
It is a cat.
Mikey.
Look, I expect this much from the barfield, but I'm not waiting four
hours for my stupid mission in heaven for hours.
I'll get to your ugly mug.
Once I finish up with the lady.
It's fine.
I don't mind if he stays red.
What are you doing in here?
Suit yourself, sweetheart.
Go ahead.
Wise guy.
Take a frequency.
Now listen up because I'm only going to say this once you got 10 days here.
The HCA will be rating your performance alongside the other competing
eons and whoever has the top score.
And if they can win, I'm going to be this for Halloween this year.
Don't steal my costume.
I'm showing up to the party like this.
You better not.
We both have the same neon white costume.
It's going to be it's going to be not cool.
I chose it first.
No, no, I set it out loud first.
I set it out loud first.
You jokers will be cleaning out lower heaven.
Sounds easy enough.
The Dracula.
Because the demons got him white.
I forgot about the Dracula costume.
That's right.
Yeah, I kind of got that.
Anyway, that just about covers it.
Any question?
Yeah.
Why are you a cat?
Okay, you're just saying whatever to me now.
I was actually wondering the same thing.
Why are you a hilarious cartoon cat?
Exactly.
You neons are all the same.
Oh, we're going to break that promise.
Moronic imagery.
Your pee brains embedded in an effort to comprehend as angels.
Oh, you're a cat.
You're a horse.
You're a sexy statue of Liberty.
How about a hey, Mikey?
How's your day, Mikey?
Excuse me.
I'm here for my appointment.
Hey, white, isn't it freaking crazy?
That John Cena is here in heaven giving us missions.
John Cena in this game?
Everybody out.
Don't come back till you finished your missions.
And Gabby, can you please keep these neons under control?
Hey, Red, before you go, I wanted to ask you if you knew what
the deal is with Green.
Stay away from him.
Uh-huh.
He's...
I could use some convincing.
I suppose I could open up more.
In exchange for a favor.
Wait, really?
Keep your pants on.
What's the favor?
What will that be?
Like, after this mission?
What's all this commotion about?
It's piña colada day at the pool.
So?
Heaven's piña coladas are to die for.
That's kind of good.
We'll see about that.
Oh, no, you won't.
I, really?
A sinner partaking in heaven's delight?
That's bull.
Stay back, neon, or I'll have you blown to bits.
Argh.
Are you...
Another cat.
You said you wanted a drink, right?
I know a place.
Follow me.
Why not?
Tada!
Welcome to the neon bar.
You like it?
Oh, it's not like the rest of heaven.
That's for sure.
I'm into it.
Thanks.
Can I actually order drinks?
Does it give me booze?
So, uh, who exactly are you?
You can call me Raz.
I'm the bartender here.
Raz.
I'm imagining you probably buy cards, booze.
White.
Well, white?
Good to meet you.
Believers don't come around these parts anymore.
So, it's the perfect place for neon to take a load off.
I like the sound of that.
What do you have?
How about one of those piña coladas?
On it.
Here you go.
What the?
This is literally just water.
Sorry.
The believers are hogging all the real stuff.
What?
How can you call this a bar if you don't serve any booze?
See, you're thinking too narrow.
A bar, give you one guy, you can fight it in another guy.
What?
Where's my piña colada?
I'm just saying.
A friend and folks in heaven has its benefits.
You'd be surprised by what you can gain from chatting people up.
And maybe giving them some gifts.
The believers wouldn't accept my piña colada patronage.
I doubt they'd let me into their crappy gift shop.
Well, no.
Once you've taken care of your missions, you can do a second
sweep to hunt for presents.
It's like a pain.
White.
And hey, if you give me a gift.
All right, let's go.
Lemon water.
Pause.
There you are.
Team up with me.
Jinx Vi, you owe me a coat.
Yellow, quit getting in my way.
So I have to choose a companion.
Join me.
And clearly the cutest choice here.
I don't know.
I'm pretty freaking cute.
Guys, guys, I'm flattered, but this is a competition.
I'm not here to make friends.
Yo, I totally get you.
That's why we should all team up.
No way.
Three's a crowd.
I'd rather eat my own pancreas.
Come on, Vi.
You sure?
And lone wolf here.
I'm not teaming up with.
You know, I met this other neon earlier who was a total simp.
Maybe I'll just go play with him instead.
Oh, what?
Who?
Looks like it's just you and me, bro.
All right.
So do I have a do I have a power or something with them?
Whoa, whoa, whoa, whoa.
Wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm not ready.
Am I going too slow?
Fuck.
That was pretty.
That was pretty good.
That was gold.
I'll take gold.
I knew you would be bad at Splatoon story mode.
True.
Godspeed soul card.
The soul card fires like a semi-automatic rifle and you get a dash
dash horizontally in the direction you're aiming.
Stores demons and breakable objects.
How far is it?
Okay.
Oh, that was sad, but I can do it.
No, no, no, no, no.
We're doing that again.
Doing that again.
Oh, I can't just cheat.
Can I just cheat?
So it doesn't okay.
You can't get any vertical.
You can.
It's only horizontal only.
Wait a minute.
Can I break this without dashing?
Oh, well 13 another one down cold only use the first Godspeed
to get on the podium.
You just jump interesting.
Oh, that was a bonehead move.
I can take it.
I can do that better.
How much faster do I have to do 1817?
Now I can do 19.
How do I get that?
Wait, that's me.
There it is.
Yippee.
This is a perfect game for a fake manga fan like you.
I see it.
Oops.
Only one shot just that instantly.
Where do I go?
Shit.
Hey, let's keep it going.
22 seconds.
I can do it.
So if you dash through you get another one platinum.
That's how it's done.
Hey, I missed some of the stream.
Did he go to hell and was Ben Franklin there?
I'm not sure yet.
Hell, yeah, dude.
Oh, wait.
Okay.
This is a double here.
This is a grab this shoot and then this is a boom.
Boom.
I think somebody was alive up there.
I can't really tell but whatever.
Oh my God.
I blew it.
I thought that somebody was still alive.
Oh, it's just it's one of the other neons.
Okay.
I thought it was an enemy.
What?
No.
Oh, only silver.
What am I missing here?
12 seconds.
Ah, all right.
Settle down.
The dash somebody said the dash does go vertical.
I can't get it to go vertical.
Does the dash work?
Okay.
When you hit an enemy with the dash, does it actually just refill it?
Doesn't only on those big ones.
I mean, how do I get up there that fast?
Damn it.
I lost time on that.
Skip dropping down.
Just dash.
Shit.
Wait, now I have to break that.
I have to kill the enemy down there.
Skip the second door.
I still have to kill the thing down there though, right?
Shoot it and then dash to the exit.
God damn it.
My brain can't do it.
I mean it can but it's just too many things in a row.
All right.
So, but how how do I skip?
How do I kill that but skip the door without getting the jump?
I get it.
Just go from here to there.
Let me take, let me go slow.
Okay.
I just go like this.
All right.
That's how you do it.
I got it.
Yes.
Let's see anyone beat that.
I wonder if you can even do it normally.
This is a fun game.
I like this.
Come on already.
Quit it with the jokes.
I can't help it.
Yeah.
You and your sunshine.
Did you do something quirky?
Hey.
No.
Sorry.
I don't.
Sounds like it was chill though.
Oh great.
He said he liked the game.
Prepare to never see it after this stream.
Man, I'd give my left nut to go back and do it all over again.
Even all the weird stuff at the end.
I don't blame you for any of it, you know.
What the hell is that supposed to mean?
Dude, chill.
The vibes are immaculate.
What?
I just want to kick ass with my bro.
Did you just say that?
You just said the vibes are immaculate?
Really?
Wow.
Okay.
I like this guy way more now.
Yeah.
My god, dude.
Remember when you messed up the toilet after you ate that chili?
That was insane.
Yo, hold up.
Wait, what?
That's not, why would you, that's a weird thing to bring up to somebody.
That's weird.
That's fucking strange.
I don't know what that's distracting me.
I don't know what that's for.
That was very distracting, but I think I still got the gold medal.
Didn't even break a sweat.
Every cutscene loses like 400 viewers.
That's pretty funny.
That's actually funny.
Shit, I fell.
Shit, I fell again.
Every cutscene loses 500 viewers.
A long way.
How did I lose time?
Oh, it's...
Yeah, that sounds good.
Stop jumping.
I, doesn't do anything.
Damn it.
Yeah.
I feel like I was pretty close to the platinum one.
Let me see.
Probably one or two seconds.
I can definitely get it.
Let's get it.
Oh, sad.
Bounce to platinum.
It's because I'm the best.
I think your Vtuber avatar isn't rigged right.
The space isn't moving.
I feel like I just lost time there.
Let's do that again.
That's definitely the best way to go.
Get a land right on the lip.
I did it too, shit.
That's definitely it.
That might have been more accurate.
Didn't even break a sweat.
Unfortunate.
You just have to hop over the side.
26?
Oh, yeah, I can have that.
That extra second was just the beginning.
I know I'm supposed to get the presence, but whatever.
There it is.
That's how it's done.
To do a Ben and Jerry's tier list.
Half-baked S.
Everything else A.
I don't even need to show it on screen.
Oh, a little too, a little too far there.
I'm gonna hold this.
Damn it.
I'm holding it for way too long.
I can definitely do it.
A hundred percent.
Ready?
Oh, fuck you.
I can definitely do it.
That's gonna shave like three seconds off too.
Oh, come on.
I know I can do it.
It's dope.
Yeah, it's right there.
But whatever.
Let's try it the regular way.
Guess I could shoot and skip this whole thing.
I'm gonna skip that whole section.
I freaked out.
I need to, where do I go?
Hold on.
Where is it?
I'm freaking out.
I need to see it again.
Because it's bounce off.
Okay, it's over here.
Can I just skip this whole section?
I shoot those two in the beginning.
Need to end up up there.
Okay.
See it up.
I don't, maybe I can't.
That's still gold somehow.
What is it?
What is platinum?
All right.
That's pretty fair amount that I still need to do.
Let me try that again.
Oh, it's gone.
Oops.
Oh, there it is.
No.
I know where to go.
You stupid idiot.
Platinum.
It's because I'm the best.
All right.
This is the last level here.
In this particular zone.
I mean, we're kind of just going here.
Oh, it was kind of ugly.
But sorry.
I wonder where the skips are here.
I think I could just do just go faster and I should get it.
I blew it.
All right.
Even break a sweat 22.
I'm making a lot of noises.
Sorry.
I can go faster.
I just got to get the whole thing down.
I'll get it.
Just skip that whole top part.
Let me look at it.
Look at that.
I'm so I'm getting so I'm getting ahead of myself.
Oh, fuck you.
Oh, 23.9 shit in my pants.
23.3.
Fuck you.
Shit.
How?
Oh, you idiot.
I hate you.
It's falling apart.
It's false.
I gotta get back.
Come on.
What are you talking about game?
What are you happening?
What?
I didn't go through.
Why?
How is that?
It's falling apart.
Is that even faster?
It might that might be adding time by the way.
That's adding time.
Oh, you piece of shit.
20.
Oh my God.
I don't like this guy in front of me.
I don't like it.
He's he's doing way better than me every time.
It's annoying.
Wait a minute.
Hold on.
Hold on a second.
I may have just solved it.
Oh, yeah.
I don't think I can get high enough.
Somebody said shoot the glass.
I don't think that works.
I don't think I can get that high.
Just look at the hand icon.
Where is it?
Oh, I see it over there.
What does it want me to do though?
Hold on.
I'm going to jump this way.
I get it.
I mean, this is slop.
This is fucking sloppy.
So how many more demons are there?
Or where are they?
One, two, three.
Okay, I get it.
Oh, come on.
Didn't mean to click twice.
When you do the same level like a hundred times, sometimes your
brain just is like, you know what?
Just do it terribly this time.
And do it terribly ten times in a row.
Still might be all right.
Yeah, I got it.
I got the platinum.
That's a platinum on every level, isn't it?
I like it.
I gotta admit that was pretty hard.
Do we lose four to 500 viewers?
Let's see.
It's kind of the end of the show and
every people are just standing up and walking.
The show is not done, but people are just getting up out of their
seats and walking out.
What we're in the bottom of the ninth inning and my team is up
by a hundred and fifty runs.
So that's about a dozen for me and the kids tonight.
We're going to go home.
Wait, I'm not starting to like this guy.
Am I?
This is part of his plan.
Waiting for me to let my hey, it's all good.
It doesn't matter for 10,000 people.
You know, here's your it could be a thousand of you hanging
out here and I still do it.
What about 10?
Nah, actually at least 12.
Yo, I didn't think I'd actually get to save your life this
fast.
You really got to be more careful, bro.
Here, take my hand.
I was like the concept of a second channel, but I had
Nah, if I'm going to be just kind of chilling out here and
whatever if you're either here or you're not you didn't save
Jack dumbass a second channel is an act.
I don't know what I feel like I would just do the same thing
I'm doing right now in act.
Yeah to see how easily I could have sliced you a master of
comedy.
You freaking crack me up, dude.
Yeah, I'm just gonna do whatever.
We're just gonna do whatever what if there's one thing that
means 5,000 people leave hard, but you really got whatever
who cares wouldn't be best bros.
If I did who gives a crap my back and like vice-visa next
time I'll save you for real.
Tell even worse jokes on a second channel.
Dead guy, huh?
Oh shit viewers increasing.
No, no, that's we don't want that.
We want to we want to drop below 10k.
We don't want to have there be more people.
Welcome back Neons you survived your first mission but
surviving is not the same as winning.
Please direct your attention to greens mechanical halo a
mechanism that grants Neons the ability to stay in heaven.
Get them out of here.
We're looking for negative growth.
I say I want to hit negative growth.
I want people to I want less people to be here.
Yeah, that's what I'm looking for.
I want I want that the least amount of people to be here
that could be what negative growth not a single neon has
come close to overtaking green score.
He's defended his position at the top for many years now
and I I don't imagine he intends to give it up now.
Not when he's made such a comfortable home for himself here
in paradise, isn't that the stomach are you saying that even
if we win we don't get to stay in heaven forever.
Oh goodness.
No God's mercy has its limits and an expiration date seriously.
That's such a rebel.
If you'd prefer the flames of hell for eternity to a year
of heavenly delights and be my guest dark and darker do better.
I have seen a lot of people playing it on stream.
I know they added a couple of classes right staring at me
again.
I'm not trying to skip dialogue.
I'm just trying to get us to a position where I can do the
next chapter in the time that I would like to continue to
stream so it's not about skipping the dialogue but getting
to the action so I can do the chapter so I can continue to
play it in the time that I would like to be streaming you
are bad tone acts.
Let's see.
Well, look at that.
You've earned yourself a heavenly delight.
One moment while I check in go ahead and take a it's all the
people I get the cool.
I'm not I'm not skipping this but I'm just okay.
Okay, I want to do the section and that's probably going to
be the end of the stream.
But I do want to do this.
What I'm so glad I ran into you.
Mikey must have thought I was.
Yeah, what the heck.
You mean?
Yeah, what is it with you?
Sorry.
You really don't remember anything.
This is important dialogue back when we were alive yellow
did some messed up stuff.
He got tangled up with some shady character.
It was you who's are we talking about the same?
Yeah, that's silly.
Let's go.
Okay, I got it.
Come on.
Wait, come on.
Wait, I cannot kill that is just line of sight.
Wait a minute.
That's pretty stupid.
Uh-huh.
Okay.
Fuck.
I don't get it.
I mean I do but I don't because you have to kill everything.
So how would does that count as a demon do I actually have
to kill this thing is it hold on it does count not make that
I guess I that was very slow.
I'm even going right way.
Wait, what the hell is down here?
Okay, hold on.
I feel like this is done very poorly but whatever.
No.
Yeah, not bad.
Could be but could be better but okay.
It's a lot of time to shave off.
I might come back to it.
Yeah, gold's gold's good.
Don't get platinum on every single one.
The machine gun stomp on the ground to create a large blast
that destroys most demons and breakable objects.
Very clear.
I think that's everybody.
Yuck.
Yeah, that that was yuck.
I wonder if I can think I'm going to skip that whole part.
Wait, let's get that part too.
Oh, I missed.
I'll get it.
Bottom, right?
Yeah, did you see that?
Hey viewer, did you pet your pet today?
Go show them some love.
I agree.
I don't know where to go.
Yuck.
I can get a couple seconds shaved off of that.
I think that's actually the play.
No, it's not.
Not at all.
Funny.
Yeah, I still can't believe the Winnie the Pooh question
that I'm going to think about that for like a week.
Maybe maybe no, I can't.
That's I got to make that a lot cleaner.
Okay, cool.
Oh, what a mistake.
What broke it the old and break a sweat.
I could probably get platinum.
What does it probably 19 18?
I could do 20 that I should be able to get 20.
Excuse me.
What was there was a hint right there.
Hold on.
What's the goal here?
Oh, does that help?
Well, okay.
Anyone beat that floppy, but I got it.
Gonna dash through the door for more time.
That's true.
I got caught right there.
Oh, saving time.
Yeah.
How old do you think we are German?
I think it I don't know.
This is a pretty big range.
I got stuck.
Oops.
Oh, it's over.
Maybe not.
Hey, sorry.
What's your target demographic?
This is a mature audience stream.
Yeah, I'm really working up a sweat is the stream is for adults.
Nevermind.
You're not an adult.
Get out of here.
Neon orange.
That's a fuck out of here.
If you're not an adult, the secret.
Damn, that sucks.
Tell me more about these secrets though.
Are you gonna skip the story?
Yeah.
Damn, dude.
I love it in all caps in the middle of this.
Everybody leave it.
It's a cutscene.
And look what happened.
Actually, I think I'm all right with that.
I think I got the whole gist of what just happened.
I'm okay with that.
I think I understand everything.
I've comprehended everything that happened.
Silver.
That was a gold if I ever seen it.
Yeah.
Why am I getting this?
That's completely unnecessary.
Another one down.
Just skip that whole section.
I don't know why I'm getting the falling down so gently.
There's a way to go down there, but I'm going to keep my tactic.
My tactic didn't even wait one.
Oh, that's sad 1647.
Yeah, I didn't even need to use the thing.
See that don't even need the hand.
I got the ace medal without it.
What I got in 13 seconds 14 seconds, but it's all good.
Okay.
All right.
Oh, okay.
Well, we'll try that again.
That's a mess up right there.
I'm doing something really fucking wrong here.
Better, but I keep losing momentum over there.
I bet I can skip that part.
Whoa, I went way too high.
Oh, it was long.
What part of your body did you wash last my hands?
Pretty good.
Gotcha question though.
Give her to shoot this guy too.
Oh fuck.
No, I win.
Yeah, I didn't know this where it was.
Oh, I think that's doable without any shortcuts.
That was terrible.
Let me try that again.
Oh, come on.
Let me try this too.
Ready?
Okay.
That's all right.
Why did I fall?
I shaved off a full second right there.
Oh, oh fuck off.
I don't I hate what this place.
Bad placement.
What is going on here?
How come I keep just jumping over that?
I have an idea.
That idea was really dumb.
Don't be impatient.
That's my entire life.
My whole life has been being impatient.
My entire existence is built off of being impatient.
Everything you've ever seen, you've ever heard is because of my impatience.
Oh, I fucked it up.
No, I used it.
It was stupid.
Where is it?
I know what to do.
I got it.
Just wait, wait, wait.
Just shoot everything over there.
I have to keep one of these.
You idiot.
I even knew what I had to do too.
I still did it wrong.
My brain was like, do it like this.
Do it like this.
Oh, don't do it like that.
Excuse me.
Oh, why?
Why?
Oh my God.
I just I started overthinking everything.
I didn't even want that thing equipped.
I wanted the rifle.
I wanted the rifle equipped.
This thing.
Okay.
Do it right.
I don't even know if it helps.
Oh my God.
Damn it.
I just I keep getting there and forgetting the entire video game.
I'm just like, yeah, jump, jump, jump.
How do I?
I don't know the buttons.
How do I play?
No, I need to jump.
Oh my God.
I'm about to skip the level.
I know there's a hand over there, but I want to do I wanted to get it
without the hand.
Does that even save time?
Hard to tell.
That was stupid.
That was really stupid.
That was so stupid.
I'm just not just go just go to go.
I'm going to get stuck here for like four hours.
Just go just end it.
Excuse me.
That's got to be platinum.
They didn't even break a sweat.
Excuse me.
It's been exclaiming random loud sounds today.
I'll give it one or two more attempts because this one was fun.
That was that was yucky.
What was that?
Okay, I'm done.
I'm done.
Oh, shut up.
That's so stupid.
That lip should not be as loud.
You know what I mean?
That was dumb.
Oh, I thought I had one more.
Oh, this game just hurts my brain.
I thought I had one more dash.
Oh, now it's all falling apart.
I'm gonna just keep going.
What the fuck?
I didn't land.
Stupid game actually stupid games that like how come on.
I should have went through annoying.
Oh, shut up.
That's why I didn't have to because sometimes things stupid.
What the fuck happened there?
What happened there?
What happened?
Why did I not launch?
I should why did I not hit the barrel?
Gamer fatigue.
This is gamer fatigue for sure.
A hundred percent.
Here we go.
I had the other dash.
I just didn't use it.
All right.
Come on.
This is the one.
Why did he not hit the barrel rewind it and play it a thousand times in a row?
The barrel is a gigantic pit box.
How am I not hitting it?
That's got to be it.
Oh, you got to be kidding me.
Oh, I can do it.
It's just like walk up the edge.
Oh, shut up.
Fuck you.
Oh my God.
I move on.
All right.
I think I missed a few people.
Oh, I'll take it.
I'll take it.
How do you like the break?
I'll always do this soundtrack is great.
Oh, I was so close.
I'm trying to go so fast.
Yes, that's how it's done.
All right.
That's a good one to go out on.
Your addiction is showing.
I understand why a lot of you like this game.
I'm kind of freaking out, but it's okay.
It working.
That's not good.
See, I keep I fell off that one last time too.
Oh fuck better.
Yeah, you haven't beaten Tomar in a single level.
Yeah.
Have I not?
Well, whatever.
That's all right.
21.3.
Bro, you're a snail.
Do you think heaven has any hot springs we could soak in?
That's for a dead guy, huh?
Not skipping because I want to.
I'm skipping because I'm skipping the toilet or whatever.
Looks like the believers are late to their own damn sermon.
I'd feel weird.
Come here often.
Wait, we're not skipping this part.
Just one of my little jokes.
Sinners have a great sense of humor.
You must have had quite an idyllic childhood.
Anyway, you know your way around heaven, right?
If you fight green, you will absolutely lose.
I think I figured out what was going on and that's the end of the stream.
Thanks for watching.
I know that a lot of you saying that he's never going to play this game again,
but I think I might disagree with you.
I feel like I'm having fun with this one.
But let's go over the remainder of the week coming up here.
So next time I stream will probably be on Tuesday or Wednesday.
I'm going to do Sorcery Part 4.
And then at some point during the weekend, I'd imagine probably Tuesday.
Tuesday around this time, five or six.
And then this weekend coming up, really going to try to get the Man vs.
Machine stuff going.
So that weekend of the 18th, 19th, 20th, there are other streamers.
I need to make sure everyone can do the same day because I know that some
scheduling conflicts exist somewhere in that Saturday, Sunday.
Really want to if a bunch of the people can't do it that I really want to play
it with and we'll figure it out.
We'll move it around.
But Sorcery Part 4 on Tuesday starting around five or six o'clock at night.
And we'll do MVM that end of the weekend there.
And maybe I'll play this again.
Just kind of hanging out one night.
Yeah, I'm very excited for Man vs.
Machine.
I've not played Man vs.
Machine in a really, really long time.
Getting a bunch of streamer buddies in there should be a lot of fun.
Especially the harder ones because that TF2 Man vs.
Machine, some of those tours are really, really hard.
They don't mess around.
Wave 666.
I don't know about that.
Take care of yourselves.
Thanks for watching.
I'll see you guys on Tuesday for Sorcery Part 4.
Sorcery Enjoyers have been waiting a long time.
So let's feed them to feed the Sorcery 4 Andes.
I told you I wasn't going to wait that long.
We're not going to finish it on Tuesday, but we'll start it.
We take us three or four sessions to do it.
Yeah, take care.
Play viewfinder.
Yeah, I'll find time to throw in just like a chill stream again.
I think most of them are chill streams now.
I like it though.
Having a lot of fun doing this.
I'm back to the basics.
Baldur's Gate 3.
I don't know.
Maybe.
All your streams are evil.
Evil.
Agree.
Evil was capital by the way.
Evil.
Yeah, take care of yourselves.
Have a great weekend.
See you on Tuesday.
Voices of the Void.
What is Voices of the Void?
Is it a new game?
Great game.
Look into it.
And I don't mean that in quotes.
I'm actually going to look into it.
All right guys.
See you later.
Call your mother.
Call your father too.
You know what?
Get everybody in the room and play Monopoly.
When was the last time you played Monopoly?
Play Monopoly.
It's 1 a.m.
They're all asleep.
Call them tomorrow.
All right.
See you guys later.
Goodbye.