Kenshi, so I hope you enjoyed that preload to the stream.
Except I don't think anybody did. Turn on the vocoder, the audio tuner for Kenshi.
Um, I don't even think, I don't think I can even do that. I don't think that's even possible,
guys. That requires, that requires like an audio engineer to be on site. I have to explain to
Kim later what I should probably just do it now. She just heard me through the wall talking
about how I was gonna eat people's bones and like fucking murder them and shit. She's probably like,
is it a bad stream? Oh man, is like chat being mean and he's gonna eat them? Is it really bad?
It's got that bad? Oh, I need, by the way, speaking of loud noises, I gotta turn this back
on. Because my compressor is now off, now it's on. Would you look at that? So now it
shouldn't sound as awful, especially when I get loud. And it should be a little louder.
So loud. Well, I can change that. Don't worry. That's probably better. Is it better? I'm gonna,
I'm gonna go a little loud here. Whoa! That's probably better. Good. It's good. Okay. All right.
All right. So we're taking the frog crew into Kenshi. Welcome back, everybody.
The last, I don't know what any of these mean. Does anybody know what these are?
Working, autosave, quicksave, get the book, l-u-l jubated, can I get away, post attack,
Vegas odds encounter, a new beginning, real timeline. It's just the top one, right? 80,
100 bucks? Oh! Does he remember any of this? No, I don't. Not at all. What happened last time?
I did buy a house last time. The house was purchased. What am I sipping on? It's just
coffee. It's just regular, just right out of the coffee maker coffee, nothing in it. Can you
see? Level one tadpole. But if you're still here and you, and you just wanted to see
a guy act like a dickhead for like an hour, well, welcome. Thanks for sticking around.
This is an interesting, this, hold on. This is an interesting game. This is an example of Speaks,
an audio compressive software. This is an example of Speaks, an audio, you know what I
mean? Like, stay here. The one thing that I have to remember though is, I gotta remember
like the basic controls, because it has been like a week and a half. Put war. War? No. All
right, we got, uh, Chatham, Adam Sandler. Let's give you a reminder of who everybody is.
Frog, uh, Musk, Massamoon, and Canroth. Canroth is currently working on some projects over here,
and everyone's in the right spot, right? 8100 bucks. This is my house that I just bought.
Show Chatham's face. Why is everybody gathering out here? No, wait. Don't do the,
I, what is going on? Why is this guy like mind controlling every single person here?
Is this a bad, oh, it's a bandit. It's a bandit. Why are they just letting him walk around?
I have no idea. All right, so let's take a look at the map. This is the current home.
We need to do, I did an expedition out here with everybody. What do I have for food?
Because that's going to mean a lot. We've got, actually, I got plenty of food here.
What is, uh, okay. So you got all the food. Five dried meats, four food cubes. What is this?
Why do I not just put this on? Who needs armor? Well, Frog was going to stay here,
although I'm going to give the grog to, let's give the grog. I need to trade,
because this thing's worth a lot of fucking money. So let's get that over here.
Oh, I was trying, I was training people in the training dummies. Okay, that's the last
thing that was happening. So we got attack minus four. So this canned roth sucks. Chatham,
Adam Sandler, I believe can still practice, right? Yeah, okay. So you need everybody
to get to like plus five. The dog can't do anything. Frog Musk is just kind of standing
around. I forgot just how fucking ugly everybody was. So I want to do an expedition. I have,
I'm going to bring canned roth and the dog and Frog Musk. No, no, no, no. She's the one
that needs to come with it. She's the one that has any training. Who can just go out
and do something stupid? Frog Musk, maybe she should just go somewhere. This is lockpicking
training. Slaughter the dog. Why would I do something like that? Although I do need to do
this though, because this is kind of low on volume. Okay. Yeah. Unequipped the bags. I need
a storage unit. Defense five plus three. Is there everybody's healthy, right? Well, not really.
I need a bandage you. Let's speed it up. Holy shit. This is taking like a full two days.
Put your camera in the window. Yeah, I could do that. So I'm part, I'm part of the team.
All right. Yeah, we're at a, we're at a boring part of the game right now, but that's
just wait till we get some training. Once there's training, then we can go from there.
I know this is a very polarizing game, but you got, look, I want this is, this was just a chill
stream. I'm just hanging out playing Kenshi. As long as you play GeoGuessr next, I'm good.
What do you do in this game? I'll show you real quick. Oh, by the way, uh, 700,000 games
part two is, uh, is actually, is actually ordered now. So it'll be here. That'll be
what we stream on you Thursday at Friday. In case you're curious. Oh my, is, is this bar
even going up? I'm on times three speed. All right. Yeah. This is not going to work. His
was going to have to happen. All right. So you get off of that. Frog Musk is going to
instead start training on that because that at least level you up once. So you are at,
I got to take the bag off of you. We need a storage unit. Oh, there's so much to do. Okay.
Hold on. Use. Uh, I need to, where is it here? Is it in a build? Okay. Storage, animal
feeder, armor storage box. Oh God. Storage, a storage for copper storage. You have to,
there's a different box for every single material. Shop counter. I just need to,
I need a place to put my boxes. I'm just going to put them on the ground
because I really, what am I supposed to do? I can't, I need to get like materials.
So just put this shit on the ground for now. I'm going to put this on. Oh my God. That's
minus 11. The defense is so bad. I can't even, I can't justify wearing this. I need to just sell
it. All right. So put this down. That puts me at minus two. What happens if I give this to
Frog Musk? No, he's still at minus two. Damn it. What if I put who does anybody in here
even? Can anybody even, okay. With that bag off, nine plus four. She's the only one with any
training. He has to sit here for, everyone has to sit here all day and do this. So
Tana's one. Tana, who has the good weapon? I know one of you does. What happens if I do
this? No. I think, I don't know what to think actually. This is going to take a long time
because it's been, it's very, very clear that if I go out in the, in the wilderness, I'm just
dead. I'm trying to think of the correct solution here as to what I should do because
nobody, everyone's worthless except for her. How much money do I have? I need like another
mercenary. That's not useless. Maybe I should just take her out and just fight and just
get beat up. I don't know because every time I take everybody out, they get their asses
kicked. And then, because who, what's the, what's the, what's toughness? Everybody at three,
ten toughness for the dog. Four, one. She has to go get like, she has to go get beat up and
fight. Let me, where's the, what are the backpacks that I just did on the ground?
Let's just open it up. I'm gonna take them all. Somebody has to be the food carrier
because it really, this is just so bad. But I mean, it doesn't matter anyways.
You're, this person's gonna be the food carrier because this is just a 100% useless
character. Even with the bag off, even with the bag off, this character is totally useless.
So you might as well just carry the fucking food. You need the best armor I can find.
Need med kits too. Well, at least you're at almost level fucking one, minus five.
God damn it. You know, 2020 hindsight, I should have off stream just sat here for
like two hours and just had everybody just get to level five because we kind of,
we have to do this. There really is no other scenario. So how's everybody day to day? You
having a good day? The other scenario is to just have her get beat up outside. All right,
take the dog. Nobody has a job, right? Take, get rid of the jobs. What do you have for a
weapon? You've got, this armor is not that great, but you can at least hurt things. Level
five is still like nothing. Yeah. You can dump like 500 hours in this game and, and still
barely have a character. So there's a lot. I need to find a shitty bandit that the dog
and I can go fight together. So let's take some food. You just train your fucking lock
picking or something because you two guys, the two frogs suck. I got money. I need some food.
We'll just take it from you. You already ate it and go on an expedition. I need some first
aid kits too. Do you have any? You do. I've got one. Take a, take a few of them. I need
to heal because I'm not at full health. Okay. Do I have enough of, I got bandage. I got a
standard first aid kit. I got a splint. I might need another couple of first aid kits.
All right, let's go buy a couple of first aid kits and then I'm going to go and get my
ass kicked. I need a store. That's alt, right? Yeah. Some of the weapons have minus attack.
Yeah. Let's save it. What's a, what's quick save F9? F5. Okay. Let's trade. I got food.
You don't have any first aid kits, do you? Nevermind. I want blood. Well, that's not how
Kenshi works. Kenshi is one of those games where you can't go get blood because actually
you can. It's yours. That falls on the fucking ground. You just die. Well, you want blood.
You're going to see my blood. Do I, who, where can I? Oh, it's been like too long since I played
this to be completely honest with you guys because I just forget where everything is.
I know there's like a medical tent or something, right? Fuck. This might not have been a great
idea. He doesn't want to play. No, I just forgot that I'm at a point with an extreme
amount of downtime. So, Oh, we don't sell anything. I remember hitting this point and
being like, all right. And then now it's like, I have, everyone has to train and shit.
I can't, there is no like run out there and fucking attack. We got to like actually
play it, you know? So that's what I, that's what I'm going to do. I want to just stay
today to be a relaxing day anyway. So I'm okay with it. I just need to remember where
everything is because there's a lot of information in this game. It's really easy
to have it just kind of slip away when you do other shit. So where can I buy
first aid kits? The bar? I've been into like almost every one of these places.
There's got to be like the adventurer's tent or something. I'm trying to remember.
Steal them. Oh, I just wish I fucking remembered where anything was. The
adventurer's tent? Wasn't I just in here? He had six kits. The scale avatar? 61. All
right. Well, I gotta go look because I can't just sit here. My brain right now
is like just turned off for some reason because I just bear with me here. I need
sustenance. All right. Where the fuck am I going? The bars usually have kits,
don't they? At least some of them do. I know there's like a medical tent.
Am I just not seeing it? The shop across from the bed store? Like this
place? Here's the bed store, right? Okay, good. There they are. How did I
miss those the first time? Because they're tiny. All right, that's good. I
don't want to spend that much money. All right, let's go. You two just train. Good
luck. I'm going to take you guys. Let's go. I was already down here. Let's go this
way because that's what like the weird bug people are. I'd rather just go.
Let's try to get like out here. So down this way. We have not seen over
here. Let's go. The reason why I'm taking these two. Oh my god. Sorry.
Is because they're the only ones that really can do anything.
And if anyone wants to get to fight, it's probably should be these two.
Because the other two are kind of useless right now. So they train.
We go. What's this? Can I interact with that? No. Speaking of need to have things done,
you need to bodyguard and follow. And then we turn it on there. All right, let's go.
Match each other's speed. Pick up the cigarette butts. I only just noticed the webcam.
Can you just give me like some shitty dog or some shitty guy walking around?
Remember that wicked shitty guy? That guy just was walking around town and I
kicked the shit out of him like four times. I need just like a one guy standing around.
What's down here? Not much right now. I can see them training over there.
Good. Keep going. I gotta save this game. I'm gonna get fucking collapsed on.
Someone's gonna come from stage left and rip my fucking teeth out.
All right. Looking good so far. Any resources?
That's not a resource, is it? No. Don't mind. No, I don't need to. I have plenty
money right now. I have like $8,000. I'm good for mining. I need to discover a new place.
Well, just did. All right, here we go. Even if they're friendly, I think I'm gonna throw a
sword in somebody's head. I mean, that sounds terrible, but you know, I gotta work in reality
here, you know? I have to fight somebody that sucks. I have to get into a conflict with
somebody that sucks. Anybody in here suck? Anybody in here suck? 59 plus two. Oh my
god, we are such shitties. Welcome. Take a look around. Okay, well, what do you got?
Let's talk. Show me what you got. A crossbow? What does this do? Katana. 120,
27 armor penetration, defense, attack bonus. Damage versus robots. 12 to 24 damage. Should
I get a crossbow? Oh, I forgot. Don't idle. I forgot about that. How much is a crossbow?
1,500? Should we make this character ranged? I feel like that would be helpful.
High. This is a good 16 to 28. Chatham, Madame Sarelin might have to be ranged,
and then what? Build up dexterity, right? Cell value is what you buy it for. Yeah,
so I got, I got, that's 1,500. I think it's worth it. You have no ammo. What can I make?
I got ammo right here. Bolts, right? So that's 11 bolts, and I could probably make them.
It's 6,000. Well, I thought, didn't somebody say it's the cell value? Value 6,000. Oh,
that's how much I sell it to them for. This is six grand. Oh, so that's how much I can sell
it for. One person was trying to fuck with me. It's all right. So, um, steal it is what you,
what the correct answer here is. Time machine. Raw meat. Uh, do you, do you have any to
sitting around? I wonder, okay, you got a chest back here, but I, there's probably nothing,
there would be in here. Weapon cabinet. Condition two. Should I wait till night?
Maybe just wait till it's dark out. All right, a couple people up here. This is some body
guard. These people are all, will kill me instantly, so no, I can't do anything here.
I gotta either buy it or steal food from them. Well, I know there's a crossbow here, so
some guards may fall asleep. That's true. I don't think, I don't think I can do anything
there. I'm just gonna have to keep going. Where's the rest of the party? The rest of
the party is back here, uh, training because they're just, they're just truly awful and
you can get up to five points on a training dummy. I'm going to switch off between them.
Lockpicking is training here, so they're back home. Your characters should get jobs.
Not yet. I need to be, I have to be able to withstand one punch before I go get like a job.
So let's take you guys down here. Let's keep going. I got plenty of food. I got plenty of
first aid and, uh, Madame Sandler has nine plus four, so not totally useless.
Why are you going up the mountain? We want Dr. Phil. No, no, Dr. Phil. Not today. What is this?
It's an iron. No, don't need a mine right now. I'm looking for new places and new people
because there, there's like a bunch of shit down here. I was told last time that down there
is worth looking at, so we're gonna do it. Why are you turning around? What's the frog gang
goal? Uh, to just live, just survive. That's all I can do. Look behind you.
Oh, are you talking? Yeah. Just live. I've walked past a town. Well, there's, I got the town
right next to me. I want to get down into like the swamp area down here. Zoom out and
go back. Well, even if there is like a little town. Yeah, but no, it's. Take a look. Can you
guys hear like the children? I don't know. I don't know what's going on with like the children
I can hear. Uh, this is, what's this town called? The hub. Just hearing things.
Now I'm telling you, I can hear them. I can hear them. Let's go inside here
and I wonder what we can find. Fallout reference.
This game reminds me of Fallout 2. Take away a lot of the dialogue options.
And I guess like the guns, this like feels very Fallout top down ish. All right.
This is a new town. Is there anybody in here? This is still a holy nation outlaws. That
person's by that person's name is sans. In case anybody was curious, a bunch of
rundown, shitty buildings. I can buy this one. Do I buy this shack here? This town
kind of sucks. What's even in this town that's worth doing?
Holy shit. Look at this place. 4,800. This is a big house, but I'm in the real estate is
I don't think it's worth it. There's nothing here to. I'm going to have to rebuild the whole
town. You could make it your own town. I guess. Yeah, that's true. I don't have the money to
rebuild the whole town. Welcome friend. Let's do business. What do you got? More, uh,
more crossbows, bolts, polearm. What's this one? Cutting damage 47, cutting damage 29.
No, I mean, it's plus six attack bonus. This was plus four minus 30% armor penetration
and damage versus animals. That's not bad. Crossbow would be good.
I just, I can't reliably have bolts though. Anybody upstairs? Who are you? Talk to stone.
Need yourself a gunner. I promise you I've got good eyes. Eyes of a hawk been manning turrets
since before I sprouted a beard on my face. The guy doesn't have a beard. Maybe how much?
6,000 cats is all I ask that and a clan to watch my back. I don't have 6,000.
Why is my dog growl? What the fuck is going on? Who are these? Oh, I just thought the
ton was being raided by like mutant taffy. God. All right. I don't even have turrets. Yeah,
forget about that guy. Anybody else? Maybe I should just buy that guy. Does that mean
he comes pre-packaged with good attack? At least good enough. You know what I mean? Does
this guy come with like all the assembly? I just have to build it. That's a lot of money,
but still. Pacifier, bar, thug, drunk. Need some organs. I can get kidneys,
spleens, limbs, whatever you want. All working and tested. Best quality. You're creepy. How do
you test organs? I need to talk to someone over here for a sec. How do you test organs?
Only with the best scientific equipment. That's how I'd give these kidneys to my
own mother if she was still alive. Ocrin, bless her bones. That sounds like bullshit.
Then I get out of my face, stop asking questions. No one's forcing you to buy them.
The fuck is that? All right. Well, I'm going to do something here. I'm going to save.
I don't want to see what this guy's worth. 6,000 cats. Everyone else was three.
That means he's worth it. I want to try, but I just want to see how much- what his attack
points are. He's a scammer. I mean, he's got 11 plus 12. That's not bad to start. 11
plus 12? Everybody that's been free has been shitty. Well, I guess not. He claimed he was
a gunman. Yeah, but maybe I need that. I might need a gunner. Anybody to expand my crew, guys?
All right. Well, this town is- there's nobody here. All right. Hold on a minute. Who are you?
Wait, wait, wait, wait. We got some interactions here. Heft. Had not a city. Need any recruits?
Yeah. Sure, but I'll need 3,000 cats first. Help me out and I'll work off my debt for
you. You're trying to rip me off. I ain't trying to rip you off. Four plus three,
minus four, minus five. You want $3,000? What's up with that? Anybody else in here?
You got to give me something to work with if you want that kind of money.
Any other spot to go? There's like a rum in here or empty rum. Is there any other spot?
Because there's one bar and then- there ain't shit over here. This place is just destroyed.
There's nowhere else I can go. It's just this place right here.
Go into the tower. I guess I'll go in the tower. Somebody's standing out here. Thief boss.
Thief boss. Is this a fence? So you want in on the shinobi. The guards try to lay the crack
down, but they ain't fooling nobody. They're nothing. Nothing. A few cats can. I want to
join the shinobi thieves. Should I- should I be a thief? I think that's what I'm gonna do.
You can join for a fee. That's it. I don't have to complete a test to prove myself or anything.
Do I look like I've got time for handing out busy work? No, this is a business we're running,
not a social club. Just one time membership fee of 10,000 cats. I'm- I- I could-
yeah, the thieves guild. What do you think they're doing to me? They're robbing me
right now. What do I get in return? You get yourself allies. We have hideouts like this
one in lots of major towns. We watch each other's backs. Shinobi thieves stick together. Okay,
worth it. It's a safe haven for you to rest and recover. We have specialist training equipment
to use. You can sell your stolen items to our fence, and they also sell some hard-to-find
specialist equipment at a huge discount. Okay. How you guys doing over here? You ready to go,
like, sell everything you own? We gotta get money, because that's a very- I- allies. I
heard the word allies. This boomer is about to get scammed. I'm not gonna get scammed.
Here you go. Like, I gotta go into, like, a better spot. Is there even- there is no good spot for a
webcam. Because I feel like this is distracting down here. Is this- this is distracting down
here. Top left, but then I'm, like, looking the wrong way. I'm gonna have to, like, spin
this around. See? That's, like, kind of better, isn't it? Yeah, that's too distracting
down there. All right. All right. Now, this is what we- this is what we started. This is
what we- I know. I know a lot of people, you know, maybe- maybe it's about a bunch of
people left. People didn't want to watch this. You know what I mean? It's boring. But, I mean,
some- this is fun, you know? I just- we're just having fun. We're just chilling out.
I know it might not be the most interesting stream we've ever been to, but it's all good.
Sometimes you gotta do one of these. I need to just chill sometimes, you know?
Now I'm, like, fucking- let's go. I was a little, like, concerned at first,
because I thought I was gonna be so lost, but now I'm- I am- I'm found. I have been
found. It just takes a minute to get back into it and get ten thousand dollars to join
the Thieves Guild. See you in two hours. So what are you at? What are you- what's your
attack at right now? Attack is at five. You- that's as much as I'm gonna get.
So you have to stop, Frogmask. You're not gonna get any more points from a basic
training double. We got fucking- we got- we got the Thieves Guild. So you stop,
switch places. Let him train. No, he's not- look at this. He's not gonna go anywhere.
He's hitting a rock right now. You're done. Switch. Because he is at attack two. So you're
gonna get a few more points. While you do that, work on your lockpicking. By the time they get
back- lockpicking eight, yeah, lockpicking's terrible. It's 22 lockpicking. All right,
they're good. They switch places. We are in pain. We need music.
Not to- not right now. Not right now. Is there- actually, there is music in the game,
but I turned off, didn't I? Yeah. Bring the music back from Kenshi. What an awful streamer.
No, don't- just hold on. Everybody just chill, you know? The title of the stream says,
let's chill out. All right, let's- speaking of chill, what are you guys up to here? Okay,
I- I get 7900. There was an iron vein out here. What's going on here? There was an iron-
wait, I actually have- no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Just wait one second here. Somebody- I have
like a huge, expensive piece of armor. Who has it? You do. 1500 to sell this, but this might be
worth keeping to put on. This is also expensive. Sell value 2000. Look at this shit. I could do
it right now. It's too heavy though. Wait, 19. This one is only three. I might hold on to
this one, or this one. Sell it to a fence. Yeah, and I have- I have access to a permanent fence
later, so I guess I'm just gonna do it the old-fashioned way. Let's go get some with- hey,
welcome to the mining stream. I need to mine. Maybe I should take everybody to mine.
Let's see what we got here. Can you make the face cam smaller? Is it too big? Anything,
any veins or anything out here? Whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop, whoop. Who's that? Where are
they? Hungry bandit. Chase this motherfucker down. Oh, you're like a little ant. Don't let
him get away. How can you sprint that fast? You're so hungry, yet you're running this
ridiculous marathon right now. Are we ever gonna catch this guy? He's like Sonic the fucking
hedgehog. Look at how far away we are. Are we- is he- he eventually has to stop and start
walking, right? Nobody can run forever. Am I like in a full sprint? Whoa, he's turning
he just ripped around the other direction. Okay, here we go. Speaking of training, it's time to
kick somebody's ass. Let's go. He's running right back into us. Here we go, here we go,
here we go, here we go, here we go, go, go, go, go. All right, this is what we trained for.
To beat up feeble hungry bandits. Get back here. No, it's- let's go, get over here.
First of all, attack. Dog is set to bodyguard. Yeah, dog is set to- dog to run.
Attack. They're both attacking. How are they gonna even make it there? Oh my god, why?
Why is this guy so fast? And what is this? There's a copper vein right here. It's not worth
it at this point. This dude has 500 trillion stamina. Fuck it. Sorry, I mean I got- I'm
not gonna chase this guy across the whole world. This copper right here, forget it.
Recruit him? I can't even track him down to have a conversation.
Unless he's not- is he like running back? No. That dude- he's just gone. See you later.
Thanks for playing. This is the closest we're ever gonna get to Jerma playing RuneScape.
I'm not gonna- I- I'm not gonna play RuneScape. Uh oh. How much are these worth? 167. I'm
not gonna have enough space because I didn't bring a backpack because I was trying to get
out there and swing at people. Shit. Why are you hungry? I'm not gonna- I did say I wasn't
gonna play Minecraft but then I got shit faced and it- I played it. Don't waste time mining
without a backpack. Yeah, I know. That's probably a bad idea. And I can't even carry
anymore. I have to- I want to fight somebody. Where the hell even am I? I spent- I chased
that guy around. All right, here's the plan. You go back to the hub. Maybe I'll run into
something on the way there. These two, now that they're trained up and now I'm gonna take
them to go mine while we head back. Sell a piece of armor. I need a fence so I gotta take-
Dead. You're dead. You're dead. Hungry bandit. Oh, you're dead. Let's go. Get him. Nice bite.
Beautiful. I mean, you missed but it's okay. Go- Okay, got him. What do you have on you?
Nothing. Martial arts. I forgot- I forgot how fucked up this person was. It's like they're
just running into me. It's like they're just trying to let me- They heard me. Don't let
them get away. Oh my god, they're everywhere. No, they're too fast. This is just a line of them.
Just- Oh my god, hold on. This is too overwhelming. Kill. Just stay here and just
farm them. Get them. This is another- There's another one. Oh, he figured it out. You
deserve to live. You're a smart one. What am I fighting? This is nice. Destroyed. Excellent
work. Pretty good practice I'm getting here. Did I level up anything at all? Combat. Melee
attack. Ooh, almost. What about the dog? Eleven. The dog is fucking strong now.
Anybody have anything? Why would they? They're hungry bandits. That was pretty cool. That was
for free. The dog is finally useful. Feed dog. Dog fed. To all everybody that said,
why don't you just kill the dog? Throw the dog down a cliff. Why are you carrying the dog around?
It's just- Look at that. Eleven melee attack now. Strongest person in the party. Just is.
The dog is the strongest member of our party. Something's already wrong with you.
All right, here we go. Just drip feed us, enemies. Okay, both of you. Hold on. Can I
heal? Enslave, enslave, enslave. How do I do that? Heal the- I don't have- I don't have anything.
Start. Why would I- what? No. You can't. Yeah, I can't. So what is- what is going to
continue our free, uh, our free attack? Bring it on. Level up. It's almost like the
game was listening to me. Because now these two are the fighters. No, don't- dog, don't let
him get away. He does- he's hurt and you can't even catch up to him? This guy has like a broken
leg and I can't even catch him with the dog. He's gonna fight me for a second.
Get over here. I'm closing it. I'm clo- ooh, I cut him off around the corner.
Get it! Ah! Got it. Nice. Okay, good work, dog. Come back here. This is just the bandit
pass. I'm a monster. But am I though? I need to level up. Melee attack six. It leveled up.
Good. That's good, good, good, good, good. Ten plus four. Excellent.
None- they're not gonna have anything. But okay, it's time to sell. Who's dog? Get over here.
Match each other's speed, if you will. All right, I was in the process of moving
somewhere. Where the hell was I going? Back to the hub. Bandits and dog food. Pretty slow,
though. The dog. All right, I don't- I don't want to run into anything. So let's go- let's
check on- nothing over here, right? I'm not gonna get jumped. All right, let's go take a look at
the other two. See how they're doing. Still training. What are you at? Melee attack five,
melee attack five. So not gonna get any more use out of this. They both at five.
But why do you suck so much? Minus five? Is it because he has too much weight on him?
26 out of 43. Is that why you just suck such ass right now? 45 out of 43.
This is too heavy. Let me see if that- is it the weapon? Why do I have this thing on?
What's the point of this? This thing's made of- my maze will be made out of rubber.
I'd like whip it around a fucking socket, people. So this is going away because what the
hell? I need a different weapon. That's not a minus five attack. Just sell this thing.
What a piece of shit. What about you? Minus two attack. Why do I have these even on? I need to
sell- this is gonna get put on. So I'm gonna give this to Sandler because this thing is
actually good. Blunt resistance, cut resistance. It's a standard grade. What's the weight on
this one? Three. This is also blunt. This is- these two- look at this resistance on this,
though. I almost want to put this all on- I'm at a loss. I'm not sure if I should just put this on
everybody. Just have them build up their strength. So this minus five is coming from- it's coming
from the equipment penalty. So this should be five. And then this minus seven is coming from
equipment penalty as well. Equipment penalty. Damn, how bad is the stuff I'm wearing? Have
I just been wearing awful stuff the whole time? Why does my character suck so much?
Combat skill bump. Minus five from the backpack. Somebody just has to be a mule.
Somebody has to be a mule. That's the only way it's possible. And it's gonna have to be
Canroth. Canroth is the item mule. That's just what's gonna happen. So get everything over
here. You just- just put all the items over in your backpack, your body. You're gonna be
worthless anyways having a huge backpack on. So let's see how that changes things.
So you are now still at minus seven from all that shit. You just have a terrible weapon on.
So I just replace your weapon or just take it off. Right? Why- why even have it on? Oh my
goodness. Nine plus eight. This is just weighing his arms down. This dude's arms are just
spaghetti. But they made- there's like razors on them. I'm getting an indoor bonus.
So you- you're the item mule. Speaking of item mules, I need to find a fence because
I'm gonna sell this armor. So let's have a fun job of finding a fence. Put on- hold on,
let me save it. Just in case it crashes or something. All right, oh we got- let's put on-
let's put on something relaxing. Let's fall out too.
Okay. Made sure it was on the right volume. I don't want it to be loud. I just want to
be in the background. Okay, let's go. I put Avril Lavigne on loop or riot. I think you
might be the only person that's gonna riot. If I were to guess. It's gonna be a one-man riot.
All right, let's go find a fence. What's that- why is that here? Go get that. No,
no, forget it. Just go to- go find a fence. I got all this shit to sell.
Find, let's look at a bar. Oh, a forced one-guy riot. What's the percentage to sell this stuff?
27, 27. Fuck this sword, this thing sucks.
Uh, 27 percent. 27 percent. Avril Lavigne deserves it. And Avril Lavigne- don't- just- no.
That's fine, I can buy one of my anti-riot shield. You want me to play the one song that Avril
Lavigne does. You guys understand she- when Avril Lavigne does a concert, she loops two songs.
She gets on the stage and she does, hey you, I want to be your boyfriend,
and then she does, um, I hope you have the time of your life, and then she just repeats them both
17 times. All right, uh, no fence in here. Let's check upstairs. I know I get a fence when I
join. I'm kind of at a weird spot right now because I need a fence to sell the stuff to be
able to get enough money to get a permanent fence, and- but I need 10,000. I don't have 10,000
yet. Where are you guys? Oh look, you made it. All right, sell this couple of copper that I have.
I need a fence. Grab your rocks everybody, don't you even think about it. Don't even think about
picking up a rock right now. Throwing rocks. Everybody wants to throw rocks at me. It's not
fair. All right, let's uh, talk. So I got some copper to sell you. 8300. That's all I have.
What's going on with you? Escaped servant? What do I do about this guy? Can I help this person?
Who's this? Eat him? No, I'm not gonna eat this guy. If I first aid this guy, that's not gonna
do anything for me. Join the thieves? Yeah, I need 10,000, so I'm trying to figure out the
fastest way to make money. See what happens. Where's my first aid? Level up first aid, but then
that's spending money. Wait, wait, wait, wait, hold on. Wait, wait, wait, why is it not leveling
up first aid anymore? Should I leave him now? Oh, it is, okay. All right, so what's this guy-
is this guy gonna be thankful? Give me money? Help me join my team? Splint his injuries?
Uh, I don't- I don't know. His blood has to come back. Oh, how do I- can I give him blood?
Wait, hold on, he's getting up. Stand up. Hold on, I got- I got plenty of first aid left.
Dog, feed, dog, feed, dog, feed, dog. I guess he's just gonna be there for a little while,
whatever. If I hit him on the leg, it'll- I'm not gonna hit him. I don't want to like,
kill the guy. Steal him. I can't. All right, uh, fence. That's what I was doing before.
8300, I need another- get out there now. Who's available? This is free leveling up.
Right when the raid ends, come on. All right, fence. No, you know what? No, you just- you go
in mine. That's what you're gonna do. Just run with all your dumb shit and find a vein and
just sit there and smash on it. Is there any other veins anywhere? Max, the drifter. I can't
fight this guy, so I'm not even going to. I need a vein right there. There's a copper vein
right here. Just sit here for eternity. Yeah, just sit there for eternity. What are you up to?
How you doing? You need- I can't really build much. Show research. Let's see. Book times two
to make a house. Small house. Crafting, defense, walls, field- fuel generator,
training, smithing, hats and headgear, industry, iron plates. No, you get- get your ass out there
and help with the mining. It's right here. This is how I'm gonna make the money. And then
I get the access to the fence. Plenty of backpack space on both of you. It's right here.
Yeah, let's go. We'll check back on you guys in a second. Why do I wear the same three
shirts? Because I only have three shirts. I have Nightwing, Aquaman, and Captain America.
And then a bunch of Star Wars t-shirts. What's going on out here? I have three dress shirts
and four v-necks. Two pairs of jeans, three pairs of slacks, and her sunglasses.
You don't need much. You really don't need much. No, I'm just gonna wait. I'm gonna
wait till I have an opportunity. Can I train anything or do anything? Maybe I can steal.
Steal. You're still hungry? Here, eat like a fucking food cube. Actually, I can't. The dog
can't even come inside. If I drop a food cube on the ground, is the dog gonna eat it?
I- did I just steal that? I don't get it. What? It's- it's- I don't understand why- if
we're in the same party, why can't he eat the food cube? They have cactus rum. That's
pretty cool. All right, how are we doing on the mining? Yeah, it's another mine stream. I
know. I know every Kenshi stream turns into a mine stream, but I need- I need the money.
You know what I mean? It's gone. Sell the armor? I can't- I- wait, hold on. Can't sell
the armor until I can unlock the fence so I can make sure- because I- I gotta run down
and track down a fence. Over there, I gotta check every bar, every location, go to a
different town. They're hard to track down. Sometimes it's just not in the places you
think they're. So, there's a 27% chance that I can sell this to an actual vendor, so I'm
not gonna do that. I'm just gonna save scum for like 30 minutes? No. Just do this, get the money
from the vein, then after this we can get out of here. Sell that stuff, join the thieves'
guild, and then- wreck! You know what I mean? I'm actually in the way of the notifications,
aren't I? You can sell all the- you can sell the items at the hub's bar. They buy stolen
items. Yeah, but also remember, I- I have the items over here, so I have to run these
items all the way down here. There's a vein right outside this town. I mean, let me just-
hold on. I have to bring them down here anyways, so just- I'm gonna sit here for a second.
I'm gonna have these two do something else. I gotta run to the hub anyways? Yeah, well,
let- hold on. Let me at least run to the hub with some copper, because I'm standing right
in front of a vein. That's 80% quality. The thieves' guild actually gives you plus 50%
profits, by the way. Oh, that's awesome to hear. That's amazing. I can't wait to do it.
Let's times three that, and what can you guys do in the meantime over here?
I just want like two stacks of copper, and that's it. There's copper outside the hub.
That's iron. Iron. It's iron. There's copper right here. Okay. All right, all right,
hold on, hold on, hold on. Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, hey. I almost just said something,
so glad I didn't. All right, let's go. Take it over there. Go to the town. Go to the hub.
I need this- we just wait for this last bar to fill, and then we're gonna go from here.
Three, two, one, go. Okay. You guys are done. Run to the hub, but hopefully there's nobody
in the way. I gotta get that before it gets dark. In the meantime, why don't you-
you go out there and just start mining it, because there's two people that can be on it.
Might as well just improve your mining skill while I have you here, Chatham. Where was it back
here? Where was it? It was just kind of up in the corner, wasn't it? Somewhere. Oh,
oh, Jeremy, did you lose your place? What the hell is it right there? That's iron.
Is it right here? There it is. You go mine this now, times 25,000 speed. Bring the dog
to for a company just in case something bad happens. Let me check and make sure you guys
make it not with any impeding factors here, and you guys are far away from each other,
so I have to- what's going on here? You both on sprint, but yeah, you gotta match the speed
together here. Oh, shit. Are those bad? Yeah, stay the fuck away from those. 15 attack,
14 strength, no thanks. All right, match speed. Looks good. I'm gonna get attacked. I know it.
I'm staying with these two because I'm terrified of somebody just popping out of nowhere.
Small iron, not worth stopping. Save this shit. All right, what's- why are we counting?
What's happening? Why are you counting? Streamer gnomes somebody? When did I-
oh, he's gonna sing a dumb song. Okay, speed it up. She's mining down at the copper.
I left Frogmust going to town with the- I know, I left Kandroth going to town with the goods.
He's got them all anyways. What's going on? What- did I miss something here? What did I miss?
I must have missed something. You know what my favorite part about this stream is?
Uh, the fact that- wait, yeah, okay. Does anyone remember what I did like two hours ago?
You guys remember that, right? I almost forgot that I did that shit. All right, time to sell.
Sell at the bar, which is down here. I wish I could forget. I will never forget.
Who are you? Nobody of interest. Sell. It's time to join the guild. We got everybody here
too, so that's good. 9600. Stolen goods, no problem. 1500. 2000. But I wonder if some
of these are worth keeping. Which one of these should I actually keep? This thing's-
Ugh. Somebody could just wear this and be protected. All right, get this out of here.
Because that's- that's faction, right? I don't want anyone to know who I- where I am and who I am.
Faction uniform. Okay, get this out of here. Now here come the letters. I got 10,000, but
let's see. This is one- this way is- this is such a good piece of armor. Put this one on.
This thing is one kilogram and it's got great resistance. I'm putting this one on. Am I gonna
have to go nuclear on this chat? Am I- am I gonna have to go nuclear here?
Buttons on the desk. I could press it right now. I can go- that'll make me do it. Do it,
you coward. So this is a chest piece, right? I think we're good. I want- I want to wear this
stuff because it's very, very good. Do something funny. The holy chest is really bad. Well then,
fine. It's gonna go right now. You ready? Time to buy. Let's go. Actually, everyone
meet up together so we can do this at the same time because there's training dummies in there
and shit. German is as bad as chat making random exclamations. Just trying to keep order. All
right, where is it? Tower. So everybody- everybody meet up over here. No, you stay- you're- hold on
a second. Stay there for a second. Dog can go. Let's get that last piece of copper. Good.
Get to the tower. Let's join the guild. The first time our crew has been together in probably
10 days. No, like three days. Dog is getting hurt. Dog's fine. Where? Dog's all right.
Dog's not getting hurt. Dog's just hungry. Why did you leave him? Leave who? Everybody's fine.
What are you guys on about? I want to make sure we're all here. Where are you going? Oh,
it's because you're on bodyguard, right? Okay. Okay, so kind of an odd route but I'll take it.
Okay. We made it. Here we go. All four of us are here. The four useless dickheads.
I would like to join the guild. Thief boss. I want to join the thieves.
You can join for a fee. 10,000 cats. Can I negotiate? What if I said no? I want to join
and 10,000 is a little steep. You're not a very good thief if you can't afford it.
Done. Welcome brother to the shinobi thieves. Shinobi thieves are now your allies.
That was a lot of money. Wow. Okay, now what do I get? Follow. We can go in. All of us.
Everybody get in. Look it. Who are you? Where are my allies? Guild plastic surgeon. No,
I don't want my face changed. So what do I get for $10,000? A trader. Let's take a look.
What? I have something to trade. Um, hello. Excuse me. Uh, take a look.
Ooh. Stolen goods. No problem. So let me take a look here because this is important.
Minus 50%. Why mine? I thought I thought you guys said I got a plus 50%.
Minus 50? These are actually pretty good. No one said plus. People just said 50.
50 plus taxes. Oh, but there's a discount on everything. All right. Let's I got a
little bit of money. Let's buy some good armor here. Getting rid of this shit, right? I guess
this is all right. This is 16%. 32%. And it's three. It's a chest. This is where does this go
here? Yeah. Okay. I'm going to get rid of this dumb thing because why the hell do I even
have this on? Let's get rid of all this shit except for this. So I'm going to wear this stuff.
Somebody else is going to wear this one. This is a shirt. Only the strongest deserves this.
So what do I want to get for you? 16%, 26%, 800. No, it's 30, 200. No, fuck that too much.
11, 17, 5 kilograms. That's not bad. That's affordable in a way. 16, 24, 4 kilograms. I think
I'm gonna buy this. You're doing a great job idling. Stealth effect. Assassin and melee
attack bonus. Look at that shit. Look at that. Oh, man. 3,200. Look at that attack bonus.
Give it to me. All right. I need to figure out who's going to wear this shit. You are the
strongest. So I think you should wear this all. Let's see. So this is the armor you got right
now. Melee defense plus five. Melee defense plus four. But this is way better in regards to
resistance. Let's see. Let's just see what happens. Boom. 14 plus eight. Total weight.
Oh, you're gonna have to walk around like an idiot though, because it's too heavy.
She has to walk around with this heavy stuff on for a little bit. Acid 40%. How much is this
way? You can take that off for now. Melee defense bonus. You're the mule, so this is
gonna go to frog. Okay, look. What's going on here? Oh, it's gonna go outside. I get it,
okay. I need to be closer. All right. So you're gonna put this on, because total weight. Okay.
12 and a 25. Just go. This is the game. This is what you do. There's nowhere to,
there's nowhere to go. This is where we are. This is game. This is where we are.
So everyone's got good stuff on, except the dog can't really be, can't have anything.
Need to walk around to make it so that build strength with the heavy shit on.
You just suck because you're carrying all the items. Nine plus eight. 14 plus eight.
Let's take a look upstairs. There's a training dummy up there.
I can't, I don't want to steal from the place that I just got accepted to. That would
be a really bad idea, wouldn't it? Let's explore the tower though. Shit, what is this?
Can I use these? Locksmith training box? Locksmith training box two. Oh no.
Training dummy, training dummy, assassination dummy two. MK one, training dummy two.
Fuck. Here we go again. This is so much in here. It's in the top floor. Beds. I can sleep.
Finally. All right. Everybody up here. What are you, what's wrong with you? Get up there.
It's time to train. Only one person at a time. Only one person at a time. So the person that
needs to be there the most. Get there. Do you even have a weapon? What is this? Is this doing
stealth? No. Melee attack. Defense, dodge, martial arts. What is it leveling up here?
Is it just attack or is it assassination? Okay, it's assassination. All right. Nice.
Stealthy knockouts. Chance to successfully kidnap somebody. Chance to break free when
being carried away. Resist knockout. So are there any other training dummies I can use that will
level up the just general skill or no? Well let's do the harder lockpicking then. Or maybe I can't
do that yet. Am I too high already? I might be too high. Let's see. Because my lockpicking's
at 22. I think I'm too high. You can do the better dummies with tech two plus research.
What is this? How about you on this one? No. Okay. He's not too high. All right. Click on it and in
the bottom left is max training. I see. 20. Right. 10. 5. 19. 19 assassination. All right.
Looks like we're all going to be assassins. I need you to go do something because you're
kind of just standing around. We need food. Are we out of food? No. We got a little bit
of food. Who's hungry? The dog's hungry. Everybody's hungry. Everybody wants food.
This has got to go into his backpack. Back into the backpack. Put the food cubes in there.
Who's eating? Everybody except I need the dog to eat. So go down and feed the dog please
while you two keep training. Dog? What? My dog's not allowed in there? That's kind of
bullshit if you ask me. Dog is just eating. Good. So we got strength will go up when the food is
better when he's eating. 9 plus 8. 14 plus 8. I'm kind of getting to be all right. I'm getting
to be worth walking around. So speaking of walking around, how much money do I have?
592. How much food do I have on these two? A couple of food cubes. I still have this.
Let's just put it on. 6 plus 4. At least I have some defense now while they train up there.
Who else? I mean what else can I even do? Let me just check the other spots. I need to know.
I just paid 10 grand. Let's go all the way up. We're at least in the next room.
What's up here? Steal from the assassin league. That's a- I'm not doing that.
This is all the way up. I can sleep. Maybe the dog should sleep. Sounds like a plan.
The dog can't sleep in that bed. The dog can't come in here. Well never mind on that. Front.
Let's just go out. I need more money. So you two. What are you at right now for lockpicking?
What's your skill? Lockpicking 11. So I can do this 10 more times. What are you at
for assassination? Six. You're gonna be here for a while. Good luck. We're both gonna be
here for a little while. In the meantime. What am I gonna do in the meantime? They're
gonna have to trade off. I need money. I need food. Make canned broth. Oh never mind.
I'm not gonna read that one. The two of you just go. They'll be fine. They're not like hungry
yet. Probably should. Is it like a general- is it really that- that's kind of fucked up. Okay.
Twitchy Barthug. I don't like that look in your eyes. Scum sucker you smirking at me.
You got tasty looking eyeballs.
Uh crack your knuckles. I just wanted to buy a drink. I was uh just admiring your sword. That's
all. Uh what's the- what do you got for like attack? I don't want to start a fight here.
What does this guy have for attack? I'm gonna get my ass kicked. Maybe I should.
You got tasty looking eyeballs. 14 plus two. Six plus four. Stay the hell away from me.
The dog's got attack. We could have probably done it. So I need to check over here.
Skip. Oh this guy got up. He actually got up. Wait wait wait. Wait a minute. Hold on. Get over
there. Get this guy. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. Go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go.
Get over to that guy right now. All right. What's the plan here?
Unlock shackles. I'm gonna unlock his shackles. Let's save it. And then maybe will he join me?
I could probably get another party member here. Let's wait till he gets out of sight.
Once we get out of the- is he trying to escape right now? I'm not sure. Are there any guards?
This is a- this is an escape. 90% chance. Well stop moving man. What are you doing?
Got it. Kill. I can't like talk to him? I can't- can I not? I undid his shackles and he's
going back in here. For what reason are you doing this? It's because I have a negative attack value.
Yeah but I- yeah. This guy's good. I can't have this guy in a party or something.
Well whatever. Good luck. Take care of yourself. Have a good- have a nice life.
There's a chance that they'll join you. They aren't assured to. I guess that makes sense.
All right how are we doing up here? Block picking 12 and you are at assassination 9.
What the hell are you two gonna do in the meantime? Can the dog train? I know it doesn't
even matter. Dog can't even train on it because dog can't go in there. All right it's- it's
almost time to go and try to fight. To go on an expedition where the purpose is to get in
a fight. That's- I just need a little bit of- who's malnourished? I need to get a couple
more pieces of food and then we're going outside and I'm gonna just start a fight and just try to
level up. So let's get some food. Does the- is there a trader in here that serves food?
Or is it- does he just do- does he just do clothes? No you just have clothing. Oh well.
Gotta go to the bar for the food. But that's too much money. And then we're gonna go on
an expedition and we're gonna fight. Even if I lose? Good. How much health do I have? Plenty.
Come on down. I have to put on the fight music. Good to see ya. I hate how I have to walk around
in a circle. All right we got dried meat. Take it. Fish. Ah that's- I don't have enough money
for this. I only- I don't- I only have one food cube. I can afford one of these. That's
all I can get. No new- the green fruit doesn't do anything. Steel. I mean that's easier said
than done. This grog that I could take. There's too many people in here. Go upstairs. Anything
up here? No. I mean they're not looking this way. Save it right here just because I might be able
to pull something out of here. What- what's in here? First aid. 51% chance to steal it.
That's bad. All right here we go. Here's food. Stealing chance 53%. It's saved right here,
right? Let's try it. Random furniture. Okay hold on. Okay I got it. What is random furniture?
Displaced in interior wall support beam. Tech level 2. Needs research bench level 2.
I got it. Whatever the hell it is. Well I got one piece of food.
It's not going to do very much for me though. We might have to actually go to one of the
other smaller towns and just try to steal all this stuff. Yeah I got enough food to last
at least one small expedition to the next town. That's a lot of resident sleepers.
I missed a free recruit in this bar. And why am I still sneaking? Stand up.
Free recruit. This guy's not free. 6,000 cats. Please get him. Yes he is free. Who?
Free? Oh I just got baited. All right that's funny funny funny funny funny.
All right let's go. We're at a level where I can at least do something. So we've got
14 plus 8. 11. Negative 8 and 1. Find hobs. Hobs. Find hobs. I don't see a hobs. I see hungry.
This is a holy citizen. Hobs.
Yes that's it. Have a drink on me. Say have you ever heard of the story of the wailing phantom?
No. What's it about? Well legend has it it dwells in a sunken cave south of the outlands.
Are here it has bones made of solid diamond. Just one tooth would fetch you kabillions,
no poobillions of cats. It has the gigantic tongue of a lusty tree hag and a marvelous
pair of bingo wings that droop like smooth potato butter. Some even say that it has the snout of
fondled truffle. Even the most handsomest of man warriors haven't been able to hunt the peppery
thing down. What is this? Wow this is a strange way to talk. That sounds amazing. How do I find
it? If I knew that I would have tracked it down myself but if you're going to head out
in search of it you must take me with you. Call it an old man's dying wish. Then I will
grant you your wish. Join us in search of the beast. New party member except this one's just
a this is a regular this is a regular guy. What do you have for items? 7 plus 4 go to plastic
surgery. Take him to the thieves guild for plastic surgery. Oh yeah all right that sounds
fun. New party member good. Now you know now somebody can die right? I won't feel that bad.
Where's the plastic surgeon? What the hell are you? All right Hobbs.
There's the traitor. The plastic surgeon was sitting here before.
Plastic surgeon where are you? There you are. Need your face changed. Yes tell me. Here we go.
Okay name. I gotta change the name too. So much for normal. Why does everybody have to
have this? That hurts. That just hurt my back doing that. All right we got it. Let's do
small chest. Oh what happened over here? What's this? How's that chest? Slender man.
It's just just a kingdom hearts character now. No that's fine. I think that's all right.
They all have this. Can one of my characters not have this? They all have the horizontal
neck. Every one of them. Every single one of them. Oh my god what the hell am I doing?
Not bad. It's another doctor house. It's doctor house again. Every character I make is doctor
house and then I make it somebody else afterwards. It looks good. All right I like that.
Looks all right. This is one of Roger's characters from American death. That's bad.
No no mohawk. Oh that's bad too. It kind of has to be Roger. In fact I think I have to go back
and make just make him Roger. Please don't go for the low-hanging fruit. No no
youtuber hair. Just regular. That's fine. I'm gonna do beard. No. Why why does it look like
you? It shouldn't. All right that does not look like me. Give me a break. You think this
looks like me? It fucking kind of does a little bit. I like the no beard though. No mustache,
no beard, none of them. All right looks fine. We're done. Name. Decrease the height.
This is like a that's like a Roger name. That's me part of his gold standard. Right.
That would that would be oh you can't even see the name. That's a Roger persona name right.
Take off the hat. I will. Give him the Roger proportions. I can't just do make Roger.
Let's just see what it looks like. Perfect music.
Taller. There. There you go. Barnabas gold standard. One of Roger from American Dance personas.
Look at this down here. 15 plus 12. Where did that come from? I have 85 cents. What do you have
for attack? Seven. All right. Field medic six five minus two lockpicking. Terrible. Melee
attack seven. Defense six. Uh you're gonna. Excuse me. Barnabas you need to go over here.
Keep him unarmed. You better believe it. Why is this training going down?
I had to give negative to go positive. Okay. I guess so. Where are you at? Looking good.
12 assassination. If you are in stealth mode you can sneak behind people and knock them
out. This skill determines how long they stay unconscious for. Good. I hate all these
motherfuckers. The dog's probably the only one that I actually like. They're all so fucking bad.
Madame Chatham is actually not bad either. All right we have our designated mule. If you
kidnap somebody you can practice assassination on them forever. Yeah but that's mean.
This is free. All right here we go. I think it's time to get going. We got a team here
and what was the super secret treasure area? What what that guy was talking about something right?
What was where was that? Didn't he say that there was some magical Brazilian treasure?
Somewhere in the middle? Like here? I gotta turn the camera off for a second.
Oh I can't even never mind I can't even turn the camera off. Well that's a good song.
Uh I don't know a good song. Time for a sneeze. All right um is this even doing
anything for you? Plus six perception I guess. All right I don't want to run out of food.
Everybody let's go. Forget about your training. You're good enough. It's time to figure it out
where we're gonna go. We are playing Fallout now apparently. Where the hell is everybody?
Uh guys they're all Roger personas. Let me stand let me put them all next to each other.
And
where's the dog?
Where's the dog? There you go. There they are. No look it's a Roger persona. Oh look another
Roger persona. Hey look it's me it's me Roger. All right time for them all to die. Save it.
I don't know how many will die but who wait we still have I can hold on a minute let's go
together. No you just stop sprinting everywhere. Match each other's speed. What have you done?
I gotta sell. I have and then buy a couple of pieces of food. Fitting music. Yeah Fallout 2
it has a great soundtrack. It does. This is really good. All right sell the last little
bits of things that I could sell. Looking to buy. Yes that's trade. One at a time please.
All right I have. Keep this. I'm kind of I need I gotta buy some food. Bang bang bang.
Put this back on. I got plenty of healing. Let's give that to you because uh who had that you?
As long as the frog stays alive he'll have all the medical. He's just the mule. He's here just to
carry items and shit. Anybody else have any items? We're ready. I got 580 bucks. Let's do
a little bit of business. I got some I got plenty of heals. I got food's not that great but
I could buy one of these and that's a huge amount of nutrition or I could get two.
Just get this. Yeah I'm getting it. Nutrition. Here we go. Let's move out everybody. Oh I
remember this one. Butcher butcher butcher. Oh right. Time for the crew to do something.
Ben how long has it been? Two hours? Let's go. Let's go right to the middle. Everyone's fed.
Everyone's ready to go. Save it again. If I see a group of bandits
I'm going after them. I'm going to tear their skulls off. Sounds like me singing. We already
heard that earlier and it was not it was not good at all. Speed it up. What if I just
jubate you guys so hard and all of them just go mine and I just walk away from the computer.
Why are you jumping off the cliff here? This is not where are you going? Where are you going?
Meet up over here please. River the dog. How's everybody doing? Food food. Some people need to
eat here. Dust storm. Can somebody I need to give food. I I got food here. Why are you
guys not eating this? I guess you are. Let's move fast. This music actually works here.
Just check your surroundings every once in a while. I'm not going to walk into like a mutant
and loading in something. It's a long way. Long way to go. Dust boss. How to get in his aspect.
Two starving bandits. Why don't we go help? He can be spoken to. Let's go help him up.
All right let's go troop. Come on hurry up faster. All right let's go you.
Attack you. Attack you. No you you you shut up and stay over here. You don't do anything.
Actually no yeah yeah you attack. Attack target. Attack target. Attack target right here.
You go for this one. You go for this one. Yep attack and let's go. He just he just cleave.
Get him. Wait did the dust boss die? Hold on a second here. Why is this guy fighting me?
Get him. Somebody hit him. Can somebody please. This guy's just baseball swinging the back of
my head. He's blocking everything. Get him. Just collapse on him. He's almost done. Chest.
Knock him out. Come on. Yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah yeah. Turn wait hold on.
Turn your attention. What do we got here? Dust bandit. Dust bandit. Why they were just
fighting each other. Who's hurt? Oh fuck you're really hurt. All right you gotta get back.
Canned Roth. Go down here. Go away. Like where can I put you? Over here.
Massamune is still fine. Collapse on. Frog musk is dead. Uh unconscious. Bleeding. Attack.
Bleeding. Attack. Go. Nice. Nice double tap. Get it again. No shit. Oh fuck. Shit.
Left arm. Bleeding. Still all right. This might be winnable. It might be. Barnabas is
doing good. This guy's eight minus five. Tons of defense though. Where are you at? You're
okay. Attack this one. This guy needs one hit or so and he's done. Get him. Nice. The dog is
oh. Oh Terminator. Eat the dog. Eat the dog. Got it. Pause. Best character in the fucking game.
Game. Here we go. Last one here. That's it right? Oh shit. No you dead? I gotta get out of here.
I have to get the fuck out of here after this guy goes down. Can we collapse upon him?
Gonna go for it. Go. Got it. Come on. Come on. Good. Two hits. Nice dog. A couple more hits
and we can get the fuck out of here. Beautiful. That's it. That's it. That's it. That's it.
One more. One more. One more. Come on. Stay up. Stay up. Who has medkits? That's really important.
I'm gonna do it. I'm gonna save something here just because.
Oh my god. That guy's got a hundred dollars. Hold on a second. We just
gave a hundred fucking dollars. Uh Kvas gave a hundred bucks. Oh my lord. Thank you Kvas for
the hundred dollars. Oh my god I fucking bought these kind of on accident because twitch said
the purchase failed. But oh well. Uh love you Jerma you're still my favorite. My dog passed
away today but as long as I got you I'm good. Uh Nickelodeon. Way I got that slime. Slat.
I'm Nickelodeon. Uh I'm sorry that's terrible to hear. Sorry about your dog. That sucks. It's
always hard and there's no real easy way to deal with it. You just kind of have to. So
I'm terribly fucking sorry to hear that. But thank you for the accidental hundred dollars.
That's a that's a big that's a big money accident. Thank you so much for real. Thank
you. Can I get some Nickelodeon splats? Uh what's the what's the Nickelodeon reference?
I need to I need to be very cautious with this because I have
med kits. I got two bodies two bodies in the ground. Two able bodies to carry them. That's
the first time I've ever had like a successful battle and it feels great. It feels actually
fucking great. All right let's get uh Nickelodeon. That just sounded like Nickelodeon.
This is a we're in Fallout 4. This is a Fallout 4 soundtrack. Uh let's just uh whoops.
I kind of don't want this to get claimed though. This did that if I keep playing these these
are claimable songs I think. Are they? I'm not even sure anymore. Loot the enemies? Oh no
I'm going to don't worry. New Vegas. I'll put on the New Vegas soundtrack in the background
here. You can just hang out there. All right wait hold on. Okay everyone's fine.
So let's I need to assess the situation here. Unconscious. Bleeding. Almost dead. Um
conscious but need of attention. Unconscious. Almost dead. Wounded. Arms almost gone.
Wounded but you're okay. So we gotta we gotta deal with the the critical injuries here first.
So who has decent first aid among you? Field medic six, five, ten. How does a dog have uh field
medic four? How does a dog have ten field medic? Turn the music down a little bit.
That's better. So how's the dog a field medic? That's kind of strange.
Dr. Dog is on the case. Uh I don't the dog can't have. Let me just see. I keep panicking here.
Now the dog cannot heal anybody. So frog musk needs to be healed so it means
we're gonna take Barnabus as the highest of the two that can carry anything.
Yeah so Barnabus needs those med packs. So go get them. You two stop running that way.
Stay. Oh my god where are you going? We gotta run. Get off. This guy's shooting a crossbow.
He is. I'm gonna have to pick people up. This guy's still alive too. Okay here's the plan.
You got nothing on you of value. Holy shit that thing's actually kind of good.
Just go into melee. I saved it right but they're all so hurt. I'm I if I get hit
once with an arrow I'm fucking dead. I saved it though. I had it saved. Let's go. One
down. Oh my god there's so many. There are so many. There's like three more in the trees.
I gotta have faith. Oh my goodness. 18 precision crossbow. Junk bow. What is this?
Armored rag. Standard grade. Wow that's kind of good. 24 39. It's heavy but take it.
What about the boots? Too heavy. Give me the bolts too. All right I gotta get out of here.
They're ranged. I think I can outrun them. Where is the boss? Dust bandit. Where's the dust
boss? Because dust boss. I got a feeling this guy might have something on him.
So we're going to run. We're gonna go to the dust boss. Pick up the two and book it.
Oh shit his leg is broken. Another one of these. Oh that's good too. Don't I can't get
overburdened on this. Who is this? Who has this? This is Chatham. He's overburdened.
Fuck. Let's get out of here. I can't risk it. I just gotta. Okay how are you doing?
Pick up. Frog musk is your task. Your task is pick up can bro. Pick up.
Go. I can't carry anyone with this arm. Oh shit. How many are following me? Three. It's
very possible that I can't kill them. Look at my guys. I can't even hold a sword.
These guys are not. Look at the attack. 16. Crossbow is 18. I'm fucked. 15. Attack 13.
How are they doing right now? Unconscious. He's gonna get up.
All right we're just gonna have to we're just gonna have to try to get out of here.
Just try to get out. I need a town. Holy military base.
Holy shit he's alive. Okay hold on. Frog musk is currently alive.
Is there a button I have to press to have him play dead? Or this just is him sneaking play dead?
He does it automatically. Okay just don't move him. This is so stressful. I just I I took
so much beating and I leveled up probably like three times. Why does this keep getting
unchecked? Oh he just took a fucking shot right in the head. Sacrifices to get away.
Frog musk. No get frog musk. Can you run? He's I think he can run. Go go go go go go go go go.
All right we need a location. Holy military base or try to run back to the hub. I don't
know what to do. I don't know what I don't know what the safe option here is. Everybody
just try to get back to the hub. Good luck go. Oh Barnabas. Miss miss. Yes I think we
did it. I think we did it. I think we did it. They're not chasing. Get out of there. Okay
meet up over here. They're not chasing. Holy shit. Okay we need to have like a heal party.
They're not chasing. Are they? I mean is this guy? They're coming this way. We gotta keep
moving. Yeah they're coming this way. We gotta go. We gotta get out of here. Now
out through the little. We can't stop yet and here comes another troop.
Those are slavers. Those are slavers and we got out right at the perfect time.
Damn they're coming down this way. Meet in the middle. I gotta splint that leg. Fuck oh we
gotta get out of here. I'm gonna save it right here. Should I hide? What if I like what if I
hide over here? No no no we were so close. We were so close to getting out of there.
Come on. Put him down. He has all the health packs. He's the motherfucker in the road that
has the health packs. What if they don't? Okay hold on. What if can I just be a dead guy in the
road? They might not see me. All right nobody fucking move. You gotta be fucking kidding me.
Oh you slow motherfucker. What what's going on? Why are they running this way? That guy died.
Free. They're going that way. All right let's go. Let's go. Save. Wait is he gonna get
that? He's gonna stand up. Go chop that guy's fucking head off. Okay here we go.
Save this shit right now. No no you I need to give these to you. He's the healer. They actually
they both can do it at the same time. Got splints. Okay I'm out of food too. So you
Barnabas take care of Candroff. Madam you need to heal Frogmusk.
Um oh okay hit play. Okay how many what do you got? I need a couple of these. All right
who's okay we got leg head. Okay he's not dying anymore. Dog is okay. Left arm. You gotta splint
that shit don't you? First aid. Pick up first aid. Go over here to Frogmusk. All right you
gotta get everyone stop sneaking now. First aid. Heal that arm first. You're gonna be
fucking useless without it. How do I heal that arm? Splint the arm. Do I not have any
more splints? Bottom right. Medic. First thing splint will order your selected characters to
automatically heal everyone in the squad. Okay no no but that wouldn't that I need to heal myself.
Why can I not splint my own injury? Is it splinted? The wound is getting worse.
Doesn't have a little bar that goes up when it's splinted. Jesus christ. Just heal.
Candroff is okay now. Can I do that to you? Splint injuries. Let's actually get me to a
safe place before any more of this shit's going on. Pick up. Get over here. This is just a bad
place to be standing. Just medic. Just press this button and that's it. Heal her arm. I'm trying.
I don't understand. What do you what do you mean? I can't when I do first aid she just stands
there. First aid. It's what where where is the first aid happening right now? Because you're in
the negatives. And now I'm fucked. So I have to move again. I quick saved it before all this
happened. I mean this these guys are all terrible but are they terrible enough? No I don't I'm
gonna get destroyed here. I mean we can see how this plays out. Oh no I'm getting my ass
kicked. This is too many of them. No that's not gonna happen. All right first of all you
gotta put him down. How's everybody? The arm is gone. The arm is gone. What? Wait wait what?
Hold on. All right let me I need to get this straight because this this is like
very confusing. You have to have a med pack. Do you have to have a splint kit to splint
your arm and if you'll just it'll just do it automatically if you press like the medic
button down here. Like there's so many different moving pieces here. So just click
the medic button and they'll just do it. You don't need it. It's just a med kit. It's only
visible if it's not negative. Medic has it heal everyone. Well let's just go back there.
It was in the negative and that's why it wasn't showing. Well I mean like that how
to hell am I supposed to know that? Just just use first aid and just wait. All right
this is where we left off before. I need to just I have to get out of this place because
there's just so many different opportunities for people to come over here. Nobody's here now
but they will be. So we need to go back to where we were. Let's select everybody.
No more sneaking. Get the fuck over here. You. Trade. Get the first aid off of him.
You want it in here. Give one to Barnabas as well. Okay now I'm just gonna I'm just
gonna press the medic button because that'll just heal everybody in the squad or does it
just happen? Is that correct? Right? That is right. So just medic. Medic. But no first
heal myself because my arm. So heal first aid. Let's go. You're on just medic job right?
You're up here. Wait where are you? Nobody coming. All right heal. Get that arm healed.
Okay that's what the problem was because it was so it was apparently so negative that I couldn't
even see it. That's why I was panicking. I could get a robot arm. I could. You're right.
All right just check. Make sure there's no bandits or people running over here to come
get me. They're not so this should be fine. All right now medic how you doing over here?
Good. Grand. Wonderful. Minus 10,000 it's too negative. Almost time to get out of here.
Good. Good. Come on. Come on. Okay why would you say that? I thought he was a bad guy.
Frog musk is now in recovery coma. How about yourself? How about the dog? The dog needs
healing too. Heal dog. Holy shit who are these people? Oh it's just a bunch of goats thank
god. Let's get out of here. All right out. Pick up you. You pick up Roth. You pick up
frog. Let's get the fuck out of here. I can't. Shit. How the hell am I gonna transport anybody?
You're gonna you have to pick him up. We gotta get off the road. We're gonna get out of here.
Someplace safe. I need like a shelter or something. Just I know I'm gonna splint but
I just gotta get off the road. I know it didn't matter last time but just so far away here.
Okay splint. I need you to splint. Okay I've splinted.
Uh doesn't look like it. That does not look like it's splinted. It is though.
Hydrate. It's too negative for sprint uh splint to work. Okay can you pick up?
I can't carry with this arm. The dog can't do it either.
When are you gonna get? When are you gonna get up? Can you carry two people?
No you can't carry two people can you? We gotta get we have to move.
Sorry frogmust. We'll come back for you. He'll be safe. He'll be safe right? Don't go back to
the hub. Wait why not? That's that's like the safest place. Hold on. Food? I don't he
don't think he has any food on him. He was pretty empty wasn't he? I mean he has items but
should I take the items off of him? That sounds like a bad idea.
Okay he is plenty his food is okay. He's at 272. He'll be all right. Yeah he's fine.
Yeah he doesn't have any food on him or anything. So this is the reason to really I can't really
do much to him. He'll be all right over here. He'll be fine. I need to go rest up at the hub.
Let's go. First of all let me quick save this. We're gonna move pretty slowly because I
have to carry. I should really move together just in case something bad happens. Oh this
sucks. This is so bad. They have to move so slow. I can't leave him behind and your arm
is doesn't work. You got nothing on you. It's worth taking. Go to the way station.
Yeah but I mean I don't know what's here. This is I I paid 10 grand to be able to come
back here and use this place. I'm just gonna walk in here and be like hey hi guys. It's
neutral. No I mean I got beds here. I'm going back here. Even if the way station is safe I got
beds and I got food and shit that's there. And it's they're both I would say they're pretty
much this is like maybe a small the distance is not a big deal. The guild is in other cities.
Yeah that's not a guarantee for me right now. They're in every town. Yeah but I mean I mean
am I just getting like spoiled back seated here? Should I just go down to way station
and just because that's where I need to go? What do you want me to say? I wouldn't know that.
You all just told me. Like you what? I'm just I'm going to the hub. No hub. That's where
we're going. Don't eat the raspberries. It's right here. Speed it up. Here comes a meltdown.
No it's not a meltdown but like I I don't like know what this is. So if I had stumbled across
this place and I'm like no that's not safe but if you know it's safe you know what I mean? I
don't know it's there. It's a trading place. Well that's that's great. I'm sure I'll see it
again real soon. Let's go. I'm like right there anyways. It's not a big deal. Yeah and
why would I trust chat anyways? I can count on 25 fingers and toes the amount of times
that people have told me to do something and it turns out to be the thing I should I absolutely
should not have done. How am I supposed to know what's real? All right frog must just got up
and can you walk? They're not coming over to me right? I had nothing to do with this. Jesus
Christ. All right let's meet up. You guys can walk. He'll make it and we'll go. Turn on
Yakety Sax. Actually I'm just gonna wait for him. That's the right thing to do. He's
right here and he's right he's like full sprinting so he's fine. Actually it's probably
ah no no no just just get there safe. All of you. Goats just saved my life. They probably did.
They probably did. Now it's the right thing to do. Well if he can move then yeah it's the
right thing to do. He made it. Good job frog musk. Good work. Uh we're there. We'll go in
there dude. What are you doing? Hello. That's because it's lagging away. I don't want it's
gonna crash the game. It's loading the town. There we go. On your way in. How do I like the game? I
found it hard to get into. What start did I use? I did the dog wanderer. The game is incredibly
hard to get into. It uh it asks a lot of the player because you just start out at zero and
you're terrible and everything's terrible. But I think that it's a lot of fun. I think that
it is a lot. This is a great game here if you have the patience for it. I think it's
good. I did do yeah I did start with slave. That's right. But I didn't finish on slave.
If you're into hardcore RPGs it's great. And then that's the thing I'm I'm not really at all.
I'm actually really not into hardcore super hard death patience kind of RPG games. But
something of this one's just doing it for me for some reason. So I don't know what that
means but it's fun. So uh you're safe. Save it. I'll save it when I get in the town
because I have an auto save that just happened a few minutes ago. So it's because it's goofy. It
is kind of goofy but it's in a charming kind of way. What is this? Copper. Don't want it.
And then from here I'm gonna go I want to go the way that I wanted to go in the first place
which is kind of like down here. So we'll see. I've ever played enter the gungeon. I have.
I streamed it once. I didn't really play it that much afterwards.
Probably the freeform sandbox is better for your play style.
Yeah because you kind of just get to do whatever you want. You just kind of get to do whatever
the hell you want. And that could be anything. It could be whatever the hell you want.
You want to eat food and just sit by fire and tell ghost stories? Go for it.
You want to go get your ass kicked by a group of bandits? Sure.
There's no nobody tells you what direction to go. But you better go to the way station
Is that how you think we sound? No I was making a funny comedy joke.
Actually it's been a while. I should probably take a second to get a drink.
Fill up my cup. Play mountain blade. Okay is mountain blade. Would I like mountain blade if
I liked this game? Would I? I know a lot of people have wanted me to play that for a long
time. Would I have fun in mountain blade? It's not really the same. Yes but yes. Maybe
I'll try it one day. But I can see my voice is getting a little so I'll be right back.
Don't go. Oh they didn't even turn up my webcam. But that didn't work either. Okay see you in a
second. What's the noise? I've got the fallout soundtrack. Wait no yeah this is New Vegas.
Oh shit my house is on fire. Ah crack it up with a cold one. All right where were we?
No there I am. All right we've made it. We've made it to the town. I got a coke. They're
just easy. This is not an endorsement. All right everybody is normal hungry. I need food.
Did I get anything to sell? Let me take a look at the toughness and shit. So five toughness.
That's good. Everybody kind of got hit. Twelve toughness. Six. Four. Five. At least they're
not at zero or one anymore. Coke? They're easy. Yeah they are. They're pretty easy.
So let's go sleep in the beds that I have up here. Everybody move. What a Pepsi show. I
actually don't like Pepsi. I think Pepsi is like I'd rather have a Coke than a Pepsi. But
I'm not one of those people that will refuse a Pepsi. They're pretty much the same damn thing.
So I gotta go all the way up huh? Everybody go rest. The thing is the dog can't rest up there
can he? Unfortunately. That's a very controversial statement. I don't think so. I don't think it's
that controversial. All right. Frog musk. Get in bed. Everybody get in bed. Am I still carrying
canned rothy? I am. Pogchamp. Dog can rest. Is dog allowed somewhere else? Because the dog
can't go in this building. Where can I put the dog to sleep? Just carry the dog in.
Oh whoever's last standing here. All right. Madam you go to bed over here.
Put down Woods' space. Can roth get in that bed and pick up the dog.
Come on up. Well the dog is allowed up here. Well look at that. Dog not sleeping. I guess
dog is not sleeping. Well he's pretty much in bed. How's everybody doing? We just have to
rest here for like a full day probably. Pick him up and put him in bed from carry. Does
that actually do anything? That's weird. Okay. Well they're all sleeping. Welcome to the rest
of the stream. All right. Fastboard. I need food. Oh man we're going to be in here for
a little while. There's some actual regular beds. A floor or two down. Is this more
comfortable? Bed versus camp bed. I guess so. So how many there? Three? No there's
enough. You get in that one. You get in that one. You get in that one. It's times eight
versus times four. Is there any more? No it's just those three. So everyone is in bed.
Uh you. What the fuck is this camera doing? Good luck. Well now we do. We don't we all
of our party members are in trouble so just keep them here. We'll switch off the beds too.
Everyone in Germany embarrassed themselves singing. What a mess. That stream didn't even
happen. What an odds beginning to the stream that was. Play Oregon Trail? It's kind of what
I'm doing. Isn't that like a version of sort of what I'm doing right now in a way. All right
almost at full head. We need food. Bad. Uh Kenroth's almost completely fine. Dog is completely
fine. Madam Shatam is. Yeah Madam Shatam needs to be moved to one of the more comfortable
beds. So wait till you're all at 100 and there we go. So let's just go down now.
Swap beds please with really anybody. Just get up. You get in this one. All right we've lived
to tell another tale. 14 plus 12. 16 plus 8. 10 plus 8. 8 plus 4 and 13. Hungry. That's
almost just all fell out of my mouth. I don't know why. I like went like and the whole thing
just almost came out. So I don't have any money and I have no supplies except perhaps
a couple things I could probably sell. Not really though. Uh you're gonna be there for
a little while so everybody else get up. The three of you need to go mine. Yeah I need some
miners. Can you not get out of bed? The dog can't get out of bed. Everybody out. Why are you
sneaking? So get off a sneak. Put the dog down now. Who's sneaking? All right mine. I need some
ore. I need. I could do iron too. Copper. Is this this is iron right? Yeah. Where's the
copper? It's over here somewhere. On the side. Small copper. Small. There's two small
coppers but wasn't there a bigger one? I swear there was a bigger maybe. Is it gone? Did they
did they despawn after a while? Iron. That's iron too. Uh I guess there are there are two
over here. Only two people can mine these though. I could go. Oh what's this? It's iron.
Shit. Really? Hmm. I guess we're gonna go one two and then how many people can
fit on this one? Three. So we're gonna have who has the best mining skill right now?
Use prospect. I mean this is in those two spots that I saw and then down here. Oh yeah. Copper
iron. This one's this one's a lot farther away though isn't it?
Not really. All right who's got the good prospecting? Everybody can just get it. So
we got one two three four. That'll work out. Who has the best skill? That's the question.
Got laboring five, laboring 18, laboring 28, laboring 52. You can get over there.
The two the two strongest should be on the one that both of them can go right?
Because then they'll just power through it and then you other two are this way. One here.
Yeah right here and then your arm is almost better so you can do it.
We're just gonna have copper going and the dog can run in a circle.
You need to nuke the chat. All right you're good. Get up. Go mine. How's everybody doing?
We good? Making your way over there? Start the mining. Good. They're already doing it over there.
Out you go. Time to make some money. Chat is awfully quiet for Kenshi. No back seating?
Oh I had a reprimand moment. I said excuse me. Excuse me. And everybody went
that face that go to the way station now. How long is it gonna take you to get one? Long time.
Well uh it is kind of a joke but it's not. Welcome uh welcome to the next view a little
bit of the stream here. This is this is Nightcrawler. This is this is Nightwing.
This is a Nightwing shirt. Boomer comic? Nightwing? They're like bringing Nightwing
into mainstream now. A Boomer comic. Oh my god can you believe it? Boomer comic. How dare you?
How double dog dare you? I'm gonna make 50 fucking thousand. I kind of need to have a lot
of bullshit in my inventory. It's all right it'll be enough. Zoomers burn. Zoomer. I can only get
two more. How you doing over here? I think it's time for you to one two two more for you.
You guys can stay here all day for all I care especially because I can stack.
Oh yeah at least canned Roth is gonna stay. I still haven't turned up the music.
What the what the what the
Let's see. How about uh fun time? Shovel Knight. What on the dwarf mining music?
How about something simple? Iron Forge. No that'll be annoying after a few minutes.
No no no no ST. I'm going musicless for a little bit. It's almost we're almost done here anyways.
Is that near me at all? Kind of. It's okay. What are you two doing? Get to work. What are you
doing? He just paused. I apologize. Dog is hungry. You can get one more. Uh oh damn it.
Just fill it up with five. This hat's worth like a cent. Just like I'm fine. Can't arrange
this any better. Are you sure? I guess not. No I'll just get it to five. I can come back and
grab it. So you go back to town. Go hang out with Masamune and then you are probably done
here. Yes you are. Same deal this thing is worth like two cents. Just get rid of it.
Take this last one and arrange and now you go back to town too. That leaves just the two
of you. So frog go back to town. Keep working. Keep working. I'm gonna have him fill his entire
bag. What is the goal of this game? There is none. The goal of the game is to do whatever
you want. Whatever you want. You can buy up stuff. Make money. Build a town. Have a shit.
What's wrong with Masamune? Oh hungry. You could just go fight. Steal. Attack. Kill. Kind
of whatever you want and I just itched my head and there was like something in my hair.
I don't know if it's a bug or not but I might have a scream panic moment right now because
there's a bug in my fucking hair. That was weird. That was a weird feeling.
It's not lice. I wash my hair all the time. At least twice a year so it's not that.
Sell. Who is this? I don't want to sell to this person do I?
Because does this person have a 50% discount? Yeah I know. Sell to the bartender. Don't sell
to this guy. Where's that fucking bar? Over here. How can you only wash twice a year with
all the product? What the fuck happened over there? All right you back. You back. You back
here. You back here. All of you. Sell. You have a lot of things to sell. How you doing?
You guys are all going the weirdest possible way. Why would you run all this way?
Where the hell are you going? You can't just walk across the town like a normal person?
Bar thug. Got a problem. Take it somewhere else. Pacifier. Everybody need help with
some things over the hounds okay. Twitch bar thug. This is a chat member.
You got a problem? Runt. The hell do you want? I was just curious. I'm just like playing the
game and I'm gonna go like to the hub. Idiot. What are you stupid? I'm just admiring your
sword. I just think you look great today. I would like to buy you a drink. Make it grog.
A cold one. Oh this is embarrassing. I don't have enough money. What are you fucking stupid?
Show me you goods. Yeah sell. Sell. Sell. Back to even. Just eat this because you're gonna eat it
right now anyways. All right. Who else has got stuff? You do. Go on in. Oh I forgot. This is my
this is my character. Show me what you got. Yep. Now this. 24.39. Martial arts bonus.
You should buy that. Yeah. Those are epic pants. Barnabas what's wrong with you?
Why was I like not allowed to go in there? Should I keep the crossbow?
I don't think I I mean for a while. He's he's he's martial arts. Okay now martial arts bonus
plus four. That's what he currently had on. That's five and five percent eight percent cut
resistance and it's let's take that off and just go trade with you. Not you. You. Because
yours is just way better right? 24.39. Six kilograms. Four kilograms. Acid. Coverage.
It's a little makes me a little slower. Let's see. Oh let's see. Oh they're pants.
Okay I thought it was like a armor. Oh they're way better. I thought they were pants.
I mean I thought they were. It was like a something to go on my chest.
I don't know why I thought that. This on the other hand can just go back to where it was.
That's pretty damn good. Keep that metal plate on.
Keep this one on. 34 that's. Eat the deer. We're in a Jupiter storm. We'll be fine.
Somebody just subscribed and I have no idea who the heck it is.
But thanks. Boots. Boots. What about this? Look at the martial arts because that's really
good now. Barnabas is fucking fantastic now. All right let's go back to selling.
Sell those pants. I don't know why I thought that just said boomer.
All right. Everybody is good now. We just need food. Health pack. Health pack. What do you
get for food that I can afford? It might be time to steal a bunch of food from some random
person's house. Make money a job and they will pocket the ore by themselves. Interesting.
Operating machine copper resources. Is that it? Is that gonna do it? I don't need storage
for that. They won't pocket it unless I have the box. Well it's all right. Let's go back
here. Endless Coca-Cola. 4600 I'll have probably about 10 grand. I need food. It's
probably worth buying. Is it worth buying some of this shit? Oh can I just steal it?
Bread. All you have is the expensive food. It's 500 bucks. 700 bucks. 287. 575.
I need to make food. Big money. I'm gonna buy one of these. No I can't even do that.
It's worth it to make storage. It will make it so easy to make money.
That's bad. I gotta buy a new house. Right? The house that I have already bought is back
there and it's got like a shit. It's got like a level one training dummy. What are the houses
here? Because this is I mean the journey is supposed to be taking me. I started up here.
I went up here. I got screamed at. So I turned around. I went down this way through here,
through here, and then down here. So I was gonna think about trying to go through like
this section here. What's going on? Now this is what I call a chat experience.
It's pretty good. I like it. Why did I just say that? I do like it. Because I do. All right
let me just get this saved. I might just have to go hungry. Down. Let me just look. Yeah I
might have to go hungry down. It's very possible. If you get storage they'll auto mine
and then you can just have your guy with the backpack go in and out of the world.
It's sweet. Yeah I think it's probably time just to make somebody a permanent worker
and it's probably gonna have to be this person. So where... I gotta go back to my house.
My house is back here, right? Get a storage unit built. Have him just be a permanent miner.
Can't Roth is not not at all fit to fight. No he's not. Get a new house. I could do
that. This is expensive though and what does it take? Is there any cheap cheap houses here?
This one right here. 1500. Anything cheap in this? 15 15 1500. Because I could just have
build the storage thing here. There's a lot of mining and resources out here. I'm gonna buy
this. But should I? Could I? I can't build in here. It might be worth it to get a
larger building. I don't have any more. I don't have any money. I guess I could come back
with the... All right here's the plan. Here's the plan. I'm gonna sell all this, come back,
buy a big house here and then I'm going to have him permanently mine copper with the storage unit
and just keep mine. This one is 10 500 or 6 000 or I could get one of these for 4 000.
Small storage shack. I could just get a yeah I could get a cheap house and have it only be
for storing materials. That sounds like a good idea. All right 7 800.
Who you vote? There's no vote kick. Vote kick? I'm thinking this one's 10 000. No it's too...
I think I just want to have for now I'll do I'll get a small one build a I need a
really need a research bench in there too. Oh do I? Wait I don't do I need a research
bench in here. Storage copper. I need one iron plate. Don't vote kick me. What's why vote
kicking me? Yeah how big is how big does this need to be? This is just barely is this
barely gonna fit in here? So long streamer. Uh oh I'm gonna be fucked. Yeah I'm gonna buy
this one. I'm just gonna do it and have a couple things here. I don't I don't have the
means to do this right now. I'd rather just kind of get this going. So I'm gonna put a
bed and some storage units in here and then have him just permanently mine forever. Building
purchase. Everybody get over here and help. Oh I need three building materials. That's easy
I can get them. Oh can I? Does the trading who sells? I need to get building materials. Shit.
Did you have any? I need how many do I need? Oh you do. I only have two though. Shit.
How many did I need? I think I needed three. I need three building material.
Damn it. That's all right. There's two. Damn it. Well bring them over here. That's adding
materials. So now I need one more. What time is it? Uh everyone just chill for a little bit of
time. Anything I can do in the meantime? Maybe I could have somebody go back and
yeah you know what you go mine for now just go mine. Go mine that same dumb vein because
then after that eventually I'm gonna upgrade it. So go back there and mine. All right. Midnight.
Sleep. What have I done? I haven't done anything. The fence might have building materials.
Last time I went there he only I think he only had clothes. All right it's almost
midnight. Is it exactly at midnight? Let's find out. Midnight. Hey you got any new stuff?
Idling hunt times 10. I kind of have to. I don't see anything else over there.
What did I do? What did I do? Rest. That's the fucking arrest steam train. Go to a different
place with materials. I have to send somebody on an expedition then. So I'm gonna say
can I get them? Will they sell that at the hive village? They might. I guess you could go
just go get them. Although be careful because I'm gonna save this. What if you get like
jumped on the way there? That's like my hometown. What time is it? 8 30. When does
when does my new game come in? Massive. Oh fucking god damn it. That's right. I gotta
give. I have to buy like one piece of cheese for the dog. Come here. Where's the can drop?
I gotta. No no no no no no. Stop stop stop stop stop stop. Go back and get this.
Yeah I ordered a new game. He only notices when we're in morning. That's not true.
Ah come over here. Now give me. I have to buy something for the dog. I'm gonna buy a
fucking food cube. 25 nutrition versus 75 cooked vegetables. Will the dog eat the cooked vegetables?
I don't think so. What about the food cube? Because the food cube is uh has a bar. So face
cam stream. I don't I have no idea why this is even on. You're right. The dog will only
eat meat. Well that's not good. Call food cube. He's crying. I'm gonna get a food cube
and then bring it back to the dog. All right dog. Where the hell is dog? What is dog doing
all the way over here? All right you on an expedition yet? You are. Probably not in any
trouble. Where the hell did you end up? Yeah you're almost there. Keep going. Good for you.
Why aren't I stealing food? Because it's hard to do where I currently am because there's really
no food to steal. There's one building and that one building is a bar and there's like two pieces
of bread and there's always somebody there looking at you. This one I just I spent 10
grand to be part of this place. I don't want to take from this place. So you know. Are you
eating? Are you eating this? I didn't eat. Did I eat the whole thing before coming over to
him? Who bought that? Who ate it? Who ate that? Somebody fucking ate that before I brought it to
the dog. Everybody is so hungry. I have this like box of food that I'm like sneaking around. I
just got like fucking my pockets ripped open. Well it's all right because Barnabas is almost
there and we've been going for about five hours. I'm probably gonna stop. I'm probably
gonna move on to something else in the next like 20 minutes. I want to get this like
situated though. We'll transition to something else. All right here we are.
Play the original Fallout. Now I can't go from this to that. No no no no no no no.
Come here. Show me your wares. All right this meat here I kind of need to buy a lot of this
for the dog. So just buy it. Don't eat it all. Bread? No. These meat things? No no no no.
I came here for a very specific... I need building materials. So I need to go to...
You left your old backpack at the old house. I did. Did I? Did I? Interesting. Which one of
these is mine? Where the hell is my house? Isn't it that one right there? Small shack. Private.
Private. Which one of these do I own? Is it this one? Found it. Out of bounds. Leave it
once. Get the fuck away from me. I'm in my own house now. I picked the wrong house. I'm not
out of bounds. I'm in my own house. Get out of here. Thank you. Well you leave the door open.
What do you live in a barn? Okay that leaves me with... Where's the backpack that was in here?
Like sneaking into the town. They're sneaking into the town. Or sneaking out I'm not sure.
He's missing a leg. I wonder what happens to these two. What's this guy gonna do? Just watch
these guys. They are now your new characters. All right are they gonna get out? You think they're
gonna make it out? Phantom Pain. They actually made it out. Oh my god. Okay. You did it.
Kill them. It's free experience. I'll take the free experience. Let's just watch the bar go up.
Seven. Oh my god I thought he had all that food. I was like what the fuck?
Where's my martial arts? There it is. It's free. This is the leader? Yeah.
Take out the leader and that's it. You're done. Did I just break my leg? No. Well that was fine.
All right let's go back in here. I need two building materials. I'm gonna assume I gotta
get in here. What happened to the other backpack that was in it? Did somebody steal it?
Did somebody steal that backpack? All right we got I'm gonna need two. I need more than that
though. I need at least two. Fuck. I can only carry two. I'm probably gonna need like
iron plates. Save the dog. Whoops. Put a backpack on this guy. What happened? That's
what I'm asking though. Like what happened to the backpack that I had?
Did somebody come in my house and take it? No dog don't come all the way across the world.
I don't know. I don't. Stay there. Just go to the bar. I gotta have a guard in my house so
somebody did steal it then. All right I'll go to the backpack store and buy a backpack.
A good one. Where's backpack store? There it is. All right where is this one? This is a
wooden backpack. That's ones you can stack. So how much is it? It's only 800.
Buy it. Purchased medium backpack. Now I can buy some more stuff. Give food to the dog.
He's thinking about... He's thinking about letting it... I'm not thinking about that.
Just buy a fucking little food cube and it's already almost gone. God damn it. Dog come
over here. I can't walk this by anybody else. He ate it. Okay. Dog has eaten the rest of the
food cube. We're good. I'm gonna go back to do this. I got what I wanted. I'm gonna go
buy a couple more building materials and then I'm gonna come back. And actually I'm
gonna stop there and save it. Save the game and get out of this game. That's what we're gonna do.
Where's the... Where the fuck is the... No where is it? It's the one with the... Over here.
And I'm gonna give you my final thoughts on Kenshi as we sit here for a moment. I think
it's great. I think it's a lot of fun. I need a couple of these. Three. Just get...
Stack them up because I'm probably gonna need more. I know I need at least... I need... Yeah
I'm gonna need like four. Uh but yeah this is the last Kenshi stream you're gonna see
on the stream. End of Kenshi voice. Wait are you people really asking why? That can't be
happening in the chat right now. For real? It seems like every time I look over here
there's like a thousand complaints. One guy. One guy a thousand times. Not more Labo.
Oh shit no okay no it's not going. I like this game. I think it's fun. But I feel like the
downtime that the game is designed to have is not sitting well with a lot of people here.
So I don't know. I feel torn about this. All the people that hated it left. If I actually
listen to chat then... But that defeats the whole purpose of the game. But isn't the whole
point of this game to like just do whatever you want? You understand? That's the point of the
whole game. Don't listen to chat. Just play it all year. No I can't do that. Don't listen to them.
Well I mean it's kind of hard not to listen when a bunch of people are talking about how
they don't want this to be on the screen. You know what I mean? It's one thing to be like
oh forget about chat. Who cares? Well one it's a shitload of you. I mean if it's like
three people and you know at some point it's like what am I doing here? It was three guys.
All right so here's what we're gonna do. Do a poll? You played like four games this whole year?
It's January 8th. There's only been eight days this year. There's only been eight days.
All right here's what I'm doing. Here's what we're gonna do. I'm the only one that doesn't
want me to play this. Do I have a different chat? All right here we go. Here's your poll.
Let me save the game so I don't crash it though. I'm gonna name this.
Okay that's what I'm gonna name this. So here's your poll. Let's find out for real.
There you go. 34 guys. Oh Kenchi wins! What's the something else? Naked! I'm gonna get naked.
Only like three people voted for it. Nobody that didn't like change it at all.
You should have waited till I told you what the next thing was possible. All right I'm gonna keep
playing but just don't hear me out. Hear me out. All right hear me out. You know we're
having like we're just hanging out. We're just chilling. But like when I look over here and
I just see everybody so angry and annoyed and bored. That's not the kind of stream that I
want. I don't want that. You know what I mean? Like that's not what I want. I'm sorry if you
think the game is boring but like uh I don't what am I gonna do? Six more hours and kill! Oh
that was embarrassingly bad hair. You can't please everyone. I know but that doesn't mean
that everyone has to be bored. You know I try to make as many people happy as possible
because I want to have fun streams and if people aren't having fun then like I'm kind
of doing my job wrong. Right? I wanted to be fun. You know I'm concerned about it. I'm
concerned about this. It's not out of anger. It's not out of being annoyed or anything. It's
just I you know I want us I want you guys to have fun. I don't want you guys to be like
this sucks. You know what I mean? Like that's not that's not my goal. So if I look over
and I see a bunch of people going like I hate this. It's like well I got I have to think
about what I want to do. He's a concerned parent. Anyways I'm here's what's gonna happen.
Okay I know I've said that like three times. We're gonna stay on Kenshi for like another 40
minutes or so. I want to get to a position where I can move on out. Maybe we'll go on
one other expedition and we're gonna stop. I'm then going to transition from that. I'm gonna
play Book of Demons or GeoGuessr for like a couple hours. That's a pretty nice businessman
voice you got there. Alright so here we go. The last thing I was doing. Here's the last
thing I was doing. Let's see. I had it saved right? You guys okay you gotta bring the materials
back. So you go back where you were over here sir to the hub. You got the materials right?
Yeah yeah I got some food. Let's go. Let's move in the Lego Island waiting room.
I couldn't even get that fucking game to run. So that leaves the three of you here
and I'm gonna wait till you get back. Dog's been fed. Kind of just need to wait till you get back
and then get some food. The three I'm gonna leave canned roth here.
Whatever I want to go. Come on let go. Make sure. I hope I saved this right here
just in case he gets fucking. I knew it. Is this a wanderer? Bad guy? Good guy?
Tech hunter. Does that mean are you a person hunter? No. Alright thank god. Yes we're good.
Tech hunters are good guys. That's good to know. So in the meantime uh you just go back to what
you were doing. You were mining over here right at the copper vein which is over here.
Alright uh iron. Where is copper? Where the hell is it? It's right there. Oh that's like a
tiny little. That's a tiny one. It was it was that was a is that the one I was just on?
Have I almost depleted this thing? Alright where are you at? Almost there come on.
Hurry hurry hurry. Dog status alive. It's good. I almost just fucking poured this on myself.
My lord. I just almost drank out the other side. Alright build. Add the materials. Let's go.
Pour it down your shirt. God damn it. Alright hurry up and build this so I can get some
more food. All of you work together on it please. Almost done almost done almost done almost
done done done done done done done done done done done done done done done done done.
Small shack is built. Good. You get in there. And who's the who's the techie here? Oh yeah
muskets right? Musket in there. Where are you? What the hell are you? What are you doing
over here? What? What is he doing over here? Didn't I send Barnabas here? He just written
is he on follow? Did I accidentally click? I think I accidentally clicked on the hub
or the whatever. Oh my god. Okay well I don't I accidentally did that apparently.
So let's see if anybody else can build anything. Storage. Copper. Looks pretty good.
Tilt this again. How do I it's is it like this? Yeah this is so big. This is all that
can fit in this whole house. Alright what do I need? I need one iron plate through a bigger face
cam. Hold on give me a sec. Uh-huh. So now you're telling me that I could do mine cell mine cell
right? This is lagging. I just put a dumpster in my house that's all I did. How much in
this hole? A hundred. Okay that's alright. So now uh inventory auto haul. I'm assuming
that's what I need to do. So we're gonna put auto haul as a job right? And then
should I have this be? Where would he go? Stop stop stop stop. What are you doing?
So how do I get him to mine and bring it back automatically?
You put someone on a mining job they'll auto bring the ore back to the storage.
So this is use right? Operating machine copper resource. What's he doing?
Is he just doing it now? He's trying to go back now. He only has three. How often does he do that?
I tried that but for me it only mines one ore and then he goes back.
So he's only gonna pick up one. I feel like he's gonna wear himself out. He's probably gonna
mine five. This is kind of far away too. So he'll mine five at a time. How to get him to
mine a full? I think he needs food too. He's currently not doing terrible. Speaking of food,
I need to buy it. I need to have it. I guess like somebody was saying you can lure animals
and pull them back to the gate and have them get killed and then pick up their meat.
That's kind of a tall tale right now though. Well he's just gonna do that. So keep doing
that for as long as you can. Speaking of food, frog musky finally made it back.
This is my favorite stream. Let me tell you something. I'm happy you're watching. I don't
want you to be bored. I want you to have a good fucking time. So you know it is frustrating
for me right as the person that's doing the stream to know that a lot of people aren't. So
you know it's like nothing to do with anybody's personal taste or anything. It's just like damn
that sucks. He's insecure. No I'm not insecure. I'm broadcasting to twitch.tv. What's the goal
here? You know the goal is a community of people that watch and we hang out and we play games
and we do fucked up shit sometimes and we have fun. That's the goal. That's just the goal.
So I don't want it to be a situation where people are just like this is dumb.
Now I know a lot a huge amount of you guys didn't say that but a lot of people did and
not a lot but enough enough for me to notice. It has nothing to do with the game being bad.
It has to do you know obviously people don't want to watch somebody like mining for
like an hour and I get it. But you know it's not something that I take lightly. I hope you
know. That's pretty much it. So is he this three and all right so he is bringing it back
automatically. Make your face cam only show your eyes. No all right uh dog needs to eat
now otherwise dog is gonna die. You are doing your thing over here that's good.
Make sure you have like rooms shit you do. Okay you what the hell are you doing? Give
that food to that dog. No no no no pick that back up because somebody's gonna eat that off
the ground. That's not the dog. Dog come here. All right dog is eating. Get some more party
members and let's let them stay in town. Yeah I need money. I need to like add the the initial
the initial less than six eight party members is it's hard it's hard to make enough money to
have more people and make money to get more people and then send them on jobs. It's just
a slow process. Did he already take it? Okay Kanderoth is doing that job forever. I wonder
if somebody else should do it too because dog I need food I need to buy I need to okay new area
let's go. I'm going down here or I will go maybe I'll go to the way station. I have enough money
where I can buy food there. Dog can come with us he will just be mining until day dies.
Dog is back on the menu. No let's go over here don't go there to spite chat
because it's probably a good idea. It's probably actually a good idea.
You all need to run together though. Here we go. Who's the slowest one here?
No nobody's that slow. Save it. It almost spilled. All right way station see if I can
buy some food some supplies maybe. Who has shit on them? Somebody does don't they?
The operating copper machine good excellent. Where are you guys going?
Why did you change course like that? That was odd. What am I drinking? It's just coke.
It's just a coke. I thought that was an animal at first it's not. This is bridge.
Where does that lead to? What's this? Small copper no don't do it. How close am I to
the way station? Almost halfway there. 3,600 bucks good getting scary. Almost there. Enable
monka s. I probably will. I'll probably enable all of them eventually. Wait wait wait. Copper
I gotta hold on. I'm coming up there. This face cam is too big. There we go that's better.
Not big enough. How are you doing? Not terribly. Smart maps has been enabled.
Where are we? All right way station. Who the hell is this? Somebody get left behind. Can you
walk? We're almost there I promise. Got it. We're good. So where's the way station? Up here?
This is up like a fucking mountain. All right do I have to do anything weird?
Who's the group that owns this place? Are these? There's a bed. There's supplies. What about food?
Is there a place to buy food? I mean is it a bar? There's a bunch of random supplies huh?
A new buyer. Welcome. Hello. Let's do business. Show me your goods. Okay not literally not every
single one he has to come over here. You. You go. You solely just go. Cotton. No you
don't have anything do you? Let's go here. You have some food. Did a big donation come in?
Oh soup. We had a couple more than ten dollars. No soup for you thanks for the fourteen dollars.
Thought about giving fifty bucks for this occasion but I need money.
Don't that's more than enough. Thank you. German I know you love your fans but sometimes
you have to play the games you love. Many of us will stick around for it. The ones that
leave that's their own fault. Just please for your own sake don't let chat get to you.
Thank you. Don't worry about giving me fifty dollars. But there's two sides to that coin
right? There's do whatever the fuck I want. Whenever the fuck I want because I want to do
it. But the other side of that is remember you know there's a lot of people that pay
this stream money and it at the very end of the day I do want people to be happy.
I do want people that think ah this is not fun. You know what I mean? Like a lot of people
pay this free money. So there's like and I do agree. I do agree sometimes I am just going to
do whatever I want to do. But it's it's a weird balance that I think it is hard to do
in my personal opinion because I do want people to not be bored. I want people to have fun.
Do I not like this game? No I love this game. I think this game is great.
All right so with that being said Dry Ski also gave ten dollars.
Thank you for the ten bucks and thanks for the message. Appreciate that.
So did you just hear that like there's uh there's people in here.
I'm also looking to hire you. What do you think?
I don't have I don't have enough to do that right now. Uh who is even in here?
There's so many people in here. Mercenary captain. That's not something that's going
to be like 10 grand per day. Flash box. Looking to hire some bodyguards. I need
some mercenaries to guard my outpost. Two thousand per day. I can't afford that right
now. Peace. Looking for someone to join together with. Maybe. But who are you?
Just a nobody looking for like-minded people to band up with. Uh okay I'll join you. How much?
Three thousand cats. So there are two people in here that I can get the three thousand.
Plastic surgeon. Traders. Guild pacifier. Rin. Okay let's talk to Rin. Now looking to join
not much to tell. The city is getting pretty chaotic these days so I decided to
band up to find myself a new life. How much charging? Three thousand. Why not join for free?
Of course don't want you leaving me stranded and butt naked in the sands now do I? Give me some
value so I know I'm not just disposable fresh labor meat. Well this is apparently where you
go to hire a million people. Here to buy? Let's do business. What do you got? All right
thank god. You got a lot of food. That's exactly what I'm looking for. Let's get some
of these. The food cubes are great. That's all I can really afford but I have people to eat.
Can I get one another one? I can't afford another one. I do have enough. I should be okay now. Now
we got food. At least enough to survive. I can put the dog down. I might steal some
shit from here as well. It might be time to steal if you know what I mean. What's in here?
Wooden bowl, building material, fabrics, gears, fuel, but upstairs. What do you got upstairs?
Well it's not entirely true. This is a this is like this is a material bin. Storage or
hold on. Got nothing in there man. Not worth it. Holy shit that's a lot. Chain mail sheets.
Average price 2,500. 32% chance? That's a lot of money. The preemptive safe scum. Yeah I had to.
Five community subs from beer. Me a username. Thanks again for the community subs. A lot of
them tonight. You've done it before. You did it earlier. Thank you. Wait for this to load. 32%
might not be worth doing this over and over again but maybe it is. It's a lot of money.
I don't know. It probably it's probably not. It's probably not worth doing. Speaking of
money. How's shit going over here? How are you doing as a person? You need some food don't you?
Oh my goodness. Storage box. About to head back. How much is in the box?
Let me just see how much is in there because I'm gonna sell it. What do you got? Five yet?
Oh just pick up. Pick up one two three four five. Head back because I can't even look
in there. Time to sell the copper. Hurry hurry. 17. That's pretty good. Let's cash it in. Why not?
Oh what's happening here? Um what's going on? Okay sell it and then go back to what you were
doing. Dog's dead? No dog's eating. He's currently eating. Now I just gotta go sell
this at what is what are they doing in here? Oh my god is this free meat? This is gonna be
free meat. Uh how do I how do I get free meat? This is meat. They just wandered into the town.
What a godsend. Free meat. I can't kill them by myself. This is gonna sound the alarms or
something right? Help me help help help me. Run away. Thank you. Oh yeah beautiful. All right
now take the meat while they're fighting. That's food for a goddamn whole winter. That's
food for an entire winter. Yes. Oh my god that's so much food and the pelts are worth so much money.
All right I need to heal myself. I don't have a med kit. What's around my body?
What's around my arm? Am I holding holding my head? Okay I got a lot of stuff to sell and
shit. Wait okay I'm just gonna panic attack. Let's go. That was perfect. They just waltzed
right into the town. Oh my god I couldn't have asked for something better than that.
Put the camera in the top right corner. Uh I will just give me one second. What am I not
taking the ore out of the container? I thought I did. Uh am I going crazy? Am I am I doing this
right? What am I doing is wrong? It was weird. I guess maybe because he was doing the return.
All right I'm gonna sell all the pelts. I'm gonna cook all the meat and then I've got an
expedition. These pelts are worth 200 each. Should I save any of these or should I just get
fucking rid of all of them? I can turn them into leather but maybe it's not worth it.
5500. I've got a bunch of meat that I'm gonna cook in the fire. Didn't miss any meat right?
That was so lucky. I can't believe. I can't fucking believe that happened.
They just waltzed right in here and it was just free food for at least a week.
Does the food not go bad? Well I have to make sure I cook it. I don't know does it?
I do need some med kits. Three of them heal my broken head because you know I need to.
And then go back to mining. Well I'll actually cook this shit first
because does it go bad? Uncooked meat from some dead animal probably. Possibly edible.
Possibly edible. Dried meat does not rot. That's good to know.
Did I heal enough? I think I did. Yeah apparently I did. All right so now I need to cook this shit
in a fire. Is it gonna burn my house down? All right am I all right? I look tired.
Um I don't think so. Maybe a little maybe a little bit. Oh a little baby tired boy.
All right you're gonna you'll do this for a little while so that's fine. I'll check
back on you in a minute. Dog is still eating. That's good. You're up here you're
gonna go down and I want you up there when the night falls. Let's save it. Save game.
So what the fuck do I want to do now? I need to look for some veins that are close by.
Even if it's iron it's probably is it worth is it even worth collecting iron?
How much does it sell for? I can't. Depends on the zone.
The warning? Not if you start building a base. How much longer will I be streaming for?
Oh well because I decided I was gonna just stick with Kenshi.
It's been about six hours. Probably not that much longer.
Probably maybe like another hour or two I would say. And then I'm going to stream on Thursday.
I'm gonna go Thursday and Friday because I'll get 700,000 games on Thursday.
And then uh the um I probably shouldn't say that yet.
12 hours you should start just doing 12 hour streams every other day. I think my health would
decline. Yeah there's 700,000 games too came out and I got it. It's gonna be here on Thursday
so that's what we're gonna do on Thursday. And then we're gonna go Thursday and Friday.
So we'll do two days in a row after tomorrow. Uh how's that food doing?
Oh shit I'm eating it right okay well of course I am. It's food.
Is it gonna automatically put this in here? No I gotta I gotta do it manually I think.
Maybe I can just do this right on a halt. Uh it'll just keep going. I need what do I need to do?
Stream 24 7 for a week and then retire. I wouldn't be able to even stay up that long.
Let's go this way. What is what what people are freaking out for what?
That guy's sprinting around like a psycho. All right let's see uh personnel check.
5200 food is over here. He's cooking it all. Empty backpacks. Some food on
Barnabas. Actually quite a lot. The dog is still eating. That's good. I'm trying to think of
what else. I should probably check the other building here. So let's do that because I
went in this one. Did I go in? At least that's the only two that are here. Cool outpost.
I think I might want to go. I need to go get that food. I need that food from the hub and
then they need to go down because I want to keep him there mining. So we kind of have to go back
unless I can find something to fight. Great Canadian fuck club. Five community subs.
Thank you. More community subs. You guys are fucking awesome. Thanks. Five five five ten.
That's a lot. Thank you guys. Seriously. Every time he reads the username.
Well is it time to make my own damn town? Not yet probably. I need like another couple people.
Give it a total of 300 subs. 300 subs? That's uh that's fucking crazy.
You need more people and more money. Making your own town as a grind. I could probably
imagine. I'm trying to think of where I want to go from here. I just have to go back to the hub.
We got some food. We have some resources now. Now I'm going to take
the troop. Deck them out with food. Deck them out with resources and shit and we're going
to go down. These are slavers. I don't think my band of idiots can defeat them. Although it's
minus 12. Hold on a minute here. This number right here. 12 and then minus 13.
This number is what it is. It currently is now. That is with the minus 13 on it already.
Included. I just need to triple check that. So I am not going to go fuck with them. I'm
going to get my ass kicked. There's too many of them. Go this way if you will. So you
don't cross the path of all these dudes. Holy military base. I haven't looked at that yet
though. You guys are going to get on get off the road so I can walk on it.
How you doing? You still cooking food? Yes you are. Keep it cooking good. Dog is fine right?
Yeah. I want to get fucked over there. All right go. Just shift click it and automate it.
Hold on what the fuck is this? Escaped servant. Two six nine
three. Why do you all suck so much? From what what's happening here? Weather penalty.
That's this fucking weather. So they're not hostile right? State normal. This this should
be I should be able to walk right by them. I'm not going to cause a problem if you guys
don't cross don't cause a problem with me. I won't cause a problem with you.
In fact yeah that's fine. Recruit? I don't have an option to. I don't have mods installed right
now. I'm just going to playing the base game for a little while. All right so the hub. There
it is. I made it home. We're here. We did it. No we didn't. That's the military base. Might
as well take a look. All right let's auto haul this. Let me get a chance. I have so much fucking
food. Auto haul right? There we go. Where's the dog? Where's the dog? What are you doing back here
dog? Let's go. All right this is all destroyed. Why is this place destroyed? There's nothing here.
There's a ninja blade in here. Flesh cleaver. Mercenary club. What is all this stuff?
How do I get in there? Holy shit. Are you kidding me? Well that's fucking awesome.
Oh my god this is all free stuff. This is ridiculous. There's nobody. There's nothing
here. Can I fix this place up? Damn. All right well get to it then. You're the one
with the backpack. Iron plates. Long cleaver. I mean that's not that great but still it's
free. Ninja blade. Oh that's outside. All right hold on. Iron plates. Horse chopper.
What about stuff I can open? Go check out that ninja blade. Damage versus humans.
Attack bonus plus two. I mean it's all right. Cleaver. You can just sell them. This is not
technically stealing. It was just on the ground and nobody wants it right? Something like
that. Any other boxes to open? Look at this. Are you kidding me? Damn. How much does it even
sell for? 113? I mean that's not great but that's not terrible. How many are you just
gonna pick up? That's a lot. Well now I know why it's free. Because it kind of sucks.
Mercenary club. People could just load up and put that up. Iron stick. Worthless.
That's not terrible. Welcome to the mercenary club. Never do it for free. Ever. Unless there's
something I'm missing here. These aren't really that great. I kind of had a moment there.
There's no other tools or anything. I can tell. These really just kind of suck.
These sell for... I'm gonna get 99. 24. 84. 387. That's not bad. 197 is not bad. I might
as well just put this up here. That was weird. The storage purposes just hold on to it.
20 iron stick. Horse and mercenary. No. I think I'm gonna leave it all. Flesh cleaver.
Long cleaver. 93. 86. Well that's not good. I mean I guess just... I'm going back anyways.
Does everybody pick something up? It's free anyways. 19 attack. Not worth it. I'll get
my ass kicked. Somebody will get hurt and die. You fool. Where the hell are you? Get over here
man. You can't pick that up. Why the hell can't you? What do you mean you can't pick
that up? You stand right in front of it. Too long? Too long. All right. Everybody has a bunch
except for you. You need to actually keep that on. Get another stick. Let's go. Everybody has
their pockets full. You can head back to the hut. Make a fat 1.5k. Something like that,
yeah? So let's get together again and... minus three. Minus two. Minus five. Minus five.
Minus four. Minus six. Minus five. Minus six. Minus three. Minus two. Minus five.
Minus two. Seven. Isn't he better with unarmed? Four. Yeah he's better with unarmed.
Dogs here. Two with fifteen. I gotta get rid of this stuff. I gotta put it on the ground for
now. Where is everybody? Get back inside. Throw all this shit on the ground for now.
Because this is a fight here that I have to fucking win. Okay. Is it ten? What about you?
Doesn't matter. You? Drop. I gotta drop it? I have to. Otherwise I'm gonna die.
Really matter does it? Dog is fifteen. Ten. Oh they're all so weak. They're all doing
minus five. I can't get in there and just fucking destroy them. Dog is malnourished.
Not starving. We're good. Eight and fifteen. There's just so many of them.
Got one, two, three, four, five. How much do I have? I would have a heels.
Not very much. What's lowering my attack? It's the weather. There's like a weather
problem here. Equipment. This. It's like isn't there a weather penalty going on right
now? Because I don't have any like dust protection. Minus nine. Weather penalty.
Defense. What do they have for defense? Six. They have much more defense. It's probably not a
good idea. All right. I'm probably too bad I just threw everything on the fucking ground.
That's great. It wouldn't have worth that much money anyways. I'm going to save it
here and just see what happens if I could fight them. I'm just going to go for it.
Everybody get together over here. Just bring them in. Bring them inside. Okay. Jesus. Look
at this fucking mess. Let's go. We just got destroyed. There's too many. I just got my ass
kicked. That wasn't even a contest. This is too many. It didn't matter how much attack they
had. I mean there's fifteen of them. We're gonna have to run because they'll just take
everything I have. How much food do I have? That's the real question. The food. Actually
the food. That's a lot of food. These things are like six hundred bucks. They're gonna eat
the dog and shit. Let's try to get away. See if I can get out. No they might not even.
They might not be here. Dog turned into a food cube. No they're here. All right.
I mean the question is can we run? Look at how close I am. I might be able to just bait
them over here. If everybody's in a full sprint, go for it. Sneak away. It's too
late. I think they are running right at her right now. I think. Go! Okay. Apparently
no one's running. Why is that exactly? What happened there? I have everybody selected.
What? Okay. Pick that shit back up then. I'll take it. Let's go. Back to town. How
come none of you listen when I do that? All together now. Wait for...
Oh yeah. You're over encumbered. Ah yeah. Forget it. It's not worth that much money.
Hub. And everybody go. What's going on? I can't run. So once we get back to this town,
I'm probably going to call it for the night. I'm getting hungry. I need some food. I need
to go check on some things. Bad path. It probably is bad pathing. End it with karaoke.
No. I'm kind of drained at the moment. I can't do karaoke six plus hours into a stream.
Not right now. No geoguessert. We can... You know probably when I get 700,000 games in the
mail then we're going to... Maybe we'll just warm up with that and then play that on Thursday.
The way my facial hair sits on my cheeks makes me look malnourished.
I have to shave anyways. Thanks for the reminder. I need to do that.
The hub. Let's get in here and make sure we're safe. Monsters right now or something. Just
watch. Now I can't unsee it. It's all right. I'm well fed. We're safe. Everybody inside.
Everybody in? There's tons of food over here too right? Let me just check. Well that's a lot
of meat. Food will be cooking. People get to eat. That's good. Everyone's safe and sound.
Oh I'm gonna like burp. But that's gonna conclude the stream for tonight. We'll do the
bits and the subs too. About seven hours. It was kind of a wild one tonight. We started
with some extreme stuff and moved on to a chill stream and now I'm going to get some food.
Maintaining a beard can be difficult. Oh yeah. I can't grow a beard.
Facial hair does not grow here. It does not grow here. I get like a really sporadic
shitty beard here, here, and then like here. I don't grow any facial hair here. It's strange.
It's very strange. But thanks for sticking around. I'll see you guys not tomorrow.
I'll give you the tentative plan here. So tomorrow I have a few obligations. Human
obligations right? Thursday 700,000 games part two comes in so it's gonna be fun.
Knees never coming back. No I am. What's going on here? Itchy? And then Friday I'm
gonna probably try to plug in the Dreamcast. It's been a long goddamn time. So much love to
you if you take it off. See you on Thursday. Take care of yourselves. And I'm gonna disappear
from the camera. I'll give you a last final wave. See ya. I'll see you guys on Thursday.
Oh why? Okay hold on, hold on. Slow down, slow down. Where are you going? What are you
doing? Stop it. Please. And there's the outro. There it is. I like the game. I think it's
fun. I think it's an interesting experience. Just takes a while to get going and that's kind
of the way it is. With that being said I'll see you later. Let's go back a while ago for the
bits. Starting back here. Hey chicken foot thanks for the five dollars chicken foot. Hey Jeremy
I showed my 60 year old mother your videos and she loved them. My family also watched
your Christmas and New Year streams together and also I made this. YouTube was broken for me
so I uploaded it to streamable. Resident Evil? Resident Evil 4? I have only one very important
question. Do you eat ass? There's the link for those of you that'd like to see it.
Thank you chicken foot. I'm glad your mother likes the videos. Lazy Luke thanks for the
one dollar. What is something in your life now that you weren't you wouldn't have believed
five years ago? Besides your fans saving over 60,000 seagulls. Something I didn't
think was this streaming on like Twitch. I never thought this would ever be possible.
So this is you know impossible. What is playing right now? Oh that. But thank you Lazy Luke.
Thank you binary man for the five dollars. Hey Jeremy here's the thing that I think chat might
like. By the way I did make the stupid musical gnome song thing in FL studio. That thing you
have never mentioned definitely never told us you would stream. What's this? Spider-Man?
Is the guy throwing a dynamite out of a window in a Spider-Man video?
It's called oh uh whatever owo. Thank you binary man for five dollars. Hey Divus thanks
for three dollars. Drummage door. Drummage door thanks for the one dollar. Why are you
gonna play me like this man? You kind of hinted you check out Lisa but in viscera
stream you didn't even know that game. Um that's probably just messing around. I've
heard Lisa a thousand times. I was probably just kidding that I like never didn't know
what it was or something. Bart. I want to sample Jeremy saying thank you Divus and use it as a
tag. You give three dollars every single stream man. Thank you. Darkstar thanks for
the one dollar. You're a handsome motherfucker you know that. I think sometimes you know you
look in the mirror and you go I look okay. Sometimes you go maybe not so maybe not so
much today. But thank you. Appreciate it. Jornhorn thanks for the one dollar. Jerma
it's Jake from the video game accreditation agency. Your gamer license is about to expire.
Please complete the chips challenge level blob net to renew it. I don't even know what that
is. Crypt world thanks for the five dollars. Crypt world play your automaton. I want to
see some of your gifts you haven't used yet. Oh that's right I do that. That's true.
That's true I do have that. I do kind of I could break that out.
Thanks for the reminder. L on a you knee thanks for the one dollar.
Thank you. E dragon thanks for the one dollar. Darkstar thanks for the one dollar. By the way
it's been six months since I last changed my name. Any suggestions? As it is now most
streamers give up after Darkstar because they don't want to read a big number. Well think
about 700,000 games. It's 700,000 games. It's seven syllables. So you got Darkstar
700,000 games. So it's it's a it's a lot of syllables. Darkstar 700 it's it's it's
number 700. 700. Darkstar 7. Darkstar 700. Darkstar 70. But uh speaking of your name
that should be a very interesting stream on Thursday. Suggestions for your name?
I don't know. You want to keep the Darkstar apart? There's two years worth of content on there.
I'm sure we'll blow through it all in about four hours. But thanks a lot. I don't really know
what to yeah I keep keep your name the way it is. I think it's just fine. Jerma still short
ha ha ha ha one dollar they say five foot one. I mean your name just certainly you know
there it is. Jerma still short. I mean when was I supposed to be taller at some point?
How can I still be short? I didn't plan on getting any taller. But thank you for the
one dollar. Thank you Alec for the one dollar. Try not to use a face cam for like three months
and don't shave so that one day you'll turn it on and have a full beard. Oh it would look
bad. I could I try I can't. As long as it's ever been is really in October.
With the balloon thing. I can't do it. It doesn't grow. It just kind of spreads out strangely.
Hey Jess homeboy. Thanks for the one dollar. I'm still working on that painting. Sorry it's taken
so long. The beard looks good. Do you still main Pac-Man and Ultimate even though he sucks real
bad? Um I don't really play Ultimate. I had a realization when I played Ultimate that I
I just can't do it. It's very hard to get good at a fighting game. You have to put a lot of
time into it and getting dunked on by people in like 2v2s when me and it's Alex are playing
is just like holy shit. I ain't gonna be able to do this. It's still a fun game.
Still an interesting game. Still fun to play. Smash is still easier than something like
Street Fighter. Oh boy I could never ever. Not in a million years would I be able to handle that.
But thank you to Drummage Door again for the one dollar. Also to add up to that Lisa painful
RPG donation. I want to underline that these bits are basically my last money from my bank
account. But if you'd play that game the entertainment value would be worth it. You're
the funniest guy I know especially after super best friends split up. Greetings from Finland
love you man. Well thank you for the one dollar but I hope you take care of yourself.
Don't worry about me. And to kind of give a very very clear answer and I don't
the thing about games and recommendations and things that people want me to play or things
that I should play. It really just comes down to maybe one day I would maybe one day I won't.
I don't really I don't really have a necessarily like a day to day this is
the game I'm going to play. This is the game I'm going to play next. This is a game to play
after that. Usually it's like a week to week basis when I'm trying to figure out what I
want to do. So I don't really have a plan to play like Lisa for instance. I'm sure maybe at
some point like earlier today I was thinking about doing the Obra Dinn. It was like what I
want to do today Kenshi or just fuck around in IRL and it was kind of just a stream
where I was dicking around doing nothing today. So it really there's no rhyme or reason
to when I'm going to play a certain game. Just kind of happens organically if I want to.
So I know there's a lot of people that are like hey you should play this you should play this
and they recommend I take I've taken a lot of stuff already from that recommendation channel.
So I do know and I do see that they're worth playing but I just can't like guarantee like
oh hey you better stick around because in February middle of February you're gonna get a
Lisa playthrough. Like I don't know if that's gonna be the case. I'm always open to pretty
much anything. But take care of yourself thank you for the one dollar donation here
and have a great day and a great tomorrow. Oh shit is he gonna play Lisa? Is he gonna do that?
Whoa you sick. Hey Captain Scruffy thanks for the five dollars. It was awesome meeting you
the other day. You as well. Thank you so much for the five dollars and I love meeting people.
I love talking to people. It was a pleasure. Thank you and thank you for the five dollars.
ZeroSnakey thanks for the one dollar. Man Dom Requiem thanks for the one dollar. Stop singing
please. I did. I did. I did. Eventually. El Cobra thanks for the 10 dollars. This was
beautiful 10 out of 10. How have you not hit the top 10 yet? Top 10 on the billboards?
I don't know. I'm as shocked as you are. I can't believe that my singing voice has not carried me
to the top of the charts. It should be there. But thanks for the 10 dollars. Smelly Boy thanks
for the one dollar. The singing was more embarrassing than German Raptor. No it wasn't.
I don't think that's true. No way. Not in a million years. Thank you Schmegs for the five
dollars. I love all your content. Thank you. Thanks for sticking around. Thanks for paying me
money. Thanks for everything. Thanks for the five dollars. Super Frogman thanks for one dollar.
Hope this covers the cost of a name tag for the sneeze gun. Would have given it to you earlier
but had to name mine first. Seriously I've been watching since Burger Boy puked. I've never once
seen one of your videos and not laughed. You are a great inspiration. Oh yeah. Oh yeah I
forgot about that. He did puke on he well not on camera. He ran out of the room into
the bathroom. That's a fucked up video. Good old Burger Boy. Thank you Super Frogman. Thank
you Jess again for the one dollar. Look how terrifying this is. Pretty terrifying. Smelly
Boy thanks for the one dollar. You were for used to play Kenshi for this. I did play Kenshi
for about just about six hours. So I did. I did do that. I did. I did. I did. Thank you
though Smelly Boy for the one dollar. I think you see 4G for the one dollar. Karaoke Boy has
arrived and left at the same time. Hardcore candy store thanks for the one dollar. I love
your IRL streams. Sometimes we have some fun and sometimes I just don't know what to do with
myself in front of the camera so I embarrass myself profusely. Sky King TV thanks for the
one dollar. Hey I just finished a stream. Only had three people show up but you inspire
me man. Thanks for all the laughs. Wish I could give you more. Don't worry about that.
Thanks for even the consideration. Good luck with your stream. It's tough. I wish you
luck. Hey spuds thanks for the one dollar. What a good bit Jeremy. Very nice.
Maybe I should have picked a voice that was a little less ridiculous.
You couldn't hear a god damn thing I was saying. Absolutely nothing.
You couldn't hear anything. I was in there for like a full minute. At least or two minutes.
Oh my god. God damn it. Thank you Mini Clips for the 10 dollars. This is the engaging content
I come to watch. Wild Fox thanks for the one dollar. Thank you to 10 bucks though for real.
Thank you Wild Fox and one dollar. Hey Jeremy I want to thank you again for being such a cheery
and upbeat personality. The amount of emotion I'll help you streams have given me over the
years is ridiculous. I hope you find comfort in your community as much as we do with you,
Jeremy Hart. Yeah I do. I do. You guys are great. I butted heads a little bit today
but nothing serious. And by butting heads I mean me versus myself in a way. If you
hear earlier you probably know what that means. But uh no it's great. Everybody here is usually
99.9 percent of the time a fucking joy to be around. You know every point zero zero point
one percent somebody says German is short ha ha ha it's tiny man and you know some you know
that's just one zero point zero zero zero one percent. But it's all good. That's like 78
percent. No it's not that much. But thank you Wild Fox. Avon Grad thanks for the one dollar.
Jeremy Hart right back at you. Valky thanks for two bucks. Don't worry man this stream is great.
If it was boring you wouldn't have almost 4 000 viewers. Love you Jeremy. I can't even
believe that there are that many people that would be here in the first place so thanks.
Really really appreciate that. Bro Luck thanks for the 15 dollars. I was watching
a different streamer on mute open to your stream and watched the other for a little bit
I thought you were insane at the Witcher 3. I wasn't surprised when I realized what was going
on. It's okay I can go back to pretending you are good at video games. Beat Simpsons hit and run
first uh first sitting. I mean I don't know that's the latest one. Thank you for the 15
dollars though really appreciate that dude. Love it our speed run by the way. Yeah that
guy bit his controller. I didn't. Came kind of close. But thanks for the 15 dollars bro.
Luck thank you Freudian Weapon for the one dollar. I'm definitely checking out Kenshi
once I hook up my PC. Thanks for showing it to me. It's a great game. I feel like it just gets
better as you play it. Thank you Bro Luck again for the 20 total dollars. I just did it again.
I was looking at Shroud's stream on mute with yours in the background. I mean this is just a
lie at this point but that's uh I'll give it to you. And I thought maybe wow he's not a
trash at video at the game. Apparently. Thanks for the 20 bucks Bro Luck. Uh Yakubu thanks for
the one dollar. Jazz Jelly thanks for one dollar. Hi Jeffrey. Hey hi Jazz Jelly.
Prodbreaker thanks for the three bucks. Yo Jerma what's up man. Have been watching you
since the Jerma is mad and Jerma rumbled 2k14 days. I I'm wait you didn't know that I
streamed. I wonder how many people didn't know that I stream. I feel like it's probably a lot.
We talked about this like two days ago didn't we? Like three days ago.
Wait you stream? Because the uh from YouTube and all that people still don't know surprisingly.
Yeah I'm gonna have to think about how I want to handle that. It's more like internal conflict.
We have discussed it but we don't need to discuss it now. Thank you though Prodbreaker
for three bucks. Welcome. Swiggy swanky thanks for the one dollar. This is my favorite OST.
All right I gotta compose myself here. I'm fucking losing my mind. I really was losing my mind.
Thank you ToshirodoTV for the one dollar. Can't wait for the Kenshi exclusive Jerma
rumble at the end of the year with a full squad of dumb bitches primed for our entertainment.
I hope Massamoon wins. Oh goodness. Thank you Sir Tardigrad for the three dollars. Big fan of
the Kenshi streams. Keep it up. You really should keep playing Gungeon on stream. It's a lot of
fun once you get the hang of it. I don't know if I have the capacity to to play it. I've
watched people play Gungeon. It looks great but I think uh I feel like I need to like really
sink time into games like that. It's like Binding of Isaac. I put hundreds of hours,
hundreds and hundreds of hours into Binding of Isaac and Isaac is at this point is just
that game that I could go back and play and have a meltdown after Mario Tennis.
But thank you. Thank you Darkstar for the one dollar. You know if you value freedom to do
whatever the hell you want in sandbox type games you should get around to playing
Breath of the Wild. So if you ever did choose to stream it I would suggest maybe only one or
two streams considering how you can get bored when playing long games on stream.
What the fuck is playing in the background? It's like Michael Myers in my house.
Hello? What the fuck was that? All right well that was I'm just gonna mute the
desktop. That was weird. Yeah Breath of the Wild seems cool. I don't know. Thank you
the Jewish bro for the dollar 50. Oh sorry two three six hold on six seven eight nine ten.
Thanks for the ten dollars. Spread out over about probably 30 minutes or so. Thank you so much.
Really appreciate that. Uh thank you Ragtor for the one dollar. Dude I love Nightwing. I
love his emblem tattoo. I have his emblem tattooed on my arm. Do you remember where you got that
shirt? I gotta have one. Have you read Nightwing the new order? Hugs and kisses. Xoxo how do I
end these? Face caming. Wait what's happening? Oh I actually don't know where the hell I got
this. I think this is on a clearance rack somewhere. That's one of those music stores.
I don't remember exactly where I got it. I'm certain it was on the clearance rack though.
That's all I remember. It was like a buy five get five. Ghost hunting? What's going on?
But thank you uh brown cow balls for the one dollar. Thank you Garfield the Monday killer.
Thanks for the one dollar. Uh Garf stones meet the Garf stones of the modern feline family
from the land of Toontown. They give bits to Jeremy. Yabba dabba doo Jeremy your
trusty feline ambassador hath returned with a new kitty cat viewer in the chat.
Wait there are new cats? Who are the new cats? I bet you thought Garfield was slacking off with
his cat related duties but no siree potpourri. I know how to say potpourri. Garf just got you
like a ton of new viewers. They're in the chat right now. Make yourselves known. All cats.
Did Garf deliver or what? I don't see any cats here. Thank you Garfield. Thank you smelly
boy for the one dollar. Jeremy we like watching you play Kenshi. Stop pretending like you don't
know twitch chat is full of assholes who lie and fuck with you. No that was not. Come on
let's be completely real here. I can I know the difference between we're fucking with
Jeremy man and I don't like this. There's a big difference even before we switched to Kenshi.
You know come on. All you gotta do is look. Can Jeremy ban? Can you ban Jeremy?
Jeremy ban. Jeremy ban. Can you ban Jeremy? Jeremy ban. But thank you smelly boy. Thank
you dryski for the ten dollars. We caught you earlier. Thank you so much. And then no
soup for you. Came in with 14. Talked about how thought about giving 50. Don't worry about
that. They say don't let chat get to you. No it was it wasn't chat. It wasn't about
like the chat. It was about that the collective collective boredom that a lot of people were
experiencing. And even look even with a poll right 30 what like 30% said that they were
just like oh my god get off the game. So you know I gotta read that right. So when when
you when at least 30% of people are just like like telling me hey I don't like this.
I read it. I have I'm reading it. It's not about because look at to me it's if you don't
like a stream or if you don't like a game that's all right. But I at the end of the day
it's something that I need to either to do change or take care of. You made him sad.
You don't always have to listen to chat. And I mean I I don't I I kind of don't in a lot
of ways. But just but always but keep in mind right just always keep that in mind.
That I am reading the chat. So sometimes you look over it it's just like shit man and
that's this all right I guess. Oh fuck he saw all the bad things I've said about him.
Sometimes you look over it it's shit man. Hang in my badge tomorrow. But don't take this as me
complaining about chat. Complaining about things that people say. Because I like I told you that
I know there's a there's a very there's a huge difference between banter and boredom. I just
hope you guys know that I want to make sure every stream is fun and it's hard to do that.
And that's almost an impossible task. But I'm gonna try to do it.
Thanks for the 14 dollars and 10 dollars here. Dry Ski and no soup for you.
Well to touch up to kind of expand upon this one final time. It's it's it's tough.
Here's one reason why. Because I get a lot of requests to do stuff like today. Just play a
game and just hey let's play something and play it and do it again. Play that game again. Play
that game again. That was that was fun. It was relaxing. But it's almost an equal amount of
people that would rather see something else. So when maybe I'd say probably half the people
don't want to watch a game like Kenshi and half the people do. It's kind of this it's a
rock and a hard place. It wasn't equal. But but my point is that there's a lot of people
that want to watch me kind of just play a game and hang out. And there are a lot of people that
want to watch me do something else that's maybe a little more intense or a little
crazier or more interesting right. And it's trying to find a balance between those two
things. Do a live knitting stream. But I'm I'm really I'm really absolutely I'm just
absolutely nitpicking here. Because it's this is like that this is a great problem to have.
A bunch of people like this. A bunch of people like the other stuff. A bunch of people like
the other shit that I do. No I like that so much I want you to do that. No I like this
too. That's a good problem to have. And I wouldn't even classify it as a problem.
It means that I have a big audience. Yeah and as the channel continues to grow I need to
start to figure out how to handle stuff. Because this channel look I come from YouTube
right four years ago. Where I didn't have to oh it wasn't live. I could just upload a video
and that was it and like leave the comments. And what do people say about that video? This
video sucked. Oh shit all right I'll make sure to change that. I bet I'll change that video
style. In real time it's almost like oh fuck this is happening right now. This shit's
happening right now. You know not like days later when I go look at a comment section.
So it's different. And the channel has almost doubled at some points even tripled in viewership
over the last six months. It's been absolutely fucking insane. Yeah really yeah. Oh Jesus.
That's just me watching a bunch of times in a row. Wait like what right now?
Uh there's a huge amount of money just came in right now. Uh thank you thank you Jingo
Jango Wizard Spy for these 65 dollars. 65 bucks. Hey I only meant to buy 1500 bits but it kept on
saying purchase failed. Turns out it worked every time. Rip. Anyway I wasn't here for the
beginning of the stream but I know the kind of situation you're talking about and I hate
it when it happens because it grows from being a joke into being something real. Hope you know
that fans like myself love anything you put out. You're doing it great. You're doing great dad.
First of all apparently Twitch is having a strange bit problem tonight
and people are buying way fucking more than they wanted to. Holy shit. That error is
that's not all right but thank you anyways regardless. But yeah I it's hard to even
comment on because I do you think I I don't know how to like deal with that.
I mean I do to an extent but and I'm and I am acting like this was a huge this was a huge
problem. No it wasn't at all. Essentially if you if you weren't here there was a portion of
the stream where I felt that people were bored and they but they didn't want to see this
anymore and they wanted me to move on to something else and that's what I felt. That's
how the way that's the way I felt. And then it was kind of like an equal amount of people were
like no stay no go I'm leaving I'm out of here. It's like did you see Barnabas? Barnabas just
like just sat down in the bed and it's cool right? Dermot you work for Twitch. Fix this
problem. Enter. But I'll move on for a bit. It wasn't a big deal but might as well talk
about it because why not right? Thank you for the 65 accidental dollars. When Vinny played
Bad Dead Redemption 2 he finished the game because he enjoyed it and he had the lowest
numbers. No it's not but it's not a it's not a numbers thing. It's not a numbers thing. It
doesn't I don't doesn't the the fact that the viewers you know were dropping when I
started playing Kenshi that's not the problem that I'm describing. I'm talking about people
audibly in the chat room talking about how how badly they don't want me to do the thing
I'm currently doing. Audibly typing right but that but that's the only reason why
I even thought to address it in the first place because I was in the reception so let's just
give again an example here. So if you have like 4,000 people and that drops down to like
3,000 all right whatever that's fine but then like 3,000 people you know people still talking
about it maybe they're still bored they're still talking about it then you know did people
leave because they were bored or people still sticking around hoping that I'll change to
something else right it's tricky probably both yeah but regardless I don't want to I don't want
to smack into this dead horse anymore it's not an issue it's not it's just something to talk
about. Hey pin thanks for the one dollar coffee Cheetos chicken compact exoskeleton bug
millennium burger yeah yeah boy boot leg duck dynasty yeah batman I always just threw up when
I read that I don't know what that was pin but thank you uh elinor thanks for the one uh zero
down on one dollar ten dollars thank you for ten dollars elinor thank you modus pons for the
one dollar have you ever played any of the Bioshock series yes I a long time ago I completed
Bioshock infinite uh Bioshock 2 I don't know if I did I ever play through Bioshock 2 I think
I watched somebody else do it in Bioshock 1 but thank you uh thank you Avongrad for the one dollar
did the Pokemon socks come in yet I think they got stuck in the mail somewhere they think they're
stuck in the mail I think uh somewhere in that mailbox thank you for the one dollar spoon it
thanks for the one dollar hey Jerma I was watching the NBA on mute with you in the
background I was really impressed and thought you were good at basketball and being tall
but then I realized my mistake soon after is love you buddy thanks for the one dollar
ha ha ha oh man that okay that was good thank you pin for the one dollar hey Jerma just want
to take this opportunity to tell everyone in chat that I met you at TwitchCon and you have
these huge Boston paws for hands and it personally intimidated me when you shook my hand
and stared straight into my eyes as you squeezed my hand way too hard
it's true uh big huge bucket I don't even know how to respond to that you just threw me
over the edge straight into my eyes what what thanks for the one dollar and yes I did meet
you at TwitchCon I did oh yeah you were swell you were swell dude it was great to hang out
but thank you pin thank you Tingy for the one dollar oh another thing the night Nova
raided you he had some really nice things to say I figured you should hear it
tonight I'm going to raid my main man Jerma because I never got to raid him and we played
with him ages ago eons ago and he's been absolutely destroying it on Twitch I actually
actively watch his stuff um he's really really funny everything that he does is great um
he will if you haven't seen any of Jerma's stuff I guarantee you he'll probably hook you in and
you'll probably continue to watch throughout the rest of the night I'd imagine if you're
looking for something entertaining um so we're gonna raid him he's really cool and I never
raided him before I'll see you guys next week next holy shit that was fucking yeah that was
an incredibly nice thing to say wow that I'm like floored right now that was that that's
unbelievable unless he's playing Kenshi come on you you had to say that you had to just say that
right now after that like 20 minute conversation about trying to make people happy and trying
to please everybody and people are bored and but now Nova Nova is you know back a long time
ago I used to watch his fucking YouTube videos he's like one of the he's one of those like
original still still doing it still having a blast still making people fucking laugh all these
years later so hearing that from somebody like him is that's unbelievable it's incredible
every time I ever watch something that he's that he always comes off as a fucking just
fun loving awesome dude so thank you for sharing that clip that that was if you're not following
Nova over hacks on Nova James if I absolutely do I would say the same thing uh about him so yeah
and you know that adds uh to kind of wrap up that conversation about how I don't want people
to be bored and how it it concerns me when chat is saying this I don't like this what the
fuck this is boring dude you know like it that like hearing shit like I want to make sure you're
entertained that's very important to me it's the most important thing and absolutely absolutely
I take that shit very very very seriously and I just imagine scenarios when people come over
and they something happens and they don't like it and they leave or something it's like fuck I
wish I could have convinced you otherwise but that's all I'm gonna say about it I'll see you
guys on Thursday I'm not even done what the fuck are you doing I'm out of here no no no no
no no no there's still like another 10 bits to read if you're worried about people being
bored wide then why do a poll in the first place I mean that's because I'm curious about
people want to see the reason for the polls is because I have a couple of ideas
and then you know most people whatever they think is they would want to see you know
but no I'm not I'm not gonna skip out I for some reason my brow is at the top
so I'm not skipping out on bits don't worry there's not very many more to do here anyway so
uh cherosophilia thanks for the one dollar also if you like this game we think you'd
really like rimworld I have 500 hours in it it's one of my favorite games it generates crazy
stories like the time I tried to replace someone's busted leg with a prosthetic
but I chopped off the wrong leg and she had to hop around on one foot for a few months
by the time my best sniper got his entire head bitten off by a lynx and then I re-grew it
good as new with some robo juice but his wife remained emotionally traumatized
I have heard I mean it's Alex plays a lot of rimworld and he talks about how it's
fucking hilarious and fun so maybe one of these days I'll load it up
rad Bruce thanks for the 10 dollars it's my man Evan's birthday can you give him a shout
out and tell him he's been a good boy this year absolutely happy birthday Evan you've been a very
good boy very good boy you deserve snacks and cookies and presents and shit thank you rad
briz for the 10 dollars happy birthday Evan FGWGWF thanks for the 10 dollars hey German just got
charged 80 dollars for bits when I only wanted to buy 20 because getting the error message
I have too many now that I think they need to like fix that if you know what I mean
that's not all right hopefully that can be resolved because that's kind of not cool
but thank you regardless for the 10 dollars rad Bruce thanks for 10 bucks another 1k for the
rat's birthday shout out for Evan happy birthday Evan the rats are in your house right now
in your toilet in the plumbing and you're probably under your bed too thank you so much
rad briz flug boy thanks for the 17 dollars hey German hope you're doing all right accidentally
bought 20 dollars worth of bits instead of five so here's a little extra tonight I would I would
not be um I would not be offended at all if twitch fixed this and you didn't that didn't
happen so hopefully that you didn't want that to happen that could be resolved because that's
that's what the hell is going on there is it a joke at this point I don't know if it is
I don't think it is drosophilia thanks for the one dollar also since you're not streaming
tomorrow I thought I'd say that it's that's my 21st birthday I've been struggling with depression
a lot this past year and you've helped bring me back to reality a lot of the time because
the green screen stream and your anticipation to see what people would make with it I created
almost a dozen things and I realized that I have a much greater drive to be creative
than I originally thought thanks for helping me discover that hell yeah thank you drosophilia
that was kind of the point of that whole thing and that's the point of the second
one that we'll do as well to have in the community dip down into their brains and come
up with stuff because I see you guys come up with some funny fucking shit all the time
interesting stuff all the time I'm so happy that that happened I am beyond beyond happy
I'm filled with joy that even one person got to get their creative juices flowing for a
little while I would love to do more stuff like that in the future so thank you take care
of yourself thanks for sticking around tingy thanks for the one dollar cheered this last
dream but I think stream labs ate my bits anyways the other night my friend and I were
watching a meme playlist when we came across this how many of these are there how many of
these are there thank you tingy uh piranha pit thanks for the one dollar do you ever miss
Massachusetts I live in lol and I'm thinking of leaving myself all the time uh all of some of
my closest friends and family members all live there so you know you miss it you miss it
sometimes for sure what that is 300 000 views holy shit I didn't even notice that
wow oh my god but no it's good to it's good to change things up every now and again
I lived in Massachusetts my whole life so it's the first time I've ever been away from New
England so I think it's a good change for now thank you germa is the best for the one dollar
do you ever try to learn another language if not what language would you want to learn
oh I think it's probably hard to learn a language at this point you have the easiest
time learning a language when you're a young kid and it's almost for me at least at this
stage of my life would probably be impossible for me everyone's watching it on repeat but if
I wanted to learn a language um that's really tough because it's probably like a bunch that
I would think would be interesting to learn and know to learn language in older age though
yeah he's been trying to learn English that's what those videos he keeps listening to are about
that's true um I don't know maybe like I can't even it's hard to even answer that
because that one answer is not right I'd probably want to know at least a couple of
European languages maybe be able to understand something like Japanese would be interesting
I don't know that's tough no no that's that's not why it's just I just would be interesting
I want to go to Tokyo one day so it'd be nice to maybe know and understand what
people are saying and read be able to read menus at a restaurant or something you know
by the way ladies and gentlemen no I'm not even going to announce this until Thursday's stream
I've got an announcement to make a big announcement I have watched my 2019 anime
big announcement coming up on Thursday and we're gonna have a conversation about it
and hey oh and I loved it I loved it uh thank you P337R for the five dollars they say hey man
seems good hey how you doing P337R how are you hope you have a great day great rest of your night
and a great afternoon P337R and that is the end of the bits except for one minute ago the one
Freeman gave two dollars hey Jerma are you aware of the concept of parasocial relationships
as a popular streamer I feel you'd have a unique perspective on the phenomena especially
after moving from YouTube to a platform with live interaction has been difficult to change your
relationship with chat as the channel has grown e.g. not being able to read subs chat going too
fast to interact with also do you make any conscious decisions to discourage the less healthy
interactions um I mean here's the the long and short of that I want everyone here to think
that they're part of a fun community right because I think they are I think hanging out
here hanging out in the discord making friends in the discord and being able to have a great
great time together is important but I think that there is I think there's a line
for at least for me because it's I it's so hard when I want to give personal attention
but I can't and even something like the end of the stream here is is is hard to do sometimes
just because of the fact that there's a lot more people and like you said chatted moves so
fast it's sometimes it's hard to even know what's going on but for the the main I guess
question that you're asking is discouraging a less healthy interaction I don't I don't think I
I don't think I do that I think that most of the time I collectively want to address everybody
as a community because once you if you start kind of having like a singling out people and
establishing uh what what some would call like a parasocial relationship with
a singular person or entity on the internet it's uh that that's not good both ways I think
because you know it almost takes that person out of what is the intent of this community is
and that's to have fun and enjoy everything together as essentially one large single entity
the hive mind and I look I'll be completely honest I'll be totally honest it's not it's
really not possible for me to even have that kind of relationship with a singular
person in the chat anyways it's not it's kind it's kind of impossible for all the aforementioned
reasons that you brought up I enjoy this community because we get to all experience it
together not because this one person or one small group or something that has to be the
group that is oh well like I'm here because of x I'm here because of y I'd rather everyone
just enjoy themselves and just be able to take their mind off of whatever they're currently
dealing with or if you're just kind of bored and you want to hang out and you want to just kind
of fuck around it's more fun that way it's a collective experience merchandise plans yes
they are the shirt so we'll be here in the next probably in the next week without a doubt
but thank you for the interesting question one freeman and yeah it's going from youtube to
twitch has changed a lot and it's it's still something I'm trying to deal with too
even though I've been doing this for a couple of years three years now total
it's uh it's it's always interesting but thank you thank you rad yourself for the one dollar
hey jerma just came to the realization that for the past week or two I've been doing
nothing but watching you non-stop when the stream is down I've been watching your sorcery
streams this is probably really unhealthy at any rate I recently got sorcery from myself and
I just got around to telling the time serpent to kill himself after making the water serpent
eat the sun serpent I'm surprised I never heard this weird fucking game until you
well first of all sorcery is probably one of the best games ever made
but also you know it's if you have time if you have free time and you like watching
something then that's there's nothing wrong with that you know there's not I don't I
I don't think there's anything wrong with watching something and enjoying something
as long as it's not negatively affecting you because if it is then you know you might consider
trying to figure out um some solutions as to how to not have something like that be a negative
influence but if you just if it's free time you're talking about and if it's if it's not
negatively affecting your life then I think I think that's fine but just be careful with
anything this stream included all time management and moderation of yourself is important
I would much rather and I know I know there's a lot of people that
would say oh I can't wait to stream again I'm gonna hang out here until you do right
that's incredible that to hear that somebody is that dedicated to this community
but just please take care of yourself first give time for yourself give time for you
allow yourself right because that kind of flows back into the but that question about
parasocial relationships just make sure you're taking care of you you all collectively take
care of me every fucking day so of course I want to make sure that you are taking
care of you too you know just stream less and now I don't like streaming way more than
I used to we're all yeah we're all you guys we're all just a couple of humans okay
he's making the parasocial stronger by saying that you guys get it you know what I'm trying
to say you know what I mean by this but that's kind of the end of the bits we have
the credits to roll no soup for you thanks for the one dollar and sir and sir tardigrad
thanks for the one dollar this is supposed to go with the other bits anyways hi I have
an exam tomorrow wish me luck good luck soup good luck to you and then thank you for the
one dollar also to sir tardigrad you should play gungeon on stream besides that loving
the kenshi and the irl stuff and the general vibes lots of love germa thank you you guys
are fucking awesome you guys are great sorry that the stream today after and you know what
it's kind of it kind of my own doing today because it did all like the crazy shit with
the irl and the voice changer and then it's like hey look I just like sang karaoke with
a fucking auto tune on and I pretended to be a monster in my closet you guys ready for
kenshi that's kind of my own doing as well I missed bits are you sure from from when how
long ago what how long ago because I have maybe bits are just all screwed up lately
mine was three minutes ago yeah I got an oven from you from three minutes ago I got
uh two minutes ago soup seven minutes ago and then elizabeth 10 minutes ago and they say
peepee poo poo oh wait no hold on hold on hold on this is all the way down here
all right yeah this is like this is down this got knocked all the way down okay so I
think I caught some of these here uh this is shawnee noodles for six dollars germa don't
worry about what your viewers want just keep it a good work by the way if you drink a gallon of
milk on stream I'll donate six thousand dollars keep your money buy something nice for yourself
take care of somebody else buy somebody buy like a nice thing for somebody I'm gonna
drink a gallon of fucking milk on stream and like puke that's not gonna happen trying to
kill me thank you for the six dollars though shawnee noodles
moo means moo thanks for the one dollar I was watching the stream with chatty muted and I was
so impressed with your ability to make such consistently funny and reusable jokes but then
I looked over at my screen and realized my mistakes anyway love you pop pop heed the warning
uh play a big d danny thanks for the two bucks missed the stream but still wanted to
keep say keep it the great work a bad germa stream is still a good stream although this
is not a bad this is not a bad stream I enjoyed myself during this stream very much so
from beginning to middle and then the end this is not I don't we're kind of what we're like
going through two or three different topics and kind of combining them in a bunch of strange
ways by no means that I not think this is I liked I just I had fun my concern was lying
with other people not having fun you know you know what I'm saying you know what I mean
he's finally done play somebody just wrote fuck him fuck him oh my god I know I'm not
gonna say that because that's I'm not gonna say that I just know I was reading what somebody
in chat said and I was very shocked by it that was the that was a shocked what the wtf
reaction hey dobski dude thanks for the one dollar germa you're just too damn nice you need to sit
chat down and tell them they can't have their made up bttv emotes and they have to eat their
kenshi veggies or they don't get to go to Disneyland caring but firm germa caring but firm
thank you dobski dude pin thanks for the dollar oh one oh shit I meant to buy one bit
to send to you but I accidentally bought a hundred times what I was gonna get so
here you go germa thank you moo for the one dollar just accidentally remortgaged
my house to buy bits amazon's really acting up tonight thanks a lot bezos
is it true that jeff bezos makes like six hundred thousand dollars a second
is that real is that a made up is it a meme okay so you know you know when you get to
in the ipad idling game like let's just use cookie clicker as an example you know you
get to like the end of the cookie clicker where you have like 40 a thousand 40 giant
factories making the cookies and like 10 000 fucking grandmas making the cookies
and you get to the point where you're just like this game's not fun anymore
what do I do that's where jeff bezos is right now he has like 10 000 cookie factories
and he's just staring at the screen I mean at some point I would probably just be like
oh god it would scare me that would be scary can you imagine how scary that would be if you
were making tens of thousands of dollars a second it would be like what do I do what
the fuck is happening what do I do what do I do am I gonna get in trouble am I gonna get
in trouble I would think I was gonna get in trouble you gotta do new game plus at that
point he makes a hundred ninety one thousand dollars per minute I would think I was going
to jail somehow I don't know how but I would think that like what do you do at that point
what do you what like do you do with that money let's okay like how much is a private jet
okay we're talking okay somebody figure this math out because I'm actually curious okay how
much does it cost for every major city in the country in the United States so we're talking
every capital city you know obviously we're talking about Las Vegas that's not even the
capital of Nevada by the way but that's like a fun place to be so if you got 50 capital cities
and you have a like a million dollar house in every state every capital that's 50 million
dollars right so if you have every you could get you could go anywhere you could get in
a car and just drive for like an hour and you'll end up at another million dollar house
yes that was good math okay so 50 million dollars for a house in every single city in
the country and then parked in the garages in those 50 51 million dollar houses are two
250 thousand dollar cars so you got 500 thousand dollars per 50 that's that's 2.5
million dollars no it's not it's 25 million dollars 25 million dollars so now you're at
75 million you got two of the best cars and you could ever have in every garage in 50 states
okay and if you want to fly around you get five private jets that are always fueled up ready
to go like 10 million dollars for a private jet 20 million dollars two four six eight ten
twelve four take day twenty two hundred million dollars so now you've got let's just say you got
like two hundred million dollars and you buy every week you buy five fifty thousand dollars
worth of food because you have to stock up all the fridges in your 50 houses five ten five
twenty that's five fifty thousand times fifty you got 50 fridges stocked with you know
that's fifty thousand dollars a week because every fridge has to be stocked with the finest
quality meats and cheeses oh and by the way you uh you buy a thousand dollars a day in lottery
tickets just for fun how much money is that in like 10 years that is not how being rich works
but yeah go off how do you live in all those houses i'm just taking the piss obviously i
just it's a i'm just an experiment wait i'm a finance major what's the question how much
is 50 houses 50 fridges with two cars at each 50 houses million dollars each how much does
that cost all right all right we're done i'm done fucking around point is jeff bezos has his
shitload of money if i had if i had five if i had 10 billion dollars i would have a fucking
lg 6200 water purifying dispensing fridge damn those things are like 20 grand they're
like stay like 18 grand for like a triple fridge with its own sectioned off water refrigeration
utility unit all right good night everybody good night i'm gonna stop fucking with everybody
filtered water a filtered water filter is like 40 dollars okay at the very end thank you pin
for the one dollar if jeff bezos turned all his money into pennies and flooded the entire
world with pennies and he would be the only human live human to live on earth with all his
have a great night everybody we're gonna let the credits play out here i will see you guys very
soon how many fridges could jeff bezos buy for all of his houses one for every room you could
have a hot tub in every room and a cooling tub in every room if you felt you know one day
you feel like i'm a little hot in this room just go in the cool tub is it a little too
cold in your room just go in the hot tub it's behind you every single room and have
just one room in your house that just has oxygen pumping into it so you can just walk in and just
breathe in there and there's a hot tub and a cool tub in that room too and and uh like 10
awesome cool pinball machines from like the 80s yeah just pump oxygen in there and have one of
like the one of those like five thousand dollar grills in that room too you feel like having
a steak that would be bad don't do that don't have a grill in a an oxygen room that would be
not good for you a house a house with a garden in it no the garden could be the house you
have another house right next to your other house and it's just a giant green like troll
house made it like a giant it's made into a giant legend of zelda tree that face
that's where you put your grill yeah there was a shitload of subs tonight thank you guys
so much honest to god soon i'm gonna be bezos with these subs you'll know if i get to that
level because there will be a fucking grill behind me and there'll be two hot tubs and
i'm gonna make like and by the way i'm gonna just make like fucking beef stew in one of
those hot tubs there's no one's even gonna go in one of those you could have a permanent
beef stew fixture in your house and you think that's bad that the world always bubbling
and boiling and shit you just like to get a ladle and go in there it'll be in one of the
fucking 25 rooms in your house i'm afraid you'll cancel the stream thursday because
you can't get 700 000 games to work no i will because i have i if if that doesn't work on
windows 10 then i'm going to use my windows 7 laptop and pull that footage through into
this computer so you that will strip that stream is going to happen but thank you everybody
kind of a long-winded end to the stream here sometimes we have to chat sometimes we just kind
of have to have a little chat see everybody's doing see how i'm doing too thanks for watching
as always thanks for participating and uh yeah i'll see you guys on thursday we're gonna go
thursday and friday have a great rest of your evening and yeah talax is streaming demon
souls you're right go see how good he's doing oh raid raid yeah take care guys see you soon