Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with some more Call of Duty Black Ops 2.
Now, this is the Zombies mode in Black Ops 2. This actually was very heavily requested that I do this, especially on Transit and especially by myself.
So this is a solo run. I'm gonna do the Transit mode like you're seeing, and I have no idea what's going on, by the way.
This is the first time I've ever, ever played Call of Duty Black Ops Zombies, ever. Never. Never done this, never.
So I have no idea what's gonna happen. All I know is I'm supposed to shoot these zombies, and when.
So we're gonna go with that. I don't know what to do. I've seen a couple videos on that. What the hell is that?
What? What, there's like power-ups in this mode? Cool.
Probably have limited ammo. I probably shouldn't just be shooting like six bullets at a time, but let's hope I don't screw this up.
Black Ops 2 zombies! Whatever this is, I'm buying it. Sweet.
So now what, we just like wait around and just like sit around? Whatever, I can do that.
Oh, power-up's running out. Power-up's running out. I gotta find somebody to shoot. Power-up! Oh, my power-up's blinking.
Blinking like an old Super Nintendo boss.
Well, come on in. Come on in, Joppies. There's a one-head shot.
What? What? That's it? I just lost. I just lost. I just lost right there. I got hit. Oh my god, that was terrible.
Oh, rebuild. Rebuild. Make sure there's nobody behind me, man.
I feel like I'm playing The Sims. It's like the same buying noise.
You buy like a sofa. All right, am I missing something here or no? It's just slow at first.
Anybody else out here? Which one of you zombie bricks want to take it to the face? Rebuild.
No! No! What? No! You put it where it didn't even come from!
Doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo-doo.
Jeopardy Baby Beatbox Edition. Where are the enemies? Oh, cool. You spawned like an enemy.
Oh, you're on fire. All right. I'm going to change position here.
Oh, what? What? This lady just came out of nowhere. Do they spawn behind you?
They spawn behind you! I'm going to lose! I'm going to lose on fire!
No! Wait! Wait! Time out! Grenade! Oh, eat grenades! Everybody eat a grenade!
Oh, Jesus! I'm still alive!
Oh my God, what's happening?
Okay, that was insane
You know what happened once I moved from my little area over here
It got crazy like I ain't moving from this spot again. I could promise you that anyone behind me
Get away from my spot. Get away from my little area
Oh, no, wait, wait, I'm not ready. I'm not ready yet. I'm not ready for this. Get away from me
So after the three fails in a row
I think I finally figured it out and we're gonna try and go for gold here and by gold
I want to at least make it to like wave five
Okay, I'll be like happy if I make it to like wave five or six or something
I just can't keep dying at like wave two. All right, we're at wave four. Where is this guy? Where is this guy?
I got I got some bullets. I'll be okay wave four. Oh, there they are. There they are
See ya. Uh, I don't really want a hug. You can take that out of here. You bastard
Do I have enough money for the smg? I think that's an smg. Pretty sure it is. Let's go get it times two
What what? Oh times two. Oh
Get exploded
Wow, they're coming in fast coming in hot coming in hot coming in hot coming in hot jump over. No
Not screwing this up again, you're not gonna like take this from me. I'm getting away five
You understand that you understand that lady?
I'm getting away five right now and i'm gonna be the master of call of duty black ops 2
I get this would be so much easier with like another person because you could all like
You can like talk to each other and know what's happening and know where you're going
And this is a bad place for me to be right now for sure. Yeah, I just killed myself
I think I need to be very very very
Oh my god, just eye of the tiger eye of the tiger I got out
I used eye of the tiger and I got out. Can you believe it? Yeah, everyone right there is done
Eye of the tiger that's like crawling. At least I got to wave five
That's all I wanted to get to wave five
At least uh, oh man. Well, thank you for watching. Ladies and gentlemen, I hope you enjoyed
Uh my black ops 2 pro- ow my elbow
Professional black ops 2 zombies with germa 985 make sure to like and favorite the video because of how awesome I did
No, but uh, seriously guys
Uh, thank you for watching. I'll see you all soon
And maybe i'll try this again with a different person so it's not just me getting my like ass kicked over and over again
But uh, yeah, thanks for watching. I'll see you all soon and take care everybody damn it