I'm here. Yes, I am. People saying he's not really here. Yes, I am early. No, I said I was gonna be here at one o'clock. We're here. I'm right here. Yay. Just give me a second. I'm crafting a tweet. I'm saying well, I look if you don't those of you that don't know what's going on, you can read the title. It's I mean, it's it's it's in the title. That's right. After crossing 1 million followers on Twitch, it's time to go back to sorcery. Oh, that's a good one. That's a good. That's a good tweet.
Actually, the reason why I'm here right now. Oh, what the heck just happened there? Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. Hold on. I might have changed servers. Hold on. Let's just make sure that was just a quick little fluke. I might have to change servers real quick. Do I have to change servers? Let's see. That's not a good sign. Let's hope that was a fluke. Just check one thing. Yeah, but hello. I don't like this. I'm already seeing some some frame problems with this.
There's ingest server. See, there's only been one problem so far. Yeah, but that's a that's a bad sign. Let's chill for like 10 minutes. Because I really don't. This is my 1 million Twitch follower stream. I don't want it to be messed up by a bunch of F's. This is this is the stream. This is the stream for a million Twitch followers. We got to make sure this doesn't happen. We'll see. If I have to change servers, I change servers, right? That's how I usually fix it. Anyways. Hello. How are you doing?
Something very important is going to happen today. Those of you that have been around for a long time know that I used to. Well, hold on. Let's just give it a let me. Okay, I'll be right back. I don't want to do my 1 million follower speech before a million people are here. I want to make sure this is not going to happen. All right, give you two seconds. How are you doing? Is it still having problems? I think I'm going to change servers. Yeah, it's I'm dropping more frames. My 1 million follower stream. It says I dropped more frames.
It says I've dropped 400 frames so far, which is 2% of every frame. You're ruining my speech. Is it all right? Is it okay for now? If we have to switch, I'll switch in a minute, right? It should be fine. You think I can? Should I just do it? Let's see if we can write it out.
Dude, you brainwashed a million people. Okay. On the viewer end, we're not really seeing it. Really? Okay. It's clearly showing up on my OBS. So I'm just making sure it's not a problem. Whatever. We'll write it out and see if it works.
I'm gonna make my I got to tweet this out and then I'll talk about it. Okay, so for those of you that are new viewers, maybe you've been here for a year, maybe two years. I used to be a YouTuber. I was just on YouTube. I didn't stream. I still have a little bit of a problem here with my with my voice and throat. So just want to make sure you're aware of that too. But those of you that don't know, I used to be on YouTube. I have two like YouTube channels at this point. Second German German 95.
I was on YouTube for like six years or whatever it was. Do the speech in the tuber voice. No. Wow. No, who cares? Nobody cares. I care. And that's you know what, I'm gonna do it. Somebody give 100 subs. What the fuck? Thanks for the 100 subs. That was matters of darkness. I don't shout out subs, but that's a lot. Just breaking my own rule. I just looked over and saw it. Okay, you're doing it again. All right, not shouting it out. No more shouting out subs. That's a that's way too many. I'm gonna I don't do this. I won't shout out subs anymore. So I'm not going to
do it because that's that's a that's a crazy amount of sub that I'm not gonna do it again. Thank you though. Thank you to anybody that subs to this channel, regardless if it's one or 100. Okay, so I was a YouTuber. And I took the plunge moved over to Twitch. And on Twitch pretty much ever since obviously the second channel has edits and everything right. And there's that. But the first thing I did when I came over to Twitch was you know what, I'm gonna play my one of my favorite things of all time. And one of my favorite things
of all time is sorcery. It's one of the first I think it is the first actual stream I did when I said I'm going to go like full time on Twitch. So after crossing a million followers, we're going back in. We're going to start at part one. It's been like six or seven years. I like to actually play this game anyways, every five years or so because the game is so fun. And there's so much weird shit you can do. And if you don't know what sorcery is, listen to me. It's required
reading for this stream. Let's go over required reading for German 985 for you to be a viewer. You have to have seen every earnest movie twice. You have to be on record saying that Gremlins 2 is better than Gremlins 1. You have to have seen the first at least two Ghostbusters movies. What do you mean we have homework? This is just the way it is. You're gatekeeping. This is this is the way it is. You have to have beaten Glover for the Nintendo 64. That's a fake one. You have to have made at least one dirt house
in Minecraft. Don't tell me what to do. What a consumerist. And you got to go do sorcery. Or just watch this, right? You can just watch it. Let me just tell you something that I the reason why I thought to do this. This didn't. This didn't kind of jump out after a million followers. I mean, I was thinking about what I wanted to do for a million followers. What the hell would I even do? I was probably not gonna do anything. That is a little F. We actually might have to restart it and go to a different server. I'm paranoid by this bullshit. All right, I
know I'm out. I'll see you in a minute. I'll be right back. I'll be right back. I'll be right back. I'll be right back. Don't go anywhere. I'm gonna get it. I gotta get this is gonna be a huge problem for like the next seven hours. I'll be back. Don't leave. It's for a million. Don't leave. I'll be right back. Let's try this again. Let's try this again. I changed servers. Hopefully this fixes it. We don't have any more frame problems. Look, I am not late. Did anybody leave? How many of you left? Did you leave? Hopefully nobody left. It's been 45
seconds. My friend just left. Well, give him a ping and say, Hey, Draper985 is back. All right. So where was I? Let me tell you. Where was I? What was it? Oh, yeah. Wait, it says I've been streaming for 12. Have I been live this whole time? Was it just on like the disconnect like not like this thing? Really? Oh, no. Okay. All right. So again, let's go over this again. Sorcery is one of my favorite things of all time. It's a choose your own adventure book that was turned into
a game by this company called Inkle. I have a video on this game from like seven years ago or whatever. I played this game on Twitch. You know the deal. We're back in it for a million followers on Twitch. And if you don't know anything about this game, do you know what to look much up? Don't look anything up about it because we're going to do it again. It's a choose your own adventure book by Steve Jackson. It is fucking unbelievable. And guess what? I wanted to do this for a million followers, but oddly enough,
the completely coincidentally almost because I was thinking about what again when I say what I want to do for a million. They Inkle released it again. There's the complete edition exists now. And I think they put it on all the consoles. Because it used to be it was on iPad and on Steam and shit, right? But you can get this on Xbox now. They re-released it. So that's kind of cool. You don't have to get it on an iPad or get it on Steam. You can get it on Xbox and stuff now too. I was like, holy shit. Well, I mean, why does
people just talk about that? But anyways, I'm very excited. I'm it's been a long time since I've done this and I'm gonna get into it. You better believe it. Stas is from this game. It's choose your own. There's gonna be lots of drama people. I'm expecting to see lots of hog champs. I'm expecting to see lots of what the holy shit. What the fuck, dude? It's gonna be crazy. It's gonna be crazy. But I do know that after a while, we'll see how people
like it. If people want to keep doing it after the first and second part, then I'm going to keep doing it because let's we can do the whole thing, right? Are you guys ready? Are you guys ready to get to do sorcery back to sorcery? I don't I'm not seeing enough excitement in this chat room. I'm seeing a lot of I'm seeing a lot of like, dude, just watch the earnest movies. I'm not seeing enough excitement here to turn this on. I'm saying, dude, go watch earnest saves Christmas like pog. Like, why don't you just get the right buy the rights to it? It can't be more than a few hundred grand. I
I don't know that I could be inaccurate. So don't I don't know why you're saying that they could but I don't know how much the rights are to the whole franchise. It's probably in like the fucking 10s of millions. Okay. Are you ready? This is like my favorite game of all time. This is like the my favorite thing ever. It's like in the top five stalling I am stalling because I just had to turn my stream off and like 5000 people left. I gave everybody the opportunity. It's like, oh, germ is live. All right, click it. Oh, germ is not live time to go do anything else.
Oh, no, I'm gonna go watch somebody else that doesn't have internet problems. That guy German high five sucks. His internet sucks. No, it's not my internet. It's fine. Start already. I hold on. You ready? You guys ready? Ladies and gentlemen, it's time to begin Steve Jackson's sorcery.
You have walked the wilds of Kakabad, Bukkare and the spiky backlands all the way into Mampang. You survived traps, thieves, serpents, vengeful gods. And now it is here. The crown of kings. Let's go. Let's freaking go. It is said that the crown was never forged only found by Kalana the reformer, a lowly foot soldier who became emperor of the
eastern world, such as the power of the crown. The air around it crackles with influence. Okay, chat. So should I take it or should I wait? Did I take the crown or should I wait for a little bit? Take it. Your destiny awaits with the crown in your hands, you will be as powerful as Kalana. The goblins are arming the giants awake and the birdmen carving cruel daggers from stone. War will come, but you will prevent it. Then the image of the crown begins
to flicker. You rush forward. It's a trap. And startle yourself awake. You are alone, exhausted, in a little hut in the outpost settlement. Your unimaginable journey is not even a single step beyond.
I'm so excited. Inkle presents. Sorcery. Yeah, I got no cam on. I figured cam off, right? Part one, the Shumatanti Hills. Are you ready to get obsessed with this? All of the people in the chat right now understand something. This is required reading. Turn this up a little bit too, so we get some cool sound effects. All right, so this is me. Here's the map. Yeah, something about sorcery that you need to know. Cam on. No, cam off. Cam off. Cam off. It breaks the
immersion. Cam off. It breaks the immersion. You know what I mean? It breaks. It breaks the immersion. We'll do cam off. I'll turn it on periodically. But so the thing about sorcery is this is this is not like a lot of other choose your own adventure things that you see nowadays. Steve Jackson literally made like a hundred million different things you can do. There's so many different things to do here that I've played this game three or four times through all the way. Every five every like three or four years or so, right? I still don't think I've seen everything. And I'm
going to go for it again. This is the original Elden Ring. It kind of is just when you think it's that's the end. Oh, just wait. Here we go. I'm going to get into this. Hope you're ready. It is sunrise. You dress breakfast on bread and goat's milk and collect the pack and sword from beside your bed. Test the blade. Pray for luck or leave the hut. F. Why do computers suck? It's fine. It's going to be fine. Don't worry. Don't worry. Computers suck. Just everybody
repeat after me. Computers suck. We're going to let it ride out for a second. I've changed servers like three times. That's getting worse. God damn it. Right after the intro. You can't do this to me, Twitch. Come on. Hold on. Let me do this right for a second. Let me just run a test because my internet every time this happens, my internet is perfect. And I will run a test to Twitch overnight and into the day that has zero drop frames. It's just for some reason, some of these servers just can't fucking handle
the traffic for some reason. I literally have a thousand, a thousand up and down right now. I'm doing it right now. I'm looking at it right now. All right. Whatever. I'm going to go for it. It's just it's just the way it is. Computers suck. Yeah. You're going to get a huge F right now because I'm doing a speed test. It's just locked in at one thousand one thousand. Whatever. Hopefully it evens out. All right. Please even out. Don't do this to me. Come on, Gwen. Really? Anyways, as we were saying. OK. Classic. This is the classic Jerma Stream experience.
You know what? That's actually true. It's definitely an issue connecting to this server. This one, too. You want to know the crazy thing? I'm going to tell you guys the secret. Remember last time this happened and I was like, I'm going to try a different server. Do you know what server worked? It gave me zero problems, literally zero drop frames. I connected to the Mexican server. I literally connected to Mexico and it fixed it. That's how I fixed it last time. Shit. This is getting worse now. Oh, my God. I'm going to have to tell me if it gets bad and I'll fuck it up.
I'm going to fucking try it again. Pain in the ass. Like sometimes I just want to like hook up like 16 like SIM cards to my computer and just like beam down Internet here in case this happens every day.
I mean, what am I supposed to do here? All right. Here we go. Go to the Mexican server. Why don't I switch to Mexico? Because it doesn't work anymore. You know, and the most frustrating thing about this, I streamed literally two days ago without a single problem.
I have perfect speed tests, but I can't connect to these Twitch servers on the West Coast. What the fuck? It's very, very frustrating. I will tell you. I'm just going to go for it. Oh, well, turn it off and turn it on again.
I already did that and I changed wherever server I was going to. It might get better or it might get worse. We'll just look. Let's just sit here and talk about a million followers. It's probably your attitude.
But it's just my like I have a shitty attitude. All right, here we go. Fuck it. We're just going to go. If it drops, it drops. I'm going to test my blade. Okay, you pause to test the blade against your thumb. The blacksmith has done well.
The edge is keen and it draws a narrow line of blood outside the hut. You hear the outpost settlement stirring into life. So praying in this game is interesting. You have a god that you pray to right now. It's the panther. It can change.
And it will over the course of the of the game, right? I don't want to use it because you can only use it once a day. By the way, you have health, you have money and you have food. You need to be very careful with these. It's time to go. I don't want to. I don't want to pray.
Time then to depart. You lift back the flap of the hut and step into the early morning sunshine. So as we continue as we play, you're going to see flags are going to appear for places that we can go. It's not always as simple as going in a straight line. The outpost settlement.
Eyes follow you as you leave the hut and walk towards the great Schumatante wall. The frontiers people of this tiny settlement are well aware of your mission. Greet them? Let's greet them. You turn. Oh, and we've got these amazing pictures. I forgot about this. The artwork is by Ian Livingston, by the way. It's awesome. It's so interesting and scary. There's a lot of crazy artwork in this game.
You turn to them and bow, some smile and reply, but are too afraid to approach. Others make gestures of protection. You are going beyond the wall, so they believe you to be cursed. A man is waiting on the path to the Cantapani Gate, the final doorway between Analand and the wilds of Kakabad. You recognize the Sergeant of the Sightmaster Warriors. He holds out his hand.
Greetings, Sergeant. Get out of my way. Wait, what? Wait, what? There you go. You got it. You got it once. All right. Greetings, Sergeant. Greetings, Sergeant.
Take the whole thing, and I have a lot of money. I could take half. I'm going to take the whole thing, because that's just what I wanted. You accept the gift graciously. Thank you. You should buy some supplies before you pass the wall, Sergeant says. And you must collect your spell book if you wish magic to aid you. Finally, should you wish to practice your swordplay, I will go one last round with you. And he points with his staff towards the training ground. So something that's interesting to note about this, for those of you hardcore gamers, you can, I believe you can just not do this.
And not be able to cast spells through the whole game. So that's kind of like stupid. See, like you could just one one of the huts set slightly back from the others is decorated with glyphs and strange symbols. A terrible smell emanates from its doorway. This is the hut of the chief mage. He's been preparing your spell book for days, reading star charts to work out which spells will be available to you in the different locations in the hills and beyond. Go inside. I need the book. I ain't doing this for
the book. You lift the flap and go inside. The mage looks up at you with haggard, sleepless eyes and presses the book into your hands. You understand how to use this? He asks. I do. I actually do. And I can tell you guys how to do it. But I do understand how to do it. I will show you in just a moment. Just very moment here. Yes. The mage nods. Good. He scratches absently at his ear. Remember, some spells will cost you effort to use. But the ones that don't will not work without a focus. An item
of some kind. You will need to read the book to know what. Okay. Research magic using the spell book. So here's the thing about sorcery. Computers suck. It's gonna happen. I wish there was something I could do about it. But I am at the mercy of the internet working perfectly to turn a live stream on most of the time. You know what I mean? It's just we're at the mercy of this. We're fine. It's gonna be all right. So why don't we open this up and listen to one of my favorite songs? Hopefully it's not too loud, but let's go. Let's see the spell book. So in sorcery,
in almost every scenario, in almost every single scenario, it'll give you the opportunity to cast a spell. The spells range from zapping people, shooting fireballs out of your hands, floating, putting walls up, controlling non-intelligent creatures, making them stupid. Yeah, there's a ton of stuff you can do. I don't know how Steve Jackson sat here and came up with all these potential scenarios to write out and have different ways to go. But some of them you need actual materials, right? You need, for instance,
gob. Someone's a goblin. And some really, really fun, funny shit can happen. You guys know that you've seen it before. Where's Sus? Let's find it. Come on. Let's get nostalgic here. Where is it? Come on. Where is it? Did I pass it already? There it is. This is Sus. This is sense danger. This is not somebody being suspicious. This is where that comes from on this channel. You know why? Because I would cast this fucking spell every five minutes because I was terrified of everything. I would be like, boom, look to the stars and be like,
sense danger. What's wrong? Maybe casting the caster suspects a trap and it will indicate telepathically to the caster if the danger and the best protective action. If already trapped, this spell may be used to minimize the effect in certain cases. This is Sus. This is what it is. It's not the Sus guy. I know it has two meanings for you all, but I'm going to buy some rations because it's very important. I'm so excited. I really hope the internet holds up because this is like, I'm so ready for this. Small traders in the settlement supply the site master warriors with weapons, armor, food, and clothing. You go over.
With the sergeant to a stall selling flatbreads and cheese, two gold paces per ration. The owner says, two boys, Andy, two boys, Andy. Let's haggle. You know who I am? I'm Anna land's greatest hero. You tell him the man looks uncomfortable. I know that. But I have to feed my family today. Whatever happens to the crown. I want to actually should probably buy a lot. You check your pack. There's room for plenty inside. I'll take four. I'll take six. I don't want to spend all my money. Maybe I should just spend all my money here. I'll take four. Four rations is eight.
Gold paces, the man says, holding out a hand. It's too much. I just say it's too much. You're just going to lose him. Is it too much? Should I try to haggle? It's too much. The man shrugs and begins to pack away his stall. All right. Wait, wait, wait. I'll take two. I fucked it up. I'll take two. You hand over your coins and the man places two rations carefully into your pack. You must be sure you eat every day or you'll suffer. The sergeant points at the other guy that was talking and says, that's what you said. Standing
at your side, eating more will give you extra strength, but it's not necessary. This is just tutorial stuff. We have to go to the training grounds. I'm going to explain how fighting works because yes, you fight in this game. There's battling. It's like a fighting system. There's combat. Get excited. You walk with the sergeant to the training ground and he wraps the base of his staff in leather. Ready my sword. Here we go. To begin, the sergeant says, we will practice the stances. First, defend yourself against me. How this works is you can either defend and take one damage or try to
overpower the other person. It's simply a numbers game, right? So let's say I decided to defend. I will always take one damage no matter what. If I get hit, turn the volume up, turn the volume up. It's a little too low. The problem is the sound mixing is not fantastic. So it will be some stuff is a little too, the music's a little too loud. So just be ready for music being loud. All right. So yeah. So if I defend right here and he attacks, right? We both defended. So nothing happens. It's pretty much like a rock paper scissors almost. The site master is a powerful enemy by defending. You will receive the
minimum damage from any attack he makes. Sight master sergeant defends himself as well. The round is a stalemate. I will now defend myself. Whatever attack you play will damage me, but a strong attack will use up more power. Choose a weak attack. So again, if I swing with one power and he defends, he's going to take one damage. If I swing with nine power and he defends, he still takes one damage. You always want to and if he attacks and I attack at the same time, it's just based on who has the
higher number of power to the decimal. That's who takes the damage, right? So he's going to, I, he's, he said he's going to defend. I'm going to give him a little swing. It's going to do one damage. It'll always do one damage. All right. My next attack is going to be weak. You will be able to overpower me by playing a stronger attack, but be sure your attack is stronger, right? It has to be stronger. So if I do four, he did 1.8 bingo. You took two damage now. So what happens is when I swing for four, I lose four on the bar.
For the next turn, that's how it works. That's how it works. Here we go. All right. My next attack is going to be medium strength, but you will be able to overpower me. So let's go for it. Let's do the whole thing. And there he goes.
Oh my God, my head. Oh my God, my fucking brain. Oh my God, my fucking head. That went into my brain. Okay. I didn't, I tell you about the sound mixing was off and I tried to make that clear that the sound mixing be careful.
Yeah, that's what I'm talking about. The ear wig exploded. Okay. You play a strong attack. There he goes. All right. Enough training. I'm ready to do it. Here we go. You shake your head. Very good. The sergeant agrees. But if you wish about an earnest and I warn you, I will not go easy on you. He indicates the wider yard where there is a space for a true match.
Um, Joe, I don't think I really need, I don't want to, I don't run. I don't have to fight him. Oh, Ernest, the most powerful Avenger. You want to do a true match. All right. I'll do it. Fine. Let's just so you can see how it works.
Let's go. Not going to tell you my intentions. So here's what we're going to do. We're going to go with a medium attack. Let's see if we get him. Fuck. And this is why I didn't want to do this. This is literally the reason why I didn't want to do this.
Cause now I have, I have 17 health. Does he heal you after? All right. All right. You can sometimes get an indication if you read what they're doing here. Sightmaster bows to you, taps the ground with his long staff, takes his position. You rush him quickly, conserving your energy while still delivering a great power behind your blade. The Sightmaster Sergeant comes in with a tough blow, balancing his strength and his impact. He slips the foot of his staff neatly under your blade. Yeah. All right. Let's go full power. Fuck it. There we go. Okay. Now I have to be careful, but he doesn't, he doesn't have much either.
You see his grip change on the heel of his staff as he readies himself to strike again. All right. Let's go full blast again. Yep. Just got him. Cool. His breath begins to heave. He is struggling to stay upright. He changes his grip to hold the staff more loosely. He seems to be preparing for a simple jab. Chance to overpower him. Do I have enough though? Oh, God damn it. I'm losing so much health already. He faints left. All right. I'm going to defend. Oh, fuck you. Now we go full blast. Okay. We're good. I got it.
Acting quickly, you slash violently across his chest. It is enough to finish him. The Sightmaster throws down his staff. You have me. You have me. Six to him and a loss. Shameful. Oh, he does heal you. We're fine. Everyone shut up. Shut up. Shut up.
So if you have a chat delay right now, pause the stream and hit play again. Like do refresh the stream because that'll fix it because the frame drops that we had. I think we're still having them periodically, but it's all right.
Okay, the Sergeant is gasping for breath. He bows to you once more. You are too slow, he declares, shaking his head. I will tell the King to ready another champion for you will not survive long. As he talks, a nearby healer hurries over with a salve in your health and the Sergeant is quickly restored.
All right. Time to go to the gate. You reach the foot of the mighty gate. It is sealed. The Sergeant places one hand on the wood. The gate has been locked for some time to deter raiders, he tells you, but you will have no difficulty.
Stars in this place allow the dot spell to be crafted and he stands back. It's time to cast our first spell. So again, the way this works. So you have to spell out a spell and in any scenario with a spell, you get potentially a few options, five options, two options, 10 options.
Sometimes it really depends. So what I have available to me right now is these letters first, right? You have to spit a three letter word. So I could I could zap the door. So it's uh, but this is going to take three health and it's going to be a disaster. Okay, this is going to be a
fucking disaster. Like, let me just be honest with you. Um, there's also, I could do hot probably. Hot is throw a fireball. I'm probably going to kill somebody. Did I, I don't, I don't think I've ever done this before. Yeah, I know. All right. I'm going to throw a fireball at the fucking
door. You cast the spell winding a fireball around your palms. Then you release it at the door. The great wooden gate explodes in a flash of light. Sightmaster laughs grimly. We will have to rebuild that before the goblins raid us. But I am pleased to see you have power.
My apologies. Be assured I do or be silent before I blast you too. Why would I say that? I like this guy's like a friend. This guy's one of my friends. No, be assured. I do have power. Sergeant bows to you.
A fucking waste of time. By the way, that was three health. I think Dopp is one. Let's go through the gate. Together you step into the wreckage of the gate. One last word, he declares. When you have the crown, find the highest point you can find. We will be watching.
Watching from where? From here. The Sightmaster warriors are selected from birth for their incredible powers of telescopic vision. You do not know how far he can see. What lies ahead? This path leads to Kanthapani, settlement of traitors. Though most are rogues and thieves. You should be there before the sun has reached its peak. From there, three routes lead on to Krista Tanti. But no single route is safe. Kakabad is a land of devils. Enough talking. It's time to go.
Striding away, you pass through the gate. The faces of the folk watching your departure reveal the hopes that the- rest on your- I'm a terrible actor! The faces of the folk watching your departure reveal the hopes that rest on you and your quest. The early morning air is crisp, and the rising sun paints the slopes in shades of peaceful beauty, concealing the evil that lies ahead. On to Kakabad. It's time to begin the actual game. Are you guys ready for this? That was tutorial bullshit. This was tutorial bullshit.
Choices actually matter. There is a rewind feature, although people get mad when I use it. Let's fucking go. I'm- let's go, alright? Fuck the internet problems. This is the- let's go. It took us 30 minutes to get here, but I'm ready. And I'm here all day. Let's go. I'm actually really excited. On to Kakabad.
The path winds through slopes of wild scrubland. The countryside is deserted and the eerie silence is broken, only by the cawing of the occasional crow. The birds appear to pause in the air to examine you as they pass. They make you uneasy, as if you were an intruder in their presence.
Barely an hour beyond the wall, and the air begins to grow foul. The Sumatanti Hills are infested with the pestilence of the Baklans. It saps the energy from your body, leaving you feeling nauseous and weak. Cover my mouth.
You cover your mouth with your neck scarf, but it does no good. They warned you of this. You will grow accustomed to it the longer you are here, but for the moment you must be very careful. Your maximum stamina has just decreased. You can see your stamina at the top of the screen. If it reaches zero, you die.
Stamina can be regained up to maximum by eating rations or resting. But yes, you die. This is how you die. And tons of things will kill you in this game. This is not safe.
Alright, first real choice of the game. We're going to let's take a look. We can take the road to Kantapani, but we can cross up through this Kantapani gate area and head up through this field area over here. Or we go this way. What do you think?
Should I stay on the road? Do click maps? I don't think we should do click maps. I think that might take a little too long. For really big major decisions, I think we could probably run poles that are like 30 seconds long, right? I'm going to stay on the road. A low rise road.
Another hour passes and you crest a small hillock, from the top of which you can see the path continuing downwards into a small settlement of huts. This must be Kantapani. Look at the village. Look for a way around or move on. Look at the village.
From this distance, all you see on the town is its poverty. The fields on either side are brown with caked mud, and the few penned animals are thin and wizened like thirsty vines. No wonder the site master warriors don't trouble themselves to protect this place. There's nothing here to protect.
Should we avoid the village or should we go into the village? What do you think? What do you think? Village, village, village, village, village, village, village. Go, go in, go in, go in, go in. Alright, let's go in. Of course. Let's make it so you can hear some of this stuff. I'm going to try to make it so it's not super loud when it changes, but be aware that it could get loud.
Of course, if you were scared of a town like Kantapani, then you could not hope to survive in Kakabad proper. You follow the path down into the town, obviously.
The round huts are made of a hard baked bright clay, and the roofs are thinly thatched. As you pass, eyes appear at dark doorways, tracking your every move. For a moment, it seems like this will be all you see of the town's inhabitants, but then a villager appears from one of the dwellings and blocks your path.
Look at him, threaten him, push him out of the way, or cast a spell. Here comes the zaps, right? Just, you want me to palpatine hands everybody I see? We can't just do a carbon copy playthrough of the one we did six years ago.
We can't just palpatine hands every person in the game. No, we can't do that. Threaten him. Alright, how about we just look at him first? We don't know who this is. We don't know what this person is. We don't know what they're capable of. We don't know why they're here.
They're standing in the road. Look at him. He is five feet tall. They cannot grow much taller out here, in this poisonous air. He has thick set arms and thighs, and is half clothed in tattered breeches. His eyes are wild, and his long red hair and beard stand out from his face in a wiry tangle.
Hot, stranger, he commands. What business you have in Canterpani. I want to buy equipment. I'm merely passing through. I need directions. I'm a hungry traveler and need to eat. It's just you. I don't have a beard. Alright, what do you think?
But how about just like, oh, I need directions, right? Or I need equipment. I got money. I want to buy equipment. He grunts, but you can see that he is pleased. With emotion, he encourages you to follow, taking you through the village to a large hut, into the storage house.
Inside you find that the building is a storage house. A quartermaster, somewhat flumper than your guide, is seated at a table. No, am I going to kill this guy? I'm going to wait to be introduced.
This man here to do business, the villager explains. Get out of here, fruity. The fat man replies, getting up from his seat to hustle the villager out. Then he turns to you with a smile and beckons you to sit. Greetings, stranger. Shall I show you my wares?
Please, do you treat your customers so roughly? Same voice. Yeah, whatever. Please, please show me your wares. The man wags a finger. Wait there. He disappears for a moment into a side room. Search the room or just wait for him. What if he has cameras?
There might be cameras literally everywhere. While the man is out of sight, you quickly rifle the nearby shelves but find nothing except for a small vial of potion. Take it. You pick up the vial. It is quite full and stoppered by an old cork, but there's no label to indicate what it might be.
Smell it or put it in your bag. Smell it. You slip back the stopper to take a cautious sniff. The smell is truly appalling and you seal it up again. Glimmberry? But what is it used for? The merchant returns carrying a large box.
For you. He declares moving his hands as he speaks. You've come to the right place. This collection is the very best. Our most strange and interesting artifacts. Collected from other travelers who've come this way.
He begins to lay the items in front of you, treating each with great care. You have 20 gold pieces to spend, but is there anything here you'd really want to buy? A musical pipe? A weapon? A leather bag? Or a jewel?
What was that sound? What the fuck was that? A musical pipe? This actually is kind of important so maybe let's run a poll. 1, 2, 3, or 4. Do like a 30 second poll because this actually is important I think. Pipe, pipe, pipe, pipe, pipe. What about jewel though? Jewel could be good.
I'm so happy that I'm sitting here right now. This is bringing back so many memories. I don't even remember doing any of this but maybe I did. I don't know. It's been like 7 years. I can't wait to continue with this.
How's it look? Pretty unanimous that we're going to go with one. Give it another 5 seconds or so. Musical pipe. Do I even have enough money to do this? Yeah, that's unanimous. Alright, we'll buy in one. Thank you for participating. A musical pipe.
You pick up a bamboo pipe off the table carved with a split reed and 6 finger holes. 3 gold pieces, the merchant says. That's so cheap. Never mind, we can buy everything. I can't promise you that it has any magic, but it may well cheer you up at night. Play it.
You place the pipe on your lips and blow a few clear sweet notes. The merchant nods. It's a well made little thing, don't you agree? I just put it through my mouth and went like pew. He handed 3 gold pieces and he thanked you with a nod. You place the pipe into your bag. Please. The merchant says. Something else today.
You still have 17 gold pieces. How much is the jewel? Shreemur's choice. You reach greedily for the large jewel in the center of the box, but he stays your hand. Please, hey. It's too valuable to allow you to handle. 10 gold pieces.
I have no use for valuable things. Look closer at the jewel or pay him. Look closer. You lower your eye to the table to peer more closely at the gem. It is clear, glassy, and its surface seems to be slightly sweating. If it is worth as much as you might hope, it could be useful for bargaining. Or you could keep it for yourself.
Dragon's tears. The merchant says. Never heard of such a thing before? It's an ice cube. Is it actually an ice cube? I don't remember. Did I ever go in this hut? It's literally an ice cube. But is it though? What if it's a magical ice cube?
Alright, I won't buy it. No, I will not take it. The merchant nods. Very wise, I'm sure. He replies and puts the jewel carefully away. Very good. The merchant says, padding his money pouch. You're a man of good judgment, I see. What else?
About a weapon. What weapons do you have? The merchant looks at you carefully, sizing up what kind of customer you are, the kind to place a newly bought dagger against his neck, or the kind to tip him for the quality of the blade. But he must see your honor shining through as he wags his finger once more, and then collects an axe and a fine broadsword from another corner of the shop.
These are both treasures, as well as deadly weapons of war. Sure you'll agree?
Broadsword or axe? I mean, we gotta go axe, right?
You lift the axe from the table, the head is carved with symbols in a familiar language, but the quality of the shaft and head indicate that the axe is well used and may not last many more battles.
Seven gold pieces, declares the merchant.
I mean, this thing's messed up, right? You give him this as a shitty axe, it's had a lot of wear, I don't think it's worth that much.
That price is too high for this, you reply. I'll give you five. The merchant looks uncomfortable, but eventually, with a glance around his large storehouse in this empty, unvisited village, he agrees.
Very well. Five. But it is my children who will suffer for it.
I'll take it, you reply, nodding once, you give him five gold pieces, put the axe into your pack.
Please, take your time.
Keep looking.
I don't want to blow through all my money. Let's look at the leather bag. You lift a bag from the table and its contents rattle.
Teeth, the merchant replies, showing his own a little.
Minus creature teeth. Three gold pieces, too.
What kind of creature? You ask, goblins, giants, or mole rats?
All sorts, the merchant replies.
I couldn't tell you myself, I'm no expert. But there's ten or twelve in there for three gold pieces, that's a good price.
It's a good price, I'll take it. I won't buy teeth without seeing them. It could be goblin teeth in here, I'll take it.
You hand over three gold coins and take the bag of teeth.
The merchant nods, then begins to pack his box away once more.
I must save at least something for my next customer.
He replies with a smile.
But perhaps you will return this way and it'll be you.
You get to your feet and take your leave from the merchant.
Just outside the doorway in the sunshine, you pause to examine what you have acquired.
Let's examine the carvings on the axe head.
You'll tilt the axe head in sunshine to read the carvings on the metal.
This axe was crafted in the year of the ox...
Alright, there's like a pig talking to me.
This axe was crafted in the year of the ox for Glandragor the Protector.
Its powers may be realized only by its owner.
Interesting.
Look in the bag of teeth.
You open the drawstring bag and sift through the contents.
It's quite an assortment.
There are three teeth from an ape, four from a goblin, two from a snatacat, and a large molar from a giant that is the size of a ripe plum.
That's pretty good. That's pretty good.
We got some materials now, but I ran out of money.
You head out of Cantapani and along the path into the Shumatanti Hills.
We did it. Pass Cantapani.
Passing the outlying huts, you feel strangely uneasy.
Hissings from within and sly faces disappearing from doorways make you feel decidedly unwelcome.
Then at the edge of town, you pass a large boulder, and at once two rough-cut villagers spring out with swords drawn.
Bandits.
It's two against one, the first declares.
You lost, calls the other.
So hand over your things, come on.
Hand over your backpack.
Reason with them or deal with them.
Imagine handing over your whole backpack.
I wonder what this does. This must do something.
Deal with them.
You draw yourself to full height.
You have mistaken me for someone else.
I would like to give you a moment to reconsider, because I will kill you if I have to.
The bandits growl and advance on you, one on either hand.
We have LAW, which is control non-intelligent creatures.
Are they stupid enough to control?
Jig.
Cause lively dancing and I have the flute.
I could make them dance.
What else do we got?
Ball.
No, no, no. What is it?
F.
A.
L?
No, nothing there.
Fog.
Summon darkness.
Create a force field.
Should I just make darkness?
That's terrifying.
Make them dance?
I mean, right, come on.
That's the comedy routine.
All right, let's do jig.
You pull the bamboo flute from your bag, raise the spell, and begin to play a merry tune.
The angry faces of the bandits turn to expressions of astonishment as they find their limbs jerking in time to the music, quite out of control.
Their swords fly from their hands and they are soon dancing merrily around you.
Lead them back to the village or lead them to the nearest pit in the ground.
Just make them walk off a cliff.
Lead them to the nearest pit in the ground?
You want to pit these people?
All right.
The foothills around you are full of sudden drops, edges, and deep pits in the earth.
Piping loudly, you lead the two bandits to the nearest gap in the ground you can find.
Their expressions, already turning sour from exhaustion, move to looks of horror as they find themselves jumping and jigging on the edge of a pit.
Then, with a final leap and clap, they disappear over the side.
You put your murderous flute away and continue on your journey towards the hills.
About half an hour later, you reach the start of the climb into the hills proper and continue upwards.
That was horrible.
Have this running? It's an hour of occasional weight?
No, I don't want to take that.
All right. Well, there we go.
Climb into the hill.
Leaving Kanthapani behind marks the true start of the wilderness.
Beyond that tiny outpost, there are scattered homesteads and kar, a thriving city port.
But all are touched by cruelty, isolation, and fear.
The baklans and the long shadow cast by Mampang fortress darken everything.
And with the crown gone, stolen, things can only grow worse.
In the long years since Kalana the Reformer founded the Alliance, the crown has been passed from kingdom to kingdom every four years.
Ensuring each one has had its turn to lead, but no more.
Ruttlestone, Lenderland, Galantaria, and Bryce have all enjoyed its power, but not Analand.
But when the crown came to Analand, it was stolen by Birdman from Zamen and carried off to Mampang.
With the crown, the Archmage will be unstoppable powerful.
There's no chance of sending an army against him.
A military force would not survive the journey.
So here you are, a lone hero, walking the long path to Mampang alone.
Five minutes later, you reach a fork in the road.
The sergeant for all his eyesight hadn't mentioned this fork in the road.
Who is he talking to?
You're going to pull a who is he talking to right now?
I'm trying to get you immersed in the world of Analand.
Analand. Who is he talking to right now? Really?
Let's go. Fork in the road.
The road splits around the base of a gigantic tree, but does not rejoin on the other side.
The left path winds down into a valley, and the right rises up a slope towards the first thick forest of the hills.
It's hard to see much further uphill, though the forest is sudden and thick, and the path narrow.
It may be hard going in that direction, but the hills will involve a lot of climbing eventually,
and you make it a decent view of the next leg from the top of the ridge.
You pause to consider the lower route. There's a river there, and the path follows the left bank.
It's a safer route, secluded and protected, but the curve of the landscape would mean you were almost backtracking.
You're about to make your choice when you hear a faint cry from somewhere close at hand.
Ignore it. It's a trap time to move or look around. Make your choice.
Look around. You look around, then finally, up into the branches of the tree,
a pair of wizened, calloused feet are dangling down over your head.
About to drop on you, perhaps? Throw something at the tree. Who's there?
Climb up. Just throwing a rock up at the tree.
You just grab a boulder and just hammer it up there.
Climb up. You want to just climb up? Climb up.
Climb up. You swing yourself up onto the lowest branch of the tree,
and the owner of the feet shrieks in alarm. You see it's an old man, dressed in rags and as thin as bone.
Oi! He calls, trying to retreat along the branch. What do you want?
A few branches above him, you notice a buzzing beehive.
Ignore the man and climb for the hive. Help the man down.
What are you hiding from? Where does he leave?
Fucking zap this guy. I kind of want the hive. Should I help him down?
Question. What are you hiding from?
Actually, that's a good point, considering that, why is he up here?
What are you hiding from? Oh, the old man got up the tree as a puzzle.
He must have been escaping someone fearsome to climb so high.
What are you hiding from? You cry.
Down to Elvins. I was traveling from Dumpers to the outpost settlement in Analand.
But I was wayland by Elvins. Robbed me blind, all but took my eyes.
And left me up here in the tree. I keep getting older, you see.
We all do, but some worse than others. Climbed up, but now I'm too old to get down.
Help him out of the tree or just leave him. Let's help him out of the tree, right? Come on.
You reach up and grab the old man by the waist. He is as light as a leaf.
And within a moment, you've lifted him to the ground.
Thanks for that, he remarks, brushing himself down and almost knocking himself over in the process.
Oh, I was just starting to get a bit, you know, perturbed. But I'm on the safe side now.
He seems remarkably confident, considering that the slightest stumble might break him into bits.
What will you do now? What do I get in return? Leave him. Climb higher and investigate the beehive.
What will you do now?
Keep going for Analand, he says. That's where I set off from.
A while back now. You wouldn't believe the story if I told you.
Suffice to say, though, if I know my eyes from my eyes, you're heading up to Manpang and you'd better be smarter than I was.
And here. He presses a page into your hand. It is a page torn from a spell book.
This might be some use to you. I found this. I just found it.
Mine, I don't go asking how, but it's no good to me anymore.
Take it, refuse it, or look at it. Let's look at it.
You look the page over suspiciously. It seems to be half of a spell.
Ka, C-A. That might have been used for pest repulsion, but it is unworkable in its current state.
You take the page and thank him. Climb up to the hive.
Leaving the old man sighing with gratitude on the ground, you climb higher through the branches of the tall tree.
Up to the beehive.
The beehive hangs like a ripe fruit from the very highest branch.
A huge number of bees dance in and swarm out and about. Climb higher or use magic or give up.
Zap the beehive? Guys, I only have 10 health.
You get your balance enough to free your hands for a spell.
Big. Grow in size.
Zen. Hover in the air. I don't have the item.
Zap. I can shoot. I can do Palpatine hand.
Doze. Cause slowness.
Open locks and doors. That's interesting. Why can't I do that here?
Law. Control non-intelligent creatures.
That's three stamina though. I guess that would work, right?
I guess bees would be correct, right?
Open the beehive door. Go for law? Let's do it.
You cast the spell, concentrating on the swarm that surrounds the beehive.
You feel your mind taking control of theirs.
Several hundred small consciousnesses falling under your will.
You lead them like a general directing an army away from the hive.
Allowing you to clamor up and relieve them of a succulent honeycomb and a nice ball of beeswax.
That's a nice trick!
The old man remarks. You stash your finds in your pack. The light is fading. It's time to move on.
Oh!
The man cries suddenly.
Do you want to hear me, Riddle? I learned it from the Elvint.
Sure. You gesture with a hand for him to speak.
See him though he sees you're not. A stinging beast in a box not left.
To guard a key it is his lot. To gole a witch of luck bereft.
You thank him. You nod once and then you turn your attention to the path ahead.
All right. The high path or the low path? Where am I going?
I'm going through the forest here or over the road here on the low path.
Take the high ground. Take the high ground. High is fuck.
Low. High. High. High. High.
Follow the river. That'll take us down here.
All right. Let me get you. You got to get a big picture here.
The bees are swarming me.
This goes through the forest and into the mines here or potentially up through the river area up here.
This goes across potentially this big open field thing and then this little village or this village here.
Make sure you vote wisely because this is this is actually pretty important
because I don't if we go this way we cannot go this way.
The bees are attacking. I think they have decided.
It's close though. It's pretty close.
Which one was the high path? High path is right.
Through this forest with a branch or like a fork in the road or up kind of more safely this way.
I don't know what's going on dude. I just voted for whatever.
I hope you're having a good time.
All right. They've decided.
Also have we had any F's? I keep I'm still dropping frames I think but has it been anything bad?
Are we good? Is it okay?
All right. All right. The high path. Let's go.
The high road seems the most secure.
In a valley you can be easily observed from above and lead astray.
But out on the hills you can go whichever way you choose.
Of course when night falls it may be cold and exposed up on the slopes but no matter.
This journey was never destined to be easy.
You begin to climb.
Letting the old man's jabbering fade quickly away.
He's still with us by the way.
The path winds upwards into the hill into the cover of a wood.
The afternoon sun glints through the trees and place tricks on your eyes.
Every so often you catch a glimpse of some strange shaped animal or other watching you.
Long to the find that it's the silhouette of branches and leaves caught at an odd angle.
After an hour's walk you're starting to feel hungry.
We eat one of our rations or do we keep walking?
I think we have to eat here.
You clamber to the top of a low stone dolmen.
Then sit and pull out the sugary honeycomb and eat.
While admiring the view down the hillside through a break in the trees.
You feel better for your rest.
Keep that old man safe.
And move on.
You stand and put your pack on.
Which you had been sitting to prevent any creatures getting in or any of your things falling out.
Then you return to the path.
The climb continues with the path twisting this way and that.
The air grows cold and the sun flickers on the horizon.
Then sets making it hard to see your way.
But the moon is full and when twilight is done it will be bright once more.
Keep walking or make camp.
We do need to sleep.
We're at the point now where it is night time.
We do have the ape.
Oh we can't do it yet.
I'm gonna camp.
But to tire yourself out on the first day would be inauspicious.
You settle down to make camp for the night.
In a natural shelter provided by the roots of three gigantic intertwined trees.
Your backpack will serve for a pillow and your cloak for a blanket.
Before settling to sleep you check through your pack.
You have two rations left.
Gotta eat again.
Eat again?
Or just sleep.
Let's just sleep.
Oh shit.
Spoiler alert.
That was a problem.
You lay yourself out on the ground and are quickly asleep.
The moon has fallen high in the sky when you are next opening your eyes.
You feel warm and more cozy than you did before.
As if wrapped in a gigantic blanket.
There is a pain in your leg.
Slowly you realize what is happening.
A giant bat has settled on your chest and is feeding on your leg.
Hurry.
Protect from magic.
So that's uh...
Big.
I can get huge.
I could do jig?
Will this work on an animal?
Will this work on animals?
What if it doesn't work on animals?
This is free to do though.
Let's do it.
You raise the spell and play a sweet tune on the bamboo pipe.
The bat begins to hop absurdly from foot to foot.
Spinning around and holding out its wings.
You entertain yourself with the thing for a few minutes.
Then grab it in one hand and lob it away into the trees.
Where it takes flight not to return.
Smiling to yourself you settle back down.
I didn't know that that worked on animals.
You know what? I just like so long bowsered it into the trees.
Hopping on what?
You entertain yourself with the thing for a few minutes.
It was just feeding on my leg.
That's bad.
Man, imagine not getting the flute.
And there's a ton of scenarios where you just don't get it.
You just don't even go to Cantabani.
Jig is OP.
There are a lot of OP spells that you just won't get.
And sometimes I get no spoilers or anything.
You can get stuff taken from you.
So don't think that this is safe.
We gotta make the right choices here.
Once again the crown fills your dreams.
Only now instead of being hidden away in Mampang.
Fortress by the Archmage.
You see it on the head of the burly villager from Cantabani.
Anyone can wear the crown.
He declares to you.
But wearing the crown you are no longer just anyone.
And then he points a finger at you.
That seems to crackle with energy.
And you find yourself drawn towards him.
Commanded to do his bidding.
Suddenly you're surrounded by angry bees.
You're walking towards a crack in the ground.
It seems sure to swallow you whole.
You stumble at its edge.
You're about to fall.
Having dreams of the bees the next morning.
The second day of your journey begins in the morning cool.
Still halfway between sleeping and waking.
You feel the presence of your spirit.
The ape.
Close nearby.
Its form has changed since you left Analand.
Just as you have changed.
But still walking beside you.
In the temple they taught you that a prayer to your spirit could heal disease.
Lift curses.
Even save you from certain death.
But the spirits are not generous.
And decline to help often.
You can now ask for aid with the pray button.
So this is interesting because over the course of the game you get certain gods that you pray to.
And it changes based on what you do and your actions and stuff, right?
So right now we have the ape.
A strong beast, intelligent and prudent.
Who takes great pride in acting faithfully.
To be depended upon.
During certain scenarios you can pray.
And the ape might help or might not.
It kind of depends on who it is.
You can feel yourself getting accustomed to the fetid air of these hills.
You've now ascended several hundred feet.
And can expect to make excellent progress.
Before the end of the day.
As you crest the brow of a hill.
You see something that makes you stop in your tracks.
To your left is a clearing.
And in the clearing are several poles.
Planted firmly in the ground.
And atop each pole is a head.
Look at the heads.
Or go.
Whoa.
Look at the heads or run.
Look.
The heads are all kinds and ages.
Some are recently fixed while others have decayed.
And some are nothing but skulls and hair.
There are human heads.
Goblin heads.
And one or two heads of creatures you do not recognize.
All have sewn up eyes.
And mouths.
A large X painted on a rock nearby is obviously intended as a warning.
Not to venture any further.
But ahead the road forks.
Left and right.
And you cannot be sure which path you are warned not to take.
The right hand path continues to climb.
And the left hand path.
Wides down the side of the hill.
Very interesting.
You cannot cast directly from the book.
I would cast it.
Yawb.
Will summon a giant who the caster may control.
Oh my god.
I have a giant's tooth, right?
Blue.
Always very useful.
Doc.
Doc is useful.
Okay.
Which way are we going?
This is a chat choice, by the way.
I'm not going to decide this one.
I ain't going to decide this one.
Where are we going?
There is a warning.
You can look at it again.
A large X painted on a rock nearby is obviously intended as a warning.
Not to venture any further.
But ahead the road forks.
Left and right.
And you don't know what path you are warned to not take.
A loud bird.
There you go.
Here you can see.
We have a path to a town.
Or a path up this way towards some mines and another kind of bridge area.
Leading up to another little settlement.
Chat, don't pick the obvious choice.
Where are we going?
What's winning?
This is close.
Come on.
Vote. Vote. Vote. Vote.
What does prey do?
You can prey at any moment, but not right now.
The game essentially just told you what it does.
But if you prey in a random place, it'll heal you potentially or might do something bad.
During the course of the game, you'll get the option to prey.
And you know how it says, cast a spell.
Draw your weapon.
Prey is one of them.
And depending on who you have as a god, it might come and help you.
Or might mock you or might try to kill you.
We're going right.
Look at the items.
I have a spell book.
I have blimberry juice.
Blimberry juice.
I have beeswax.
Goblin teeth, giant's tooth, and a bamboo flute.
I love this song too.
This song is so good.
Let me read this.
I don't know if I can use this right now.
What about treasures?
We got nine gold.
He plays this song in his car.
Everybody quiet.
This is the part.
This is my favorite part.
God.
Okay.
That's such a good song.
Are you shitting?
What?
All right, we're going right.
Yeah, I apologize for the little F's that are happening.
Sometimes it just happens and I'm not going to get angry about it.
I was angry about it an hour ago.
I'm not going to make it mad.
And when I say it, I'm not going to make it.
I'm not going to be mad about it, right?
It's just the way it is and I can't fix it.
We just have to hope it is not a problem.
I hope it's not been a problem.
I really hope it hasn't been.
I'll get angry.
Okay.
The climb continues up the hill for several hours until you are not far from the top.
Then the faint sound of bustling activity reaches you.
Flampling feet, grunting voices, and the clanking of metal against rock.
There's something ahead, hidden by the ancient trees that line these slopes.
Follow the sound or keep to the path.
Could be investigated.
Couldn't, but maybe not.
Or, I mean, we had a warning.
There was a warning.
But we do have zap.
We do have dop.
We do have sus.
What do you guys think?
I actually think I want to have another poll here because this is important, I think, either way.
I'm not sure.
I don't remember.
The theme's pretty divided as well.
So let's get a decision here.
We do have jig, too.
But, you know, jig will only work if I have the ability to play the instrument.
Follow the sound or just stay on the path.
I would imagine the sound is this way and the path is the path.
And we can just keep going.
Path leads up here and the other thing leads in here.
You attempt to cast sus, but Jerma's the one playing sorcery here.
Not you.
That's funny.
I like that.
All right.
We're going to follow the sound.
It's unanimous.
Let's go.
Follow the sound.
You leave the path and continue through the woods.
A short distance onwards, you hide behind a tree and survey a clearing.
A number of goblins are in the clearing, working at the mouth of an open cave.
They trudge in and out of the opening, carrying large bowls in their arms piled up with glistening rocks and dull metallic nuggets.
Treasure.
Watch them work.
Leave them to it.
Make a break for the cave entrance.
I'm going to watch them.
You stay hidden, getting a sense of the scale of the operation.
There are at least 30 goblins inside the cave, each coming out every few minutes or so with
a new pail of stones.
Then there are other goblins working in the clearing with hammers, smashing the rocks
into small pieces, extracting metals from inside, loading them into carts, and finally
pushing the carts away down a wide track between the trees.
It is quite some operation, but not without its weaknesses.
There are too many goblins to create any kind of distraction, but they move away into the
trees fairly often, and sometimes the cave is left unguarded.
Try to slip inside the cave.
Try to steal from the bowls, or leave and go back to the path.
Try to steal from the bowls?
I want to try to get, yeah, let's try to get some, I mean, there's probably like diamonds
in here.
You wait for the right moment, then leap out from behind the tree to snatch a little of
the glistening rock from the nearest bowl.
It's hard to pick out good metal from bad so fast, but you manage to lift a couple of
pieces worth of gold.
But your actions have not gone unnoticed.
You're quickly surrounded by three goblins, all armed with picks and ready to use them.
All right, we don't have access to Jig.
But we got Zap.
We also have rap?
Talk all languages.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Raz, sharpen your blade.
No, hot either.
I don't have access to it.
I'll zap.
Let's go for it.
Time to create some lightning, guys.
For the first time in seven years, I'm about to cast Zap.
You cast the spell and point at the nearest goblin.
A streak of lightning shoots from your finger and catches the creature squarely in the chest,
killing it instantly.
The smoke clears.
The second goblin, enraged, rushes into attack before you can raise the spell again.
There it is.
All right.
So I got a much bigger stamina bar.
We're going to just go about...
Let's go six.
Yeah, that's all right.
That's all right.
The second goblin growls and gnashes its teeth, then throws away its pick and snatches up
a shovel.
This one you realize is vicious and an idiot.
You strike for its head.
The goblin raises his shovel and hides under the blade.
Get out of here.
You push forward, showing no mercy, leaping over a cart.
You drive your blade straight for his throat.
The blow connects and the creature falls down to the dirt, dead.
There's no time before the third goblin's on you.
Let's go another full blast here.
It's all right.
This third goblin is bigger than the others and furious at the death of his comrades.
He paces forward menacingly.
You show him the force of your blade and the goblin jumps quickly back.
He escapes largely unscathed.
From arm's length, he hisses and glows.
Full blast.
Kill him.
Dead.
You strike again with vicious force.
It is the final blow.
The goblin drops to the dust.
The clearing falls quiet.
Search the bodies or get out of here.
And there's like 40, this is what, 30 goblins here?
All right, I'm going for it.
You quickly rifle the bodies.
There are two gold pieces, a pathetically small sum to be killing for.
There are also eight goblin teeth lying around.
Oh my God, take them.
I have 10 goblin teeth.
I can make a whole army soon.
Working quickly, you gather up the teeth and add them to the bag you bought at Cantapani.
That's done.
It's time to move on.
There'll be other goblins here soon enough.
You've been lucky that you have emerged from the woods while you were dispatching these.
Quickly, you hurry back into the trees, leaving the mine behind you, continuing on along the path with the tall trees at either side.
How many teeth do I have?
I have 12 goblin teeth.
Oh my God.
All right.
That's actually insane.
The bridge.
Follow a path that leads sharply downhill into a narrow valley in which a stream runs.
There's no path along the bank, but there is a bridge.
Cross it.
Inspect the ropes.
Find another way.
Stop collecting teeth.
I need them.
Let's take a look.
You test the ropes.
They seem to be firm.
If this is a trap, it's not one that will dump you into the stream, but you could always
struggle through the vegetation on the bank and try to find a fording point.
I'm going to use the bridge.
Let's use the bridge.
Moving slowly and with one hand on your sword hilt, expecting the boards to give way at
any moment, you inch across.
The bridge holds and you reach the other bank quite safely.
You now have a long walk ahead of you along the ridge and through a light covering of trees.
So that was the right thing to do.
This would have been probably a disaster.
Long walk here to further on, which is over here.
The path climbs again up a low hill, covered over with thick bushes and shrubs that snag
at your clothing.
Halfway up, you hear a sound.
Twigs breaking.
Freeze.
You freeze as a large creature the size of a bear emerges directly in front of you.
It has black and white fur and a long bushy tail that trails out behind.
It growls menacingly.
Oh no, it just snagged again.
Prepare to attack or try to edge around it.
Should I go for it?
I'm going for it.
How hard could it be?
Prepare to attack.
You will not be able to avoid a confrontation.
The creature is a skunk bear and when it raises its tail, it releases a nauseating odor.
The smell that hangs around is terrible.
Let's get a...
What can I do here?
Wow.
All right.
There's some weird things here.
What about sap?
Cause depression.
Six.
Clone the caster.
So I just clone myself and go, you go do it.
Nap.
Cause sleepiness.
I don't have the item.
Nothing with K. Law.
Yeah.
This is very expensive though.
Control non-intelligent creatures.
Is it non-intelligent?
I wonder if this is a bad idea.
That's a lot of stamina.
I think that's too much.
I'll do six.
Let's do...
Let's clone ourselves.
That's only one.
Let's do it.
You cast a spell and in a flash, five replicas of yourself appear in front of the creature.
The confused beast lurches forward to attack one of them and you use the opportunity to
escape, leaving your magic clones to fight your battle for you.
The path leads down through another valley and back up a hill.
Two hours pass.
The worst part about that though is I don't get any loot for that.
I don't get any loot for that.
I just run.
Oh, and I didn't see what was up here.
Yeah, it's all right.
All right.
We're going to be approaching Christa Tonti now.
I want to see where we've gone so far.
And by the way, I want to make sure people understand something here.
This is very important.
You know Elden Ring?
You ain't seen fucking anything yet.
This game is so overwhelmingly large that you're going to get Elden Ringed here in a
minute.
I just want to make sure you understand that.
You're about to get...
Pretty soon here, you're going to get Elden Ringed.
I just want to make sure you know that.
Let's go to Christa Tonti.
The sun has now just passed its zenith and everywhere a dusty heat rises from the baked
earth.
You begin to think about where you will stay for the night.
Another night sleeping out in the open would be best avoided.
But then you see a small village set into a hill.
Smoke rises from the stacks.
The houses are well set with stone at their bases and thatched roofs of grasses and thick
leaves.
There is unusually more than just the one street running through the center of town.
It's as though this place, once rich, has had its heart scooped away.
Litter surrounds the buildings and on the edge of the village are rows and rows of empty,
abandoned houses.
You continue your slow trudge along the path.
Okay.
Into the village or avoid the village.
As you can probably understand, avoid the village is going to take us this way.
Into the village is going to go in the village.
Let's get a decision from Chat here.
You're going to get mugged in this village.
Oh, they stumped us.
What do you guys think?
We going in or we going around?
We going in.
We going around.
Around the village or in the village?
Please go to Dumpus.
Well, we'll find out.
Expand your influence.
Avoid Dumpus or Riot.
Dumpus or Riot.
Well, Jerma, when are you going to play Genshin?
I'm sick of it.
I'm not going to play Genshin Impact.
I told you I played it for like an hour in bed on the iPad and it was overwhelming to me.
All right.
What's the verdict?
That's unanimous.
Let's go.
We're going into Chrisitanti.
Here we go.
You walk into the village.
Young hill dwellers pass you and stare at your strange clothes.
You nod back respectfully.
Look at the people.
Their own attire is rough by comparison to your gear.
They wear their hair long but piled up on their heads.
These people are ghastly poor.
The village is like a ghost town here on the knife edge of the backlands.
Talk in the ale house or go to the inn.
Let's go to the ale house.
I want to go in here.
Walking down the single road you quickly find a hut with its front covered hold wide open
and the smell of brewed beer coming from inside.
You go in.
Several hill dwellers are here talking gruffly.
When you enter they watch you with understandable caution.
The owner of the hut comes over to you.
Welcome to Chrisitanti.
What do you want?
Read the owner or ignore him and sit with the dwellers.
Say hello.
An evening's rest and a drink to wet my throat.
You reply.
Hell is one gold piece.
Please sit.
You go over to the table where the hill dwellers are.
Sit with the old man, sit with the young man.
Two voice Andy.
That's the way it is, alright?
Hold.
You turn your attention to the oldest man at the table.
Whatever face he once had is lost in a labyrinth of wrinkles.
And his skin is the color of tanned hide from a lifetime of the beating sun.
What are you looking at?
The old man's face curls up like burnt paper into a kind of smile.
Don't get too many travelers around here.
So I'm looking at you.
Where are you from?
I come from Analand.
Hmm.
Not many has crossed through Cantapani Gate.
In either direction, if you know what I'm saying.
You should go and look.
The gate has exploded.
Like what?
Like I didn't do that?
You should go and look.
The gate exploded.
You grin widely.
If they haven't fixed it, you might be able to get in at last.
The old man laughs.
Now my place is here.
They say there's a war coming.
Something to do with a crown.
I seek that crown.
Not if I can help it.
A crown?
Crown?
You ask cautiously.
The crown of kings.
They say it's how a leader leads.
Without the crown on your head, no one will follow you.
The crown can raise an army from the farmyard.
Or command a population to walk into the sea.
Sounds like a bad idea, if you ask me.
But if someone's got to wear it, I'd rather they were in Anna Land than Manpang.
You sip your beer.
The old man exchanges glances with the younger man sitting opposite.
Talk to the young man.
Ask the old man about the area.
Can you tell me something about this region?
You ask.
Christa Tanti?
Certainly.
I'll tell you that around here, we're always glad to help out strangers.
I think you're a crazy old man.
Tell me what lies beyond this town.
What lies beyond this town?
Beyond Christa Tanti, there are two paths.
One takes you past Aliana's home.
And you will need your wits about you if she's there.
The other leads up into the hills of Liyaki.
Domain of the great ones.
Either way you choose.
I wish you the luck of Sindler on your journey.
The god changed, by the way.
We have the monkey now, not the ape.
No one talks like this.
Yes, they do.
All old men talk like this in fantasy literature.
And fantasy movies and TV shows.
We all talk like this very, very theatrically.
I'm not going to pray.
Okay, intelligent but cheeky.
The monkey understands others but does not respect them.
He is quick to turn his tail, but not rash.
What he lacks in courage he makes up for in caution.
Yeah, we're getting some Fs here.
More than usual.
We're getting a few Fs here, more than usual.
There are no Fs?
Oh, there definitely are right now.
Let's see if we can write it out for a sec.
I have a little thing that shows the amount of frames that are dropping.
We've dropped like 500 or 600 in the last 30 seconds.
Okay.
All right, so here we go.
We have the monkey.
Who is Sindler?
He says pray to Sindler.
I'm going to ask that.
Who is Sindler?
God of hopeless causes.
The man replies and laughs.
The crowd in the inn is starting to thin out.
You finish your beer in a single drought and get to your feet.
You make to leave the inn.
The owner stops you holding out his hand.
Pay him a gold piece or knock him aside.
The frame dropping is not a big deal when it's stationary.
Yeah, that's true.
That's true.
I'll just stop.
I'll stop talking about it.
It just it like burns a hole in my head looking over there and seeing frames drop and being like fuck.
That's true though.
It shouldn't be that big of a deal.
All right.
I'm going to pay.
I'm not going to be a dick.
You pay him his gold piece and step out into the street.
You look this way and that.
Trying to decide what to do next.
When you realize the old man has joined you once more.
He ignores you and is gone.
It's now evening and time to sleep.
We're going to find the inn.
You stop a passerby and ask for an inn.
And they lead you there directly.
The woman who runs the place stands in the doorway with her arms folded.
Are you from the king?
She demands.
No, I'm a traveler.
I am on a mission for the king.
We're getting a party of old men.
Do I just lie?
No, I'm a traveler.
I don't want to give attention to myself.
No, I'm a mere traveler.
The woman narrows her eyes at you.
This is a guest house.
The best in Christa Tante.
Only guests stay.
And any guest of mine knows it cost me three gold pieces to host a man of a night.
And two to feed him.
But it's all between friends.
Uh, two gold?
Three?
Three gold?
Why is...
Hold on.
Hold on a second.
Oops.
I have to do something real quick.
Very quickly.
Give me one second.
Give me a second.
Okay.
Sorry about that.
Yeah.
I had to remove something from my, um, from my channel description.
Thank you for the heads up, by the way.
I did not even know that was still there.
That's so funny.
Oh, all right.
What were we doing?
Right.
This.
All right.
I'll take a room.
Should I eat though?
I should eat.
I need to eat first.
Food is just being served.
The woman steps aside and you go inside and sit down.
A few minutes later, her husband appears with a steaming pot of skunk bear stew.
As you eat, you can't help but remember the terrible smelling beast dead on the path.
And the thought makes you gag.
You wolf it down all the same and leave your coins on the table.
Do you want a room as well?
Um, yes, I do.
Thank you.
The woman shows you the way upstairs to a room.
There are three other guests already staying and asleep.
So you settle quickly.
The bed is not clean, but it is comfortable.
And after a long day and all its narrow escapes, you're grateful beyond measure for the rest.
Your dreams are vivid once again.
You're walking endlessly.
The hills moving up and down under your feet like a rippling sea.
Every step exhausts you, but no step moves you forward.
Meanwhile, a tall black creature strides towards you, breathed in a foul smelling smoke.
And in the distance, a deep voice is booming with laughter.
The long, cruel fingers of one hand are curled around the metal frame of a crown.
With the other, he beckons you forward as if into a trap beyond Christa Tonti.
There's just one dog barking.
Let's continue.
You wake early and sit for a moment in no great hurry to leave the village.
This is now the third day of your journey, and the muscles in your legs are feeling lean and strong from so much walking.
You spend a short while enjoying the peace, then unhurriedly collect your possessions and set off along the path.
Christa Tonti is surrounded by several miles of fields, sits in a well-protected ring of hills,
and is close enough to the river to be reasonably prosperous.
As you follow the path between lines of sun-baked crops, you come to a fork in the road.
The right-hand way leads past a set of outbuildings,
while the left heads directly off into deep woodland.
Let's decide.
Where are we going?
Between the buildings up this way or in the woods?
This will lead us through here to the Leakey.
This is a ruined town, by the way.
Or through the woods, potentially to into the forest and potentially over to Dampus.
We might be able to get to Dampus if we go up, or it might head us this way over the river.
Where to?
Dampus.
Well, that's up to you.
That is up to you.
You're probably wondering what that was.
I had to just refresh my Twitch TV.
Hold on.
That wasn't in the game.
I had to refresh my Twitch page and move it over here.
All right.
Let's do it.
That's pretty unanimous.
Into the woods we're going.
Towards Dampus.
Your journey is too important to slow down talking to locals.
You must pass unseen, and so you disappear into the jungle of all tall trees.
For a short while the sun is fervorous.
Feverous, even.
And then you are between the trees once more,
and everything becomes cool and still.
You walk for several hours uneventfully.
This land that was never settled or explored, and very few travel this way.
In places, bushes and shrubs have grown over into the path.
Hack your way through or move cautiously, just wildly swinging your fucking sword.
We just gotta go nuts through it, I think.
Yeah, hack away, hack.
Moving carefully forward, you use your sword to cleave the bushes.
Your progress is quick, but silent.
Then you come to a fork in the road, still deep in the forest.
Fork in the forest.
Uh-oh, it's decision time.
I don't know what's gonna happen here.
Chad, I don't know.
It's either on to Dampus, or creepy hut in the forest.
That's gonna be a tough one.
Someone has thought to make a sign.
Perhaps as a guide, or perhaps as a warning.
The way to the right is marked for Dampus.
A left turn points to Aliana.
A name you remember from what the man in Christa Tonti told you.
Neither way seems the better, Trod.
You will have to choose.
To Aliana, or to Dampus.
Make your choice.
It's time to go to the shack.
Or Dampus.
Get the dumpy.
I don't know.
I don't remember.
Because if we go this way, there's also probably a possibility that we can still go to Dampus.
Or it might take us out into this fork, and we have to choose again.
Which might lead you still to Dampus, but could also go this way, too.
And up here.
Alright, what are we doing?
We're going to Aliana.
Pretty unanimous.
The path winds between trees that get greener and more lush.
You must be closer to the river here, although you cannot hear the water.
After about half an hour's walk through dappled shade, you come across a well-built hut.
Flowers decorate its walls, and the door has been painted with ornate designs.
The path ends here.
Knock on the door.
Scout around it.
There's a knock on the front door, right?
Just go knock.
You approach the door and knock.
There is no reply.
Scout around it or turn back or open the door.
Scout around it?
Let's scout around it.
You perform a swift circuit around the hut, but find nothing unusual or concerning.
It seems to be what it is.
A hut, set by itself deep in the forest.
But for someone to survive out here on their own, surrounded by the beasts of the jungle,
they must be someone quite powerful.
You want to leave?
This is your last chance to leave, or are we going to open this door?
This is sus as fuck.
Alright, open it.
You push open the door and stride inside.
Inside the house.
The hut is neatly laid out.
You detect the touch of a fastidious woman.
Chairs are set around a table as if for guests.
A mattress lies in one corner, and a large kitchen area indicates that whoever lives here,
they are fond of cooking.
Take what I can.
Or call out.
Just like, grab, grab.
Why would you steal?
You can't just steal everything.
We have stolen from every single person we've come across so far.
We'll call out.
We have to, right?
We can't just take everything.
Hello?
Is there anybody here?
To your surprise, a voice answers quickly.
Who's there?
Who is that?
Ignore it.
Locate the speaker.
I warn you, I am armed.
I broke into your house, and I have a weapon.
Why would I do that?
Locate the speaker, or ignore it.
Locate the speaker.
Looking into a corner, hidden by a large cupboard,
you see a cage in which a young woman is imprisoned.
Good stranger!
Let me out of this cage, I beg you!
Get her out.
What happened to you?
I'm sure you were there for a reason.
What happened?
You move over to the cage, quite shocked.
What happened to you?
Oh, good stranger.
I've been locked up here for two days.
It was Elvins that did it.
Those mischievous, prankful Elvins.
Please, you must help me.
I have not eaten, and they left me here,
where I can see all my cooking things, but cannot reach them.
I'll help you.
If I let you go, what do I get in return?
Going over to the cage, you try for the door.
It's locked, of course.
Use magic, try an item, or break the lock.
You can use dop, right?
Use magic.
You should be grateful I waste my strength on you.
You declare as you roll up your sleeves.
Oh, no.
No, I can't.
I can't.
What is pep?
Cause strength?
What a dick.
Raz sharpen my blade?
Should I just do it?
But what if I kill her?
I don't want to kill this person.
Dop is, it's dop.
Dop is, wait, cause slowness?
What would I do?
I'm doing this.
You begin the spell.
Aliana watches you and must have some understanding of magic as she calls out to you.
Wait.
What are you?
But it's too late.
The spell has taken effect and Aliana has passed out on the floor of her cage.
Should I rewind?
Can I?
No rewinds?
Hold on.
Let me see what's in here.
Perfect.
Now you can search this place in peace.
You begin to carefully search the drawers and cupboards of the hut.
It's very empty.
Perhaps whoever locked the woman up robbed her themselves.
All you find is two gold pieces and a pouch containing soft brown sand.
You need to rewind.
I thought you didn't want to steal.
What's the sand?
Can I just see what the sand is?
Take everything.
You pocket both and turn to go.
The woman snores quietly away as you slip out of the hut.
You retrace your steps to the last junction.
Wait, hold on.
Whoa!
The vixen?
This is my new god.
The vixen is a creature of high cunning and low morals.
She will lie, cheat, swindle, and sidle her way out of trouble and into riches, always
taking care to cover her trail.
I've never seen that before.
You need to rewind, you monster.
All right.
This is an important thing for us to decide if we continue to do this.
I would like you all to vote besides death.
Okay, because there are hundreds of ways to die in this game at any moment.
Besides dying, am I allowed to rewind?
Let's get an actual opinion here.
Please, if you are lurking right now, this is a very important thing.
Remember, if I die, I can rewind to before I died.
But in a sense where, oh, I just did something.
Oh, that's bad.
Am I allowed to go back?
This is very, very important.
This is going to dictate a lot.
Because do I have to live with my decisions?
Do I have to sleep in the bed that I make?
What do you think?
I know this is going to be close.
Action should have consequences.
Or maybe I can only rewind once or maybe like a few times a game.
Maybe, right?
Oh, this winning.
Wow, I'm surprised.
I'm really surprised.
I thought that that was not going to win.
Okay.
All right.
That's pretty close though.
Just don't abuse it.
You get three rewinds.
Rewind, rewind, rewind tokens.
Okay.
All right.
I can have three rewinds total per part, per game, per episode.
We already did a no rewind.
I can't even say that word.
Okay.
So I, so, but I get to decide when I use those rewinds, right?
Three times per game.
Okay.
I'm not using it here.
I don't need, I don't have to go back.
I got a bunch of sand.
I'm not using it here.
Omega Lo, what the fuck?
We should get one.
Wait, just because I can rewind doesn't mean I have to.
I don't want to, what if I need, what if it's a really important thing that happens?
Terrible morals?
What do you guys think?
Three times per, oh yeah, I think that's fair.
You should zap yourself.
Yeah.
Hey, let me tell you something.
I get to choose when these happen.
Okay.
Something that you should, hey, all of you that are watching right now, there's so many
things to experience.
Go get it.
It's fucking awesome.
And you've got opportunities.
You're a vixen.
Yeah.
I'm not using it here.
This is not, to me, I made out from that exchange.
Do you understand?
I got a bunch of sand, which that's fucking pretty sick if you ask me.
That's so worthless.
You're a piece of shit.
Why?
I casted like the go to sleep spell and I stole everything in this person's house.
No, I am sleeping in that bed.
I want to keep the sand.
Wait, let me, wait, let me determine.
Can I, is sand actually for a spell?
Because if it is, I want to know what it is.
Mud?
Ooh.
While casting, the caster must sprinkle grains of sand onto the floor to create a pool of
quicksand.
Any creature stepping into the quicksand will slowly be sucked away.
You shitting me?
I've got quicksand now.
I'm going to dump us.
Aliana died for this.
Aliana didn't die, okay?
Look, I'm playing a chaotic, lawful good.
You walk for several hours following the twists and turns of the path through the trees.
Then suddenly you stop.
You've heard a noise up ahead.
Something is moving around between the rocks at the edge of the path.
Vixen.
I draw my sword.
You draw your sword and ready and you're glad you did because a moment later you're
attacked.
In a flurry of foliage and dirt, a rat bear leaps from underground.
It's much closer than you thought.
Its sleek black fur allows it to hide in the shadows until it's almost upon you.
You bring your sword.
I'm glad I did that.
Holy shit.
Okay, this is bad.
Look at this fucking bar.
I'm going to defend.
Good thing I did.
The rat bear is startled by your approach but drops quickly to all fours.
You drop quickly behind a tree and raise your sword, ready to defend yourself.
At the last moment, the rat bear leaps, all claws off the ground and gnarling and lunging
at you.
You brace yourself as it comes down.
It rears back, claws raised.
All right, we're going to go four.
No, six.
Fuck.
Okay.
You risk an attack.
Rushing forward, you charge at the rat bear but it has read your intention and drops into
a crouch.
It grunts as it pushes you away.
Afraid of you, it stumbles back, tail whipped high in defense.
All right, you're going to go for probably another defense, right?
Let's do two.
Yep, that's good.
That's fine.
Side stepping, you slash out at the rat bear but it knocks you aside with a paw.
You scratch the creature's hide.
It squeaks and snuffles, standing up on its hind legs.
It's coming in for a hard one.
Do I have enough though?
Kill him.
Don't root for the rat bear.
Why?
Because I took a bunch of sand from some lady's house?
Holy shit, that would have fucking killed me.
All right.
You can almost smell the creature growing enraged and duck quickly behind a tree.
Squeaking with rage, the rat bear charges forward but you keep yourself guarded.
It edges back, claws raised.
All right, it just used its whole bar.
I'm going to go with like four.
No, like three.
All right, that's fine.
Swing a mighty blow at the rat bear but it has guessed your move.
High defense again.
All right, let's go two.
Okay, that's fine.
I'm slowly chipping away.
Fainting left, you slice at the rat bear but it bats you back into the mud with its tail.
It's weakening little by little.
It drops to all fours and lowers its head.
All right, I think it's coming in hard.
Ooh, good.
Splashing through the mud, you race into the rat bear, catching it at light blow.
Light plays through the trees and for a moment, the true extent of the rat bear's injuries are revealed.
I'm going to defend.
Oh my goodness.
Okay, we're good.
The creature's getting angry and probably desperate, right?
Launches its front claws aimed at your eyes but you knock away its attack.
For a moment, it's close enough for you to smell its sewer breath.
It stumbles back, claws raised.
Go in.
All right, fuck, whatever.
Fuck.
Okay, it's going to come in at a full bar here.
It growls and grunts, rearing up, showing its full height.
Defend.
I'm losing too much health for this.
All right, I got to go full blast.
We're good.
Get out of here.
I win.
You risk an attack.
You charge into the rat bear.
Then your sword slips between the creature's ribs and drives deep into its putrid heart.
The rat bear squeals and falls to the ground, face down in the mud.
Competent combat.
With the bees dead on the path, you are free to move onwards.
Approaching?
Dump us.
The path winds a few more times around gigantic trees, thousands of years old, and then emerges
onto a sudden plain, as if the forest had been scooped away by a gigantic hand.
A river trickles, thinly, between short grasses and by its bank stands a tiny village.
We don't even need to run a pole going into Dumpus.
It's going to be like 95%.
We don't even need to run that pole.
Today has been a short day with few true dangers.
With a decent meal and a night's sleep, your next day will start auspiciously.
So you begin the gentle climb down into the village.
You follow the path down into the village, passing a sign, which declares it to be Dumpus.
The streets are thin and narrow, and the buildings have been set close together, as if trying
to withstand a storm.
There's a terrible smell hanging in the air.
All in all, it seems an unpleasant place.
Find an inn, talk to villagers, or explore the town.
Big F? Yeah.
Why did you leave that person in the cage?
I don't know.
I stole stuff.
Because I just did.
Because I'm evil.
No, I just wanted to click it and see what happened.
And then I didn't want to waste a rewind on it.
You killed her.
I didn't kill anybody.
Uh, I want to...
Hmm.
She's going to starve in there.
She's going to be fine.
I don't...
Go steal more sand.
I'm talking to villagers.
Sand is...
But I have sand now.
Who is going to save her?
I don't know.
She can't get out.
But you don't know that.
How do you know that?
Alright, you pass along the main path through the village.
And pause outside a hut in which several of the disheveled hill dwellers are sitting and eating.
They seem deep in discussion about something.
Several are shaking their fists in the air.
Lifting back the canvas flap, you step inside.
The hill dwellers stop talking immediately and look up at you.
One gets to his feet and gestures you forward.
Step over and bow my head.
You murdered a poor, innocent, caged woman for a cup of literal sand.
I'm going to bow.
You nod your head once to the man who returns the gesture.
Then one of the others calls something in their native tongue.
And points at your side to where your sword hangs out below the hem of your cloak.
In broken common tongue, the first man croaks.
No weapons!
And he indicates a table by the door where you can leave the blade.
Remove the sword, look over the table.
Enter with my sword, shake my head, and leave.
Oh, we got the ape back.
Look at the table.
There are plenty of other weapons there, so they appear to be honest enough.
Remove my sword?
You unfasten your sword belt and leave your weapon on the table.
The hill dwellers nod to show their appreciation, and then beckon you to sit with them.
Then they continue their conversation just as animately as before,
speaking in a local tongue that you cannot follow.
But as they talk, they pour you a drink and provide you with food.
They seem quite welcoming.
Let's listen.
As you eat, you listen, catching a few words here and there.
Goblins! Arms! Christa Tonti!
They seem to be very concerned.
Tell them you've been there, ask about the goblins, or keep listening.
Keep listening.
Your interest peaked.
You keep listening.
Slowly, you piece together the story.
The group seem...
I just burped.
The group seem quite sure that a horde of goblins are planning an attack on Christa Tonti,
which is apparently one of the wealthier spots in the hills.
They're discussing whether or not it would be worth helping the village to defend itself,
which might mean they are offered some kind of reward.
You must help them.
Let them fend for themselves.
Wait a while and decide later.
More teeth.
You must help them.
Let them fend for themselves.
Wealthier, yeah.
You must help them.
You must help them, you declare earnestly.
Christa Tonti, it does not help us, one of the men points out.
They are rich.
We are poor.
You can be better than them.
You will place them in your debt.
You will place them in your debt?
The men nod, swayed by your ruthless logic.
And you?
How do you fight?
One man asks you.
I serve the King of Analand.
I serve myself.
I will help those that need it.
I serve the King of Analand.
No, I don't want people to know that.
I serve myself.
The men nod.
So you do not understand what we might lose.
The evening draws to a close.
The men thank you for your counsel and leave one by one.
All right, that's one.
That's one, that's one, that's one, that's one, that's one, that's one, that's one.
Okay, I'm going to bow my head, remove my sword.
Listen to their talk.
Keep listening.
You must help them.
Place them in your debt.
Okay.
I will help those that need it.
Wait, what?
The men nod.
Let the goblins attack tonight, they cheer.
We will use your strength.
The evening draws to a close.
The men thank you for your counsel and leave.
I'm fucking out of here.
I'm leaving.
I'm out of here.
I'm literally out of here.
I'm going to fucking leave right now.
I can't rewind a second time.
Should I leave?
I think I'm going to leave.
I have to leave.
Oh, okay.
I'm going to...
Fine, I'll stick around.
I'm going to explore the town.
Fine.
Halfway along the track, you come across a couple of merchants' huts.
You browse for items worth buying with your nine gold pieces.
Your attention is taken by a finely woven skullcap,
a finely crafted sword, and a small bag of provisions.
Name the skullcap.
You pick up the skullcap and turn it over.
Stolen from a priest of Dadu-Lay, the merchant declares with pride,
a fine piece of work.
Four gold pieces.
You can tell from the feel of the cloth that has no inherent magic,
but it might be useful in spells.
Try it on.
I'm going to put it on.
You place it on your head, but you feel nothing.
You take it off again.
I'm on it.
You pay him four gold pieces.
You place the skullcap in your sack.
That's enough.
You nod to the merchant.
Is there anything else I can help you with?
Yeah, no, I think I can use that.
Hold on.
Yep.
Hell, to activate the spell, the caster must wear a cloth skullcap.
The user may then read the mind of any intelligent creature nearby,
learning its weaknesses, the contents of nearby rooms,
and other such details.
There we go.
That works.
I'm running out of money.
Is there any work to be had here?
I need to earn some money.
The merchant sizes you up.
You look like a good worker to me.
One of my friends needs some digging doing.
I'm sure he would pay you and feed you for it.
Digging what, you ask.
The merchant shifts uncomfortably.
Does it matter?
You'll find out.
He stares at you.
So?
He looks over his shoulder at the path.
I'm going that way now myself.
You coming?
The goblins attack tonight.
I'm going to go dig stuff for money.
I'm doing it.
Follow the merchant.
He leads you to a house on the edge of the village
and introduces you to the householder,
a stout man who is probably incapable of lifting a spade,
let alone digging with it.
I'm ready to get started.
What is it you need doing?
Suspit.
Outback.
Needs digging.
How much?
Well, it's pretty urgent.
It's pretty urgent.
The old one's overflowing.
How much money?
Three gold pieces.
That's it?
I don't remember doing this.
Did I do this in the other playthrough?
You can keep your money.
No, I'll get started.
Spade's outback.
He replies with a jerk of his thumb.
You walk through the man's house into the back garden.
The smell is terrible.
The job is not just to dig a new suspit,
but to dig over the old one.
And it's going to be several hours work
that'll probably take the whole night.
You collect the spade stuck in the ground by the hole.
Pause strength.
Nothing with a D.
Oh, I can do big.
Grow in size.
Do toilet magic.
Z.
All right, I'm doing it.
You cast a spell and point your finger at the hole in the ground.
With a flash, a burst of lightning flies from your hand
and hits the ground.
Earth explodes upwards.
And when the air clears, you have created a fine hole,
a little rough around the edges, perhaps,
but you still saved yourself plenty of work.
I did the same thing.
Recycled zap.
You go back into the house and collect.
I did.
Shit, I did the same thing.
This is literally a rerun.
Fuck, really?
Shit.
It's all right.
It's fine.
It's classic.
You go back into the house and collect your money.
Three gold pieces.
The grateful householder also provides you with some food,
as well as a spare, as well as a space on the floor
to rest for the remainder of the night.
You settle down and fall asleep quickly.
You dream strange dreams as you sleep.
Your thoughts are dominated by the strange woman in the hut.
In your mind, she has become younger and more beautiful
than she truly was.
Flowers seem to blossom from her hair,
as though she was grown from the earth itself.
Overhead you fancy you hear the flap of giant wings.
The birdmen came for the crown, perhaps.
Before this journey is finished,
it will come for you, leaving Dumpest.
You did this.
Guilt is now setting in.
Yeah.
It's okay.
You rise early, dismiss the attentions of the householder,
and head out onto the street.
Within a few minutes of walking, you are out of Dumpest
and back on the road.
After another hour or so, the way branches,
with one path leading up into the hills
and the other turning downhill
and along one side of a barren, stony ridge.
Is that a village you can make out on the top of the hill?
Seems a lonely place for it.
Where are we going?
Uphill to the town?
Or go downhill around here to this big bridge?
Uphill or downhill?
Back to Dumpest.
Oh, I forgot to say, pull!
Sorry.
Forgot about the goblins.
They'll be all right.
They'll be okay.
They'll be fine.
Turn back.
Oh, this is close.
Uphill or downhill?
Dude, you're going to hell.
You're going to abandon Dumpest like you did that old lady.
Or did the lady.
You're a monster.
All right, where are we going?
You bravely ran away.
I think this is close.
Where are we going?
Come on.
We're going up to Urestanti.
The gentle upward slope becomes a steep climb
and you're forced to rest several times.
So far, you've been walking through the foothills.
Now the journey will become more serious.
When finally you reach the summit
and can look out over the low plateau you've crested,
you see the path runs through a small settlement
of crudely fashioned huts.
There are villagers out in the street talking and working.
It seems a happy bustling place,
despite the filth in the streets
and the barren surroundings.
Why do I have a memory of this place?
I like remember this person's face.
I remember this person's face.
I don't know why.
Another filthy city.
Yeah, every city is like filthy.
You see the filth and the stench in the air.
I'm going to wait.
You stay at your vantage point
and watch a while longer to see if things change.
After a while, you begin to notice something strange
about the way the people in the village are moving.
First, you notice one is limping.
Then another.
Then you realize they are all shuffling as they move.
Some use sticks.
One is even crawling.
I don't think I want to go here.
I don't think I want to be here.
Watch more.
You stay hidden and watch for longer.
After a while, you realize that whatever is happening
in the village, it is desperate.
There's no laughter, no joy.
There's no trade or commerce.
The women do not walk about and the men do not watch them.
It is like a prison camp.
I don't think I go here.
Go in.
I remember this place.
I forget exactly what happens in here,
but I know it's not good.
You must atone for all your other sins.
All right, what are we doing?
Let's do a poll.
Am I going in or am I going to try to help?
Maybe I can do it right this time.
I feel like something really bad happened.
If my memory is correct, I feel like something bad happens.
I don't remember.
Go in and help or stay away.
You have two rewinds.
Don't be afraid.
That's true.
That is true.
Seems pretty unanimous so far.
Yeah, seems pretty unanimous.
I can't believe I zapped the hole last time too,
and I did the same thing.
All right, I'll go in.
I'll go in, but it's going to be bad,
and I'm going to have to rewind.
I'm going to go and visit these people.
These are people in need of a savior.
You may not be that man, but you can try.
You approach arms open to show you are not a threat,
but the message is not understood.
The villagers see you and panic.
They begin to scurry inside their huts
as if you were an army and not a lone traveler.
Their bodies are thin and malnourished,
and as they disappear through their doors,
you notice some are missing limbs.
Walk straight through the village.
Stop at a door and knock.
Am I going to get attacked?
I don't remember what happens.
Break through, Omega Lul.
I can't.
I'll knock.
You knock on the door of one of the nearest huts.
There is no reply.
Enter the hut.
I don't remember this.
Enter the hut?
Another hut?
Or leave the village?
What do I do?
This is up to you guys,
because I actually don't fucking remember.
Yeah.
Leave, enter this one, or another hut.
I'm going to leave this up to you.
Why would I just go in?
Dude, we could steal some more sand.
Oh yeah, dude.
That would be sick.
Okay, let's see what you guys want to do.
Check another hut.
It's winning by a lot.
There are 10% of you are smart, right?
This is probably bad, what's going to happen here.
There's no way you're going to leave.
You're not going to steal from these people, are you?
No, you're going to scare them.
That part of chat is boring.
90% of us, dude, are dumb as rocks.
All right, we're going to go in the other hut.
Check, okay, another hut.
You approach the next hut.
From inside, you hear the murmur of voices, so you enter.
The hovel is tiny and foul, with no furnishing of any kind.
A small fire burns in the middle of the floor.
And by the far wall, a family of three cowers from you.
The woman lifts a shaking hand, as if to hold you back.
Create a force field.
What if she's going to cast a spell at me?
What if she's casting a spell at me?
Create a stench.
Oh, I can't.
Gack?
Cause fear?
Rock.
Turn them to stone.
That's fucking awful.
I don't have any materials.
I can't do anything.
I could do force field.
That's a lot of stamina.
Wait.
Dim.
Cause stupidity.
Doc?
Heal disease.
Holy shit, I can heal the disease.
I can heal disease.
I can heal them.
I have a potion.
Remember the potion I took in the very beginning of the game?
Remember, I sniffed it.
I smelled the potion.
I could fucking heal them.
I don't think I've ever done this in like the three playthroughs I've ever done.
I don't think I've done this.
I'm gonna heal them.
Heal disease.
Go.
You pour the blimberry juice out onto your palm and cast your spell across it.
Then you cast the liquid onto the terrified villagers.
At first, the potion seems to burn them.
But then you realize it is the peeling skin, boils and warts that are burning away.
The man is shivering as though he has been cold for days.
And through chattering teeth, he declares, you have cured us.
We have suffered the plague.
Plague?
Goodbye.
So that's what affects this village.
The man nods.
We are no village in truth.
A few of us were cast out of Virutanti.
A few from Dampus.
And a few from other places.
They forced us here with flaming torches to live or die.
He looks at his wife, who is weeping.
Most do not live.
How many are here?
Thirty, perhaps, the man replies.
We were a hundred once.
Please.
He steps forward, hands outstretched.
You have saved us.
You can save the others.
I cannot.
You can save them now.
Understand this.
You must leave.
I don't have enough blimberry potions.
I can't.
I cannot.
You shake your head.
As you show them the empty potion bottle, they understand.
So what should we do?
You need to leave.
You must leave immediately.
The woman is looking at her hands.
Her skin is soft once more.
And richly brown.
But we are well.
We are blessed.
The magic will wear off in a few hours.
You must leave before then or you will become ill once more.
They do not hesitate.
Taking nothing, they race back along the path towards Dampus.
You head quickly the other way.
From across the plateau, you see the man pause and shout something at you.
Beware the black lotus!
Then he's gone.
I can't save them all, guys.
I don't have enough potions.
I can't save them all.
If I had more potions, maybe.
Somebody just said, Ruh-roh.
Brach rotus.
Like Scooby-Doo?
Scooby-Doo.
Ruh-roh?
Why would Scooby-Doo be here?
Ruh-raggy.
Ruh-roh.
Brach rotus raggy.
What the fuck?
The path beyond the village heads downhill once more between thick trees.
Before turning into a narrow goat track that crosses a rough peak.
From the summit, you get a wide view.
Look around.
Head down a steep slope.
The next village is sprawled out before you.
And even from here, you can catch the sound of merry voices and shouting from the trees.
The streets.
It didn't say trees.
You remember, they're in the way to the goblin attacked village.
You haven't saved anybody.
Oh, no.
I sent them to their deaths.
That's right.
Oh, my God.
You're right.
That's horrible.
Oh, oops.
What's new, Scooby-Doo?
Coming after you.
Gonna fight.
Hold on.
No, I can't do it.
I can't.
I'm not good enough.
Head down a steep slope.
The next village is sprawled out before you.
And even from here, you can catch the sound of merry voices and shouting from the streets.
It must be a carnival.
Looking right, you hear a roaring noise.
And could just make out a beautiful, majestic waterfall.
Plunging from a cliff into a great rock bowl.
You watch for a few minutes, marveling at how clear the water seems.
Then it's time to move on.
You follow the track down a steep deadline.
Deadine?
Whatever that is.
Okay.
Only one way to go here.
Bridge of Van Kass.
Deadine.
I'm sorry.
Some way down the hill, you stop for a rest.
And sit on a boulder to survey what lies ahead.
The path leads downwards and at its foot, cradled between three peaks is a village.
And quite a large one at that.
Behind you, the sun is falling rapidly into the hills.
It will be night soon.
Could approach it or avoid it.
What do you think?
Should we get a poll?
Poll time?
In the village or avoid the village?
It's always approach the village, right?
Although, look, another village to kill.
Yeah, everybody's going to say pro.
I don't think there's ever a scenario where you avoid villages.
I mean, it changes things though.
You actually don't go to the village and you go completely somewhere else.
You end up in like the woods.
Yeah.
I mean, it's a bit that.
That is no way.
Okay.
Let's go in.
The village looks like a good place to stop.
You hop down from the boulder and make your way forward when an overhanging branch touches your face.
And you hear a lively chirping.
Hey guys, I think I remember this.
I think so.
If I remember correctly.
Turn around.
You turn around quickly.
Hovering by your shoulder is a small creature the size of a bird.
It is childlike, but very thin with green skin and it flits around you on transparent wings.
It seems friendly enough.
It even lands on your shoulder.
It's tiny clawed toes pinching slightly.
Talk to it.
Shake it loose.
Cast a spell or carry on.
Nothing with H greatest shield.
W.
Okay.
Wall is creating an invisible wall.
Yeah.
Bye bye.
Hey, hey, hey, hey.
No spoilers.
Some of no spoilers.
There are a lot of people that don't know what this is cause fear.
Get rid of them.
All right.
Let's we'll talk.
Talk to it.
Greetings little creature.
And hello to you.
The creature replies chirping.
My name is Jan.
It's Jan.
What are you?
What do you want with me?
See that village?
The creature replies.
Last time I tried to go through, they told me I wasn't welcome.
So I wouldn't mind some protection.
I can protect you.
What are you?
Where I'm going is dangerous.
No spoilers, please.
If it's supposed to be the Elmo voice.
Did I do?
What did I do for a voice last time?
What was the voice last time?
What are you?
It was Elmo.
Was it?
It was the Elmo voice?
No, it was not.
All right.
What are you?
The creature does a backflip and gives a low bow.
I'm Minnie.
I'm a Minnie Mutt.
Pleased to meet you.
It reaches out a tiny hand and shakes your earlobe.
The creature starts hopping up and down.
Come on.
Let's get going.
Can't we?
Is that correct?
That's it.
Okay.
I'm not going anywhere till you're gone.
What can you tell me about the village?
I can protect you.
What do you know about the village?
You point down the valley.
Is it safe?
That's biratanti.
It's very safe.
It's the largest village in the whole of Schumann-Hutty Hills.
Every traveler who comes this way spends at least one night here.
So it's a little bit expensive, especially for Minnie Mutes, but pleasant enough.
All right.
Hey, this is the replay of sorcery.
We need a poll.
Do you want me to get rid of them or are we keeping them around?
We need a poll here because I know what happens at this point.
I mean, I don't remember every single piece of dialogue,
but I remember sort of what happens.
So we need some opinions here.
What should we do with this new friend?
Keep them around or get rid of them.
I hate him.
Eat him.
All right.
Fuck friends.
Fuck them.
Fuck the friends.
Get rid of them.
No spoilers.
And stop effing.
I keep dropping so many frames.
Why?
I need somebody at Twitch to look under the hood and see why my connection has so much
trouble going to some of their servers sometimes with my internet being perfectly fine.
All right.
I can protect you.
The creature squeezes your shoulder gently.
It's like having a spider trying to burrow into your skin.
The creature flits to your other shoulder once more.
You're not in any hurry, are you?
It observes.
Do you want to sleep out in the rough?
Where I'm going is dangerous, by the way.
Let's get going.
The creature shakes you by the ear in excitement and you set off along the path once more.
You descend into the bowl of the valley.
The hills on either side are toweringly tall and throw the village into deep shadow.
It would seem a very gloomy, threatening place, but from the streets come the distant sound
of laughter and merriment.
I mean, we can sleep outside.
We can go in the town.
It's an earwig.
You should have killed him.
That was up to you.
That was not up to me.
We're going to go in, right?
We're going in.
This is what I want.
I'm making this decision.
You continue along the path.
The sounds of festivities grow louder.
It's almost spooky.
Here in the shade of the valley and after so long on the dire road, the people in this
village seem to be enjoying themselves.
See?
The minimite on your shoulder remarks.
I told you it was a happy place.
What's going on?
Jan, what's going on here?
Are they bewitched?
No.
If there was magic, believe me, I'd know.
This is the festival of the young.
What is that?
Well, take a look.
Jan waves his little hand around the village.
The idea is that once a year, the children are allowed the freedom of the village.
It's a time of great fun and lots of pranks.
It becomes quickly obvious what he means.
You pass the first building, first few buildings, where you find a number of children sitting
in the street and drinking ale from deep mugs.
Further on, a young boy is holding an old woman over his knee and is spanking her.
On the other side of the street, a group of boys is fighting outside a hut with a sign
that reads, Glandragor's Tavern.
Funny.
You've definitely seen that name somewhere before.
Wait a minute.
That's the axe.
What the hell?
The axe has that.
Isn't it Glandragor's axe?
Dude, let's get in there and let's figure out what's going on with this axe.
All right.
What am I doing?
Am I going to rescue the old woman or am I going to leave this person?
The idea is that once a year, the children are allowed the freedom of the village.
It's a time of great fun and pranks.
It becomes quickly obvious.
You pass the first few buildings.
The children are drinking ale from mugs.
What are we doing here?
We need a potential poll.
I'm seeing a lot of leave.
Leave, leave, leave, leave, leave.
I don't think we even need a poll, actually.
There's a lot of leave.
Leave, leave, leave, leave.
Okay, leave.
You consider helping the woman, but there's nothing you can do.
It is their festival after all.
All right.
I want to go in the tavern because we have the axe.
I one million percent did not do this last time.
Not a chance.
Behind the bar, a thick-set man is wiping mugs down with an old rag.
Greetings, stranger.
I'm Glandrigor.
Can I be helping you?
Greetings.
I've come a long way.
I'm sure you have.
Take a seat.
You do so, and Jan leaps up onto the counter.
Glandrigor seems amused rather than alarmed by the creature.
I have something for you.
Oh, yes?
He looks at you expectantly.
Give him the axe.
Should I give him the axe?
Give him the axe right now.
Let's do it.
Yeah.
You take the axe from your pack and lay it on the bar.
The old man's eyes light up as he sees it.
Where did you get that?
He exclaims.
I bought it from a merchant, or it doesn't matter.
I don't know.
Which one?
Like, it doesn't matter?
Doesn't matter where I got it.
No, but wouldn't that mean maybe I like took it or something?
I bought it.
I bought it from a merchant, but it's yours, isn't it?
He reaches forward almost nervously.
He is clearly overjoyed.
I haven't seen this thing in at least 20 years.
I spent every day with it.
He mimes a gentle chopping motion with the blade.
Perfectly pitched at neck height on a goblin.
Incredible.
I remember the weight.
How did you lose it?
Why did you stop fighting?
It was part of a raiding party.
There were four of us exploring the giant's ruins at Liyaki.
We descended into a cave system and the roof collapsed.
I was knocked unconscious.
They left me.
Couldn't get me out, I suppose.
Except that someone reached me enough to steal my famous axe.
Did you ever find out who?
Is that when you stopped adventuring?
He did onyxia with that axe.
Did you ever find out who it was?
No.
He shakes his head sadly.
No, I went on a healthy quest for revenge, but I never got it.
Not something else instead that made me hang up my traveling boots.
If you don't know what that is yet, well, you will.
Now here, I'm forgetting my hospitality.
Without putting down the axe, he quickly gathers a mug and fills it with ale.
For you, on the house.
You thank him and drain the mug deep.
The beer is thick and refreshing.
Then it is his turn to question you.
How long are you staying here?
Only for tonight.
Or I can't talk about it.
I see.
Well, and he nods.
Let me give you some advice.
There's a site nearby.
A place called the Crystal Waterfall.
Whatever trek you're on and whatever you feel about sites, you should go.
It's more than just something to look at.
He grabs a bit of paper and scribbles down a note.
Hand this to the idiot who collects the toll and he'll let you pass.
Okay.
What's so special about the waterfall?
I won't tell you.
That way you'll go just to find out.
You nod once.
And once you leave, where to next?
To Carr or to Canterpani?
I mean, I already was at Canterpani.
I would say to Carr.
Carr!
Now there's a town.
Listen, let me give you some more advice.
You're full of advice.
Okay, go ahead.
I have some powerful friends, you see.
He says, and his tone might be slightly threatening.
There's a man I know.
And he's quite an important man, too.
Name is Vic.
If you get into trouble, just remember that.
Even a name can be a thing of power sometimes.
Same as how you found me.
This is bound to be useful later.
Advice Andy.
Who is he?
A man of power and influence.
A politician, you might say.
Anyways, you'll find out, no doubt.
He takes to wiping down the bar again.
So you'll be heading through Torrapani?
It's a Svin village.
No humans there at all.
The chief will probably try to persuade you to help his daughter.
She's been carried off by marauders.
Vic, for first and overly,
you guys remember, some of you do.
Of course I'll help or it's not my trouble.
Of course I'll help, right?
Good, I'm glad to hear it.
Poor girl, she's been left as a sacrifice
in a dark cave guarded by a deadly manticore.
If you've not met one before,
well, watch your back
and your front.
And if you know a spell or two,
then all to the good.
The beer is done.
You stand to go, nod to Glandrigor, and head out into the street.
Jan flits quickly along behind you.
Or along behind you, right?
Alright, we going to the waterfall?
Okay, are we leaving town this way?
Are we going to find an inn or are we going to the waterfall?
Oh right, there was a mini dude.
Yeah, there is a little guy that we have.
Waterfall, waterfall, waterfall, waterfall, waterfall, waterfall.
Let's go.
You head up a path that climbs through a crack in the mountainside.
Soon the air is filled by a thundering.
It's quite a climb.
But eventually you turn a corner through a narrow cleft in the rock
and see close up the waterfall
you glimpsed from the hilltop earlier today,
lunging down from the cliffs overhead.
Large crystal stalactites hang down either side of the water.
There's only one path to reach it,
winding up the rock face,
and it passes by a small hut where a ruffian is collecting money.
Uh, don't I have a note?
Let's see what I can do.
Dud? The illusion of treasure.
Not the S. S?
Hey, sap, I can cause depression.
Uh, I can do the clone thing again.
I know, yeah, I have a note.
So I can just skip. I'm just curious what you can do.
Uh, yeah, dud.
Cause speed.
Cause stench.
Yeah, I have a note. I'm gonna go greet him.
I don't need to do a spell.
Greet the ruffian.
You make your way over to the hut.
Greetings, you begin.
You collect a fee for the waters?
These waters cannot be so healing that he has...
Whoops.
He glazes the ruffian.
These waters cannot be so healing that he has not caught an awful flu from them.
Read gold pieces!
You hand the scrawled note over to the ruffian.
You probably can't read, but he seems to recognize the penmanship as he nods furiously twice.
But he seems to recognize the penmanship as he nods furiously twice.
And then stands aside to let you pass.
The ruffian hands you a towel.
Alright, let's get in the waterfall.
You head up the waterfall.
Which cascades forcefully into a deep pool.
You strip off your clothes and dive into the pool.
While Jan flitters through the froth.
The cool water is fresh and invigorating, and you feel yourself getting rapidly better.
You feel a huge swell of confidence.
Coming here was the best decision you have made.
Wait, this water cures disease.
Wait, this water cures disease?
Something about that seems terribly important.
People should be told about that.
The villagers up on their lonely mountain, ravaged by the plague,
they should be brought here.
They can be saved.
But it is late already.
The walk back to the plague village will lose you a day, maybe more.
And with this place so close, they must know of it.
Perhaps their symptoms are too serious to be healed.
Leave them, start walking, or send someone else.
Start walking.
If you send someone else, they might not do it.
Shouldering your pack, you begin the long, weary walk back to the village of the plague.
You're not really doing this, are you?
Jan hisses in your ear.
You're crazy.
You ignore the small creature's complaints.
Walking overnight.
Let's go.
After an hour, you are within sight of the rise up to the village.
Jan is hopping mad.
Where are you going?
I thought you were on a mission.
You don't have to come, okay?
You don't have to go.
This is important.
Sure it is.
So is sleep.
You say nothing but keep walking.
A few minutes later, Jan pipes up again.
All right, all right, all right.
What is it?
What?
What do you want?
Jan shakes his head, leaping up from your shoulder to flitter,
irritatingly, right in front of your face.
Listen, you can't go.
I won't let you.
Why not?
Because I'll go for you.
Many mites can't catch plague, so there's no risk.
And I can fly faster than you.
And if I save a whole village, I'm bound to find someone who will look after me properly.
He looks at you, expecting you to argue.
Good idea.
Come with me.
But what if I get the plague?
Get two birds with one stone.
You're going to kill Jan and the village gets saved.
Don't get scammed.
But okay, but if I don't see it, then it didn't happen, right?
Oh, I can just go, I can go in the water.
Right, right, right.
But you know, what's the old saying?
If you want something done, do it yourself.
Come with me.
Jan shakes his head.
You don't want my company.
Trust me.
Then he turns and with a buzzing sound, he flits away into the dark.
You are alone again.
The villagers should be in safe hands.
But you cannot stay to receive their thanks.
It is time to find somewhere to sleep.
With luck, you will reach car tomorrow.
You wouldn't have done it.
We lose Jan.
Wait, so what's bad about Jan?
Ah, I don't think we tell anybody.
Don't tell anyone.
That's something to experience on your own.
Ah, sleep outside the town.
I don't want to spend any money.
Well, maybe the maybe he'll let me sleep for free.
Yeah, no spoilers.
No spoilers.
It's actually really, really interesting what it is.
I need to know.
It's pretty cool.
It's very interesting.
I wonder if will that guy let me sleep for free here?
Let's see if he'll let me sleep here for free.
You find the village in buried under a rocky overhang.
The proprietor stands in the doorway.
A formidable young girl armed with a baker's paddle.
What do you want?
She squeaks at you.
Where's my friend?
Different inn?
I don't know.
How much money do I?
I don't have enough money.
Room and board.
Nine gold pieces.
What are you talking about?
How much for a meal?
The girl looks down at you with a severe expression.
Four gold pieces.
No discounts.
No, fuck that.
You shake your head.
That's too much.
You run a lowly inn and not a palace.
The girl scoffs back at you as you turn and walk out of town.
No, I'm going to camp outside.
Fuck that.
14 gold?
I don't have enough.
I'll sleep outside.
You make your way out of the village
and into a stand of tall dry trees under the overhang of one of the cruel mountainsides.
Between curling roots, you find a small place to settle down and rest.
You're tired enough to feel your eyelids drooping,
but you're hungry from not having eaten.
Oh, god damn it.
You pull out a quantity of your cheese and bread and eat it quickly.
The night's darkness draws in around you.
In the distance, you hear screams and whoops from the village that only slowly fade.
You feel lonely.
Distanced from such revelry, you rest your head onto your backpack and close your eyes.
Perhaps a few hours pass when you wake suddenly,
aware of a shadow moving between the tree trunks.
It turns as it sniffs the air, a wolfhound.
You raise the spell and when it's ready,
you take out the bamboo pipe and play a sweet and merry tune.
The stupid wolfhound finds itself racing in circles
and curling up into an absurd little ball.
You play long enough and energetically enough
that it eventually falls asleep upon a stone.
You hurry in the other direction to find yourself a new spot to camp.
Then once satisfied, you lay down again and try to sleep.
Your dreams are filled with walking with peaks and valleys and endless paths.
A curious light plays across them,
building walls to heights before ruining them as it moves away.
And above it all, there is a warning.
Beware the black lotus.
Bard playthrough.
All right, so we're going back up here.
Actually, that's interesting that we're going up here now,
not like this way.
You rise early from your spot beneath the tree.
You rejoin the path on the far side of Viratanti.
The sun sits on the horizon like a gleaming jewel.
If all goes well, you will reach Torrapani today,
the last village in the Schumantanti Hills.
After a short climb, the path breaks,
heading uphill to the left and downhill to the right.
With Torrapani so close, it hardly matters which way you go, surely.
But it does.
But it does make you a choice.
You ignored the plague town?
No, I didn't.
I told everybody that it existed, and I'm hoping that they go there.
No, yeah, I told them.
I'm curious what that does potentially later.
All right, poll time.
Are we going right through this kind of brush over here?
Are we going left into this other brush over here?
Left or right?
You didn't walk back?
No, I did.
It was back here.
It was like this little area here, this little zone.
There's no obvious answer.
No, there isn't.
I'm actually surprised I haven't really died.
I know for a fact there's like at least 10 to 15 places
to just instantly die and magically avoided them all.
Okay, which way?
A lot of rights.
He did, yeah, the description was really quickly written.
No, I said it.
You yelled at the hotel lady and left.
All right, we're going right.
You climb a rise.
The way is not too steep.
And as noon approaches, you have crested the ridge and are descending yet again.
You're now at the highest point of the hills where the trees are thin.
The view west goes on forever.
And sometimes you catch a glimpse of CAR on the northern horizon.
I'm not going to eat.
I only have one ration left.
It's probably a bad idea.
I'm going to keep going.
You decide not to stop and eat, but push on.
A line of trees approaches the shadows between their trunks deep and threatening.
And then you are under the canopy and it takes your eyes a moment to adjust.
You come to a dead stop.
Something is moving through the trees behind you.
A moment later, a point of steel has emerged from the darkness between two trees
and touches your neck.
You've seen me.
Whispers a voice.
I know it.
Look into the darkness, walk away.
Answer, draw the sword.
No spoilers.
Keep those spoilers away.
I'm going to answer.
I see nothing.
You call back.
You're quite safe.
It is not I who is not safe.
Returns the voice.
Who is there?
There's no reply.
But the tall dark figure of an assassin emerges from the trees.
He is dressed head to toe in black and you had not seen him a moment before.
Even though he had been standing a mere arm's length away,
he wields a sharp scimitar in expert hands.
Fix.
Causes fixedness.
What does that mean?
Do jig.
Can I do jig on on this guy?
Walk a shield.
Oh, it freezes.
Okay.
Zap.
Maybe I'll make a shield.
Is that the only fix?
I'll make a shield.
What was K?
Nothing.
Yeah, I'll make a shield.
You could fix him.
You can fix him.
All right.
I'm going to make a shield.
You lay a gold piece on your wrist and cast your spell.
The gold melts into your flesh with a burning sensation and a shield blossoms into place.
You bring your sword up to bear.
Murder him.
That's actually pretty cool because that gave me an extra like 10 to 20 percent stamina bar.
F, F, F, F.
I hope this shit is fixed tomorrow.
I hope there's not any internet bullshit.
Hope there's no internet bullshit tomorrow.
All right, here we go.
I think he's going in hard right off the bat.
Let's see.
Oh, bad.
Very bad.
The assassin nods at you, taps two fingers against his chest and readies his stance.
Yeah, yeah.
My duty is to sever your head from your neck.
He declares in a voice is cold and polished as marble.
You will not hold me from it.
I'm going full blast again.
Okay, good.
I got it.
I caught that off guard.
Good.
Time to attack you.
Rush forward with a deep heavy slash outclassing his own sword swing.
You catch him deep in the side.
Red blood soaks his black tunic.
All right, let's pull it back.
Yep.
You drop yourself into a crouch behind your shield
and he hangs back and watches you without emotion.
Okay, you hold firm and keep your shield high and he circles away.
He's going to go full, isn't he?
What the fuck?
You circle around him at arm's length and he waits and watches you in return.
Damn it.
Acting quickly, you swing a masterful swipe,
but the impact clangs against his turned sword.
He grins.
He is left breathless, but otherwise unharmed.
Closing his eyes, the assassin murmurs a quick prayer as he sets his stance.
I have to defend.
Yeah, fuck you.
You whip up your shield as he powers forward,
but it only tires him out.
The shield takes the blow.
Oh, I don't get hurt.
Okay, he drained his whole bar.
I'm going to go light, like two, whatever.
Okay, he grimaces with effort.
Blood drips from the assassin's tunic.
He curses under his breath.
All right, ready yourself to block.
He steps away a little.
Do it again.
Oh, my God.
He's going to do it three times in a row again.
Again.
What the fuck?
Stop.
You move around him watchfully and he hangs back and watches you in return.
Breathing deeply, the assassin whispers a mantra as he readies his blade.
Full blast.
Let's go.
Got him.
Cast Earwig.
Painting left, you dive forward with a deep, heavy blow.
He is off balance and moving slowly, and the blade goes deep.
He turns and tumbles, releasing his sword as he topples.
I am not so proud as to not admit when I am beaten.
You may finish me if you choose so.
But if you do, do me an honor and use my own blade.
The assassin is not dead.
Flies on the floor, gasping.
Finish him and search his body or spare him.
Chat, no spoilers.
It's time to decide.
Finish him and search his body or spare.
I'm going to leave this completely up to you.
I know things about this game.
I'm sure a lot of people here do as well.
He has fought honorably.
Yes, he has.
You're right about that.
Y'all are weak.
Finish him.
You need to kill him.
Kill him.
It's dishonorable to let him live.
I have no say in this.
I'm going to let everybody decide here.
Whoops.
All right.
You have spoken.
We're going to spare him.
What's in the pockets?
I know, right?
I don't know.
We're not going to find out.
And get up.
You tell him, holding your sword back, but not putting it away yet.
He nods and sheathes his own blade.
You're an honorable man.
I'm glad to have met you.
Now you've saved me.
You own me in part.
My name is Flanker, and I am an assassin and a thief.
For those of you wondering, six or seven years ago, I was a really, really big fan of Game of Thrones.
And this was Jorah Mormont.
And I had a really good Jorah Mormont impression.
And I haven't seen the show in a long time, and I don't really give a shit about Game of Thrones anymore.
So, I mean, I'm trying to kind of redo my Jorah Mormont here.
And I don't know how well that's happening.
All right.
Why did you attack me?
What will you give me for your life?
Why did you attack?
It's a simple matter.
I picked on wayfarers for practice and hiding and killing.
I assumed you would be no match.
But I see I was wrong.
He bows his head once, perhaps in respect.
Perhaps from the pain of his injuries.
You're traveling to Ka, he asks.
Yes.
No.
Why do you ask?
That is the way I'm going.
Well, perhaps.
I will not see you again once we part now.
But if I do remember me, I will not forget the debt I owe you.
He is useless.
Finish him.
That's so funny.
He is useless.
Finish him.
They give you a second opportunity.
You're turning into Johnny Carson.
You're turning into Johnny Carson?
Oh, my God.
I could still kill.
I remember you there.
He bows his head again.
This time it's definitely from pain.
Oh, you cannot aid me.
And I actually might be able to help him.
No, you reply.
I have caused your wounds.
I will help you.
He grins with gritted teeth.
Are you a doctor?
I do not think you are.
Kill him.
They want you to kill him.
So they give you so many opportunities to kill him here.
It's three different times.
Bind his wounds.
Tearing strips of dark fabric from his clothing,
you bind his wounds tightly and the bleeding lessens.
You are too kind to a man who is about to kill you.
Let that be your lesson.
You reply as you gather up your things
and head out of the forest, leaving him behind.
You have a sense that you've made a powerful friend.
Very cool.
Leave the trees.
You continue along the path and around the side of a hill.
A wooden hut is set into the slope
with an old woman sitting on the front step.
A river seems to emerge from beneath her.
As you get closer,
you realize the water flows underneath her house
and the house itself is set on a splayed struts
like an insect straddling the water course.
A few paces from the front of the house,
the water plunges over the edge of a sheer cliff and disappears.
Greet past or greet the woman.
Look, another woman to kill.
I didn't kill anybody.
I stole stuff from somebody's house
and accidentally casted a spell
that like turned off their brain for a minute, okay?
I didn't kill anybody.
That person is not dead.
I didn't kill anyone.
Let's say hello, greet the woman.
Greetings, you call.
The woman looks up at you and smiles.
Get over here, won't you?
I can barely see you.
All right, what do you want me to do?
Walk past the house or approach the woman?
Let's do a pull.
Are we going in this house or are we gonna leave?
What's the deal?
What do you think?
Rewind to flank her.
There you go.
Somebody got it.
I like the water sounds.
Yeah, I love the sound effects.
It's just super calming.
This whole game is just like this.
And I wanna make this really clear to everybody here.
You're gonna get Elden Ring in about probably 30 minutes.
This is the tutorial.
What?
What are you talking about?
I thought this was it.
No, this is the tutorial map.
Just saying.
All right.
What are we doing?
All right, we're going in.
Approach the woman.
You approach the old woman.
She smiles a toothless smile and gets up from the step.
Come in, please.
She beckons.
I get so lonely living out here on my own away from the villages.
Go inside.
Thank you.
You follow her inside and take a seat by a long wooden table.
I'll bring us some tea, she says.
She sounds almost nervous.
Hurrying to her kitchen, she returns with two large cups.
Drink the tea.
Make conversation.
Let's make conversation.
The tea is still hot.
You cup it between your hands as you speak.
This is a beautiful place, you remark.
Watching the river outside the door plunging away over the cliff face.
This is the top of the crystal waterfall.
The river runs right under my house.
They say it carries all my goodness and youth away while I sleep.
And the villagers bathe in it for luck.
She giggles meanly.
I'm sure it isn't quite true.
Don't drink that tea.
Drink the tea.
What's your name?
They call me Gaza Moon.
She replies with a smile.
I used to be quite well known in my way.
You nod but you have never heard of her.
Don't drink that tea.
Why do you live alone?
It must be more dangerous.
Oh, no one bothers me about me.
Why would they?
You can't help but notice she has not answered the question.
You make to sip your tea when the old woman stops you.
Catching your arm before the cup reaches your lips.
Oh, I've forgotten the pot.
She goes back to the kitchen to fetch it.
Drink my tea, switch cups with her, or make a run for it.
What do you guys want to do?
Let's do another poll here because what do you guys want to do?
What do you want to do?
I'm going to leave this up to you.
I remember this.
So let's see what you guys want to do.
It's fun involving the chat with this because when I streamed this game six or seven years ago,
I think there were like 600 people here.
This is I kind of I like this.
It's a whole new experience.
You guys get to live with your own problem right here.
Because some of the things I don't remember, but some of them I do.
And this is one thing that I do remember.
What do you want to do?
Why would she stop you if she wants you to drink it?
I don't know.
It's a good question.
Drink the tea, switch the cups, or leave.
Looks like switch cups.
All right, which switch cups with her.
Let's do it.
While she is away from the table, you switch the two cups around.
Then when she returns, you lift the one closest to you and drink.
A sudden deep pain grips your stomach and you double over.
What's happening?
You wince and cough as you find yourself seizing up.
Oh, suspicious stranger.
I can count on travelers suspecting my witchcraft.
I'll kill you.
Please release me.
You try to shout out, but you are paralyzed and quite powerless.
The old woman begins to search through your bag.
Then with a coup of delight, she pulls out the spell book page
you were given by the old man in the tree.
My book.
She cries, the missing page.
Oh, why didn't you tell me you had my missing spell?
She scurries off into the kitchen and returns with a cup of liquid,
which she pours into your half-open mouth while ducking and stroking your head.
It is an antidote and you feel your body slowly unfreeze.
Finally, she slaps you to bring you around.
What is the spell?
Who is the old man?
We got the page, but that saved us.
What is the spell?
Who was the old man?
A rogue and a bandit.
Four days ago, I was visited by a traveler such as yourself.
But when I was away making my tea, as I always do,
he started leafing through my book and tore out a page.
He must have been a wizard of power because he vanished almost too fast for me to curse him.
Will you uncurse him now?
Well, she looks a little uncomfortable.
I'd rather think it might be too late.
I aged him to almost 130 years, you see.
I wanted to slow him down, but instead I sped him up.
She fuses with the page, preparing her spell book with some gentle magic.
You take the opportunity to leave.
Well, that's how that happens.
I lose a spell, probably.
The guy in the beginning of the game was a wizard and he was not old.
Zen, Yaz, Sun, Kid, Yap, Wrap, Zip, Far, Zed, Zed, Rez.
Bring the corpse back to life.
You lost the C-A-T spell?
I don't remember.
She took something.
Yeah, I think she took something.
All right, outside the village.
We made it out of that one.
The old man gave you a page and she took it.
Yeah, that kind of sucks.
I hate losing items.
It is now late afternoon.
You pass over the brow of the next hill,
and below you is the village of Torrapani, slung from one side of the valley to the next
like a flood barrier, observe.
Torrapani is a village of the Sphin, an aggressive-looking race of man-orcs.
You might expect their village to be rowdy, but it seems strangely quiet.
Go to the town.
Still, there's no way around it.
You will have to go through it.
Into Torrapani.
You enter the village.
There is a definite air of depression hanging over the place.
The Sphyns are going about their business slowly and miserably,
and pay no heed to you.
You sit yourself down on a tree stump in the very center of the village to consider your options.
Find an inn or make contact with the villagers first.
You're illiterate.
I messed up one word!
We should probably rest.
We should go to an inn.
There are three inns in the village, but two are closed down,
their windows boarded and their thatched roofs rotting through.
The third looks a little better, but at least its door doesn't look very good.
But it's still open, and the smell of well-cooked food drifts out.
From a sign by the doorway, it seems that food costs three gold pieces,
and a bed for the night costs five.
God damn.
Oh, I might need the ape later.
No, save the money.
The price isn't worth the value.
You turn away intending to sleep for free under the stars instead.
You walk out past the borders of Torrapani and settle down under the trees.
There's time to eat.
I have no more food.
You wolf down the last of your provisions, then rest your head and try to sleep.
Perhaps you manage a minute or perhaps an hour, but suddenly you wake,
certain that something is moving in the bushes nearby.
Show yourself.
Pretend to be asleep or arm myself.
Pretend to be asleep.
Actually, that might be a play here.
You stay still, listening carefully, waiting for your moment.
But there isn't a moment.
Out of the bushes on either side, five figures leap forward,
each grabbing a different part of your body.
Your ankles are held, your arms too.
We got him!
Cries a spin voice.
Then they are hauling your body out of the thicket and along the path back to
the village.
Where are you taking me?
Wait to see.
Pray to my spirit for aid.
Oh, we can pray to the ape.
Should we pray to the ape?
Pray to the ape.
In a whisper, you begin a prayer to your spirit, the ape, for aid.
Nothing happens immediately.
Then you reach a low hut and are thrown to the earth.
Your arms and legs are released.
Perhaps your spirit has heard you.
You cannot be sure.
But now that you have summoned the powers above, they will not help you again.
Somebody said, NFT ape?
No, dude, it's the it's the ape.
It's the do you hear that?
It's the ape.
The door is slammed and locked.
A moment later, it reopens and your possessions are thrown inside.
Wait to see what happens.
You pull your knees up to your chest and wait.
The long watchers of the night pass slowly.
And in the end, nothing happens and no one comes for a daybreak.
Everybody has that dog.
Daybreak.
You're still alone.
An hour passes before you hear any noise outside.
And then the door to the hut opens and five spins come in.
They drag you roughly out and across the street to another hut,
where an old man with gray hair sits.
He's wearing outlandish, colorful robes.
I name Prasius Chief.
He slaps his chest twice.
I apologize.
Then he bows, brushing the dust on the floor with his sleeves.
Rush him.
Tell me what you want.
Apology accepted.
Rush him.
Punching, germa punching.
Did I just rush him?
Rush him.
While his head is bent, you spring up and rush at him.
You almost reach him too before the other spins catch you
and hurl you painfully back onto the ground.
The Chief looks at you sternly.
Brave.
This is what we need.
He waves to a menial who brings in bread and milk.
Eat it.
It's free.
Grateful you bolt down the meal.
It does not seem to be poisoned and it nourishes you.
The bowl is removed and the Chief squats down in a pool of cloth.
I have need of you and your strength.
I'll help if I can.
Tell me I will kill you.
I will kill you.
I'll kill you.
The Chief nods.
No, I fear I kill you.
My daughter, my child, she is taken, offered to a terrible demon below.
She deserves it.
You want me to rescue her?
I will try or die trying.
He deserves it, Omega Lol.
He deserves it.
You want me to rescue her?
The Chief nods.
Succeed.
And you may choose your reward.
Fail and...
Safer yourself.
I'll do it.
Why don't you do it?
Safer yourself.
He gestures to the other spins who is still taking no chances.
Grab you by your arms and haul you to your feet.
Crack in the ground.
You are led along a short pathway through the forest to a crack in the ground.
One spin has brought a rope and another a basket.
They are preparing to lower you down into the pit of the earth itself.
You will pay me richly for this.
Take the adventure, try and escape.
I do have vague memories of this mission, by the way.
Giga Chad, escape.
I keep just running away and they just keep grabbing me.
And I keep losing health every time.
Take the adventure.
You will pay me for this.
You wait until they are ready, then step into the basket.
The Chief nods to you with respect.
Watch the darkness, he declares as they start to lower you down.
You hit the floor with a thud and peer into the darkness.
Your eyes can make out nothing, but a slight breeze suggests endless space in all directions.
You are blind, helpless, trapped.
Something clatters to your feet from above.
One of the spins shouts something down to you.
Feel around on the ground.
You crouch down and feel around your feet until your hand closes on the base of something.
You pick it up.
It is a dry wood torch.
Something else falls from above and strikes you on the head.
Tinder Box!
Calls the voice.
Curse whoever hit you.
You hurl a curse upwards.
The spins, despite their concern over the missing tribe member, laugh.
The sound echoes like water between the walls.
Feel around for the Tinder Box.
Rubbing the bruise on your head, you reach down and find the Tinder Box, like the torch.
You strike a light, and the torch blazes into flame.
Below.
You can see now you are in a large cavern, wide and deep.
At the far end, passageways disappear to the left and right.
When uneven rock fall at the far end of the cavern, you hear a murmur.
Listen by the rocks.
Go left, go right.
It's time to decide.
He has the Tinder.
He has to swipe right.
Well, that's up to you, because we're going to listen to you.
Left, right, or listen by the rocks.
A pole is up to you.
Listen.
Rocks.
Tinder.
Swipe right.
Swipe left.
I mean, that's unanimous at this point.
We're going to listen.
You clamor over the rocks at the edge of the cavern to investigate the sound.
It is a whimpering coming from the other side of the pile of stones.
The spin girl, perhaps.
She came in this way, but then the cave-in blocked off her path.
We'll have to find another way to reach her.
Where are we going?
I'm not going to pick this.
Unanimous Andy.
Yeah, we're going to have to do, we'll do a new poll for this.
Unanimous doesn't mean anything now.
That's unanimous.
80% is not unanimous?
Yes, it is.
That's 80% is unanimous.
That's me just describing what that is.
Unanimous means 100%.
Oh, okay.
Sorry.
Let's play semantics.
Unanimous means 100%.
Whatever.
I like saying the word.
It's a fun word to say.
80% would be majority.
Whatever.
But I like unanimous.
It's a cool word.
It makes me sound smart.
It's 50-50.
Good luck.
I actually don't remember.
So I can't help you here.
You're on your own on this one.
May as well do a coin flip.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Oh man, this is, this is fucking unanimous.
Wow.
By four votes.
We're going right.
You turn right, creeping forward slowly.
The passage rises up a gentle incline.
At the top, a thick crystal seam glitters in the torchlight,
and the tunnel ends in a T-junction.
Look at the crystal.
I'm going to look at the crystal.
The seam seems to be made of pure diamond.
It was no doubt in quest of this that these tunnels were carved.
But why is no one mining here now?
I want it.
Dig it out.
You try to pry some diamonds loose from the incredible seam in the rock,
but your sword is not up to the task,
and you would only make it blunt.
You could perhaps return with a proper pick,
but only if you can escape these tunnels first.
All right, let's go.
Left or right?
It's going to be quick.
It's literally going to be 30 seconds.
So are we back in the mines?
You are.
We are.
Those mines that you're referring to are way down here.
This is where the goblins were.
We didn't go in here though.
Although they could, could be similar.
No, it's probably too far.
We've got the pickaxe.
I think there was a possibility to get one at some point.
Up, up, down, down, left, right.
Oh shit, I forgot to say pull.
Left, right, which way?
That's my fault.
I keep forgetting to say pull.
If there are 10 of these choices, are you going to do it every time?
I don't know, maybe.
It's kind of fun to me in a way.
Always right gang.
Honestly, it's still it's legit 50-50.
So I could just pick random ones if I wanted to.
Look at this.
Always left gang and always right gang.
It looks like always right gang seems to be winning each one of these
by a very small amount.
And that's it.
Right.
You take the right-handed tunnel.
You walk down the passage for several minutes.
Then slip on some dirt.
And the ground beneath your feet gives way.
You plunge into a hidden pit and land on something soft.
Lucky escape.
Or maybe not.
Whatever it is you've landed on is moving.
And what's more, it's hissing.
You are in a pit of snakes.
Oh no, the ape is far from you.
It's too bad we...
Why did we pray?
Try something else.
Use magic, pray to the spirit.
The ape is gone.
We used it because we were getting captured.
What can we do for magic?
You ready a spell.
There's law.
There's illusion.
Pop.
Explosion.
We need a pebble.
We don't have any pebbles.
Nothing with F.
There's zen hover.
Jig is not available.
Looks like law, pop, or zen.
There's no F, really?
I could do law.
Probably would work pretty well.
If I had a grenade, I'd throw it.
Let's do law.
It's expensive, but it's worth it.
You cast the spell and feel the snakes come under your command.
Order them back or order them to help.
That's interesting.
Let's order them to help.
You command the snakes to approach.
They slither nearer and nearer and then they begin to climb the walls,
holding themselves erect until they form a living ladder that stretches up the passage above.
Should I test it?
Is this bad?
Should I just go quick?
I'm gonna go quick.
You steal your courage and climb quickly back up to the tunnel.
Back on firm ground, you watch as the spell leaves the snakes and they tumble,
snapping, hissing, and hungry back to the cavern floor.
You're soon back at the crystal seam where a side passage opens on the left.
Go left or go straight on.
Left, I believe, would just take us back to where we just were, right?
Because we went right, yeah, so we're gonna go straight.
You push on.
Here the cave system widens.
Pendulous stalactites hang from the ceiling as if about to fall and skewer you into place.
You skirt between them, following a thin safe path until a passageway appears on your right.
All right, it goes straight.
Right, gang?
Okay, I'm gonna take the reins here.
I'm gonna say right, gang.
You move through the opening in the right wall.
After a few minutes, walk up a shallow incline.
You begin to hear something in the distance.
A low rumbling.
Turn and run, or just, what happens?
Let's see.
I think I'm in trouble here.
Let's, you turn and run, but not fast enough.
The rumbling gets louder and louder until you look over your shoulder
to see an enormous boulder rolling speedily down the tunnel towards you.
The ape is not here.
Do I have, can I cast a spell?
Probably something.
You check the stars to see what spells are available to you.
Right, gang, and shambles.
Gum?
Create glue.
I don't have any glue.
Wall.
Create an invisible wall.
That's a good one.
That's three health, though.
Fix.
Cause fixness.
Ball.
Float in the air.
Wouldn't it still just hit me, and I'm just floating?
I think it has to be wall.
It's expensive, but you'll float above it, will I?
Will I?
Is there enough room to float above it?
I'm doing wall.
You cast your spell just in time,
and the great boulder hits your invisible wall with considerable force,
causing the whole cave to shake and shudder.
Then the boulder holds in place like a pawing horse.
But your spell will not last long.
You'd better move on.
All right, go right.
Swipe right.
The passageway slopes down a short way, then a crack splits the wall on the left.
Two stones are stacked on top of one another against the wall here.
Dammit, the stones.
There's nothing special about the two stones,
except that they happen to be on top of one another.
Turn back, go left.
Right, gang.
There is no right right now.
Go left, go left, go left, go left.
Straight, left, left, left.
How long can you hold a note for?
I held a Wilma for about 45 seconds, so a long time.
Left.
Anything but left.
Left, gang.
Right, gang, had their time.
It's time for left, gang.
You go left.
Then you spot, you see a spot of sunlight up ahead and rush forward
to find yourself back beneath the crack in the ceiling through which you came.
Climb out of the hole.
I'm out of here.
Get me the fuck out of this hole.
Left, gang.
Come on, man.
What have you done?
Can I climb out of the hole?
You set your toes into a crevice near the base of the rock wall and begin to try to
climb your way out.
The stone is coarse and cruel on your fingers and soon you have cuts below your knuckles
and on your knees and elbows.
Halfway up, the slope of the crack begins to curve over and the going gets more difficult.
Keep going.
You will not give up.
You keep climbing, one hand after the next, testing every foothold.
After some more effort with blood trickling between your closed fingers,
you are within a few reaches of the sunlight.
That's when they notice what you're doing.
A svin eye appears over the lip of the crack, then something.
One end of the coiled rope is dropped straight into your face.
You lose your grip and fall.
Do I survive?
You hit the floor with a horrible crunch.
Your ankle is badly twisted and you are lucky to not have broken your neck.
The rope is quickly whisked up again out of sight.
Get me out of here.
You ball up to the sky.
There is no reply and no rope is lowered down.
Classic left gang.
Okay, we're going straight on again.
You creep forwards through the dark, quite sure you are going in circles.
The ground begins to...
Oh, that's so stupid.
The ground begins to slope upwards and the walls begin to glitter
as you encounter a seam of crystal.
Have you been this way before?
Here the passage you are following splits.
You climbed out.
Left gang.
You take the left passage.
The way is soon blocked by a large boulder.
You turn back.
You're soon back in the crystal seam where a crawl space gapes on your right.
Right gang.
Soon you're back in the spot of sunlight below the opening in the ceiling.
Turn around.
Go straight.
You move onwards along the tunnel, quite sure you're going in circles.
This ground seems to dip and its lowest point,
the path you were creeping through finishes at another fork.
There's a stacked pair of stones here as well.
Run the pole.
Actually, I can do it.
Turn back.
What is it?
Straight.
Turn back.
Left or right.
Okay.
Go.
Turn back.
Left or right.
I love this game.
It's so fun.
The left gang is trying to kill you.
What is this game called?
It is called Sorcery with an exclamation point.
There are a few other things called Sorcery, so make sure you...
It's Steve Jackson's Sorcery.
This is the tutorial, by the way.
We're gonna be stuck here for hours.
All right, it's left.
You slip through the opening in the left wall.
The tunnel twists and bends sharply as if carved by a river now long since dried away.
You lose all sense of which way is which except to keep going forward.
With a winding seam forks again.
Another pair of stones are stacked in one corner.
Another pair of stones.
Okay.
Left or right.
Is there up or down?
There's only left and right.
How about face cam?
All right.
You've been good.
We'll do it for a minute.
What do we got?
Still pretty close.
You can just shave.
I know.
I will eventually.
This is left.
By a lot.
All right, let's go.
You go left.
The going is suddenly more difficult and you realize that the tunnel is climbing
at a quite a sharp gradient.
Little stones.
Little stones rattle and roll away downwards into the dark.
At the highest point, the cavern flickers in the torchlight and reaches a split.
As you enter, two stones roll away down the slope.
Two stones.
Where are we going here?
All right.
Last one.
Then I'm going to start picking.
Make your choice.
Yeah, I got to shave bad.
It's been a long time.
How long has it been?
A couple weeks.
Probably like a week and a half.
Delay is bad.
Do I have a delay on the mic?
Shouldn't be.
Looks like left gang is winning again.
Three lefts is just turning around.
Yeah.
Hey, don't tell them that.
They're making their choice.
It's too close to call, but I think it's going to be left.
There is a weird delay, by the way.
Yeah.
There's so many frame drops that hopefully it's been at least watchable.
Let's go.
The cave walls crush in close as though the rock is squeezing you to death.
Your shoulders rub against the walls.
When you feel certain you can go no further, the tunnel branches once more.
Two more stones are stacked against the wall.
I went left again.
You squeeze into the gap in the left wall.
You follow the passageway when you hear an echo of whimpering coming up the corridor.
Your torchlight falls across a frail shape.
Hiding in the shadows is the young spin girl.
Stacking stones into hundreds of little towers.
Traps first.
You run the torchlight around the walls of the cavern.
No switches or triggers that you can see.
The girl watches you with silent fear.
And then the torchlight falls on a deep scratch in the rock.
Claw mark.
Suddenly there is a loud roaring from the mouth of this short cavern.
The walls begin to shake and crumble.
The spin stone towers topple and scatter.
To one side a gap in the rubble begins to open, letting through a mean shaft of light.
But before you can head for it, the roaring sound is joined by a scream from the spin girl.
You turn slowly and peer into the gloom back along the tunnel.
Is there something moving?
Something coming closer?
Perhaps the roaring is the wind rushing through the tunnels.
Something is coming.
You hear the scrabbling sound of claws on rock.
And the exit from the tunnel is blocked by a dark and looming shape.
A manticore.
Huge.
Terrible.
It stands between you and the light and it howls in bloody rage.
Look at the creature.
Fight the creature.
Use magic.
You clear your mind for a spell.
I thought that was Pog.
I was like, no way.
What?
Strength.
I don't have fire water.
Puff.
Create wind.
I don't have a gale horn.
Dumb.
Cause clumsiness.
That's a lot of stamina though.
There's also goes.
Cause slowness.
Dopp.
Open locks and doors.
There's only huff.
Not hot.
No zap.
This fog summoned darkness.
Force field.
What would Dopp do?
I mean, hold on.
Let me look at Dopp.
I'm just curious.
I know it opens doors, but...
The spell may be used to open any locked door.
Casting the spell works directly on the lock tumblers and the door may be opened freely.
If the door is bolted from the inside, the bolts will be undone.
The spell will not work on doors sealed by magic.
Okay.
So why is it available?
What can we do there?
Or I don't cast a spell and I just fight.
I only have eight stamina.
I'm gonna try it in rewind.
I'm curious.
Dopp.
You cast a spell and the rock wall behind the manticore shifts and tumbles,
opening a wider passage through which you see the daylight from the crack in the ceiling above.
One of the tumbling rocks hits the manticore's sting,
which was swinging through the air towards you.
A lucky escape.
What?
Did I get out?
Wait, draw my sword and cast another spell.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Can I get out?
Whoa, there's new things.
Hold on.
Yap.
Oh, I can't talk.
I can talk to the manticore?
What?
Yob.
Summon a...
Oh, you shitting me.
Are you shitting me?
Should I summon a giant?
That's cool.
I wonder how cool this would be.
Hold on.
What else is there?
I can cast fireball.
I can go up.
Summon a goblin.
This goblin is going to get instantly killed, I think.
Giant versus the manticore?
There's more.
Mud.
Look at that.
Would you look at that?
Are you telling me that I have this ability to do this now?
I can suck this motherfucker down into the earth.
All right.
Can we just see what Gob does and rewind?
Let me see.
I'm curious.
Let's do it.
You toss down one of your goblin teeth and quickly cast the spell.
With a cloud of smoke, a furious goblin warrior appears,
making the spin girl shriek with fear.
But he is under your control,
and you direct him straight towards the manticore.
The little goblin fights valiantly,
ducking nimbly between and around the swings of the gigantic stinging tail.
But ultimately, he is no match for the vicious beast.
One strong swoop of a claw and his little body is broken in two.
Do it again!
You throw down another goblin tooth.
This one fares a little better than the first.
Perhaps each learns from the last.
He lands a few good strikes and then is crushed beneath a gigantic paw.
Then the beast is on top of you, and there is no more time for spellcasting.
Oh, god damn it.
They did two damage.
Go back, go back, go back, go back.
I'm using one of mine, one of my things.
I'm using one of my things.
Okay, it was Dopp.
But should I save the gob, the giant tooth?
I only have one.
Something else that you guys need to remember.
I, these are, these are my items and I carry them on through the rest of the game.
So if I use this giant's tooth, I might not actually be able to get another one.
I don't know.
I forget how rare these are.
I have two giant, let me hold on.
How many teeth do I have?
Two beeswax.
I have a ton of goblin teeth.
They're just so useless though.
They're funny.
Sometimes they can help a lot.
All right, I only have one pouch of sand.
I have one giant's tooth, not two.
Do the mud?
You're never going to be able to beat the manticore in a fight one on one.
Actually, it's going to be really hard.
You got to use yap.
I don't have the item.
I didn't get it.
Let's try, let's try mud.
I'm going to try mud.
I mean, I stole it.
Might as well try it.
Or that's too expensive.
It's just like fucking Resident Evil, man.
I don't want to lose all my items.
Let's do it.
You pull out your pouch of sand and quickly toss it across the floor, raising the spell.
The floor begins to bubble and bend.
And then suddenly where there had been solid stone,
there is now a sucking, grasping pool of quicksand right beneath the manticore's feet.
Before it can react, its front paws are being dragged below ground.
The creature beats its wings in a furious panic.
And its sting lashes and bashes at the wall as it struggles and tries wildly to free itself.
The sting is lancing towards you.
Oh, fuck.
Dodge left or dodge right?
Left gang or right gang?
Which one?
This is where the different gangs really need to shine here.
Okay, okay, okay.
It's running away.
It's actually running away right now.
This is what we're up against.
Do you understand how important this is?
Currently being sucked into the ground.
The manticore has about twice as much stamina as me,
so fighting it head on actually really sucks.
Dodge left.
You dodge left as the sting swings past you to the right.
You laugh.
A lucky escape indeed.
The terrible tug of war continues, but the spell is beginning to wear off.
And the manticore is such a large beast
that the quicksand is not enough to contain it.
However, it has worn itself out considerably from the struggle.
The manticore roars, making the walls of the chamber shake,
but listening closely, you can hear a note of fear in its too human voice.
It is still a beast of ferocious strength, but you have weakened it.
You'll have to make this next and final spell matter
or take it to task with your sword.
Wait, I can do six.
I can also do sap, which is depression.
Law, no way.
Will this work?
He's weak.
He's weakened.
Can I control his mind?
I could throw a grenade if I had one.
Zap, zip, teleport.
I could probably teleport out.
Law probably won't work.
Are manticores intelligent creatures?
Try law.
I got one more rewind, guys.
I have like no health either.
You cast the spell heart in your mouth.
This enchantment only works on unintelligent creatures.
But is the manticore intelligent?
Or is it a foul beast of base urges and rage?
You step back, sword drawn, ready in case the spell should fail.
For a moment, the manticore stops quite still.
Its sting lowers to the floor.
Its expression becomes one of dark confusion.
The great wings flutter and flap.
Shit!
Oh, no.
Then a moment later, it seems to wake once more.
The great sting rises in the creature's bellows,
a howling roar of rage and defiance.
Those old man's eyes glower at you with the hatred of all the ages.
Your spell has failed.
You're out of time.
You must fight the creature.
Oh!
The fearsome creature paces forward, teeth barred.
At the last moment, the manticore pounces all claws off the ground
and bared to plunge into your flesh.
It takes you by surprise and wide open, knocking you painfully back.
Spin Girl screams out an alarm.
The Spin Girl screams.
Only then do you see the giant sting plunging down towards your forehead.
In your weakened state, you are too slow to roll out of the way.
The sting lands with the force of a hammer blow piercing your skull.
The last thing you feel is the pumping of burning poison as it enters your brain.
What's my fate?
You've been killed in combat.
Your adventure is at an end.
Where the fucking ape when I needed him?
That's the first death.
It's fine.
All right.
We're going to layer the manticore.
We're going.
Let's go.
It's all right.
Okay.
This time, we're going to do Dopp.
Dopp lets us continue the rest.
Although Doze might do it, too.
Does anything cost no stamina?
Dopp is a good start, always, yeah.
Okay.
Now let's pull it back up.
Time for the giant.
I wish I had.
Should I go for it?
Is it time to bring out the giant?
But I want to keep the giant.
What if the giant could help somewhere else?
Mud was, I think mud was good.
We're doing mud.
Duck in the sand.
It was dodge left.
Swings past the right.
Okay.
Let's go.
This is the last chance.
Here we just, I mean, try to zap.
I could do six, too.
I could confuse.
Yeah.
Or sap.
Depression.
Can a manticore become depressed?
It's already afraid.
Pull up the six.
All right.
We're going to do clones.
Let's do it.
Whatever happens, happens.
You cast a spell, and as you lower your hand,
the spin girl gasps.
Three identical figures have stepped out from behind you
to the left and two more to the right,
each making the same magical gesture.
The manticore opens its spittle fleck jaws
and howls at all six of you.
What?
You can't even see.
All six of us.
Then it pauses and sniffs the air.
Of course, your clones have no scent.
However, you still have six times the attack power
and the monster will be forced to move slowly
to ensure it hits its target.
You draw your sword and close on the beast,
eyes focused tightly on the terrible sting,
but at least you have caused it some injury already.
All right.
I have six times the attack power.
Um, all right.
Defend.
Yep.
Good start.
I'm all right.
The fearsome creature paces forward, teeth bared.
You and your clones drop back, raising your guard,
hoping the beast will wear itself out.
At the last moment, the manticore pounces,
all claws off the ground and bear to plunge into your flesh.
You brace yourself as it comes down and leap aside
at the last moment, claws raking your skin.
For a moment, it is close enough to smell its warm, fetid breath.
Okay, that was all in.
We're going to go like two.
Fuck you.
Oh my God, that's bad.
What?
Oh, come on, dude.
Full blast.
There it is.
We have...
Look at how much damage we're doing,
and I have six times the attack power.
Really?
Okay.
The creature snarls and snaps at jaws.
You must finish this monster before it finishes you.
With the rock wall at your back, you have no way to hide,
but a perfect platform to spring forward.
You and your clones race at the manticore,
catching it a light blow.
The beast growls at you.
The walls shiver with its fury.
The spin girl edges nearer,
as if thinking of scratching the creature with her claws.
It's scared.
She whispers to you.
You might not believe me, but you've scared it.
Going again.
Oh, got it.
Beautiful.
Standing firm, you, along with your copies,
swing a mighty stroke against the monster,
slipping a little strike past the manticore's outstretched claws.
The creature crashes against a wall.
Smash.
Rock dust pours onto its back,
but as it tries to shake itself, it stumbles.
You can hardly dare to hope.
The foul beast is weakening.
All right, I gotta be careful.
Is a big one coming?
I don't know.
What was the last thing, what was the last thing he did?
It's like 2.4?
I think I have to defend here.
Yep, okay.
Fuck, I'm gonna die.
You can almost smell the creature growing enraged
and drop quickly away.
The manticore makes a nasty swipe with its fearsome claws,
but you and your clones duck and escape real injury.
You are gasping for breath.
The creature's relentless assault.
Its sheer rage is almost too much for you to take.
The manticore chomps and grinds its teeth,
its expression an ugly frown.
All in.
Good.
That's another three.
I'm going all in again.
In the darkness of the cave,
it's hard to read the monster's intentions,
but you cannot wait forever.
Dropping your weight, you and your copies
chop a heavy swing at the vile beast,
catching the manticore, passing cut again.
Right?
I think so, right?
Because he's used his whole bar.
I'm going in again.
I'm gonna, am I gonna die?
I have to do it.
I have to.
I'm dead.
Go again, go again, go again, go again.
Try again, try again, try again.
Okay, we're gonna go in just a little bit at like a three.
Fucking god damn it.
Try again, try again, try again, try again, try again.
All right, stop, stop, stop.
His guy, his bar is so much higher than mine.
All in again.
Just die, just die, whatever.
Fuck.
All right, I have to reset.
Reset, reset, just kill me.
All right, start over, start over.
I have, why did I spend all my health on?
I was doing, I did too many spells throughout the whole game.
All right, hold on.
I can't overpower this for a half to take this first hit.
Okay, now it's, I gotta go in at least at a seven.
Wow, that was good.
Okay, okay, now I think I can do it again.
This is 4.7, all in again.
All right, this is huge, actually.
That was actually a big deal.
Now I can, I'm gonna take a, I'm gonna defend.
Wait, you've scared it, right?
It's scared.
You might not believe me, but you've scared it.
I don't, I think it's gonna come in with like a one or two.
I don't know.
Defend, defend, defend.
Don't believe, don't believe.
Isn't it gonna be a little bit?
I fucking told you guys, I told you, I told you.
Now I have to defend again, okay?
Now we go in at like a five or a six.
Six, just to be sure, yep.
All right, I gotta do one more all in.
Grinds its teeth, expression ugly frown.
Does it have enough to do like six or seven?
God fucking damn it.
No, I'm so dead again.
The monster rears up and in its back legs, it fills the room.
I'm dead.
Oh, the manticore screams and howls
in a voice that is almost human and is dying.
Slowly, furiously, but nonetheless, it weakens.
I have to go in.
You fucked me up.
You guys fucked me up.
Okay, when she says it's scared, I'm going in.
Good, that's a four.
Again, good.
You've scared it again.
All right, now we defend.
Yep, we're gonna make it out.
This is it.
This is it right here, all in.
All right, literally have to hit it one more time,
but I'm gonna defend.
Should I?
Yep, good call.
Now we go all in.
See you later.
Goodbye, see you later.
The manticore laughs at you with a human expression of twisted joy.
You risk an attack of racing across the stone,
you and your five copies.
They didn't do anything.
Would I have done one damage?
Your sword blade seems almost to be possessed.
It finds its way past the manticore's sweeping claws
through its thick hide and down into its ancient, cruel heart.
For a moment, it howls loud enough to make the walls shake,
and then everything falls very quiet.
I'm almost dead.
The only noise in the chamber is the hammering of your heart
and the quiet breathing of the spin girl.
Thank you, the spin girl murmurs.
Then tugging at your arm, this way,
she leads you towards the light through the gap made by your dop spell
to the pool of sunlight in the first cavern.
Oh, that's good.
You wave the torch, hoping to attract attention.
Tell the girl to call up.
Girl, call to your father.
The spin child nods mutely, then balls at the top of her lungs.
Proceus, I'm here.
Then something drops down, a rope with a basket on the end.
The girl first.
Calls a voice from above, Proceus.
No, I come up first.
You call back, stepping into the basket.
The rope doesn't move.
The girl.
The girl comes first.
I ain't moving.
No, you call back quite calmly.
Once I'm up, there's nothing to stop you rescuing her.
If we're both to be rescued, you'll have to rescue me first.
A minute passes.
Presumably, the spins are talking it through.
The girl is looking at you, eyes wide with fear.
Recycle joke, Andy.
Come on, it's funny.
All right, swap places with the girl.
Her filmed eyes reflect the ordeal she has been through,
alone down here for so long, and your cold heart melts.
Don't let them leave me.
You whisper to her as you step out of the basket and lift her in.
I won't, she promises.
You cup your mouth and shout upwards.
Haul away!
The spins give a great cry and begin to pull,
and the basket starts to slowly rise, spinning as it goes.
The girl waves to you as she disappears up into the sunlight,
and she is gone.
A minute passes.
Nothing.
Wait.
Another minute.
Still nothing.
No sign of sound or movement from above.
That treacherous cur, Proceus, has betrayed you clearly.
The tunnel echoes very slightly.
A noise from the depths.
Perhaps the manticore was not alone.
Someone just said, you stupid bastard.
You wait a little longer, settling down on your pack.
You can imagine the celebration going on above ground.
The tears and grateful reunion.
No surprise if they lose track of you down here in the dark.
And then, sure enough, the basket and the rope tumble down.
You clamor quickly in and they haul you up.
Above ground, the chief himself helps you out onto the grass.
His daughter is with him, clutching his hand.
My daughter tells you fought bravely.
For that, I grateful.
I invite you with us.
Back, Torrapani.
Will you come?
Carry on to Carr or back to Torrapani?
Go back and kill them.
After all the shit you did.
Back to town.
Go back, back, back, back, back.
All right, yeah, yeah, yeah.
I'll go back, I'll go back, I'll go back, I'll go back.
A little generosity cannot hurt you.
You nod, I will come.
As you enter the village, it erupts into celebration.
You're given a place to stay and recuperate from your long journey.
A visit to the healing priest treats your wounds.
And when you emerge, it is to find the village.
Before so somber and silent, now in full life.
Flowers are tied to every rooftop and bands of sphyns are playing music on long, strangely
shaped lyres.
You are whisked away into the dance by Proceus's daughter before the chief can give you his
thanks again.
The night is glorious.
That night you sleep heavily and rise the next morning to continue your journey.
The chief meets you before you go.
You are rude, he declares, but we sphyns pay our debts.
He presses two gifts into your hands.
A pouch of ten gold pieces.
A fortune for a place like this.
And a key.
This opened the south city gate of Carr.
I hope it use.
I hope it is use.
Time to go.
You take your leave.
The path winds away from Torrapani.
And soon you are on a downward slope away from the Schumatanti Hills through stepped
rice fields.
As you walk, you feel for the first time the loneliness of the path ahead.
Though Carr is a busy city, it is cruel.
And beyond Carr, there is nothing but the vicious wasteland.
You'll have no time and no one to trust in the days ahead.
Wait, what?
For a brief moment up on the hills above the path you fancy, you see a figure stealing
its way along by some high and secret route.
A figure in all black.
But when you shade your eyes against the sun, whatever was there has disappeared.
In the distance rises the wall of a great city.
The first true stonework you have seen since you left home.
Your journey through the Schumatanti Hills is completed.
Along the way you have gained the friendship of Vic, an influential man in the city.
And flanker the assassin.
And have been given the key to the gates of Carr.
You've collected a fantastic number of magical artifacts.
A large lump of beeswax.
A cloth skullcap.
One giant's tooth.
Twelve goblins' teeth.
And a bamboo pipe.
You are still armed only with your original sword.
And have no rations and seventeen pieces of gold.
And dispelled book.
The adventure continues in Sorcery 2.
Ah.
City port of traps.
Now.
It's Carray.
Ah-ha.
Don't save Giga Chad.
What?
Why would I not do that?
But yeah, I want to show you something.
I want to show you something.
It's out now, yeah.
I would like to show you guys something, first of all.
But hold on, wait.
Oh shit, I didn't want to do that.
Okay, there we go.
This is actually kind of interesting.
Because this...
Oh, whoops.
I need to take a screenshot of this.
This is...
Oops.
I have like a save spell.
How come it's not showing on the screen?
Well, I'm going to print screen.
That was...
Okay, wait, why...
Wait, wait, wait.
Oh, there we go.
What the fuck?
Oh, that was weird.
The crown of kings has been stolen by the archmage
and taken across the backlands to Manpeng.
You've been sent to get it back.
But you fail.
The whole of Kakabad will surely fall.
You didn't save, did you?
Journey began.
Because I alt-tabbed.
From the outpost settlement in Analand,
you crossed the Shuman Tanti Hills.
Along the way, you spared the life of a defeated assassin,
saved a village from the plague,
fought and killed the dreaded manticore.
You faced starvation and disease,
a test of character.
To survive, you used your blade rarely
and your intelligence frequently.
You deceived, charmed, and tricked your way through.
The spirit guide changed as you changed,
becoming the ape.
Now all of that seems a distant memory,
but you're approaching Kare,
the city-bottom trash.
And look at how huge this fucking map is.
Pounded on a ford of the Jabaji River.
Kare was once a camp for the pirates
who ambushed merchants sailing from Lake Lumli to the sea.
But the camp grew.
It became a village.
The village became a town,
and now Kare is a magnet for ne'er-do-wells and thieves
ruled over by a council of villains.
It cannot be avoided.
Let the city do its worst.
It is a place of treachery and traps.
You will have to be constantly on your guard.
As you cross, your goal is the North Gate,
the only entrance to the backlands
and the next stage of your journey.
Your quest is to succeed.
You must enter the city port of traps
and make it out alive.
Ladies and gentlemen, Inkle presents
Steve Jackson's slaughtering.
Our to Kare, the city port of traps.
This map is fucking huge.
There's a ton to do in part two.
Kare also, I want to make this also clear,
Kare is the best part of the four parts by a long shot.
So, ladies and gentlemen, I'll see you tomorrow.
That's a good place, I think, to stop.
But we'll pick it up tomorrow.
You asshole.
On a cliffhanger, yeah.
So you, hey, you should better show up tomorrow.
Tomorrow will not be a four and a half hour stream.
Tomorrow will probably be about six to seven.
Tomorrow, is that, oh yeah.
This is a, I wanted to give you guys a taste.
Out of curiosity, I'm very curious, I'm wondering.
I know this was a little shorter,
but I knew I was gonna get through that first one
and I wanted to do the next one tomorrow.
So here's the plan.
Tomorrow, we're gonna do Kare.
I imagine we'll get probably
maybe halfway through Kare tomorrow.
And trust me when I say, there's so much,
there's so many things to do here
that it's gonna take probably two or three streams.
That's your introduction to Sorcery.
Is the game worth getting one million percent?
Yeah, this is one of my favorite games of all time.
You didn't save?
Yes, I did.
So today, part one, tomorrow, we'll start part two.
The next day, Sunday, green screen movie night.
We're gonna have three streams in a row here.
But yeah, I'm gonna put you on a cliffhanger here
because yeah, let's see you tomorrow.
We'll show up tomorrow.
Plus it gives me an opportunity to rest, I mean,
talking and doing voices and stuff
for like four or five hours is, especially with being sick.
I kind of want to, I don't want to overdo it too much.
So we'll start tomorrow, probably around the same time.
So we're around like one, two, one p.m.
And then it's green screen movie night on Sunday.
Hope you had a good time.
I know this is not a very fast paced thing,
but I do genuinely find this to be,
it's one of my favorite experiences ever in all media.
It's just so whimsical and so interesting, especially here.
That part one is literally a tutorial.
But we'll see how people like tomorrow.
Hopefully the internet is, I can actually connect to the server
and it's not gonna be a pain in the ass tomorrow.
Yeah, hope you guys liked it.
I love this, so we'll see you tomorrow.
1 p.m. Pacific.
Yeah, Swindle Stones is literally coming up
in the first like 40 minutes of the stream tomorrow.
Try a non-West Coast server.
Yeah, maybe I'll try to connect to like a central
or like an East Coast, but we'll see you tomorrow.
Thanks for watching, guys.
Shorter, I know, but I think it's a good place to stop.
Makes sense.
Take care of yourselves.
Good night, goodbye.
See you tomorrow.
It's always a pleasure.
I'm, we got exciting things back to back here.
I'm so ready for the green screen night.
I've been told that there are a lot
of really good submissions so far, hundreds of them.
So this is gonna be interesting.
Is it actually gonna be ready for Sunday?
It should be.
I'll check back in with everybody.
Tomorrow I'll give you an answer, but it should be okay.
I'll give you a time tomorrow.
It'll probably be Sunday night.
I feel like Sunday night's a good place for it.
And look, if it's not ready, then it can move in a day or two.
That's fine.
Will there be an encore?
Probably, likely, yes.
Did I change my mic settings?
It cuts out again when I get loud.
I did, I did.
I feel like it, even with it cutting out,
I feel like it's better overall.
But I need to find out why that's happening.
Your mic is weird again, yeah.
It's better than it was two days ago, though.
If I was gonna be getting loud, loud,
which I don't understand why the compressor keeps doing that.
I've used a compressor for like 12 years.
This guy is always loud.
Should've just used your first stream mic, oh god.
Quit stalling and leave.
Come on, dude.
I'm just hanging out.
I might change to the other setup if I can't figure it out by tomorrow.
Because I don't want my mic to be a piece of shit, you know what I mean?
Oh, that's a cool poll.
Was this your first time seeing Sorcery?
Please, please, guys, if you have an iPad or whatever,
wherever you can get comfortable, like really comfy and just relax and shit.
Man, getting into Kare for that first time is...
You just get comfortable.
Just sit there with like a cup of tea or something.
Just relax.
Take a shit, you know what I mean?
Just take a shit and play for like an hour.
It's amazing.
This is my favorite road trip game.
Oh, that's so cool.
Or like an airplane.
If you plan on taking a long trip,
Kare will take you probably 10 to 12 hours to get through, at least.
And remember, there's like a dozen different routes you can take in these games.
You're going to miss everything.
So you're going to have to play through it like fucking 10 times.
I hope you enjoyed it.
It's the first thing I ever did really on stream.
When we get to the end of Kare, we'll do another poll to see how people are liking it.
If people want to continue, if we want to go to part three, which is really crazy.
Part three dials up the...
Well, I don't want to say anything.
Part three is wild.
I think part two is the best.
Part three is probably a close second best.
And then part four is a mess, but not in a bad way.
It's just crazy.
The whole game is crazy.
But good night, guys.
Thank you so much.
We'll see you tomorrow.
Take care of yourselves.