Good morning, or good afternoon, if you're from the European prob.
My name is Jeremy. I'll be joining you here for a few hours, at least probably three, four hours or so before my doctor's appointment today.
That's why I am live.
So early. I have doctor's appointment. This is the follow up to my colonoscopy. So I have to go to it.
Can't just not go. So I figured that we would watch some old YouTube videos. Remember, we were talking about that last week.
Epic? What's epic? Old tuber? Yeah, we're gonna dig into the old VHS file here.
I'm at work. Well, just, you can't, you can't be productive. Look, just, okay, here's my, I don't know where you work. But let's say you work at
retail or something. If you work at a retail shop, or you work at like a department store, this is something you should never do. This is part of a funny character joke.
But what you should do is just put me through the PA system in the store. So then you don't have to worry about missing something.
Can you imagine the customers in like a department store just walking around and they'll just hear this? They would think somebody at the store was doing this.
Yeah, I'm really trying to get my podcast career going. All right, dude. But anyways, I'm going to show you, I'm going to show you me real soon here.
You're going to get to see, you're going to get to see my face. Oh, I've got another thing to tell you too, but I'm going to wait till there's enough people in here before I talk about that one.
I've got a, this is an update stream. Yeah, I'm going to do a face reveal. It's been long enough. I better be in a Spider-Man costume, right? No.
Your hair? What about my hair? You know, somebody asked me, what, what is with you and having like the slicked back hair for E3?
Well, it's nothing to do with E3. That's a joke. This is a stream before noon.
Because I got, that's like, that's like I showered today hair. So anything you see my hair like this, it means that there was very, very recently there was a shower.
It's not, this is just water. It's not grease. Your hair's really greasy today.
This shows my real hairline though. Now you, nobody can tell me that, that I don't. Look at, look at that. Oh, no, we're not going to do that. We're not going to do that. We're not going to do that. That was just like, there was like a McDonald's M right here.
I'm 34 years old. All right. I look, I look pretty good for 34. Anyways, let's get that off. I don't know, get me out of here.
No, you don't. I look good for 34. That's what I tell, every time I get to look in the mirror. Anybody else do this? I stand in the mirror naked and just like move my shoulders around. Like you go like this, you just go, I look pretty good.
And then you fucking move on. What a fucking freak. Am I a freak? I just like move my body around. I don't flex in the mirror. I just like fucking move my arms and shoulders around for like five minutes. And then I say 34, by the way.
I say it like 10 times. I hear Kim walking back and forth, just like sighing. I don't know what that means. Does that, what does that mean?
Anyways, let's, let's do some videos. We're only going to be here for about four hours or so because I have to, got to go. So I got to leave by, what time is it? 11, 12, 1, 2, 3, 4. Okay. I got like, I got like four and a half hours.
Four hours. So the first one we're going to watch is Streamer's Choice. We're going to watch old videos. And Streamer's Choice is the video that I have to figure out right now because I didn't pick one.
Let me think here. What like old video do I want to watch? I don't have any. There's so many. Shit. I just went into like the chocolate store and went up to the front and the person behind the counter, like the candy, coffee, not the candy, the candy, the chocolate candy, the chocolate candy counter.
I got it. I figured it out. The lady at the chocolate candy counter is like, can I help you? No. Then you leave because you're fucking scared to pick chocolates. All right. I got one. I got one. I got one. Hold on.
Yeah. We'll, we'll watch the Wonder Book. We didn't, we didn't watch that one last time, did we? If you type in Wonder Book, which one? Book of Dinosaur? Book of Spells? I haven't seen these in a long time.
All right. We'll do Book of Spells. This thing was so fucking stupid. I look like a fucking psycho. God, that's short hair. Like just didn't do much justice for me, I don't think. Oh, but I forgot about the update. I have an update for, whoa, whoa, wait, hold on.
All right. This is Book of Spells. Okay. Don't mind me. I was just, I just, every couple of weeks, I just relive the fact that I beat Sekiro and I just like, I watch some of my old Sekiro playthroughs to make sure like, see how good I did.
Oh, this is Book of Spells. Hey, there it is. You guys want my dumb ass on camera? Or is there, that's how this works, right? Holy shit, hold on. I gotta like tape these down. It's, all right. It's getting to the point where I'm getting like old man, like fucking Christopher Lloyd hair back here. And I really considered at one point putting like masking tape just like this.
All right, let's go. Intro music? Is there, is there, did I just, there, let's go. You ready? This is the Wonder Book. Hopefully you can hear it. Oh, I'm ready. Oh, intro music. You mean the intro music was on. Okay. I fixed it. Why is the intro still on? I turned it off. All right. Here we go. Book of Spells.
Welcome to the, I found in my Book of Spells, it seems.
Wooden paneling.
We're going to go with Slytherin.
Because I have my ceremonial wizard garb on.
Look at my hand.
That's good comedy.
I'm like glitching through this.
You're going to take your wizard photo?
Okay.
Gave me my wizard photo.
Come on. I was, I was a fucking, I was a path maker.
Am, am I a wizard yet, mommy?
I was the AR guy.
Oh, it's a frog.
Whoa, look.
Oh shit.
Wee.
Where'd he go?
Come here.
Come here, frog.
I got ya.
Bye.
This shit was actually really cool.
No, come here.
Come here.
Ah, he's gone. See ya.
All right, get another frog. Good.
All right, I'm going to do, when guardian of the author.
He's saying so.
Oh, there's Mr. Frog.
Oh shit.
I need another frog.
I need another frog, please.
Respawn the frog, please. Thank you very much.
He looks so young.
Where am I supposed to put him?
He's going way too far away.
Of course, this toad was just conjured up.
Oh, there he goes.
You need to be a bit more careful.
Watch where you spray that thing.
Oh, where's the book?
Oh, that looks bad.
Oh, look out.
Look out, man. I got ya.
It's like a super soaker commercial.
That's a super soaker commercial.
I got ya.
Look out, Timmy.
What do you want?
Keep your wand under control.
Cool.
Let's go.
Let's move on and go back later if you like.
I look fucking 17.
Oh, fascinating.
It appears to be a hole in your book.
Oh, look at you seeing that hole there.
Look at it there.
Whoa.
I can't see you.
I feel like I'm on a Universal Studios ride.
Where's your book gone?
There we go.
Nice tuber reactions.
These are pretty good tuber reactions, I would say.
Ow.
What the fuck?
Oh, shit.
I'm back. I'm back.
It was a joke.
I'd still do that.
That was a joke.
I was just fucking around.
All right, let's go.
The master of the test.
What?
Oh.
All right, what am I doing?
My grandkids are going to see this.
They're going to feel like what the fuck was wrong.
What?
Oh, this is so fucking stressful.
To cast there, try again.
I think water is the key to solving this bit of the test.
That's water.
Oh.
All right, what am I doing?
Pull up the glowing text on the page to begin.
Oh, this is so fucking stressful.
Okay, I thought for a second I was speaking a different language.
I think water is the key to solving this bit of the test.
That's water. Isn't that water?
What?
Not quite sure which spell you were trying to cast there, try again.
What the fuck is it?
What is water?
Why am I looking down at the book to see what it is?
The book is not, there's nothing here.
That's not here.
Why am I?
Get some water in there.
Oh.
You should be able to run out of water.
Oh, I spilled it.
Oh, come on.
He's telling me that's not going to spill out.
Are you kidding me right now?
This is just like jello in here?
What the fuck is going on?
What the fuck did he say?
What?
It's me, I said it, it's me.
What the fuck?
I'm stuck right now.
See, this wasn't even like part of making a book.
Get up!
Get off of me!
I just do this shit.
What the fuck?
I'm stuck in my robes.
Remember how I told you about how, we're going to go back here.
Remember how I told you how I just do shit?
Remember, you cut up a video.
This video, I probably took like two or three hours playing this game.
And I was just sitting there doing this.
The only reason why this clip was used is because I got stuck instead of ripping my robe like in half.
That's the only reason why this is here.
This, what you're looking at right here, is what I probably did for 20 straight minutes.
...in this chapter.
And now here's the part that I wanted to keep.
Get up!
Get off of me!
Fuck, I'm stuck in my robes.
You see these like birds, these butterflies?
I just really can't have a kiss.
Inspector Patronus!
I've had a kiss!
Oh, this clock is broken.
I gotta...
Oh, it's all over me!
Oh, boy, what do I do?
Reparo!
Oh, come on now.
I get it.
I wasn't even trying.
Nearly there.
Trial number three looks straightforward.
My guess is you need to make things a bit more balanced.
Big!
A scorpion smaller won't help, making him larger might though.
Do I have to make the scorpion big?
Why do I use this?
I don't want a big-ass scorpion!
Wait, it's still glowing.
Does it look like stinging balls or something?
Why do I use this?
Hey! Hey! Hey!
I'm in a kiss!
I guess this is kinda cool.
Shit.
Okay, I'm turning the page.
Oh, this is a classic.
This is classic, what happens here?
I think I busted it.
Classic.
I'm pretty sure I broke the book.
I'm pretty positive the book is all screwed up right now.
If I hold it...
Come on! Classic!
Come on!
What the fuck is going on?
The book is messed up!
Book of Spells, my ass!
How long does this go on for?
It's all glitched out.
It weighs like the calibrate button.
Cool, it's me, right?
Fuck off.
This is like last second parent Halloween costume.
I don't even give a shit!
That's like, oh, my kids want to go trick-or-treating.
Oh, may as well just put a hood on.
Now I'm a wizard or sorcerer or like a guy.
That was it.
That was the book of spells.
If you're new to this channel or you haven't been here for that long,
there are like two more of those and we're going to suffer through them right now.
No, that was fun.
That was a fun video.
What was wrong with that?
We're going to suffer through it.
First let me find it.
Oh, the update.
The update, the update, the update.
What's the point of this stream?
This is one of the most highly requested streams.
I get it all the time.
A lot of people want me to watch old videos of mine.
So the point is to just hang out and watch for a couple hours.
I mean, there's not really, there is no like point.
I mean, the point is just to remember things and watch things.
I don't know, just for fun.
Oh, the update.
Let's just say it.
The robot carnival stream.
Let's get on camera for this because I want people to make sure
that they can see my mouth moving and shit.
The robot carnival stream is going to have a hard date in like less than a week.
That shit is going to be on total fucking lockdown and it's going to happen in September.
And I will have a real hard actual date.
And we'll be talking about this all for the next two months straight.
I'm going to have to fly out like two or three times to this facility
because it's not happening in Vegas.
It's not happening in Vegas.
This is happening on location somewhere because it's not here.
So an announcement of an announcement.
Well, the announcement of the announcement is that it's going to be late September.
I can't give you the exact day in September,
but just know that it's probably going to be the last week or so of September.
It's probably going to be, well, you'll see, alien carnival.
What do you mean alien carnival?
What does that mean?
Wait, wait, wait, hold on.
Explain this to me.
I get all of my fucking meme news from like you guys.
So I need to be dealt with.
What is this Area 51 thing?
I don't get it.
I don't understand what this is.
Area 51, we'll go and find the aliens.
I don't understand.
People are planning to raid Area 51.
That's it.
That's the joke?
So that's like a thing on Facebook that you sign up for and like five million people say like, yes, I'm going to go.
And just like your fucking birthday party that you do on Facebook, like three people show up.
Like, why the fuck did you accept the Facebook invite?
Don't do that.
Just ignore it.
Just pretend like you didn't fucking see it.
I would rather you pretend you didn't see it than say yes.
By the way, you're going to get liquidated if you fucking try to do that.
They have like liquidation rays pointing like in corners.
Are you serious?
You're going to be like, your body's just going to fucking, I ain't doing that.
All right, let's get the next video.
In fact, those liquidation rays happen so fast, you don't even know what happened.
You'll be talking to somebody next to you.
And you'll like turn like this to like look over you like a bird will fly by.
You'll turn, the person's gone.
It happens so fast.
You don't even hear a noise.
You'd be like, oh, hey, yeah, you got the supplies.
You get the Campbell's tomato soups.
We're going to need those.
The tents are set up and they're gone.
And those people are gone too.
You won't even know.
Cut his mic.
Everybody knows this.
Okay, this is not.
Guys, the Area 51 was a meme back when our parents didn't even know what the word meme was.
They've got a little gray guy in the Area 51.
Did you see the pictures?
That was like fucking 80 years ago.
This is like, this is old news.
You're on old news now.
All right, let's do book of dinosaurs.
Just move the secret stuff there.
Yeah. Okay.
If you were the government and people knew that Area 51 was like the jokey alien place.
Don't you think that that would just be like a.
Oh, yeah.
Area 51.
That's right, guys.
Don't say anything.
That's where the aliens are.
No, they're fucking somewhere else.
I should know.
That's in my backyard.
That's it. That's it. That's in Nevada.
That's it. I know. I know the state.
There's nothing there.
I know my state is a young German.
Again, this time it was a hat on though.
That's it.
You want to talk about like the ultimate boomer meme?
It's like Area 51 has aliens.
Today, we're going to find out something really important.
Real important to me, real important to you, real important to the social studies of your school.
Ask your professor, ask your teacher this or a guardian.
What happened to the dinosaurs?
Did they get extinct?
Oh, preparation.
Use your hammer to crack open the shells.
Use my hammer to crack open the shells.
This is the kind of power that I don't want to have.
You want me to smash up these eggs?
Easy.
Frustration.
They're OK.
This is one of the rarest things I've ever come across.
That's an archaeologist.
That wasn't right.
You need to really look and find them.
They're hidden all over the place.
Check it out over there to the right.
You might be able to find one.
What the fuck? Oh, right.
Juniper, I've got a little snack for you.
Come look. It's a snack.
You're hungry, aren't you?
Come on.
Come get it.
Put that in mine.
Oh, she's really nervous.
Try gently waving the plant to make it come closer.
And keep it nice and quiet.
It's a fucking cartoon clutch.
I didn't think I'd be taking a quiz.
Which of these animals is the loudest?
Is it a blue whale?
A howler monkey?
A bullfrog?
A tiger?
Bullfrog, final answer.
No, I didn't want to.
Of course, of course, tiger.
No, bullfrog.
It is a bullfrog.
Bullfrog is the loudest animal on earth.
How could you not know that?
How do you make that mistake not knowing that?
What is it, a fucking blue whale?
Oh, yeah.
Yeah, in your fucking made up history books.
You looking at me?
Are you looking at me?
Hey, hey, whoa, whoa.
You want to fight?
That's so easy.
Oh, another one of these jokes.
What the fuck do you think I'm doing?
What the hell are you talking about?
That's what I'm doing.
That's the front cover.
Is this not the front cover?
You'll need to turn the ones but there was sounds like trouble
This was way in the fights time though. Are we gonna get to see a fight?
All right. Let's take a look
Front row seat front row seat for the fight
Here we go, so who we which one of these are we got like on the side of
I'm just like a dickhead in the bush. Oh, what are they doing over there?
They could have put a little bit more interaction in this they really do just put you like in a book
Why do I have to be the bush creep every single time?
Why can't you just like be in like why can't I be riding on the back of the triceratops?
You know, I mean, I should be riding on his back and like throwing bricks
similar extremely heavy object
But no, I'm sit I sit here and give fucking Wiimote commands
Full commentary stop agreeing. It's me. How am I not gonna agree with myself?
Wow, that was some
What do I have to do here? I have to weigh this
How do I weigh him?
There's so much dump like dumb weird shit in these games that didn't get show. He weighs more than he weighs more than a bicycle. Oh
two bicycles
Does he weigh more than three bicycles?
He could weigh more Wow
Wow
Laugh it up. It's such so funny. Yeah, it's so funny dinosaur droppings. Laugh it up guys. Here's your opportunity to laugh it up
Okay, is that is that suggesting that I just got dinosaur shit on my face
Is that what they're suggesting that has to be what they're suggesting that you just got shit in your face
Like when it splashes and hits the screen
Rated E for everyone
bullshit
I can't stop fighting
Right easy
Easy easy. Hey, hey, hey easy
This goes to your brother first not for you first. He eats first
He did his homework before you
No, I already
Been over
We can't view this page. You have any idea how much this wonder book cost me this one?
You know how much you have any idea how much it costs for a wonder book?
five bucks
Yeah, it's fucking cheap
It was but that was five dollars the games on the other hand were like 20
How much of that? How much of those right now? That was like ten years ago, right?
2012 2013
Have they appreciated in value or are they could I have like made like a ton of money with with my wonder book?
No, it's depreciated
Yeah, but
It's selling for $15 on Amazon. So I got up a five bucks
Five ten fit. That's a two. That's like a two hundred percent increase. I would have a two three X to my money
That's a big deal
Four dollars plus shipping on eBay. Never mind. Okay, so I didn't make any money. I didn't make any theoretical money here
So that was our book of spells. There's one more might as well just do the whole saga
There's book of potions
Wonder book book of potions is the last one
This is the one where I wait do I do I do I actually do that? That doesn't sound very nice
Book of potions. This is the most recent one. We did him an order
But you didn't you didn't think we were gonna play every single wonder book game
Let's make a potion
We have the ideal guinea pig there. That is a poor soul the cure for boils
Expertise of you know, I gotta make this potion. He's gonna break it
If you can make it correctly
Pungent onions
Crushed snake banks. It's German
pungent onions
dried nettles a dash of flabber worm
mucus and sprinkle of ginger for this is a lot of ingredients
Dude, why don't you just go to CVS and get fucking boil cream. Why do I have to do all this still having them?
They make like Neosporin
Get out of here job should vanish those boils if you get this you're tracking mud all over my wonder book get out of here
Dobby get off the book
Duffy get out of here what page three keep an eye on those
Duffy get out of the potion at least until you try mixing flux. We don't think he's supposed to be here
To start lifting it up
Okay
Am I making of potion or am I looney-tune style cooking Dobby in a pot?
This is fucked up
Yeah, all right get him out get him out Dobby get out get out of the get out, please
What a mess, try to get some of it in the cauldron
That's fine scatter those lovingly gathered ingredients everywhere, not to worry
Say the same line again, please
Try to get some of it in the cauldron
Oh, that's fine scatter those lovingly gathered ingredients everywhere
Try to get some of this thing is still going to miss you need to be really careful when you're using your chopping tools
Here it comes. There's a chance that you might cut yourself
Yeah, that hasn't been chopped
My child
This time we must say buddy who's holding the knife too much. Okay, I did it right
Yes, are you still with me press the move button to clip off some of the nettle hold the clippers clue
Oh
Cure for boils
We still need that ingredient pick it up again
Dump the
Fuck is right. It's like a pepperoni pizza. It'll cure him. I don't get him in there. Just dunk him a little bit
Come on Duffy get in there
Duffy we're curing you a fucking watch. I just don't give a fuck anymore. Like I just don't look
That's two figs worth of juice that was sick. I was that was hold on what the fuck just what was that?
Stop there. That's two figs worth of juice. I should have made that a much bigger deal. That was a huge deal. Oh
Dude he's sucking my blood
How much is he gonna drink after that close encounter time to learn more, okay
I just let these things drink. That's a rare auto signing auto sighting not signing
He's not like he's not like releasing a book
Look at look at her like rare auto yawn in the corner. I didn't know he was in this video. There's no couch
juice my hand down
Yeah, oh dude, he's sucking my blood had to have been like not even a year or two after how much is he gonna drink
After that
Okay, I just let these things drink a bunch of my blood now, I'm gonna kill a mash him up and put my blood in this potion
You want to get arrested? That's how you get arrested
That's how you get the health inspector to be like you're putting blood in your fucking food
your blood
My restaurants gonna be closed
Still a bit chunky give them another bad blood wasn't green go to it
I had green blood. I don't have green blood. I'm pretty my blood's red
Kid humor there it is. I would still do that. No, that's not kid humor. I would do that
If that was sitting on my lap right now, I would do that right now
I
Forgot how fucking dumb these really were I stupid that's covered in shrinking solution
He's just a little baby. Well, he certainly won't stop us passing by now
for the knife
Can this chop dude a horn? Here it is again
Just
You know what the most fucked up thing is this entire time
I haven't even had a chance to sample my own material. I've been able to change to drink my own fucking potions
That's changing right now
Whoa?
Whoa, that's spicy. Whoo
Whoo at first. I really didn't think I was gonna like that but
man
That was pretty tasty
That's my favorite. That's one of my favorite old jokes. I do this like four times
How many times did it did I actually do that?
That I had to have used it like this and same ambulance thing like three or four times
There's like so many like people here to take what happened to me
There's like three paramedics like a two fireman a spit just went flying. I don't know if you caught that one, but it's gross
No, no story electro. Don't
Does it happen in that too? No, it doesn't doesn't hold on. Does it actually happen in that video?
That video is kind of fucked up, isn't it?
I remember this video being like strange. I forget let's watch it. This is right before
Metal Gear Solid 5 I really tried to like jump on the Metal Gear Solid 5 like train
Because it was a big deal that that game was coming out
And I was like, hold on. Oh, let me let me like try to do something cool
And that thought it was funny because the story is like fucking I don't think I could
Metal Gear Solid and Kingdom Hearts of the same game in regards to storylines
They may as well just be the same exact story
Explain to me Kingdom Hearts storyline, but replace the Kingdom Hearts characters with people from Metal Gear Solid and vice versa
You'd have the same story
Once he got to Metal Gear Solid 2 and they started going that the last like hour-long cutscene
May as well have been fucking Sora and Roxas like playing rock-paper-scissors
Here we go. I
Forget this whole video. I hear it's a good game. I hear it's an incredible franchise
I haven't played Metal Gear Solid since I was probably 16. I played the first one and I played the second one
It's true. I don't know the story and it's become so complicated and so intertwined at this point
I seriously don't even know where I would even start dozens of hours of cutscenes tons of reading
I don't got time to read you who's got time to read nowadays, you know, so what I did is I picked up this
this is
got this online a
Comprehensive Metal Gear
NeuroStory ElectroDump
They have them for all kinds of things. This is for Metal Gear because obviously the story is so complicated like we've talked about
So that goes into the CD tray. I think it's just a standard disc at this only now we put on the electrodes goes there
Okay
Standard USB it goes right in the back of your computer. Just like that. That should be it. Oh
My teeth. Oh
That's my favorite joke in the whole video. Okay, let's all get hype for Metal Gear Solid 5 get hype play button
You were injected with Fog Star as a part of this operation
SPOILERS FOR METAL GEAR
There's room for only one snake and one big boss
You'll ruin your eyes playing so close to the TV
Get out of my mind
Big boss was the boss
No, the boss was the boss and then big boss big boss man took over
Because he had to kill her because the third game into the fifth game or the fourth game in the worse than second
Was the boss
No, the boss was the boss and then big boss big boss man took over
Because he had to kill her because the third game into the fifth game of the fourth game in the worst than second
God damn it. I gotta watch it again. I gotta start over. I gotta start over
I'll get it this time because I just it was getting confusing when they were all clones and shit
One more time
Get hype get hype for Metal Gear Solid 5 get hype
You were injected with Fog Star as a part of this operation
SPOILERS FOR METAL GEAR
There's room for only one snake and one big boss
You'll ruin your eyes playing so close to the TV
Get out of my mind
Auto! What's happening?
Where am I?
Oh no no no no no
Metal Gear Solid story
I must not have hit play I must have fallen asleep
I got time it's for the launch of Metal Gear
Metal Gear Solid 5 the launch party
I like that video
I like this video
There it is that's the other time
How did I get like that?
It's called this
They filmed at different times
I think I stayed up really late for this one
I'm pretty pale
Yeah because this is like obviously look this is very
Obviously during the day look in the corner
Oh we're gonna watch my favorite video I've ever made
Yeah this is my favorite video I think I've ever made
Yeah I don't even need I don't care
This is streamers choice we're watching
We're watching the basketball video
When this first released
People were like what the fuck is this
And let me tell you something about this video
This is no
I did not cheat in this video people thought
People thought that cheats existed to do this
Oh no they didn't no they
Did not I was on a call I think
With like MLC Stealth
And Star maybe I think I remember at the time
I was trying
I was over and over and over again
Throwing the fucking ball from across the
Entire fucking court
Over and over and over
Until I captured it and edited together
It took like 12 fucking
Hours to do this
You can't do this in this game
This is real we're watching it right now
Can I even click it?
People thought I cheated on that one no no no
You can't do that in this game
You'll know what I'm talking about very soon
That's my favorite video I think ever
I love this video let's watch it
And I remember when I was putting it together
I was like this is a sports video
Is anybody gonna give a shit about this video
And then I was like whatever
It was I thought it was funny
And that's all that really mattered at that point
I think it's funny I'm gonna
Put it up let me get it hold on
Move out of the way I fucking
Love this video
And editing this together was hell too
Because I had to make it look like it was really happening
There you go this is your insight
This is not done with cheats
This is the real deal
Nice hit
Today's video we're gonna open up a box
On camera
Oh I've already done it
I've already done it
Mayo coming up the front of the court over the Boston Celtics
Side passing it over to Knight
Knight layup that's two points for Milwaukee
Good score
Now we've got Gabe Groom and Degrossi gonna do well
That's what he typically does
And it's in another three points
Oh a Boston Celtics
A deficit like this is gonna be hard to come back from
For the Milwaukee Brews
But maybe they can mount something
They need to get some type of offense and keep the defense alive
Oh what a fake there passing it over to Sanders
Two points
For Milwaukee again
You gotta give Milwaukee some credit here though
They've showed perseverance this entire game
How do you go up against a team like the Celtics of 1997
I'm not entirely sure to Degrossi now
Passing technique
That's another three points
I hear the speechlessness in my voice
It's because I need somebody call a
Nuclear physicist right now
And ask them how this is even
Possible to score three points
Every single possession the entire
Season
You've got Gabe the glue man Degrossi
They gave him that name because he's got hands like glue
And he can throw the ball so well
And he was able to teach the entire team
How to do this
And I just don't understand and Degrossi's not gonna get the ball
Of Wallace, Wallace is gonna do it now
That's gonna be three points
They've never missed one time the whole season
I haven't casted a game
From the Celtics but this is the first time
I've casted a Celtics game and I must tell you
Ladies and gentlemen this is
One of the most remarkable basketball games
I have ever encountered in my entire
67 years on the planet
So now we're gonna just try to calm
Down here glue man, how do you
Calm down, how do you calm down
When something like that happens, how do you calm down
How am I supposed to
Judge night's got the ball now we have night
On the Milwaukee team with the ball
He's gonna try to come up court, he's gonna do a jump shot right
In the pan and he misses but Frank Pizza's got the ball
Now Frank Pizza with a toss, this is for real
Oh
He missed it, Frank Pizza
Just missed the first shot
Of the entire season
And that's just unbelievable, I really can't
Believe that and of all the things we've seen here
Tonight ladies and gentlemen I can tell you I did
Not expect Frank Pizza to be
The guy to ruin the streak of the Boston Celtics
But can we start it again?
We're gonna start it again
Start that counter at zero and add one to it ladies and gentlemen
Because that is the first of many
From these Boston Celtics
They are making a speed leave again
Which is something that their GM
Over and over again has said in
Interviews, Dan Bringus we caught up
With him earlier this afternoon
Look I'm gonna say the same thing
I've said like 12 times now
I fucking hate this job
And I hate this whole fucking organization
And this whole throw the ball as hard as you can
From the back of the court
Was a joke to get me fired
And it didn't work
Boston Celtics are going to win
In near perfect fashion
And because obviously
It's the end of the game as we see the players
All take off into their respective locker rooms
I'm gonna have to give the player
Of the game award to
Gabe Gloomander Grossi
That's right the fan favorite you all know him
You all love him I really truly think
He is one of the best players to ever live
And honestly
I hope to God nothing
Bad happens to this guy like
10 years from now
I really can't believe
Frank Peets is missing the first shot of the whole season
It was worth it
I remember like
Like 8 hours into trying to get this to happen
Being like
This ain't worth it
This is not fucking worth me doing this
It was absolutely
I'm not entirely sure to Grossi now
Passing technique
Doing that from across the court
I don't know which one it was
Maybe like 15 or 14
Whatever it was
You can't do that
That's so rare
In life and in games
Oh it was like
1 in fucking 50 it happened
Something like that
You couldn't make them
You had to like play through my like
Career mode or something to get them to build up
You can only make one person
And ask them
How is it even possible to score
3 points every single possession
The entire season
You've got Gabe the glue man to Grossi
These are all edits right
So here's the thing
This down here
It's covering up the real scores
Because this jumps around I wish I could move this out of the way
So you could see
But like for instance right here
Because he's got hands like glue
Right
And he was able to teach the entire
This is a completely different cut
This is a different clip
Because I had to Frankenstein them all together
To make any sense
So every time
Somebody on their team scores a basket
It's a new clip
After that
But once I went all in on it I was like I have to do that
How to do this
I just don't understand
And Grossi is not going to get the ball to Wallace
I love this
I love this video
That was like it was worth it
Compare the scores on the hoop
Are there scores on the hoop
Oh 24
Right
Okay so 24
No no no
That's the
Shot clock
That's not the points
That's the shot clock
Alright so what's up next
I picked them let's see
Let's get some patch notes
Yeah patch notes
We'll do patch notes
This is actually one of the last videos I made
Yeah I think this
Is this the last video I made
Yeah I think so right
Let's see
Because it was JermaRumble Live
Was after that right
Yeah we are about to witness right now
The last
Like at my desk
The last video I ever made
It's interesting
It's kind of like a culmination
Of like
How I felt about YouTube at the time
Weirdly enough
You'll see what I'm talking about
Alright here we go this is called
Patch notes
So I feel a little bit bad
That I haven't been covering as many games
As I used to on this channel
I used to go over patch notes, game updates
How I felt about them
In a very long time
So I wanted to play catch up with myself
In a sense and go over
All of them
All the patches and updates that I wanted to cover
That I didn't get a chance to cover over the last 3 years
So this one's probably going to be quite a long one
We're going to go over all these patches
And we're going to start with Team Fortress 2
The invasion update
Get yourself excited
Are you excited? Well you should be
We're talking about patches here
Ladies and gentlemen welcome to the patch video
Hey hey hey
Whoa whoa
You're fast boarding right now
I just want to make sure your finger is holding
You're doing that intentionally?
Is that another mistake?
I'll let them talk
Why did the rat just come here?
Remember how annoying that was with light poles?
Okay listen
I
I sometimes
Skip all of Overwatch
Because that was a pretty big deal
Look
This video took me like 3 months to make
So I don't want to be like a dick about it
But if you could just pick something
So I could at least feel like it mattered
We have one for Nazgoth here
Sonic Boom actually finally got
The nerf it deserved
It's now under 8 seconds for a cooldown
And they fixed a couple of crashes
The desktop launcher, the crash on exit
Thank god we can now not have to deal with that
It's true
No look
There's no reason for you to go this fast
Okay I'm just going to be very frank with you
Take your finger off that button right now
Right now, if you have any respect
Why is Dark Souls 2 even on here?
I'm just going to hang out
I'll be over here on my phone
Got a couple new apps to check out
I downloaded Face Swap
You can do it with your dog
I got a new keyboard app too
I'm not sure if you've heard of it
It's called Key
You can make a little tune
It's pretty cool
What the hell is this?
Hold on
Pause the video for a second
Pause it
You're in a different video right now
I haven't even made this video yet
You are at least 20 to 30 uploads in the future
So you're going to listen to me very closely
and very carefully
You're going to rewind
a few months
and you're going to stop, okay?
Very simple instruction
There you go, right here, right here
Stop, stop, stop, stop
Stop right here
I'm overlapping here
Pull forward like 2 inches or so
On the bar? Almost there
One more, got it, perfect
These are my patch notes
My dress came out today
I haven't even seen these yet
You picked a perfect place to stop
So let's see what they changed
They're actually shrinking me again
This is the second time it's happened
We should only feel that Jerma's current height
has been causing performance issues
He couldn't easily fit into a clown car
With this change, clown car videos are now much more accessible
I don't want to do clown car videos
What are they talking about?
My lumberjack outfit is going to get removed too
Now that is bullshit
What else do we got?
This patch is fucking terrible so far
40% more vacation vlogs
No, I'm not doing vacation videos
No way
I would rather do 100 clown car videos
than one vacation video
So, opting out of this one
As you could say
It's downloading
When did I do that? I didn't press any button
I didn't accept anything, there was no cancel or anything
Nothing's working here
Do I seriously have to rip out my ethernet cable?
I do, I don't want this patch
Hold on a second
I had all these installed
I'm connected to my whole damn house
I think that's it, is it?
God damn it
Ow, ow
That's the cable
I gotta put that back in, I want to watch Better Call Saul season 2
I can't jack out
Hello
You are going to have to call back
at a different time
I'm in the middle of some shit right now
Look, please put me on the do not call list
Fucking asshole
That's not it
I think I might throw up, I hope not
What is this? What is that?
Why do I have a sneeze switch?
This is it, right here
Whoa, colors
Gone
I can't see anything, I'm blind
I must have pulled out the HDMI
Oh boy, oh boy
Where's my mom? Where's my phone?
Mom? Fuck
Where is it? I got it
How much time do I have? I don't know, I can't tell
I can't see
It's actually scary
This is a weird feeling
I hide this feeling
I can't hear, I can't see
Is there a way?
I'm coming
One, two, three
No
It happened
And that was the last video
I ever made, besides
Germa Ripple Live, interesting
We got the bad ending
on Germa985 apparently
Door Cube? Alright
Funny thing about Door Cube
Door Cube is claimed right now
This video, apparently I don't
own it anymore
I don't know why
This video has been like demonetized
and DMCA'd by I don't know what
I think maybe the ending sequence
but I paid for that
I couldn't figure it out because all the things were like legally
obtained
I'll give some context, people that don't know
about this
So, somewhere in
like 2012
I'm gonna get bigger for this
Somewhere in like 2012
to like 2016
There was like a
As of like two or three years ago
There was this craze of
opening loot boxes on camera
There was like loot crate
and
They all had the same fucking name
There was like
Yeah, but this trickled all the way into like
late 2015 too, I remember
There was like five of them
And tons of people
tons of like YouTubers and streamers
were like doing
sponsorships for these
And I kind of
I guess this is just
how I felt about it
in a way
Loot box
Yeah, it's weird because we went from like
opening loot boxes to like then opening
loot boxes to then opening loot boxes
in real life
in games
Everyone was trying to jump on this craze of
gambling for Mega Man t-shirts
You know what I mean? Like
Oh, by the way, funny thing about this video
At the very end, I was gonna pull out a Mega Man
sticker and go
Mega Man! Mega Man sticker!
But I never did it
I feel like that would be too obvious
So, let's go
Here comes Dork Cube
Let's see what happens in this video
Hey, what's happening everybody?
Jirba here with something a little
different today. This is not my
typical video that I would make
But I decided to do it
because I'm approached by this company
There's a super cool bunch of guys
over at Dork Cube and it is
The Dork Cube! Take a look at it
This is a monthly subscription box
that comes in the mail
And you buy it, you open it, and there's all
kinds of nerdy
geeky, epic, kind of funny
gamer culture type stuff inside
And I thought
I should get one and I should open it for you
Give these guys a shout, give these guys a shout out
and give you guys a shout out
and we'll give them a shout out. This is Dork Cube!
I don't know what's inside of it
I have no idea, they sent it to me, so we're gonna see
what's inside
A link will be in the description
If you want 2% off your next
order, it's $20
So, save a little bit of cash
Look it up for you guys, you know what I mean?
Alright, let's make this a little interesting
How about that? Write when the box
opens. How about everybody writes
the hashtag in the comments
LUTEGAP, you know what I mean? Like we got LUTE
That's what we'll do
So in the comment section below, right when this opens
everybody say
LUTEGAP!
There's blood in the box! There's blood inside
this box! This blood!
The box was blood! The box was just blood!
This video, I no
longer own this video, it was claimed
Is that the Dr. Phil song?
Is it the Dr. Phil song?
The box was just blood!
It is, isn't it?
No, no, no, no. This is like a royalty free song
Who claimed this video?
It was for the song
Wait a minute
That's not it, right?
I did not get claimed
by Dr. Phil
The box was blood!
The box was just blood!
That's not the same song
One of them is like a shitty pretend rip off
of the other one, I think
No, it wasn't Dr. Phil
But yeah
That was Dorku
The sound it makes?
Oh god
Do we have to fucking listen to this video?
The sound it makes!
No!
Oh god
I fucking forgot about this video
This video is so
meaningless
This was like the state of making a TF2 video
after making like 200 of them
Alright, here we go
It's called The Sound It Makes
Okay
Alright, hey
Welcome, thank you
Ladies and gentlemen, welcome to the new
Settle down, settle down, okay, thank you very much
Welcome to the new series
here on German 985
It is a game show titled
What's the TF2 Sound?
So we're gonna go ahead and invite
our first ever contestant, Star Underscore
Welcome to the show, Star
Hello, what were you doing today?
I was away from Kentucky to be here on this
Alright, yeah, okay, so here we go
You're gonna have to guess the TF2 sound
Can you get it right? Here we go
That's the scout, that's the scout
What is the TF2 sound?
That was just you
I thought you were gonna get like an actual sound clip
What was it?
I don't know, what is that sound?
You don't know what that is?
No, I don't know what that is
Cut it, cut the music
No, it was the Mini-Sentry
That's not what it sounds like
Now you see, I disagree
But not gonna start an argument about this
That's not the sound it makes
That is the sound it makes
It doesn't go...
I'm gonna put it to you right now, you wanna hear?
You wanna hear, are you listening?
You wanna hear the sound it makes?
No
Well, it's set up time, so you're gonna have to just wait a second
Okay
Watch out for the spy, watch out for that spy
I tried to warn him through voice communication and he didn't hear me
Alright, where are you?
I'm fucking dead
Oh, you died?
Well, you're about to get proven
Are you ready to get proved wrong?
I'm ready to get proven
Here we go
You're not with me, oh, you're the healer
I'm the healer
Take a listen, it's gonna start here in a second
No, it's not, he blew it up
He's ubered, run
Just run away
Now is the moment of truth
This is the 20th century sound
Ladies and gentlemen, here we go
I don't believe
I think you're delaying, I think you're doing this on purpose
No, I'm just going back to the medicine cabinet
to get some aspirin
and let's go
Okay, I'm following you everywhere
I'm the healer
Time to hear the sound once and for all
I got a pack of sand
I feel like this video is going to be 90% built up
Can we please make this
thing
Alright, kill me
It's always a soldier
Kill me
Okay, I'm gonna put it down right here
Ladies and gentlemen, here we go
Time to hear the sound
We're gonna hear that this is not the sound
Listen to the sentry right now
Somebody just gave 10 community subs
But first of all, let me just say
I really appreciate the lawnmower being
started in my left ear over here
Anywho, that was
Soup, you just gave 10 community subs
Thank you for the subs, really appreciate it
That just threw me off
My head hurts
But thank you, Soup
Really appreciate it
Ladies and gentlemen, here we go
Time to hear the sound
Here we go eventually, we're gonna hear that this is not the sound
Listen to the sentry right now
It's just going beep beep
It beeps like one
No, it goes
See, you're gonna hear it double
I'm gonna hear a lot of it
He's gonna rancho relaxo all over this
See, right now
Listen carefully
No, now no one's going to come over here
Just wait
Somebody will come through the door
Going up the right side
I'm currently moving up the right side
Just put it in this corner, just put it in that corner
And someone will come out eventually
No, not that fucking corner
They're gonna come out the door and just see it
Which corner? This corner?
Alright, it's very sneaky
Okay, now we just need to wait and hear the sound
Yeah, and we're gonna see who's right and who's wrong
I think it goes
And you don't think so
I don't think so
This scout, this scout's gonna get d-d-d-d-d
But not, that doesn't
I would love for him to walk out here
Will you just walk out here?
He's gonna do this forever
He's gone
See, listen
Did you hear that?
You heard it, didn't you?
No, no, no, no, no, it never did that before
Why is it doing that now?
It's doing it
It's not doing it
You can't have my bananas, I just bought them
Those are my bananas, I'm taking them from you
I'm gonna have to wash my dishes again
Look at all these d-d-d-d's I'm getting
Oh, you think it's gonna work?
I forgot that
What is going on in here?
It's me, I'm the medic
I'm the medic
Oh, you're this medic
Things in your brain just don't add up right away, do they?
No
Hey, I'm this medic
Oh, you're this medic
Alright, well, for the second part of this video
That's our s- just bye
For the second part of this video, I need you to be on my team
Okay
This is part two
This is part two of sounds
What's- how do they make them?
So, for part two
Quiet, quiet, quiet, quiet, quiet, quiet, quiet
What sound is that in the game TF2?
Uh, that is no sound in TF2
You just screamed for like 12 seconds
Oh, that's not a sound, that's you
Great joke, I think I already fucking made it
No, that sound isn't TF2
Oh, really? What was that sound?
It's- you have to guess, you have to figure it out
So you're telling me there is a sound in TF2
Mine at least was close
Yours was not- yours was nothing
Mine was close enough
Mine was really fucking close
No, that sound is part of
Of this map?
The ecosystem
Did I win?
No, it's a weapon
We were only doing weapons
Like you did the weapon slinger
Do it again for me?
It's different every time
Did I get it?
That is not a sound in TF2
Yeah, no, it's a gun
Rocket launcher
No
Uh, the
Scatter gun
No, no, no, no, no, you're not thinking the right way
Katana
What the fuck is it then?
It's a- some- I mean it doesn't have to kill people
Huntsman, the huntsman, the huntsman
That was pretty good
Lock and load
Critscreek, critscreek
Yes, yes, god it was obvious
How did I not get that?
I know, it doesn't hurt people, that was the clue
I know, the hurting starts as good as the hurting starts as good
The hurting starts as good as the healing starts as good
What the fuck
Is wrong with me?
Well that uh
That sounds absolutely nothing like what you did
At all
No, that's exactly what it is
The first initial activation
It starts off like that and it goes down
Okay, well we got that
That mystery solved
I'm gonna go ahead and play some demo night
For the remainder of the video
And then end the video
What a YouTuber
Pretty good YouTuber
Alright, what's next?
My first Dark Souls video
Holy shit
This is- oh yeah, this is great
What a great idea
The best part about this video is I had no idea
How to play Dark Souls at all
I was one of those people that
Just started to play it
Because it was a new
Game that came out
I didn't understand anything about it
I didn't get it at all
I thought the game sucked
I thought it was a shitty game
I was like this is a dumb game
Like it's crappy
I didn't get it
I really didn't- I didn't get it at all
And we're gonna find out why
This is a buried video I think somewhere
Does anybody have the link to that one?
Because this is old
I'm not sure how many people have even seen this video
I can't even find it
Oh man, oh man, this is gonna be bad
Oh
Fuck
Hold on
I wanna show the image of this on screen
Don't- nobody click it, don't click it
Hold on a second
Here is the thumbnail for this video
I am not ready for this
I really am not
What am I clicking on this for?
This video is like in 8 and a half minutes
This is not- this is the-
I wasn't doing that ironically
That was me saying like
And uhh
How long was this video made?
Six, seven years ago? Seven years ago
I'm gonna hate this video
This is gonna be like Modern Warfare 3
Tier of video I think
And it's the title of this video
Why is the title this?
Look at the title of this fucking video
Hold on, what is wrong with me?
Why is this the title?
The title of this video
Is Dark Souls
Prepare to Die Edition
In brackets
Ha ha dot dot dot
Oh god
Dash uncensored germa
End bracket
Just in case you were curious
Now it would be funny
If this video was playing
And then I like fucking
No nevermind, I was gonna say like
I'm like get halfway through the video
Oh hey by the way it's uncensored
Ha ha oh god
I don't know if I wanna watch this
Ha ha oh god, uncensored germa
This is a fucking video from a long time ago
Okay let's go
Let's do it
I just clicked it
Wait but remember
This is important, I need to
I didn't know anything about this game
It wasn't like oh you know
I can't, whatever
Hey what is going on everybody
Welcome to Dark Souls
Die
Alright it's not bad
Dog
Alright let's make this guy
Class
Did you hear the dog
Alright let's make this guy
Class
Warrior, knight
They all have different stats
I probably should be looking at that
You know whatever, hunter
Sorcerer, pyromancer
Cleric
Oh he's naked
What
Hold on, all these guys have like armor
And like clothing and stuff, why does this guy only have like
Underwear on
What the hell is this guy
Alright we'll go with this guy
The worst possible thing I could do
I'm gonna get my ass kicked
But like the funny joke and I don't even know how to play
Alright
Good thing I look like a dipshit
I'm happy about this
Oh my word
Is there anything else I can do
This is a two video
This guy looks like a fucking idiot
Tuber hair
Hey, what's up man
How's that wall looking
Looking good enough for this
Dark Souls is
So hard
Left stick and hold that, alright like that
I don't even know what that is
Eye frames, I just think it's a fucking
Action game
Rock release
Alright
Hey buddy, so that's a weak attack
This is a strong attack
Good to go
What am I using for a weapon, what is this
Am I using like a popsicle stick for a sword
Pretty funny
What's for dinner, are we gonna have lobsters
Tonight
Read the message
Oh my god
That's a big boy
I wouldn't stand here and like watch him while he smashes you
What is this, Mag Veradon
From Warcraft
Holy shit, that's a good reference
Whoa
This is Mag Veradon from Warcraft
This is Mag Veradon
From Warcraft
I gotta get the hell out of here
Do I have to fight him
I don't know, just go, run this way
No, not this way, what am I doing
Oh my god, I'm an idiot
Oh an exit
Woohoo
Yeah, what you got on me
Do I have to watch the whole video
I'm gonna delete this video when it's over
I'm gonna delete this video
This video is getting deleted
Ouch
Alright, first hold on a minute
This is important, I gotta step in and give you some commentary here
Listen to me, this is important
You know
I've made like a thousand videos
And maybe like 800
I like this video, this video is fun
Download it quick
Get it quick
I like this video
And it was at a time when YouTube was very young
And you had to do something fun
And different
And playing Dark Souls and going out
Was different to me
I like this video
Because it was like
Seven years ago it was me trying to
Get the YouTube game going
I was young
I was like 30
I was like 27
I didn't even pay attention to any of that
I was too busy laughing at my like
Stupid jump
Yes, I'll do it, sure
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah
Yeah, screw your family
Can I just shut this guy up
Oh, oh my god
I didn't think you could kill him
Oh, oh
I didn't know you could do that
Was I not supposed to do that
Uncensored German, what does that even mean
Sorry
Wield right weapon, two handed
This video is almost half way done
Oh, I can use this as a two hander
Oh great, yeah, let me use it
Dude, you know what, seriously
Get the hell out of here
I'm fighting in a stupid hallway
I can't even swing my sword
Seriously, you are
So annoying, I should have just gotten rid of you
But I had the chance
God
This is the lamest fight ever
No, don't kill me
I'm just gonna go this way, screw you
Where's the bonfire
Oh, it revives enemies too
Oh, shit
There's the uncensored part
God, I don't
No, why can't I attack
What the fuck is going on
Oh, get me out of the menu, there we go
Not gonna be an idiot
That does so much more damage
So, remember, this is important to note
This is very important extra commentary here
Can you imagine
Somebody doing this now
Imagine you went to a
Twitch stream right now
Somebody's just playing Dark Souls for the first time
And this is what they're doing
You'd be like, what fucking year is it right now
He never changed
It's only been like seven years
It hasn't been that long
You do this
I'm talking about in Dark Souls
If somebody would have played
Dark Souls now and like walk around
With the tutorial knife
And get killed by like the
Skinless ghouls out here
Like five times
Horde or Alliance, Alliance
Horde to begin with
And then Alliance
Literally, what do you mean me
I did fucking great in the
Dark Souls games on these streams
Two weeks ago, what
Are you guys really trying to compare
Having random
Bosses around every
Corner to starting
Dark Souls for the first time ever
In 2013
Horde, but then
I went to
Alliance because my friends played Alliance
So much better
This game just became so much easier
Holy shit, come on
No
Holy shit, I can't fucking believe it
I'm getting chased
I don't even know what this does but I'm drinking it
I don't know what this does
But I'm going to drink it
What does that even do, I can't even do it
Get
Get me while I'm jumping
I want my shield back
I like the shield back
I wasn't like
I don't even know
I'm getting chased
I don't even know what this does but I'm drinking it
Holy shit
What does that even do
I can't even do it
The guy that played two weeks ago
You can't get me while I'm jumping
I want my shield back
The guy that doesn't know how to drink an Estus
Is on the same level as the mod guy two weeks ago
I wasn't even locking on to enemies
I was just flailing around
Holy shit, Tingy just gave 20
You've given like 150 community subs
The last week
Thank you for the 20 community subs, Tingy
That's a shitload of money
A shitload more subs
Thank you, that's a lot
Who was I talking to when I recorded this
Nobody
I was just like this
Except there was nobody in the chat room
I just sat there
I just did it
Yes, I am stalling and pausing and stopping this video
Idiot
Give me my lost power
And this time
We're going to do lost power
This is the end of your parents
Calling every console you own a Nintendo
Just to be clear about that
Fuck guns
Because it's going to be way much easier that way
That was a double hit
You like double cheeseburger hit
Yeah you do
That's a klat right there
Come on, shoot it
Oh, this video
How do I delete somebody else's video
Let's get behind this guy
That's my video
Oh, how's your back
Now this guy
This guy is dead, alright buddy
I'm prepared, I played for a little bit
I know how the game works
Let's go, yeah
Get locked on, come on
Oh, dance baby
That hurts still, it's alright
We're good
You ain't got nothing
Hey look, I learned how to play the game
It only took me like 25 minutes
Bullshit
That's the biggest lie I've ever said
Look at this guy
Holy shit
Oh my god
Oh god
20 minutes
I was trying to make a joke
About what he looked like
Slow bro
Let's go
You big ugly bitch
When does this stop
Oh lord
Get smashed
Whoa
Is that the same audio clip
I think it was
Get smashed
It is
I don't think I was
I don't think I did that
No I didn't
I need two for this, hold on
Oh lord
Get smashed
It's different
But somehow the same
Can I break these
Maybe if he breaks these things I get like
Items or health or something, oh he's stuck
Go analyze it
Get away from me
Can I punch him in like his bum
I'll hit him in like his thigh
Of his leg thigh
That didn't make any sense, but I'm going to beat him
Holy shit, I thought he was going to belly flop
He is going to belly flop
No, how do I drink these flasks
How do I drink a damn flask
Escape
Dodge through his stomach
Alright, I need to figure out how to drink this stuff
Recover lost power, take it
Is this like a potion
Like a healing potion
Where's my shield
I didn't even have my shield
No, put it back on
Hold on, time out
There is no time out
You can't pause it
Get him
I'm hitting right in his butthole
Wow, the butthole technique is going to work
I can't believe
My butthole technique
Is going to work
This is working
I can't believe it
Give him the kill
Yes
Yeah, victory
Is achieved
Yeah
That was pretty ridiculous
But yeah
Muscle man weirdo
To the rescue
That's it
This video has 175,000 views
You know, I think
What happened was
Most of these old, old videos
Have like 20 to 40,000
I think
People found this and they watch it
And they go holy shit
What is he doing here
That was fun
For somebody not knowing
How to drink an Estus
This is a Dark Souls video
This is an edited video
By the way
Of somebody that does not understand
Until the end of the video
And they still don't know how to do it by the end
How to drink the healing mechanic
But come on, I went like
Worth it
I don't delete videos
It shows growth
I'm not going to delete it
I only delete videos
That I
Accidentally delete
I'm not going to clean my channel up
And delete like 100 videos
I told you that story
About that time in history
When I was like
How many videos do I have
I have too many videos that just like suck
Or are fucked up
Or like they don't
I have like streams
I remember I used to stream on YouTube
And these whole
Like trial run
Two to three hour YouTube streams
And I was like
I don't want these on the channel
I don't want these just sitting here
So I deleted them
Watch the Pacman video
Didn't we watch the Pacman video
We didn't watch the Pacman video
Where I'm like
Sliding down the slide and shit
Somebody just gave 100 bucks
Hold on, let me see here
Who just gave 100 dollars
That was die335
Thanks for the 100 bucks die
And they say just want to thank you for spending so much time with your fellow rats
Been watching since these
Videos were first made
Been around a long time
You and your videos have helped me through so many tough times
Thanks a million P.S. Don't delete it
This is part of your origin story
I'm not going to delete it, I'm just kidding around
Thank you though
That's an incredibly nice thing to say
Thank you die for the 100 fucking dollars
And your really really nice message
That's just a really nice thing to say
Alright what's next
Why is the kingpin video gone
A bunch of videos are gone because
YouTube used to have a feature where you could just click a box
And then like just delete videos
I could just like check, check, check
And I don't know
I thought there was something in it or something wrong with it
I don't know
I went through and deleted like 80 videos like in 2015
Or something 2014
Did we watch the fire watch video
This is streamers choice
We didn't watch the fire watch video
No we haven't seen it
Alright let's watch this one
This is another one of my, probably one of my favorite videos
This is another one of the last videos I made too
Another butthole technique video
Technically yes
But physically no
You know what I'm saying
Alright this is called the photos are in
This is like one of the last 4 or 5 videos I made
I like this one a lot too
Let's go ahead and see what happens
So I just recently beat fire watch
And I came across a feature that I haven't really seen
Very many people talk about
There's a disposable camera in this game
That allows you to take pictures
You can take a picture of whatever you want
It never leaves your inventory
And you have it throughout the whole game
But the cool feature is
They actually ask you if you want to develop
Those photos and they will
Mail them to you
And that's exactly what I did
They got here today and I kind of want to just go through them with you guys
Like I thought it would be a really neat idea
To look at them together and see what I took pictures of
Now
It has been a while
So I don't actually know or remember
What's on these
Hey your memories have arrived huh
That's real cute, photo dome
Look at that
Okay let's open them up
Let's see what we got
First one is the sky
Skies can be cool sometimes I guess
That's a rock
Pretty interesting growth of a rock
The way that it was growing out of the ground was pretty cool
I think that's the inside of a bush
Yeah that's the inside of a bush
I think I was trying to take a picture of a
These are fucking terrible
Seriously
Did I take these?
Somebody had to develop these
What even is this?
Is that a thumb print?
Oh there we go, there's a little selfie there
Selfie action, sometimes you gotta take one
Okay
That's a private one
That's gonna go in a different pile
That's gonna go in the privacy pile
Hey a fence
Take a look at that, interesting right?
What am I even taking a picture of?
That is actually sensor
Hey there you go
Got a picture of the toilet
Oh this one's great, I like this one
This one's like there was a rock on a stump
And I thought that's such an interesting rock
That's so odd
Why would there be a rock on a stump like that?
I don't know why
There's a box up there I guess
Oh here we go, I remember this tree
I remember saying to myself
Man it's got such interesting moss growing on the side
I gotta get a picture with it
So there you go, there it is
Privacy pile
Do I still have the pictures?
No, I don't
What the fuck?
Who am I?
I don't know who the fuck this is
I have no idea
I've never met this person before in my entire life
No, I wasn't actually naked
Rock, good one
Oh look another rock, oh cool
And there's a sunset that you could have taken a picture of too
Oh good rock in the way
Come on, come on
You know what, I apologize
For this
Oh my god, that's somebody's asshole
I hope it's not mine
Nah it's mine, it's mine
Hey Ma, don't look in the trash
Yeah
Somebody at
What's the name of
What's the name of the studio
That made that game
Somebody had to develop those shit photos
They probably thought it was like a little kid or something
You know what I mean
Like every photo
Was of a rock or like of a ceiling
And that cost money to do that
That wasn't free
Somebody had to develop all those shitty
Photos in the game and send them to me
That's the funniest part of this video to me
Is that somebody was like
Putting that package together and going
Holy shit
Like why did you pay for this
The studio that made Firewatch is now part of Valve
That's true
Something that I've noticed over the last
Like hour and 20 minutes of this stream
I have been
Putting this up to my mouth
To drink this coffee
For about an hour
And there's nothing in it, there hasn't been anything in this in over an hour
I'm gonna go refill this
But who is that guy
I have no fucking idea
I don't have any idea
Why am I drinking from Kim's cup
Because, tell us
Tell us, do you want everything spoiled
Yes, yes
This is Kim's cup, there's your spoiler
Was it Devil's and Burger Boy
No, some things don't be
Some things don't have to be described
You know for Twitch
Terms of service purposes
That was all fake
So, just kind of hidden that realization
Right now
Anyways, I'm gonna go get some coffee
I will be right back
We'll continue to do this for like
Another hour or so
Let's get the BRB on the screen
I'll be right back
Yo, I'm back
Watching Rat Movie 1 and 2
We did that last time, I think
The secret pancake recipe
Yeah, yeah we'll do that one
Isn't this a video where I just like
What I'm shooting at people through the sniper
I just say that they're part of
Like a pancake or something
That's the whole video, right
That's the entire video
Let's see
Let's see if it holds up
This is the wrist recoil
Somebody said this is one of my worst videos
We'll see
It's a terrible recipe too
Is it?
It really is, this seems to be pretty polarized right now
This is one of my worst
Look at this hair, come on man
I need to get this part just cut
It looks so much better
I need a haircut, that's what I need
Yeah, people saying
This sucks, this is great
We got 50%, 50% here
Let's see
I have not seen this video since I probably uploaded it
Hey what's going on everybody
Jerma here with recoil
I was just spectating
I was just spectating a guy that knew what he was doing
Looks like Artman is going to go in
Going for the double shotgun shot, gets the shot
Gets two shots on him
Right there we got Artman going to be going for the kill
Going to see on the top left staircase, gets the pistol out
He's going to get him in time
He's dancing, I'm not going with the knife kills
What the fuck
What was that
That was so unexpected
What
So I guess now is a good time to do a player profile on Shizzy Boy
I guess now is time to do a player profile on Clidio
Clidio is one of those players you just love to watch guys
He has a lot of things in his arsenal
He's one of the best AK-74 players in the world
And he also plays the piano, so a good little bit of information on the player
Now we're going to do a player profile on V2FXX
He is one of the best SMG players in the world
As you can probably imagine
Having an SMG is a lot better for movement and to be able to get the speed that you need
Now we're going to do a player profile on
Now we're going to do a player profile on Shizzy Boy
Shizzy Boy is another one of those characters you love to see
Now we're going to do a player profile on
Now we're going to do a player profile on Zayoshio
That's a wrestler
I want to be like a WCW NWO wrestler
There it is, killing machine
That's two
Fucking WCW guy killed me
What the fuck happened to you?
I definitely want to be a WCW
We got this WCW guy
This guy is just kind of crazy looking
He's kind of creepy
And then we got tattoo guy
Why is tattoo guy the guy with the face paint?
This should be tattoo guy
Something I've noticed in every video game
That has this gun
The Draugnov always sucks
It does
Has it ever been a game made
Where the Draugnov wasn't a fucking piece of shit
Has that ever happened?
I just got three kills in a row
So let's just pretend I didn't say that
It's good in COD 4
Somebody's
Somebody learned how to play
Why?
Be a part of war
I'm gonna teach you guys
How to make pancakes, alright?
It's gonna be pretty easy
There's the first ingredient, that's two eggs
Around this corner we got
Some butter
And then of course you cannot forget
Fucking God
This is the secret recipe for pancakes
Two eggs
Then you gotta also put in the butter
But I can't find the butter, the butter ran down here
There's the butter
I missed the bowl, put the butter
Fucking God damn it
Hey what's going on everybody, Jerma here
Welcome to Cooking with Jerma
This is a new series I'm doing
Where I show you how to make a very healthy, very nice breakfast
And what you want is you want a bowl
A bowl large enough to put a bunch of stuff in obviously
Because we're gonna give you my secret recipe for pancakes
So what you want to do
Is of course you want to put in
Two eggs
A little bit of butter
Hold on, hold on
The butter fell on the floor
I gotta pick up the butter
There's the butter
There's the butter, butter's in the bowl now
Then of course you gotta add the flour
Flour is shooting at me
Flour's shooting at me, it's okay
Flour killed me
Welcome to Cooking with Jerma guys
In this episode
I'm gonna teach you how to make pancakes
Those of you that think you know how to make pancakes
You got it all wrong, you see
Then once you get that bowl
You throw in two eggs
Once the eggs are in there you put in the flour
Once the flour's in there
You roll your sleeves up
Get your hands a little bit dirty
And you add a little bit more butter
God damn it
Do you understand how hard you're trying
To make one of the worst jokes I have ever heard
I'm getting behind them
I'm getting in their spawn
And it's gonna be a big fucking surprise
When I get in there
Speaking of big surprise
Somebody would just be making a video
And the other person would just be like
Reacting to what the hell they were saying
What is this?
What is this fucking Gumby?
What is that like fucking
Stretch Armstrong in like a fucking
Taffy factory
And we're coming out of the wire here guys
This is the final moment in the 2016
Recoil tournament
Welcome, I'm very glad to do it with you
We're very glad to cast
With you
Very glad to do it
V2 coming around with a
Shot rifle, get a couple of shots on him
Shizzyboy is looking bad here
He's gonna jump on the top and he gets the kill
With his super duper scoper
And he gets a good
Shot
And he turns around, we got the cash drive
We're getting wrapped around by two people and oh my god
Did you see that fucking backflip
Super duper
Super duper scoper doper
Ow, my fucking teeth
Do you ever do that? I hate that
Sometimes I wish I could just like
You know how an airplane pulls its wheels up
Before it lands? I'd love if I could just like
Pull up all my front teeth
Like before I take a sip
I hit my teeth all the fucking time
I got these big ass teeth
I really just want to like
Have them retract up into my mouth
Time gun? We watched time gun last time
Let's see
Impossible creatures
Somebody was asking for that earlier
Oh shit, I do remember this
I remember this video
This game is so strange
I feel like I'd want to play this game again
It was a weird one
Impossible creatures
I don't know
Star also in this video, you didn't know
No, there's something wrong here
There's something wrong
It's the elephant, I know elephant
It's gotta be something else
Now that's what I'm talking about
That is the perfect animal
This game is fucking so stupid
Hey
What are you doing over here?
Click on him and look at his name
What is that? Look at its name
Jerma in real life?
XT
Is that a hippopotamus gorilla?
Yeah
Get out of here
This is a giraffe
Skunk turf
I don't think you could have hurt him
Can I not kill this?
Get out of here
He's too awesome
Come help me long guy
What do you mean long guy?
Oh you can do like dachshund right?
Is that a dachshund?
Ready boss
You're the boss
No building is up
Somebody's cheating
Oh really?
Thanks for the heads up
No
Stop
Just stay here
Can I do anything?
Shark, can I do any funny moves?
Where are my funny moves?
One of these times you're gonna spawn there and it's gonna kill you
The critters are under attack
Got him
That's not fair
No it's really not
And what the hell are you two doing?
You're supposed to be guarding the perimeter
Kill him
No kill him
Kill the disappearing shark
He's dead, no you got him
I did not kill him
He is very much alive
He has like a teleporting laser ant shark
How am I supposed to win?
I can't
Stop
Let them have a fight
You're not supposed to just let them die
That was all the fight I had
The critters are under attack
Come on
This game is so stupid
What the fuck?
What?
You don't like
You don't appreciate the meta
What meta?
The overlord scouting meta
No building is up
I don't think I understand this joke
That's a whale bee
The overlord?
No he's like a zerg
You send your overlord out to scout first
I didn't play starcraft
I have no idea
I have not played starcraft enough to know what that is
I think everyone
Who has ever played a video game
At the very least
Knows what a fucking zerg rush is
Yeah well
Here comes my zerg links
I wasn't even ready
That's so fucking cute
Come on
It's like turtle ants
Okay alright
You're overarching theme
You're doing a starcraft thing with your turtle bugs
That's really great
It is really great
Get the fuck out of here
Get this thing and get your overlord
And fucking stuff it up your ass
He's coming for himself
We have plenty of units
The strangest animal
The whole time
I love how they're not even attacking
Attack them
Kill them
Kill the people
This is so shit
Get them
We're not going to win
Steal their coal
Get out of here
Spit it out
Start mining
Everyone mine it
I would have figured these guys would be dead
Way long ago
They are going to eat
My giant crocodile bears
He's getting out with the coal
Where are all the sound effects
Are you making that
You don't let them get away with the coal
That's our coal
Kick his ass
We're taking this into the base
We are taking this shit into the base
After you kill them Darren
Go for it Darren
The fights in this are so anticlimactic
Kill them all Darren
That's right
Who is Darren
Very good Darren
Very good job Darren
You thought for one second you could fuck with the Darren's
I didn't think I could
Come on Darren
You've cracked this Darren
He thinks he can beat us with his beaver praying magisters
Does he know who you are
You're fucking Darren
No
For centuries
I don't know how to start this
How do you start this
I don't know
What are we fighting for
I would like to speak with your leader
Yes
The other leader
We have plenty of leaders
When one goes down the other will take his place
I need at least one
There's another one right here
Would you like to see a new one
This is also a leader
One of your guys
We caught the other day
He was on our sand
Play this again
I don't believe that
We had a treaty 2000 years ago
Your people and our people
That this bridge shall never be crossed
Unless for diplomatic reasons
We're crossing it right now
We caught one of your
What are you going to do about it
It's an act of war
You back up while that is an act of war
What
Holy shit
Oh my god
I forgot about that
Why did you say nuclear transform
I don't know
Nuclear
I said not nuclear this time
Right
Do the pacman first person maze video
No it's not
Co-op crusade
That's a good one
This is another one of those videos
That half way through making it
I said this video is bad
But then I powered through it
And it turned out it was one of my favorite
Just stupid shitty co-op videos
It got to that point
I was in the editing zone
I was at like minute number 4
Or 3 or something
Just going no
I'm going to have to can this
I've canned videos before
This is what people I don't think understand
I wish I could go back in time
And just tell myself
Look don't upload it
You don't have to upload it
Just put it in this folder
Just put it in that folder right there
And just hold on to it
Put it on the thumb drive and forget about it
This is one of those videos that I made
That I didn't like and wasn't happy with
That 2018-2019 me
Would love to show you
Unfortunately
But that's not the case
It's too bad
Too bad
But that's just the way it is
If he was in the editing zone
My name is Jean de Baille
One of the Order of the Night's Tempest
This is so loud and annoying
Fucking Gerald
This is a long opening cutscene
It was very long
What if it turns out me and you are these two guys
Alright can we play
I want like 30 more cutscenes
Wait is this us
I think that this is supposed to be both of us
Alright let's fucking play this dumb game
What
Their story didn't just begin
My family
February evening in the year 1199
My quest remains unfinished
As for Dems
His is about to begin
But as fate would have it
There is another hero
Who would be impossible to forget
Who are these people
There's like two even introduced to so many characters
There's too many people in this game
They're prized with pretty tunics
Have any wields that sword
No better than a farmer
This new character
Wait we get to play
Dems is a talented swordsman
Who has never let fear get him in a fight
Perhaps that strength
Returns to him
The Templar's threat
Is a terrible one
I wasn't this good
That was not doing this good
Is that you
I don't know
Why is there a Mortal Kombat character here
Alright different universes
Where am I
What is happening
I died
He's gonna kill me
Dems is a talented swordsman
Who has never let fear get him in a fight
Perhaps that strength
Returns to him
The Templar's threat
Alright but hold on
Wait a second
Here's the thing about this video and about this game
What the fuck is going on right now
I hit space
I still this many years later
Have no idea what was going on here
There's a prompt on the screen
But you can also move your character
So I'm on the top
Right
See the prompt on the screen is down
Down press down
So I'll press down
The screen prompts
I did
What it told me to do
I pressed the down key
Dems is a talented swordsman
Who has never let
Direct D perform a normal attack
Counter co-op star
Why does it say that
Why is it DC
Why wouldn't it be like ABC
Why is it star
What's going on with you
A lot of weird shit going on
That's performed when I grab an enemy
Gee that's HML
The low isn't star
That's another character
He missed every arrow
Did you see how many arrows he just shot
He missed every one
They didn't even get close
They were all in unison
They landed right in front of these guys
They just missed them
They really are just firing
Like 10 feet in front of them
Come on you gotta do some more work
I'm doing all the work here on the left
Are you dead
Take cover
Now's our chance
Let's go
Right in the mouth
Right in the face
Now's our chance
Let's go
It went clearly all the way over my head
Right in the face
He just put his hand up and wiped his face
This game is a treasure
Where are these guys on the right
Which characters are we right now
All of your audio is on the left
Mine's all on the right or something
I just ran away
Fuck
He just took off
This guy died
I'm outta here
Listen to this shit
All of your audio is on the left
Mine's all on the right or something
I just ran away
I fucking love this game
He just took off
This guy died
I'm outta here
Those guys on the left are dead
That guy got shot with a machine gun
So I can, you step out and
It's inverted
Mine's inverted
Shoot him
What the fuck
That's a bad guy
Oh yeah, we didn't know if they were NPCs on our side or not
Look at this fucking co-op
It could probably fit us both on the same screen
I don't really
It could probably just be one screen
We probably could be on one screen right now
Is that an enemy
This is really gonna be a headache
This is where we came from
We're going the wrong way
They have two screens
Your turn now
This is the boss
Alright, first boss fight
You ready?
What's the strategy
Alright, just co-op him
Just co-op him
Just co-op this guy
Right into the fire
Good god, we co-op'd him
Yeah, you guys know how to do that
Oh shit, he's a demon
You ready to co-op this guy?
That shit probably went down
In real life though
What a fucking useless enemy
Dude, in real life
If there's like two or three people swinging at you at the same time
You're gonna get fucking pelted over and over
Pope Innocent
Guaranteed that guy's a demon
You don't have a name like
Pope Innocent III
If you're not the bad guy of the whole game
It's funny cause this is all historically accurate
That's probably a real guy
That is a real person
Here's the typical bored king
Eventually, I hope somebody makes me
Come from my sleep
And see these two gentlemen
See how good they did
I'll speak to them now
You, you won't defeat me
This game sucks
Uh oh
Rain is back
Mortality
This game was not made for two people to play it
He's dead
No, we have to do the sacred flames
No, he's dead, he's gone, we won
What? There was a whole plan
We couldn't even hear the whole plan
We co-opted him too fast
We couldn't even hear the plan
This is not normal
The way they were talking
That wasn't even supposed to happen
It was like you create a diversion and we'll do a purifying flame
No, he's just dead
I pressed X
Some of these old videos
Me and Star used to play some of these games
God, I just don't remember
Everything that all of my emotions
Are coming back to me
Some of these games are fucking so hilarious
This is a good one too
Hacker and the slacker, that's a good one
Raven's cry, we watched
Raven's cry last time
We did that before
I think we did both Raven's cry last time
We did tactical intervention last time
Let's do hacker and the slacker
This is a long video
This is a ten minute video
This is a long one
Hacker and the slacker
Dude, Diablo 3
I made like a
I streamed it and played it a bunch
Replay all of my blazing bullet heads
In Sekiro
I need to wait for you
To disable that camcorder
Take out that camcorder
Hold on
There's a lot more to hacking
Than there is walking down an alley
And getting caught
This screen is four different windows
Of views and each one has a tutorial
On it right now
Pager, Martin can lure enemies
Away from their post by calling a thrown pager
A thrown pager
So apparently I can throw this pager
And this guy is gonna go get it
Can you make that thing buzz
This game is actually really cool
Oh shit, you just did that, okay
Yeah, I just called it
So I just sprint by this guy?
Oh, he turned
It's okay
Is he still turning?
I think it's fine
Stop calling that
Stop that
Stop
Okay
You just, no, you idiot
You like
You are hammering my
Brain
Is there a computer? Yes
Then plug me in, I'll see about getting you the code
Oh, well there's a gun in here too
Hey, plug me in
Plug me in
Oh fuck, was that the computer we were supposed to use?
No, there's three people in here
They'll all hear you
It's been a while
Throw your fucking pager
I don't have my pager anymore
Oh no
I'm running
They don't see me
He's running towards your door
He's walking through the door
Sneak over here
His pathing is bad, he couldn't do it
He's coming
I'm hiding
I forget this whole thing
You gotta shoot
Shot like nine times
No one heard that
You're clear to go Ghost Rider
Alright, thanks a lot
He's coming up the stairs
He's coming, dude
Hold on, page him
Page him
It actually worked
I did, I paged them
There's three of them
Just keep paging it
This page
Page, page quick
I'm paging
Making a break
Can I please stand the fuck up? That'd be great
Stand up
I got fucking destroyed
He's coming around
He's looking out the ocean
You can snap his neck
He heard you walk
No, hide
Where am I hiding?
What the fuck was that?
What did you do?
What happened?
What?
You gotta keep an eye on these cameras
There's three people coming for you
Run
Where am I running to?
Right
I don't know where to run to
I'm gonna hide in here
Stop there
There's a guy coming in for you
Three people are coming in here right now
No, he's marked as three
Three is close to you
They're walking away
By the way, I'm holding down G
I have to let go of this and throw this at some point
I can't let go
I can't
Open the door
Throw it that way
Oh no
I have to let go of G to open the door with E
So I'm going to flashbang myself
Two is right there
I can't even open the door
I'm stuck in here
What?
Throw another one
Can I take...
Give me hammer
Why did they hammer this guy in the head?
I want the hammer so bad
I don't know, how would you not know I'm behind you?
I'm trying to reach for your desk hammer
I'm trying to get his hammer off his desk
Are you serious, dude?
Oh god, what the fuck
What?
I love this game
Alright, hold on
Hack his computer while he's on it
I've already hacked his computer
I'm on his computer
I'm looking at his emails
Let me hold your mouse and browse your emails
Thanks, dude
I appreciate it
He's going for the desk hammer
Is he going for the desk hammer?
It was self-defense
So there's a guy here
If I can get three and at least the guy next to three
Mark the guy next to three
I'm going to flash him
I can only have three marked at a time
You gotta be fucking kidding me
Turn around, open door
Door on your right, open that door
Door right, open it
This guy sees you down the hallway, keep going
Open this door
Don't leave
Wait, wait, guy at the end of the hallway
Run out of this door, there's a door on your right
Got it
There's a camera in this room
That guy's checking the wrong room for you
Turn to your right, there's a door
Door
No, no
Go back
Go back in the room
There's a door in front of you, to your right
Right door, go
What do I do?
Forward, forward, forward
You got it
Keep going, keep going
Right
Get in
Turn, turn, turn, turn
In this room
There's a guy in here, shoot him in the face
Shoot him
He's still alive
Run forward
They're on your tail
Door on your left
Get in there, double door
Straight in front
Shoot, shoot, shoot
Keep going, keep going, keep going
There's going to be a door on your left
Open it up, run to that
There's going to be a guy around this corner
You're going to want to kill him, turn this corner, shoot him in the face
You got it, captain
In his face
Open this door, there's going to be three guys and you're going to die
So immediately turn left, double door
Hold on, let me just open the door with my
What the fuck is that?
You got it
Forward, forward, forward
Right, right, right door
On that door
Double door
Shoot him in the face
Ignore him, keep going
Turn around, there's a man behind you
Fire
Motherfucker
Run, run straight down the hallway
Just page him
Page him
Ready for Groundhog Day Agent Smith
Stop, stop staying in this room
Kill the guy following you
He's about to come out, it's marked
That was the right guy
He's looking at the wall
Get this man, that's important, crucial
Okay, there's a door right here
Right here, there's a stairwell
Down here, I want you to get downstairs
You got it
Open door, come out this door, come out this door
Double door
End
Okay, keep running forward
Which one?
Snickers, snickers, snickers
Alright
You're gonna want to go kill him
Oh my god, I can't, hold on
He wants your snickers
Got him?
He's got him
Okay, run through that doorway
There's a guy back there in the cafeteria
Those are couches
This is so bad
Double door
Which one, just two double doors
This one, no, other one
Back, back, back, back
Get in there
Hide in this room, hide in the corner
Hide in the corner, behind the door
Ow, my mouth
Oh
Alright, I'm done
Seriously
This has happened so many times
That was a lot of fun
God
The Diablo 3 incident
Well that's one of Star's videos
That video was so, I was so irritated
That's like chipped my tooth
That was just a hair in my mouth
Weird, how
The Diablo 3 incident
Was, here's the story behind this
And I don't know if Star gave you this lore or not
I don't think he did
This is called
When you get desperate to make a video
And you don't have anything done
This is kind of how this happens
And why can I not find this video
I can't, does this video exist
Oh it's unlisted it
Why did he unlist it
Was he embarrassed over this video
He's embarrassed of me
What did I do in this video
This video has like 700,000 views
I don't think unlisting it did very much
Oh yeah it did
Did very much
Doesn't he just follow me around and go like
Blah, blah, blah
How long is this video
You guys want me to watch this one
Star's here right now, Star what's going on here
Devil freak, devil freak, devil freak, devil freak
Devil shoot, devil freak, devil freak, devil freak
So he can make Jerma is mad part Diablo
Which like, who
Why would you make that video in the first place
You know go ahead and make it
Make Jerma is mad part Diablo
It's gonna suck, it'll be like the worst video you've ever made
You're just jealous because I get all the women
And it's unlisted
And the video is unlisted
You know
Look at me and Leia over here
Let's talk about
The temple, no your childhood
I don't care
You know which doctor has right now
What
Oh you're gonna
Make me die
Oh
I'm assuming
I'm assuming you're happy you made a fucking witch doctor
No
I'm not playing Diablo
You're playing annoy Jerma
It's your favorite past time
Blah, blah
You're still going with this
No mana
Blah, blah
Blah
I'm not here
Got a legendary, thanks Jerma
Did you start to say?
You wanna drop that again?
Fuck you
I got it
Dude you're gonna fucking shit your pants
When you see
The stolen ring
Wonder why you had it
Oh my god
Does this have vitality and
Intelligence on it
What a unique item
This game is so bad
Mela
Wanna come play Diablo?
Wanna come play CS?
I'm gonna
Solo a game right now
And then after that maybe you can play with me
I'm in the middle of something important
He's not in the middle
Of something important
This is important for me
Come here
Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle
I'm gonna get you
I am gonna get you, I'm a fucking wizard
Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle
Yeah you think that's gonna keep you safe
You fucking piece of shit
Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle
What the fuck
This is so weird
Okay I'm fucking done with that
I'm so done with that
This isn't fun
This isn't the most fun you've had
In Diablo 3
I'm done with that
This is the Halls of Agony
You know what happens in the Halls of Agony
This is not my video
Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle
Alright Mela
I'm gonna have to ask you to stop for 3 seconds sir
Mela you need to do like
Just
A general assessment
He's following me around
As a witch doctor
Completely nude
Doing this I throw up on you animation
That comes down in pubes
And he's making this a video
Do you like this video so far?
I think it's pretty dumb
It's so dumb that I have to mute and mumble
So I can't play SEA
Wiggle, wiggle, wiggle
Wiggle
You see you just like really pissed off Mela
You know it's great
It's actually a good thing because you can't revive here
I can stay alive
No you can't
Here I'm gonna help
You're dying in less than 5 seconds
Let's count to 5
And if you're alive in 5 seconds
Then I owe you a dollar
One, two
Shut the fuck up
I need to know where the guy is
I'm alive, I'm still alive
He's fucking having, alright I got him
God I'm deafening
This wasn't even up
This is not gonna get on me
I tried
Can I get a revive?
No just
Dude I've never heard him
scream like that
Can I get a revive though?
Alright since you passed the test
I said
One dollar
Count to 5
And if you stay alive in 5 seconds
Then I owe you a dollar
You're not counting
One, two
Shut the fuck up
I need to know where the guy is
I'm alive, I'm still alive
He's fucking having, alright I got him
Alright we heard that one
Can I get a revive?
I'm like seeing through my own eyes
I feel myself playing the game
Dude I've never heard him
scream like that before
Can I get a revive though?
Alright since you passed the test
You get to get revived
You did pass the test
Oh man
Oh you did
It's another snake
Look at the snake
I am Jon Adventure Man
Look at the snake, look at the snake
I need a revive
You keep enabling me
I'm glad I have like
Anchor Star
It's just driving around the ship with the fucking anchor down
I've stuck to this for a while
Yeah you really have
You've just been being like a pain in the ass
For the last like hour and fourteen minutes
Does he have anything else to do?
No
Apparently not
I don't know
Anyway before you go down into the cellar
I was supposed to leave and make this game
Different before like an hour ago
Have you considered not going into the cellar?
Because if you go into the cellar
All of these guys
Are going to turn into snakes
If you don't go into the cellar
They won't ever ever turn into snakes
He deleted it?
Wait hold on a second
This video doesn't exist?
He deleted the video
The video is gone
No he didn't
It's gone, he deleted it right now
It's live deleted, why did you do that?
I'm never closing this video
I'm never closing this tab ever again
I'm never turning my computer off
What the fuck
Is he in chat right now?
Why would I write that?
What am I doing?
What is this like a discord?
Why are you here?
I can't download it
It doesn't exist anymore, I have it just cached
Wait a minute
Guys look at the video
I think I only have up to this point
Cached
Just download this VOD
Why did you delete it?
We weren't done
He said he hates you
What?
This is a good video
Anchor star
That's not where I wanted to start the video from
It's just driving around the ship
With the fucking anchor down
I've stuck to this for a while
Yeah you really have
Here's the best part about this video
He uploaded this video
You don't know the fucking balls
It takes to upload this video
That's some like real
That's
Come on
There's got to be some respect there
Being like a pain in the ass for the last
Hour and fourteen minutes
Does he have anything else to do?
He can't play it without
Apparently not
I don't know
Wait before you go down into the cellar
I was supposed to leave and make this
Where is he?
Hold on a minute
Wait a second
I'm just checking on something
I'm asking him
You want me to defend myself?
That's not what I meant
You said defend yourself
Because you deleted the video
You're a snake
On the stream you say
This is a good video
In private you want to defend yourself?
If it's a good video I have nothing to defend
He's right
I said hey you want to come in and
Defend yourself
Why did you delete it?
I didn't I privated it
Why did you do it?
You want to watch the rest of it?
I'm at six
We're committed at this point
You got to watch eight minutes of me
I can't believe watching this back
I have blocked this from my memory since I uploaded it
I can't believe you got to act too
While I was doing this
I'm not wearing gear
I know
Why do you think it was so frustrating?
Why was this on?
It says Torment 1 at the top right
Really? I must have been in some pretty good shit
This is Star by the way
This is the guy
I'm the guy in this video
Ready? Listen
Consider for a second
Have you considered not going into the cellar?
That's him
We got a live interview with the guy that
Uploaded this video
If you want any pro tips on becoming a
Successful YouTuber now would be the chance
To ask those questions
I'm making myself nice and big here
Questions
For a YouTuber
When was the last video that you uploaded?
The Netflix video that you promised
That you would watch, you never responded to me
And then did a video watching stream
And still didn't watch it
I watched it after I told you that
I guess you had a lot to say about it
I saw the video
I can even quote you pieces of that video
In private
Okay after this you can quote
After this I'll quote the video
Okay we'll see
But first of all
My last video was 20 years ago
What was your last video?
Defend yourself
Okay
Like a million views on YouTube was worth like
$64 now
I thought you were going to say 64 viewers on Twitch
It's about accurate
And Twitch was just more fun
At the time
64 viewers
I haven't been paid by YouTube since April
Really?
Wait
Maybe March actually
How does that make any sense?
It was all about the money
Before we play the rest of the video
When you say the word
For instance
Are you watching this right?
You probably have it muted or something right?
Yeah it's muted
So anytime you say the word money
Does that happen to you when you do that?
Your neck?
No just say money
Money
I can't do it without having a fucking mean face
No that's just you
Money
Are you ready?
Because if you go into the cellar
All of these guys are going to turn into snakes
If you don't go into the cellar
They won't ever
So Phil cue the video up then
I'm at 5 minutes and 39 seconds
It's your video
It's not like
Hey by the way
Why am I doing the out the window thing
The train like stop
Take it
You're going to get to 5 minutes and 39 seconds
I'm there
Are you at 5 minutes and 39 seconds?
Yep
Okay 3, 2, 1 play
Ever turn into snakes
We've been discovered
See this all could have been avoided
Is that shitty joke over?
No
It's not he fucking is still going
Alright I'm eating them
This is turning more into like Mela is mad
Than it is anything else
I walked completely backwards
Did we walk back here?
I'm getting the fuck out of here
No
I was supposed to be done with this
By now
I'm fucking getting that right
You're not getting in here
Unless you're on a real character
Okay just so you would wonder
I'm not looking at the chat anymore
I'm like not even paying attention to it anymore
Pause it
What are you saying?
I'm saying
Like 2 weeks after I uploaded this
I was already regretting it
I don't remember exactly when I unlisted
But it was fast
Did you actually
This video has a lot of views to get unlisted after a week
Because people keep
You know it's
It has it's own life now
The video I never once
Published the definition of
A German joke video
That's crazy
You said you'd always be there
Now look at us, I can't even look into your eyes
It's rough, I don't do drugs, it's called emotions
Don't be so defensive, let's sort this out
My witch doctor bit is genius, can we agree to look?
If I didn't do all the things I've done
Then where would you have to do it?
What?
What does that even mean?
If I didn't do all the things I've done
Then where would you have to do it?
Oh because I wouldn't let you in the game
You ready?
One, two, three, go
Get the fuck away from me
Will you leave me alone?
Alright
Alright, alright, alright
If I invite this
If I invite you right now and you come in on the witch doctor
I'm leaving the game and I'm blocking
Ster's account
What are you doing?
Why are you not talking?
What the fuck are you doing?
Can I get a revive?
Revive
Move her
It was like full, like a minute
Where'd you go?
What?
Where do I do this?
My game's crashing
My game is legitimately crashing
You've crashed my fucking game
What's the point of this video?
Holy shit
Your whispers actually broke my game
Okay, I have to look up
When Diablo 3 came out
What's the next call upstream we're going to do?
Oh I don't know
Play with that guy
Play Diablo 3
It came out two years before this video
So I think yeah, I was just surprised
You wanted to play Diablo 3
And I don't know, it probably upset me
I think this was also before
Reaper of Souls
Was that before Reaper of Souls?
I think so, because in the beginning of the video
Your whispers were still garbage
Yeah, why would I have played Diablo 3 again
I think I was trying to talk you
Out of playing Diablo before the video started
That's my guess
That's me defending myself
Of why that happened
Interesting, okay
Interesting
What are you up to this week?
You know, nothing
Is there anything fun we could ever do?
I don't think so
Alright, we'll see you in a year
Okay
You coming over?
I don't think so
I don't think it's going to happen
You're not coming over
I don't think so
Really, we're talking about cryptic behind the scenes
Discord, defend yourself shit going on here
You don't think it's not going to happen?
I don't think it's going to happen
When it was planned to happen
I still want to get out there
But not
That's alright
Well, it would have been great to see you
Yeah
It would have been good to see you
Yeah, I'll let you get back to your stream
I don't have very much left because I have to go to the doctor
Oh, I can come
Are you going to come to the doctor with me?
I mean, if you need someone
Let's play something, like this week or something
We'll figure it out, we'll get something fucked
Okay
Alright, that was twitch.tv slash stir
Get check him out
He's got great fucking videos
You got anything else to say before you leave?
Quote the video
Why do you have to like leave?
I don't know
Why am I saying bye to you?
You were saying like it was nice to see you
You're so busy, your stream's going so well
And then I came on
And now it's like I'm sorry to interrupt
I'm like trying to like shoe him off the stage
Like alright, well that was fun
I mean, we should all just
We could all just watch videos
We could
Okay, you got one?
I don't know what you have and have not watched on your stream
Throw us some out
Did you watch handball showdown?
I did
I think you did
Wait, no, did I? I did
I know that I did on my stream
That video is one of those
Oh, by the way, we talked about
A little bit
How many videos do you think that you made that you never uploaded
That you never saw the light of day
That you wish you like saved in a folder
So like this year you could like just watch them
I can tell you
That I have some videos I never uploaded
That I'm so glad
That you never did?
I only very recently deleted
When me and you played Half Life 1 together
Oh
Do you remember? I do
Wait, you, you, you
You like deleted all that
I had like the footage of it
And it was like unedited raw footage
So it was like 30 gigabytes of footage of us playing
So I finally was like I need the space
This is, I'm never doing, I'm never going to look at this again
That's unfortunate
Yeah
But no, I've done that quite a few times
Remember when we played that game where we weren't talking at all
But our characters, it was like text to speech
The game where you're on a boat
It's like a murder mystery
Vaguely
Oh yeah, you didn't upload that?
No, I didn't upload it because it was too
We didn't talk, there's no dialogue
It's just you and me giggling to ourselves
It was unedited while our characters say stupid shit to people
I don't know why
I wish it was there because I'm having a hard time remembering
Yeah, well I didn't
I don't have it anymore, that's what I'm saying
I wish I still had some of these old videos
That never saw the light of day
Alright, but what do you got, do you got anything for us?
Did you watch Dastardly Devil Boy?
Dastardly Devil Boy?
No
I forget what the games are called
Lucius? Lucius, yeah
Is that a star pick?
I'm trying to pick from your videos
And that was a good one
As I recall
Let's watch Dastardly Devil Boy
It's a fun remembering thing
You tell me when you're ready
I am ready
I am also ready, but not quite
Ready?
I'm sorry
3, 2, 1, play
That's a sick intro
Father, father
When can I go and play with the puppies daddy
I'm Lucius
I'm such a bad boy, such a bad bad boy
I'm gonna kill you
What?
What's wrong with this guy?
Okay, now I remember why
This guy was just trying to get me
And yell at me and stuff
And now he's just marveling at the sink
We're gonna try this
Hello
I'm taking you to the authorities
Yes, please
Take me to the authorities
You would seriously think that after doing this like 15 to 16 times
This guy would look down and be like
I shouldn't walk on the green shit
No, of course not
Murder
Hello nurse, hey what's going on
I'm Lucius
I'm gonna take over your fucking mind
I'm gonna go walk into a
I'm scared
Ah
What am I seeing
Dude, I'm like a supernatural
Psycho dragging her on a bookshelf
What do you mean what am I seeing
Do you know there's another one of these
Oh yeah, did you play it?
No, apparently it sucks
What the fuck is this
Pick up those shaggy butts, pick up those shaggy butts
She actually did
She just took them, what?
All those cigarettes
I clearly threw those on the ground
So now
I'm gonna fucking can ya
What's this, I'm gonna fucking can ya
You wanna get canned? You ever been to Kansas?
I'm gonna fucking can ya
This lady keeps ducking
This is just psychic hit man
Invisible food? I love invisible food
What's the guy on the left, what's he doing here
Just wearing that nice shirt
Fucking naked guy
I forgot about this part
He's gonna have a lot of trouble
What the fuck
He dropped it
You're not even doing anything
You dropped it dude
Without context, this is really strange
What's this guy's story
I wanna know his full story
Yeah, your arm's gonna be fine
Don't worry, we're in a hospital right now
You're probably here for surgery or something
Let me get you to your emergency room
Surgery room, jeez
So on the right here, as you can see
I'm gonna give you a little quick tour before we go to your room
That's gonna be the operating room
But I want to introduce you to one of my favorite doctors
Over here is Dr. Dean Dingleman
Dean Dingleman, here's the patient you'll be operating on
His name is
Kryden, Kayden, whatever his name is
Kayden
I just wanted to give you a close interaction with the doctor before you go and prep for surgery
Just take you up the floor too
That's all we gotta do here
Just don't mind me
Things always broken, gotta throw a can of dog food at it
To make sure we can get it open
But yeah, can you believe that weather?
I mean, we had like a foot of snow today
I mean, can't you believe?
Aw, ruined
You're not gonna let me push him out the elevator?
Let me push a guy out a fucking elevator
Fucking high-sea ectocoola
Let's see how you deal with this one
Alright sir, so go ahead and
They always slip, it doesn't matter if they're sitting
If they're on a fucking workout bench, it doesn't matter
It does not matter
I was gonna say
I remember having a very long
Discussion about something editing
On a naked man, I couldn't remember what it was
No, it's cause
I was trying to figure out how I wouldn't get
The video banned
I think that guy's dick is there
It's just full on
That guy's dick
His dick is there
That's so funny, the guy's walking around naked
So
We were trying to figure out
How do I make it so I can upload this part
And not like show a guy's dick
So
It was just like, oh
We'll just keyframe close on him
I really wanted to
Upload it just uncensored too
Cause that's so stupid, the guy's just walking around
Just naked
His like AI got
Screwed up or something
And he was just supposed to be clothed
But he was just walking around the office like this
Oh whoops, I forgot to tell Star to pause
Star, pause your video
Just keep going
You paused too much
Anyone ever tell you that?
You pause and then you talk for like a minute
And then you rewind a minute, then you rewatch the same thing
Get back to where you were and go, see what I said
And then you rewind like 10 more seconds
No I don't, I have like twice
Alright, get to 417
Look, you gotta give insight
You gotta like give insight to the video
It's director commentary
3, 2, 1, go
I didn't even tell you what time to go to, whatever
Everybody just saw that I came back from
I loaded into the game
I loaded into the game and this happened
I don't know what happened here
I had nothing to do with this, absolutely nothing to do with it
Naked guy come back?
Who's gonna get the sandwich first?
Everybody wanted the sandwich
What?
I didn't poison that sandwich
That guy just died
Because he ate a dirty sandwich
Wait just a second here
So you two, that's normal
You should be doing that
There's no reason why two people can't be sitting in the same spot
At the same time
I mean why
What are you doing?
Hey guys, welcome to my new hit series called
What would happen if this would happen?
So today in this new episode of
What would happen if this was gonna happen?
We have a thing of donuts here
And we've got these pills, we're gonna combine them
And we're gonna see, you know
What would happen if this was gonna happen?
See the doctor here, he doesn't even know there's donuts behind him
He's gonna pick up those donuts
Oh man, I mean like what's gonna happen here?
He's gonna eat these donuts, he loves donuts
With a giant pill box on them
So next episode on
What would happen if this was gonna happen?
Was that you?
I think so
Wait, I tried to like
Yeah at the very end
I had like three lines of dialogue in this video for no reason
That's because you're just in the call
Yeah
I tried to explain this before but sometimes
One of us would just be sitting in
See back in the day we didn't have
Discord, we had
Like a mumble or a team speak
Or like Skype
And you just would have to see if
Somebody was hanging out in like your team speak
Go in, oh I don't see any names
And then leave
Sometimes somebody would just be in there
With their microphone muted
And you'd come in and just be like, oh hey what are you doing?
Oh I'm just like recording a video
I'm just making a video and then the other person would just be sitting there
And I think that happened a few times
For videos you made too
Yeah?
Like I would just be there and I would just
Because we were in the same call
You would just react to something I would just say
You were just doing it, you just were because you were in the call
Like
What was it, my Go Go Nippon video
Where Mayla entered while I was recording it
And I didn't know he joined
Which is such a hard thing to explain to people
What happens in that scene
And like why it's so weird
But yeah we had a very open relationship with our voice chats
Yeah because that was how
You communicated because
Skype sucked
And nobody wanted to use it
The program was like a piece of crap
So the only way you could even
Communicate was you had to have
It was almost like AOL instant messenger
You just had like your, I'm away right now
But oh hey are you here?
That screen share was cool
I wish they would bring that to Discord
Are they bringing screen share to Discord?
It's there, they actually edited it a while back
Really?
Oh my god
I am late to the party
Have I updated my Discord in like two years?
Have I skipped every update?
I may have
You're gonna want to update that Discord
Alright I got time for
I got time for like two or three more
Because I have to go to the doctor so
People are saying zombie pianists
Zombie pianists
Is that
You gonna delete this video live or
Are you gonna keep it up?
I'm thinking of something else because I watched that when I did
My thing
Let's get one that you and I both haven't done
I
I like
You have a loadout video
I suspect it's probably
Loadout?
Yeah I'm just curious because
Remembering that loadout existed
Gives me a tickle sometimes
Do you want to know, okay
This is just
This is funny to me for some reason
Would you like to know my
YouTube search history?
I just clicked in the thing
Okay
The first
Let's just read, let's go down the list
Ludwig fight
McDonald's review
Review
Funny cats
And then Ned and
Varus
Like scene
Like I wanted to rewatch like a Game of Thrones
scene
What about you? What's your last like
YouTube search?
How do you even see what your previous ones are?
Just go to YouTube and then click in
Like the search bar
Nothing shows up. I don't think I've searched anything
And I reformat it somewhat recently
Ludwig fight
I like don't use YouTube at all anymore
Neither do I which is why I think some of these are old
Alright so which one
How convenient
No it's a bad idea and I know
It's a bad idea. Is it a shitty video?
I don't know
I don't remember it so it must be
I don't remember even having a video
Are you sure it wasn't one of yours?
No I'm scrolling through your videos
I saw it. We could watch
Starforge video
Oh yeah I remember that
Yeah that's right
With like the weird, yeah let's watch the stirforge one
That one sounds pretty good
Stirforge. Is this the first time you
Ever used this name? Is this how you
Changed to stir?
I think this was
Even before I ever
Used stir on anything
I think so yeah
This was 2015
I think I just thought stirforge sounded funny
Okay I have a
Rumor too. You do? You have rumors too?
Well I don't have rumors
I have almost like
50% chance when I'm streaming you will hear
The lawn being mowed or a thunderstorm
And then there's one guy who plays
His music really loud
Here it's just people just blasted
Down the street as loud as they can
In like a motorcycle or a car
When they get to my window they go
It's time to go to like fifth gear
I know he's up there
It's just like okay
It's always like that
Noise counseling walls
Noise counseling?
Forget it. Are you gonna watch this video?
Yeah. Alright you ready? Yep
One, two, three
Change it from like simple to like
Good and then take a look around
People thought that was me
That looks pretty good
Why does it look like I'm looking into the inside
Of my computer
I'm looking at microchips
Oh my god walk around it's like
Magnified grass
Walk
It really is
It's like a bunch of movie screens
Who's watching me?
It's you. You're watching
You have to walk into one of them. It takes you to like another dream dimension
Yeah I thought that too. Thought it was gonna be
Amazing. Turns out they're all just
Bushes
Oh what's this crazy
Oh it's a bush. What's that over here
Something tells me we're going to need to reload the game
I'm not doing it
You're gonna play the game like this
Yeah we're just gonna move on
Why?
Hey you wanna see? Hey dude check it out I got a hamster
My mom got me a hamster. Oh be gentle
Yeah
You can't why
Try and get your view and like see where the tunnels are
Yeah maybe like another like 100 feet this way
Oh
What is it starting to show me now is my gun in my hand
What the fuck it's a Hydralisk
Behind you
Let's not fight this
Kill it
Nothing in here
I can't look at this screen
This is awful
Alright
I wanna jump off that cliff in front of you
Did this video get darker?
That mountain? Yeah I'm gonna jump off that mountain
This is a problem with YouTube
I don't think I knew about it back then
We're gonna get to the top of that and I'm going to jump off
Wait wait wait wait
Wait you won't listen to me
Wow
I'm not moving
I'm standing still
No one is here
What the fuck was that
It's fucking wild
You like my moon shoes?
Well use your moon shoes and
Fix the spinnies that aren't spinning
How do I do that? Do I just remove them?
Yeah you have to hold key
You have to get in there
What button is it? Just make sure there's a couple of glow sticks in here
Alright
What button do I press?
Where did you go?
Hello
This is Gary's video
You didn't tell me there were gonna be monsters
I didn't know
Don't you mean like an obstacle course?
Whoa
What's going on? What is that? Turn it off
What the fuck is that?
Is that a truck full of bees?
We got more bored with the actual game
The actual game is like
No no no
What are you doing?
Are you alive?
Yeah
Where are you?
They're following you now
I love how they're doing this
That's so awesome
You've got a pyramid and I've got a pyramid
We need to put them together
We need to make a bigger pyramid
They're on me
He just like toppled it over
Well the video also is running at like
How are these guys not dead?
I don't know, it's absurd
Why would you build this?
What's the point?
There is always a point
Progress
Yeah
I'm not sure if the helipad is in the correct spot
That sucked
Did it just get launched out?
It just tapped one of them
It's out
Not even dramatically
We're doing this again
What the fuck?
Are there enough of them?
No, not enough of them
There's enough of them
That's enough
We're down to like 14 frames a second
That's not the stream, that's the video
Dude, I gotta get out of here
I'm about to exit the game
Through the wall
Am I wearing it?
On your screen?
It's like five mini guns
It's like
One, two, three, four, five, six
It's seven mini guns
There's just seven mini guns coming
I remember this
It just goes like
Can I shoot them?
I just ripped my headset off
I distinctly remember how fucking loud that was
This is the clip that
Taught me what contagious
laughter Reddit was
Does that kill you?
Oh yeah, absolutely
Alright, what if I shoot it down?
See you later
Hey Star
You ever seen the movie Jason?
Fuck, I'm at 10 frames a second
I can't tell what's happening, all I know is I'm just trying to keep myself alive
What is happening?
Why is this all down here?
You've done a terrible thing down here
You put too many down here
You put way too many
I need to get out of the pit
Help me
Where's the little safe hole?
Good luck finding it at 7 frames
I'm getting launched back up
Oh yeah, we made a safe hole in the side to get out of the carnage
The safe hole, the safe hole
I see it, I see the safe hole
You've gotta get in the safe hole, dude
Shut up, I know
You've gotta get in the safe hole
Blighttown, somebody said
This is too much
Blighttown
I think I got in the safe hole and you fucking chainsawed me
Alright, so, question
This is a very important question
You're gonna get what's coming to you
So, I have a question
Yeah?
Did that game ever release?
Good question, the answer is probably no
Was that game an early game?
That was an early game
Was there ever a 1.0 of that game?
It's been what?
It's been like 3 or 4 years
It has to be
The game was released
That's probably not the actual release
I'm gonna assume no
When did it was release?
It says September 18th, 2014
I feel like you made that video
When was that video?
It flopped miserably and the devs continued to
Scan people with new games
Really?
I don't know
It was removed from Steam apparently
Alright, we can do 2 more
And then I've gotta go to the doctor
Let's see here
Everyone wants to watch
Jerma is mad
I'm seeing like 2 options
There's only 2 options
Yeah, but I feel like we've seen that already
Like a bunch of times
Didn't you watch it on your stream?
Definitely
Yeah, we've seen it
We've seen it already
I think we're just gonna have to make a new video
We've seen them all
Let's make a new Jerma is mad
You can just make another one
Yeah, like Diablo 4 when it comes out
Just follow me around and I'll be like
Fuck, fucking idiot, fuck you
Fuck, dude
Hello?
What the fuck was that?
I'm a soundboard boy now
Oh, okay
That wasn't me that just said that
No, it wasn't you
Why do you have a like, fuck, dude?
They're doing the he doesn't know
I record people's
Outrage in Overwatch now
It's my past time
Oh, I know
I thought you had that
I thought that was me because I just said, fuck, dude
Yeah, and it reminded me that I have
Two separate people saying it
What else do you have on there right now?
Fucking ungrateful DPS fucking cuck
People get mad
Is this Jerma uncensored right now?
No, no, no, no, no
This is not
Nope
I'll give you the longest
Jerma uncensored right now
But you have to wait until the end because the last guy who talks is the best guy
You're ramming DPS against the fucking wall
And praying to God that it fucking works
But you're fucking
Shit at the game
Dude, you're fucking a mercy player
Show us
Why do you
I was looking for the mute, I was
You asked
I said mad people in Overwatch
Why do you do that?
Because
Okay, for one, it's really funny when you play it back
To the person who said it and they get to hear themselves
Right
That's kind of a defining moment of life
And the second reason
Wrap one of me
And save this for whenever you need it
Can we get somebody on the fucking
On the cart please?
Because there's been like 10 fucking minutes straight of this bullshit
Somebody else change to DPS too
Can we get somebody on the fucking
On the cart please? Because there's been like 10 fucking minutes straight of this bullshit
There you go
Just so you can play that somewhere
I can't wait for this play of the game dude
That's my one wholesome one
You need a wholesome one
Listen to the sounds of despair
Like I don't understand
Please
He's given up, his life is over
Alright, let's watch another video
I don't want to listen to like the spy cam
Like recording people
We want to talk about YouTubers
Alright, let's go
When are we going to watch Jerma play the goat game?
Oh no, no, you said it
Why did you have to say that?
You're going to talk shit about me
You're going to watch the Diablo incident
Oh fuck, I do have a video on this game
The goat simulator game
Shit, okay
Alright, this is like you just
The lawyers finally proved you're guilty
And you can't even deny it anymore
The verdict just comes through
The evidence comes through, it's like they'll never get me
They'll never fucking catch me
And all of a sudden like a bloody knife comes in that you recognize
And you're like that's my knife and that's my hand
My hand prints on it
It's over, I lose
There it is
I didn't think they'd get it
But it was there on your channel all these years
Damn it
Remember to plus like to help spread the infection
You did that too
You can't throw that on me
No I didn't
And if you liked the video
I used to watch your YouTube videos
Back before I even started making YouTube videos
And you would say
Hey guys, like the video if you enjoyed watching
Like it likes help
That's fine, I'm talking about
Plus like to join my cult
Alright, I'm stalling too much
I mean, you could bail
I could bail, it's too late to bail though
Oh, the internet, Cox internet
I'm clicking it
Are you watching this too at the same time?
Is this really one of the ones we're going to go out on?
One more after this? Do you really have to go?
I can do one more
Okay, because you can't end on goat games
You have to end on a high note
This isn't really who you are, it doesn't define you
Plus, we can do this shit again too
Like we can do this like next week or something
Is Cox actually being a problem?
Oh fuck, fuck
I mean it is apparently
Ready, three, two, one, go
I think it's funny
It's already funny
I'll give this one to you, it's pretty good
Fuck, I think this is funny
My legs are so weak
I really need to
Strengthen them on the treadmill
The tower of the goat
Was once
Key to the treasure of the gold
Buried underneath
Mortamus, the grey goat
Helmed the tea to the tower
For generations
And
Excalibur, the black and white goat
White goat
Nice setup
Somebody on the computer over there, they eating dinner?
Hi, I'm Mr. Goat
I hope you are enjoying your dinner
This game is amazing
Trampoline baby
I used to have one of these in my backyard
Want to see what I used to do in the trampoline guys?
If you gave me trampoline right now
I can do three black flips on it
Hold on, this does not seem to be right
Did I go trampolining with you?
Yeah, pause the video
Pause the video
We went to a trampoline fun park
And how sick was I at trampolining?
You were probably
Besides the people we came with
The only adult there
And you were very good
You were better than all those other six year olds
Take that to the grave
I think we were probably the only people
Over the age of like
We may be the only people that were over 30
That didn't have children
There
I was like, dunking on people
I wasn't over 30
I don't know
How long ago was that?
Dude, I was like jumping so high from like
Thing to thing and I was doing like
Backflips off the wall
I was like, I was flexing on everybody there
We did the thing where
I was like, wait, wait, wait, wait
There was like a ton of people making a circle around me
And I was like, dancing and fucking doing flips and shit
People were like, clapping along
If only we had a video of the
Trampoline park when people would know
It was pretty fun, but I was
Confirmed that I could do a backflip off the wall
I just want you to
Thank you
Well, the walls were trampolines
I jumped into the wall, jumped off the wall, backflip off the wall
Land, another backflip
Then into a twist
The skater
9, 10 out of 10
Yeah, I held up a 9
I thought it could have been a little better
Yeah, but I mean I'm pretty fucking sick
At that
Alright, ready? 3, 2, 1
Push, catch me
Catch me please, help
Not gonna invite me
To your backyard
Party
I'll show you
I wanted the hot dogs
What?
I was trying to kick the thing
The thing over there and it didn't even work
You know what? It is gonna work
I'll make it work
I hope
He's flying
And he's on fire
Oh, and these people
Are all still dancing
Do you see what just happened to the guy that was hosting
The event?
What kind of dance is this?
Do this dance? No
I've never seen anybody do this
Dance, unless you were a toddler
These people are doing the
I'm a toddler learning how to dance
To like Mickey Mouse music
Any sensitive streamer makes fun of white people dances
Like this?
Honey, can you just go check on the greenhouse
And make sure my petunias
Are in line? Oh sure thing honey
Oh, the glass doesn't break
I've got your
Favorite breakfast cereal waiting for you
It's
Pop tarts
Oh, pop tarts
There's that in
I hate going grocery shopping
I always have to go grocery shopping
It sucks
I'm gonna get Coca-Cola Classic, that's like my favorite
And I'm gonna get Doritos, Spanada chips
Those are good too
I also want, what else do I want?
I guess I could use
A little bit of ham, do they have ham here?
I don't even know, maybe
Excuse me, sir, do you have ham?
Oh, he's not here anymore
Oh, she's dead
You must take
The garbage out of the cave
Of mystery
And you shall not pass
And do it fast enough
You can go first
Because best friends let their best friends
Go first on the slide
Okay
Have fun
Have fun on the slide
Wee
This is so much
Fun
I'm laughing at it
I am, that's humorous
Whoa, whoa, sorry
I'm sorry, I'll pay for that
I'll make sure you get like an extra monitor
A 27-incher
Not just a 22-incher, whatever that is
Who are you, Bill? How's life?
How's the kids?
Yeah, the kids are good, huh?
Yeah, that's great
Everybody expects me
To just trash this place
But you know what?
I think I'm gonna have some self-control
Because I could just
Trash this place right now
And it's really
Starting to build up that I really
Want to do it
But I think I'm gonna hold back
Just a little bit right now
Get out before I
Change my mind
Pretty humorous
Fuck you
Hello, sir
This mower
I feel like this video is like two hours long
Yeah, I was gonna say this is one of those videos
Where it's only
Six minutes and it just feels like it
Extends time
Oh, pause, by the way
Okay
You're just making it take longer by pausing, you know
Yeah, I know
Goat station
Did I tell you that today
Was baseball day at the gas station?
Oh, do you know
The stream that I'm doing?
We haven't talked in like fucking two months
Hey Mortimer, welcome to the party
Hey Frank
How are ya?
What are you cooking on the grill?
We've got some
Various meats that we are
Cooking here on the grill
That better not be
Goat meat
If it's goat meat I'll be upset
With you
It is lamb
My family we eat lamb
Time difference
Come here
It's not like two hours have gone by
Holy
This is like Katamari Damasi
Pretty good burger
How much stuff can I pick up?
Whoa, whoa, whoa
That's humorous
This is
Alright, this is the equivalent
Of going back and looking at your yearbook
Go back to your junior high yearbook
And be like, what did I do back then?
It's because back then
We didn't have the common sense
To say there's two minutes of good clips
I have, why don't I just
Combine it with another game
It always had to be all one game
You try and make
And then it has to be like at least five minutes
To make it feel like it's worth anyone's time
Who's gonna upload a two minute video?
It was always like, oh this is like three and a half minutes
Fuck, is that
Long enough?
I haven't had a video up in like
Four or five days
But yeah
I heard you mention a weird stream
At the beginning of the stream
So I don't know if it is
Oh, um
I
I'm doing a Twitch controlled
Robot carnival
Where I'm gonna have like a bunch of carnival games that Twitch
Chat controls and tries to win
And clowns and shit
This is reminding me that
At E3 Twitch had a stream
Where you controlled the person walking around E3
And what they did
And it did not go well
This is gonna go very well
Okay
Cause I'm worried about you
Hey I'm gonna mute for a second cause this is like spoiler
So they're not gonna be able to hear me
Okay
What?
Not muted?
No no you're muted now
I muted myself
To say that to you
Okay well chat was saying not muted
I don't think they are
You're not muted
I was going to repeat word for word what you said
But then you hit me with a fucking bomb
And I cannot
In good conscience repeat that
What do you mean in good conscience?
I just
I feel like
If I was just a germa viewer
And I didn't know you
I'd feel really bad for you
It puts people in a very uncomfortable situation
Wait what?
Why?
Mute! Mute! No no no
Hold on
We can just talk after the stream
Yeah like I'm not bound
To your stream
What am I doing?
I feel like I'm scared
This stream is gonna edit
We're never gonna talk for two months
I couldn't just say hi to him
One more one more one more
One more
What really happened?
Garbage
We need to end on a very good one
No that video
What's wrong with that video?
It is a good video
I wouldn't say garbage
People have been asking for GTA 4
All stream though
What's your favorite GTA 4 video?
I
I like playing zebras dance and shit
It's like the club
Club tornado
That's a pretty good one
Hold on is this
Wait a minute wait a minute
I remember this and we never used it
We never used this
Remember I did this every GTA video
Hold on we're gonna pause it after we watch for a minute
We're gonna pause after a minute
Okay so we're doing club tornado
And
There was a very specific thing
That I used to do every time
The loading screen would pop up
And it would be that
Let's see let's listen
Are you ready?
Three two one go
Shout out to all those back home
Hey mom there's a new night
That's not what it was
Didn't I used to say like
I used to go like
Like star up like
What was it was something about like
Was something about like weirdly enough
I think you did used to do a star you suck
It was star you suck
And then it was something about like
I don't even remember
I have no idea
Wait what say that again
I think it was star you suck
It was something about me getting a broom up your ass
It was something about me getting a broom
No no I think you doing it to me
What no
Okay mute us both
No no
Are you ready
What the fuck are you talking about
Three two one play
Club tornado
We've done the establishing
Transition shot so now
That's how you can tell that I traveled
To get here there's people throwing up outside
Probably because club tornado is
That amazing of a place
Fun is measured in vomit
You get off a roller coaster you fun
It was fun
Get the fuck out of my way
I fucking love this game
I don't get it it's just like any other club
Now we're leaving
We don't like this club
Club tornado you guys been there
Don't fucking come to club tornado
It's not even cool
It's kinda cool I like it
He's sitting down
No he's not
Watch out watch out
Watch out
Ten people just get fucking thrown around
By a tornado
This is a good beat man
That guy is on fire
Being an impressive motherfucker right now
It's gonna go out don't worry about it
Yeah I'm good
I remember we tried to figure out
My dancing mechanics for like 30 minutes
Go in the bathroom and make out or something
Fucking done
Another episode like that not gonna shit my pants
That was a problem quite frequently apparently
Damn it
Oh that filled up
That was a good one
Damn it
What the fuck happened
Ever since I made that video
About club tornado this place just sucks now
It's not even worth coming back here
This is pathetic
I'm leaving the worst review I can leave
What have I done
Why would you do this
I don't want to dance with this dusty old hurt
Well if that club is ruined
Let's try this knock off
Like imitation club tornado
Already
Oh my god
Everyone just look at these guys
Just standing around looking at you
Get me out of this dude corner
This isn't even a tornado
This is just a bunch of guys just like stuck up
In the ceiling
This is club vacuum
Come on you can't be giving zebras alcohol
Cause then they just throw up out of their chest
Everybody knows this
That's why there's the law
Don't serve zebras
Someone's gotta put a stop to this
And there's only one thing that can stop this
And I think you all know what it is
That was a pretty good night out
Through all of our GTA videos
You just had the truck button bind
So at will
You just had
At free will
Would just be pressing a button
And it was always just a truck
You never did delete that
I bet you if you opened GTA 4 right now
On your computer
And you did like CTRL T
It would fucking work
It's probably still there
That's so fucking funny
Well that's it
I gotta go to the doctor
I mean I could give
Like a webcam
Like I could give an opinion
You always gotta make it weird
Alright
He's muted
No I'll let you say goodbye
Goodbye everyone
Thanks for letting me exist
On Jerma's stream
I normally don't exist
But this last hour of being out of the bottle
Has been very nice
Now get back in there until I have some more wishes
I left the call
That's just kind of what he does
But anyways
I will see you guys tomorrow
I gotta get out of here, I have to go to the doctor
That's what friends do
They make it weird on your stream
I don't make it weird
No I don't, I just go like this
That actually looks like
Look at how fucking bad that looks
That looks like fat and then like tiny
That's Popeye
That's worse than Popeye
This is what happens
This is what happens when you put on like the Walmart muscle suit
This is what you look like
Bad ratio
Alright guys
I will see you tomorrow
That didn't even pop up but you can hear it
Thanks to Star for joining us
And adding some insight to some of those videos
I'll see you tomorrow
We're gonna do the regular time tomorrow
I just had to start early and leave early because of the doctor
If you've taken off
Take care, see you tomorrow
We're probably gonna play Sam and Max tomorrow
We'll probably start Sam and Max season 3
Tomorrow at the regular time
And then after that
We'll see
There's a couple things I wanna do
So we will do them
But good night
Let's do the bits
Oh good night, right, it's not even like fucking 2 o'clock
3 o'clock
Let me scroll back here
To 4 hours ago
Raid Kiwo after the bits
Yeah that sounds, yeah we'll do that
What's Kiwo doing?
What's Kiwo up to? GTA?
Hey we entered on GTA but you might as well
Go see some more GTA
So we had, earlier we had
Anthrobots thanks to the 3 bucks anthrobots
No message
3 bucks, appreciate it
And then Freudian Weapon 250
Thank you Freudian
Can't stick around to watch live today, hope you're feeling better
Jeremy Hart, good luck at the doctor
Yeah this is a follow up to the colonoscopy stuff
So, one I can't really miss
But yeah, I'm feeling alright
I've had some stomach issues over the last couple days
That have just been annoying
But we'll see
Everything should be fine
Mitchell, thank you Mitchell for the 15 dollars Mitchell
Mitchell says
The glue man basketball video is easily
Top 5 videos you've ever been in
And the pissed off GM has to be
My favorite Jerma joke of all time
Thank you for everything that you've done
I love that video
That video is just
Everything about that video
But how long that video took
That's a 3 minute video, that's not a long one
Remember we were talking about, oh shit this video is fucking 3 minutes long
Which one?
That's the Gabe the glue man degrosie
Basketball video
What's that video called?
I think it's just called like Gabe degrosie
Like b-ball or something
I think I changed the title of it
A while ago because the first title
Was a little too
Like ambiguous so
It's like his origin story right?
But yeah thank you for the 15 dollars Mitchell
It's fun to do this
Because like I said before
When we did this last like a couple
Like a month ago or so
You just forget all these things that were interesting
That you thought were fun
And I'm like just reliving
Being in the game
By the way that game that people were asking
That like spy hacker in the slacker game
That was called a clandestine
Right clandestine clandestine
What's it called?
That's the name of that game
Somebody asked and I just didn't even think about it
But it's fun to do
Jerma has
A sexy voice thanks for the 15 dollars
Thank you
Thank you for the 15 bucks
Jerma has a sexy voice
Really appreciate it
Marvash Mcgally thanks for the 250
Your patch notes video is basically a black mirror
Episode
Kind of
It may have
That was what like 2014
Interesting
Thank you door cube for the 250
Door cube we watched that video
Feeling a bit sentimental
So here's some bits
Thank you for being so good and funny
And for making one of my favorite videos
The door cube
I love this community and I've made some great friends here
That's really great to hear
Your name is that video
I like that so much that you're able to
Put yourself in this community so much
And get that much joy out of it
So that's great that's good to hear
Thank you door cube for the 250
And for sticking around
Glad you made some friends
DubSky dude thanks for the 250
I'm glad you still go back to your old stuff
I cherish those videos
I was even marathoning your main channel with a friend recently
Reminds me of the innocence of youth
Thank you for being such a positive influence
You create more happiness than you realize
I'm
That means a lot
I really
Anytime somebody says this
I'm just glad you think that
I'm not perfect
Anytime I can hear somebody say that
It makes me not only feel good about the community
And about the channel and everything
You just kind of hope you're doing your best
You know
So thank you
I'm glad you have a good enough time here
Thanks for being part of the community
Hey Zake thanks for 250
Okay I watched all your Minecraft videos
312 times can I see my family now
I don't know
Just push the chair away from the desk
And go
That's up to you
That's not up to me
Hey S10W update thanks for the
Hey Jerma when I said I was going to stop my bit streak I lied
Anyways glad we got to see the Jerma
Greatest hits before you
Die at a carnival
I'm going to be fine
Good luck peace and love also
E Jerma is going to be the death of me
E Jerma
Is going to be the death of me
What's E Jerma
E Jerma
I'm not sure what you mean by that
Hey Lycrae
Or Lycrae thanks for the 5 dollars
Hey Jerma not much cash but I'm a bit strapped right now
Would you ever consider playing the game
Frostpunk
I think it would easily be funny to watch
Since forever and we'll keep watching
The heat till the heat death of the
Universe
I haven't really looked much into it
Frostpunk is an 8 out of 10
What's this
Nice like turkey
That's actually a turkey
Play Blade and Sorcery I already have
I've played it like 2 or 3 times already
I've played that already
But thank you Lycrae
Jerma lied about Taco Bell thanks for the 250
Who took the pictures for the privacy pile
That was me
Googly Gareth thanks for the 10 dollars Googly Gareth
Hey Jerma boy it's your old pal Googly
Field back with another donation and animation
Hope you enjoy it and thanks for all the
Laughs throughout the years
I'm going to have to play this
Right now
No I can't
I'm going to hold on to this till tomorrow
We'll play this tomorrow
This is like a 4 and a half minute video
I have to go to my doctors appointment
So tomorrow we're going to watch this
Jerma animated streaming super star
Source Filmmaker video
We'll probably just start with it
Those of you that want to see it before
There's the link
We're going to watch it on stream tomorrow afternoon
Tomorrow evening
But thank you Googly Gareth
Talented Source Filmmaker animator
We'll watch it tomorrow
Cereal Star thanks for the 10 bucks
Why not revisit some of the games in these really old videos
With stir on stream
Also hi I have my first thousand bits ever
We were talking about that
That it might be fun to go do some of these
That you didn't get to see the whole thing
You just got to see a little snippet of info
You got like 5 minutes of
Footage with it when there was like hours
Of stuff to see
Once there's not a whole lot of new games
And new material and new stuff coming out
Then we'll probably go back and try
Some of the old stuff again
Come into it
But thank you
Cereal Star
I'll PayPal him like fucking
I'll PayPal him some money
I'll buy him a fucking
Massage chair
No those are like 5 grand
I'll give him half those bits
That's fine
That's a vocal contract
No it is not
I just rejected it
It's time for slime thanks for the 20 dollars
Time for slime
There's like a couple of fucking great
Videos here
We'll start with this tomorrow
I just do have to get out of here in the next like 5 minutes
So I've got to run
But thanks for the 20 dollars
It's time for slime we'll open up with these two videos tomorrow
They look pretty interesting
Dr. Zoot Zoot thanks for the 5 dollars
Hey Jerma I can't watch for a week
Because I'm going to the San Diego Comic Con
I'm really nervous this year
And your infectious confidence in front of an audience
Is exactly what I need before I go
I won't say why but let's just say that
Any chat members who
Go to the masquerade at the con
Will know why very very plainly
See you in a week
Thanks again for being the cool internet uncle
I don't know what that means
But
Hope you have a good time
Thank you for the 5 dollars
Is it like a nervous thing?
Do you like dress up in a costume?
I don't know what that is
Is it a furry thing?
Oh I see
Well whatever
I'm not competing
What did I get furry for?
That's just what people were saying
I've just been trying to figure out what it is
Do you just believe random people?
Well when
Like 20 random people
Write the same thing
It's just a costume contest
He's going to dress up as a glue man
Hey thank you Clueless Sniper
For the 250 other than Jerma Rumble live action
Which video are you most proud of?
Most of them actually
Most videos I actually
Obviously
Making little jokes and talking shit about
Random videos but every video I've made
I was happy with
At the time you know
They can't all be perfect
But yeah maybe 20 percent or 30 percent of videos
I've made I wasn't like 100 percent happy with
But most of them I thought they were fun
Otherwise I wouldn't have
Uploaded them at the time
So that is the thing
Thank you Clueless Sniper
That was you
C4G thank you for the 250
Someone asked for the chart at the end of the
Coin game
Here it is
Pretty strong
That's a pretty strong chart
Let's take a look
This is from the coin game stream
That looks like some pretty steady growth
And then here is from tonight
Not bad either
There's a drop over here
What is this drop from?
This is from the coin game
As you can see it was pretty steady the whole time
Is that talk
Where Goat Simulator was played?
It is
Really?
That's when Goat Simulator was loaded up
Wow
Holy shit
These are so interesting to see
Goat Simulator was cool
That was a pretty good voice I think
But thank you
That was C4G
Thanks for the 250
21 like the number
These throwback streams are a blast
Hope they continue to be in every now and then thing
Just love and take care
They will
You'll probably see one of these once every few weeks
Once every like month or so maybe
The thing is though
Once we run out of videos it's kind of it
Or ones that I would want to watch
But thank you for the 250
Thank you Sim for the 317
They say bonus 31
Mostly thanks for the 250
Mostly lost
Raid someone you boomer
Let's get the credits on the screen
Thanks everybody for joining
See you tomorrow
We will start Sam and Max season 3
Probably do a couple of episodes
Here are all the subscriptions
All the new subs, all the old subs, all the community subs
Thank you guys
Thank you to all of you
And there are a couple more bits to do
We've got Dr. Clay for 250
I have an important message, they say pickles
And that's it
Pickles is the message
Thank you
Thanks for the 5 dollars
Sorry to bother
But we've been trying to find the solution to this dilemma
For a day, what picture is the spray
You're using here
That's an easy answer
That is burger boy on Halloween
Dressed as Ronald Mcdonald
From like
2008 or like
2009 or something
Thank you for the 5 dollars
Thank you Germas
For thank you for the 5 dollars
Thank you for 5 bucks
Reptio, thanks for the 15 dollars
Thank you for continuing to make such amazing content
I'm trying
Sometimes you swing and miss, sometimes you hit a home run
But I swing
Every god damn pitch
Which is probably not a good idea, but you know
Whatever
Probably a bad analogy, because that means I strike out
All the fucking time
I'm very patient at the plate
I take balls
I take strikes
The average is like fucking 500
But thank you Reptio
For the 15 bucks, my pleasure
Glad you enjoy it
And then finally Sprio, thanks for 250 Sprio
Hey Germas, I just want to thank you for everything
You've inspired me to start streaming
And for letting me join this amazing community
I've met my best friends from this community
You've honestly changed my life
Thank you so much from the bottom of my heart
Looking forward to your future endeavors
That's fucking awesome
I can't believe
It shocks me all the time
But it makes me really happy knowing
That this channel, this community
This group, this
My streams and my videos
Have been able to lead people
To meet some of their best friends
That's
What do you even say to that?
That's just fucking crazy to me
That's awesome, thank you so much
And we'll see you again tomorrow
I'll be back tomorrow
I'll see you at the regular times
That's Pacific, Sam and Max season 3
Time to go to the doctor
Good night, good bye
And we're going to raid Kibo
See you guys real soon
Take care, have a good one