Somebody said he fell in the toilet again.
I mean, just imagine how that would play out.
Like butt sinks in, arms and legs both sticking out, wiggling.
Everybody help, I'm stuck!
That's not possible.
Maybe you got a tiny little toilet.
Like reaching with my index finger to try to press a text.
A phone that's in my other hand.
Send plunger!
Or just go live like that and not even fucking care.
Why are you live?
Why not?
My birthday was great.
I had a very good time on my birthday.
I went out to dinner.
Had some snacks.
It was actually very good.
It was very nice.
I have one problem though.
I got this...
I don't even know where it came from.
I want some medical professionals in the chat here to tell me.
Hold on, let me tweet this out first.
My hand.
My hands have been immaculately clean and perfect.
Just baby soft.
Since I was a teenager.
I've never had a single problem with my hands.
They have been delicate.
They've been strong.
No calluses.
No warts.
And until yesterday.
What happened?
I think I have it.
I think I know what happened.
But let me just keep going.
I got a wart on my finger.
And it happened the day after my 35th birthday.
So I got one of those things and I was like,
what the fuck is going on?
This is bullshit.
Why do I have a wart on my finger?
I've never had a single growth.
Ever.
Like I said.
So I went and got one of those freezing kits.
I freaked out and I was like,
I have to freeze this thing off.
I got one of those liquid nitrogen little like...
You don't get an STD on your finger.
Okay?
That's not what...
It's not...
Look at how...
What's the definition of that word?
Your fingers are not a sexual organ.
I have an STD on my hand.
That's not even...
That's not what that means.
They are though.
What are you talking about?
They are.
Omega Low.
Tell the STD story.
No.
Well, I looked this all up.
Apparently like...
This is why I don't like to touch anything.
It's like a vi...
You can like...
I don't know.
Touch like a door handle that somebody touched.
Touch like a...
Touch like a surface.
This is why I don't touch anything.
The day after my 35th birthday.
Bang.
You have a wart on your hand.
Now I've freezed it off and now it hurts.
So my gamer finger...
It's in it, by the way.
Debilitating retirement incoming.
It's on my gamer finger.
It's right where it sits.
Like on the fucking mouse.
Like barely.
And I know everyone's going to say show it.
I don't want to show it because it's disgusting.
And I will never...
I will not show this.
So okay.
If I click very gently today, you know why that is.
I'm not going to show it.
No, I'm not going to.
It's revolting and I hate it.
I don't like showing gross things on my body.
No, I don't want to.
I'm not going to do it.
I can't.
I won't do it.
All right.
Okay.
What if I blur the camera?
Oh shit.
Okay.
What if I censor it?
Anyway, let's just go over what we're doing.
We're going to be playing The Long Drive today.
We're going to play Left 4 Dead today.
But I had a bunch of scheduling conflicts.
So we're not going to do that today.
We're going to do it maybe another time.
Who knows?
I don't know.
You know as good as I do right now.
Tomorrow I'm going to be on Kitboga's stream.
I'm not streaming tomorrow.
I'll be elsewhere.
I'll make sure you know exactly where that is.
I have no idea when that is, by the way.
All I know is that it's going to happen.
Because the nature of what Kit does.
If he gets a good call, then maybe he'll want to bring me in.
If he's like, no, no, this one sucks.
No, no, no, no.
Forget this one.
But I will be on that stream.
Just kind of in the wings waiting to do something fun.
Am I going to use your voices?
I don't know.
It depends on whatever he wants to do.
That's the plan for the next, the remaining couple of days.
Now, if The Long Drive, if I'm done with The Long Drive in like an hour,
I'm just going to move on to that super game.
Like House Whipper.
All right.
Let me hold on.
Let me.
I have to put on pants.
And this is just I didn't think the cam was going to be on at all today.
I have to put on.
I have to put pants on.
I'll be right back.
It's good.
We're still on the starting screen.
That's fine.
Okay.
How do I censor this?
I don't want to show this shit.
It's disgusting.
Okay.
Webcams not even plugged in.
There is a monster that sneaked into this room at night and unplugged my webcam.
It's not me.
Why is it unplugged?
All the stupid things.
Why?
Why unplug my webcam?
Why not pull the power cord out?
That's way funnier.
I don't know.
I can't turn my computer on.
There's something wrong with it.
I'm going to fucking work.
Who is unplugging my webcam?
Did you guys hear like a doodledoo?
You did?
You should have.
Hey, there we go.
Okay.
All right.
So here's the deal.
I'm going to blur this.
My hair is a fucking mess.
Hold on.
It's delayed too.
I'll tell you that the trouble I'm going through right now to show you guys a wart on my finger
is it's insane that I'm doing this.
Okay.
So please not have like a weird frame here.
I'm like so scared.
I like don't know if I should do this.
Okay.
You see?
Can you see?
Okay.
So here.
Clean.
Clean normal hands.
Regular.
See?
There's nothing weird there.
I cannot put my right hand up.
Okay.
Should I do it from far away?
No, I have to blur it.
This is not how big this was.
Okay.
It's after I froze this shit is when it did this.
So I like put the freezer on there for like 10 seconds or whatever.
And you take it off and your skin turns like all white.
And then it like it started inflating.
It actually started inflating.
I'm not kidding.
Okay.
If I show you from far away, that's that's like, oh, it's okay.
Right?
This is so embarrassing.
Do you see?
It hurts.
I'm not going to show it up close.
It's not alive.
All right.
I'll show it up close with us with a sensor tag on it.
Hold on.
It's literally nothing.
No, it is something.
You don't make me show it up close.
I will.
Okay.
Hold on.
I need to put a I need to put a blurring effect on this.
I need to focus the camera.
Okay.
Here we go.
Ready?
All right.
Okay.
So we're completely censored now.
So like doesn't matter.
Like you're not going to puke.
See?
I've been completely censored.
I could be in a fucking TV commercial.
I could be like a law show and you would have no idea who I was.
We need more censoring for this.
We need more censoring.
See?
I told you.
I told you it wasn't good.
And this shit's right on my gamer finger.
It's a homunculus.
No, it's not.
I it's that's from the freeze.
It was tiny but I freaked out because I'm 35 now and I can't have warts on my hands.
35.
I'm not 80, 105.
So it's on my gamer finger.
Long story short.
And you ain't ever going to see me again.
I'm turning the face cam off.
I don't want it on.
This ain't a face cam stream.
Imple popping.
Don't say that.
Oh, it's disgusting.
I hate it.
I don't even like looking at it.
I'm an incredibly clean person.
I'm so clean.
I shower.
I bathe.
I I do the I do I you know what I mean?
Like I bathe.
I go like this and like that doesn't bathe.
Yeah.
I go under the armpits too.
You don't.
You just put the shampoo conditioner combo can thing that you buy at the grocery store
and you pour that on your head
and you shake that into a lather and then you let it run all over your body
while you smear your hands all over your body
and like all over your legs and balls and stuff.
That's what you do.
I know it is because that's what I did until I was about 30.
No, I use a puffy.
No, you don't.
You don't use a puffy until you're at least 28.
It was five years ago.
Five years is a long time, man.
That's a long time.
Every time I click.
Do I have to go on like the streamer like disabled list for 15 days?
Because I can't click the mouse.
All right, the Boston Red Sox have to put German 985 down to the disabled list.
You see, it's a big wart on his finger.
It isn't that embarrassing.
Back to you, John.
Please just drain it.
You're not supposed to.
No.
The wart specialist that I watched on YouTube said don't drain it when it becomes a boil.
They said after you do the freeze, it's going to do that and leave it alone.
Yeah, there's a...
Guys, are you that shocked that there's a wart specialist on YouTube?
You're like witches and warlocks on YouTube.
You don't think there's a wart guy?
All right, here we go.
This is the long...
I don't know what peaceful means.
I'm assuming there's like monsters or something.
I don't know.
I got $50 from Goiki.
Thanks for the 50, the 5,000 bits.
And they say, hey, Jeremy, the monkey ball timer ticking down sound haunted me while
I tried to sleep at the last stream.
Keep up the good work.
Get well from the gameritis growth on your gamer finger.
You know, you have a really great message because it says,
Hi, Jeremy, the monkey ball timer trickling down sound haunted me while I tried to sleep
last night.
Your stream was haunting me and I felt horrible.
Keep up the good work.
Thanks, though.
That's a lot of money.
Thanks for the 50 bucks.
Silence Serenity.
Thanks for five subs.
And Nuclear Waffle.
Thanks, guys.
Are we ready?
How do we...
I don't know how to play.
Wait, this is like...
I thought this was a driving game.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
E is open.
Why do I feel like I'm playing fucking TF2 at like 400 FOV?
Oh, you actually have to hold it.
Is there any sound?
Why is it so low?
Hold on.
Seed.
All right.
Okay, there's my fucking personal telephone number.
Hold on.
Let's put this up.
Is it better?
Okay, I can actually hear now.
All right.
What does this do?
Tab is equip.
Middle mouse button is rotate.
Oh, shit.
It's one of these games.
Move.
Okay, see, that's how you wash.
Okay.
Scroll is move.
You can move it towards you or forward.
Right mouse button is rotate.
Middle mouse and right mouse.
Well, this is going to be a fucking joy.
Wait, you guys can't see anything?
Why did that happen?
Okay, so tab is equipped.
We got mouth wash, left mouse button, mouse wash.
Oh, cool.
This is so much fun.
Okay, cool.
Wait, cotton candy.
All right, so how do I pick this up?
How do I put this down?
Oh, F, pick that up.
And what the hell is this?
This is a duster.
Okay, I don't think that's what that is.
Eat this.
Can you?
I'm trying to do like party tricks.
All right, well, what am I supposed to do?
This is the cotton candy.
Do I need any of this stuff?
Wait, there's a gas tank.
This is going to take a while to get used to these controls.
Why is there a gun?
Is it a gun?
How do I use the gun?
I gotta clean the barrel.
A little rusty.
Oh, dude, I'm going to do the thing that happens
like John Wick when he goes,
get the hell out of my way.
You know what I'm trying to do.
Hey, seems like you're the one that's in my way.
How do I put items down?
Do I have to shoot with my other hand?
See, to me, this is like if you were like
a gun novice or something,
this thing on my right hand would be like
a product that somebody would sell.
That's just an absolute stupid bullshit product
that's supposed to help with suppressing the fire.
Here's the gun grip.
I feel like that would be on like an infomercial
that like four o'clock in the morning
that no one would buy.
You sick of the big recoil on your shotgun?
Not anymore.
All right, what the fuck do I do?
How do I put this down?
All right, I gotta look at the controls.
Mount, pick, mount, dismount.
Equip, reload, sleep.
Wait a minute.
Why is there a piss button?
Okay, this just turned into a completely different game.
This turned into a different game.
I don't know.
This is stupid.
Okay, I'm gonna be honest.
I still don't even know how to put things down.
All right, one, two.
Okay, so that's...
And I have a gun now.
How do I fire it?
What's this?
Okay, oh, there we go.
It's just in my inventory.
All right, give me the binoculars.
Good, okay.
Give me the fly swatter.
No, fuck that.
What's the pointless...
Ammo!
Nice.
Okay, pick up the ammo.
Okay, let's clean the car.
Is this doing anything?
Dismount.
How do I open the garage?
It's fantastic.
Okay, let's...
That's bright.
That's really bright.
What do I have to do?
This is a long drive, apparently.
I'm actually...
I wanna see what's in here.
Anything downstairs?
Ah!
I'm gonna put this in my dashboard thing.
You know, people have it on their rear view mirror.
Can I put this on there?
All right, hold on.
Open the door.
Okay, how do I get in?
Sit.
Nice!
Oh, I have to drive.
Okay, close this door.
And then we pull out?
Do I have gas?
How do I drive?
There's a crosshair.
Put this down.
Put the ammo somewhere.
All right, how do I turn the car on?
Oh, shit.
Okay.
How do you drive?
Oh, boy.
Okay, okay, all right, all right.
Okay, let's go.
And then we just drive.
Wait, we're driving too.
Dude, I can't even see!
I can't see the road!
Is there a road?
Oh, okay, but this is the road.
Okay, is it like this ultra bloom effect or what?
How far...
What do I have to go?
How do I turn up the super bloom?
You can't.
What do you mean I can't?
Wrong side of the road.
Ow, my gamer wart!
That hurts so bad.
See?
That's why I told you I couldn't fucking play.
That would have killed me, I think.
All right, slow down.
I gotta slow down.
Slice it off.
Wait, what am I doing?
No, don't open the door.
How do I use this?
Oh, it's cigarettes.
It's not ammo.
Okay.
How do you throw shit?
How do I drop?
Yeah.
Oh, okay.
All right, now I got two hands on the wheel.
So what's the goal here?
Do I have like a task?
It's just to drive.
All right, well, I'm gonna fucking kill this.
This game is gonna be done.
What's the end goal?
How far do you need to get?
Turn on the radio.
I don't think I have a radio.
It's long.
All right.
Well, I'm all right with that.
Actually, I prefer this.
Is that weird?
Watch out for that fucking rock.
What's that?
Did they just keep putting more obstacles?
You have gas.
I have like no gas in the tank.
What do you get gas?
I'm going 130, 140 miles per hour right now.
I need to go to a gas station, a gas store.
Really?
I have a GPS.
What's that?
I see something right there.
There's a house right there.
Hit the brakes, hit the brakes.
Brakes, brakes, brakes, brakes, brakes.
Brakes, hit the brakes, hit the brakes.
Holy shit, there's other cars here.
What happened?
What?
Did I drink it?
What did I just do?
How did I drink that without taking the cap off?
How do you throw things?
Nice.
Pick up.
What even is it?
This is gonna be fucking...
This is disgusting.
Come on.
It's been three days since I've had anything to drink.
Okay, that's probably against the rules.
I probably shouldn't do that.
Is that gas?
Ow.
Oh, shit.
Okay, here we go.
Push.
Ah, that's fun.
Okay, gas.
How much is in here?
I can drink the gasoline.
All right, how do I fill up a car?
Okay, here we go.
Open this and then gas.
Nice.
Is there an easier way to throw?
Okay, wait, can I suck the gas out of this one?
Hold on, I can...
Can you actually do that?
All right, how do I put this back on?
All right, this game just got way cooler.
Wrong side.
Okay, I gotta back this thing up.
I don't know why I do...
Okay, that song, was it...
I'm just telling you that's what I hear, okay?
How do I get the fuck out of the car?
I don't want to take the other door off.
Get out.
Out.
Lean is Q and mouse?
Oh, that's kind of cool.
Okay, how do I get the fuck out of here?
I don't...
What?
I don't want to take the radio out.
E, okay, let's go.
What else is in here?
Extra tires, take them.
Oh, shit.
Can I put this in the trunk?
Okay, put the tire in the trunk.
You always need to spare.
What is this?
Can't see.
What does it say?
Car oil.
Extra virgin car oil.
All right, let's put it in there.
4% oil.
Diesel.
All right, 47% gas.
40% diesel, 30% oil, okay.
Can you open this?
Oh, wait.
Right.
I didn't...
Look, it's a video game, guys.
I didn't think I could actually open the hood.
It's getting dark out.
Put this back on.
All right, I gotta go.
I'm probably just gonna bring like creepers and shit.
Okay, this is scaring the shit out of me.
Wait, I gotta fill up the gas.
Fill up the gas, fill up the gas.
All right, fill this up.
Can I fill it up with this?
All right, hurry up.
I need to take one more thing.
I don't know what that is.
I don't know what this is.
I don't know.
I'm gonna take it with me though.
Ow!
Shit, that fucking hurt.
Let's go.
No, don't take that off.
Get in the car.
I can't see anything.
Okay.
How do I turn my headlights on?
How do you turn headlights on?
What does it say?
What's wrong?
You broke the car.
Turn on the headlights.
I don't know how to turn the headlights on.
Because you put oil in the gas tank.
I can't fucking see anything.
You put three types of fuel in here.
Fucking whatever.
All right, give me this one.
Get in here.
This one will...
This one probably at least has gas, right?
Shit, I just have to use my shitty car?
How do I turn on the headlights?
Handbrake, space, accelerate, brake, steer, ignition.
Eye, lean, lean up.
Lights!
You lost in the tutorial.
Well, I'm learning how to play in the tutorial.
I'll get it next time.
Go back for the motorcycle.
I didn't see a motorcycle.
Oh, blood.
That came out of my mouth.
Just spit out a bunch of kool-aid.
Can I get a different camera angle?
Oh, that might have been it.
That might have been it.
Longest drive, seven kilometers.
Doesn't seem very far at all, actually.
Okay.
All right, let's go.
Continue.
Wait a minute.
It gives you checkpoints?
This is not good, though.
I still don't have the gas.
This car has a bunch of fucking different fuel in it.
Can I do anything about this?
All right, what's this?
Can I bring this with me?
Oh, what's this thing?
This looks dangerous.
Oh, shit.
This is a way better car this time.
Give me the gun.
Give me the pew-pew balls.
Give me the oil if I need it.
Give me the coffee.
Whoa.
Oh, this is the front of the car.
No, it's not.
What kind of trunk is this?
What?
It's a front engine, a back engine.
What the fuck?
I've never seen a back engine.
This is freaking me out.
I've never seen this before in my life, in my entire life.
Oh, there's a block of gold.
This actually is a brick of gold.
All right, I need this.
Fucking god damn it.
It's over here.
Okay.
Holy shit, Jeremy.
Are you stupid?
There's like a bunch of gas here.
Pick it up.
Good.
It fits.
I don't care.
What am I going to be?
Binoculars for what?
Oh, airbrush?
Oh, wait.
That's an emergency light.
I need that.
Go get the girlfriend downstairs.
What girlfriend is downstairs?
Whatever.
Wait, can I take...
What's in here?
Is it alcohol?
This is just all full alcohol.
I can just make...
Can I make...
Wait, this is diesel.
Okay, can I pick this up?
Okay, we're going to take this.
I'm going to put this in the back seat.
You never know.
I might find a truck and I could use it.
All right, this is like...
Okay, I bought a coffee table one time.
And I jacked up the entire inside of the back of my car
because I was like, no, I can get it in there.
And I technically could.
I could technically get it in there,
but not, like, safely to not ruin your entire backseat.
It technically fits in there,
but I ripped up a bunch of shit.
I ripped up the seats.
I scratched the fucking ceiling.
Let's see if I can get this in here.
Oh, yeah, I can.
Just remove it.
Just take the doors off.
What the fuck am I going to need these for?
Who cares?
Yep, just like the coffee table.
Wait, can I put this back on?
All right.
Yeah, we're good.
This is exactly what it looked like, by the way.
Except it wasn't as tall.
I can still see.
Okay, I need this emergency light.
Oh, that's how you throw.
That's how you throw.
What's under there?
That's pretty cool, but I don't...
Wait, wait a minute.
All right, I'm ready.
It's time to get huge.
I think I'm ready, right?
What the fuck was that sound?
Close the door!
I'm safe in the car, right?
What was that?
Oh, what happened?
He died.
He's dead.
What happened to him?
What is this?
It's like a giant bunny.
Get out of there.
It ran into the wall and died.
I know.
I'm just scared.
I'm just...
I believe.
I don't know why this just scared me so much.
Why did that scare me?
I thought another one was right there.
All right, I'm out.
Let's go.
I can't see anything.
Okay, I'm going to get this.
This is going to be fun.
Let's go.
This way, right?
I'm good.
All right, I'm looking for a big truck.
Turn on the radio.
I don't have any song files in that folder.
I saw that.
Music distracts the shit out of me when I'm driving.
That's why I never drive with music on.
You're not going to fuck with me.
No, I don't like driving with music.
It distracts me.
You're a psycho.
No, I just...
Look.
What?
So you want me to drive around with distractions?
I have to take a sip out of this drink,
but I'm afraid to because I think I'll drive into something.
Let's slow down.
No, I don't drive music.
All right, so I have a whole thing of gas.
We're looking for a truck.
Why did that just go down the wrong pipe?
Hold on.
Okay, sorry.
I just like swallowed that wrong.
And no distractions.
Stop distracting me.
No, I don't talk.
I don't want to talk to you in the car either.
This is how every car ride is.
No, it's not.
I'm not that...
All right, easy.
Look, I can talk and drive, but I cannot listen and drive.
So you want to get in my car?
I'm going to monologue the fuck at you.
But you can't talk to me.
All right, we got a pit stop here.
What do we got?
Oh, dear.
Okay, hold on.
What about my gas though?
I want to get out of the car.
I want to get out of the fucking car.
What is this?
This is like a Marty McFly bike.
I hear a fucking weird noise.
Oh, there's no tires on it.
All right, let's go.
Ah, what kind of tires does it need?
Does it have gas?
Turn your car off.
All right, turn it off.
Push and steer?
Why can't I push?
It's so stupid.
Okay, turn the car off though.
For real.
Turn it off.
I turned off the car.
Aye.
Okay, thank you.
What's that?
Okay, stay there.
I got to get tires for this.
What is it?
Radiation?
Gas.
What does this take?
Does it have a fucking gas tank?
Is this just a bicycle?
This is just a bicycle.
This is not a motorcycle.
Get out of the way.
Really?
Okay, tire.
Get this.
Pick this up.
Oh, okay, that does not work.
Does it need special bike tires or what?
Do we need a bike tire?
Where am I going to find a bike tire?
This shit should work.
Hey, all right, this one.
All right, sit it down.
Okay, pick this up.
It's dirty, that's why.
What the fuck?
What's wrong with this?
Because there's a hubcap on it?
Oh, shit.
Okay, I got a bike now.
I got a bike, I got a bike, I got a bike.
I got a bike.
Give me the bike.
All right, is there any space for me to pick the fucking thing up, please?
All right, what's a better car?
The green Cadillac or the red McQueen?
No tire?
What do you mean no tire?
It's right here.
Well, it would work if I could sit on here.
Whoa, I thought you said there was no gas.
You said there was no gas.
You said it was a bike.
Why?
Liars.
Stand this up.
You said it was a bicycle.
All right, let's go.
Here we go.
This is a bicycle.
What's the gas for?
It's for turbo.
All right, I have to get on this now.
I have to leave now.
I have to get out.
I'm freaking out.
I got 100% gas.
Can I put anything on the back?
Stay upright.
How do I get it to stand up?
Where's the kickstand?
Oh, my fucking God.
Press B.
Balance.
Okay, I have to get on now.
Get on the bike.
Just get on.
Why is it doing this?
Where are the lights?
Wrong way.
I'll get it.
Okay.
Okay, I'm going.
I have the gas.
Ignition.
It's a battery.
You need the battery.
What?
Don't run into a rock.
I'm going to use the headlights from the other car.
I find it.
Okay, that's not even a fart.
I can't get the funny fart joke thing,
but that is like you shit your pants.
Okay, I need the headlights.
They don't even...
Okay, I thought that was just like a supernova.
I need the headlights.
Thank God.
All right.
I need to be able to look.
Okay.
I have a little bit of light here.
I'm going to see if there's a battery by the gas pump.
Battery.
It's green.
No, this is oil.
Seriously?
Okay.
Just put this fucking thing.
Can I fit it in the car?
Can I fit the...
I want to take the bike with me though.
The engine's in the house.
Well, then I'm just going to have to sit and wait.
What's this?
All right.
I should probably shouldn't be breathing that in.
Well, it's a paint.
It's paint.
I get it.
Right.
Okay.
This isn't...
We're just not doing anything.
Somebody just gave a shitload of subs.
That's 59 community subs from Red Zed Rider.
Thanks for the nearly 60 fucking subs, dude.
That's insane.
Thank you, Red.
Holy shit.
We also had a bunch of donations too that came in that were huge.
What's that?
Is this it?
I just can't see anything.
Oh shit.
Like it doesn't turn the lights on in the house.
Oh man.
We're going to be fine now.
Oh god.
Is this it?
I think I found it.
This is definitely like a bike engine or something.
Yeah, absolutely.
What is this?
A bike engine?
It's a bike engine.
Pick it up.
I'm going to lean this against the house.
Get in and close the door!
Get in!
Drive.
Drive backwards.
Okay, I got him.
I got him.
Is it it?
Okay.
I don't hear any more noise.
Is it weird if I just want to sit here until the sun comes up?
What if I just don't want to do anything?
I'm safe in my car.
It's like lightning, right?
When you're in your car, if lightning strikes your car, you're going to be fine.
You're protected in the car.
I don't know if that was a lie that my parents would tell me
because I was terrified when we were driving around.
There was thunderstorms.
Is that true?
It's the safest place of all.
Yeah.
Ow.
I'm a gamer wart.
Sleep.
Oh, I can sleep.
I think it's huge.
Nice.
Red, Zed gave another 50 subs.
Red, you are a fucking maniac.
That's like 110 community subs.
Thank you.
That's insane.
That is way too much money.
Oh, this is shit.
It's a ton of subs though.
Thank you, dude.
Okay.
So can I put this on?
Mount.
Ooh.
Bingo.
There we go.
It's been done.
Let's do it.
Hit the gas.
Oh.
There we go.
Oh, you didn't build the engine.
What?
Look at how fast I can go now.
Needs a battery.
Okay.
I have daylight.
Let's go.
Is there a battery in the house?
I'm going to prank my friend.
Oh, dude.
Did you see what happened in your front seat?
Somebody shit on it.
No, this is not real.
That's like the plastic poop stuff.
Like his friend didn't squat down and shit in his front seat.
Hey, dude.
Look, there's shit on it.
Did you just do that?
Yeah, I did.
Battery.
Give me a battery.
Let me see one.
Look, I want to take this bike there with me.
I see it.
No, you don't.
You do not see it.
Remember the headlight.
Okay.
Let me do what I was going to do before.
How much gas does this car have?
Where's the gas tank?
Is that in the trunk?
Is this an electric car?
Fuel tank empty.
Well, what the hell are you talking about, man?
That's the weirdest place.
All right.
Let's go.
Fill it up.
Fill up the tank.
Is this all the gas that was in here?
What is that?
Oh, right.
This is perfect.
3.9 ruined, ruined, ruined, ruined, water, water.
What are you talking about?
Derma, don't, don't.
Omega, well, please don't, don't, don't, don't, don't, don't.
It's a gas.
No, it's not.
It's water.
Why does it have water in here?
I have a water meter on the right.
Peak hydration.
I'm just a running fountain.
Drinking and peeing at the same time.
All right.
That was cool.
Now what?
Oh, right.
Gas.
This thing's got gas now.
This thing's...
Oh, yeah.
Right.
This is missing a tire.
That car is way better anyways.
All right.
Let's take...
Wait.
Let me get the sponge so I can clean it.
Make, make, make, make.
Close this.
I want to clean this car.
I think this is...
Okay.
This is a good...
Never mind.
It's not the sponge.
Why did I not take the sponge?
What a sick asshole would you be if you were doing that?
Just rubbing a gold bar all over your car.
What are you...
Oh, fuck it.
Are you a leprechaun?
I want to take that with me too.
Let's paint it red.
Oh, I hate it.
I don't like it.
I hate it.
I want another one.
Look on the roof.
What?
What color is this?
Blue.
Yep.
Tilt.
How do I tilt it?
This is going to look sick.
Stop grabbing it.
Let go of the...
Why am I magnetic?
Oh, it looks good.
Don't you think it looks good?
Chat.
I hate chat.
Don't you think it looks good?
Chat.
Look.
All I care about is taking the pictures from this side.
It's okay.
It don't work.
Guys, it's a Craigslist car.
I take the pictures from this angle, this angle, this angle, this angle, and this angle.
You don't see the whole other side of the car.
There's fucking dense scratches like smeared shit all over.
It doesn't matter.
Half the car could be missing.
All right.
This thing's ready to move.
There's no back seat.
No back seat.
Dudes.
How are we going to take our diesel?
To start the engine, climb the...
What are you doing?
Start the moped.
Climb on by looking at the seat and press the E key.
Press I to switch on the ignition.
Press space to lift the kick then hold W.
Climb on.
Press E.
Press I to switch on the ignition.
Press space to lift the kick then hold W.
That's what I'm doing.
Okay.
Press E.
Press I.
Hold W.
See?
Doesn't matter.
Kickstand is up.
And yeah, I need like a battery or something.
All right.
I got to take this with me though.
I won't eventually use this.
Let's pick this up.
Let's try to get this somehow in this car.
Take the battery out of the car.
The car battery.
Oh shit.
Wait.
I got to sleep in my car first.
Too late.
I can't sleep yet.
Why?
Get out of the car, are you buffoon?
What do you mean get out of the car?
This is the only place I feel safe.
All right.
That could have been me in the chair here like in real life.
Hey Jeremy.
Hey.
Oh shit.
There's a person.
No, don't come in yet.
Hey.
What's up, man?
I'm just chilling here.
Don't come in the car though.
Just stand out there for like another five minutes.
You smoke, right?
Smoke a cigarette.
Come on.
Go to bed.
Adjust your mirrors.
What do I need to adjust the mirror for?
Until I get to look at me.
That's all I can do right now.
I can't sleep yet.
Are there other people?
I'm going to sleep with the lights on too.
The doors are locked, right?
Nobody can come in here.
How can I not sleep yet?
It's pitch black outside.
Please don't murder your battery.
Oh shit.
Almost time to sleep.
I see it.
What do you see?
What do I even look like?
It's fucking coming.
It's coming.
I'm in my car.
I'm safe.
Nothing can hurt you in your car.
I got the lights on over here.
I'm fine.
Aliens.
What's that?
Is that what you're talking about?
What is that?
It's like a meteor.
All right.
Time to sleep.
Okay.
That's what I look like.
Wow.
That's cool.
You can actually see a head moving around.
All right.
What was I doing?
Battery.
Right.
Stupid back engine.
Wait a minute.
If I take the whole engine and put it in that car,
won't this have full gas?
Is that a battery?
What is this?
Coolant tank.
Where's the battery?
This guy doesn't have a battery?
Guys, I don't think batteries are in the game.
There's no such thing as a battery in the game.
Bike is already ready.
All right.
Let's just take it with us.
Can I take the seat out?
Did I do that?
Hold on.
Did I do that in my sleep?
Why?
Just drive.
Hold on.
I have to close that.
That's not going to work.
Or is it?
What's wrong with this?
I didn't put water in here.
What do you mean water?
I did not put water in there.
The thing is the tank is open.
Hold on.
Holy shit.
There's an animal.
I didn't close the gas tank.
Okay.
We're good.
Why?
I didn't fill it with water.
I drank the water.
Look.
100% gas.
Nothing else.
See?
What happened?
I need oil?
Oh, no.
What?
Check the oil.
Fuck.
All right.
Where's the oil?
That's the gas tank.
This car is freaking me out.
Where's the actual oil?
Isn't it underneath?
You need 3% oil.
3% oil in the tank.
Is it for real?
Like a lawn mower.
No.
That's gas.
I thought this is a gas tank.
3% oil?
Didn't do anything.
That's gas?
This is gas?
It says car oil.
Give me fucking oil.
Who's got oil?
Is this oil?
Oil?
Huh?
I can't.
Where's the indicator?
Oil.
Go.
All right.
3% oil.
What's going on?
I'm not even putting it in the car.
Is that OK?
Just drive.
Hold on.
I need to close this.
All right.
We're good.
Let's go.
Long drive.
Nice.
All right.
I'm on the right track now.
Wrong way.
I care more about the mirror.
This was a face cam.
What do you mean?
Am I going the wrong way?
I don't remember what side this was on.
Guys, I don't know what the hell's going on.
This is the right way.
Hey.
Thanks, Jack.
Appreciate it.
Bike needed oil.
It's OK.
We'll get another one.
This car sucks.
Hey, guys.
Don't ever take your eyes off the road.
Hey, based 20.
Thanks for the five.
Just need to be able to use it up.
Your face cam in the mirror.
No.
What's that mean?
Is the car too hot?
Why do I have a minigun cooldown meter?
I don't understand.
What's that for?
I'm going on over here.
It means everything is fine.
OK, cool.
This is loud as hell.
Turn this shit down.
All right, we're good.
Do I need water?
How far have I even gone?
Is there a way?
The alignment of this car is so wrong.
It's just pulling to the right.
I'm just being ripped to the right side.
Spit in the engine.
Hey, German on 85 here.
I'm still alive.
OK.
OK, let's just get this shit out of me.
Can the car still drive?
It's all right.
I'll be OK.
Oh, boy.
Was somebody...
Yuck.
OK, we're OK.
Put this back on.
Wait, put it in neutral and roll it back.
I lost a mirror, but who cares?
Let's move it back.
Did the engine just fall out of the car?
Oh, shit.
It's all messed up now.
I don't need this.
OK.
Stop moving.
Stop.
No.
No, I don't want to kick it.
It's going to hit the other pole.
No, no.
Don't be...
Thank you.
Wait a minute.
Keep going.
Keep driving.
Hit that motherfucker so he doesn't kill me.
Get him.
Oh, my God.
There's a guy.
OK, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
I'm fine.
Where's the gun?
I have a gun, don't I?
I didn't use the gun.
R plus mouse.
What?
Brake barrel.
What do I do?
R plus mouse.
There's no bullets in this.
How do I use these?
Holy shit, I did it.
What the fuck?
OK, reload.
He's still alive.
Fuck you.
All right.
Go, go, go.
Where's the car?
I have 198 shots to fucking kill it.
God.
OK.
Where's my car?
Come on, I don't have a tire.
I don't have a tire.
It's getting dark.
I can sleep in the car.
Oh, thank God.
Get me in.
Oh, I'm so glad to see you.
Where's the front?
I can't tell.
Where's the front door?
I don't care where it is.
Just get in.
Get in, get in, get in.
Sit, sit.
There are no lights.
It's OK.
I'm going to be fine.
The car is rolling.
OK.
So, I got oil.
I got...
Can we stop the car?
Oh, boy.
I got to push this.
Why is this shit in here?
Why do I keep shitting in my car?
It doesn't make any...
All right.
I've got to push this thing.
How do I hold on to it and push and steer?
That works.
Get me in the car.
Get me in.
I just need to push it so I can steer it.
OK.
Get it back on the road.
That's all I care about.
The handbrake.
Put it in...
What?
It's in park.
Oh, fuck.
OK.
Then I got to get in while it's still going.
You don't think I'll be able to do this shit?
Oh, yes, I will.
Hey.
All right.
Where's the tire?
No, no, no, no.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Get back over here.
Come here.
No.
Making it go faster.
I can't, dude.
Fuck this.
I'm going to be chasing this.
Just restart?
I don't have to yet.
I'm going to...
Don't worry.
I didn't go that far from that gas station.
I'll be OK.
I had to look in the fucking rear view mirror and be a dick.
OK.
Brake.
I'm ready.
Here we go.
Push and steer.
Where was it?
Come on.
Push and steer.
All right.
Which was the right way?
This way, right?
Or was the car accident?
Yeah.
Somebody just said it.
I can just Flintstone this thing.
I'll be fine.
Um, why did that happen?
Because I stepped on a rock.
Is that really what that was?
I tripped on a rock.
It's OK.
It's going to end up in the right spot anyways.
All right.
Can I just shoot it?
Stop.
What do you mean stop?
I have to.
I jumped to it again and...
Perfect.
I have to clean the blood off this thing.
Oh, shit.
There's one of those antelopes.
I'm so scared it's going to run at me.
I have to do this.
Otherwise, they're going to kill me.
All right.
No, they're running away.
We're fine.
Back to the road.
It's self-defense.
It's just running down behind you.
No, I'm good.
I'm good.
All right.
We're getting back to the road.
Does a spare tire in the trunk always bring a spare tire?
I know.
Exactly.
Always bring a spare.
Even if you're going down the street or behind you in real life.
Oh, the dog back there.
I've made it back to the road.
OK.
Now it's just a question of just be careful here.
Don't be an idiot.
Put it in brake.
Get that spare tire.
Yeah.
Gold sure is worth a lot right now, isn't it?
What can I do with gold right now?
I could be the richest man on all of the earth.
If I don't have a spare tire, I'm dead.
OK.
Now what?
I just have to make it to a gas station.
I'll be OK.
I don't even know what happened.
What happened?
I didn't do anything.
I just ran.
I'm better off just walking.
Just abandon the car.
I can't.
I have to.
All right.
At least give me at least give me the gold bar.
Restart Roy.
No, I'm not restarting yet.
Not yet.
I'm not done yet.
Let's go.
Get.
Shit.
Where's the fucking road?
Where's the road?
What's on the front seat?
Just restart.
No, but it's I'm so close to the gas station.
I can feel it.
Look, I'll just do a Mario Kart skip.
All right.
Fine.
There's the road.
Road's right there.
Oh, oh my God.
He's starting to believe this is.
No, I'm not.
I don't.
I just want to.
I just want to get to another gas station.
Use the save state.
I don't have save state.
It doesn't have an engine.
Odd Watchers skip.
Don't.
You stay right where you are.
Open the hood.
If I open the hood, I can go faster.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
If I just take this whole thing apart,
but leave the wheels on,
will I be able to run faster with it?
Is that for real?
Like if I just push a skeleton,
will that be okay?
I'm not going to mess with anything right now.
No, not messing with anything.
Just leave the car.
There'll be another one at the next station.
Yeah, I'm running.
Turn the radio on.
Okay.
No, don't tell me to do that.
This is the correct way.
Yeah, I'm good.
It's not even going that slow.
I'm probably running like 15, 20 miles per hour.
I'm just going to walk.
I'm just going to walk, whatever.
It's too fucked up.
It's too hard to do that.
Hey, maybe it'll meet me there.
What about the gold bar?
Money is useless in the apocalypse, dude.
That thing was so cool too.
It's all right.
I have my gun.
I'm ready for anything.
I drank a shitload of water.
I'm fine.
Get to the homeland.
There'll probably be one very shortly.
A long walk.
Restart, reload.
I think I'm in too deep right now.
I don't think I can.
All right, if there's not a gas station
within the next 60 seconds, I will.
If there's not a gas station on the horizon in 60 seconds,
I will restart.
Reload the gun, they mean.
All right, I got it.
Why did I have to look into the rear view mirror?
This game is really fun though.
It's just stupid.
Okay, hold on.
Is there a gas station on the horizon?
Hold on.
This is going to load up here in a second.
I got a hundred and nine.
Can I wait?
Can I sleep on the ground?
Turn up the draw distance.
You'll be able to tell.
Kill for food.
Oh, I'm making it to the gas station.
Fuck you.
I don't even care.
I'll sleep on the goddamn ground for all like it.
Wait a minute.
What's that down there?
Is that a tire?
Is that the car?
What is that?
Is that blood?
What's that over there?
What is that?
Come on.
Give me a gas station like right now.
No.
All right.
Fine.
I know.
But that's like the whole point of the game
is not to just be like a restart Randy.
No, I got this.
I do.
Okay.
After this.
One, two, three.
After the fourth street light,
if there's no gas station on the horizon,
I will restart.
There's one.
Here comes two.
What's that noise?
Somebody has one of those toys
that they're turning upside down though.
Donald Trump?
Excuse me.
All right.
There's two.
Here comes three.
No.
I don't want to restart.
No, no, no, no.
Whoops.
There's two.
Don't ever restart.
What's this?
Oh, shit.
Evidence.
I think this is where the car was.
Wait, is that my...
What is that?
I think we're close.
Do your Donald Trump as a cat again.
No, I don't even know what I did.
Look at all the resident sleepers.
It's like...
I know.
But look, I'm making progress.
Trust me.
I know.
I'm just trying to make progress.
Look.
Okay.
Let me...
I gotta be upfront with you.
The last stream I did was Super Monkey Ball.
And I save stated restart Randy'd
six or seven hundred times.
I gotta...
We gotta go to the other side here for a little bit.
Let's just do it three times this time.
Okay.
Hold on.
What is that?
I'm looking for...
Whatever.
I need the light.
Fuck.
No.
Pretty good in-game noises, don't you think?
Okay.
All right.
Okay, PUBG.
Okay.
Shotgun needs a little bit of fucking tuning.
Now, don't it?
Why can I not hit this thing?
What?
Okay.
I get it.
Just like all the people that complain about game mechanics like that,
it's usually their own damn fault.
I don't understand.
Like, what's with this hit-wrench?
You don't have any bullets.
All right.
But yeah, whatever, dude.
Time that guy.
I'll ban him.
I don't want that person in my chat room.
Fuck.
Come on.
I really do have to restart soon.
If I can't...
It's gotta be right here.
Right?
Come on, man.
This is so boring.
Please.
I'm sorry.
I know.
I'm working on it.
Trust me.
It's fucking Super Monkey Ball.
I didn't fucking have to restart the...
No, it's a mirage.
Press F4.
What did you just do?
Wait, what the hell is this?
You can just put a camera down?
Why?
That's so stupid.
I love it, though.
The vlog cam?
Hold on.
No, no, no.
Now, no.
Now it's a vlog cam.
Oh, okay.
Here we go.
No, I don't have time to do this.
I don't have time to do this.
I believe the camera there.
I don't have time.
You want like a four-minute bit right there?
No, no, no.
I have to find my way to a gas station.
Look.
I'll make everybody happy.
See?
You don't even care what happens now.
Wait, was I drinking my own piss?
What?
Am I going the right way?
I just turned around like five times.
I don't know.
Is this the right way?
I have no idea what's going on.
I don't know.
Am I going the right way?
All right.
I mean it this time.
I really seriously mean this.
If I do not...
If after this rock formation right here,
there's not a gas station,
I'm going to restart.
Times two, ResidentSleeper.
Just you're going to feel so much better about this.
When I go back and there is a POG truck
that only spawned in this seed
and I found it, you're going to be like,
well, I'm so glad this motherfucker didn't restart.
You're going to be so happy.
You'll be like, oh my god.
I was telling him restart Randy.
I was going, restart Randy.
Andy, restart Andy.
And by the way, you're calling me restart Andy?
Restart Randy?
I haven't restarted once.
You call me walking Andy.
Walking Walter.
You guys got it wrong.
Come on.
You guys Twitch chat.
You're supposed to know these rules.
Okay.
It's coming up.
I'm about to restart.
It's going to happen.
I like this game though.
I'm here for a while.
I think this is fun.
Okay.
All right.
For real.
I know.
I can't have like half the stream
be me walking to a gas station.
You're right.
Right.
How do I...
You can.
Okay.
You know what?
You guys got to...
The enablers in chat,
they're enabling me so hard.
You're almost there.
I'm probably not.
I see the gas station.
Where?
There's no gas station yet.
You're almost there.
Am I?
It's right there.
Right there.
Where?
Is that it right there?
Walking bus simulator.
Walking desert bus.
Now that would be a real, real game.
You know how people do like the desert bus thing
and you have to do the whole thing.
Imagine walking this whole thing.
Desert walk.
Yeah.
It just saved a checkpoint.
All right.
Come on, man.
Come on.
I don't want to restart yet.
Please.
Right over here.
Right when I turn this...
This bank right here.
It's going to be right there.
Brink the oil to go faster.
Turns out that's a lie.
That didn't do anything.
All right.
Are there any nutrients in oil?
Somebody look this up.
Like if...
If I...
Because isn't oil like dinosaur bones ground up
and fossils and stuff in the ground and everything?
It's like all...
There could be some nutrients in there.
Oil is just the earth's blood.
What do you mean false?
It's the opposite of that.
It's like decomposed like soil
and then boogers and stuff
and old shit and piss and diarrhea and bones and jello.
All the old jello that they threw away.
It all turns into oil in the ground after like 600 million years.
Okay.
I have to pull the plug on this.
I got to restart.
I can't believe I did it for this long.
I'm so ashamed that I did it for this long
and I didn't see it to the end.
I'm ashamed.
You're almost there.
Get to that rock formation.
I can't...
I feel like that rock formation is permanently in the background.
I did tell you when I hit this bend
if it wasn't right here that I was done
and I was going to restart.
Come on.
Right here.
What's that?
We found...
Okay.
We've got something.
We got something.
We have something.
Something here.
What's that?
What is that?
I see something in the distance.
I see a tower.
I see like a...
Is that an oil tower?
There's definitely like a car over there.
We're good boys and girls.
Stare at this until you can't see anymore.
We're almost there.
We're so close.
Okay.
I'm happy now.
But how far away is that actually?
Get my gun.
Spawned in.
Holy shit.
Why do you have so many hits?
I might need this.
I'm going to take this from me.
Where'd it go?
There it is.
All right.
I'm going to hold it up to the sun.
I'm going to cook it with the sun's rays.
If I hold it here long enough,
it'll get like at least like internal temperature
of like 140 degrees, right?
You and me, buddy.
You and me are best friends now.
Come with me.
This is my Wilson now.
Wilson.
Do you see what's out there, Wilson?
It's a bus.
Can you believe it?
I can't even believe it, Wilson.
And you all wanted to restart Randy.
You're not going to get it from here.
He's just my shade.
He's my sunglasses.
There's a big bus over here.
You can do a better Tom Hanks.
Maybe.
I'm so happy that there's this huge bus over here.
Yes.
This thing is huge.
Okay.
So now what?
Does it need anything?
Do we have gas?
How tall am I?
Okay.
First of all, let me look up here.
There's a ladder here.
Can you get up there, please?
What's in there?
Bring this up.
Why can I not touch this?
Get it.
Get it, get it, get it, get it, get it.
Quick, quick, quick, quick.
Get it, get it, get it.
I couldn't pick it up.
Draining.
It's draining.
It's draining right now.
How do I go down?
Stop.
Oh, fuck.
There's a hole in it.
What is this, though?
Snow.
Stop.
Pick up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up, up.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
What is in this?
Can empty whatever.
How do I get in?
Get me in.
How do I get in the car?
How do I get in the bus?
Push, push, push, push, push, push.
I don't understand.
Can I not get in this?
I won't even tell me that I walked all this way
and I can't get in this fucking bus.
Under the front bumper.
Smash the window.
Blind.
What do you mean blind?
Right there, right there.
What are you talking about?
Where?
You see a button on the bumper?
There's no button.
Where is there a button on the bumper?
What are you talking about?
Under the bumper?
What kind of car?
Why does...
What kind of dumb car is that?
Why do you have a hidden open the door
under the bumper button?
Why can't it...
What do you...
What?
All right, I'm ready.
Is there anything in here?
Okay, thank God.
Let's go.
Let's get the hell out of here.
Oh, thank goodness.
All right, how do I close the door?
Come on, man.
Come on.
Oil.
Oh, I have oil.
Okay, where does it go?
Why is the bus moving?
Why are we moving?
Is oil in here?
I don't know.
How do I open up the bus?
How do I open up the tank?
I've never driven a bus before, guys.
I don't know.
Where's the secret James Bond button
to open the fucking front hood?
It's in the back?
Okay, let's put this down.
Is there another weird button?
Side panels on the back?
I don't know how to open this.
Side panel?
There ain't nothing in there.
Shit, the fuel tank is empty.
It's empty.
Oh, fuck you.
You guys are not even...
He's fast.
Fuck, are you doing?
Fire.
I seriously...
I can't believe it.
Was it gas in that little tank that I shot
because I couldn't pick the fucking thing up?
All right, 3% oil.
It's 100% oil right now, but that's okay.
I'm so sad right now.
I can't believe it.
There's nothing in there.
Nothing at all.
Absolutely nothing.
I can't just like drip the drops in there.
Will that work?
Can you imagine if this is fucking turned on?
Why?
That's so sad.
Now I actually have to restart.
Check the panels?
Check the side panels.
Wait, there might be gas in these?
No.
Wilson!
Wilson, I'm sorry.
I'm running over your head right now.
It'll be okay.
Okay, I have to restart.
I have to restart.
I'm so sad to do this.
Check under the tower.
If there's nothing under here, I'm done.
That's so sad.
Oh well.
No, nothing.
Damn it.
I had to try.
Okay, I'm ready.
This is the real one.
What's the point of having that?
Hey, Shimpa, thanks for the 20...
Okay, Shimpa gave 40 community subs.
Thank you for the insane amount of money, Shimpa.
Thanks for the 40 subs.
Of course, this car sucks.
Anything else back here?
Also, I think I got base burning already,
but thank you base burning for the five.
Thanks for the fucking 40 subs.
Can I call anybody?
You guys are giving stupid amounts of money today.
Thank you.
This is the only car that I got.
This is it.
Nothing else in all the secrets back here.
6,000 of you just thought that was the funniest thing
that's happened the whole stream.
And I'll take it because, you know, comedy is comedy,
even if it's not very good.
All right, what we got?
All right, this is water and gas.
This time, I'm not going to fuck around.
This is the real playthrough.
This is the real one here.
Fair tire in the back, good.
Get this in there.
Take the water too.
We might need it.
But we're good.
We're ready.
Fuel tank, is that 100%?
Oh, upstairs.
Okay, there's a rabbit.
Go upstairs.
How do I get up there?
Oh shit, there's a bucket here.
Who's trying to get in the window?
Windex, what is this?
Oh, it's a face mist.
What even is this?
What about in here?
Cool little like hobbit hole.
All right, let's drive.
Yeah, I just realized what I was just doing right there.
You're right.
Yeah, that was kind of weird,
but it was not what I was trying to do.
Let's go.
Time to really drive for real.
Get the diesel this time.
No, no, no diesel.
Can't even adjust this mirror.
There we go.
Stop.
I'm not going to do that.
I will not do that again.
I 100 million percent promise.
Thank God I dodged that accidentally.
Okay, this one, I'm going to get far on this one.
I can't help it, I have to.
How much gas do I have?
Not a whole lot.
Look at the fuel indicator.
Is that full?
Wait, that's left to right.
Right is empty.
In what kind of world is that?
Don't be a fucking idiot.
Slow down.
That's the fuel right there, right?
Oh, no, that's the fuel.
Okay, what the hell is that then?
B-O triangle, triangle?
Temperature, yeah.
Why is this camera in here?
Oh, it's because it's in the car.
Well, that's doesn't do.
That's not a good place to put it.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
This is going to be cool.
Ready?
Here we go.
Let's go.
See you later.
Cool.
Come back.
I just dropped you guys off.
Good luck.
I just every 90s comedy movie'd you guys.
Oh, I got to walk in the fucking desert
for potentially two or three minutes.
And then somebody's going to pull up.
It's going to be a bus full of like cheerleaders.
No way.
Tower.
Where's that tower?
Let's get that off.
All right, where's the tower?
Let's go.
All right.
Do you want me to give you my best?
Let's go.
No, it probably hurt.
Nothing here.
But there might be a treat at the top of the tower.
No, no bus friends for us to be happy about.
All right, but there's something up there though.
Hopefully it's oil or fuel or gas or something.
Let's go.
Ow, my eyes.
All right, do you want me to like to like 14 year old Xbox live?
Let's go.
Or like 35 year old adult screaming?
14, okay.
Yo, let's go.
No, let's go.
You don't want to wake up anybody in your house,
especially like your parents or something.
If I drop this, is it going to break?
Easy.
All right, what's in here?
Gas.
It's 1.3 liters of gas.
Hey, go into the gas storage.
No, don't do that.
I want in here.
I got plenty of gas.
I'm going to be the guy that sells it to everybody.
And then be the guy who gets robbed and killed first
because you have all the stuff that everyone wants.
You can't just pull up like this in an apocalyptic scenario.
Okay, so that'll be $10 a gallon, please.
Nope, I'll take it all.
Oh, but my plan.
Chimpa just gave another 20 subs.
Chimpa, that's 60 on the day.
Holy shit, dude.
That's a fucking ton of money.
All right, which way is the right way?
I don't remember.
I think it's this left, right?
Yeah, it's like if you're the guy with like 500 cans of Campbell's soup,
500 people are going to show up to your house.
Uh, give me one of those.
No, okay.
I'll be back with 100 people to take them.
Oh, I had a minute.
I know I could do it in time.
No one likes Campbell's soup.
You don't have to like Campbell's soup.
You're going to eat it in an apocalyptic scenario.
I'm sorry, but if you don't...
Oh, I don't enjoy Campbell's.
I guess I'll die of starvation.
What was in the road?
What was possibly in the road?
Oh, like a fucking trash bag.
Like a sleeping bag was in the road.
Okay, cool.
I lost a mirror.
I'm good.
Can I put this back on?
There we go.
We're fine.
Everything's fine.
Uh, what happened to the...
Why can I see through into my car's skeleton right now?
Toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat, toy boat.
I can do it all.
I can do it all day.
Right, right, right.
What?
What's right?
There's a boat?
Is that a boat?
Is that what you're talking about?
What do you mean boat?
Left.
Oh my God.
Holy shit.
It's actually just like made out of like paper.
It's a plant.
I'm okay.
I'm fine.
I felt like I was going to go through the windshield from hitting a cactus.
I don't know why I thought that was like a cinder block.
Why is there a boat over here?
That's weird.
It's a battleship.
Yeah, that makes no sense.
Let's investigate.
I didn't do it.
Can I actually...
Dude, are there uh...
Is there like secrets in here?
Let's just live here.
We could, I guess.
There's a little place you can go in.
All right, I gotta get my gun.
This is probably a monster.
Holy shit.
Look at all that fuel in here.
I need to...
Do I have room for that?
I'm going in.
Pick up.
What is it though?
What's in here?
I can drink it, but what is it though?
Empty.
This is oil.
Shit.
I might need to take some of these.
Can I like siphon some of this?
Can I just dump it in the back of this seat and shit?
Can I take any of this?
That's a lot of oil.
Okay, hold on.
What's in this one?
Gas.
This is 57 liters of gas.
I have to take this.
I need to take all of these somehow.
Let's fill this...
Okay, we're gonna fill this car up completely.
We're gonna fill the whole tank.
All right, let's take it in.
Okay, this is gas, right?
All right, let's go.
Fill up all your other containers.
Holy shit.
I think we just hit the jackpot.
Can you get in?
Get in the car and drive.
Just run in front of him.
Run, run, run, run, run.
I'm going to bed.
Oh, no, no, no, no, no.
I left the lights on all night.
Is that bad?
I left the lights on the whole night.
That's not gonna be bad, right?
All right, pray that it's not a problem.
Thank God.
Okay, it turns off.
This is heavy.
How am I even picking this up by myself?
Can I just dump it in there?
We're gonna have so much gas and so much oil.
I'm gonna be rich.
All right, here we go.
Want this in here?
We were out of gas.
I didn't even know that.
Fill this whole thing.
As long as I don't run anything over,
this car could probably take me pretty far.
Sure, this is original shit car,
but I could take the doors off other cars and repaint it.
Don't forget the oil.
How much oil do I need?
3% oil, right?
3%...
Okay, 1% of 40 is 4.
4, 8, 12...
Hold on.
No, wait.
1% of 40...
Okay, now what?
That oil over here is the one, right?
Yep.
No, no, no, stop.
This is not a 2.
I don't know what that even is supposed to mean.
What do you mean this is not a 2?
Guys, I just go to the gas station,
put the thing in and just hold it down.
I don't even know what's in there.
It's just this makes your car move.
I don't know anything else about it.
So just gas.
It's not a two-stroke engine.
Do not put oil in the fuel tank.
Okay, saved.
This is a lot of gas too.
This is great.
And there's still more in here.
Oh, have you seen a full tank before?
Close that up.
Okay, what about in here?
So this is...
What's in there?
Is this water?
This is water.
All right, fuck this, just drink it.
How much is left in here?
3.3.
Stop, stop, stop.
You need water.
Oh, get out of here.
Okay, put this away.
Fill this up at least.
This is...
All right, here we go.
This is gas.
Let's fill the gas up.
Open the hood for the oil.
Yeah, I will.
Let's fill this up.
Is this...
How much is left in here?
Oh, plenty.
Okay, let's go.
Ready?
Mix water and gas to make a potion.
Stop.
What do you mean stop?
I'm filling this gas tank up.
What do you mean waste?
What are you talking about?
I got it.
I'm good.
I'm not missed.
What are you talking about?
All right.
Now it's spilt.
Now you spilled it.
Thanks a lot, chat.
God, I had it.
And then we're gonna put the oil in the front
and then we're gonna load up
and get the hell out of here.
I'm sorry.
You're not drinking water.
You're drinking coolant.
All right.
That's good.
That's filled up.
And you tell me don't...
I need the water for something eventually.
All right.
Well, this is gonna be fun.
Let's just do this.
I almost just died.
I was trying to do skeet shooting.
It doesn't even do anything.
Okay.
Oil.
Fill it up.
I don't know, dude.
Okay.
That's 100% coolant.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
We got 100% full.
Get out of the way.
I can't see this.
You dare.
Don't, please.
Okay.
Everything's full.
Close it.
I'm taking this.
Fuck.
No, there's still plenty of water in there.
Let's get a couple of sips.
All right.
Okay.
We're good.
It's time to continue.
But wait.
I'm gonna bring a barrel of this with me.
Find a water barrel.
Alcohol.
What do I need that for?
Do I need alcohol for something?
Water.
Alcohol.
Empty.
I'm looking for water.
I just want to fill my water tank.
Gas.
Water.
Oil.
Gas.
I probably can take one.
I could take one of these with me.
I'm gonna take one of the gasoline with me, at least.
Come on.
Take a keg with you.
No.
I'm not taking one of these kegs.
I'm gonna take one of those with gas.
That's gas and oil.
Okay.
That's a weird combo thing.
I'm not sure any of these can even be water.
I think it's just either gas, oil, or alcohol.
What the hell is this?
What is that?
Oh, it's a cactus.
Yeah.
Gas and oil.
All right.
I'm just taking one of the gases.
I'm just taking one of the big gas ones.
Which one?
There's one line here somewhere.
It was just all gas.
This one here?
No.
Take the alcohol.
Do I need the alcohol?
Do I?
All right.
Well, this says 35.
This is the most so far.
I'm taking the gas.
It's more important to me.
Alcohol.
Take the alcohol.
Fix the alcohol and the gas.
I can probably fit them both.
I just drank it.
Shit.
Don't let them alcohol light you.
You're right.
I'm not even sure I can take any.
I don't think I could even take any, guys.
I don't think it's not going to fit.
I'll try.
Try the back seat.
Which of this one here has what?
Where is it right here?
All right.
This one.
Let's go.
Put it on the roof?
You're going to physics the fuck out of the car.
Yeah, that's a bad idea.
Can I mount it to something?
I don't think that's going to work.
Save the game.
Save.
Can I take the seats out?
All right.
Let's get slow down.
Slow, slow, slow, slow, slow, slow.
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Please, please, please, please, please.
Okay.
Take the door off.
I thought that was going to kill me.
I was about to be so annoyed.
All right.
Okay.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
We can actually do this now.
We just need to move some things around.
The spare tire is going to have to leave.
Sorry.
Useless.
Okay.
What is in here?
This is water.
Gas.
And is that oil?
I'd really like to pick that up.
Why can I not pick this up?
Pick up the oil.
Yes.
We might be able to get another one in here.
All right.
So what should I take?
The alcohol?
What should I take?
Like packing for a trip.
Hold on.
These are all sealed up, right?
Yeah.
Okay.
Take the tire.
Let me put it back together again.
Why is that?
What?
What's the?
We have lots of advice friends.
It's okay.
It's good.
No, I can't take the tire.
I'm not going to be able to fit in that.
Wait.
I can take the front seat out.
Can I just take out both seats?
I can't.
No, I can't take the seats out.
All right.
I think I can still fit it.
So do I take the alcohol?
Yes.
Okay.
Give me the door.
Where's the door?
Quick, quick, quick, quick, quick.
Give me the door.
That's a couch.
Shit.
Okay.
I got it.
It was in there too.
I just couldn't put the fucking door on.
Just leave it.
But fuck it.
Let's go.
I have to leave.
Put it on.
Put on the stupid pain.
Come on, man.
Put it on.
You're killing me.
I gotta piss.
Give me a sec.
I'll be right back.
Oh, shit.
Viewers dropping.
Five minutes.
There ain't gonna be anybody left.
Shit.
Don't I know?
Don't ever go to the bathroom on stream.
Especially with the camera on.
I'm thinking, Jeremy.
Fucking idiot.
Somebody just wrote, fuck him.
Well, no.
I'm not gonna say that
because, you look, I'm not gonna...
Look, I'm at a BRB screen for five minutes.
Oh, I guess I'll wait.
No, there's other shit to do.
All right.
What was I doing?
Do I use a random number generator
to choose games?
All right.
That motherfucker right there
just almost turned on
Ratatouille for the Xbox 360.
I was about to press the button.
It was one second away.
But I'm gonna press it.
I think I'm gonna hold off.
Don't do it.
Okay.
Car tire.
Found.
You know what?
I'm just gonna do this in the morning
when I can see.
Just go to the fucking bed.
I'll do it in the morning.
Oh, cat.
There's an alien cat.
Oh, boy.
Oh, there's an alien cat.
I don't know where he is.
I don't know why I'm talking like this.
What?
Is the door open?
How many doors are open?
Okay.
If I don't move, he won't see me.
I'm not gonna die.
I'm alive.
Okay.
All the doors were open.
Well, that's great.
Let's continue what I was trying to do before.
Why can't this go on?
Oh, well, that's why.
It was dark.
Give me a break.
Well, you tried to do that shit in the dark.
Ain't gonna happen.
Good.
Should I take the chocolate?
No.
It's too much.
We're good.
We're completely loaded up.
I got gas.
I got alcohol.
Bring Wilson.
Wilson left.
All right.
Is everybody ready?
Back to the road, boys and girls.
Let's go.
Full tank of gas.
Whoever's texting me.
I can't talk to you.
Oh, we got to get back on the road, which is this way.
I don't like that view.
This is fine.
No, this is kind of how I sit in the car, like right here.
All right.
That's good.
Left, idiot.
I'm adjusting my shit.
No, that's one guy.
Ban that guy.
All right.
Ban that person.
Actually ban them.
We need to start.
There has to be consequences for one guy fuckery.
And then unban him and give him a $60,000 a year salary.
And then fire him.
And then invite him to your birthday party.
And then don't show up.
Yeah, a $60,000 a year salary working 12 seconds.
All right.
What's the math there?
Is it like 12 cents?
Where am I going?
Where's the road?
Go back to the ship.
No, I need to go back to the road.
I'm going to be lost.
I need a GPS.
I need like a compass or something.
Stop doing that.
It has to get out of my way.
I'll keep doing it.
Let's find the lampposts.
Wrong fucking way.
Rip, rip it off.
Good idea.
Now there's no distraction.
Where's this ship?
All right.
Yeah, I got to find the ship because the ship is going to give me a good indicator of where I am.
Okay.
So it's this way.
I don't know.
Turn on the radio for fuck's sake.
There's nothing on here.
Jesus.
I got plenty of gas to find the road, okay?
Your car sucks.
Oh, yeah?
Look at all the materials I have.
Turn fucking right.
Where's the road?
Smooth as silk.
Right, right, right, right.
Oh, I see it.
Okay, we're good.
I see the road.
I'm driving into the sun.
That's the road right there, right?
With all those lamps and all those things.
Am I leaving the map?
No, I'm right here.
We are right there.
That deserves one coffee sip.
Find somebody that can fucking do what I just did.
You never will.
I'm the only one that could have just done that.
Only person on earth.
Talk about my reaction time behind the wheel.
All right.
So is it left or right?
The correct road.
Which way?
Left or right?
I have no idea.
Right, MLG.
Is it 50-50?
Yeah, I'm getting kind of a lot of answers here that I don't know.
Left, then right, then mod him, then ban him.
All right.
Yeah, there's the boat.
Keep the poles on the right.
That's how you know you're going the right way?
I don't know how fast I'm going.
I don't have a speedometer anymore.
Tiny little rock in the road almost just ruined everything.
Slow down.
No reason to go that fast.
Go faster.
The faster I go, the faster this run ends.
Okay, one kilometer in American toddler-speak is what?
Two, three miles?
Two miles?
2.2 miles for one kilometer.
Oh, that's pounds to metric tons or something.
Was it pounds to?
What is 2.2?
2.2?
One kilogram is one pound.
Slow down.
Oh, pog car.
Pog car.
Wait, there's no...
I don't have a mirror.
All right, let's go back here.
What is over here?
Oh, get out.
What am I getting back in for?
Don't turn that back on, stupid.
All right, we have a yellow car.
It looks like it could be a little faster.
We also have a...
What is in here?
Okay, this is disgusting.
But I'm going to take the gold bar.
Like, this is just...
This is gross.
This is disgusting.
How would you miss that much?
Like, I don't know.
Are you like...
Are you sitting up here?
And then...
I don't understand how you do that.
Take the gold bar, though, for sure.
All right, what do we got in this car?
Good trunk space.
Okay, like it.
Take the gold.
Okay, what else we got?
Ooh, look at this leather interior.
We're going to change the doors out.
Ooh, nice leather seats.
This thing is shiny.
What do we got under the hood?
V6 with an injector, with a piston injection.
Really, really cool, actually.
All right, let's fill this up.
Definitely a better car.
Wait, what's inside of the weird, scary cement...
Ooh, a new door.
There's a blue door.
Who cares, though?
What is this?
Ooh, a new hood.
Put it on.
I can, but hold on.
Okay, turn the lights on.
Don't turn them off.
That hurts.
Use the new car.
I'm gonna...
What do you mean, idiot?
I'm gonna use the new car.
I want to make it look nice.
What's in here?
All right.
I don't get out of bed for more than three liters.
You know what I'm saying?
I couldn't be cool about it.
Let's just fucking waste it.
Okay, I might need this.
It's an emergency light.
How many times have you seen me go,
Whoa, I can't see anything.
All right.
What's in here?
Ooh, shit.
What's that?
No.
What's this?
Do you need any new dashboards in here?
It's so far away.
Why am I just such a fucking idiot?
It was so far away.
I'll make a sad explosion.
Wow.
I thought it was gonna be so much smaller than that.
Was it worth it?
No.
When was the last autosave?
Oh, thank God.
Thank God the game is understanding.
Holy shit.
That was awful.
I'm so...
Every emotion just happened.
What's this?
What's on her mind?
Free poster inside.
Oh, as if I get a poster.
1987 interview with the new rock star.
Yeah, I'll store it up there.
Just get me away from it.
I don't want it.
Okay, let's do some work here.
Where's the other car?
Let's bring this over here.
Use the old car back on the roof.
What is on the roof?
What is that?
What's that?
Wrong fucking way.
What?
What did I do?
Where?
How do they...
The bed.
Do I bring the bed?
Oil.
You know what I'm saying.
I don't even fucking get out of bed for more than...
Whatever.
What's this?
Rockboard?
Easel?
All right, nothing up here.
We gotta hurry this up though.
I need to fill the oil tank.
I got oil.
I got oil in this thing.
How do I smoke one of these cigarettes?
Can you?
What's the point of having this?
Use stave with the old car.
What do you mean use the old car?
This thing sucks.
This thing is gonna be faster and more efficient.
It has more storage.
Hey, but look at this.
That's stupid.
It's stupid.
It's not cool.
I can fit some of the gas tanks in here.
I'm gonna dump this whole thing.
This is gas, right?
Fellas.
Just check me out.
You can't.
You're stupid.
What do you mean no, you can't?
How much gas?
Oil?
Coolant?
Yeah, I'll be good.
You're stupid.
What the fuck?
You don't have oil.
Yes, I do.
This is gas, gas, and water.
I don't have any oil.
Okay.
I'm taking the fucking...
All right.
I'm taking all the cool stuff though.
It's too late to do this.
Get in and sleep.
Sleep in the bed.
All right.
Give me the gun.
The monsters are stupid in this game.
Okay.
Let me replace some of this shit.
I want some new...
Oh, look at that.
Wait, this was already on there.
There we go.
The nice blue, new blue one.
Nice.
Okay.
And then where's the other blue one?
Gross.
It's the new hood.
Is this the...
No, where's the blue hood?
Please take the new car.
Fuck what Chad is saying.
I can't.
I don't have any oil.
Why are my hands doing this, by the way?
I feel like I'm playing VR.
Why are my hands doing this?
All right, mount it.
I want this fucking thing.
What the hell?
Wrong door?
Well, what is going on?
Why can't I put this on?
Even if it's wrong.
Here we go.
Okay.
And then this is...
I need this door.
He's so high.
No, he's not.
He's not.
This sucks.
Can I take the bumper off?
Look at how nice this car is, though.
This is so sad.
Okay.
I need a door to...
I want this on the trunk, too.
Perfect.
All right.
That fits.
I just need a door over here.
I'm gonna eat the poop.
I want that person timed out
for at least five minutes.
There we go.
Okay.
It's a two-faced car.
All right.
What do you mean?
Like, Batman, Tommy Lee Jones.
Barbie Dent from The Dark Knight.
Which one?
Probably that one.
Probably the Tommy Lee Jones one.
Take the new engine.
Holy shit.
Oh, it's oil.
All right.
Let's go.
I got everything I needed from here.
Three doors.
Give me that fucking thing.
I might find oil later.
Take the gold, too?
Yeah, I will.
This is heavy.
Wait, what about...
Sick.
Okay.
What about...
These are all corroded and shitty.
Tires...
It doesn't matter what tire is what, right?
It's just as long as the tire exists.
This one's ugly.
All right.
This one looks pretty good.
Which one's in worse shape?
Oh, definitely front tire right.
You know what I mean?
Front tire right looks like shit.
Why am I getting minus two for that?
All right.
Take the dashboard.
Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And the steering wheel.
And everything else.
Take the speedometer.
This doesn't even fit in my car.
All right.
What if I just leave it here?
Will it still work?
Just hold it.
No, I can't.
There's a hole in the...
Oh, hold it in your hand.
All right.
Here we go.
Does it work?
No, it don't work.
It looks kind of cool over there.
All right.
Let's move.
What about the radio?
I don't want...
Who cares?
Don't move.
Did this car just stall out?
I can't take the steering wheel.
Can I?
Review mirror.
Oh, shit.
Nice.
Okay.
It looks good.
Good thing out of here.
All right.
I need to get back on the road.
Radio?
All right.
It was this way.
I forgot about the bed.
I can't put the bed anywhere.
Was it this way?
No, it was the other way, wasn't it?
No, wait.
Wrong way.
Yeah.
Hole's on the right.
Right, right, right, right.
All right.
I'll try to...
I'm going to put the bed on the roof.
Fuck.
It's too involved.
Don't turn it on.
All right.
Where's the bed?
Save.
Um, I don't know.
Whatever.
Save right there.
Why does it...
Why do I have a negative seed?
You're infertile.
Can I actually put this on the car?
I mean, people do this shit,
but I don't have any bungees.
I think it worked.
And yeah, I'll just...
This is Snoopy's house.
When I get tired,
I'm going to get out of the car,
climb up here,
lie on my back,
and fall asleep.
Still up there?
Yeah, it's on there.
All right.
Back on the road.
The emergency light.
I don't need it.
I'm fine.
I have all the nice supplies.
All right.
Hole's on the right.
Is there a horn?
H?
There is a horn.
Bed.
The bed, the bed, the bed, the bed.
Don't do anything idiotic.
Don't.
Okay.
Slow down.
I'm going to have to readjust this bed.
We've got to take the poop.
Okay.
In a different playthrough,
I would have taken every single shit I found
and put it in the front seat
until there's like 400,
just right here stacked up.
We could play highway to...
No damage at all.
Wait, what did I lose?
I lost a couple of dinner plates.
I put it back on.
What about the mirror?
I don't need it.
Rip mirror.
Click the link.
I can't right now.
When I get to another gas station,
I'll click the link.
How much gas does this car have?
I guess I can go out
and just reach my hand in
and see how far the line goes up my arm.
That's not going to help.
I can't fucking see.
Bed to bed to bed to bed to bed.
I can't see anything.
No, turn the fucking thing off.
Stop.
Do not.
Thank you.
Fuck the bed.
I need it.
I need it in about 10 seconds.
I wish I could tie it down.
Go on.
This is good.
This is the farthest I've ever been, by the way.
I've not gone further than this.
Grab it?
What did I just grab?
What the hell is this?
All right.
Where are my lights?
Why is the road so beat up right now?
Rip bed.
What do you mean rip bed?
It's still up there.
It didn't fall off.
I don't think it did.
I'm going to get hit by a rock.
I know it's going to appear.
I got to slow down.
It's not.
I don't think it's even funny anymore.
Just spam it.
No, I got to.
That's how you lose the bed.
How am I spinning?
That's how you lose the fucking bed.
Thanks.
Why did you tell me to do that?
Where's the bed?
Uh, the bed is long gone.
Go on.
Hurry up.
Buy a cactus.
What is this?
It's annoying me.
Why did I drive by?
You...
No.
How am I ever going to sleep?
All right.
I got to get the bed.
You're right.
I can't just leave it.
It took all the fucking trouble to go get it.
Where is it?
Where?
All right.
It's time to go to sleep anyways.
Get those lights off.
Leave the fucking bed, you pothead.
Why am I a pothead?
What?
Oh, wrong way.
Leave the bed, you pothead.
Okay.
Let's get in it.
Let's sleep.
Is this the wrong way?
I can't tell.
It's pitch black.
I really wish somebody could drive the car when I'm sitting here.
All right.
Don't worry.
A bed percent is still strong.
Well, let's go.
The game is neat.
Yeah, I mean, this game started as an F.
It immediately became a D because one full letter grade for a car.
I mean, it's slowly climbed up to at least a C plus somehow.
Slow down.
The FOV is fucked.
Well, it's because I'm...
Don't tell me I'm fucked up.
Don't do it.
Just let it...
Just let the car do what it wants.
Don't fight that, okay?
If I tried to fight that turn, I would have flipped over.
That would not have happened with the yellow car.
It really might have, though.
I got plenty of gas.
I got all my materials.
This car is going to make it all the way.
That's how you style kill somebody.
Just like tailwhip them.
360 no scope with a car.
Sorry.
Excuse me.
A bed car.
Make sure we're accurate here.
What is that?
What's that thing on the left?
Airfield?
Is it actually an airfield?
There are no planes in this game, is there?
Oh, it's just a weirdly popping in cactus.
Plane car bed.
Just keep stacking shit on top.
We got a building right here.
Let's see.
All right, take it.
I'm going way faster than I...
When you zoom in like that,
you don't have any idea just how fast you're fucking going.
Bed joke again.
Minus two.
I just...
Look, I just want to get it to the next safe house
so I can put it in there.
I'm not trying...
I'm not trying to be funny.
I promise.
I want to do this.
This is...
Look, this has nothing to do with me making a joke.
This has to do with me wanting something.
I just want to get it over here.
What is...
Is this like a bus stop?
All right, this is where we're going to drop the bed.
Okay, you know like in like...
Spoilers for that...
What's the Kojima game that came out and everybody...
Okay, spoiler for Death Stranding.
Okay, ready?
I have to put this bed here
because I want to leave it for another player to come and sleep on the bed.
Isn't that how that works?
I just told you I was going to...
I just told you...
I'm warning that I was going to talk about Death Stranding for a second.
Oh, it's like a fort.
That's a...
That's pretty cool.
What's this?
A toilet?
Some sort?
This is nothing...
This is nothing even here.
Whoa!
That's a new radiator.
48 water, 34 oil, 18 alcohol.
Oh, look at this piece of shit.
This thing sucks.
Coolant tank.
Oh, wow.
100% water.
Not bad.
All right, I'm going to take it with me in case I need it.
I just have so many car parts in here.
This is just hoarding but with car vehicle parts.
Like, why do I have this speedometer that I can't even use?
What's the point of having this?
I have an engine that I can't use.
I have speedometers.
I have wheels left.
I can't use any of this shit.
Is it a tower?
There ain't no tower left.
What are you talking about?
Is that...
I mean, that's where we're going right now.
The goal is to go to that weird tea tower.
What is that?
Teen Titans tower.
Oh, wait.
Are we talking about Teen Titans original or Teen Titans...
Let's eat tacos and mess around in every episode.
We don't actually do anything.
We just eat tacos, right?
You know, it's like, let's fight that enemy versus tacos.
Which version are you talking about?
You'll never get away with this, Sandler versus ice cream party.
What's the guy's name?
Slap?
What's his name?
It's not Sandler.
I know, but what's his name?
Slade.
Yes.
Slap Sandler.
Boat.
Wait, boat or Teen Titans?
There's two boats.
Teen Titans?
Okay.
I don't want to smash into a rock both ways.
This actually looks kind of interesting.
This is the most interesting thing so far, this whole playthrough.
Please stop dri...
Okay, I can't read.
Please stop driving so fast.
It's terrifying.
I'm in complete control of this vehicle.
Don't worry.
Just avoid...
Damn, what is that thing?
Does the horn wear out?
5G.
Not a 5G tower.
You're alerting the horde.
Witch!
Am I going fast?
Yeah.
All right, let's investigate.
Off.
Brake.
Done.
I'm ready to go.
Don't go anywhere.
Well, okay.
You guys ever stand up to a really tall building?
Go like this and look straight up.
You will fall backwards.
Your body, it's like an equilibrium thing.
You'll fall all the way backwards.
Don't do it.
Your door?
Wait a minute.
What is this?
Why can I turn that?
What is the point?
This is a water tank.
What?
All right, turn it off.
Turn it off?
Oh no, I'm going to be the reason why the whole town runs out of water.
Smooth open close?
Let's take a shower.
This is going to be like really fucking weird.
Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Where's my bed?
Turn this off.
There's no monsters going to be there.
I know I left it at the bus stop.
It's okay.
There's no monsters over by the water tank.
Click on the spout.
I will.
I want it to be light out.
Fill the new coolant.
I could.
Can I just do the wicked fucked up thing that I think is not funny?
No one's going to think it's funny, but I will for one second or I'll regret doing it.
Let's find out.
Holy shit, those arms.
I can't see it.
That's not funny.
It's not funny at all, actually.
It's the complete opposite.
The water is running down my head and I'm drinking it.
That's enough of that.
Turn this shit off.
What else can I do with this?
Should I wash the car?
Crouch down and mouse scroll.
Why is this happening?
I'm like a gorilla.
All right.
That's enough of that.
Let's go.
I'm going to.
This thing was cool.
Can I climb it?
Just leave it running.
You're a monster.
More, more, more.
The ladder on the other side, is there?
I'll see a ladder.
All right.
Well, that was cool.
Get out of here.
You just wasted 200 liters of water on a piss joke.
That's right.
I did.
And I would do it again, too.
You fucking kids.
Can I drink it out the window?
Wait, can I drink it out the window and piss out this window?
No, just go.
Just go.
Fuck it.
Who cares?
All right.
Now, I drove all the way in the middle of nowhere for this.
Where do I go now?
This way?
Over here?
Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
Over this way.
I think.
Coolint Omega Lull.
Go back left.
What the fuck is that?
Is that another?
Wait, there's another water tower?
Oh, shit.
There's another one.
And it's a boat.
Play X-Men Origins Resident Sleeper.
What are you talking about?
Same joke.
No, I'm not stopping.
Look, I'm just saying that there's one there.
Too fast.
Tree coming.
I can just dump the...
I can fill everything up again.
Why don't they put X-Men Origins?
Is that game any good?
No.
It's better than the movie.
All right.
Look, you only get one weird Xbox 360 request a month.
This thing is weighing the car down somehow.
Probably you're in the movies more.
I probably will eventually.
All right.
Let's get some gas.
Brake.
Okay.
How much gas is in this tank?
Turn off the headlights?
I'm fine.
Oh, my God.
We haven't even used...
We haven't even used two-tenths of a liter.
I might as well just throw a firework in here.
I might as well just shoot this.
What's the point of coming here?
All right.
We're going to blow this boat up.
I'm going to drive by and fire through there.
I'm going to get a safe distance away.
You need oil.
Oh, yeah.
Yep.
You can put the new engine in.
This is going to be such a pog moment.
I can't wait.
Wait.
Why does this engine look way cooler than this engine?
This engine...
This looks like Bowser's engine, and this is like Koopa's engine.
It's the same person kind of...
You know, the turtle.
New engine.
All right.
Let's get oil.
Oil.
Gas.
Nope.
Alcohol.
Gas and oil.
I don't think there's a barrel of oil in it.
Diesel.
Oh, shit.
That's for a big one.
Nice.
Good.
All right.
Is this engine like a three, four stroke?
What par is this engine?
I don't know anything about this shit.
Am I doing this right?
That's it.
Sounds good.
Gap this up.
Let's get it in there.
Boom.
Nice.
Can I change this coolant tank to a better coolant?
I have that, right?
Somewhere.
All right.
Wait a minute.
This one is...
This is 48% water, 38% oil, 14% alcohol.
I feel like I'm going to fuck this ratio up.
Can I bring some oil and alcohol and water over here?
Dump it.
Why?
Just water.
Oh, okay.
I got water.
Let's not use our water though.
Let's use the house's water.
Is there water in one of these?
Pee is not going to work.
R slash water.
You're going to ruin this.
Just pee.
Okay.
If pee works, I will be very surprised.
It works.
Okay.
Well, I got to drink something.
Am I not getting it in?
Why?
Wait, I'm peeing the oil out?
I need water.
Wait, there's water.
All right.
Where's the...
Wait, isn't one of these like alcohol, water, and gas?
My own filtration system.
One of these is...
Come on.
None of these...
Oh, gas, oil, and diesel.
No, that's not what I want.
Empty.
Yeah, of course it is.
Get out of here.
Gas, oil, and diesel.
Get this out of here.
Oil.
What's this?
Look at the water.
Oil, no?
Gas, no?
What's this?
Empty.
Fuck it.
I'm just going to drink the water.
What about that water tower nearby?
Yeah, well, I have to go drink and then pee into it.
I can't...
I mean, I guess we could just go do that.
Let me fill this up.
I have a water tank in here.
This one right here.
Okay.
Fill it up.
No, don't drink it.
I want to fill this.
That's all right for now.
Water, oil, and alcohol.
It's going to explode.
Where?
If I put this in here, is the car going to turn on?
Yes or no?
Yes.
I hope you're right.
I hope this engine is good.
All right.
We have a new engine and new stuff.
Oh, listen to that purr.
Oh, nice.
Wait, just sleep.
Turn the car off.
Car off.
The engine's not even on.
Okay.
What?
Go.
Still go.
Don't hit a rock.
Okay.
I'm good.
Oh, you know I have to fucking go like 80 miles per hour and sleep, right?
Like, I have to try.
Self-driving car.
Something actually moves now.
All right.
Where am I going?
Where the hell do I need to go?
The water tower?
It's so far away.
No, I don't care.
I need the road.
Get out of here.
Water tower.
I need the road.
I don't want any...
Back door.
I got it.
I'm good.
Something flew out the back.
Okay.
Here we are.
That's coming in fast.
All right.
Let's get to the spigot.
Okay.
Oh, that's just a crack in the wall.
Never mind.
All right.
Drink.
Is this death stranding iron?
I made that joke already.
Move.
Close the cap.
Oh, yeah.
I probably should close the cap.
Fill the water tank.
Yep.
Come on.
Fill.
Fill it.
All right.
Spill.
Oh, my.
Good.
Just fucking fill it.
We're out.
This is turning...
This is a legitimate pee-pee poo-poo stream.
It is not.
I'm better than that.
Come on.
All right.
From here.
Where's the road to keep progressing?
Is it left or is it right?
I think it's this way.
Right here, isn't it?
Oh, my God.
Schimpa.
Schimpa just gave another 20 community subs.
You are a madman.
Two, four, six, eight.
That's 80 community subs from Schimpa.
Do a monkey noise.
Look at that shiny hood.
Good.
Curious George?
Curious George didn't talk.
He didn't make any monkey noises.
And he just pointed stuff.
And that guy with a really, really weird fashion sense took care of him.
The guy that was going to like a Dick Tracy convention every single day.
Get.
Oh.
Okay.
I turned around though this way, right?
Is that the road?
There it is.
You said you were going to blow up the boat.
Yeah, plans changed though.
I can't believe I've been playing this game for four hours.
That's the biggest shock to me.
Watch out.
There's rocks incoming.
I don't know which way the car's going.
All right.
That did slow me down a little.
It's been four hours.
Yeah, it has a boat.
No, I don't need any materials.
I need to find a new gas station with a new awesome car.
I've been driving this piece of shit around the whole time.
Wait, what is this?
This is a little house.
Ooh, wait a minute.
Is there a car?
There's a car here.
Ooh.
What do you got in there for an engine?
Oh, shit.
What is this place?
Okay, cool.
What's this thing?
Okay, is this good?
No, that's the same engine that I had before.
Sucks.
This car is made of clay.
Pretty good room back here.
Is it gas?
No, is it?
All right.
Is there any gas in it?
It's a much nicer car, though.
Steal the dash.
Oh, shit.
You're right.
Shitty engine.
Back in business.
Look at that.
Perfect.
It's a perfect fit.
Investigate here.
Can I open these doors?
It's in an alien language.
I can't even get in here?
I can't put this shit in here.
How do I get in?
Oh, boy.
This is...
Oh, yeah.
A lot of parts in here.
What do I want to do with these?
What's this guy?
What kind of engine is this guy?
This looks like a pretty cool engine.
What do you think?
What's happening?
Gun.
What do you mean, gun?
Is there a gun?
I already have a gun.
I already have this.
I have a gun.
There's blood in here.
Why is there blood in here?
I think I want the blood.
I'm going to take the...
Wait, should I dump it out to attract the animals?
No, fuck this.
Get this out of here.
I don't want this thing.
Disgusting.
It's a better gun?
A big tire.
What's this?
What's this thing?
I don't know what any of this stuff does.
It's a microphone.
It's a better gun?
No, it's not a better gun.
Okay, but what about this engine?
These engines look...
I don't know.
Is one of them better than the other?
Let's examine them.
There's a big one over here.
Another gun.
The same gun.
Yeah, it's the same thing.
Oh, blue paint.
Yes.
It was worth coming in here.
I want to spill this.
How much paint is in here?
This is bullshit.
It's just rusted.
This car.
It's got a concrete.
Why is this car concrete?
Why am I sleeping?
It's a shotgun.
No, it's not.
Where am I?
What's going on with my body?
What's going on?
Why am I behind myself?
I do.
Cue?
Oh, shit.
Okay, there we go.
Uh, let's blow this place up.
Let's push this car over here.
Fuck this car.
Fuck the clay car.
I got a concrete car.
I'm gonna get very far away.
Don't worry.
Oh, shit.
Sit.
No, don't sit in there.
All right, so this isn't a good spot.
Take this out.
There's oil right there too.
This is gonna be a disaster.
I need to get very far away.
There it is.
Perfect angle.
Let's get in my car and let's fuck off.
Save the game.
Yep.
Good call.
Okay, this is probably far.
Is this far enough away?
I mean, it's not a nuke.
It's not a nuclear bomb.
Nice.
All right, back on the road.
Sleep in the car.
Okay.
Wrong way.
Wrong, wrong, wrong, wrong.
All right, I'll sleep on the road,
but I'll make sure the game is saved.
I'm gonna go like 150 miles per hour and then sleep.
80.
Yeah, save it.
I'm gonna save it right here.
Is there money on the ground?
All right, save.
We're in a perfect spot.
Back it up.
Here we go.
Get this to about 120.
And then I'm gonna hold V.
I actually might make it.
If it's a straight enough straightaway,
I should be fine.
We'll see.
Okay, now is a pretty good time to go to sleep.
That's efficiency right there.
Dodge the rock in my sleep.
It's the DeLorean I time traveled.
Morty!
No, it's not Morty.
It's Marty.
What's that?
What was that?
That was weird.
That was a weird thing in the road.
That was a weird thing in the road, wasn't it?
Nah, who cares?
Let's go.
Save it again.
Sure, not a bad idea.
Go to the rock.
How many kilometers have I gone so far, you think?
I've been on the same tank of gas.
I have so much gas in the backseat, too.
There's so much gas.
I haven't even used a tenth of a liter.
We only measure in miles.
Well, that's just what my brain has to do
because I grew up in the one place on earth.
They did that.
Rock in the road, rock in the road, rock in the road.
Oh, this engine can't even go past 120.
Come on, we need a better one.
Somebody said press B and it fucked up everything.
Ban that person.
The person that just said press B,
I want them timed out for 30 seconds.
It's gonna take 30 seconds to find them.
All right, we'll just pretend they got timed out.
I have to investigate this because it could be a truck.
If there's a bus or anything, it's possible.
No.
Sad, sad, sad, sad, sad.
What is it?
Sadja?
It's a J?
Sage?
How do you say it?
This is an interesting little spot right here.
Anything here?
Rolling up like this.
All right, what do you got?
Bumpa?
What do you got?
What's in there?
Gas?
Just use it.
Blood, put blood in the tank.
Oh, yeah.
Yep.
Thank God.
I can actually wash the car now.
What gold?
I don't even want it.
This is stupid.
Here's the thing I was talking about.
What is this?
There's a secret engine in here.
How do I get it?
There's an engine in there.
I'll get out.
Check this shit out.
Was it the last save?
I don't know.
I don't remember what it is.
This one here?
No, it was after.
Where is it?
Oh, it's right here.
Look at the auto save.
God damn it, I had it.
I think you can fucking trap me in there.
Don't think so.
Give me that.
Polishing concrete.
Looks pretty good.
Do you know what you think?
Better than ever, I think.
Wash the concrete away.
That's not how that works.
Too bright.
It was working?
It was working.
I can't go back for a sponge.
I've yaded it into the sun.
There'll be more sponges.
No, there won't be.
Yes, there will.
That's like sponge number 10
we've found in the game so far.
We're going to be fine.
I'm going to lose control if I don't stop.
No telephone pole.
We're fine.
No!
Back on the road.
Every sponge is personalized.
Oh, pretty good tuber voice.
I had to do it.
Not that there's a lot of people here.
I do want to make sure I let you know.
Tomorrow.
I'm not streaming tomorrow.
I'll be on Kitboga's stream.
Popping in from time to time as a guest
when he finds a good call.
I already said press B.
I just did.
I'm going to host it.
The stream will just be hosted the whole time.
Maybe I'll pop in a little bit.
Maybe we'll get a fun call going.
That's the plan.
I won't be live tomorrow on this channel.
I have to have gone pretty far, right?
What time is that stream at?
That's a really good question
because I know Kit starts streaming
around 10, 9, 10 a.m. Pacific.
Somewhere around maybe noon Eastern.
That's where he typically starts.
I'm going to assume somewhere around
10 to 12 Pacific is when I'll be on.
Maybe.
Maybe a little later.
Maybe a little earlier depending on
if he gets a call that he likes.
That's good.
This has been pretty clean so far at 130 plus.
140 now.
This is it.
It's over.
No, it's not.
Just calm down and go through the gap.
Okay, we're good.
Just let the car ride a little.
Let the car ride.
Break, break, break, break, break, break.
You're good.
Watch out for that tiny rock.
What happened?
Why did the oil come out?
I need that.
What happened?
Let's assess the damage.
Hold on.
How did I get out of there?
It slipped through the tire.
Did I lose a tire?
Hold on.
I lost a tire.
I think I did.
No, I didn't lose it.
Why is there a tire out here?
Oh, that's the spare.
Why does it look like shit?
All right, we need to.
I got to recalibrate this.
Hold on.
Right over a fucking stone.
All right, get in there.
Long ways, please.
Long ways.
Why?
Won't fit anymore?
Thank you.
You don't need the barrel?
I have to take the barrel.
The only way I feel comfortable.
Fuck the spare.
Just get it.
I don't even care.
I don't care.
Get me the fuck out of here.
Safety barrel.
My, like, gamer growth hurts so much.
Oh, there's a bunch of people that might not have been here.
You had to be there.
That's all I can say.
And really, that's really all I'm going to say.
Oh, shit.
I'm going 140.
Oh, my God.
It's okay.
But don't touch anything.
I just missed it.
Break.
Let's go.
But no.
Here's the surprising thing.
No new gas station.
You guys remember when I actually thought
that I was going to be able to fucking walk?
Thank God I actually restarted.
I would still be walking to that gas station.
And there would be, like, 1,100 people still here.
Thank God.
Why did that happen?
It just clipped.
I just clipped it.
It just got clipped a little.
I lost something.
What did I lose?
Something fell off.
I didn't lose anything.
Everything looks...
Wait.
Everything seems to be in order.
No, I didn't lose anything.
I took out my gold bar.
I lost a hubcap.
That's okay.
All right.
Slow down because the sun is unbearable.
Stop driving.
You're losing gas.
Yes, I am.
That's a big building coming up.
Finally.
Slow down.
I can't see shit.
I'd rather hit something going 30 than hit something going 80.
Just the thing you pull down.
Oh, right.
I threw it out the window.
That's a big building.
I'm doing the Ace Ventura Jim Carrey thing.
Loud as hell.
Look at that big house.
Am I okay?
I'm fine.
The car is fine.
Cool.
All right.
Nice.
Look at this big ass house.
Yes.
A bike.
I don't know how to work it.
Fuel tank.
Empty.
Gas.
All right.
Pick this shit up.
I want to get this to work.
I'm going to ride a goddamn bike.
No, please don't.
What do you mean?
No wheels.
No.
I can get wheels.
I have plenty of wheels.
Why can I not fill this?
How much gas does it need?
What's the combo?
Get gun.
Get new.
That's a new gun.
Not a new gun.
Sink.
What actually is this?
It's a trailer.
Holy shit.
Can I use it?
I hope I can actually attach this thing.
Put the bed in here.
Oh my god.
Yeah.
There are no wheels on it, but it's okay.
I think I can still probably attach it.
Stay right there.
It is that.
And then here, right?
I can't pick it up.
I can just push it.
Other way.
Damn it.
I thought that was going to be awesome.
We're going to attach?
Make a train.
I don't think I can attach this.
Press F to hold it.
Well, F. Grab the end of it.
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
And I can bring this.
I can bring the bike.
I can actually carry it.
What's happening?
Stop.
I'm going to bring this bike wherever I want.
I'm going to find wheels for it.
Excellent.
And the bed?
I don't think the bed's not going to fit on there.
This thing is too big.
What's wrong with me?
Why am I hearing bells?
I died?
What does it say?
Here?
Bed killed me.
Wait, did I?
Okay.
Shit.
All right.
Bike.
So are you sure I didn't die from dehydration?
That's not what happened, right?
Cap the thing.
Well, I can't bring the bed then.
I'm sorry.
I can't.
I want to, but I can't.
Go upstairs.
I know I'm not done exploring.
How do I get upstairs, though?
Is there a ladder?
Can I climb that?
Big money?
Oh, there was a lot of big money.
Yeah, let's take another pee break.
And I'm going to, when I come back, I'm going to do,
I'm going to go over some of these bits.
There's been like a bunch of huge ones.
I'll be right back.
Holy shit, guys.
I just realized I haven't brushed my teeth in like eight or nine days.
They're green.
Should I just take a minute to brush them or whatever?
I don't know why I thought that was like, well, that's like a funny thing I'll say.
Like, that's not even funny.
This is gross and strange.
You're just a weird guy.
It's disgusting everybody.
That's not like, oh, funny, huh?
No, it's just gross.
All right, we're back to the long road.
What was I trying to do?
Get on the roof?
I don't think I can.
Can't climb pipes.
I brushed him like, I brushed him right before the stream turned on,
like five hours ago.
I'm fine.
I'm kidding.
It was a joke.
Oh, I need this right in the back.
Kind of violent, but whatever.
I got plenty of gas.
I got my bike.
I have my trailer, but I don't, I can't, I don't think I can get up there.
Throw your teeth.
No, that's too, that's way too intimate.
Don't jump in there, stupid.
That's too like, I mean, personal.
Oh, the bits, right, right, right, yeah, yeah, sorry.
Attack of the Hank gave five community subs.
Thanks.
Board of Bones gave $50.
5,000 bits from Board of Bones.
I've been watching your videos for about seven years.
I want to give a huge thanks to all the entertainment throughout the years.
You're the best.
That's a long time.
Hope you stick around for season eight.
That's the season that everybody says to skip.
And then we had Lorag for $50.
Hey man, long time no see.
You've left a couple dozen voice bails.
But I guess they haven't been getting to you for some reason.
Ha ha.
Anyways, I just wanted to check up on you and chat.
Hope you're all doing as well as you can.
Except for Keith, he sucks.
Sorry, Keith.
Thank you, Lorag, for the 5,000 bits.
Potion Dweller, 5,000 bits.
Belated happy birthday.
Just celebrated my yesterday.
Question, have you considered doing any D&D streams with Stir and Arcadium?
I think you'd be magnificent on them.
I know your schedule tends to be a little crazy,
but you should give it a go if you can work the time up.
Well, I have something to tell you.
Star is working on a custom sorcery-style D&D-like campaign
that I'm going to be playing on stream.
He's in the middle of doing it right now.
It's going to be a choose-your-own-adventure game board.
Custom made.
I'm really looking forward to it.
It should be good.
I don't have a timetable on when it's going to be done
because he's just going to do it.
There's no like, oh, that'll be next week.
But maybe by the end of the year, early next year,
whenever he gets around to making it and doing it,
there's no rush on it.
So whenever it's ready, it should be a lot of fun.
Thanks a lot, guys, though.
Let's keep going.
Show those teeth.
No, I don't want to show you my teeth.
There's only two people in the world that are going to see my teeth.
The dentist and me.
And I hate the dentist.
Not because I don't like going to the dentist.
I don't care.
I don't like when they open your mouth really wide
and they take a look at every single inch
and they can see everything.
You can't hide shit from the dentist.
And you think that you're so clever
by brushing your teeth and flossing 20 minutes before you go.
Look, aren't they clean?
No, they're not.
They're not.
Not at all.
That doesn't do anything.
You think it does, but it doesn't.
I haven't flossed in four and a half months.
But look, I flossed.
No, there's this buildup back there.
They know what you're doing.
You're an asshole.
All right, how do I get up?
I don't think I can't get up on the roof.
I can't.
Why are you such a tool?
What?
What do you mean?
That kind of made me feel bad.
I'm sorry, dude.
Anyways.
Yeah, that kind of just like, I don't know.
That like really, they really just like threw me off.
Yeah.
All right.
Well, I'll see you guys later.
That's, I don't know.
It's like fucking with me.
You know what I mean?
Whatever.
All right.
This is still connected, right?
You need tires for the bike.
Yeah, but there's none in there.
I take it back.
See?
Oh, Raid from Tomato.
What's up, Tomato?
What's going on, everybody?
Welcome.
Thanks for the Raid, Tomato.
Hope you had a good stream, whatever you were just doing.
Welcome, Raiders.
You're witnessing a game called The Long Drive.
You may or may not have seen it before.
I am currently about 20 minutes away from the world record.
So really trying to get that world record.
Did the bike fall off?
No, stop lying to me.
What are you doing?
No, but thanks a lot, Tomato.
Hope you're doing well.
Thanks for the Raid.
Let's continue our, if you don't know Tomato, go follow him right now.
What are you, crazy?
Water tower or the pyramid?
Keep your eyes on the road.
Sing the welcome Raider song.
No, because even the welcome Raider song joke song will make them all leave.
I know it will.
Trust me.
Pay attention.
Don't, okay, I'm going too fast.
I got, I got, I got a carriage now.
I got a carriage.
I need two tires and I need a battery.
Were you guys lying about the battery or what?
Actually, it is kind of like a pyramid.
Can I go in there?
You need four tires on the bike?
No, you don't.
It's a bike.
The reason why it's called a bicycle is because it has two wheels.
And it's a sickle.
Where I have something.
I don't know.
Cycle.
Yeah, it's a, it's a, it's a two cycle.
It means it's two wheels on the bike.
What's that noise?
What does that sound?
Stop.
What's the problem?
Oh, this doesn't have wheels.
Right.
This doesn't have wheels.
Is it smoking?
No, it's fine.
It's smoking, but whatever.
Get your hand off.
What are you doing?
Get your hands off that.
Get your hand off that.
Why is he still holding it?
Why is he still holding that and shaking it around?
What's he doing?
Stop that.
Uh, who's the guy in this?
This isn't even the backseat holding a gun up to my body.
Drive.
I'm going, man.
I'm going.
That's right.
Keep going until you get to the bank.
I'm doing that.
It's okay.
The screeching is me doing that.
I can't go more than 40 miles per hour because the game's making me do this.
I can't even hit the brake.
Why won't he take his hand off the clutch?
Take your hand off.
Oh, I'm sitting in the other seat.
Okay, we're good.
Okay, there we go.
He's still doing it.
I need wheels for the bike.
There we go.
Get your hand off.
Stop touching the clutch.
Stop touching the transmission thing.
Rip the clutch out and throw it out the window.
I don't think you can.
What is this bit?
Uh, it's me driving the car.
It's the whole game, man.
That's not a clutch.
You know what I mean?
The stick that you move to drive the car.
You put it in drive.
You put it in reverse.
Uh-oh.
Gear stick.
Yeah, you get it.
All right, what do you guys want for food?
And by what do you want food?
I mean, what should I get for food in like a minute when the stream ends?
No, no McDonald's.
I'm over that for now.
Um, something's going on in the back.
Is the bike still there?
It's still there.
Mayonnaise sandwich.
No, thanks.
That doesn't sound good.
Italian food.
Mmm.
What kind of, what kind?
I mean, like pasta?
You mean like meatballs?
What do you mean?
Pizza?
Eh, I'm not into pizza right now.
Something else.
Korean food.
Mmm.
That's actually pretty, that sounds good.
Waffle house, maybe.
I'll have to think about it.
I'll get back to you later.
Kiss me on the mouth.
That's not food.
But no.
This thing is so hard to control because of the shit behind me.
Okay.
Just got a super speed boost somehow.
I just did the sonic.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
And then went forward.
Interesting.
Now I'm over 100.
Is that thing still there?
Uh, okay.
It's the, it's the little, it's the pole trailer behind me that's doing it.
Going right for that pole.
Aye.
Oh, it's just bouncing around everywhere, ain't it?
We're fine.
Get rid of it, please.
I'm still fine.
Stop getting out.
Well, I'm freaking out because I don't know if it's still there.
I will put wheels on it.
I will.
Press B to check the bike.
No, just making sure there's no shit on the seat.
Wait, can I drive from the other seat?
Can I grab the wheel from the passenger seat?
Nope.
Go inside the pyramid.
I'm kind of, I really want to ride the motorcycle so bad.
At full speed and not this bullshit pedaling with my feet thing.
I want to go full speed.
On the motorcycle.
Is that a building?
Oh God, this bullshit again.
All right.
I need to, I was trying to block the sun out of my eyes.
That's better.
Sun's gone.
Shit!
It's fine.
We're fine.
Are we?
Are we though?
Oh, watch out for that thing!
It's a pothead.
I'm not, I'm not, I've had none.
I've had none today.
I was feeling, I was feeling okay today.
Chest wise.
I didn't, I don't need to take it right now.
I'm saying that or you're going to get banned.
Idiot.
Okay, that, somebody is standing right behind here.
Crouching where the other tire is on the other side.
They scared me with a puppet and threw it behind them.
And then they're hiding under the car.
I'm going to go investigate this fucking thing and the car is going to take off.
God damn it, man.
Hey, I told you I was going to need this.
Great, I really used it well.
Let's go.
Oh, I'm not going to bring Wilson.
I need a new house.
You have a nice hall.
Please say that you'll play this again.
I don't know.
Maybe if it gets some more updates.
Isn't it currently not done?
I'm going to hit that rock, aren't I?
Nope.
Sleep?
Okay, the tank is now in the front seat.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Just draining into my mouth.
Oh, God damn it.
There's a thing right here too.
Just reload the bucket save.
I don't care.
Where is it?
This one here, right?
20, 09, 24, 16, 34.
Which one is it?
This one, right?
This one.
Reload Randy.
Well, load last.
Oh, oh shit.
Okay, we're good.
But the car turned off.
The bike is not gone.
The bike is still there.
There it is.
There's the thing.
Bike is there.
Look, that's bike.
These little bus stops.
Why can't I find a bus?
I got one in the very beginning of the game.
I didn't have any gas or any diesel.
I couldn't use it.
I want to drive a bus so bad.
You have no idea.
All right, looking for tires.
If I see a tire, I'm going to be really happy.
I see one.
I see a tire.
That's kind of huge though.
Will this work?
Can I even put it on?
This shit ain't going to work.
It's too big.
Can I paint the bike?
Oh, there we go.
Working.
Spray paint your face.
No.
Empty?
What?
I just...
A new bumper.
Definitely.
Oh, look at this thing.
This is Radio SteelPens News.
The latest news for you.
Today, it's harder than ever.
I can say, seriously, I wanted to tell you some news,
but since 90% of the people died in the apocalypse,
I can't really tell you anything.
But I can bring you some amazing ball-busting rap music.
Listen to this.
What the fuck am I doing?
Disgusting.
Why?
Let's store it in here.
This is way too loud.
We're on 98.4.
Oh no, tires.
Stop.
What?
Get it out of my hands.
Get it off my hands.
Ew.
Disgusting.
Get rid of this.
Get rid...
Put this back on.
There's more?
Oh shit, there is.
Oh my god.
Why is there so much of this?
I don't want to show that in the vlog.
This is like MIDI vlog music.
Oh, wait, wait, wait.
Vlog music, right.
Okay, hold on.
Pay attention.
The road is...
You're just watching a vlog in this slowly,
just going way off the fucking road.
It's like, whoa, dude, somebody should probably pay attention.
Where are they?
I can't crash like that.
I know you all want me to,
but it would be over at that point.
I'm not going to start over.
This is NeonSynth Radio.
Get on the road.
There is almost as hot as me, my friends.
Well, really, I am much, much...
Last week, we had a call that said...
I missed the mirror.
Don't you...
I so badly missed the mirror.
...steel pants radio, but seriously,
how can you say something like that?
I mean, that dude is a douchebag,
and he has serious personality disorders,
or bipolar, or bisexual stuff,
or I don't know.
And he even works alone because everyone hates him.
I have so much coworkers,
and he has, guess what, not NeonSynth Radio FM 98.4.
Some weather forecast for you guys.
Mostly the weather will be sunny,
just like my life and yours.
Let's make it even better with one of my favorite songs.
Jennifer, hit it.
NeonSynth Radio FM 98.4.
Jeremy, what?
More mirror jokes.
That's not...
I just can't...
I have to look.
Isn't there an animal that if it sees its reflection,
it freezes and just goes,
I need to stare at you now.
Whatever it is, that's me.
All right, new radio.
The same guys on every radio station.
There we go.
I would love to find a tire.
That would be great.
It's too loud.
Max volume.
I don't think I want to do that to you guys.
I feel like that would hurt.
Fine.
Okay, I'm gonna...
That's way too loud.
I don't like it.
Normal level.
Drive on the road.
Yeah, I know.
But isn't the road probably more dangerous
because of random rocks?
I can see the rocks from a mile away
if I drive on the other side.
Louder and floor it.
This is as fast as this little shitty engine can go.
It can't go much faster than this.
Look, you want to see?
You want to see the engine?
Look.
It's not very good.
It's pretty slow.
Hold on.
I gotta give it a little more extra cooling.
On every station.
Get out of here.
All right.
All right, if I'm going fast enough,
can this start to spray out into my mouth
and I can drink it while I'm driving?
Can I just drink this coolant while I'm driving?
If it goes fast enough?
Close the cap.
Hold on.
I got it.
It is open.
You're right.
Why do I want to do this so bad?
It's not even funny.
Okay, what...
Wait.
funny
Goddamn, what a long road trip this is.
I'm getting so fucking thirsty.
And I got no Gatorade in the car.
That's empty.
Desperate times call for desperate measures.
I can't drink it.
I'm trying.
I have to use your two-stroke vehicle urgently.
Someone, please give me a two-stroke now.
I have to go to the toilet urgently, but I only drive with a two-stroke vehicle into the toilet.
We go back here?
Do you want to be you in the backseat?
Germany is always the best.
Oh, fuck! That's a pole!
It has sand, but it also has a lot of dust.
Alright, it's you in the backseat, guys.
Yes, you have a good ear tip, panna.
Germany still has a small forest.
Are we there yet, are we there yet?
Shut up! Quiet back there!
We've got another 250 miles at least.
Here, have some drinks of gasoline.
You'll feel better.
I don't like that.
It's alright, we'll stop somewhere and get some Powerade.
The purple Powerade, my favorite.
Want to sing a car song?
Um, no.
I spy with my little eye something that is orange.
Is it the sky?
You got it!
That's my son!
He got it!
It's the sky and everything else.
You got it!
Hey, hey, stop, stop, stop!
Shh!
We got him.
We got a little bit of him.
Dad's going to get out of the car for a bit.
He's sitting right here.
Here, just put on your favorite radio.
Dad, I'll be back in a few minutes.
I'll be back.
Oh, let's just go to bed.
It's so funny with the car idling at volume 10.
This poor kid.
Oh, just do F10 for the kids cam.
Do I have four?
Okay.
Hey!
Try to keep my eye on the road, son.
Done.
Yeah.
We'll be back in a few minutes.
Just hang tight.
If you get thirsty, just bring a gasoline in the backseat.
Don't go anywhere.
Hey, son!
I found something!
This is going to look real good.
Your favorite color, blue.
You see it?
Oh, I got to be careful.
Blue's not my favorite color.
That's, son.
What happened?
Oh, I didn't hear you.
I thought you said blue's my favorite color.
Hey, your dear old dad will be right back.
And look what your dear old dad just found.
People leave this crazy shit around, son.
Yellow power rate.
What's up?
Son, we got a problem here.
Son!
Turn it on.
There's a fucking UFO.
Dad, I didn't see anything.
What are you talking about?
You didn't see the UFO fly overhead?
Dad, I didn't see anything at all.
Are you sure?
No.
There was food, I think, in that house.
Food?
What are you talking about?
Are you fucking crazy?
The UFO just flew overhead.
What are you, a dove?
I don't want to drink anymore.
I think you should stop drinking gasoline.
Gasoline is the most delicious fluid there is.
Don't move.
You won't get hurt.
Okay, we're going back on the road.
I'm going to catch that UFO.
Rabbit!
Dad, why did you do that?
What?
Hey, son.
Did you know your dad could do this?
Oh my god.
Yeah, your dad looks kind of like Beetlejuice, doesn't he?
Can you drop me off at the sound?
Is it piercing my ears?
I'm missing a tire?
What?
Wait, put this back on.
The spare.
Yeah, it's all right.
Whatever.
Is it front wheel drive?
If it's front wheel drive, then I'm just taking this off.
It's rear wheel drive.
Okay, two rear tires.
This one kind of looks messed up, though, doesn't it?
It's one of the door.
No, we're good.
All right, we just need a gas station.
Hey, doobie roller.
Thanks for the 10 community subs, doobie.
I'll take them.
It's 10 subs.
Thanks, dude.
Scooby dooby roller.
Oh, fuck, I'm hungry.
What about you?
All right, I got to make a decision here.
I'm going to say whatever.
I can stay there.
Papa John's.
Why would I eat Papa John's?
Papa John's sits in this weird sort of limbo of pizza places.
It's not that good to order.
It's not that bad to care about that you ate it.
But I don't want it.
There are much better pizza places that I would eat before Papa John's.
So I would never order it.
That's just a fact.
That's just how I feel.
I haven't you want to hear?
Here's a fact.
I have never ever in my entire life picked up the telephone and ordered a pizza from Papa John's.
There's been maybe three or four times where it was just cold sitting out at somebody's Super Bowl party.
And I had maybe one or two slices.
I've never ordered it before.
I've just eaten it maybe once at a football party game thing.
How can you judge it then?
I just don't want it.
I've had it.
Look, I just don't want it.
See, back in Massachusetts, we had Papa Gino's.
Papa Gino's was way better than Papa John's.
Papa Gino's was a thousand times better.
If you ordered Papa John's instead of Papa Gino's and you're from New England.
Oh my God.
No, you wouldn't do that.
There would be no reason for you to do that.
So now, since I've moved across country, there's no more Papa Gino's anywhere, right?
That's an East Coast kind of New England thing.
But I'm not going to order Papa John's still
because there are other places out here that are better than that.
Turn on the radio.
I am the radio.
Where are the ads?
Like the mid-roll things that Twitch decided was a great idea.
I think they deleted them.
I don't think they exist anymore.
This car is still going.
I haven't even used that much gas either.
I want B, I want B.
There you go.
Press C.
I didn't even know this existed.
It's been five hours and 20 minutes.
I didn't even know you could do this.
Good save.
I've been driving on three wheels for five hours.
No, that just happened like maybe 20 minutes ago.
We got something over here.
Yeah, I'm aware that I'm missing a wheel.
What would you like me to do about it?
Walk?
I'll get a wheel right here.
I see a wheel.
I see two wheels.
Oh, yeah.
Yes.
Take it on there.
Back in business.
Hooray.
All right, there's another one here.
Let's put it on the trailer.
Thank God.
At least I could have one.
Anything else?
What's this?
Ammo?
I don't care.
I have a thousand.
You can change it up a little bit here.
Maybe a Herman bike?
Yeah, I think so.
Cotton candy car.
Come on, do it.
I can't believe I'm still playing this though.
I really can't.
Why do I like this so much?
That didn't even go out the window.
By the way, that would have stuck to the window.
As disgusting as that sounds.
Finally, I can actually move.
That was not a house though.
That thing on the right.
It's a gas tank.
No, it's a Minecraft diamond block.
Why do I think I'm driving so erratically?
Worth a lot of fucking money.
Erotic driving?
No, erratic.
See, see, see, see.
How far back can I go?
I can't lose the Phoebe Herman bike.
I refuse.
I can see too much.
You know what I mean?
I feel like I can see way too much.
I want to ride this so bad.
All right, guys, tell me the truth.
I've got gas and I have gas and oil in here.
Can I ride this fucking bike?
If I put two wheels on this, fill it and then turn it on.
No, you need an engine for it.
What the hell?
Can I put my car engine on it?
No.
Yes.
It's not how that works.
I can though.
Why not?
Let's go.
Try it.
The next pit stop I will.
Wrong way.
No, the things are on the right.
I can't believe I'm still driving.
We've got the kid.
It's all right.
He'll put his thumb in the ear and some horror movie character will pick him up.
Oh, no, I'm out of control.
Bad view.
Look, okay, is he the main character or am I the main character?
It's really important because if he's the main character, he's going to be just fine.
An eagle will come pick him up for all that matters if he's the main character.
It's okay.
It's all right.
Just give me the...
This fucking bike is going to be the end.
I swear to God, I saw your character fly out the windshield.
Can you clip it?
Are you sure?
Did that actually happen?
Wait, you can put the car engine in it.
It's better be a one guy moment or I'm going to be very annoyed.
Give air.
Yes.
Save the game.
The moped runs on two stroke fuel as used in the Trabant with a cruising speed of approximately 50.
To start the moped, climb on by looking at the seat by pressing E.
Press I to switch the ignition.
Press space to lift the stick, hold W.
Okay.
So I need oil and gas in here.
Oil and gas in there.
Add oil and fuel.
Do we even have any oil though?
Might be in trouble here.
Okay.
Do I have oil?
I need oil.
That's water in there, isn't it?
Move this out of the way for a minute.
I need to look.
This water oil in the engine.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
How much oil?
All right.
Four?
Four percent or three percent?
Three percent.
That's it.
Okay, good.
Now I'm going to...
Can I put...
All right, hold on.
Another massive amount of fucking subs just came in.
Holy shit.
Another 20 from the chef's corner.
Thank you, chef's corner.
That's a shitload of money.
All right.
Is that good?
This isn't doing anything.
It's no engine.
Fuck.
Look down.
I know there's no engine.
I know, I know.
Okay, but cap that, please.
Get back up.
Stand it up.
Okay.
Put the car engine in it.
Did that work?
Oh, fuck.
Easy.
Careful.
I'm going to put the kickstand up.
Oh my god.
Whatever.
Just...
Why is it such a pain in the ass?
I can't put the kickstand up while it's...
God.
You motherfucker.
All right.
It's ready.
It's ready, it's ready, it's ready.
Is it going?
It still doesn't work.
It's because I'm pedaling.
It's just a bicycle.
This isn't using any gas.
I'm the energy.
Old eye.
See you later, sucker.
It's so hard to control.
It's impossible to control.
Oh, the kickstand.
No, the kickstand.
Turn it off, turn it off, turn it off, turn it off.
Is that another UFO?
Oh my fucking god damn it.
Why does this have to be like this?
Why does it have to do this?
Why can't I just sit it up?
Turn the kickstand on?
I can.
Wrong way.
Let's move.
Oh, really?
No, you can't.
Why is it two of us?
Why is it two of me?
Is it two of me?
You see that?
Why is it two of us on the bike?
Is this shit out of gas?
Stop doing that with your hand, man.
What are you...
Stop doing that.
I don't know why he's doing that.
It's overheating.
Stop doing that.
Okay, you done?
There we go.
Thank you.
Stop.
There's no radiator.
But how do you get a radiator on here?
This is not how this works.
Make the gun talk?
No.
What?
Why did you tell me to shoot the engine?
Are you out of your mind?
This sucks.
If I just piss, will it go?
I think that kind of works.
No more piss.
Oh, no.
This can't be the end.
Time to walk?
This goes faster than walking.
I can't believe there's no radiator.
How was I supposed to know that?
Reload to the car?
No, no, nope.
I can't.
I'm just going.
Don't worry.
I'll be fine.
What's wrong with this guy?
What's wrong with his body?
What did I?
Why is he doing this right now?
I think that was probably part of the problem.
I'll be honest.
I think that's why that was happening.
I really do.
John Arbuckle.
I don't think it needs a radiator.
I think that's bullshit.
It has a hole in it.
It's got plenty of fuel.
See?
No.
At least I'm not stretching anymore.
Just pedal for a while.
Wait for it to cool off.
All right.
Desperate times call for desperate measures.
No, I wanted to kick-stand it up.
It's empty.
Shit, wait.
No.
I so blew it.
I thought I could pee on it.
It's okay.
There's still a little oil in there.
Whatever.
Reload.
Reload this shit.
Reload it.
Whatever.
Wait.
Radiator.
I got it.
3%.
Bingo.
Radiator.
Give it to me.
The engine with Mountain Dew.
Blast.
Okay.
Fuck this.
I'm done.
Get the fuck out of here.
I'm taking the car.
Put it all back.
You know what?
I don't need you anymore, bike.
Wait, is there oil in there?
I could use the gas.
At least I got to ride the bike once.
No.
Smashed my dick in the car door to death.
All right.
That's it.
I'm done.
It's been about six hours.
I need to get some food.
I'm hungry and I need to get up.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
I will see you guys tomorrow.
Not on this stream.
I'll be on Kitboga's stream tomorrow.
This is a lot of fun, though.
Thanks for sticking around.
It was very, very good.
I...
Yeah, tomorrow...
I will...
You know what?
I'll probably send a tweet out or something.
I would assume.
Before I'm on the stream, I'll be like,
hey, I'm coming on.
Just so people don't have to wait around, maybe.
But it should be a lot of fun.
I'm looking forward to it.
New tweet?
That's right.
Raid, raid.
All right.
Who are we going to raid?
Who have we...
We need somebody we haven't raided.
I want a new raid.
Raid yourself.
Let's see.
Who's streaming right now?
Who's streaming that we have not raided in a long time?
You know who we have not raided in a while?
Who has shown this channel tons and tons of love over the years?
It's Boxbox.
Boxbox raids this channel all the time.
And they're awesome.
You're going to do House Flipper VR.
Let me...
Yeah, we raided Lemmy last week.
I want to try to do new raids
instead of raiding the same, like, four people every time.
Let's...
We got to branch out.
We got to raid other people.
Who's this?
Wait, Wayner?
Wayner?
All right, save that one for next time.
But I did already commit to Boxbox.
Go say hello.
They are awesome.
They're playing Team Fight Tactics.
Team Fight Tactics.
Apparently, it's a try-hard day for Boxbox.
Raid someone with, like, 10 viewers.
You know, I...
Okay.
Here's why I don't want to do that.
Because maybe if, like, they really want...
If you get, like, 10,000 people dumped on you,
it's like, okay, do I have...
Can people even hear me?
Is my mic on?
That's a heart attack, yeah.
I'd rather, like, warn somebody that that was going to happen.
7K.
Well, there was 10 earlier.
Raid quick before everybody leaves.
Oh, we got to do the credits, though.
Actually, there was a shitload of people here today.
Much more than usual, show.
Apparently, I'm having trouble talking.
I need to get some protein.
Yeah, I mean, this game is really fun.
Did I get a clean 100 kilometers?
I don't have...
I don't have to open this game ever again.
Holy shit.
All right, let's do the credits.
Thanks for watching, guys.
I'll see you guys on...
I don't know.
Tomorrow, I'll be on Kitboga.
And then maybe Saturday or Monday?
We'll see how it goes.
Keep an eye on the sus over the next couple of days.
Let's do the credits, though.
Here they go.
Load them up in alphabetical order.
These are all the subs today.
For those of you that don't know,
if you're new to the channel, you might be.
I do not read subs or most bit messages, really, at all during the stream.
I used to do all the bits at the end of a stream,
but since I had some medical problems recently,
I've canned that indefinitely and probably permanently.
So a six-hour stream is a six-hour stream.
A six-hour stream does not turn into a six-hour stream,
and then an hour and a half post stream, if I need to get up.
I do appreciate it, nonetheless.
This channel gets a ton of support,
and I still can't believe this many people care.
Seeing the amount of names that just pop up, it's...
It can be overwhelming sometimes.
So thanks a lot, everybody.
Don't change your raid commit.
No, I...
We're raiding box box.
Birthday?
Well, we'll say happy birthday.
Just say happy birthday to the...
Like, next week when we raid them.
You can do a belated happy birthday for a week later.
Within seven days, a belated birthday,
that's a happy...
That works.
That's a terrible friend.
Look, you can't keep track of every single person's birthday.
So what ends up happening is one of your friends will have a birthday,
and you'll go,
Oh, yeah, that's right.
I knew it was...
I knew it was in September, but...
No, it's all right.
It's been like four or five days.
It's okay.
Okay, now if like November rolls around and somebody said,
Hey, happy birthday, Jeremy.
I'd be like, all right, what the fuck are you doing?
It's unnecessary, man.
You might as well just say Merry Christmas, too, at that point.
Boxbox has a follower-only mode for 30 minutes.
That's perfect.
Here comes the rain!
That's kind of funny.
I committed...
I...
Look, you can't be like, let's raid this person,
and then like 10 minutes later be like,
Just kidding.
Fuck that.
No, you make a commitment, you do it.
I'll see you guys on...
Maybe Saturday?
Maybe Monday?
Saturday?
Sunday?
I don't know.
You'll see.
Thanks for watching.
Take care and go say hello to Boxbox on our behalf.
Like it.