Hey, the title sucks. Yeah, I know. I just, I don't know anything about this game.
So I don't know how to title this game. I know it's about you're in space.
You start, you look, you're searching. I don't know anything about the game.
Just searching around space. You're yearning want to, I don't know, whatever it's staying. I don't care.
Uh, I know that, I know that this is a very spoiler filled video game.
So I'm going to do my best to not pay attention to chat. It's gonna be really hard for me to do that.
And we'll be talking to pre stream chat about how, oh dude, just put it in sub only.
Well, um, I'm not sure that's going to do very much considering that almost all of you
at this point are subscribed to the channel. Uh, there's almost 11,000 subs on this channel.
So all I would do would be flipping a switch that doesn't have a light bulb plugged in.
Maybe that's it. Let's, let's, let's turn the lights on for this one.
Oh, there's no bulb in there, but I flipped the switch.
So we're just going to let it, we're going to let it ride. Let it ride. Uh, I'm going to try to not
look too far into what people are saying. I'm going to just, I did a wink.
Good. I can see that. I can actually see a real one. All right. Uh, $50 from five.
Can we, okay. I'm going to rename you phylactery 50. Phylactery 50 is your new name because you
give $50 or more every single stream. You are, you've got, you've got money to spend
and I cannot believe you still give this much money. It's unbelievable. I can't believe it.
Thank you phylactery lich for the 5,000 bits. I'm actually going to get my, uh,
my better dashboard here. Uh, this is the way to play outer wilds today. I was going to do
Tony Hawk's underground, but, uh, we're going to have to move Tony Hawk's underground because I
needed an official Xbox 360 hard drive. It's been ordered. It just, you can't get it anywhere. I
can't get anywhere in real life. So I have to buy it online. So it's got a ship that we're going
to do that at the end of the week. I actually have a full plan for the rest of this week.
If you believe it, but phylactery, uh, said with his 5,000 bit donations. Hey,
Jerma played the DLC for a service wrath or I'll eat a delicious Caesar salad. Good stream last
night. Hope you enjoyed the game. Yeah, that's the plan. That's in the plan. You guys ready
for the plan? Here is the plan today. Outer wilds. No, not outer worlds, outer wilds.
This is a different game than the one you think it is. Maybe tomorrow outer wilds. Uh,
this game is apparently what 10, 12 hours long. We could probably split this into two, like six,
seven hour streams, something like that after that. So that's today and tomorrow for you,
it's going to be 20. Well, we'll see if we can do it in two, but today and tomorrow,
out of wilds, Friday, Tony Hawk's underground. I'll have the hard drive by then Tony Hawk's
underground. It can be done in one stream. I'm certain of it. Cause I remember playing it
Saturday Diablo to hardcore. Going after Diablo with our skeleton necromancer,
depending on how long that stream goes, possibly a sir's wrath DLC.
Now I also want to address this as well. Uh, the get well card I'd like to experience by myself.
I looked into it a little bit and that's something that I don't think I would like to stream.
I want to experience it on my own. Uh, it seems a little personal for me, so I definitely want to
over the next few nights do it on my own. Thank you everybody that's contributed. I'm not just
saying this. I'm actually going to go through every single slide over the next three or four
nights. So thank you again, but I do want to experience it on my own. The what a ton of
people contributed to a get well card for me, which is insane because I've had been having
some stupid, annoying, uh, medical problems with some rib cage bullshit and people are nice enough
to want to come together and do that. So thank you all of you. I will be experiencing it over
the next few nights. Uh, we had another $50 come in right now. 5,000 bits from AB Joe,
5,000 from phylactery, 5,000 from AB Joe. I always thought that the German Merc was wearing a scarf
or something. After looking at it on mobile, he just has a really weird chin. Well, it's Mercury.
It's just Thanos, but that's the plan for the remainder of the week. Should be some interesting
stuff here. I have not, I've outer wilds is one of those games. Remember we're,
we're fulfilling our quota on this stream of, I'm playing a game that came out within the last year.
We have to fulfill that quote. I've got to play at least one recent game for every 10 old games.
You know, another link just come in. We're going to start to see a lot more of these
play devil may cry five. Oh fuck sake. I probably will, but we're going to do outer wilds. Let's
just move on to it. Let's go. I'm ready to go. Hopefully you're ready to go. Hopefully you've
got like a snack or something or something out of wilds. Now I got to remake sure I read it. I'm
going to re re re re iterate this again. I, I'm just going to kind of experience this game. I'm
not going to be paying too much attention to chat because I've been told, um, I can spoil
like the last season of this show in one sentence, right? So like, I got to be careful and please,
we're not going to do sub only, but just know that, you know, if you, if you, you know,
you drop a fucking spoiler line here, you're out, you're gone. Like you're gone. You're out.
So we're, uh, I can't, I'm not going to put it in emote only. Don't ignore me.
Another wink come in? No. Wait, what? No, only what? Yeah. Another one just came in. What the
fuck? I'm just going to keep this up for a minute because I feel like we're going to get like a
shitload of these. Another one. No, I got, I actually have it up on my dashboard. I can see
when they're fake. Let's get started. Uh, I've been told that this is one of the best games of the
year from last year. I'm curious. I want to know why I'm playing with the controller, by the way,
I've heard the music's good. I've heard the game is good. I heard it's really fun. Really interesting
outer wilds. Are we ready? You're in normie normie loading. This is weird.
This game needs a controller to be good. Uh, I got one in my hands right now.
Wake up. Is it, is it FPS? Oh, it is FPS. Talk to slate. Roast a marshmallow. We're doing that
first. Oh, God damn it. I've ruined it. Although you got to go all in. Yeah. Oops. If you end up
lighting it on fire, you got to go all in and then you, you pull the charcoal mess off the top and
you eat it. No, I wanted to eat it. Why am I so bad at this? I get so obsessive compulsive when
it comes to roasting marshmallows. Every single centimeter of this whole thing has to be a golden
brown or you go all in and you burn the fuck out of it. It lights on fire. And then like I said,
you peel it off like that. You let it burn, blow it out, pull off the weird exoskeleton that's on
it, eat the exoskeleton and suck on the fucking juices inside. All right. That was good. Let's go
There's already more gameplay than yesterday's stream. There's our pilot back from your pre-launch
campout under the stars I see. So it's launch day. It seems like only yesterday you joined the space
program and suddenly here you are leaving on your first solo voyage. What do you say? Ready to get
this beauty off the ground? It's all fueled up and ready to go. Uh, you sure you fixed the retro
rockets? That was only a problem one time and then maybe a few times after that. But hey, no reason
to dwell on the past, right? Anyway, you'll need to get the launch codes from Hornfels at the
observatory before you can lift off. Just bring those here once you said your goodbyes or whatever.
Right to the point. I like it. Launch codes from Hornfels. Okay. Requires launch codes. Oh shit.
Uh, can I have a jump, a hold and release? That's kind of weird. Holy shit.
Fly model ship? Wait a minute. Hold on. Hey. Hey, it's you. Slate said you're blasting off
on your ship today. I'm really excited to see the launch. Aren't you going to go into space?
Aren't you? You better not have changed your mind. Uh, I want to practice before I leave. Oh, you're
just saying that. But if you really want to practice, I guess I could help you. I need,
I can learn how to fly. Try to land on one of the geyser pools. Show me what you got.
Am I in it? I'm in this? Okay. That's not as easy as I thought it was going to be.
How do I drive it? How do you fly? Up, down thrust, horizontal thrust. Guys, I'm not,
I don't think I can do this. Horizontal, like you go forward. It's going, it's like doing way too
much thrust. You know what I'm saying? It's going like a, it's going too fast. It's less than four
buttons, Jerma. I, okay. How do you turn? Okay. I'm serious. I don't understand this. You're
thrusting too fast. It's, it's, is it pressure sensitive? I mean, I'm holding it down kind of.
Was I not supposed to do that? And then the geyser. Is it my Xbox controller that's doing
it so much? It's like, I'm trying not to do too much pressure, but my Xbox one control is
a lot like blowing it out. I did it. I did it. Okay. That's I'm done, right? Leave. Okay. No,
I got it. I guess I, I guess I kind of understand. Wow. That was just like the time the external
fuel tanks exploded on reentry. You'll be okay flying the big one, right? I hope so.
I don't know. You tell me. What is this? It's Corfi. Hey yo, Hatchling. I hear you're leaving
us to seek adventure amongst the stars. When you return, let's you, me, and Gawson open up a bottle
of that good stuff. I'm only seeking adventure amongst one star. Actually other stars are too
far away. Good stuff is less delicious sap wine and more daunting digestive challenge.
That's pretty funny. That looks like you. No, this, this guy looks like, you know, those images
that hurt your head when you put two eyes underneath somebody like you have humans eyes
and it's like that weird image where they have four eyes and it hurts your head looking at it.
That's what I see. An iron stomach is the mark of a true Parthian, my friend, our hardy hunter
gatherer lifestyle stem from the trial and error of which I mean our ancestors survived eating a
lot of bad things. All right, let's go. Where's my ship? There's a lot of people. You're actually
blasting off in that thing, huh? I told my odds of survival is statistically quite high.
Yeah, the space program certainly come a long way. I should probably thank you for causing fewer
flash fires than your predecessors. By the way, good luck with those retro rockets.
All right, for a second, I thought that was a something bad happening.
Outer Wilds adventures presents postcards from orbit. Use satellite camera. This projector is
linked to our sky shutter satellite, which is currently orbiting timber hearth. The satellite
is equipped with two onboard cameras. See if you can take a snapshot of our village.
Where's the village? Oh, there's a geyser, right? Am I doing this wrong? All right,
there's a village right here, right? That's us. All right, cool. I got it. That's cool. All right,
moving on. What do you sell maps? Marl. So it's launch day. How's going to miss you? Speaking of
launch day, I was thinking about it in the platform. Those ships launched from is getting old.
Isn't it about time you built a new, less flammable one? That big tree in the village
would be perfect choice. I wouldn't mind helping the space program. Just say the word. Launch pad
is flammable? Ah, you didn't realize that. Don't worry. It's held up for the launches so far. It'll
definitely be fine for yours probably. Oh, it's the guy with the guitar. Hello there, space cadet. I
hear you're leaving the crater today. If you meet any of the other travelers up there, remind them
to take proper care of their instruments, won't you? What are the instruments? Oh, sure. I made
all their instruments, you know. Let me see. There's church drums, Rybex banjo, and Gabro's
flute. And Feldspar's harmonica, of course. Though Feldspar's been missing for a long time. Sometimes
it feels like yesterday they were playing their harmonica around the campfire. Anyway, you hear
music in space. That'll be one of the space program's other travelers. If you feel like
company, you can always pull out your signal scope and track them down. All right, let's get those
launch codes. So many people to talk to. What are you guys listening to? Hello, astronaut. If it
isn't my favorite troublemaker, what's with the radio? We wanted to play hide and seek, but
Moiraine won't let us borrow their signal scope because it's really delicate and I'm not supposed
to be thrown around like that. Hey, can we use your signal scope? Can we? Can we please? Sure,
let's play. Well, okay. Here it's like a tutorial. Galena and me will hide with these radios and you
will use your signal scope to find us. Last one to be found wins. Okay, close your eyes.
I'm gonna open up. My money's gonna be gone. All right. Frequency. Change frequency. Zoom in.
Unknown. Isn't this the person playing the guitar? No, it's up there. How do I get up there?
Shoot and add an NPC. I don't think so. Is this game dark? It's like the darks are too dark and
the lights aren't light enough for my screen. I don't know why. All right. Can I get up there?
Jump. All right. Found you. Got you. You found me. I did. Now, where's the other one? I get how this
works. Is there fall damage or anything? No. Up and down in here and then go. Can I die?
Where are you? Like under the waterfall? I don't understand. Not there apparently. No. It's gonna
be up here. Oh, there you are. This shit is dark. You got me, but I'm the last one. I win.
I promise you'll play a game when you get back to the space. Okay, gotta go.
Me too. Let's get those coats. Should I or is it just this kind of personal area that's dark?
Don't. Okay. All right. What the hell was that? Use camera. There's so many gadgets.
What are all these gadgets? What was that? Hi, astronaut. You know the patch of ghost matter
inside this fence? Ghosts said it used to be bigger when they were hatchets because ghost
matter evaporates. It just takes a super long time to go away. There's still ghost matter in
the village when I'm grown up. Ghost matter is awesome. You shouldn't be throwing rocks in there.
It's dangerous. Obviously, that's what makes it so awesome. Geez, I'm not dumb enough to touch it.
Oh, you're such a grown up. Yes, I am. I don't throw rocks and stuff. I saw smoke coming from
Young Bark Crater up north and figured I should go check it out. You can use the scout launcher.
Just please don't break it while I'm gone. Scout launcher, launch scout. What the fuck is going on?
Okay, so I get a fire. This is a cannon camera. Oh, it's still flying. Oh, shit.
All right. Get it back. I want to see what I look like. Hold on. What do I look like?
That's me, right? No, that's cool. Where are those coats? Gotta go to the observatory. Birds
fly. Sun shines. All right. This way. Why does this remind me of Firewatch?
The walking with the acoustic guitar in the background is just... I'm waiting for the radio
to come up. All right. I'm going the wrong way. Big bits just came in. Oh, shit. They did.
You're right. Hold on. I just missed it. All right. Here we go. Whoa. Dude, it's bright. It's
really bright now. Oh, because the sun is coming up. All right. Now I get it. I get it. All right.
Yeah. Sun. Sunshine. All right. Hold on. Parfale Mule gave 5044 bits. Thank you, Parfale Mule.
50 bucks. This might be the only time I ever donate so many bits at once since I can by no
means afford it often. Don't ever give me money if you can't afford it for any reason.
Like, if you give this channel money, make sure you can afford it 100 times
before you even think to do it once. But very important. That's very important. But this is
my absolute favorite game of recent years, and I'm so excited and happy that my favorite internet
man has given it a chance. Hope you and Chad enjoy this masterpiece. Heard it's very good.
I've heard it's very, very good. Read that stuff. Read the... Oh, I'm not supposed to be looking
at Chad. All right. I'm not going to look at Chad. I'm not going to look at Chad. I'm not supposed
to be looking at you guys. Stars like our sun generate light and heat by fusing hydrogen into
helium. It's boring. As it grows older, the star runs out of hydrogen, starts to contract.
As the star's core contracts, it gets hotter, causing the outer layers to expand. The star has
become a red giant. When the core is hot enough, it starts to fuse the helium into carbon.
Man, I'm not going to lie, when I first passed this, I thought these were fruits. I thought it
was like apple, peach, nectarine. I didn't realize it. Like, when I walked by them and I glanced over,
I was like, oh, those are pretty good nectarines. If a star is massive enough, it will continue to
fuse carbon into even heavy elements like iron. Ultimately, the star will collapse under its own
gravity and then explode in a violent event called a supernova. Based on Chad's observations, this
will one day be the fate of our own sun. Manka. Fucking. S. Right, guys? This anglerfish specimen
was found attached to the landing gear of one of our ships that flew close to dark ramble.
It appears well suited to living in dark places with minimal atmosphere.
What's this? This crystal was taken from a Nomai ruin on Brittle Hollow. It seems to create a
local gravity distortion and was most likely used to traverse steep surfaces. Try it out.
Look. Get me out. Get me off. Get me off. Get me off. I'm gonna throw up.
If I had stood on that platform for another 10 seconds, I would have had to turn the stream off.
Well, I'm not. I'm serious. I'm dead serious. What you see here are parts of the Nomai skeleton.
We can, I'm sorry, I just bumped you in the face. We can tell from their skulls that they possess
antlers and quite usually, unusually only three eyes. The Nomai body was likely adapted for living
exclusively on land. The differences in the Nomai's anatomy, such as their shockingly fragile bones,
show us that Artheans couldn't have descended from Nomean ancestors. It's not clear where the
Nomai originated from or why they disappeared. We hope to find more clues to this puzzle
as we explore our solar system. Nice. This is a little museum. The sofa, chair or something,
or like a vase. Aside from the dwellings and structures they built, the Nomai also made art.
This decorated pottery was discovered on Brittle Hollow. Some ancient Nomai art depicts strange
animals, foreign celestial objects and other subjects that can't be found in our solar system,
which makes us wonder whether the Nomai originated elsewhere in the universe or simply had vibrant
imaginations. Were the Nomai born in our solar system or were they born among other stars and
planets? If they were, how and why did they come here? All this and more on this episode of NPR.
These are just some of the questions we hope to answer through further
Xeno-Archaeological Expeditions. Bowling balls. All right, pretty cool. I got all this info.
This is a face. This remarkably intact statue was carved by the Nomai, an ancient species who
dwelled in our solar system thousands of years ago. We keep touching on the Nomai here. The
statue provides us with our most detailed look yet at the Nomai, who appear to have been covered
with a layer of fur. Note the decorative jewelry that has been carved as part of the antlers.
Although their artifacts and structures have been found on almost every planet
in the solar system, we still have no idea where the species came from or what happened to them.
So this is kind of like Mayan history like we have now where it's like look, this is civilization and
they did all this stuff, they made all these things, but we don't know what happened to them.
Hey, it's my favorite streamer! Launch day at last, huh buddy? It's the translator of
TOOL's inaugural flight too. I'm so excited. It's making me nauseous. Just think, you'll be
able to translate any Nomai text you want anywhere you are. The two of us put a lot of hours into
inventing that tool, so don't break it, okay? Haha, oh geez. Haha, oh god, do not break it.
Uh, ignore me, okay? I'm just nervous and I'm not even the one going into space. How are you feeling?
I'm good, I feel good. Good, you've only been waiting for this day since we were hatchlings.
I can't wait to see all your training pay off. So what's the dirt? You're here to see the new
Nomai statue? Yeah, I knew you'd want to see before you headed off. Hornfell's just finished
prepping it for display today. Amazing, isn't it? Makes me wish we could see what a real,
live Nomai looks like. But I guess this is as close as we'll ever get. Check it out,
looks like they had fur. Fur is weird. It's the first fully intact statue ever found, you know.
And for how old it is, it's in great shape. Ah geez, I got a little carried away there. Go on,
you have a ship to launch. Take care of yourself out there. Crew? So we're aliens, okay? All right.
Outer Wilds Ventures founding members. Clockwise from top left. Hornfell's,
Gawson, Slate, and Feldspar. Which one am I? Who am I? Am I my Esker? Hmm, what's that?
Outer Wilds Ventures Timber Hearth's first and only space program was founded to explore the
farthest reaches of our solar system. Feldspar was the first Arthian to be internationally,
intentionally launched into space. It completed the first orbit around Timber Hearth and later
made the first of what would be many landings on our moon, the Atoll Rock. Okay, nice. What's this?
This piece of Nomai writing was essential to deciphering their unique language.
Although this text is linear, Nomai text often branches off from a central point.
Interestingly, each branch tends to be written by a different author. Oh dude, that's fucking
pretty cool. That's actually really cool. From center out? That's pretty cool. All right,
untranslated writing. We're nearly ready. Felix and I have finished construction and
she says calibrating the device won't take long. What about that one? Oh wait, there's more.
Fortunately, the Atoll Rock's lack of atmosphere will make calibration simple. After all, this time
I'm thrilled to finally resume our search. What about that one? A Calab. All right, let's get those codes.
All right, you are here.
Giants Deep Timber Hearth Brittle Hollow. Okay, let's go. All right, give me those codes.
There you are. I just finished pre-flight observations and local conditions are good.
Time to get our newest astronaut off the ground. He'll be our first astronaut ever equipped with
a Nomai translator tool. I confess I've been giddy all day just thinking about it. We're better
equipped than ever to unravel the mysteries of the Nomai. You and Hal should be very proud of your
work. Tell me, what's your plan once you're in space? Uh, I think I'm gonna start with something
small. That's a sensible plan. More sensible than most of our astronauts tend to be and that's a
fact. You think you'll go to the Atoll Rock then? Our moon would be a safe place to travel and to
get your bearings in space and I'm sure Esker would appreciate the visit. Plus, we don't know
what the ancient Nomai ruins on the moon are or why they were built. You could put your new translator
tool to... All right, yeah, that sounds simple. Fly, right? I want to fly into the sun. Okay,
uh, yeah, man. Um, there ain't no translating text on the sun. Uh, you die if you go near it. Uh,
but we'll make sure we start training the other hatchlings to replace you real soon. Take a few
photos. Don't worry. I plan on taking at least three photos and then opening the window and
whipping the phone out and then one day somebody will find it. It's actually pretty interesting.
I got the idea because I found a cell phone flying around in space. There was a picture
of this planet with these giant fucking tentacles coming out of it. It's the new message in a bottle,
man. Get with it. Excellent. You'll be needing the launch codes. Here they are. Okay. Launch codes.
Dash dash dash dot dot dash dot. I don't know what that says. That's amazing lore enrichment.
Wait, hold on. What is this? Magic rock. This strange rock moving around in this grotto appears
to react to conscious observation. The level headed among us realized there must be some sort
of optical illusion in play, but Gabriel claims the rock exists in all possible states until it
is observed. Whatever is actually happening. Both sides of the debate agree the effect of
extremely creepy. I get it. That's pretty weird. Okay. Low IQ astronaut. You made it out of that
rock. Okay. I want to make a game of thrones reference so bad, but I can't. Did you let him
touch you? Did he touch you? What the hell was that? It just absorbed everything I did.
Do it. No, I can't do it. All right. That was weird. Big thanks to these additional funding
members of Outer Wilds Ventures without whom we would never have gotten off the ground.
Matthew Steinhauer, Ben Etherington, Qwerty YouUpThePie, Jordan Frith, these kickstarter
people, Patreon subs, Tom Cummings, Sean Shark Templar Farrell, Steven Ursul Ryan Omrecker.
All right. Thanks guys. These are actual patrons of the kickstarter. That's pretty cool. That's a
neat little place to put it. All right. I got the codes. Hey, did you get a good look at the
Nomai statue? The statue was glowing. Why was it glowing? Whoa, whoa, whoa. The statue was doing
what? So it's eyes open and you saw images from your own memories and glowing lights flying around.
You mean like a hallucination? Listen, no offense, but are you sure you're okay to launch like
medically speaking? No, that statue is definitely weird. And if you're saying it happened, then I
guess maybe it did. But why? Wernfeld tried everything to get that statue's eyes to open
and nothing like this ever happened to them. I don't think you're going to get any answers from
the museum statue, but Gabbro said they were going back to Giants Deep. I don't know which
island they're on though. Maybe they'd be able to tell you more. On the other hand, Gabbro is,
you know, Gabbro. So maybe you'd be able to even search for info on your own. He's a
fucking, you know, he's a dick. Geez, now I'm really jealous you're going into space. Hey,
see if you can use our translator tool to find out more about the statue. Okay.
Good luck. Is that a carrot? Oh, it's a stick.
It was a lot faster getting back here, guys. Come on. What do you mean it was not? Oh,
he's got the launch codes. Okay. Yes. I'm going to refill my health. Can I just eat them?
Here we go. Enter launch codes. All right. I was going to say this is not going to like
Charlie and the Chocolate Factory, right? Let's go. What do I do? View ship log. View entry,
Timber Hearth. Rumor mode? Village. View rumored entry. I hear there are Nomai ruins somewhere in
the Attlerock. Oh, okay. So you get to. Sounds like Esker's still stationed at the Attlerock.
They've been there by themselves for a while. All right. Let's go. I'm going to the moon.
Suit up. Little scout. See beyond the horizon. Illuminate dark areas. Detect hazards. Test the
environment. Health and full fuel. All right. Let's, let's go. How do I close the door? All
right. Buckle up. Lift off. Landing camera. Lift off. Am I in space? Holy shit. This is crazy.
All right. Wait, what's that? I need to find the moon. Where's the planet I just came from?
Where's the planet I just came from? Right there, right? All right. I need to go to Attlerock.
Is that Attlerock? Brittle Hollow. No, I need Attlerock. I want to go to the moon first. They
said that was the easy one. Giant Steep. No. Ember. Right there. Brittle Hollow. No. Use the map.
You are here. The interloper. What is that? All right. We need Attlerock. There it is. Okay.
Lock on. Let's go. Engage autopilot. Match velocity. How fast am I? Wait, it's right there.
It's right there. Okay. Slow down. All right. So I'm going to do autopilot. Engage autopilot.
I'm bigger than this planet is. Match velocity. All right. Slow down. Slow down. Slow down. Where's
my miles per hour? I got to get picked up by the gravity. How do I get in here? Landing mode. What
the fuck is happening? Is this right? This is the camera on the bottom, right? I'm not driving
straight into this, am I? No, I got it. Let's go. All right. Nice. All right. I made it. Do I have
all my tools? Hold on. Where are my tools? Equip scout launcher. Give the signal scope. No, no,
no. Put it away. All right. Unbuckle. Let's go. I have my suit on. Where's the hat? All right.
Flashlight. Holy shit. I can... All right. All right. I need to find... What am I looking for?
I'm trying to find the base of operations. This is my ship. How do I equip my trans translator?
What's going on? What's wrong with me? My god. We're turning upside down. We're going upside down.
We're upside down. I don't like this. Okay. I need to find writing and some clues. Isn't there a
base here? Oh, this is Mario Galaxy, but the whole world does it. Not just one planet. Get out of
there. Get out of there. Let me get out of here. What is that thing? What is that? Run. What do you
mean run? It's the sun. What the hell is that? Oh, no. Someone's playing a harmonica. No, no.
That's my friend. It's a friend. Where are you? Wait, what is that? That's another planet.
This people is playing musical instruments. Hide and seek? Is there nothing on this planet?
Jump to the other planet? Holy shit. I made it. Oh, we reviewed the logs.
Uh, I don't think, uh, I don't think he should have been the one on that case.
He tried to jump from a moon to a planet. Probably wasn't the smartest thing. Wait, what?
Atmospheric. Wait, am I? Hey, you ready to get this thing off the ground? Ship's all
fueled and ready to go. Did I just die? Oh, bad dream or something. You still look half asleep,
but that's a negative on being deceased. I know it's tradition to sleep out under the stars at
night before I launched. But if you ask me, it makes you a little jumpy. Did I not like that?
Okay. Uh, I have the codes. I do? Oh, I do. Oh, hold up. You're going to want to get the launch
codes from the observatory. I already got them. Must be inhaling more fumes than I realized. That
stuff is potent. Oh, if you get the codes, I'm not going to stop you. Good luck and take care
of that ship. Uh, you're huffing paint. This is the ship. Okay. All right. I'm go back to the moon.
I'm not jumping from planet to planet this time. Suit up. Okay. I got full fuel. Well, let's go.
Lift off camera. Okay. Now I get that LB hold to roll. You can actually do a full roll.
All right. Don't do that anymore. That's going to actually make me sick. All right. Let's go back
there. What the hell? I don't even understand what I did. Let's lock on. Oh my God. Pull up,
pull up, pull up. That was almost a disaster. Okay. Let's go. Same deal, except I just like
shit on here. I have to do. What was the, what was the thing? I got to look at my log and slow down,
slow down, slow down, slow down. How fast am I going? I can't tell. I'm going kind of fast.
Yep. Right there. Let's see. There is something on here. I knew it. Landing mode. Jesus. We good.
Am I landed? We're good, right? All right. Let's go. All right. Let me see. What does this say?
Here we go. Room with entry. Hey, there are no, my ruins on the adult rock. Okay. I saw them. Let's
go. We're here. Don't go so fast. Jesus. I'm going to get killed. It's up here. You have plenty of
fuel, right? So let's land here. Right here. All right. Found them. These are the ruins, right?
Yeah. These look like ruins to me. Hold down A. All right. Come on. Pull this away. What the
fuck is going on? What the hell's going on? What's going on? This is going to, I'm going to get
hit by this. What is this doing? Uh, I go in. I'm going in. I broke it. How did I break it? Wait,
there's, there's writing. Too close. All right. Untranslated. Holy. I was upstairs testing the
eye signal locator and it can hear and follow the signals from the sun. Giants deep and brittle
hollow. Hold on. Let me go get Otto. I don't want to come in the room. Perfect. I can hear him
yelling at me. It's like, Hey, open this door right now. Yeah. I just really happened. No,
no. He just wanted to come in the room. He gets really annoyed if you, if he's not hanging out
in the room with you. If he's not in the room with me, he'll just be like, um, excuse me.
What the fuck am I not doing in there? And I'm like, yeah, you're right. Get in here.
My special boy. All right. What does it say? I was upstairs testing the eye signal locator
and it can, and it can hear and follow the signals from the sun. What else you got?
Oh, for something strange is happening. When I asked the eye signal locator to follow the
eye signal, the devices indicator rotates wildly and never points to just one direction.
This is a curious result. It's possible the eye has stopped calling out its signal.
I see. I most likely calibrated the locator incorrectly private. My apprentice and I will
make adjustments and try again and update. Disappointingly, everything is correctly
calibrated after all. It saddens me to post it. This post this my friends, but I believe we need
to build a more sophisticated device. If we want to find the exact location of the eye of the
universe, then we will build it. Don't lose hope. Our search for the eye is what brought our clan
to this place. We won't give up so easily. Freeze detected. Oxygen tank refill. Oh, wait.
Oh, I have oxygen, right. They're looking for the eye of the universe. What's this? Okay. Wow.
Wow. I've seen this route in other travelers pictures, but seeing it for myself,
it's really old, isn't it? But wow, this is the coolest day of my life. Okay. Um,
time for some official notes. This is some kind of, uh, know my locator and point out the different
planets, which is incredibly cool by the way. But from what little I can understand of the writing
here, I think it was built to try to find something specific. I'm not sure. I also
was able to translate something about the South pole of brittle hollow. So I'll fly there to see
if I can learn more South pole of brittle hollow. Yup. Just going to get back in the old ship and
take off. Totally safe. Mostly stay safe. Oh, stars above. Okay. What's this scroll? What does this
do? Put it in here. Where should this new, more sophisticated locator be built? It may need to
be larger than this eye signal locator. The Southern glacier on brittle hollow has some
available space. I could construct a new building to house this proposed locator. Yes. Let's build
there. I imagine our young friend Connolly would enjoy that immensely. He's always held a great
interest in the eyes, especially for a child born so long after the crash. I'll begin construction
on brittle hollow South pole immediately. And Nana and those of us originally stranded on the
ember twin built a quantum moon locator there. The heat of the sun made its construction
challenging. I wouldn't recommend building on that planet. Okay. Don't go to the ember twin.
Don't. Okay. Brittle hollow South pole. Is there any more? What's this thing? What's that? What's
this? What's this thing? What does that do? Build the oxygen. All right. You touch a tree,
you get oxygen. That makes sense. All right. Let's go to the brittle hollow. Anything else I can do
stand in the middle and scream. All right. You can't get killed by these things. That's good.
Where's my ship? Why can I hear of somebody playing a flute? That's the ruins they were
talking about. Is there anything else here? I don't jump off the edge like a idiot. Like I
did last time. Chip is down there. I want it to be sun. All right. Bring the sun up here.
Is that here? Where is that? Oh, that's on that planet. Okay. That's on this planet. There's no
noise. There's no noise or anything on this one. Hey, jump to that planet. You could make it.
Oxygen. Do I have plenty? Is there anything else to see here? I do appreciate that little mini map
over there because it shows the trail, the drunk ant trail that I've made. So at least I know where
I've been. This is the ship. Don't die. Don't die. Don't die. Don't die. I'm just free falling right
now. Don't die. Don't die. Don't die. Don't die. Don't die. Don't die. All right. Hold on.
I don't think these little glaciers, these look really cool. What is that? Oh, okay. Hold on.
Land on that. Oh, land on the Smash Brothers stage. Come on. I can do it. What is this?
Esker's signalscope log. Day 48. Still not picking up Rybeck's banjo from Brittle Hollow. Sure,
they're fine, but I'll feel better once I can hear their music. Day 51. Listen to Chert play for a
while. Unrelated. Someone should tell Porphy and Gosan their flirting is not suitable for an aerial
perspective. Banjo music coming in loud and clear today. Sounds like Rybeck's doing okay. That...
Oh, I was worried. A week later. Today I thought I heard something strange. I don't know. It was
probably nothing. No, it's back again today too. Something strange is coming from Timber Hearth.
Okay, I know this is crazy, but the sound from Timber Hearth sounds exactly like Feldspar's
harmonica, but Feldspar disappeared in space ages ago. It can't be them. It's still here. This is
creepy. Maybe my signalscope is broken. I better talk to Nice. There it is. Right there. What is
that? It's like an asteroid. All right, I want to go there. Anything else over here? Jesus. I'm almost
out of oxygen. I need a tree. Unidentified signal nearby. Three minutes of oxygen remaining.
I mean, unidentified signal nearby. What are these living up here? The person didn't have
a space suit on. Hey, do you have any oxygen? Don't go in the fire. How do you not have a
space suit on? You got marshmallows? Of course you do. Wait, I can't breathe. I can't breathe. What?
Why would I take off my suit? Oh, marshmallows are so important.
Wait, I can do this? What's the deal with the marshmallows? Is there something about this
that's important? Stop burning them. I like them like that. Look, I know. I know that there's,
you know, like a personality test of how you cook your marshmallows. I know. All right, let's talk.
Oh, hey, it's you. Ground Control didn't tell me you were launching. Long time no see. Actually,
I guess it's been a long time since I've seen anyone. What is it? What are you doing up here?
Haha, very funny. Oh, stars above. You're serious, aren't you? That's just depressing.
Welcome to the lunar outpost, which apparently the space program doesn't bother to teach
anyone anymore. When we first started Outer Wilds, travelers used to bring their ships here all the
time for repairs. Our space bearing technology has improved loads since then, but the older ships
tend to fall apart a lot. Like more than they do now. Using the outpost cut down on the number of
launches and landings taking place in the village and also the number of fires. Nowadays though,
it's mostly just me up here raising saplings from timber hearth and keeping an eye on things.
Don't go. I mean, anything else you want? Did anyone else come by? The lunar outpost saw
more traffic back when our ships were less sophisticated and needed more frequent repairs.
Nowadays, it's mostly used to keep a set of eyes on things. Sometimes Chert comes by to say hi,
but Gabbro is Gabbro. And you know how Ryvek feels about unnecessary spaceflight.
Is it you whistling? Probably, or actually definitely. The other travelers carry instruments
so they don't bother whistling. You can pick up their music with a signal scope, you know.
Best spot for that is the North Pole. Great reception. North Pole is marked in red on
your minimap, but the Attle Rock is a pretty small moon, really. Just go north. You can't miss it.
I already went there. All right, goodbye. What do you got? Radio? What's in your house?
What's in your house? This is where we're going to find the fucking bodies. I'm going to like
put the signal scope down here and you're going to just... I thought I... No, never mind. The sun
looks kind of red. I mean, the sun is red, isn't it? All right, let's go over here.
That's kind of Monka S, dude. I love that emote. It just can be used anywhere.
You can use Monka S in any scenario. And it's just... All right, we're already here. All right,
I'm out of here. I'm going to go to that... Don't go so fucking fast. Okay, I'm out. What is this?
Spaceship. Wait, what's in here? Can I investigate this or something? What is this?
I can't do anything with this. I don't know what that is. Let's go. I can't interact with it. Wait,
can I go in it? Is it like a hatch or something? There's a hole right there. Can I go in? All right,
let's just go back to the ship. Is this... Is what I'm doing stupid? Is what I'm doing stupid?
Oh no, no, no. Where am I? Where am I? Where am I? Where am I? Where am I? Where am I? Where am I?
Oh god damn it. No, I'm out of space. I'm going to die out here. I'm going to die out here. I'm
going to die out here. Get back in the gravity. Slow down. Slow down. Stop. All right, let's get
in the ship. Refuel the jet pack and let's go to Brittle. Let's go to my log book. I see... Oh,
holy shit. Look at this. We have more quests that connect. Oh, what? Okay, hold on.
Uh-huh, this is where I started. Here we are.
We can go here.
Let's go. I just monk-a-est so hard. Are you good? All right, I gotta put that in my...
Brittle Hollow. South Pole of Brittle Hollow. What's this? What planet is this?
You are... What is this? Like, how come it's not listed? Brittle Hollow. There it is. All right,
this planet looks kind of dangerous. All right, let's go. Brittle Hollow. 19 kilometers. I
probably shouldn't fly near the sun. I'm not going to go near the sun. I'm not going to do that. That
seems like a bad idea. Brittle Hollow. Let's go. South Pole of Brittle Hollow, right? Does this ship
run out of gas? The ship doesn't run out of gas, right? All right, that's good. Am I even going
towards it? Uh, 600 miles a second. 700... Was that miles? Was it, like, milloper... millipers?
1000 millipers a second? I don't know what this is. Go up and go up. I'm going so fast.
All right, let's do that easier. That was... That was too many millipers a second. Yeah.
Okay, coming up. Here we go. Let's load this... Derma's a super brumer. This planet, it's just so
small. The sun's fucking this whole thing up. Autopilot. No, I have to be able to do it.
I'm lined up perfectly. Here we go. Load done. I'm slowing down. Dodge it! Dodge it! Dodge it!
Where is it? I have to learn how to do... Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay. We're fine, we're fine.
There we go. Get that landing gear out. All right, get it... All right, we're good.
Yep. All right. Looking at the South Pole. South Pole. Looking for the... the eye. They made an eye.
What the hell was that? Did I just miss something cool? There's, like, a meteor over here.
Uh, what happened? What did I do? What did I do? Why was it just, like, an atomic bomb?
Okay. I didn't do anything. Am I not supposed to be on that planet? Did the game get angry with me
because I went on a planet that I wasn't supposed to be on? Was that, like, a gear check? Like,
wait, you're not supposed to be in this part of the story yet. Nukem! Well, all right. There's our
pilot ready to get this beauty off the ground. You know the ship is a deathtrap, right? You're
lucky I'm in a time loop, because otherwise I'd be dead. The sun is going to supernova, by the way.
What? You're lucky I'm in a time loop, because otherwise I'd be dead.
And you're lucky I don't have you grounded for medical reasons, because I have no idea what
you're talking about. Huh. All right. Can I go to that planet? Should I try something else?
I'm going back to that planet right now. Hold on. Did I get any new info? Where is this? What's this
one? Esker's signal scope log reports harmonica music coming from somewhere on Timber Hearth.
Sounds like Feldspar's harmonica, but Feldspar just... We're going...
Which one? I'm gonna try this one again. All right, let's go. What's this? Planetary chart about a
while. So, okay, that's kind of necessary. Buckle up. Our hero. Where's, like, the nuke? Okay, does it...
Is it on this map somewhere? Follows lantern. That's the thing that... That's the thing that
exploded. Remember I said, whoa, what was that? Like a meteor just landed. Is this... This thing
crashes into this planet? Let's investigate. Just autopilot. All right, I have autopilot on.
Wow, that's so much easier. Why did I not do autopilot ever? That couldn't have been more
simple. Well, I unlocked it, so it's just different. All right, what happened here?
I unlocked the planet, so I unlocked it for fast travel. That's my... That's what I'm gonna say.
Okay, let's go. South Pole, right? Let me go take a... Is this gonna happen?
They said... Okay, I told you, see? It's just... Hell's just raining down here. I'm just not
supposed to be here. This is too... I'm here too early. I'm here too early. I have to get, like,
the anti... I have to get, like, the anti-meteor shield or something. All right, South Pole.
Unidentified signal. Freeze. Wait, unidentified signal. This guy, that sounds like a blue whale.
Or a car on the highway that's going by really fast that's holding the horn down.
It's right there. What is it, though? I'm going up. Jetpack. Hold... I want to... Hold...
Hold A. Jetpack booster. Why is it doing this? Power shard. Why is it doing this?
Plume. Felix and I have determined this atypical shard of rock is the reason objects in this
grove are behaving in a quantum manner. Okay. How do you behave in a quantum manner? Of note,
a unique signal is coming from this shard. Curiously, a friend, the wandering moon,
sounds the same. I've also heard the same signal this shard produces calling out from giants deep
timber hearth and the hourglass twins. Suppose there are other shards like this.
The only other object we've observed displaying this quantum behavior is the wandering moon.
I imagine the moon's behavior in this groves are related. In her note from earlier, Felix mentions
this strange type of rock isn't found elsewhere on Brittle Hollow. What if it isn't originally
from this planet? Hypothesis. This quantum shard is from the wandering quantum moon.
Perhaps it is even a small piece of the moon itself. What is this wandering moon? All right.
Okay. So it says the South Pole. Don't hit your face. Okay. All right. South Pole.
There's some, isn't somebody supposed to be here? Watch out. Yeah, this is an observatory here. Okay.
So when somebody was be working here that I know. Oh, am I right? Okay. Ship. Oh damn. All right.
There's a way to go down here. Whose ship is this? Outer Wilds Ventures. It looks like it's working.
Somebody already in here. I'm here. I did it. I put the ship down safely. All right.
Um, and that ship, in that, in that the ship went down and I didn't sustain bodily harm.
A few minor repairs and it's like, I just, I just spilled coffee on my cup. It's good news.
The bad news is I haven't found a way inside the structure yet. The door is broken and hold on.
I like was about to take a sip. I jittered. I jittered. My hand jittered a little and it
spilled a tiny bit on my lap. Sorry. I'm not great at exploring, but I think I would have found a
different entrance by now. If there was one, probably. I can't get inside from here, but I
know there are paths below the surface. I'm going to head north to the ruins on the equator. Try to
find a way down. Let's open it. That didn't work. All right. So there's a place. There's a cave to go.
What's it? What is this? Are we on emote only mode because people are going to give spoilers?
Yeah. I don't want to be spoiled. What is up here? Can I go in there?
You have to communicate in pictures to me. What is that scope? I want to see. Zoom in. Can I get a
signal from anything? I think I have what I want. Get this away. I can't get in here anyway. What
was he talking about when he said under the equator is a place to get in. I guess I should
go over here. I got plenty of fuel, right? I'm going this way. I'm so scared to get hurt.
All right. What about like right here? Oh, oh, oh my God. Oh my God. What is this?
What is this black hole? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, fly, fly, fly, fly,
fly. Can I fly? Grab on, grab onto the edge. Come on, grab onto something. I can't grab onto this.
Three minutes of auction. Come on, grab on, get in, get inside. What is this? What the hell is that?
I just opened a fucking ancient sarcophagus. Okay. What the hell is this? It's gravity.
Welcome to the White Hole Station. You fell through the black hole by accident. Don't worry,
you aren't the first. This warp tower can return you to Brittle Hollow. Every warp tower is turned
to a specific astral body. To use the tower, stand on the warp platform on the floor and wait until
the tower aligns with its corresponding astral body, in this case, Brittle Hollow.
If you look up while the station is rotating, you can see the alignment happens when the
astral body is directly overhead. What the fuck are you talking about? Wait, this is recording.
Pick up Ember Twin Projection Stone. What? Oh, that's not... What should I do with this?
Ember Twin Projection Stone. Alright, like, Ember Twin's a planet. Okay, I'm gonna bring this with
me to Ember Twin, right? I'm gonna bring this with me to Ember Twin and I'm gonna use it there.
How do I get there? Alright, I have to wait for Brittle Hollow to come into frame? I don't
understand. Okay, look up and wait for... Wait, oh, wait, wait. Is it when it gets to there, right?
I just have to wait till it gets to be 12 o'clock and then I do it. Look up. This thing doesn't move.
Alright, I'm going for it. Wait, I can't see. I'm going in. This is just space again. What is
going on? What am I... What's this doing? What should I do with this? I just have this ping-pong
ball. What do I do? Do I go in here? I'm stuck in this thing. I don't know what to do. I really
don't know what to do. I don't know what to do. I'm confused. Alright, it said look up and then go
into the... Step into the thing? I'm confused. This did move. This is glass. Okay, this way...
I thought that... This is made out of glass. Alright, alright, alright. It's safe down here.
Okay, alright, alright, alright. It's safe down here. It's made out of glass. I didn't know it was
made out of glass. Okay, wait. It's following me around. I did it. What do I do? What's it doing?
Where am I going? Uh, where am I going? Is this a monorail? Do I just stay on this?
There's my ship. There's my ship. Let's go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. That's my ship.
I need to get up there now. Alright, let's go. Oh, we're spinning. Okay, look up and then when
I'm ready, I say stop. I... Alright, now? Go? Alright, where the... I don't know where I am.
Where am I? Quick translator? Return warp status charge. Step onto the warp platform when ready.
Okay, that's a... So, this is a warp platform. What do I do with this thing?
Shit! No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Back, back, back, back, back, back. Go back, back, back, back,
back, back, back. But back, back, back, back. Go back in there. Go back in there. Oh, God.
Go back in there. Ready? One, two, three. Okay, don't do that again.
What do I do with this projecting thing? Alright, what's down there?
here? Oxygen? Re-fuel jetpack. I don't mind if I do. What is this? Elspar spare jetpack
fuel. It's annoying to schlep across the planet for the ship if I can't use my jetpack so
I'm leaving this here. I check with my little scout. I do too use it. Corn fells. You burnt
marshmallow. And the scout's integrity reading said this piece of brittle hollow is as stable
as any. I just, I don't know why I read that. I read that like almost like I was reading
words out of place. But who knows? If fuel's still around, fit for it to use it, I'm not
well, wherever you're reading this, I'm sure you, whatever. Language. Languages. Langu-
wait, drop. What should I do with this? There's a language here. Hold on. The hanging city
below 50 meters. Hanging city? Hanging city. What is this? What planet am I on? I'm on-
alright, alright, alright, alright, let's go. I thought this was supposed to be Hanging
City. Below 50 meters. Well, why did you say that? There's nothing here. Um, there's bones
here. Alright, there's more things to read. What is this? To our friends on Brittle Hollow,
I just warped here from the white hole station. Our design worked. We've successfully recreated
warp travel. This is wonderful news. I can't wait to see the warp tower. It's been a long time since
I've jumped through a black hole. I don't know how close it is to the known as original design,
but as long as what we build works, then I'm delighted. I knew we could do it. If you're
reading this. Wait, this can't be correct. Clarie, have you seen these readings? If they were
accurate, they would violate causality. There must be an equipment error somewhere. I'm returning to
the white hole station. If you and Root meet me there, we can run a full diagnostic and hopefully
locate the problem. Don't tell Casaba. What the fuck do I do with this thing? There's a gap here
slotting. Put this in right here. All right. Put it in. I got it. All right. Did it. All right.
Read. What does it read? What does it say? Rami and I reviewed the records you sent, Pokey,
and they appear to show Nomai are arriving at the warp receiver on Brittle Hollow slightly before
departing from the white hole station. As I've already told Rami, these measurements can't be
accurate. How can Nomai arrive on Brittle Hollow before he or she ever stepped into the teleporter?
The implications are absurd. I don't disagree. It would mean I've inadvertently broken several
fundamental theories regarding this universe. We would have to reconsider all of our beliefs
about the nature of time. Yes, I hope so too. Pokey, as Pie is confident the reading is inaccurate,
she's kindly helping me attempt to recreate this phenomenon at the High Energy Lab.
We're designing an experiment to take more data. An update, Pokey. The High Energy Lab is in the
canyon on Ember Twin's equator. Come here at once. You need to see this.
I understand it's exceedingly odd, but Larry and I have tested and retested the equipment.
The result is the same every time someone warps. The interval is incredibly miniscule, roughly
one hundred thousandth of a second. Do you suppose our instruments can't accurately measure time to
such a small degree? We got it. High Energy Lab on Ember Twin's equator. Should I take this out?
It is. The hell just happened? What's going on? What's just like magic quicksand? I'm going back.
I'm. What the hell is going on? Oh, wait. Was I looking into the future or the past or something?
What was I just looking at? I'm going to leave that here. I want to see it again. If I stay in
here for too long, am I going to like rot my brain or something? All right. That's where I am.
This is it. This must be the other planet. Sick. OK. All right. All right. I'm going to leave that
there. Is there another place to put it? I don't think there's another place to put it. OK,
cool. Let's get some oxygen. How do I not have oxygen? I read that. What's this? What about
noises? Great sounds. Hide and seek. Outer wilds. Ventures. Quantum fluctuations. Outer wild
ventures. Let's see. How's my ship over there? What the hell happened to the ship? Why is it
over there? Can I not get off this planet ever? How am I going to get in? How am I going to get
over there? What is it doing over there? I have three minutes of oxygen. What happened? OK.
Oh, my. Wait. Unknown. This is sound over here. Pull it back. Vitals critical. It's OK.
Why is my ship all the way out here? What's something here? 66 meters down. What? Where is
it? This planet's crazy. Look at this shit. This is crazy. Wait. All right. This stuff
is explosions and shit happening. I'm going over here. Unidentified signal nearby. Where?
Where is it? Where is it? Where is it? Down there. It's a guitar. What is it? OK. Where are you?
Wait. No, no, no. Not in there. Where are you? Where the fuck is this person? What is that?
I got nuked again. All right. That's the second time that's happened.
It's replaying everything I've looked at. OK. That's a that's like a time travel thing.
I get it. So I'm that we get to see everything I did. But the nuke is like a time explosion.
Yeah, that's has to be what's going on. Like, why would it show me literally everything I just did?
All right. Well, why is that happening, though? Ready to get off this ground. Hey,
what can I do for you? I'm going to time loop. All right. Yeah. All right. How am I triggering
that to happen, though? Is it just like scripted? OK. Let's go back. I got a bunch of new info,
though. I got a ton of new info. Quantum shard. This one's like a legendary quest.
Oh, that's a legendary quest. That's just a normal one. This is just like a green. This is
like legendary. And this is like epic or something. I don't know. Quantum shards.
I have rumors about them, but this one's curious to me.
The North Pole of Brittle Hollow is covered in snow and ice. There's a uniquely shaped
Nomai ruin on the surface. Nomai were able to warp here from the White Hole Station. This is
where they first recreated warp technology. There's more to explore here. I was about to do it.
OK. Every there's a lot of info. Every Nomai warp tower is tuned to a specific astral body.
To use the tower, stand at the warp platform and wait until the tower aligns with its corresponding
astral body. Nomai noticed something strange. Warped objects appeared to arrive at the receiver
on Brittle Hollow slightly before they departed. This negative time interval between an object
arriving and departing was incredibly minuscule. Nomai were skeptical if their equipment could
even measure time to such a small degree. And then over here is the energy lab.
High energy lab in the canyon at Ember Twins equator. That's where we're going.
High energy lab. Ember Twin. Let's go. I want to investigate that ship. Gear options?
Jetpack boost mode auto. Translator equip mode. Freeze time while reading.
Does that matter? Alright. I need to uh... Ember Twin, right? You are here. Where's Ember Twin?
Hourglass Twins? Ember Twin. I gotta go here. We can't lock on. OK, there we go. Hourglass Twins.
Let's go. Go to Ember Twin. This is pretty cool. This is really cool, actually. So, alright. I'm
starting to understand. So you're on this, you just have these little things, these missions you have
to do to try to unravel the mystery of the Nomai. That's pretty cool. And you go quest to quest to
quest to quest to quest to quest to quest and you trail to trail to trail to trail to trail.
That's pretty fun. Error, error. Alright. How did you... Why is that emote bigger than every other
emote? What the hell is that? That emote is three times bigger than all emotes. Alright,
we need Ember Twin. This is slowing down, right? Slow down. That's the one. Slow down. Slow down.
It's going too fast. There we go. Slow down. So in the equator of this planet, right in the middle
there's like a core in this one. Alright, go right into like into like the middle of the cookie.
Wait, no, don't. I gotta land like on this thing. This thing is spinning very fast.
How am I gonna land on this planet? It's going so fast. Jesus, how am I supposed to do this?
OK, I'm good. Unbuckle. Let's go. Alright, we're good. Flashlight on. Now it's the question of
getting into the equator and finding the high energy lab. Is this the equator? There's the
lab. The lab's like right in there. But what's this? Wait, maybe is this the lab?
This could be a lab. What the fuck is this? Uh, alright. Fire. Now. Oh shit. Alright,
there's oxygen in here? Hold Patch Suit Puncture. What do you mean Suit Puncture?
Alright, well we got something. There's a lot of shit over here. Activate the Gravity Cannon.
That is, that is a Gravity Cannon. OK. I was making a stupid joke.
Call the shuttle home. The shuttle is currently resting at the comet. The Sunless City.
How do I move this? Can I move this or something? Is it like a punch or a tool I can use? OK,
that's what that is. I can't get in there. I'm gonna go down. Walk into the spikes.
Imagine my shock when there's a hole in the suit. Anything in here? Oh, that's too far away.
Nothing else here, huh? Wait. OK. Now I think that's it. Yeah, that's it. Can I do anything
with that? Oh yeah, I can. Yep. Oh yeah. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep.
Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. Yep. What does it do? What does it do? What's going on?
Gravity Cannon. Gravity Cannon? I don't know what I just did. What is this one?
I think I just sucked something through. What is that? What did I just do? I just sucked something
in? All right, put this away. Wait, I can go in this. What is this? This is like somebody's ship.
This is not the ship. Can I fly it? I fear our situation may be dire.
No, they haven't contacted me since descending below the surface either.
Can I leave the shuttle to look for them? I want to follow protocol, but are they running?
I don't know what I'll do if they aren't well.
Okie pie, come back to me safely, my friends. All right, so what does this do?
How do I stop this? How do I stop this? How do I stop this? How do I stop the ride? How do I stop
the ride? How do I stop the ride? No, no, no, no. Go over here. Go in the middle. What? Hi.
Where the fuck am I? What does this one do? This is the same place that brings me back to the...
Hold on. This doesn't do anything. What about middle again? What does this do? Go out and then
What is this taking me? That's just launch, but then I just float around.
What about if I do that one? Ok, so what if I hit the right one? Where we go now?
I don't think I'm... I don't know. I don't know.
Ok, I'm gonna go back. Is there more readings? All right, got some info though. All right.
Quick while the streamer isn't looking, put knives out spoilers in chat. What are you talking about?
You can't even talk. You can't even talk, man. All right, so I got some info. I'm gonna go back to my...
This is not the lab though. Quick unmod that guy. Yeah, he's a real nuisance, isn't he?
All right, I gotta get out. Don't touch those. What's the best way to get out of here?
Ok, that's not the lab though. It's like in here or something. All right, let's go in here.
Is it gonna kill me? Mods think they are funny. This is turning so fast. It's hurting my body.
All right, what about up there? It said there was a lab in the equator.
So I'm just gonna skim the equator and see if I can find it. That looks like a lab.
That looks like it could be a lab. And there's sounds coming from somewhere in here.
All right, here we go. Did I find it? There's something down here. Whoa, it's another one of
these things. It's a cave shard. Wait, where'd it go? Hey, where is it? It's gone. Oh, it's one of
those shard things. Where'd it go? You have to keep looking at it. It's like SCP. What should I do
with it? All right, I gotta read this. Friends, if you find any sign of Coleus, I implore you to
tell me he vanished without a trace during our research trip and has been missing ever since.
Mulare, some of us from the Sunless City are here to help search for Coleus. Can you tell us more
about your expedition? Get my gratitude, Burr. Coleus and I were studying the cave's geology.
We hope to learn more about a unique and wandering rock that visits several different caves in the
area. Where was young Coleus lost, please? He disappeared in the cave at the bottom of the
dry lakebed of the North Pole, and it happened in an instant without warning. I turned away from
Coleus to examine a sample. When I turned back, he simply wasn't there anymore. Well, he had one in
his pocket. He had a limited supply of air. I'm afraid for him. Yeah, he had one of those rocks
in his pocket. Hypothesis, we will learn more by examining the northern lakebed cave, but Coleus
disappeared. Search quickly, everyone. We have no time. All right, I'm out of control. What's going
on? All right, so there's a cave. I'm gonna like, I'm gonna go to, there's a lot of shithair. Okay,
let's go to, wait, what's up here? This is where I came in. I can go up. All right, I don't want
to run out of oxygen. What is up here? There was a sound in here that wasn't that, though. What was
it? No, that is the cave. Wait, another one. There's like two or three cave shards in here,
they said, right? What the fuck is that? Okay, well, we're going there. We're just gonna go
over there. All right, there's a signal. All right, somebody up here? Three detected. All right,
there is somebody here. This is a Cadbury egg. Oh, wait, let's talk. Shurt. Oh, it's you. I take it
your first launch went well then. Welcome to the Hourglass Twins. Mine the sand now. What are you
doing? Hornfell has noticed our star charts are out of date, so I came here to update them, but
something seems off. I've seen what? 10 supernova by now. 12? They're in double digits now, and
that's, you know, not normal. Not normal at all. He's seeing the supernovas. I found something.
Why are somebody's stars supernova? What are you doing out here? Where should I explore? How
dangerous is that big column of falling sand? I found something. Actually, never mind. Please do
tell. What? Nothing you'd like to discuss at the moment. That's no trouble. If you do find something
you wish to discuss, please come find me. I'll be here studying the stars for a while. Why are
so many stars going supernova? I have no idea. Massive stars go supernova when they reach the
end of their lifespan. It's probably that the stars are older than we realized, or maybe our
models are wrong and they don't live as long as we expected. Honestly, I'm not fond of either option.
If our charts are wrong, what else is wrong? And our sun. No, I shouldn't jump to conclusions. I'm
probably overlooking something. That's it. I just need to collect more data. How dangerous is that
column of falling sand? On a scale of one to dead, I'd give it a seven or an eight. Awfully pretty,
though. Right now, sand is flowing from ash twin to ember twin. But did you know the process
eventually reverses? We're not completely sure why the sand flows back and forth between the twins,
but it seems to be a natural phenomenon. Oh, if you'd like to see something interesting,
check out the other twin once a little more of its sand drains off. I promise you won't be
disappointed. Is there anything else? Where should I go? Be honest, I haven't left this lake bed. I
don't mean to brag, but I'm really quite good with the little scout. I've been taking pictures of
everything from right here in my campsite. Let us free. I want to use the German auto emote.
All right, let them free. Let them free. Let them free. Let them free. They've they've they've
behaved. Let them free. To be honest, I haven't left this. Yeah, yeah, yeah. Have you seen the
old shipwreck site on the ember twin's southern hemisphere? The one shooting a bright beam of
light into the sky? It's not one of our own crashes. Surprisingly enough, this is a Nomai ship.
What ship? You find ruins across the twins, but strangely not a single settlement. Believe me,
if there was one to see, I'd have it seen with my little scout. But they live not on the surface,
clearly. The ember twin is full of cave systems. Maybe the answer lies underground.
All right. What's that? What's that? What's that? What's that? What's that? What is that? What is
that? What's that? What's that? What's that? What's that? What's that? It's a bunch of floating trash.
What do I do about that? All right, hold on. What's this? God damn it. What's this? What's that? What's
this? I need that stone. I need that stone thing. Can I touch this? What if I go in the middle and
like look up? Um, I don't know what that... We're getting close to the sun. That's too close. That's
way too close. Who built this? You can already touch the sun right now. How am I not dead? Look
at how close that is. That's so close. Oh my God. It's going to touch. It's going to scrape. It's
going to scrape. It's going to scrape. Wait. No, no, no, no, no, no. Don't do that. Don't do that.
That's stupid. It said that when the sand's done... Look. What the fuck happened to my body? What's
going on? What? Did somebody throw something at me? Did somebody shoot me? What happened?
Well, I found the egg guy. He jumped 200 meters into the air. This is ADHD. ADHD problems for me.
I want something to look at and there's something to look at and there's something to look at at
the same time. And I'm just falling off a cliff. Okay. Um, I have new info though.
This game is nothing but things to look at. I know. That's why I'm going to have a big problem
with this game because there's too many things to look at. All right. What did I do? I got some new
info. So many info. So many info. So many new things. That's too many things. I've got,
there's too many DNA strands here. I'm going to go back to this because this is,
there's too much going on over here right now. Real Hollows South Pole. There's a door to the
observatory on the surface, but it's broken. And I can remember I could, I could get in there somehow.
I got to finish one of these. I got to complete one of these.
Harmonica music coming from somewhere on Timber Hearth. Okay, wait.
That's this planet. That's where I am right now. Right. Hold on. Who the fuck is that?
Who's doing that? Where is that? I want to get back up to my ship. Where's the, where's the,
of course it has to be all the way up there. Is there, can I fly up there with fuel or is it,
can I only do like a big jump? I don't know. I can. How do I do it? I'm holding right trigger.
How do I do that? I'll just stay on this planet and go find this harmonica.
Let's go around here. Where is this harmonica? It's going to land right there. The world is
your oyster, Jeremiah. Yeah. Let's find this harmonica. Okay. You're in here. Don't fall.
Float. Okay. What the fuck is this? Um, okay. You, do you have a harmonica?
This thing's playing the harmonica. How? Hey, Hatchling. I thought you were taking that tin
can of yours into space today. What are you still doing here? Me? I saw something crash over the
horizon and didn't like what I was seeing in the pictures of my little scout was sending back.
But I come over here myself and take a look. What is it? I don't know what it is. It looks
like some kind of plant seed, but it's not anything I've seen on timber or hearth before.
And trust me, I was quite the explorer back in the day. I think it's extraterrestrial. It kind
of looks like something that might've come off dark ramble. Whatever it is, it put down its roots in
a hurry. I don't like the look of this thing, Hatchling. And that's a fact. I think I'll set
marlin haul loose on it. Let's get rid of this mess sooner rather than later. And no one can
remove an unwanted plant faster than a treekeeper can. I'll have to get a look at what's inside the
seed first though. I don't want to set anybody up hacking a potentially dangerous plant without
a better idea of what's lurking inside of it. Huff can help me haul the old scout launcher over here.
Obviously the opening is too small for someone to fit inside. And anyway, I'm not going to
politely stick my hands in anything that looks as unpleasant as that. That's a good way to lose an
arm. I got one of those. Doing a colonoscopy. What's that? Wait, what is that? What is that?
What is that? Go find out. I can't go in there. Help. Help. Help me. No, no, no. Stop. Get off.
Get off. Get off. Get off. Stop. Stop. Stop. Okay. Am I going to die? I threw a little scout into
the seed. You did, did you? And you're telling me it's bigger on the inside than on the outside.
Could be a chore to chop up and no mistake. Can we even remove a seed that doesn't have
the decency to stay the same size? Maybe I better grab an extra ax or three.
See, he did a lot of damage when it crashed. I like this crater.
My signal scope is picking up a harmonica inside. I don't know what to tell you. The
only harmonica player I know is Feldspar and they disappeared ages ago. Listener, don't go telling
Nace about the harmonica music, okay? They'll never let me get rid of this darn seed they
suspect it has musical talent. You sure this seed isn't from Timber Hearth? Back in my younger days,
I explored everywhere there is to go on Timber Hearth and saw everything there is to see and
then some. Trust me, we don't have anything like this. I reckon this thing's from Dark Bramble.
Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. Wait a minute.
Wait a minute. There's a fire there. There's a campfire there. Wait a minute. Wait, wait,
wait a minute. Error. Duplicate signal. All right, keep that camera on. We're going for it,
boys and girls. I could only fucking learn how to drive my body ship. I just want to see,
I just want to see. Oh shit. All right, let's go. Let's go. Let's go. I know what that is.
I know what that is. That's where it is. Oh damn. All right, we're going to go. Okay,
we're going to find that. Keep the camera up. Keep the camera up. Don't put the camera down.
Oh, you put the camera down, you idiot. Wait, it's still on there.
Fly the fucking ship, Jeremy. Oh wait, let me just turn my head and look around while I drive.
Duplicate signal. Let's go. There it is. I'm going to find that guy. We're going to find that guy.
That guy's here. Feldspar is here. He's not lost. He's playing the harmonica in a time portal.
Duplicate signal. All right, I got to be careful. Is this on the dark bramble? I don't have,
I don't have the thing to help. It's just too fast. Am I going too fast? Too fast. Too fast.
Pull up. Too fast. Pull up. Too fast. Pull up. Too fast. Pull up. All right. I'm going to land on
this thing. Can I just fly in there? I don't think I can land on this. I can't land on this.
Once I get close enough, I'm going to stop. Shit. Okay. Okay, hold on. Here we go. I'm just going to
dump in there. Oh, oh, oh. Where the fuck am I? I'm coming. I'm coming. I'll be there in a minute.
I'm coming. I'm coming to rescue you. I'm almost out of fuel. He's in there. All right. Slow down.
Get in here. All right. What is this? Error. Error. Error. Error. Error. Error. Duplicate
signal. Error. Fuel level critical. What the hell is going on? 1.3 kilometers. 500 meters.
300. 400. Wait, there's another smaller one? Duplicate signals. Right there. All right. Land
on it. Get it. All right. What is it? Grab it. Stick a knife in it. Stick a knife in it.
Stick a knife in this thing. No, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. No, no, no. Wait, give me my...
Shoot it. What do I do with this thing? No, stop, stop, stop. Go down, down, down. What do I do with
this? I don't know what to do with this. Shoot it in? I'm going to shoot it in. Oh, no. Wait, now
where is this going? Where is this going now? What the hell is this? What? I'm... 60 seconds
until oxygen is gone. What? But I'm not ready. I'm not done yet. I'm not ready. Am I in somebody's
brain? Is this like neurons or something? I'm dead. Could I have flown the ship in here?
I didn't know that. I don't know what to do about that. Do I have any new info?
What is that? That happens every time. What is that? What's going on over here?
This shit explodes every time I wake up. Why? What is that? I'm going back there. Wait,
I need to... I'm going back there. No, I need to shoot it in the thing. No, what do I do? I don't
know. Grab the ship. Did I get any new info? No, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Did I get any info?
Dead. Dark bramble seed inside the seed. When I launch my scout into the seed that crashed on
Timberheart, it ends up somewhere in dark bramble. The seed from dark bramble crashed here and has
taken root. I'm going for it. Okay, I'm going to do that again and then I'm going to take the ship
in there this time and I'm going to continue my investigation. Right? Yeah, that was good to me.
Let's go to the bramble again.
I'm rushing. I'm rushing. I'm rushing. Wait, what's this? Where's the... Where's the
thing? Wait, I'm like rushing. I'm too... I'm too overexcited. What? Wait, what the hell is it
talking about? Why is that 15 million meters away? I'm dying. I'm gonna die. I'm gonna die.
I'm not. I'm fine. Shoot it back in here. Okay, there it goes. Wasn't there... It looks like a
campfire there though. That's what I don't understand. Right here. See? Was this a campfire?
Okay, well, I know what that is. Let's go. I'll get it. I'll figure it out.
Get it. I'll get it. I'll get it. Don't worry. I'll get it eventually. Don't worry. I'll get it
eventually. I'll get it. Don't worry. I will get it eventually. Play Hulk. This game sucks.
I don't own a Hulk for the Wii. How many times do I have to say that? I don't own the Hulk.
What is this? Is that my ship? No. What's going on? It's because it was damaged. Would it explode?
So what do I do? How do I do? You have to... I'm softlocked? Oh. Fly into the sun. Well,
I guess I could. Wait. This is gonna like... Wait. What's down here? Secret! Is there a secret in
here? I'll do it again. I just was... I was too excited and I just rushed. I was so excited to
run down there and shoot my thing. Do I need to shoot that thing though? I probably do. Do I? No,
I don't. I know where it is. No, I just... I can just go there, right? Do I need to shoot it in there?
I don't think I have to do that. Maybe I do. All right. I'm gonna. I'm gonna. I'll shoot it in.
I'm gonna be careful. I know where it is now. Yeah, I know where it is, but I can't track down my
beam thing. Like my launcher. I'm gonna shoot it through and then try this again.
Where was that? Where was that thing? It's over here, right? There we go. Fire it. Boink. There it
goes. Get the pictures. Just so I can know what I'm looking for. There it is. There it is. Okay.
Found it. Good. Let's go. Don't retrieve the thing. Look at the signal. All right. Let's move
back over to this ship. Why is my ship over there? Wait. What happened to my ship?
Where's my ship? Oh, okay. Right, right, right. There it is. I got confused there for a second.
I forgot. Mario Galaxy mechanics. Could be underneath you, but it's not. It's above you.
All right. Now I'm ready. I'm going to go in there with the ship this time. I'm going to be very
careful. I'm going to go for it. Let's move. I'm wicked fucking excited right now. I'm going to
go fast quick. Slow down. Seven. Six. Five. Slower. Slower. Slower. Okay. We're good. Can I get in
here with this ship? It's going to be impossible. I'm not going to be able to get it in here.
How the fuck am I going to do this? Look at how small this is. This thing's going to explode.
The ship's going to explode when I do this. I lost the signal. What's the red thing? All right.
Hold on. Almost there. Do I fly in here? Can I make it in there too? I don't think I could make
it in here. Oh my God. How am I going to get in there? Slowly. What? Hello? Hello? Hello? Hello?
What was that? What? What is that thing? Put your left earphone in.
All right. So I got to go faster than that. You have an instafilter on. I do not have an
instafilter on. Now you're making me excited. I'm just going to land the ship in there.
Why have I not done that yet? Why have I not just landed the ship here?
Right? Like what the hell am I doing? I can't kill this guy, right?
Okay. So there's a giant enemy fish in here. I have to go quicker. I have to go through it faster.
I don't have any guns. I do not have any weapons. I don't have any guns or anything.
That's a little too fast. Way too fast. What? Excuse me. Okay. That doesn't get up. No, no,
no, no. Unbuckle. Unbuckle. Unbuckle. Unbuckle. Okay. We're good. We're fine. God damn it. Come
on. I had somebody fire like a missile at me. There was like an asteroid and it freaked me out.
Just take off your helmet. I don't think I can. That was a quick one too.
Whatever. I'm just doing this. Flying in the fucking sun. Who cares?
I was going too fast because I was too fightable and then the meteor tried to hit me and it freaked
me out and I crashed to fuck. Can I just die already? Can I please die? Why can't I just
rip my helmet off and have my head explode? Why can't I burn as much fuel as possible?
Did I have to leave the ship? The ship was spinning around and it was giving me progress.
Yeah, we are making progress. I wonder if I can float in there. Can't wait to watch the replay
of this one. It's gonna be real exciting. Three minutes until oxygen depletes. What was that?
Oh, that's where I was trying to go. 60 seconds. Five, four, three, two.
That's just the noise that I make right when I'm about to do the Bane impression into a coffee mug.
Exciting. Good run. Good. We did it. Oh, look. There he goes again.
My soul leaving my body and I don't know, whatever that is. Don't fuck it up this time.
This time I gotta get away from the giant fish. Same deal. I'm just a guy. I don't have my equipment.
Let's go. Okay. Don't fuck it up this time. Accelerating toward destination.
Autopilot's cheating. Well, Fortnite, Jimmy. Let me tell you. You have to let Luigi help you
sometimes. This will be the fourth time I've tried to come over here. Hey! It almost happened again.
God damn it. How fast do I have to do this? Do I have to go really fast to get away from the
giant fish? I'm scared. All right. Here we go. I gotta get in there quickly. Put your earbuds in.
All right. Your second earbud going in. All right. Now where? Oh, fuck. I'm fine. Where am I?
Straight ahead. I'm going down here. I made it. I'm in. I'm in. Shit's getting louder. Wait.
It's this thing's mouth. It's in this thing's actual mouth. It's inside of this thing's mouth.
Do I go in it? Do I get out? There is a fire over there. I told you there was a fire.
I told you there was a fire. I told you there was a fire. I told you.
I fucking told you there was a fire. Nobody believed me. Found you.
Elsewhere. Oh shit. There goes the ship. Can I, can I, what?
The ship. Oh my God. I want the ship to land. I need the ship to land.
Come look. All right. Help. Help. I found you. Relax. Relax. Relax. Hey. Whoa. Where'd you come
from? No one's coming here. And then. Actually, that makes you the second
Parthian to ever reach dark ramble. After me, of course. Well done.
Say it's you. They made you an astronaut and you haven't blown yourself up yet. Good for you.
You're alive. You never were the brightest hatchling, were you? Yeah, that's right. I'm
alive. Been camping out here since my ship, you know, crashed violently.
Crashed? But you're a good pilot. It's going to pass me aggressive.
I haven't lived in polite society for a while, so I'm just going to go ahead and assume that
wasn't sarcasm. My story goes like this. I just finished exploring the core of Giants Deep,
and I wanted to try my hand at dark ramble, seeing as no one had ever been here before.
Getting around a dark ramble was easy, mind you. Once you've dodged one massive interdimensional
vine bristling with thorns, you've dodged them all. But after a while, I run into this huge angler
fish. You've seen them. Big gnarly things. And this was the biggest one I've seen yet. Ever.
I pull a few stunts, try to shake the thing off. Nothing too fancy. I'm going full speed when the
fish clips me, knocks me into a vine, and, well, like I said, I crash. Blammo. On impact, my ship
starts making noises, like it's coming apart from the inside, and I think, well, that ain't great.
Sure enough, I barely get out of there before the electrical system starts sparkling like crazy.
It's either move fast or die unpleasantly, so I had to put a little distance between me and
my poor friend ship. I camped out near where I crashed at first. I found this skeleton later.
Great find. Would have been stupid not to use it. If I moved my setup over here,
planted my emergency tree seeds, been here ever since. Wow. Yeah, pretty much. Anyway,
that's how it all went down, hatchlings. Story's over, but I feel free to stay and enjoy the fire
a while. But don't. Fire's not going anywhere. Anything else you wanted? Uh, shouldn't I tell
ground control to come get you? Well, yeah, sure, whenever you have time. Frankly, I kind of like it
out here. Quiet, peaceful. You're a little young to understand. There's a lot of pressure being the
best that ever was. It's been nice to have a break. Well, I don't think we're going to get out of
here, Feldspar. What else is in here? Oh, oh, oh, oh. Oh, okay. Okay, come here. Okay, I found
something. Lay it on me. I found a dark bramble seed on Timber Hearth. That's bad business,
hatchling. This turret will tell you if you sow as much glance in dark bramble's direction. There
used to be a fifth planet where the bramble is now. It was an infernal planet. The infernal plant
appeared at the center and kept growing and growing and growing until it shattered the planet and
shattered, scattered its pieces across space. If we don't get that seed you found sorted real quick,
I suspect Timber Hearth will be heading toward the same fate. And I tell you what,
we Hearthians have overcome far too much to be done in by some worthless seed. Unidentified signal
nearby. How's that unknown? I know what this is. Yeah, it's mine. Unknown. No, it's Feldspar. Yeah,
I know what that is now. What are you talking about? Okay, what else? Where should I explore
here? That spirit anywhere is good, but you should know that space is weird here intensely.
Ever tried throwing your probe into one of these weird seeds? See there with the little opening,
it's just big enough to launch one through. Probe tracker will tell you the probe is in
two places at once. But I don't think that's wrong exactly because space doesn't work right in here.
That seed looks small, see, but inside it's bigger. Much bigger. I had a lot of time to think about
this. My theory is space in Dark Bramble kind of expands as you go through each sphere. That's why
it's bigger inside those seeds. Well, that's my theory. Keep that in mind while you're exploring
Dark Bramble and maybe you won't get lost inside forever. Good luck. You've reached the core of
Giant Steve. How'd you do that? Oh, that was a wild one. Since you're asking, I got to assume
you haven't made it down to yourself yet, right? I tell you how it kind of feels like cheating.
On a completely unrelated note, that sure was a big hollow vine my ship crashed into. Yep.
If I were you, I'd go take a walk and see where it ends. You want to go
to the tail end of the angler fish skeleton here and look for flickering light in the fog.
That'll be my old ship. That starts there. Put this guy on emote only mode. What happened to the
angler fish here? Oh, the skeleton. It was like this when I got here, as near as I can tell.
This angler fish must have been chewing on the vine and eaten the seed. And then the seed grew
and grew in the poor fish's stomach until this happened. Gross. The skeleton was a good find.
The light keeps the fish away, you know. See, they're territorial. So they're mostly avoiding
each other. That's why I set up camp here. Oh, I want you to look at that. All right. Let's
go do what he wanted. We got more info. All right, let's go find it. Go to the tail end.
Wait, should I try to get the ship back? I should probably do this on the ship. The ship. Ship. Okay,
good. All right, he said go down into the tail. Where the hell is he? He's over here. Go over to
the tail. And he said it's your journey begins there. All right, give me the scalp back. I don't
need it anymore. Your journey begins here. With that flickering light? That's where your journey
begins. Should I do anything? What about his ship? Did I do anything about his ship? All right,
I did it. Come in. Easy. Easy, easy, easy, easy, easy. Don't be an idiot. Don't be an idiot.
Don't be an idiot. Don't be an idiot. What? The ship doesn't fit in there. Wait. Did I go the wrong
way? Easy. Don't break anything. No, I didn't go the wrong way. I'm sorry, guys. I'm sorry that
I'm increasing. I'm increasing your puke meters by like 500% right now. Okay. All right. I'm just
gonna get out. Oh, man. We're going down the drain. Gravity? Duplicate signal. Another one?
What the hell am I? Launching fluctuation. All right. Where am I? Where am I? What is that?
Oh, we've got some info. Hold on. Trip four entry. I'm gonna say not one. Crash is three. Boring
crash is zero. Whoa. Never thought I'd see one of these beasties outside of the giant's deep. They
were awfully useful back there. Maybe a jellyfish could be useful here too. Blur. This thing tastes
terrible. The outside's all rubbery and tough. Maybe that's because it insulates the jellyfish's
insides from getting zapped by electricity. Right. I'm going inside of this jellyfish's
interior cavity. See if what's in there tastes any better. To do that. To feldspar. Do not eat
this even if you are dying. It would be too sad if this is the last thing you ever ate in this life.
I guess these jellyfish are only useful for insulation from electricity. Again, do not eat.
All right. Watch the fuel. My O2 is going down too. All right. Let's keep going around here.
What else is here? I'm not gonna eat it. He specifically said he specifically made a journal
to say don't eat this. Is that the only thing that's down here? Is that it? That's way too far away.
Any signals? I thought I was over here. There's too many musical instruments being played.
This way? Where can I go? Up? Should I go up and out or in or around or I don't know?
What's up here? Is this where I came from? Is there any other way to go?
Doesn't look like it. I don't think there's anywhere else for me to go here.
We just got to see the jellyfish. What about this way? Behind the jellyfish.
Nothing. We'll go back here. All the way to the end. Down here. Kind of. What's down here?
Well, this is beautiful. What's that? I'm all right. I'm okay. I'm okay. I'm okay.
I just am a little disoriented. What's in here? I'm gonna go this way. Out there. That's what I want.
Go on one of the ends. Right up here. This is what I want.
Got to be something on here, right? Like on one of the ends. Come on. Nothing? No way. There's
got to be like a note up here. Look. This is like these flat surfaces. How do I go down? How do I
go down? What is this? It's trash? What is this? What the hell is this? It's like an eclipse. What
is this place? Is there oxygen on this? Holy shit. Oh my god. Oh. Oh. Okay. Um. There's no oxygen on
this planet? Turn. Turn. Turn. Turn. Turn. Where's the oxygen? No. No. There's a tree right there. I
can see the tree. What? That's like seriously. I can't. Tree? Right? No. There's a tree right here.
Tree. I got a stone. Is there oxygen? No. No. No. I thought there was gonna be one over here
in the corner. Well, I made a lot of progress there. Let's go take a look at the Quest Trapper.
There it is again. Quest. Quest. Quest. Quest. Quest accepted. Quest accepted. Got it. Now.
Frozen jellyfish. Uh oh. We've reached the dead end.
Hold on to me. Hey. I hear you're leaving to see adventure. Um. How do I? Didn't, didn't he say tell
everybody? Who do I talk to? The guy in the observatory? And that thing, that thing's
gonna consume the planet. I need to tell people about it? You. I got some news. Um. Not you
apparently. Who do I tell this to? Gotta be the guy that help, Helford or something. Whatever his
names, right? All right. I'm going up. Gonna go there from here. I was holding A. Whatever.
Good run. Okay. I'm actually surprised you can die by that. Imagine seeing that. That guy must
have just watched the most heinous, awful, just person being crushed, squished right next to him.
That person. Let's go to the observatory. Right over here. I gotta make this jump or I'm gonna be
really upset. Okay. Unidentified signal. Okay. We gotta talk to um. Somebody in here, right?
Where is he? Not even here anymore. Where is this guy? Well, there's nobody. I can't. I need to
tell somebody about the. Maybe I should tell the guy down there? All right. I'm gonna tell the guy
that has the mining axe. All right. Get me the hell out of here. Wait. Hey. That you opened its
eyes but you wish you'd seen that happen, huh? Sign me too. Not even a little closer to understanding
what's going on with the statue. Was there something that you needed? Yes. I found Feldspar
and they're in dark bramble stars above. This is wonderful news. Thank you. Thank you for finding
them. That Feldspar didn't immediately join you on your ship and return here is incredibly Feldspar
of them. Never entirely sure what Feldspar was thinking back then either. So we gotta fish them
out of that dreadful place with all haste. I'll radio Gosson and have them prepare a ship. It
really should be Gosson who brings Feldspar home. Thank you. You can hardly imagine how profoundly
happy I am to hear that they're alive and unharmed. Appearance on hourglass twins.
Ryback is on brittle hollow and Gabbo is on giant steve. All right. Yeah. But what about the
thing that's taken over the world? All right. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. I'm excited. Does nobody care
about this? All right. I gotta get back. I'm gonna talk to the guy that's looking at me.
Let me get in there. Eyes itching like crazy right now. I hope I don't die.
Okay. We're good. I really need to go to the bathroom, but I don't want to stop watching.
You go to twitch.tv slash germa985 on your phone. What a sellout. Selling up my own stream.
All right. I gotta go talk to this guy. This is not even. Hold on. What the hell is this?
That looks cool. All right. Where's the, uh, I gotta go in here. Is this, this is not even right.
Where's the, oh, okay. Where's the guy? Where's the dude doing the, where is he?
Okay. There it is. Jesus. Oh, inside my ears are itching. Ow. All right. You can't, you can't,
I need somebody like a designated face scratcher to play this game. Hey, listen to me. Is that a
dark bramble seed? It is. Yes. Don't I have info? Well, fuck this place then. Nobody cares.
All right. What we got? We have some loose ends. What's, what is this?
Giants deep. All right. We're going to go to giants deep. I've never been there.
Giants deep. Oh, there, there's our Vroomie autopilot is freaking out right now. I'm
not entirely sure why. Okay. We're good. Wait, I have been here. Wasn't this the, this is where
it just was? It is. Okay. Is there a good place to land this? A little landing pad right here.
It's convenient. Oh, nice. Oh, get off. All right. The clue was he was here somewhere.
All right. This place is like super gravity. I'm going to sneeze. Oh, I'm one to, is that a
jellyfish? Oh, wait, something over here. Oh, it's one of those things. All right. Cool. Let's go.
How do I swim down? Get out of the water. This is my greatest fear. Can I go in this? What happens
if I go in here? I'm going to go in, I'm going to go in the tornado. Let's see what happens.
Why can't I swim down? I just keep bobbing out of the water. I can't swim down.
Okay. Well, this is getting me nowhere. I can barely move in this water.
I'm just dolphin-ing out of the water. I, I, why?
This shit just got absolutely thrown into the atmosphere. All right. Well, do it to me too.
Do it to me. Do it to me. Do it to me. Wait, falling? What? You gotta be fucking kidding me.
Fuck you game. I did, the gravity was that strong? Okay. Ah, I didn't even,
could even hit me. That didn't look like it hit me. I'm not getting out of the ship ever again.
I'm only going to get out of the ship if it's absolutely necessary. Let's go water planet.
Come on. Wink. This game looks pretty neat. Left trigger goes onto water. I was holding
left trigger. All right. Here we go. I'm not getting out of the ship. What am I looking for
here? Something interesting, something weird, something cool, searching, yearning, wanting.
This looks pretty cool. Whatever it is, let's land. Oh yeah. Secret crystals. There's sacred
crystals over here. What just happened? What? Where? Um, isn't this part of the planet?
Isn't this part of the planet? All right. I'm confused. This is not part of the, this is the
planet. I, all right. I gotta get out. Look at this. Like something froze. I gotta go in there.
Can I get out of here or should I? Easy. All right. Get out, get out, get out, get out, unbuckle.
Get out. I want to see, I want to read this. It's like a, I thought that, okay. I thought this was
writing. I thought it was writing on the side. It's just sticking out. Ghost matter? What does
go? Wait, I remember that. Wait, we talked about that. Ghost matter. What's that mean?
Trees detected. How do I get up this? This water sucks. I gotta like land in it. I want to see the
ghost matter. Yep. I weigh like 6,000 pounds on this planet, apparently. Get on the surface.
Too much gravity. Okay. I can't get up there. I'm going to use my, my camera over there.
I'm going to shoot my camera over here. Oh damn. All right. I got to get over there.
I got to get over there. I got to get over there. What? Wait, wait. Hold on. What's this?
Freeze. Threat detected. What? Threat detected. What? What? Threat detected. Threat detected.
Ghost? What are you supposed to do about the ghosts? There's just ghosts in there.
Shit. I was on, I was right. I was, God, I was going down there. All right. We're going to a new
planet. I don't like that place. I have open mysteries in like three different places.
The negative time interval measured at the White Pole Station was further investigated at the high
energy lab in the canyon at Ember Twin's equator. Or, a man named Cully has mysteriously vanished
from a cave at the bottom of the dry lake that at Ember Twin's North Pole. And we're going back to
Ember Twin. There's one on this planet. Wait, there's one on this planet. Let's find it.
Looking for quantum. Quantum fluctuations. Oh, crash. Don't embarrass me. Am I stuck on a tree?
Wait, it's in the museum. Is it the one in the museum? Or is it somewhere, is it another one on
the planet? No, no, there's another one. Where is that? It's in the museum. But is it though?
It's one of the museum. Wait a minute. Hold up. Hold up. Hold up. Hold up. Hold up. Hold up. Hold
up. Hold up. Hold up. Hold up. Hold up. You say museum like an asshole. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. I
apologize. I am from a different part of the world as you. Sorry. Excuse me. I have a slight
accent from a different part of the world. Excuse me. Museum. Museum. Museum. Museum. Car. Museum.
My room. Why do you say room? Hey, why does he say room? Is it possible that he's from a different
part of the world than me? How is this possible? It's not even, it's not even possible to be from
a different part of the world that it's not. Okay. Where am I going? He's malding about mouth noises.
I gotta go to my room. What the fuck did you say? Sorry. My room. My room. My room. My room. My room.
That's an idiot. Got it. Get the fuck out of here. Get the fuck out of here. Get the fuck out of
here. Get the fuck out of here. I found it. Ghost matter. Ghost. What am I supposed to do about that?
Is there more? Oh man, there's more. Wait, hold on. Photo. Well, I didn't know you could do that.
Okay, it's right over here. Can I like collect that shit or is there, can I walk around it?
Is there anything to do over there? Wait, hold on. Is there any reason to be over this way?
There's nothing over here. I gotta go find that quantum, quantum beam. It's a fun word to say.
Quantum. I want to make a username now, rather than it being like German 985,
like German. No, no, no. It would be, it'd be fucking quantum conundrum.
What? Oh, there's a way. Where is this thing? Down here. All right, let's get back in them.
I was gonna say, I know I say both every time, but wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
there's too much to see. I can't play this game. I can't do it. I can't do it.
Now it's too many things to look at. Let's take somebody like the things to touch and look at and
press. I can't play this game. It's down here, but I'm gonna just go this way. It's down in,
inside the earth. Let's go this way. See if I can find it. Okay. I can't play this game. I'm gonna,
I'm going home. I'm out. I'll see you guys in like a month. All right. I'm gonna have to play this
game for the next six months to find myself alone in like my room. Sorry, my room, my room,
my room, my room, my room, my room. This way. Is there a spot I can go in? See like a little
canyon. Ooh, there's a little canyon over here, guys. Okay, guys, we found a little canyon.
What's down here? Maybe. Okay, guys, we can go this way. Looks like we may have stumbled across
something here, guys. It's like it's in there somewhere. Okay, guys. All right, we did something.
Ah, how do I get in there? Down in the geyser or something? Let me just see what's up here.
Snow. All right. All right. Okay. This is icy. Oh, come on. I, I, come on. What? I was floating.
I was very trying to be very careful. Was I really going that fast? How fast was I going?
All right. I'm doing a quest, different quest, different quest. We're going to do, I don't know,
different. This game is good though. I like this game. I can see why people like this game.
It makes sense to me now. Okay. Quantum fluctuation. I'm going to go over here.
Let's check this side. All right. All right. Hold on. Unknown. Unknown. Here it is. It's in there.
All right. Everybody relax. Found it. Can I land this in here? Let's go. F.A. laugh. There it is.
Identified grove shard. All right. Now don't look at it. Okay. It changed. Where did it go?
How is it? I'll give you privacy. Now, where'd you go? Only two places? All right. Let's go update
this. It's that one. It's a strange rock shard in this grove that moves when I'm not watching it.
It's a signal on the quantum fluctuations frequency. What about here? I'm looking at
something. Giants deep. Quantum signal on Giants deep. Bottom of the dry lake bed at Ember Twin.
All right. I got to get to Giants. It's deep. Wait. What's down here?
Kurt saw a Gnomai shipwreck shooting a beam of light into the sky somewhere in Ember Twin's
southern hemisphere. All right. We got to go to the Ember Twin's thing. Let's go. So much shit there.
Ember Twins. So what are you guys doing for the Super Bowl? Super Bowl coming up.
Gonna eat some pizza. Wings. What are you guys doing? All right. Let's do it. Wait. Where you
going? Southern hemisphere. That's it right there. Where are you going? Wait. Oh, I was wrong. It's
over here. Who gives a shit? I mean, who gives a shit? Who gives a shit? I don't know. All right.
Which one should I go on? This thing is just going for me every time. What is this thing?
The interloper. What the fuck is this thing? I want to know what this is. No, I don't.
Focus. Where is the... Where do they go? The out... No. Where is it? Did they go there? All...
What? The Ember... Ember Twins. All right. Go. What just happened? Okay. We're on our way.
Wherever it is. Where is it? I don't even know if I'm up or down. I don't know if I'm up or down.
There we go. Ember Twins. Ember Twins. Ember Twins. Ember Twins. Not Ashton. Ember Twins. Ember Twins.
All right. Ember Twins. Let's land. Slow down a little. I gotta go to the southern hemisphere
here. It's really fucking fast, man. Slow down. Slow down. Slow down. Southern hemisphere.
Go. Get fucking hype. Let's go, guys. There? What are we looking for? Cave Shop. Cave Shop.
Okay. This is the southern hemisphere. There, somewhere. Guys, why are you not getting hype?
Fucking... I'm gonna get... I'm gonna actually get furious in a minute. I'm not seeing enough
fucking people in this chat say a ton of fucking shit. Like, what the fuck?
Okay, so here's another one. The planets are aligned. This planet sometimes, and only sometimes,
has a moon. It's also of note. It disappears if no one's watching it. Isn't that a fascinating
orbital characteristic? It's my first time encountering a natural satellite with the
ability to vanish when not being watched. Just study it. Or even better, we should travel there.
I agree. Our first step would be determining a method to track this phantom moon so we can always
know where it is. Given its reluctance to move while consciously observed, it might be a form of
macroscopic quantum mechanics. Cool. Found your note, Malore. Kindly count me among this moon's
admirers. What is happening when it disappears? Has it moved to another location? I believe so.
Not only does the moon appear around brutal hollow, I can confirm it sometimes orbits
timber hearth as well. All right, that's pretty cool, man. All right, I don't want this moon.
Freeze detected. Oh, it's a campfire. Church research note. Property of church. Clearly the
Nomai were making astronomical observations here. They chose an excellent spot. This is a big
rotating device board. What was it the Nomai were observing? I'd post it. There's something special
about the orange symbol on that device. Al and the new astronaut's translator tool would be nice
to handy have right now. It'd be cool if you had it. They didn't, never mind. I need a spot to put this
down there. Oh, there's a big beam. God damn it, Jerma. Why are you still playing this fucking game?
I thought I was gonna just, just to make you angry. I knew you were gonna be here when you came in
and I was like, hold on. Shit, we're pretty quiet. I'm gonna make this guy, I'm just,
we'll only make this guy angry. Already holding. Where's the little, what's the slot? There's usually
a slot. Did I miss it over here? There's like an empty triangle I usually can put this in.
What is going on? Am I missing something here? I don't get it. Was there a slot I could have put
this? Wait, what do you, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. This is, wait, I can take this out and
put this in. This is the first time I've ever done that. I didn't know you'd do that. I didn't know
this is, I had other text on it. I thought this was, I thought this was written on this wall.
I didn't know you could do that. Quantum moon locator is functioning. We have markers for each
of the places the moon goes. Observe the quantum moon in orbit around dark bramble. Okay. You've
keen eyes, my friends. This moon travels to a total of five locations. Jerma, it was cool to meet you
at McDonald's the other day. We didn't do that. Five locations, not four. Added a marker for dark
bramble. I thought the locator now accounted for all the phantom moon's locations, but sometimes
the locator can't tell where the moon is. Perhaps there's a problem with the device.
It's also possible there's a sixth place in the star system where the phantom moon travels.
I mean, it's one, two, they line up like this. So where's the one that was the last one? How many
would you have? One, two, three, four, five. You don't have this right. Okay. Hold on. These are
always there. This one's freaking out. These two are always in the case of one, two, three are
always there. This one, what's this one tracking? That's tracking dark bramble. All right. This is
the one that I have to be looking at it. There it is. Right. I gotta go there. I gotta go there.
I gotta go there. What the hell is that though? I gotta go there. Fuck. How do I wait? No, wait.
Where'd it go? No, where'd it go? I should, I should have. Right, here it goes.
Ah, there it is. Here's what I have to do. I gotta get in the ship. Let's get a wafer to orbit
somewhere and then go to where it is. It should be there for a little while. It appears when you
look at it. I had it. I had it too. I was looking at it. I had it too. It's invisible right now,
but it's right here. You won't be able to get in the ship without it moving.
I just can't look at it for a second. I have to wait till it comes behind me.
Orbiting around. Is it that? Right now it's orbiting around. Okay, here it goes.
It's changing to orbit around. Where are you going? Okay, you back on the hearth. Where?
Wrong strategy. I don't know. Right there. On it. All right, it's right there. All right, so how do
I keep looking at this so I keep staying at it? It's right there. All right, I know what I'm gonna
do. All right, here we go. I'm gonna go to this planet and I'm gonna hang out out here until it
comes over this way. All right, I'm going to whatever this... I don't know what that planet's
called. I'm going there. All right, I'm going there. I'm going there. I'm going there. That's
where I'm going. What's this place called? Brittle Hollow. I'm going to Brittle Hollow. I'm gonna go
to Brittle Hollow and I'm gonna... I don't think I can lock it in or anything. It's gone. Yeah,
it just it jumps from planet to planet. Unless there's some way I have to keep it in focus
or something. I'm gonna say that... I know what it looks like. I'm almost dead. I'm gonna die.
I'm gonna die. I need to go to my ship right now. All right, I'm gonna go to Brittle Hollow
and I'm gonna just chill. I'm gonna wait. I'm gonna wait till it orbits. I think maybe... Let's put
this data in here. A quantum moon locator. Quantum moon. Sixth location. I know my hypothesis that
the quantum moon might be a form of macroscopic quantum mechanics. Quantum moon travels to a
total of five locations. That's not true. Quantum moon sometimes disappears possibly to an unknown
sixth location. Disappear when no one was watching. I'm just gonna see if that works.
I'm just gonna see if it appears eventually. If I just chill. Am I getting too close to the sun?
Oh no. Oh no. We're good. Okay. We're good. All right. Looking for a moon now. Slow down. Going way too
fucking fast. Way too fast. All right. I need my fluctuations. I'm just gonna... There it is.
Right there. There it is. I found it. Why is it so far away? No, that's not it. That's not it. When is
it gonna orbit? Where is it? I need to be looking at it or something. Follows lantern. There it is.
No. What? That's not it. Is that it? I don't think so. Where is... What if... Okay. What if I go
and look at it? And then just in the ship look at it? And it has to travel to one of these
locations, right? It has to. It's got to appear here eventually. Where is the moon? Where is it?
Hold on. Easy. Easy. Easy. Easy. Easy. All right. I got an idea. I got an idea. My idea didn't work.
Wait. Wait a minute. I have an idea. Okay. Here's my idea. Go back on the planet with and go back
on the planet and listen to this shit. Back on the planet with things spinning around. You can
actually see the thing. Take a picture of it when you... What the fuck was that? Did I avoid it?
Get it in the spot that I want it and take a photo of it. Keep the photo up and then
it'll be there. It's just as long as somebody's looking at it. It's as long as there's a photo
of it or something, right? That's what I think I gotta do. The camera would technically be looking
at the moon the whole time. Technically. Let me try that. Let's go. He's reading a guide?
What? I'm not reading a guide. Why would I do that? You should fuck up though, man. You can get me
in trouble. All right. I know what to do. Let's go back to the ember place. That's definitely what
you have to do. All right. Judging by the last weird thing that I had to do. Remember when I
had to... What did I have to do that was kind of like that before? I had to do... There's something
I had to do like that before. I was eating marshmallows. No. It was different. It was
something else. Game boomers cheating streamer. All right. That's what I'm gonna do.
Give it a whirl. Is that it? Is this it? Is that it? Is this it? This is it. That's it.
This is it, right? All right. Slow down. This is it. Is this it? Ooh. This is it. All right. I'm on
the secret moon. Secret moon. I'm on secret moon. Let's go. Before it disappears. This is it, right?
Is it? Wait. Is that it? Wait. That's it. It's that one. It's that one. It's that one. It's that one.
It's that one. It's that one. No, no, no. Don't get it. Don't get it out of my sight. I have to
take a picture of it. I have to take a photo of it. Take a photo of it. Okay. Right? Did I get it?
Okay. I got a picture of it. Okay. I got a photo of it. Let's go. All right. Now, don't put the
camera down. Okay. Where is it? Is that it? All right. Does this work?
Okay. Slow down. Slow down. Slow down. Where is it? Is that it?
What? Where is it? I need my quantum fluctuations. Where is it? What's going on?
I don't know which direction I'm facing. Okay. There it is. No, that's not it. Where is it?
Is that it? No. Where is it? Wait. Hold on. Look at the photo. I was in a perfect spot. I was...
Okay. Let me try to redo that. I'm going to stay in the ship. I'm going to stay in the ship
because remember... What are you doing? Why is autopilot flying in the fucking sun?
Good last words. I just imagine like three or four people sitting around eating dinner
with autopilot on. That's the reason why the fucking driverless cars ain't ever going to work.
This cabbage is absolutely fantastic, dear. Thank you, honey. Yeah. But any news? Yeah. We
actually... Why is my game stuck? Oh, my daughter of mine. How's school? It's going great, dad.
What do you think about the snake, honey? It's so good, mom. You're the best.
Yeah, she sure is. What a happy fucking family we have. That's it. I'll do the dishes tonight.
Let me go over here. Honey, why is autopilot flying into the sun? Boom. God damn it. All right. Back
to where it was. It was right here, right? And then I'm going to stay in the ship. Yeah, I freaked
out. All right. I have a... I can take a picture. Wait, is it? Hold on. Hold on. Wait. I'm going to
do the exact same fucking thing I did. There's no cabbage in space. Oh, please.
Please. My apologies. All right. Don't fucking crash. Don't crash. Okay. I freaked out here
because I was like, oh, this is it. And then I saw it. Where did I see it? It was like
right here somewhere. I'll wait till I can see it. And then I'm going to look
for it. It's going to port over here eventually. Don't break. Come on. Where is it? Because I had
it too. I had it. Actually had the damn thing. It... All right. Take a picture of it. Quick.
Slow down. Slow down. Slow, slow, slow, slow. Take a picture of it. Quick.
Now what? Can I land on this or something? What am I supposed to do? I'm in. I made it.
I found the quantum moon and there's some fucked up shit going on over here. Wait, where'd it go?
What? Okay. Was I almost about to get squished in the elevator? Was I actually about to die to that?
That would have been so embarrassing. I would have ended the stream. Okay. Turn the lights on.
Okay. So we have some translation here. You have recalled the rule of quantum imaging.
Recall the rule of quantum entanglement. Recall the rule of the sixth location.
Eh. Tell me the rule of higher pay grade than me is going to have to come figure this one out.
Have to move these or something? All right. I remember seeing this image on... Okay. These
are just the planets. But this is currently set onto the twin embers, right? Ember moon,
ember planet, and ash planet. So why is that on there right now? Why is that there? These are
just the... Okay. There's like the bramble. There's whatever that is. What locations are these? Okay.
I don't know. I can't move this. What does this shit say? You recall the rule of quantum imaging.
Quantum entanglement. Sixth location. I don't know what the sixth location is.
Let me explore this place a little more. What's this? That's not mine. That's a different ship.
Whose ship is this? That's not my ship. What is this? I'm here after watching it wander the
skies for so long. I'm about to stand on the quantum moon. As expected, my shuttle has landed
at the moon's south pole. I will make the remainder of my journey on foot. If you don't know why the
quantum moon always welcomes its visitors at the south pole, just that this is true. As a child,
I considered such unknowns sinister. Now, though, I understand they bear no ill will. The universe is,
and we are. I am ready. Shit. I'm here. Where is here? This is that ship room before. I don't...
I think I might be in trouble here. Look, just jump on a cactus. Well, I got a lot of info.
All right. Can I make it? Let's try.
The ultimate fall joke. It's gonna last 10 straight minutes. Actually, I might get there.
No, I'll get there. I'm gonna get there. I'm never... Somebody said I'm never gonna beat this.
I think I've made pretty good progress so far. I found the secret moon. I found the Cadbury egg.
Where is my... What is my ship doing over here? Wait, what? Wait. Wait. Why is it floating? I
thought it was on the moon. What? See you, nerd. God damn it. Just watch the fireworks when the
universe ends. I'm gonna be pretty far away. Wait a minute. Hold on. Wait, what is that photo of?
How did it get up there? I just want to see it one more time. No, I just want to see it one more
time before I die. You're not leading it enough. That's too far away.
So what did I... That thing teleported me back to... I pressed the wrong button or something?
All right. Let me... I gotta go see.
There we go. Boom. Go. There it is. There it goes. Whatever it is. Okay. Let's go take a look at the
data. Data. What we got? You found the quantum moon. You found the quantum shrine. You found
the quantum shuttle. You found the gravity cannon. I recalled a Nomai shuttle from the quantum moon.
A Nomai named Solanum landed at her shuttle at the quantum moon's south pole and prepared to make
the rest of the journey on foot. Visitors to the quantum moon always arrive at the south pole for
reasons unknown. The quantum moon sometimes disappears possibly to an unknown sixth location.
Nomai detected a quantum signal coming from somewhere on Giants deep.
Where's the quantum McDonald's? That's pretty good.
Okay. I'm gonna go do this. This is red for some reason and I glazed over this.
Ember Twin. Southern hemisphere. Let's go. All right. If you went up this quickly,
would your stomach go into your esophagus? Probably would. This one. Your brain would go into your
stomach. What the fuck, man? Why are you doing this to me? It's trying to kill me. It's trying
to kill me. Autopilot again. Just use autopilot, Jerma. It's easier. It won't magnetize you into
the sun. What a depressing replay. That's the kind of replay where you accidentally
recorded on the PS4 for five seconds. Ten seconds, you're like, how the fuck did I do that?
This is me sitting at the menu. Auto pilot. Not yet. Wait till I get to a safe place.
Okay. Engaging autopilot. No, don't do that. Stop. Turn it off. It's gonna go right in the fucking sun.
All right. Get on here. Land this thing. And there's the beacon of light right there.
Jesus Christ. Where am I? I thought I did it right. I thought I did it right.
I was going too fast. Autopilot. Okay. I'm good. Oh, Christ. Where's that thing coming from?
Where's that beacon? There's a light beacon. Where is it? Where is it? Where is it? There it is.
Oh, that's different. What's that? Oh, look at that. All right. Land. Good. Get me the hell
out of here. Oh, find signal nearby. Frequency. Oh, is it one of these things? Escape pod.
Distress beacon. Escape pod. What happened? We need status reports for all systems.
The initial things first. Is everyone unharmed? Our escape pods passengers are afraid.
They're physically well. Inanna, everyone survived the crash. This is a relief at least.
You have my gratitude. Burr, we were able to find the other escape pods distress signals.
I can hear both signals somewhere in this star system, but I don't believe either escape pod
crashed on the same planet as us.
What is this? Too close to read. Launching escape pod three. Now launching escape pod two.
Collision imminent. Preparing for impact. Scanning external environment. Scan complete.
External temperature is prohibitively high. Verdict inhospitable. Do not seek shelter on
this planet. Escape pod two. Vessel has been mortally injured. Emergency sequence
activated. Awaiting departure from vessel. All right, so it hurt. All right, somebody got hurt.
Beat from the star system sun is more bearable below the surface. When our escape pod punctured
this planet's surface, it broke into what scans show is a cave system with much cooler air.
I would recommend we seek a site down there to build a long-term shelter.
Inanna, but these passages are a maze. Even with this danger, they are still our best chance for
survival. We'll form teams and descend into the caves to look for shelter. We can mark our findings
on the walls to avoid becoming irreversibly lost. Be cautious everyone and be aware of the sand as
you search. It appears to be rising gradually. There's a lot of writings down here. Put it away.
What's this? Emergency escape hatch. We have found an enormous cavern at the end of this passage
that appears promising. I believe we could construct long-term shelter there. Cavern
Malorre found. It's a wise choice for shelter. Could be... could one of you
mark directions for the others to follow? This is the start of the path to the shelter site.
I've left directions to guide you there. Of note, we must hurry as the pathway there is filling with
sand. Do not allow yourself to be buried by sand and make sure no one is lost.
Let's read everything. Do not follow this tunnel to its end.
Holius and I will examine the horror that lies in its terminus later. Why did we live through this?
We'll go down there. Keep moving, friends. There's nothing of interest at the end of this passage
but rocks. And while these rocks are interesting, they can wait until a less urgent time.
All right, what about over here? No, this passage leads to breathable air. Refill your supply tank
there. Cannot tell you how far or deep these tunnels may wind. Do not linger as the area is
exposed to the heat of this alien sun. All right, let's refill. Refill your air supply tank and
return quickly. Is there anything else out here? That's cool. There's something bad at the end of
this tunnel. Do I dare do this? I said don't do this. I don't get it. Why? Well, I can't go down
here anyway. I can't like go through here. Well, I'm gonna go down the path. Let's get oxygen first.
Which way is oxygen? This way, right? Which way? This way? That way? This way? There's oxygen.
Over here? This way? This way? Totally oxygen. Let's go down the path and see what we find.
Let's go. All right, watch out for the sand. Then move quickly because the sand is filling up.
Okay, over here. Watch out for the sand. All right, there's a spot over here. All right, guys,
I've gotten rings in Dark Souls that were harder than this. The path to the shelter site is somewhat
convoluted, so follow the instructions ahead closely. I wasn't making a joke. I'm just being
real. I mean, you do this in Dark Souls 2 to get shit, you know? Just saying.
Uh, reach the shelter site. Walk forward until you meet the sandfall at the pit.
Then turn left. Continue to the room filled with rock column formations and climb upward through
the opening above them. Sand here is rising, so you must be cautious with the swift. Forward
till you meet the sandfall. Forward until the pit. Turn left. Continue the room with rocks. Go up.
Sand pit left. Rocks. Rocks. Then go up. Go up. Are there any more instructions?
There we go. Be cautious crossing the chasm ahead. The bridge Malore and I crafted will do its job,
but it isn't strong. Oh, shit. Once on the far side, look for the tunnel hidden behind the falling
sand. Follow it and you'll reach the shelter. Can I walk on this shit? I just jump and...
Okay, now go behind the sand. Can I go, can I get back? Can I go behind this? Can I go behind that?
Does it go behind the sand? Is that gonna hurt me? Is that gonna kill me? Is it gonna kill me?
Holy fuck, I made it. I thought it was gonna kill me. You're doing well. There's only a little
farther left to go now until you reach the shelter site. You can rest there. Hurry before the sand
comes. Up there? How the hell did they make it up there? They built a shitty bridge there?
There? Sand's coming. Sand's coming. Sand's coming. Sand's coming. Sand's coming. Sand's coming.
Sand's coming. Sand's coming. Sand's coming. Sand's coming. Sand's coming.
Open the door. Up? Which way? What is this? Hold on. Wait, what about up here? This is amazing.
Look inside the cave. How did this come to rest here? We haven't encountered others in this cave.
I think this is a rare find. From what we can see, Coleus and I believe the specimen must be very
old indeed. Imagine what we might learn if we could examine it. If we both agree it's unlikely
this dry planet is this horrors place of origin, especially considering what we observed during
the vessel's evacuation. Clearly this hole is too small for it to fit through. Hypothesis,
there's another entrance to this cave. If there is, Coleus and I will find it. We can't leave
valuable information undiscovered. Update. We need to find a way inside quickly.
Melore, because when I have returned here to search for an entrance to the cave there were
children playing on the specimen. I didn't need that info. Okay, well. All right, I don't want
to fall anywhere so I gotta be careful. I can't see shit. How about over? Hold on. Anglerfish
fossil overlook. Three? What? Only three minutes of oxygen. Hold on. What is this? Hold on.
What's this shit over here? Oxygen? Nope. There's shit over here. There's stuff over here.
Um, I'm not sure exactly what I'm looking for. It's blind. I mean, I have tunnel vision right
now. I'm looking for a flashlight. How do I get in there? Holy fucking shit. I've got to get out
of here right now. How do I get out? How do I get out? Oh my god. Oh my god. Oh my god.
How do I get out of this? How do I get out of here? What the fuck? Hey, should we build a
sun station to the power of this Ash project? Are there any ways to generate this level of power?
Theoretically, as per our act, we know we can't imagine discovering anything like that.
I understand this proposal is not simple, but the sun station must be built if we hope to
complete the Ashman project. I almost can't comprehend this being the suggestion. So the
purpose of the sun station goes against every standard we hold ourselves to and everything
we believe. Unsurprisingly, I disagree if we're pushing a possible new technology further than
ever before. That, in my experience, is the defining characteristic of our species.
If we fail, and the probability of this is insignificant, we will without question destroy
ourselves. All life here and the rest of the star system I wish to protect these species.
The potential annihilation of an entire star system is too severe a cost. We shouldn't build
the sun station no matter how badly we want the knowledge that comes with it. Fear of failure is
a poor reason not to try. I believe, with curiosity, the sun station will be a work.
I'm deeply honored. I comprehend your position, however, if we aren't all but certain the sun
station will not cause destruction, once we build it then I won't support the station's use.
Sunless City. Anglerfish Fossil. Sun Station. You know my debate of building a sun station
in order to power the Ash Twin Project. Canyon at Ember Twin's Equator. Canyon at Ember Twin's Equator.
What are you doing? Well, it's full of sand now, so I don't think I can do much. I don't think I can
do anything else here. It's getting close. That thing's dumping sand. That's the other,
right, okay. So I have to go, I have to turn that sand off. I don't know. It's taking over
the whole planet. Wait, look at it. Where is it? Is that gonna keep going? Yeah, yeah, I'm dead.
Yeah, I'm dead. I'm just dead. All right, now for the next time, I know this is sad. I'm gonna go to
the, yeah, I'm just gonna bump my head a bunch more times. I'll be fine. Yeah, I mean, three
minutes remaining. Uh, actually, I might be able to get there. I wonder, should I fly to that planet?
Can I land on this? I wonder if I can actually get on top. I'll probably put your seatbelt on.
I haven't even looked at this yet. Hey, I remember this. I'm going in here. It's huge.
I mean, what's the purpose of this? The sun hungers. Uh, I think we're dead. What's the
significance of this place? Bye, everybody. Got it. Unreal Tournament map. So it's safe to say he
knows about the supernova now. Yeah, yeah, I'd say that's a pretty safe assessment. There it goes
again. I kind of want to investigate what that is. You know what I mean? I want to go just, I want
to go up there. That thing, I'm going up there. I want to know what that is. This thing keeps
exploding every time I die. Why? What's the point? Well, this is unknown. What's this unknown
signal? I can't slow down. Is it the ship itself doing that? No, it's something on that planet,
but I still want to know what this is. I'm going to hit the surface of this planet.
Oh, something in there. All right, something in there. It's going too fast. Wait, can I get
in there close? Where did it go? Where is it? What? What is going on? So we're getting sucked
into the gravity. Okay. Get over here. All right, there it is. Land on it. Land on it. I landed.
Did I? What's wrong? What happened? What? Uh, how did I? I didn't put the suit on. I, yeah, whatever.
And it took me so long to get there too. Well, look, it happened again.
I thought you were making that choking sound. I thought there was something in that hole
making that choking sound. All right, where is it? How come I can't see it?
Is it behind the moon thing? Whatever this is. There you go.
Come here. I screwed up this time. All right, let's check this place out. Damn it. My microphone's
been delayed by 650 milliseconds the whole stream because we played Xbox 360 yesterday.
You knew from the start. Let's do the whole stream again. God, I hate when that shit happens.
This capturing the 360, you have to delay your voice because it takes like almost a whole second
for the capture card to pull it into OBS. God damn it. Well, I found this. It wasn't that
noticeable. Well, it was definitely noticeable when I was just being missed by asteroids and
screaming almost a false second later. Here comes the asteroid. Oh, it just passed. Oh,
probe tracking module. I thought you were just slow. Like my brain. Sorry guys. Oh, that was
scary. Oh shit. Control module. Launch module. This thing. Fucking pea brain. Shatters through
the glass. All right. What should I go into? I'm going to go over here. All right. So this is,
I'm going to put this thing back together. I don't get it. I don't get it. It's different.
I have bad news. Yaro says there was a problem with the proposed power source.
So the orbital probe cannon won't be asked to fire. I hope you're pulling my locomotive limb here.
I wish I were my friend, but no, they aren't certain they can fix the problem. So the
orbitable probe cannon is on indefinite hiatus. Tell Privet and Malo, oh, they should return from
the cannon. My spouse and I were made at the construction yard for now. An update. Malo and
I will join you in Daz. Privet left to visit her brother. She fears Aidea may feel responsible.
Construction yard? What about this one? Does this one do anything for us?
Uh, can I read that? Well, we got some info. I guess we got some info. Okay, info. Got it.
It's been around back to where we were. This can go all the way.
I guess I'm going to put the marble through. You go down? What is that? Uh, that's a device
of some sort. With randomly selected probe trajectory, gravity field activated.
Five minutes 54 seconds ago, request to launch probe received from Ash Twin project.
Do the other one. So that's the cannon. Any more knowledge? Probe apart, as it didn't work.
Begin launch log. Orbital probe cannon. Launch request received. Probe launch successful.
Probe tracking module is receiving data from probe.
Orbital probe cannon structure compromised during launch. Damage to multiple modules detected.
Orbital probe cannon damage report. Severe structural stress detected.
Accessing damage to modules.
Probe module intact. No structural damage. Launch module. Viewport window fractured.
Module exposed to vacuum of space. Probe tracking module missing.
So wait, so this thing explodes every time I wake up and something shoots out of it.
Maybe I should follow that thing. I just try to chase that thing down? What just happened?
Well, my better 50%. The SAVA is sending the last of the cannon components soon.
Relatively speaking, we'll know the eye's precise location.
SAVA tells me he and the construction yard crew have determined a power setting we are not
under any circumstances to go above. I see. And am I right to think that consequently we'll
be ignoring that setting? Stupid. I can posit with nearly 100% certainty our friends have
accounted for our nature so I suggest we do. Giving the orbital probe cannon all the power
it can structurally withstand creates the greatest chance of finding the eye of the universe.
Yes, the probe must travel as fast as it can. As far as it can, I'll make some adjustments.
The thought of concluding our elders' curious and challenging search increases my heart's
temperature. My love. They're trying to find the center of the universe. They found it. They
went too deep. Caused a fucking time paradox and now I have to fix that. I have to be the one that
fucking closes the time loop because they screwed it all up. Because they shot whatever they shot.
What was that? Oh, these things I played on. All right, I'm going to the other module.
Really, I'm having a lot of fun playing the game. Get out of town.
Probe tracking. I don't think it exists anymore. I think it's broken. In fact,
I don't think this is a good idea, but I'm going to do it anyways.
The module is gone. Who would have thought? What about over here? This is where it fires from.
All right, is there something I missed in here? There's another section I could go in, right?
It's tracking this launching. And what was this one? This one I just came from?
Control module. It's this one up here. It's the one I had to go into, right? For a second,
I thought that was a probe module and I was like, what did I just find? Did I go in this one? No,
I can't. This is blocked off too. All right, nothing in here anymore. Wait, wait. All right,
I'm getting it out of here. I went in all the modules, right? But for this one, I'm kind of
getting turned around on the other side. Yeah, I need fuel. I got to go to the ship.
Okay, um, oh god, I'm just stretching my back a little. Should I stay? Let me try going that
other side. So I got to fire on the moon. So I got to go around. I go from here and just fly
it down here, right? I need to go in the window. Is this the right side? Where was that window?
Where was that correct window with the scout there? Oh yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Yeah.
What's in here? More stuff. Okay. Imagine, Privet, the probe tracking module will be the first to
know the coordinates of the eye of the universe. You'll be the first to see them. Honored and
terrified. You won't ask the orbital probe cannon to use so much power that it breaks, will you?
Right? Not my nervous friend. We only need to fire the probe once. Anyway, so who minds if it
compromises the cannon's structural integrity? I would mind, Malo. I would mind because we won't
be capable of receiving our probe's data if the probe tracking module is destroyed.
Dummy. Oh, there's one floating. That's the statue. Okay. That was weird. Let's grab the other one.
What is this one? Let's try this one. What is that? What is that thing? I don't know. Let's go see
what they say. It's the other room. Malo, my better 50% cassava is sending the last of the
cannon components soon. We'll know the eye's location. Yeah. Didn't I already do this?
Yeah, yeah, yeah. Our elders curiosity. Construction yard, groove, a power setting.
Didn't I already do this? Percent certainty. Yeah, I did this already. Okay. It's the other side.
Can I do anything over here? Are you reading somebody else's DMs? Well, what else is there
to do in here? Besides this stuff. All right. I need to put this data in and see what the hell
I'm going to do next. I need to find this construction yard. I just broke my neck. I just
shattered my fucking all my vertebrae in the top. All right, I made it out. Now let's go to the
ship. This data that I thought I was gonna get crushed. Input the data. I got a lot of it.
What do we got now? Probe cannon, tracking module, control module, construction yard.
You know, I built the orbit probe cannon at a construction yard on giants deep.
All right. I know where we're going. Question. No spoilers. But how far into the game am I
currently right now? Are we yet? Like, how far? Like percentage wise? And we're around 30 to 40%
35% 35. Okay. All right. 25 30% 25%. Okay. Just making sure that I don't go too far. So this
because I want to stream this tomorrow too. I just exploded. All right. We want to go to that.
What was it called? Giants? Giants deep, right? That's right there. All right. So we're gonna
find this construction yard. This planet that's all water. Construction yard. Navigate this
construction yard. No, but I mean, it looks like there's something. Hold on.
I'm gonna land here. Have I been here before? I don't remember if I've been here before.
What is happening? This is in this part of the planet. What the fuck am I?
There's a landing pad. The landing pad doesn't solve the problem of the whole island getting
picked up and thrown into space. I'll park damn thing on the pad. Hold on. All right. I'm in the
pad. This whole thing can get picked up and get thrown into space. Is this a construction yard?
Am I getting a jetpack tutorial booster? Okay. Oh my god. I'm so embarrassed because it's like
popped up on the screen and fucked with my head. I'm so actually embarrassed right now.
I'm annoyed by that. I can't believe it. It popped up on the screen. I was like, why is it showing
this? I've done this a hundred times. Yes. Hold. RT. Hold. Yes. Guys. Guys. I don't know why.
I don't understand why I'm doing that. I don't get it. I don't understand. I've done this
a thousand times. I've jumped like 50 fucking gaps. Is this text? Why is the text even on
the screen right now? Why is it doing this to me? Oh, it's the huge gravity. Right. I forgot. It's
the only planet that I've got. Oh my god. I forgot. This planet has like times 10 gravity.
The only one that does. Statue workshop. Ooh, that's broken. Can you get in? That was easy.
I'm going to jump over there. Block this way. Tree's detected. All right. Nice.
Destruction site. Oh, I've never seen this in my dream.
Text. We're going to test the memory statues tonight. Block says it could be dangerous,
so we can't. I'm dead. Well, what if we don't see the door and sneak the other way around?
We really want to see the test too, Liam, but that's a huge risk to take. We probably shouldn't
make flocks. Maybe flocks will let us test it later. Block specifically told us not to do that.
We're going to test the memory statues tonight. Be dangerous.
I only got the clue at least. Yeah. Memory statues.
Every time I tune in, you die. There it goes. All right. I'm going to go back there.
That's your workshop. That's your island. I energy lab. So these are going to connect eventually
here. That's your workshop leads to gabbro. Find steep to learn more about the statue.
That's your leads to here. You lead to statue island, which leads to the energy lab, which
leads to the station, which then leads to the sun station. And then the whole game is you've
completed the whole game. I'm going to head back there. The giant steep. I want to explore the
statue. Unknown. Still looking for whatever this is. The secret moon. Still have to go back there
and look at stuff. All right. Let's land. You didn't turn the stone off. Stove up. We're going
to space. Sorry. Back going so fast. I almost got dumped. Good. All right. Let's find where's
that little island again? Statue Island. That's right here. Slow down a little. That's actually
not it. Something else. Something else. I'm going to check it out. So many things to look at.
Here's the question. Let's go downstairs. Now this is what I saw in there. There's dead bodies
here. All right. The tornado is giants deep. That's that symbol. If you were holding this.
This is it. We finished building the final orbital probe cannon module and are ready to send it into
orbit around giant steep for assembly. The next step would be to send privet up to the orbit of
probe cannon to install the probe tracking system. All my friends here at the construction yard,
which is here, my gratitude for your tireless work. I've given up hope, but I truly believe
this cannon may actually succeed where many other attempts have not. I know my brother
Avans and his spells will want to launch the probe with as much power as possible and where the
cannon would break under the station. I propose we give Avans and Malo a slightly lower maximum
power setting than the absolute maximum possible to create room for their enthusiasm.
Not on the same page. Are you going gelatinous on us, love? I'm delighted by your words,
but they're atypical for you. Ever half as gooey as Malo and Avans behave together,
Daz. I mean, launch me from the orbital probe cannon. We know this is the construction yard.
That much is certain.
I don't like this. I want office to ride as soon as possible. What's happening? It's a twister.
I'm safe. You know, there's probably only, I get it. I get it somehow.
When you go up in the air, it's your opportunity to fly somewhere else you cannot get under any
of the circumstances. Long range probe successfully launched from the orbital probe cannon.
We've got bad news. Yaro says there was a problem with the proposed power source,
so the orbital probe cannon won't be asked to fire.
People following my locomotive ring? Yeah, this is the, we saw this.
Burned from the cannon. My spells never remain at the construction yard.
Wish I were my friend, but no, they certainly didn't do the problem.
Yeah, so this was where we have the building.
So another person's house. Yes, but we can do this. That brings us over here.
What is this? Why is it still picking up the guy from 12 million meters away doing the harmonica?
There's a crystal here as well. I could do that after this. All right, I'm gonna,
I'm gonna make the jump over here when we go up.
Right now, I could use this for a second. I could walk it. Yeah, I could just walk it, couldn't I?
I detected. Thanks for the oxygen. Can I make this jump on the other side?
Anything back there? There it is. Discs.
Now I gotta bring this disc out to the other side and play the movie.
I can have one of those somewhere around here. All right, bring it back to the other side.
Guys, let's go. Movie night.
How would I go through the water? I don't know. I did though, didn't I?
All right, new conversation. What is it?
Fire constructed a model of giants deep here at the Brittle Hollow's Southern Observatory.
And it reveals how an object might sink below the current.
I'm unable to grasp the answer by looking through the projection pool.
If I visit the observatory, would you kindly explain?
If you don't mind the trek beneath the surface to the south pole,
I'd be delighted to see you. The trailhead starts at Brittle Hollow's equator.
I don't know. You should have seen it.
We thought it was impossible for any cannon components to sink,
even for us to look below the current. But I sank straight to the core.
Interesting. This looks like that place I need to go.
Cool. All right. Well, now I got some data and now I'm going to move.
That's right. I'm going to go check that out. Walk across the top.
Let's do that. Cool. What is that? I think we're about to go in space.
Why is that active now? Why are these active?
Hold on a second. These are now activated.
Stasis machines? All right. I'm going back to the ship.
I don't know why I'm bringing this with me, but I guess I am.
The instruction here connects to the Southern Observatory,
which connects to ocean depths.
Not something to sink beneath the underwater current,
which they previously thought was impossible.
Southern Observatory. Brittle's Hollow's south pole.
The observatory, yeah, it's broken.
The model of giants deep that revealed how an object might sink below the strong current.
So I can't get in here. I have to go through the secret entrance.
There's all this shit down here too. Sun station.
They debated building a sun station. Wait a minute.
You built a station on the sun. Let's go look.
If you did, then you did, right? What's going on?
Why am I rotating? Okay. I finally escaped.
Sun station. Can I get close enough to the sun to find this?
I mean, I guess it looks like there's something right here.
Or is that just flames? This might just be flames.
I guess it just sucked me in. It just inhaled me.
It's going too fast.
Shit. We're going 300 meters a second and it didn't slow down.
I mean, I was holding the back button. I'm going to try. The sun is small now.
Let's try it now. Sun station.
I don't think there's anything on there. Maybe it's just barely off the surface.
Go to the sun at night when it's not hot. Yeah, you're right. That's not a bad idea.
That scared the fucking shit out of me. That scared the shit out of me.
What? Oh my God. There was no way in my brain that that was going to happen.
Okay. I mean, I don't see anything. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What's that?
What is that? Wait, wait, wait, wait. There's something orbiting.
What is that? What's that? Sun station?
That's going way too up. I can't land on that. Are you kidding me?
I'm on fire. You can and you will.
Where is it? Man, I'm trying to pull up. I'm sucked in. I'm trying to just like kind of float.
That's moving so fast. So I have to match that. It's super hard to land on it.
I'll try it one more time, but I'm not sure I'm going to be able to do that.
I'll give it a try. I have to be going with it, not against it.
At least I know where it is. Maybe I should just ditch the...
No, that's not going to work. Okay. There it is. I need to be going along with it.
We have to spin this way. I'm going to slow down and I'm going to be moving with the bad
things of orbit. I prefer to come back so I can tell what the hell it's doing.
Kerbal space program? No, I try to play Kerbal space program. I uninstall the game after 15 minutes.
There it is. All right. Am I going to start burning here? Yep. Oh, fuck. Up, up, up, up, up,
up, up, up, up. Please. Am I going to land on this thing? No way. No way. You can't do this shit.
I'm going to have to crash into the thing. Where is it? Where is it? Where'd it go? I just circled
the damn thing like a full time. Oh, come on. It was right behind me. Oh, God. Damn you. Damn you.
This is hard. I can't really park either because I'm going to get sucked into the orbit. I just
have to try to stay up. I'm trying to... I'm just holding right trigger right now. Just skim like
this and then wait for it. No, it's just so hard to tell how much you're moving. I'm holding down
left trigger right now. I'm holding it as hard as I can. I have no idea even where I am.
That's seriously fucking insanely... I don't think I can do that.
Speed around the sun? It's pulling you down. Too much math. Too dangerous.
I'm going to try this one more time. I'm just going to speed along the surface of the sun.
While I hold right trigger. Space is just so disorienting. For instance, I just put that on
the sun. I have no idea where it is. Oh, there it is. All right. I'm going for it. Maybe I should
just crash into it. It's the big orange thing. All right. Well, let me see where the trajectory is.
I'm apparently still going too fast. There it is. All right. If I just hold down right...
I'm holding down forward right now. I'm just speeding forward. I just got launched out.
I don't think you're supposed to do this like this. You probably teleport onto this thing.
You definitely teleport from a different location onto this. There's no way this is what you're
supposed to do. No way. Because even if I catch up to it... All right. What's going on? I'm
fucking holding down right trigger right now. I'm holding right trigger. What? What?
All right. I'm done. I'm not doing it anymore. I'll teleport into the fucking thing like I'm
supposed to do in like three hours. In like four and a half hours when I teleport to that station,
that's when we'll do it. Cool. I can't even like try to fly it along the coast of the sun.
I can't think of any more things that would be stupid to do as an astronaut.
No, why don't we just like skim the fucking surface of the sun, Greg?
That's a good idea. Oh, don't worry. I'm a good pilot. I actually want to do...
Wait, let me... All right. The sand place. All right. Energy lab. All right. Yeah. I wanted to
do this. I want to go to the statue place. Where's that statue? Did I already do it? No,
no, no, no. I got sidetracked. Where is it? Six location. My energy lab. There. Statue workshop.
All right. I want to go back to Statue Island. And that's on that tornado planet. Cool.
I just took my eyes off the road. That was not... No, it's my controller. What the fuck?
Okay. Why is this happening again? I fixed this shit already. Give me a break, man.
Why did I get... Good start. Just like looking at my watch. Fucking goodness. Okay. Yeah. I think
I'm using the... I think I'm using the cord that... Remember I told you that I was having problems
with my controller. I had to get a new cord. I think I'm using the old cord because there's
shit everywhere in this room. I think I've replaced the cord with the old cord.
Let's try this again. Bad craftsman blames his tools. Well, no, this is the equivalent of you
using a hammer and the hammer disappears out of your hand while you're about to swing into a nail
and you punch yourself in the dick. What? Quantum hammer. That was funny. Quantum hammer was funny.
All right. I got to pay attention. Stop, stop. I'm going too fast. How am I going this fast? How am
I going this fast? Okay. Statue Island. Quantum idiot. Enough, enough, enough, enough, enough,
enough, enough. I'll take your position into consideration.
There's one person in chat who knows what that was. Nice, nice Qbert reference. Thanks, man.
I love Qbert. By the way, Qbert got a real diverse shit end of the stick, didn't he?
Statue works at heart. Nobody gives a shit about Qbert. He is one of the original classic video
game characters and Mega Man's talked about every day. Pac-Man's talked about all the time.
Mario's every like, what happened to Qbert? Why does nobody like Qbert? Why Qbert not like
his show up in anything? I think the only time Qbert's shown up in any new media is I think they
like punched him in the face and family guy because he swears. It's not even a real square.
It's like a comedy square. He's in a wreck at Ralph. Imagine your first real appearance
in two, three decades. He's on Wreck-It Ralph. All right, let's open up the... Now I got a minute.
Let's read this because I didn't get to read this whole thing last time. Henry's statues. Yeah,
but what if we didn't use the other, the door and snuck in the other way? Does anyone want to?
He said don't do that. Really want to see the test too, Lanny, but that's a huge risk we take. We
probably shouldn't maybe walk, so let us see a later test. Shit. All right, there's a way over
there. Door's broken, but there's another way to go. But where is that other way? Fuck, Qbert.
What are some of the video game characters that really should have followed into
this current popular culture but never did? Frogger? Yeah, Frogger was another one, isn't it?
Oh wait, wait a minute. I know what to do. I know what to do. I know what to do. I know what to do.
Look. Where is it? Find it. Where's the secret entrance? Oh shit, we're going down. That's the
right idea though. That's the right idea. Got it. All right, what about uh, this thing? Wait, how
much further down is this? I can find distress beacons too? Shit. This is nuts. Yara, would you
kindly step back so Daz is closest to the statue? When pairing, the statue will choose whoever is
in closest proximity. See how its eyes have opened? That tells us the statue is paired with Daz.
Now, no matter where he is in this star system, Daz's statue will record his memories and send
them to the Ash Twin Project. This is extraordinary sculpting work, Vox. He has outdone himself again,
hasn't he? And now that we have our first successful pairing, we can test my memory storage
prototype. Each statue will send a single Nomai's memories to his or her own storage unit
within the Ash Twin. Each storage unit will be equipped with a mask, the statue's counterpart,
which will be able to send those stored memories back to the corresponding Nomai.
What the heck, dude? So I have, I have like a USB drive on the Ash Twin. Is this supposed to be me?
Okay, so we go from my brain, it sees me, it sees everything that I've done in every set and done,
and puts it onto the cloud, just like Google does. This is all for ad tracking. Okay, so I gotta find
the, on the Ash Twin. Now I know, I have my own personal USB drive on the Ash Twin. This just got
way more interesting right now. Right now I'm sitting there going, oh fuck, I gotta get there,
I gotta get there so I can delete all the times I went to the bathroom. I don't want to be seeing
that. I've installed the masks inside the Ash Twin Project, but the only plus two I got for that one
was from VR Josh. Everybody else did minus twos. That was a lot of minus twos in a row. Yeah,
all right, fine. Jeremiah, has anyone ever told you that you look like, you look like
Jeremy Albertson? That's me. All right, I've installed the masks inside the Ash Twin Project.
They look beautiful, although I do feel as though I'm being observed. It's comforting to know the
statues will not pair until the project succeeds, otherwise I imagine the experience would be hard
to endure. Ideally, they'll only need to activate once the project succeeds as a safety measure.
However, the statues will also activate in the event of the equipment failure. They will? Why
is that? If anything goes wrong with the Ash Twin Project, the statues and their masks will make us
aware of the situation and enable us to fix it. Otherwise, it would be possible for us to remain
permanently unaware of the problem. I hadn't thought of that. What a profoundly horrific fate
that would be. We're gonna store our, is there one of those things? This. Wait, every time I die,
I see this. And we fly through one of the holes. Okay, so those are the USB drives then. What's
up there? I can open this. On the other side. Hey, cool. All right, there's something else up here.
Okay, I thought, hear me out on this. This is gonna be hard maybe for me to describe or for you to see,
but that's a person with an astronaut helmet on with two arms sticking out and two legs.
That's a scout. And I was just like, there's a person here. This is, I gotta talk to the scout.
Ready? Left arm is right here. Right arm is right here. Hold on, let me do this from the mouse.
Right arm right here. Left arm right here. There's the head. There's like the end of the helmet.
Left leg, right leg. You're a psycho. I have to be a psycho every time. I wanna get up there.
I wanna get up there. I wanna get up there. Oh, this is how to get up there.
Read it. I'm curious, is sending a being's memories back in time the same as sending
the being itself back in time? As an example, if we were to send my memories back in time,
is that the same as sending me back in time? I imagine they're two different actions.
Wouldn't both actions be effectively the same?
Suppose that time was being rewritten. I believe this is different than receiving memories from
what is effectively the future. But isn't the end result identical in either case?
So they're sending memories back, but not a person? Does that make sense? Get out of here.
My leg. It's because it's quantum. Right, I forgot. What? Oxygen. Let's dump it into the computer.
Statue Workshop brings us over to Ash Twin Project. Every memory recorded by a
Nomai statue is transmitted to a corresponding storage unit within Ash Twin. I think that,
look at how big that one is. This is a mystery one. All right, let's go. Ash Twin. Ash Twin
Project. Okay. Right, right, right, right. Let's see. Okay. Where is it? Ash Twin. See, Jar Jar is the
whole thing here. Where is it? Ash Twin. Did I get it? Jar Jar is the key doll. It's at the
line problem. What did I say? What did I say? What did I say? Jar Jar is the whole thing.
Jar Jar is the whole thing here. Okay. Nobody just said this is the longest dream we've ever had.
Um, don't, I do not think so. No, there's been six hours. The longest dream was about 13 and a half.
All right, engaging autopilot. Let's go. Not even the longest dream this week. Yeah, yesterday was
like eight and a half, seven and a half. All right, go to Ash Twin and let's go. I want to go to the
USB storage. Okay, stop autopilot. I'm going to get the sun. Sun time. Sun time. Sun time. No,
it's not sun time. Hi. What's going on? Um, what's happening? Um, just get over there.
Dude can't even fall into the sun right. Shaking my fucking head. All the inertia.
When you're going 600 miles a second, you can't instantly start going the opposite direction.
Uh, but why is it doing this? I'm, I'm holding buttons to the right. I swear to God,
this is not, I swear to God, I'm doing, I'm, I'm not doing this. I'm holding the fucking button,
man. I'm going way too fast. I'm holding back. Okay, we're going to find them.
Okay, slow down and land. All right, good. Nice. Okay, get the fuck out of here.
We're looking for this place, place here somewhere on this planet.
It's the massive, it's a USB room. What's that over there? Oh, I can't get into any of these.
Wait here. It's connecting me necessarily. I'm not sure exactly what I'm looking for.
This is the only thing I've been able to find here. This shit.
But this doesn't really lead me anywhere. It's a bridge. Unless there's a sound cave shard
down there. This thing's getting too big. Stress beam unknown. I'm like, look, this is
I've never been in here. Look at that. Found something. Here's our first delivery.
One warp core fresh from the black hole forge. Rude is installing this core sibling on Brittle
Hollow as I write this. I gratitude Larry, but this the Ashtman project is underway.
I confess I'm deeply curious about what you and Pokey found on the white hole station that
started this project. I visit some time to learn more. I recommend you do. The white hole station
is the model for the towers being built. The Ashtman project. The visit to the station would
be doubly useful. I suppose more precisely, I would like to visit the white hole station with you,
Larry. I'd be happy to explain our findings. Here, stop using the scroll wall to flirt with my sister
and go meet her on the white hole station. I wish I could wait here for you to arrive,
but the forge and my unfinished work is calling on return with more materials soon. I needed to
learn. End of the stream song. I think that's, I really, really needed that info too, so that's
good. Now we just die. I have to watch it. I'm gonna be out of view. There it goes.
Then we fly through one of these masks, which is a USB slot. Then we go through some weird portal.
Our memories have been played to somebody. We go back in time. Memories have gone back in time.
We have shot the cannon. Okay, let's download this data. Dude, you keep dying. You suck at this game.
Yeah, I know. It's kind of tricky. I know what you mean, though. All right, what we got?
Ash Twin Towers. What we got? Ash Twin Towers. Black Hole Forge. White Hole Station Energy Lab.
Black Hole Station. No minecrafted warp cores at the Black Hole Forge before delivering them to Ash
Twin. All right, I gotta do this one. My energy lab in the canyon at Ember Twin's equator. In the
canyon. We gotta go now. Canyon at Ember Twin's equator. Nice to land on somebody. Turn off auto
pilot. You just killed the dude. No, I didn't. I did not. It's not true. I did not. All right,
abort, abort. It's right in the way. How do you not see this golf ball that's in the way?
Auto pilot. Stupid thing. All right, in the canyon. How does that look for a canyon?
How does that look? In here. Gotta get into the canyon. Quickly, hurry up before all the
sand fills the hole. All right, into the canyon. In here. Now, where in here is it? Sit. Sit.
Got something.
It happened in an instant without warning. I turned away from Cole's to examine a sample and
when I turned back he wasn't there. He had a limited supply of air. I'm afraid for him.
Hypothesis. We will learn more by examining the northern lakebed cave where he disappeared.
Search quickly. We have no time. I already knew that info, but okay. Air is here. Quantum shard.
Unidentified signal. Unknown. Wait, this is known. I've already been up here. How is this
unknown? I've talked to this person already. Church, I have a question for you. I found
something. I found Nomai writing about the quantum moon. I've observed the quantum moon orbiting each
of the five planets, but sometimes it quite simply disappears from the sky. Maybe there's another
place it travels to. Unfortunately, there is. I've never seen it. Quantum shirt. Quantum shard.
Okay, there you go. You got it. You got your comedy for a full hour. You still don't. I'm,
I gotta find something here. I don't know. Okay, I need, I already got that cave shard.
All right, we gotta go, we gotta go north. Up here, down in this way, right? In there.
Cave shard. All right, that's enough out of you guys for tonight. That's enough out of you guys.
All right, stop. The comedy meter is falling. Okay, there's, there's the cave shard.
That's death. Let's just keep going this way. Here's the cave shard. No, I just, okay,
cave shard. Police is missing. He vanished from the lake bed cave, the one at the bottom of the
dry lake bed at the north pole a couple days ago, and we're unable to find a trace of him.
I beg you, if you're reading this, help us. This rock is familiar to you to travel here,
my sedimentary friend, because your unique color and texture appear identical to the rock I met
earlier. Isn't this the rock fragment of the cave we found at the bottom of the dry lake bed at the
north pole? We plan to re-examine the north, northern lake bed cave. Wow. And Malera and I
went back to the lake bed cave and observed this rock again. Sometimes it's there and sometimes
it's not. Now that means this rock wanders like the quantum moon does. How curious. Very curious,
indeed. It's gone and therefore it's now in the top of the lake bed cave. Let's go.
North pole. This way. Like in here. In here. This is the big cave. This is so dark.
I think I missed my opportunity. The sand is all here. Did I miss the opportunity?
I might have. I have an opportunity here. The lake bed cave. It's down there. The sand's covering
it. Might as well fly into the sun. Unless it's like here or something. No, it's definitely on
the bottom. Lake bed. I think I missed the opportunity. Definitely missed the opportunity
to do this. Oh well. Start shoveling. I guess I could go back to the quantum moon. It's right there.
All right. Percentage check. Percentage check of me getting to the end. Completing the game.
Percentage check. 20 percent. Not joking. 40 percent for sure. Like 45 percent. 40 percent. 35, 30, 40.
No, put the suit back on. All right. Where do I want to go?
Still shit to do. Let me look at the map. Ash twin project. I still have to do these cave things.
Lake bed cave. Dry lake bed. All right. Let's go. I'm doing that immediately today. I'm just
going to instantly kill myself here. Trying to ghost ride it. All right. We got to be quick.
We got to go right to the bottom of that lake bed cave. How I feel about the game so far. I'm
intrigued because I kind of want to know. I kind of want to unravel its mysteries.
I just want to know. All right. There's an air of mystery here that I would like to know
how it comes together. All right. It's a little puzzle that you put together in your brain.
Sounds cool. Wow. There's time. I'm going to go up.
I'm going right for the golf ball. I always just go too fast because I'm just
I go so fast. Go like seven trillion miles per hour and then I can't stop.
It's like a it's like if you were on a train trip.
Okay.
Jerma has to eat a ghost pepper. Get me up. Let's go. Just don't blow your speed out and go crazy.
Is it going behind or in front? All right. What the hell was I doing? Oh, the lake bed.
North pole lake bed. Yep. Don't you dare block me here. I don't even think about it.
It's going to block me. It's coming for me to block me. Asshole. Okay. Hurry up. Let's go into
the cave. North pole. Why did I not land on the south pole? Why? Here it is. Am I going fast?
Yeah. Kind of. Okay. All right. Here we are. Where is it? Cave? Looks like a cave. What the
fuck is this? Stress beacon. Beacon. Hide and seek. No. Where the hell am I? Um, cave shard is
over there. Stop showing me the moon. I don't care about the fucking moon. Is it right above me?
It's above me. Oh, I'm getting squished. Damn it. Was I in the right spot though? I
looked like it was above me. That was the worst sound. Yeah, that was a horrible noise.
I don't know how to do that. Hurry up and go faster. I mean, I can't go that fast.
I gotta go slow. I'm trying. Hurry up and go faster. Dude, I can't. I'm supposed to fly into the cave?
All right. Where is it? Where's the, where's the, where's the north pole? I don't know where,
I don't know what, what, what the north pole is. What's a landmark I can look for?
What the fuck? Just get the fuck out. North? Which way is north? I'm running the equation.
All right. Let's try this again. Get in here. All the way down. Where am I? Okay. Where am I?
Am I in? Keep going. I'm going. I'm going. I'm going. That above me. It's fucking above me.
It's above me. Where the fuck did I just end up? Wait, what? Where is this? Why is it? Dude, that
All right. I, it's so disorienting down there too. Did I miss the opportunity again?
Stop looking for the signal. This is the cave right here, but like, I understand. I'm just
looking for the signal. In case you're curious, 11,000 meters that way, there's a quantum moon.
It's anybody wanted to know. Oh, and 60,000 meters behind you. There's a, there's a beacon
somewhere over there. Just in case you wanted to know for your current objective. Signal doesn't
do anything. Just go. I feel like that shit happens so fast. You want to smash this game
from making, you want to smash this game from making that noise. So forget about the signal.
Just run in and just keep going in. But I keep hitting the wall. There's the, it's like blocked
two or three of those passages blocked. Think of the cave as a maze. You have to finish in
under two minutes. That doesn't sound like something I want to do. Where's that northern
section? Slow down. Let's go here. Is that north or is that south? I don't even know.
Do I have a compass anywhere? Get in here. Right there. Fuck it. Dude, I'm just flying the shit
in here. I don't give a shit. Let's go. I don't give a fuck. It explodes. Don't get crushed by
it. Don't get crushed by it. Don't get crushed by it. I'm in. I'm in. Am I in? I'm in. All right.
Left and then left. Left. Left. Right. Wrong. Right. Left. Right. Dead end. What the fuck?
I don't know. I get this tiny circle in the middle of my screen. I don't even know what
direction I'm facing right now. I don't know what direction I'm in. I think I'm outside again.
Where am I? Where's my flashlight pointing? What? Am I in? Did I make it? Am I in? Use the scout?
Where am I supposed to go from here? Crunch incoming. I can't fly right now. I just have
no idea where this even wants me to go. Am I supposed to go up this cave? Here? I mean,
that's what I'm trying to do. Fuck. Am I in? Am I? I'm trying to stand on this.
Can I not stand on this? How did I not land on that? God damn it, man. Give me a break.
It's pushing me off. What the fuck is going on right now? Did I do it? If I go out this,
am I going to die? What? I can't go this way. Fuck this maze bullshit. Quantum fucking maze.
What? I'm losing my goddamn mind. Are these teleporting behind me? I don't even know what
direction I'm in. Wrong, wrong, but is it wrong? What the fuck are you doing to me? This is
ridiculous. I don't know what to do. Am I going crazy or is this happening to you?
I'm going crazy. I don't know what I'm doing wrong. Okay, don't. Wait, don't. All right. All
right. That's not cool. What do I do? Turn. Motherfucker. I figured it out. Now what do I do?
Turn. Get out. I hate this. I hate this. I hate this. I'm almost out of oxygen.
I did it. If you come here to look for Coleus, this is where we vanished. He's been missing
for two days. What happened before Coleus disappeared? We were examining the different
rocks. I recall Coleus standing on the largest one, the wandering rock. I was taking notes and
then my lantern died. I lit it again. Coleus and the rock were both gone. Your strange wandering
rock friend is here, though Coleus isn't. Coleus and I observed this unusual looking rock shard
in at least two other caverns. I'm unsure if this is relevant. I thought I was going crazy.
I looked over at the chat and people were like, dude, what are you nuts? You fucking just walk
straight. What's wrong with you? I'm like, what's wrong with me? I'm like, what's wrong with me?
Something's wrong with me. What's wrong with me? I thought I was going insane.
It was like, dude, are you fucking serious? Get a grip, man. What's wrong with you? What are you
doing? All right. Well, there's the cave shard. Do I move this thing? How do I? I can go. Hold on.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait a minute. Let me do it. How curious this rock took me with it to a new
location. I wonder why this happened. Curious, but also alarming. This new cave appears to lack an
entrance or exit. Also, the rock that brought me here disappeared while I wasn't watching.
The wandering rock has returned. Never before have I seen been so delighted to see a sedimentary
specimen. I wonder if I myself become quantum briefly when the rock carried me here. This seems
the clearest explanation. If the rock can bring me here, it can also carry me out. I can travel
on this rock as long as I'm not observing my surroundings, meaning I must be in complete
darkness. I'm going to bring my mentor here to see this. Malory is here now too. We theorize when a
conscious being is in contact with a quantum object and ceases to act as an observer,
the being can become entangled with that quantum object and they'd move together.
Friends, Coleus has discovered a new quantum rule. Wasn't there another one of these down
here somewhere? There was another one, wasn't there? It's the same one. No, I mean like in a
different cave. This is the same one. Oh, it's just the same. I think I did everything I can.
Turn the lights on. Wait, hold on. Can I go more? Can I do more? Wait, it does go to another place,
doesn't it? Okay, this is the one I was just in. Oh, shit. Friends, if you find any sign of Coleus,
I implore you to tell me. Ah, this is where that is. Yeah, we've read this already. So,
you're telling me I could have just stood on this rock and turned the lights off and I would have
been able to just not have to do the streamer, you're going crazy, like what's wrong with you
segment? I felt so sad too. I was getting so sad and almost upset and angry with myself because
I keep seeing like people saying, stop pretending and shit. I'm just like, am I?
I don't think I am. Am I pretending to not know where to go? I was just like, what happened? How
do I not know this? Well, all right, I got that mystery solved. So then hold on. If I go on the
moon, that means that if I turn all the lights off, I can go to the secret moon spot. Why do
you let chat bully you so much? I don't. I usually, hey, half the time I'm like, hey, shut up. What
you guys think you are? But I thought I was actually something wrong with me there.
Don't let this affect you like that. I mean, I was in the, you're losing your mind part of the game.
No, it's all good. Don't worry. I know you guys aren't really trying to make me think
them. Well, maybe some of you are. All right, put it in the computer. Cave.
On quantum moon locator. Sixth location. Quantum moon disappears sometimes.
Well, what do you know? Quantum moon time. Quantum moon right there. Where is it?
Where's quantum moon? So you're telling me that all I have to do is close my eyes.
And well, we'd like to not go that fast. So I'm going to close my eyes on this moon.
I don't understand. I don't understand what happened.
All right, I'm going to make a comparison here to something.
And a lot of you guys are going to know what I'm talking about. I remember when I played Darkwood
and I stepped in a trap every like four and a half minutes. And it got to a point where everybody was
certain that I was doing it on purpose. They actually believed it. I was like, dude, there's
no way you're doing that. You have to be doing that. You've stepped in like 30 traps.
The sun is just a trap from Darkwood. It's just, it just keeps happening. There's nothing I can do
about it. OK, quantum moon. I want to try this theory out. Where is the damn thing?
Percentage check. And we're around 40 to 50, 50, 40 to 50 ish, 50 to 60, 40, 50. Really? All right.
Is this what we're doing tomorrow? I want to make sure there's enough to do a full stream on this
tomorrow. It's been six and a half, seven hours. All right. So is there, those of you that are
experts, is there about six to six to eight hours left in the game? Yes, probably. Probably more
than that. For you, yes. Depends on how good you are. At least six to seven, six to nine. OK. All
right. Let's find that moon. The moon. Yeah, because I want to have a good six hour stream,
six to ten hour stream tomorrow. Like there's a six to eight hour stream tonight.
Depends on how fast you can solve things. OK, I got a photo. I need a note. All right, there we go.
We're on the, OK, now we're on the moon. Unbuckle. Let's get out. Now what and what do we do here?
Somebody's dead. Who is this? They have a mask on. They're wearing one of these masks. They're
wearing a memory. They're wearing a USB mask. Whatever that is. OK, so somebody's wearing a
USB mask here. OK, they're on the ground now. You landed on this guy. Let's not look. OK,
let's see what happens. He's just dead. OK, I don't want to waste any time. OK, any fluctuation?
Just on the moon. All right, so what am I looking for here? If I close my eyes, it will disappear.
Right? Wait, this moved. It's dark in here. It's dark in here. Now what? New planet? This is ice
planet. Flood. Wait, no, this is the this is that is this I think I've ever been here.
Isn't this this like the tentacle planet, right? I want to go to that one. I've not been to that
one yet. I've seen all these elements, but not this one. OK, we're here. OK, well, bye.
Quantum imaging, quantum entanglement, rule of the sixth location.
Shit, what is this one? Quantum now.
I don't know the third rule. I don't know the third rule. What's over here? Anything?
The sixth location rule. Where is that? Where's my where's my where's my rules?
I want to wear my rules. If you recall the rule of quantum imaging, quantum entanglement.
Let's go over the rules. Quantum imaging is as long as I have a picture of something,
as long as I can see something, it exists. But if I don't see something, it could exist somewhere
else. Quantum entanglement is I can ride on top of the rock, right? That's the you're entangled
in the quantum and you can move around the rule of the sixth location. This is the sixth location.
What's the rule of the sixth location? Turn lights up. Hold on. I need to be able to stand in it.
Image. If I take what if I take a picture of just the door? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I have an idea. All right. I have an idea. I'm going to take a
picture of the door with this. It's empty. And then I'm going to hold on. Oh, watch this.
Close the door. Close the door. Now turn the light off. Come on. I thought that was going to be it.
And then I don't even know what this location is. Let me let me I can't move now. That's not what
I want to be. I want to be with water filling this place. Why is this place filling up with water?
Quantum tree. Quantum tree. Okay. Quantum tree. Quantum tree. Quantum tree. Watch this. Ready?
Okay. Quantum tree. Wait, where's the one that just back here? Where is this? Hold on. Is this
even? This is not even a plant. Wait a minute. This is not the this is different location.
This is not that planet. This is bullshit. This is we're not even on that planet.
All right. Hold on. Let me get out. Close this. I'm going to check out. I'm going to
explore the other fake planet. I think I just broke it. All right. Let's see what happens
when I go back over here. Let's check this out. Because these are fake planets. This is not real.
Look at this. It's not even real. It's probably some clue around here somewhere.
If this is them, this is this is the moon. But why does it look like this?
I'm missing something and I don't know what it is. What is it though? It's rule the sixth location.
That's this thing. Can I take a picture of the moon? Because I mean it's just it's just a
hold on. All right. Where is it? Slow, slow, slow, slow, slow, slow. Where am I? I'm out of
fucking fuel. Get back there very fast. But if it's if it's the rule, the sixth location is just the
moon and I need to keep the moon in place. The sixth location is the moon. Rule of the moon.
Rule of the sixth location. What is this? What is I don't even know if the sixth location is.
Wait, let me look. I don't have any. All right. I didn't do this shit.
Giants deep to the lower boat and we're in but the statue. Didn't I do this?
All right, we're going. No. Ocean depths.
It's a path beneath the surface that leads to the observatory. The trailhead starts at Brittle
Hollows equator. All right, let's do that. Hollows equator. Let's give it a look. Somebody said,
this is boring. Go back to flying into the sun. I've been to Dark Bramble. Yes, I have.
I did a lot of the stuff there. Brittle Hollow. The equator. It's pretty much right here. I haven't
really done much in this planet anyways, so I might as well just crash into it and fucking
everybody will laugh. Equator for this place to go in. Here's the equator. Is this thing?
The trees detected. All right, we have some new info. Well, shit. Okay. The trees are moving. The
trees in this grove wander about freely. This is not normal. Even for this alien planet. I never
see them move. Is this even possible? Anyone else witnesses this disturbing behavior? I implore you
record your observations here. These trees are aberrant. My brain must be. Flume is right. The
trees do move. I confess I didn't notice until I read these notes. Alarmingly, it isn't only
the trees. There is other matter in this area, such as that unusual shard of rock moving in the
same eerie way. That rock is unusual for another reason too. It possesses color and texture I've
never seen elsewhere on this planet. This rock shard's presence is significant. We should study
it. It would be what is causing other nearby objects to move. Poor shard. I already got that.
Wait, does it disappear? If I don't look at it. It does. Where does it go? Can I stand on it?
Determine this optical shard of rock as the reason objects grow and behave in a quantum manner.
The only other object we've observed displaying this quantum behavior is the wandering moon.
Yeah, imagine the moon. I think I've already read this. I know from earlier Clitz mentions this
strange type of rock isn't found elsewhere on Brittle Hollow. What if it isn't originally from
this planet? From the wandering moon. Perhaps it's even a small piece of the moon itself.
All right, so it's a moon. All right. All right, turn the lights off.
Close my eyes. I read this like four hours ago. Yeah, I did. Why is it so dark? Beneath your feet
lies the tower of quantum knowledge. If you're preparing to make your first pilgrimage to the
quantum moon, descend the steps to the entrance below. The knowledge held within will help you
on your journey. All right. There's the black hole. I remember falling in that earlier.
There. Quantum. What's this quantum? Entrance to the tower of quantum knowledge. All right,
I'm going in there, but what's over there? Southern Observatory. Wait, I need to do this too.
Arcane Sanctuary. All right, where? Turn it on. Oh, must I missed it, I think.
I thought it was just going to go. Wait, hold on. I might be able to get caught in it.
I found Rybeck. Rybeck. Oh, you launched. That's great. Great job to you. Oh, I guess that means
I've been out here a while, huh? Well, this is Riddle Hollow, but you probably knew that.
A lot of history here. It's great. What are you doing here? I'm here to see the Hanging City.
Um, should we be concerned about what just fell? Oh, okay. It's always been my dream to see it with
my own four eyes ever since I saw Hatching. Did you miss it? Because I think it was behind you.
The alien race lived in the solar system long before our species even existed.
How could I not want to see what their civilization was like? Only you've probably
heard the other say it, right? I'm afraid of space. Seriously, I'm more surprised than anybody that
I'm out here. Want to know how I even got this far? I fell. Me too, Rybeck, me too.
Tripped over a gravity crystal. It's dumb luck I landed somewhere my little scout says is halfway
stable instead of being sucked into what's below. I'm engaging the stability of the ground around
me using my little scout. It needs to be the place with the best surface integrity. I'm just
going to stay here until I'm ready to move on. That's enough about me and my problems. You didn't
come all this way to listen to me blather, did you? Yeah, that'd be yeah. Hey, I learned something.
I saw the Sunless City on the Ember Twin. You mean there's another No-My City inside the Ember
Twin? That's incredible. The whole city and I had no idea it existed. How'd they keep the sand out?
For me, I'd be nervous about getting buried in the caves by that awful river of sand.
Gosh, the No-Mys sure were ingenious, building an entire settlement underground. The Sunless City,
wow. That means there were two groups of No-My, one that lived on Ember Twin and one that lived
here on Brittle Hollow, but they must have traveled around the solar system since No-My
writing can be found on other planets too. Where should I look here? Where shouldn't you explore?
Not the black hole. That's very no, which is unfortunate because the most exciting
stuff is behind below the crust, including the Hanging City. That's just to the north.
You can kind of see it from here. There's also this big dome on the south pole called the
Southern Observatory. You can't get inside from the surface. Trust me, I tried, but it's like the
rest of the No-My structures here. There's probably a path to beneath the crust somewhere. I'd love
to be exploring. I'd love to hear it. Okay, we got some new info. I'm just going for what that is.
Let me back in. Let me back in. Let me back in. Let me back in. Let me back in. Can I reach that
from here? I'm just gonna go to the interloper. I'm actually going pretty fast. Okay, all right,
all right, all right. I'm in perfect trajectory. Load up. 27, 28, 26, 2000, 17. All right, keep
going. 15, 13, 12, 11, 10. Okay, slow, slow, slow. 29. All right, where am I, sir? The interloper.
Is this an asteroid? Land. I'm alive. I'm alive. I'm alive. I'm alive. I'm alive. All right, let me.
We're not going into the sun, are we? No. Are we? No. Distress beacon? There's a distress beacon
up there. All right. What's going on? Hide and seek. No, there's no frequency over here. All
right. What am I looking for? Something up here? Something to look at? Is there anything up here?
What about on the top? No. Up here. The giant ice. Wait a minute. What's that? Something. Something.
It's me. Something right here. Something. Come on. I just need to see before I die. Before I die.
Before I die. Come on. I need to see before I die. I need to see before I die. Please. I need to
see before I die. There's nothing to see. Turn around. I mean, I'm dead. What did I miss? I was
too focused on my breath meter going to zero. I went too fast. Golden retriever brain? Golden
retrievers are like the smartest animal though. Dude, what the fuck? Do you think I care about
you saying that? That's one of the smartest animals on earth. I think I'm gonna call it here.
I'm gonna call it here. I'm gonna call it here. I want and because I'm getting addicted to the game
and I want enough for tomorrow as well. Power of quantum knowledge. Pipex camp. Hanging city.
Go back to the comet first. All right. I'll go back. I'm gonna just fly the ship to the comet
and see if I can find what you're talking about. Interloper. There it is. Far away.
So I'm gonna assume there's probably at least another good six to eight hours left of the game.
Have I peed one time? No. I have not gotten up for a single break. No, you're right. Maybe a
little bit more than that. That's all right. I plan on trying to finish this game tomorrow.
That's the plan. You could beat it tonight. Well, we'll see. We'll see where it takes us.
There's more than enough game for another day, I can tell you that. All right. Well, that's
gonna finish tomorrow. And then after that, should be able to play Tony Hawk.
For some reason, the Xbox 360 hard drive is not in. I'm going way too fast, boys and girls. And
this is what happens when I'm not paying attention. I'm just talking. I am okay. I think
this damaged the headlights a little. Who cares? Let's see if I can find this. What
you guys are talking about? Okay. So there's a there was apparently a ship that you said
there was a there was a missed a ship. This is just a suicide mission. Yes.
You're here somewhere? Because I remember this is this part. What's that light? We're here?
Uh, I don't see anything. Like that way. Oh, we're going towards the sun. My hey,
have to be careful. Now I can reach this. Where the hell is that ship? I don't think I think I'm
better reach. I literally can't feel anywhere. I just got at the sub that I was trying to find
this thing. And now the sun was coming up and I thought I was going to fucking fall into the sun.
I don't I don't know if this is I don't have to do this on the side with the spikes.
Like I was on that side. Let me try this one more time. One more time.
It's done. Wasn't I in the spikes when I fell off?
Didn't look. Yeah. But I mean, the things made it to ice and you just skim. I can't like walk on
the surface and just skimming across the surface. I can't walk on it. There's no gravity on this
thing. All right. Last try. And then that's the end of the stream. It's a million years away.
He's addicted. I think a little I think I'm more addicted to one. Just want to know what the hell
happens. The story has me intrigued. I want to know what's going on. Why am I teleporting back
through time? What do these people do? What did this other civilization do? And why are we here
doing this? See you later. I'm going to bed. I'm sitting there talking to you guys. I'm sitting
here looking at chat with holding the button. And I'm just like, yeah, you know, I'm addicted. And
I like to talk about the story and seeing what you guys have to say. I'm still going negative
miles per hour. I'm like 10. I'm much further. Let's try this again. This thing's so tiny. It's
so hard to find just such a small little fucking asteroid. Like this is why space games are hard
for my brain. I feel like I'm not even moving right now. In my fucking cube brain. I'm standing
still. Here comes the trash planet. Try to get on the spikes. What am I looking for here?
I see something underneath. No, it's not. That's not anything. That's nothing.
Right in the middle. Right there. Right there. Right there. All right. What's that? Found it.
It's a suicide mission. I don't care. This is troublesome. It seems the comet wishes to
submerge our shuttle in ice. If we stay on the surface too long, the shuttle may freeze entirely.
Even if it did, wouldn't someone call it back home to the gravity cannon on Ember Twin? Yes,
but the exploration of the comet would be more difficult if we were without the shuttle.
Until someone recalled it. Perhaps we shouldn't have landed on the dark side of the comet.
I suppose one of us remained on the shuttle. In the shuttle to keep it warm and continue monitoring
the surface. Could it be wise, I think? Larry, if you don't mind waiting here with it, Oak and I
can continue to investigate the surface. I didn't jump. I didn't jump. I did not jump.
I didn't press any buttons. I didn't do anything. It sucked us out. Did you not see
my friend the ship getting sucked out? I didn't do anything. Get in. Hey, we did it. Let's download
that data. All right. That's it. I'll see you guys tomorrow for more Out of Wild. We'll try
to finish the game. Final Sun joke? No, no, no, no, no. Something here. I want to see.
Hey, Jerma, that was a good try. Hey, thanks. All right. What else is on here?
Okay. What else is on here? Something else? Wait, the ice can melt? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
wait. Holy shit. The ice is... Okay. Hold on. Where's the tail? All right. Where was that?
There it is. All right. This is gonna melt. All right. This is gonna melt. Quantum melt?
That sounds like a Subway sandwich. The quantum melt at Subway.
All right. I'm so far away from the sun. Am I even gonna do it? Am I even gonna come back there?
Holy shit. I want one of those. A quantum melt? Seriously? That would be turkey, ham,
like six different kinds of cheeses. It'd be like Swiss, cheddar, provolone, gruyere, brie.
It'd be every cheese. I'm gonna sit here. I'm not gonna move, right? Secret menu. Check the orbit?
Yeah. Wait, is this gonna take too long? Is this song gonna explode? Just read bits? Yeah,
that's not a bad idea. I'll just read bits. That sounds good. Still going? Still moving, right?
Or is it paused? Is it paused when it's all tabbed? I think it's paused when it's all tabbed.
Well, I can do it because I can just load up the screen over here. All right.
Let's go back. Thanks. That's the end of the stream. See you guys tomorrow.
Let's go back a little bit and read some bits. Super Bruce gave five community subs. Thank you,
Super Bruce. Appreciate it. That was earlier, about six or seven hours ago here. Seven or eight
hours, actually, almost. Sweet Croc, thanks for the 1500 bits. $15. Say, hey, Jeremy, I've been
watching for a while. Finally getting to donate. Out of Wilds was my game of the year last year
and maybe my favorite game of the last five years. Hope you enjoy it. Can't wait to watch.
It is very enjoyable. I especially like the story. I want to know why this is happening.
Somebody's just breathing in your room. Yes. Did nobody say that? I did.
But thank you. Appreciate the 1500 bits and it's pretty good so far. We'll see how I feel about it
after another day. I feel like I'm probably going to like it though. It seems really good,
is what I've played so far. Hey, more jelly. Thanks for the 500 bits. Oh, you say it's declined,
huh? You said it was declined. All right, shit. Well, try my MasterCard, bro. Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I got money on my MasterCard. Sure. Thank you more jelly with the $5. Do not fuck with your card.
Thank you, Hikiko Morris Sunday. What just happened? We coming on? That's the wrong controller.
This Xbox fucking 360 controller. Hold on. No, we're good. We're actually getting close.
Thank you to Hikiko Morris Sunday for the 300 bits. They say, Hi, Jim. A couple weeks ago,
I had a dream that I sent a message in chat saying that I was having a birthday party,
but no one showed up. So you doxed me to encourage people to come over, but no one showed up.
Anyway, what's your favorite Destiny's Child song? Mine is Say My Name. That one too. I like that
one. That's good. Digitron Surfers, thanks for the 500 bits. In the upcoming YouTuber movie series,
are you going to be playing penis Jerma or are you going to just to play yourself? I love your
channel. I don't even know what that means. Bryant Ziggs, thanks for the, hold on. We're almost there.
All right, let's see what happens. Bryant Ziggs, thanks for 1500 bits. Jerma, I had a dream the
other night that you were doing a live show in my, another dream. Melt? That didn't do anything.
All right, goodbye. 20 jump jump. I didn't twice jump. I didn't. The sun comes up and fucking
pulls you up and I was holding left trigger. Run it back. I was holding left trigger and like
forward facing down. No, no, I got baited and that's fine. I can just quit, right?
Reset, loop and quit. Yeah, right? This is okay. We'll see what happens at the end of the game
tomorrow. Very cool. I will see you guys tomorrow for more Outer Wilds. Let's get the actual intro
or intro outro up. See what happens tomorrow. I'm going to be starting. Oh, what time am I going to
start tomorrow? Two again. And we're on like 145, 132. Something like that. But we had the 15 dollars
from Brian Ziggs. Thank you, Brian. Jerma, I had a dream the other night that you're doing a live
show in my city. I was so excited. I got all my friends and my girlfriend to go to it with me.
We managed to get front row seats and I prepared for what would be the greatest experience of my
whole life. What I got instead was you roasting the shit out of me for an hour. You absolutely
went in on me and all I could do was sit there and wonder what I did to deserve it.
I would never do that to somebody.
Oh, I'm sorry that I'm sorry the dream, Jerma, is a nuisance and a menace to society.
I don't know why. Evil, evil Jerma apparently sneaks into your dreams.
Hey, Drumager, thanks for the 500 bits. Since you don't seem to have a clue of your speed,
one mile equals roughly 1600 meters. Your speed is shown in meters per second. If you multiply it
by 3.6, it transfers to kilometers per hour. For reference, sound of speed in the air is around
343 meters per second. You're basically slamming into a planet twice that speed.
Well, it only took me eight hours straight of playing Astaroth's Wrath to find out that I
could regain health by hitting A. I didn't even need it. Beat the fucking game on hard.
It's all good. But thank you, though. And then we had PlankCat gave 1500 bits. Thank you for
the $15 PlankCat. I love your unbridled curiosity. It's perfect for this game.
This game is really cool for the one reason because you don't really have anything to do.
You do, but you don't. I like that aspect of just kind of doing anything you want without a real
goal. You just have this overarching thing that you're trying to figure out, but you don't have
like an A to B. You just go anywhere. I don't like the forced reset, but I understand it.
I think the forced reset, at least for me, is sort of tells you, all right, hey, you had some fun,
now do something else. It's almost like you have a time limit. It's good for me because I get so
fucked up and I'll get stuck on a planet for like three hours. So it helps me just be like, all
right, here comes the supernova. What are you doing tomorrow? It's good for ADHD. Yeah, because it
makes me have to do something else. I think it would be better if you had a kill me button.
Yeah, I mean, it's kind of dark and morbid, I guess, but there really probably should be like
I just rip the mask off the button if you like hold left trigger and right trigger for like five
seconds. So you can just like, instead of having to quit main menu restart, I feel like that's
takes you out of the experience. I'd rather be able just to rip the mask off and just delete it
and just go to the next day. It is, it is a lot of fun so far. I'm going to be sad when it's over.
Ocean dweller, thanks for 250. Dermagreatstream, as always, just wanted to say that the elevator
crush death summed up everything so perfectly about this playthrough. It was wonderful.
SoupGG, thanks for five dollars. Hey buddy, I guarantee it will take you at least four attempts
to beat the mission Big Apple Spot Challenge near the end of Tony Hawk's Underground this Friday.
If you can beat it in less than four, I will vomit up a Philly cheesesteak on my keyboard.
Aren't my words pal? I'll try. I'll try. Also keep in mind the Tony Hawk Underground stream
might happen on Saturday. Or sorry, yes Friday, right? Friday or Saturday because I have to wait
for that 360 hard drive to get in and it's in the mail so it might take another day. I don't know.
It will happen this week though before I leave. Hopefully it comes in for the next day or so.
But let's get the community subs and the regular subs and the credit subs,
all of them, going at the same time. Here come the credits. Here comes the janitor.
I'm gonna bump you. What is the German's favorite Beyonce song? Single Ladies.
Easy. It's the easiest question I've had all night. Thanks everybody for subbing.
Outer Wilds is a lot of fun. I look forward to completing it and seeing what happens.
Let's run the credits. I can't believe I, you know the thing I'm most annoyed about tonight?
The fact that I was like almost, I was more than a half a second
behind every event that happened on screen for like the first three and a half hours.
I'm so annoyed by that. It's all good though. Won't happen tomorrow. All right we do have a
little bit more to do. We have now similar bits to do. All of one zombie thanks to the 250. Hey
you think you'll ever play Prey? I mentioned it in the stalker stream. It's got a great art style
and soundtrack. I like space games though nothing will compare to Space Master. It's not really.
That is the best space game ever made. Oh Prey and Thief are the same game in my brain
and I don't know why. Is there a reason why that is? I don't, I'm just being honest. I don't know
why that is. They're not even the same at all. Yeah I don't, I don't know why that's happening.
Yeah put it on the list. The OG Thief games are good. Fuck the new one. Really okay.
I'll play Prey. Yeah let's go. Prey is basically a current gen remake of System Shock 2 which is
made by the same studio as Thief. Oh that's why I'm doing that. Put it on the list. Dark soul thanks
to the 250. Do you have any good awful local commercials to share? Here's one of my favorites.
Local commercials. Brothers Scrap Metal commercial.
Why would you have this much scrap metal?
Just because? Why would you have a ton of scrap metal in your house?
Uh I mean not really local commercials but anything with Kathy Mitchell is like
an automatic A plus commercial for me or infomercial. Hi Kathy Mitchell here with
the Super Cooker. She's, I love her so much. You guys like seriously don't know. I am a huge fan
of Kathy Mitchell. I'm a huge fan. If me and Kathy Mitchell were in the same room at a convention,
I would get nervous and I'd be taken aback. Oh it's Kathy Mitchell. She's not, she wouldn't,
she's not talking to me. I would want Kathy Mitchell's autograph and a photo and it would
be a great, it would be a great day. I'd feel so happy. Be like I got to meet Kathy Mitchell today.
No way. She's the dump cakes lady. Yeah she's been around for a long time. The new wave oven,
the pasta pro, dump cakes, dump meals. She does it all. I'm gonna do you all a favor.
Go to YouTube and just watch the new wave oven infomercial with Kathy Mitchell
and you will just absolutely adore everything that she does. She's just wonderful. Watch it now.
That's like a 30 minute infomercial. I'm not watching it right now. I'm getting out of here.
I'm going to get food and pee for the first time in eight hours. But we have one more bit donation
to do in this big one. $25.25. 100 bits from Lizard Amiibo. Thanks for the 25 bucks. I was
going to use this money to feed my 10 starving children but decided you could probably use it
more. Don't read this part out loud. Okay. Oh no. Okay. So uh no it's all good. Talking about the
doctor appointment I had. So basically how it goes is I probably just have a costochondritis.
It is just an inflammation in my rib cage the way they connect in the front of the sternum and in
the back of the spine. Unfortunately there is nothing you can do about it. There's only one
thing you can really do about costochondritis. Hope it goes away on its own. Which it does for
a lot of people. Sometimes it takes six months. Sometimes it takes 10 years. But it can go away.
Or you do physical therapy to try to correct it. To try to alleviate some of the pain and the
symptoms. That's another route. The other route is to get a nerve blocking injection into my ribs
in like six or five or six places around the spots where it hurts. And then it's gone. But you may
have to do that injection more than once. You may have to do those injections every three or four
months. I was told some people get an injection for two or three or four and it goes away forever
and it never comes back. I've also been told by the same doctor that for some people the pain
comes back in like a month and you have to do it again. So I am going to be doing physical therapy.
I don't like the idea of going right and jumping the gun and blocking nerves with injections. I don't
want to do that yet. If I have to I will. But I want to do physical therapy first. That's the plan.
And that's sort of what this whole thing has turned out to be. Like it makes a lot of sense
because I can lean back and I can put a little pressure on my chest. And if I lean back the
middle of my chest and sternum just pop pop pop hurt hurt hurt. Same thing if I lean to the left
or right I can feel it in the back of my ribs the way my ribs connect to my spine. It's like
and that's also another reason why I haven't done green screen stuff yet. I just need to get the okay
and it's like okay now turning doesn't hurt and leaning back and forward doesn't hurt you know
I'm saying. Just trying to get to that point. Costochondritis inflammation in my rib cage where
they connect. Don't know why I have it. It just do. But that's pretty much how that story goes.
The good thing is I've had a lot of tests. I've had spinal MRIs. I've had abdominal MRIs. They've
looked at all my organs. I've had tons of tests. They checked all my fucking my kidneys and my
liver and everything seems to be in working order. So I've been told that this is not a serious
condition. It's just one that you have you have now. So and with that that's where we're going to
end the stream tonight. Thanks everybody for watching. See you tomorrow around two-ish one
to two-ish probably 2 p.m pacific for more Outer Smiles.