Oh, that was bad. Wait, hold on. That's okay. That's the first time I've, oh, I've spoken. Like, used my vocal cords in at least, I don't know, like 30 minutes. 30 or 40 minutes ago, I went, oh, auto, auto.
And I got ready. I haven't used them. Saliva has been down there.
Hello, happy Saturday. How's your weekend? Mine's doing pretty good. You guys ready for this weekend edition of the German 985 television program? Today, we've got an exciting program. This week, we're going to play Xbox games. Some original, some Xbox 360.
And let me just right off the bat tell you that yes, yes, we're going to play, I don't even want to say it. We're going to play, yes, we're going to play Sneak King, okay? Everybody relax.
I couldn't even say it. I was, I was like, my like voice trembled from like how dumb this is. Like how stupid and shitty this game is. We're going to play Sneak King.
Like I'm a fucking toddler, like hiding behind the couch that's very visible and you can see where they go.
Yeah, you ready? Yeah, you're never going to be able to find me.
They fucking run away and you see them. You see exactly where they go and then they jump out. You don't even have to find them.
You get within a 15 feet circle around where they are and they just jump out and they go, ah!
Like yes, okay, you're very excited, I can tell. We're going to start with an Xbox 360 game. I don't know how good this is going to be, by the way.
By the way, that the rule does stand on this stream, the general rule. You don't know what the general rule is.
We have 30 minutes to play each one of these. After 30 minutes, we decide if we're going to spend six hours. I don't know how it works.
It's going to be great. That's a lot of gifts. That is a lot of gifts. That's 20. Oh, my throat is fucked today.
What's going on? I don't know why this happens to me.
Anybody else feel like this? I have a like four hour window every single day where my voice is normal.
After like four o'clock in the afternoon, it starts to get really kind of like tired.
And from four in the afternoon till one a.m. before I go to bed, it's like, oh man, like it's getting a little tired talking.
I wake up in the morning and my voice is like this. Oh, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
And it slowly gets normal for like three hours. Why does it do this? What's wrong with me?
I thought it was messed up for yelling for 20 minutes. Well, I didn't yell.
Maybe I'm just screaming in my sleep or something. Like screaming every night and I don't even know.
Talking to yourself. Smoker lungs. I don't smoke cigarettes. I don't even smoke weed. I don't do it. I don't inhale smoke.
That's not a lie. It's not. I don't smoke weed. I already went over this. I don't smoke weed.
I eat it in small quantities, controlled so I know exactly what I'm getting.
I need to tell you all that again. I haven't caught a stream live in ages. Well, welcome.
You're going to notice. I swear to God. So because we're on a once a week schedule, the like three to four hour stream is gone.
I'm going to sit here as long as I'm comfortable. That could be five hours. That could be eight.
I don't know. But something you're going to notice over in real time here, you're going to find that for our window.
It's not right now. It's going to be in like 45 minutes to an hour. You'll get I want someone to catch it.
Anyways, the first game we're going to play is the first Templar for Xbox 360. I don't this game.
I don't know anything about it. This is a guy with a shield on the front and he has a sword.
And already nobody likes it. I haven't even played it yet.
What was I going to say? Somebody had a question. What was I just going to say? I have no idea.
This game is bad. Really? You don't even know what this is. You don't know what this is.
This looks like a PC like flip. Wait, what do you mean? I didn't catch the whole thing.
Did you say this looks like a Unity flip? Is that what you said?
Well, this would be one of the original Unity flips. This game came out before Unity I think even existed.
I need to check the sound. I didn't get a chance to do that. Let's go. Ready?
One, two, three. One, two, three. One, two, three. One, two, three.
Is it good? Perfect. All right. Here we go.
No game sound. I'm looking at it right now. I can see it.
What the hell was I going to say? There was something important that I had to say.
Cabbagehead PhD gave 25 community subs. I was in the middle of saying that. Thank you.
What was I going to say? One, two, three. One, two, three.
It should be instant when you hear it. I'm not going to play on casual. Maybe I should.
I'm not playing on hard. Normal. Subtitles, sure. Why not?
Brightness. Adjust the slider until the middle square is just barely visible.
Does anybody play like this? I feel like there's tons of people that just turn the thing all the way up because I can see better.
We're just going to go here. I hate not being able to see shit in games. It's annoying.
Are you ready? Are you ready for the captivating story of the first temple? That was whatever.
You have to wait 30 minutes. You can't just say next. We haven't even seen the intro.
Sit down.
Everyone is waiting for Sneak King. What if I just fucked with you all and I had this game custom made?
And it zooms into the king on the throne and it's the Burger King.
See, that's how you don't even know what the fuck you're going to get here. So sit down.
Did I play this game? This guy just woke up. I know what it's like.
Let's catch up with this guy in like four hours. He probably sounds like this.
Is this the human starting zone in Warcraft?
Can you hear that? Oh my god.
It sounds like I'm changing inking my printer over here.
The toughness skill grants orbs. You can't hear that?
Cyprus. 1291. Oh, it is a unity flip. You're right.
This looks like a machinima. This looks like a very well-made machinima.
Wait, somebody killed all these people? Why are they ready to...
Why would you close your hands together? Alright, X's attack.
Nice. This is the best machinima I've ever seen.
Who's talking? Me? Okay.
Well, this game is not going to be very fun. This is going to be gone in a half an hour, I guarantee it.
Playing in a machinima. What, you don't remember that?
If you didn't feel like setting all the characters up and stuff,
you would go from a cinematic view to just take the HUD away and start fucking slashing at each other and stuff.
And you would use that, because how much of a pain in the ass would that be to actually set all that up?
Alright, what do I need to do? Is there a sprint? What do I have to do? Just leave?
Castle of Griffinstein 2. Oh, here we go. Alright.
You can block enemy attacks by holding down right trigger to block an attack coming from a different direction.
Tilt L in that direction while holding RT down.
Alright, that's a block. I just need like a young, like 12 year old voice to narrate what's going on right now.
And then it would be a real machinima.
Alright, block. With a really puffy mic.
What I mean by puffy mic, I mean that every time you say the word, any word with P or T in it,
it sounds like your eardrums are blowing up.
For example, I'm going to give you a warning here. This is going to be horrible.
Okay, so please, please take me to your general so I can push him over the edge.
That's what it was like. That's still kind of what it's like. I'm sorry, this is probably loud.
All the golden arrow on your minimap to your main objective. The minimap is located in the upper left corner of your screen.
Alright, let's go. Put a filter on? Maybe I will eventually.
This game is so ugly, but like I'm still interested. I'm not giving up yet.
I'm not next game. Wait a minute, just give me a minute.
Let me just do it like the fucking 12 year old does a machinima joke and then we'll move on to Sneak King, I guarantee it.
Play a Lego game? The dots, orange dots on your minimap represent healing items.
They can take food or fresh water. Lego Lord of the Rings?
I think a lot of people don't know what one of the next games could be.
And yes, I did make sure they were all backwards compatible.
It has to be, like this game is going to be fun, right?
Wilhelm screams.
Yo, I got an achievement playing the game and not doing anything.
Holy shit, wow, like what you're witnessing right now is like the achievement bubble of 2011 or 2008.
Everything was an achievement. Nothing was a real achievement.
Challenges, beating the game on hard or something or doing something really crazy, some real achievement.
Nope. Achievement bubble, 2009.
You drank a potion for the first time. 100 points.
And then it crashed. Hard. We don't care about him anymore.
I'm not listening to any of this.
I miss my beloved Xbox. A lot of 360s play most Xbox games.
What's my gamer score? I don't know. Not that high.
I know these are the rules of the order. Game score is minus two. Open your dashboard?
How do I see it? It's not just like right here? Left?
Hold on, I don't want you to see, what if like my credit card comes up or something? Hold on.
I don't want you to see that. I don't want you guys to see my credit card info.
But wait, no, no, but I even care.
The last credit card I put into this is from like probably like four years ago or something.
Do I really care? Alright, I got 3,800 points. Is that good?
3,825. What was considered a huge gamer score?
Well, let me put it this way. What was a braggable gamer score?
200k? 20k plus? 50k plus? Damn.
Well, cool. Let's continue with the story.
Oh, the 25 subs from Cabbagehead. Thank you, Cabbagehead, for the insane subs.
50 community subs.
Alright, it's time for a prediction. Is there a mod here that can do predictions?
Will the guy on my left in the next cutscene do the like, I'm gonna give you a beatdown with his hands like this?
Like he was doing, he did twice. Will he do it a third time in the next cutscene?
Hit it up there. Let's see it. I want to see.
Ah, you can't even kill NPCs in this game. Game's not even any good. Alright, let's go.
That's easy money.
Alright, let's see. Are they any good?
Oh my god. That's another 25 subs.
Alright, will he do it?
The Xbox fucking sucks. Actually, the Xbox was fantastic.
The original Xbox was insane.
The Xbox 360, on the other hand, melted in your house all the time.
Do people remember that shit? I think a lot of the younger crowd here might not understand.
The Xbox 360, there was just a random, like, probably 20% chance that it would brick itself and die and melt inside.
That was not, oh wow, that's crazy.
Imagine if the PS5 just fucking melted inside. Like 30% of them. Wrap it up in a towel.
Yeah, and remember the videos of the people opening up the heat sink?
Like turning on an Xbox and opening the heat sink up and dropping like an egg in there?
And just cooking the egg instantly and it was like made like a fucking souffle?
I remember that video. That's fucking crazy.
Alright, what do I want? How much? I have 1000 XP.
Alright, am I gonna go...
The third attack in this combo can knock down enemies or break their shields.
It's boring. I like that one. That's a cleave.
Grants an additional zeal orb. Don't care what that is.
We're not gonna get far enough into the game to know what that is or care about it.
Yeah, this one. Alright, let's go. Are they orcs?
Well, how come we don't have a horse? Why don't we have a horse?
Didn't people ride horses?
Fucking everyone's just walking around. Enemy archers can deal severe damage from a distance.
If you see a targeting mark near you, try to move away from it.
Hold LT down and tilt L in the desired direction.
Hold LT down. Oh, alright. This is dodge.
This game reminds me of something.
Do you guys remember the Viking game?
Viking. No, there is a mobile game that's like this.
What's this fucking mobile game?
There's a mobile game that's this exact game.
I played it for like two straight days and then I was like, I'll never play it.
It's a game where you only fight guys like this in an arena.
Not Infinity Blade. No, it's something else.
No, not Clash of Clans.
Blood and Glory. That's definitely it. You are absolutely correct.
How did you get that? You're right.
Blood and Glory. Yeah, it's a mobile game.
Usually I would be really happy if mobile games have caught up.
Because remember back in 2012, 2013, 2014, having a 3D game on your phone was a huge deal.
So if phones are able to make games that look like this now, that's a really huge, awesome technological achievement.
It really is.
But they also progressed. Instead of it being like mobile games that are just ten years behind permanently,
they were making their own mobile like core engine shit.
And it's like paying five dollars to not have to wait ten minutes to play the next level and shit.
If mobile games just didn't ever do that, I think they would have like been, well they are huge.
And they're huge because it just preys on like gambling and fucking people's like need to not adapt to impatience and shit.
But what I mean is if it just stayed like this, if it was just ten years behind, that would be awesome.
Where am I going? They make the most money.
I know it's like it's just an obscene market. I know.
But if they just made games on it with the technology and not just at the same time developed the like vampire parasite neck bite that is all mobile gaming mechanics,
I think they would have, I would have liked it a lot more.
Brutal Templar Strike, a powerful version of the Templar Strike.
Who cares? Is there a jump?
There are some mobile games that are actually really fun too.
Alright.
XXX breaks shields.
Okay, so it's been 25 minutes.
I have five minutes to do something interesting or we're going to have to move on because this is just like a really, you know what this makes me want to play?
This makes me want to play Shadow of War.
I mean, what do you mean not enough?
We need a cut scene.
Oh shit, that's right.
I was about to just exit the game.
I forgot about the stupid prediction.
We do need a cut scene.
That's right.
After the next cut scene, maybe we'll get out of here and we'll put out a sneak king because I'm going to play that for 20 minutes.
You know it.
And then, holy shit, I got a big one for you.
I got a lot of Xbox and Xbox 360 games.
Why is that so hard?
Why was it?
Who's?
Is this talking?
Who's talking to me?
Why does this guy have a Batman voice?
That's just Batman.
Alright.
Brutal Templar Strike.
I don't have enough mana.
This is stupid.
Jeremy, you have to play Halo.
I'm not going to play Halo.
I don't like Halo.
Alright.
Can we give that a rest finally forever?
I don't like the game Halo.
I don't like the game.
I'm sorry.
I know everyone's going to be really mad at me.
I don't like Halo.
It's just a...
I don't like it.
It's not that I hate it.
I just don't enjoy playing it.
And when you have met with the prospective here of...
There's like five Halo games.
And everyone expects you to play them.
I'm going to die.
You got your Halo stream when me and Joel played it.
And then that was it.
It's never happening again.
Will you just kill him?
It's based gamer cringe.
Look.
I know Halo.
There's a big bunch of fans.
It's got a lot of support.
It's considered a very, very good shooter.
I know.
But we don't all have to like the same things.
Your journey ends here.
No opponent's going to make special, more devastating attacks.
The Super X.
Yes, we do.
No, we don't.
Look, if everybody liked the same things,
and you wouldn't be able to go watch a movie, love it,
and then go hate read the 30% Rotten Tomatoes critic article
about the movie.
You wouldn't be able to do that anymore.
All right.
Watch these icons try to block or dodge.
You got it.
No cut scene.
No, not yet.
Where's this mercenary leader?
Is this the leader?
So this is the leader.
Here come more of my boys.
Oh, shit.
Here they are.
Here they are, the boys.
Uh-oh.
I'm going to die.
Where is there a drink fountain?
It's the boys.
Isn't that from Warhammer?
Boston.
Oh, my God.
Kill him.
Reload has been knocked out?
What do you mean, reload?
Go to the knocked out character
and perform the revive action to help them.
If you don't help your fallen teammate in time,
you will lose the game.
What?
How the fuck am I supposed to revive him?
I can't revive him.
Not enough zeal?
Did I get him?
Look at this fucking bubble.
Are you kidding me?
Ah!
What?
Cutscene?
Oh, cutscene!
I said open it, you fucking psycho!
That door sucks.
You could lean a vacuum against that door
and it would fall over.
Really?
He's going to do it.
Ah!
He did it!
Yes!
How could you bet against one of his four animations?
How dare you?
What are you thinking?
Why the seagulls?
Is somebody like 15 feet to the right of us?
Who has like a burger basket from the boardwalk at the beach?
And there's just seagulls just fucking attacking this guy.
Get away from me!
No, these are my french fries!
Ow!
No!
Honey, honey, get him off me!
He like throws the basket of food to get away and run,
otherwise he's just going to get murdered.
Why are we coming back here?
Oh, it's been 30 minutes.
Honey, save yourself!
Honey, get the kids!
Next game?
No, not yet.
Wait, we have a new area.
Just give me a minute.
Congratulations, 16 million.
Going across to 1700 people.
You guys can't hear that.
Really?
Are you sure?
Finish this game.
I'm not going to...
No.
By the way, I also had the Burger King bumper cars game.
But I think I threw it in the trash accidentally.
I actually think I threw it away.
I don't know, I can't find it.
Find and slay the beast.
We have to see who the beast is, right?
Kill the beast.
Yes.
No, I'm sorry, we're not going anywhere.
Not yet.
No, guys, don't worry.
I'm not like a three to four hour Andy anymore.
Like, I'm doing once a week streams.
I'm here.
We've got time.
Don't worry.
What, the racing one?
I thought I had two or three of them.
Oh, and that was a bird noise.
Did he fall off?
I don't know.
They seem to be done.
They've ran out.
They ran...
Look out!
They used all their arrows in one volley.
I once got hit right in the head with an arrow.
Don't you?
Won't this make it worth it?
It'll make everything worth it, won't it?
If an arrow goes through his neck
and gives him Frankenstein bolts,
this will be worth it.
Ow!
Fuck, it hit me.
Come on.
Please, just hit this guy in the neck with an arrow.
That's all I want.
I got to try to stand right next to him
so it can't hit me.
God damn it!
No, hit him!
He's in the fucking way.
Why are they hitting me first?
He's standing in front of me.
Shoot him.
You...
They keep hitting us in the chest.
Fuck, I missed it.
Did we see it?
What's this?
Eat berries?
You don't eat random berries?
You don't know where they...
All right, can you imagine being one of these archers
and you've watched four arrows connect through this guy's chest
and stomach and stuff and he's still running up here?
Dogs.
Why are dogs just unfriendly?
Help me!
Wait, what?
Why is he dead?
They're not dead.
That's like...
They're playing dead.
A chest by an open fire.
Brutal frenzy boon.
Until the end of this chapter,
Roland has been granted brutal frenzy,
a powerful version of the frenzy skill.
Frenzy gives Roland a damage boost.
This is the shittiest chest I've ever seen in a video game.
You're telling me that inside of these chests
are motivational notes?
Who's the fucking asshole that did that?
There's no gold pieces,
potions, armor, jewels.
No.
It's motivational poetry.
They're fortune cookie chests.
Well, at least spin the paper around
and see what your lucky numbers are.
Wait, these are villagers?
Well, he's...
What?
I mean, judgmental.
Where are my coins?
I think he didn't bet on that.
That guy's way closer to his microphone
than everybody else in the whole game.
I'm staying right here.
No one will make me leave my home.
Okay.
Those are the Frosty King.
Are there choices?
All right, are there choices?
There are no choices in this game.
Too bad.
Next game?
I'm not going next game until we beat the beast.
Whoever the beast is,
and it's supposed to be this big giant mythical creature,
but it's gonna be just kind of a big guy with a flail.
That's who the beast is, in quotes.
$50,000 says I could do more trivia than you.
$100,000.
$90,000 says I'm faster than you.
Oh, yeah, beast?
I graduated from Yale.
Bring it on.
And they get every question wrong.
I don't want to kill these dogs.
I felt like I was alive for a second.
I thought, okay.
There's a skeleton in here.
Let me do the talking.
Don't give up, skeleton.
Read sign.
Oh, it's gonna be like,
this is my chest.
Please don't steal.
Here we go.
Here comes drama.
Welcome, Templars.
Have you seen the beast?
Is it near?
No, we haven't.
No, we are looking for it.
You're mad.
We're glad you're safe and sound here.
I like this game.
We can take care of ourselves.
Your swords, I can see.
Why are there so many animals in here?
Take them and save me.
The beast slaughters anyone in sight.
No, no, no.
That's, excuse me.
That's like go-to bed relaxation sounds.
I'm waiting for the,
where do they start playing the ocean one?
With a light thunderstorm.
He's here.
Wait, let me skip to the chase here.
How many legs does the beast have?
Two.
He has two legs.
He doesn't want you to come over.
He does not want you to come fight him.
And he does not care.
Mr. Pirate.
It's going to be a person.
It's not going to be an animal.
It's not going to,
it's going to be a human with a flail.
It's going to, oh wow.
It's a beast.
We've seen this movie 5,000 times.
Crack the beast to its lair.
Look around.
Oh, what's in here?
Jewels?
You have found a health burn.
You'll have one additional health orb
until the end of this level.
It's because you say it doesn't mean it's real.
It's a guy.
That's a guy.
I hope they use that.
Please use it.
It's my favorite sound.
Someone is in trouble.
This guy's going to be 12 stone.
Hey, here comes the guy.
All right.
Prediction time.
Let's let's have you guys spend a little bit,
a little bit of money.
Is the beast an animal?
Yes or no.
Is the beast an animal or monster?
Like, is, well, how about it?
Let me fix this.
Is the beast humanoid?
Like a human or like a human creature?
Is it like a bear?
Is the beast a bear?
Is that better?
How do I word this the best
so the semantics people don't get mad at me?
Is the beast a guy?
Humanoid or beast?
All right.
That's a good one.
Is it?
No, no, no.
It has to be yes or no.
Does it have more than two legs?
Okay.
That's good.
Bipedal.
That's the one.
Is the?
No, because it could be like a stand up bear
like walking around with like hands.
No, no, no.
More than two legs is not.
I don't think that's fair.
Humanoid is the beast humanoid?
Done.
That's what it is.
It's human.
Humanoid is subjective.
All right.
Is the beast human?
Yes or no?
Why are we complicating this?
You guys just stand to lose a shitload of money.
Does it matter?
Does the beast have feathers?
This is a big bird.
Being a human is subjective.
Please.
All right.
Is the beast human?
Yes or no?
I like that.
Wait.
I don't want to give away any spoilers.
Because that guy next to me could be like,
Oh, yeah, that sounds just like the wolves in my town.
Is the beast human?
Does the beast come from?
What do you mean by human?
All right.
Here we go.
It's too quiet.
Does the beast feel?
Oh, the beast slayer.
Okay.
This is like a castle.
Ambush the beast here.
Yeah.
We're going to jump out.
It's going to be a guy holding firewood.
Walking back.
Walking back with a big axe or something.
He's going to be a big guy, right?
He's going to be holding firewood.
Walking slowly with the firewood.
And we're going to realize it's a human.
That's what's going to happen.
That's like a big guy.
Is that a guy?
That's a big guy, right?
That's just a huge guy.
What is it?
Is it a guy?
That's just a guy.
It's just a big huge...
Wait, don't close the prediction yet.
We don't know.
We can't tell yet.
I don't know if it's a human or not.
Not human.
But it could be.
What if it is?
We don't know.
You don't know that yet.
Just wait till he talks.
It's a troll.
We don't know what it is yet.
We don't know.
It's just the beast right now.
We're going to bring him down to like 10% health.
And we're going to get like a fucking Psycho Mantis monologue.
Just wait.
I didn't even knock him down.
That was him.
Fuck off, mate.
How could you hate dogs?
See, who's dead?
What?
Pump?
Why does that say...
What do you mean, pump?
I can't revive him.
Hurry!
I need to revive him!
How do I build up my meter?
Oh my god, he stomped on me.
Revive him!
I need to revive that guy.
He's going to die.
How do I build my meter?
Get the fuck off of me!
Oh my god, he's going to die.
How much time do I have before he is dead?
Wait, what?
Where are we restarting from?
He's human.
I don't know!
Wait, what do you mean?
Do I have to start all the way back here?
No, we don't.
He's a troll.
I need to beat him so we can confirm that.
Let's go.
He's a pretty one.
The beast.
This could be just a guy.
It's very possible this is a guy.
Like the witch!
The witch in the woods turned me into this.
I didn't want to be like this, fellas.
It was the witch and her dark heart.
He's stuck.
Watch out for the dogs.
You good?
Can I block?
Watch out!
Get up!
He's angry.
Uh oh.
Ah, you mammoth.
He didn't say die, troll.
Oh my god, he's going to die.
Can I revive him?
Come on, I got to revive him and go southbound.
Give me a break.
Not enough.
I have a full one.
Watch out for the dogs.
He's stuck.
Get him.
Knocked down.
Okay, here we go.
This is it.
All right, who is he?
He's like the butcher in the town.
He's like the barber or something.
But what is it?
No way.
He did it.
That's canon in the game.
He's human.
He didn't say troll.
He didn't say ogre.
He said human.
Game over.
Oh man, that's unfortunate that he said human.
Can I go in?
It is blocked.
I'm broke.
He was making all those kinds of like troll noises too.
I'm so sorry everybody, but it was confirmed in game that he was a human.
Game sucks.
Next game.
Now.
Look, you can be mad and annoyed.
Hold on.
Not yet.
I don't have my fill of this game yet.
Oh Jesus.
He just got crushed.
That was a really weird cut.
That was anime intro cut.
That was right before the breakdown.
That's when it's like...
And it cuts to like the next part.
Where like this shows like the animated fighting and stuff.
Why do you hate us so much?
I'm enjoying my video game called Templars.
I don't even know what it's called.
Melting in my seat watching this.
You're fine.
Turn the AC on.
Put a fan in your room.
I don't know.
You're going to be fine.
Ow.
What?
Oh.
I got you.
Watch out for this one, dude.
Careful.
Uh oh.
Dogs.
That sounded like a sneeze.
Didn't work.
What?
Hey, are these dogs human or not?
More dogs.
Oh my god.
I hate this part.
Get them off me.
The next chapter I'm done.
I don't know.
I'm having fun.
Where's your clues?
Something may be hidden nearby.
Keep your eyes open.
Something may be hidden.
Oh no.
I have to find the hidden chest.
Please stop playing this game.
I beg you.
Begging me?
You're begging me to stop playing?
I'm sorry.
There are no negotiations right now.
There is no such thing as a negotiation right now.
We've crossed the 30 minute mark, which means I'll be here for six hours.
That's how this game works.
Just kidding.
Don't take that seriously, please.
If you do, then I don't know what to tell you.
I don't know what I can do to tell you.
This is where we're going to find out who the bad guy of the game is.
We're going to find out who the beast was, right?
He was cursed by a witch, by a warlock,
and they're cursing people in the town, turning them into humans, monsters.
And stand a chance against the beast.
Your monsters stand a chance against our swords.
I'm not going to complete the game.
I have to play Sneak King for at least 20 minutes.
Listen, our holy sword, will you take it?
You don't have to repay us.
100% platinum.
Trying to pawn off a rusty blade.
Oh, she said it.
No one's seen him ever since.
Let's see.
That voice, I love this voice.
He sounds like somebody.
Disney character.
Oh, go to the outfit screen.
Employ uniform.
Commander arms.
Collect all pieces to unlock the weapon.
Why even have this?
There are 50 gifted subs.
Holy shit, from Zyxia.
We have 50 immunity subs.
Do I have to fight them?
I don't even have to fight them.
Can I leave?
Well, I think I messed everything up here.
Say something funny.
All right.
I just switched characters.
I switched characters to revive.
What?
All right, so I have to revive him now.
Isn't the one-eyed man, isn't that Bigfoot?
The person doesn't exist.
Why use that there?
Why put that there of all the places?
It was such a weird place to put that.
Spugleberry.
Oh, excuse me.
Here it comes.
This audio seems...
They're all talking from weird directions.
So loud.
Sound mixing.
Yeah, the sound mixing is very bad.
So loud.
No.
Before, I would have been doing it three or four hours ago.
Speak to Brother Lorenzo.
Wait, one of you guys, Brother Lorenzo?
No.
I'm almost done.
I promise.
There really is Geralt.
That's who it was.
Oh, hurry up.
Where's Lorenzo?
Don't touch that.
Don't touch stuff.
I'm not going to sit here and listen to a thousand years of lore.
Where's the sermon?
This is very mediocre.
Well, when did this come out?
I'm going to say 2008.
2009?
Thousand and...
Where's the thing?
It doesn't say what year.
What year did this come out?
I can't see it on the back of the box.
2001?
No, it's not.
2011.
Yeah, there it is.
That's ten years old.
Which is the greatest sin?
To torture a man's body, to save his soul, or to stand idle?
Devil consumes him.
If you, the righteous, do not oppose the devil...
How old is Skyrim?
...evil still lives.
But now the Inquisition stands against it.
I can see the purifying flames...
Watch that cuff.
...I can see a future free of the devil.
Same year?
The same year?
Bless you all.
Bioshock came out before this?
I don't know why I did that.
What brings you here, Templar Brothers?
Slade the Beast.
Praise the Lord.
Your deed will be well remembered, Inquisition.
Please 100% play through Sneak King rather than one more minute of this.
Alright, fine.
We've lost an hour.
I got what I wanted out of this.
I thought it was fun.
But it's time to put in...
The Inquisition.
Sneak King.
I thought it was fun.
Wait.
Follow Brother Lorenzo to find out more information about Marie's location.
Approach with caution.
Because getting too close will make him suspicious.
But don't fall too far behind or you'll lose him along with all the hopes of finding Marie.
Oh, it's a fucking escort quest.
We can't fail it.
It really is an Assassin's Creed walk behind the guy mission.
Stop, please.
But wait.
I need to see what happens.
Alright, fine.
Fine, fine, fine, fine.
I'll stop.
Fine, fine, fine, fine, fine.
I just want to see what happens if he gets really annoyed.
Like, if I click on him enough times, is he going to do a funny response?
Or he makes like a fart noise and goes like,
Oh, sorry.
That was me.
Stop.
Stop it.
Get out of here.
Leave me alone.
You're annoying.
Hello?
Can I help you?
Praise God.
Alright.
Alright, alright, alright.
Okay, okay, okay.
Okay.
Listen, you're hearing the, you heard the case open.
This is the Sneak King CD.
It's about to go in.
Here we go.
Is this synced up?
Is the audio synced up?
I didn't really get a chance to see that.
Don't lie to me.
I want to make sure it looks good.
We'll fix it.
Is it?
Is it bad?
Tested it earlier.
Yeah, but people just say go because they don't want to wait like five minutes.
Alright.
When did this game come out?
You know, I know this game has been a meme.
It was a meme when it came out, but I never played it.
I don't, I have no idea what this game, I know you like sneak around in like trash cans
and stuff.
2006.
This is terrifying.
Remove the context of the Burger King.
This is a guy in a Burger King costume coming to kill everyone in this house.
You know what I mean?
Like it's just a costume.
How long is this intro?
Sneak King.
This is on FMV, right?
Display view cones.
Play in the sneaking suit.
Okay.
How to play.
Move.
This is first person mode.
Move camera.
Change zoom.
Surprise.
Flourish.
Hide and cancel and run.
Wait, this is 12 pages?
Use the stick to make the King sneak around.
Move the camera with R.
If controller settings have been switched.
Yeah, whatever.
In a challenge, hold the right trigger to run.
Just go.
Yeah, who cares?
Each time you deliver food, your chain count goes up.
This multiplies any score you earn.
If anyone spots you, you'll lose it all.
This will be extra sneaky when your chain count gets high.
Burger gear solid.
Burger.
Hey, then!
Thanks for the 10 community subs, yeah?
Missions zero and a 20.
Do I have to deliver food to people?
Sawmill challenge.
It's morning and you've got enormous omelet sandwiches to give away.
Make three deliveries to the hungry folks in the sawmill.
Consider this breakfast mission accomplished.
Press the A button to deliver food, but try not to be seen.
How am I supposed to deliver food to people if I can't be seen?
I can't deliver food.
I'm like fucking Fortnite taunting this guy.
How do I deliver food to him?
Delivery zero.
How do I deliver food?
Where's the gun?
How do I deliver food to people?
Oh, that person wants a hamburger.
Okay, that person.
Just give them food.
Why do I have to do this?
If people ordered food, why wouldn't they just want it?
Was this game free?
All right, so sneak up behind everybody.
And then surprise them with a delicious six-out-of-ten whopper,
because that's what it is.
Sawmill.
Oh, wait, I can interact with this.
His head just gets fucking sliced off.
I just jumped into the sawmill.
Wait.
Come on, somebody come over here.
You don't feed everybody, only the ones who want burgers.
Oh, are they just people on the minimap?
I don't know why I just asked if it was fall damage.
I was about to say, is there fall damage?
This person wants a burger, right?
Oh, somebody wants one over here.
I see it on the minimap.
I have to find the person that wants one on the minimap
and then go sneak to them.
That guy doesn't want it anymore.
God damn it.
All right, I get it.
I get it.
Everyone told me to skip the tutorial.
Flourish.
Okay, is that one?
I want to, like, hide in the saw machine and scare somebody.
Why would you scare, like, a sawmill employee?
That seems like the dumbest thing you could possibly do.
New missions have been unlocked.
Okay, well, I get it.
Let's see.
Doesn't matter.
All right, let's keep going.
Now what?
Wait, did I not get a good enough score?
This morning you got into rank C.
No, decline.
Handing over hash browns is enough.
You've got style.
Why not use it to deliver a serving of hash browns
with the flourish?
Okay.
I did it.
Wait, is this one map?
Is it just one map?
This game had to, this game came free
in Burger King Happy Meals or whatever they were.
A true Sneaking would never keep the buttery goodness
of those croissant witches to himself.
He delivered these to three hungry citizens
as fast as possible, and he'd do it in style
without touching any blue vision zones.
I thought there were arrows coming out of his, like, crotch,
like somebody shot him twice with arrows.
I was like, who fucking gutted this guy with arrows?
All right, who's hungry?
This game was four bucks.
Did they, where did they sell it?
Did they sell it at Burger King?
How could you, where did you buy this game?
Oh, look at me.
You did?
I can't get spotted.
Somebody's hungry over here.
Is that guy still hungry?
That person's hungry.
What happened?
Oh shit, they're coming this way.
I need to, I need to dump a body in here.
Wait, won't they just see me?
Wouldn't you just see this person?
Everyone's so hungry.
I'm not doing my job.
Over here, come on.
Watch out.
Get away, go away, go away.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait,
come here, come here, come here, come here, come here, come here,
come here, come here, come here come, come here, come here, come on
Please play the next game.
The next game is going to,
It's gonna I'm gonna half I'm gonna tell you guys the next game is gonna be very very hard to get me away from
The next game is gonna be impossible for us to move on
I'm actually probably gonna play it last cuz I'm terrified that I'm gonna stay there forever
And I get this person this person coming around the side here. Is there a time limit? I think there is no not too human
But holy shit, I should get it
Right here. Oh fuck. Oh
fuck
New missions have been unlocked. I told me this is bad too human is free since they can't legally sell it anymore
What?
They can't legally sell it free flourishes without being seen kind of curious if there's anything else in this game. Let's do this fast
The unreal engine lawsuit thing only they don't nobody sells it. Anyways, you'd be buying it secondhand no matter what you did
I got to cut this tree down. It's gonna kill that would hurt somebody you're gonna hurt someone
The person this person passed out from like being hungry
Walked on their body
People just dropping like flies
Not good enough. Why wait till everyone passes out? I just beat it
Oh was that when that one quote was not a quote wouldn't be quote, but that was quote not good enough
Sneak king. I think there's more than one location. I switched the goblin commander or are we are we done with this?
What do you think? That's what's next? I'm breaking the rule here
This has not been 30 minutes. It's been 20
deliver double the jolts by not only surprising some lucky sawmill worker with a stimulating cup of BK Joe coffee
But doing it from within a hiding place. Oh
Wow, next game, please. No, I
Got to deliver some BK Joe
Get away from me. His head is so big
Alright, here comes somebody I interest you in a cup of BK Joe. Just sit here until somebody's there. This game sucks next game
Just so wait a minute. I need to scare somebody into drinking coffee
This person's coming who human is a hundred percent free on Xbox live. Is it really I?
Maybe I should get it. Would you guys want to watch to human you you will for maybe like an hour?
All right. This is not a good place to be
Sneak King
Should I hide in the outhouse? I want to see other games. Yeah, I know me too
I feel like we're gonna play Goblin Commander for a while
Let's get this out of our system. So nobody tells me Ben begs me to go back to play Sneak King
Have this guy right here. No, they're gonna pass out before I get a chance. Come on. This is stupid a
Sneak King
Dropping like flies. Yeah, are you supposed to hide and do this if this happens?
Goblin come Goblin commander is an RTS. What it does not look like an RTS. It looks like a
Game you have a bunch of goblins go do things for you. No one's even come over here
This is stupid
Yes, this is Sneak King
Everybody remembers this very fondly for being hilarious and crazy and zany and comedy and memes
As you see
This is what this is it. This is it
It's not like that funny. It's not that like crazy and rare. It's just stupid
So all the people that you've heard talk about like, oh my god
Oh my god, what type of Burger King did this thing? Oh my god
Listen where they made an Xbox game where you snuck around as a king and gave him like frappuccinos and stuff
It was so ridiculous. It was the funniest ad campaign ever. Oh, this was dumb. This game sucks
Like this is what it was. This is what they were. This is what they were talking about
Wait, who said that?
I don't know
We're making up a straw man to knock it down and can make what and be you know
Annoyed at a person that might not even exist. Welcome to the world. Welcome to 2021
I'm very angry at a theoretical person
This person could exist. I don't know. Maybe I like the previous game
I need to just do this, but if I don't beat the first level then I'll never hear the end of it
You're turning into Andy. No, no, you're turning into goofy. What did I come with me? Goofy? What do you mean?
Takes an hour to beat the first level
No, what? Okay. Well, this is the only time I'm ever gonna play this. I didn't get it when Burger King put it out
I didn't play it now. I
Don't want to miss out on the fun. I don't want to have to remember
This game ever again. I don't want to slow down. Don't do it. Don't get into that
How am I supposed to do this? Where can I hide till I get somebody? No, there's only one person that walks in the path of a
What about over here?
Finish this game for 200 million off the debt. That's not worth it to me because sure
I could finish the game and get 200 million off the debt, but
You will that this is gonna get nominated for worst stream if I play sneaking for like another four hours
This will be nominated for worst stream of the year. So like what am I gonna do? That's not enough. There we go. It already is
Oh
We say funny things we think we say things that are funny, don't we?
Look at how funny the funny things we say are right. We do a little trolling here
Just me the streamer and my like army of trolls
Seething. All right. I'm done. I don't want to play this anymore. This game's not good
Hey, you're just a man. All right, we're gonna make up a bunch of people in a room
We're gonna make them up because that's what we're doing right now
See like I just see like five or six people sitting around on a couch
They all have big large Burger King drinks like big like super size like 40 ounce drinks fountain drinks
And this is like they've already eaten the Burger King food
they're just laughing hysterically and like
This crack is like six or seven people on this couch and every time you jump out and do like the dance you hear like
And then like
They're all at the end of their drinks because they've drank almost a large fucking coke all of them and they all think it's so funny
I just keep seeing them laughing at this and it's making me angry
At a bridge
Here's your chance to elevate your sneaking to an art form worthy of that of robe and crown
Live for five of these enormous omelette sandwiches without being seen or hurt really pushing the omelette sandwich
Which may be the grossest thing on the whole menu? So
They that omelette sandwich omelette sandwich omelette sandwich. It's terrible
It's the worst thing on the menu
They must have had a stockpile of like 600 million of these that they had to really get rid of these were terrible
What was the what was I don't even know what the thing was?
This would be a good game if it was an RPG. Oh
I'm a headache. I don't know the Kings got like a big migraines like not based anti-corporation streamer
Anti-corporation yeah, you guys can trust me. You guys can trust me. I'm an anti-corporation streamer. Trust me
How does it make see me what?
based corporate pill
How does that even mean trying to figure out that means? All right, I need to do this. I'm stuck in this stupid game
Everybody laughs. Okay. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. All right. It's time to make everybody that comes to the channel
That's new. I think this is like the worst like fucking cringe community ever. Okay, we have you have to play along
We have to make it so any time I do the king dance
We all laugh really hard and we didn't like just do you don't have to laugh that hard
Don't give don't make it that obvious
Just do omega lows make sure it's like all omega lows and then we'll go back to normal, right?
Like we have to be like, oh my god, I love that dance
We don't do it like five or six times in a row
Okay, we have to make people think that we think this is really funny then they never come back. Are you ready?
Don't do it now. You'd fucking it up stuff
No, you do it reusing the joke
It's not reusing a joke. It's I love this routine. Okay, I'm gonna do this routine whenever I'm able to I
Love the like get ten people to think that this whole community is fucking crazy
Stop doing it. You're doing it wrong. Just wait. Come on. You guys are way better than this
Just wait. Yeah, like just wait
We already are it no, but like they don't they don't know that right away
It takes about a year being here in this community before you figure out. Holy shit. We're all like nuts. I
Don't want them to have to wait that long
Is this like links house? Where am I?
Imagine if I just grab this guy by the shirt and pull him off like hitman
Stop no, it don't I I'm you have to wait till I get into character. I'm not in character yet. You're blowing it
It's only when I do the dance and then that's it
Just wait till I do the day it's when I do the the arm up dance
Everyone has to do it and then stop let's kick this lady. I here we go. Go go go go go go go go go go one
two three, oh
my god
Watch out. Watch out. Watch out. I
Completely forgot about this game. Oh no
Oh
crap
Got me and my buddies would sit on the couch right when this came out. It was so much fun
I remember we would just sit on the couch. It was like five or six of us
But we would just laugh at this shit. The king is so funny
It's so funny
What should I do? Should I hide like in the leaves? I wonder if I can I get somebody like this? What the heck was that? Oh
Somebody's coming somebody's coming. So he's coming. It's so funny. What happened to that guy?
Like I get like you're seriously barely could say that I know it's coming too
This is so classic. I love it. This is like classic 90s comedy
Okay, here we go. It's gonna happen again
Look at that stupid dance. I love those two. That's like my favorite item. This is the omelet. Here comes a two in a row
That's two in a row but that seriously is like probably my favorite sandwich
I wish I would bring that back bring back the omelet sandwich. Everybody loved it. It's been at least me and my friends did
We would order it me like me and like four or five us we'd go to the drive-thru and it'd be like hey
Bros, what are we getting and at the same time?
We would all kind of side eye each other and then after like three or four seconds, we'd go omelet sandwich and we'd pull in
So funny, I love it. I'm gonna go this way. Oh
Nothing nothing beat that. Is everybody alright? Hopefully everyone gets up soon
Those are the days I did really was back in like the mid 90s like late 90s mid 90s
I wanted like the drive-thru with like your buddies and stuff. I
Missed that like yeah, you can't do that shit anymore. I mean
Like only only in like 1998 did you could you go to like a drive-thru like a Burger King drive-thru McDonald's drive-thru?
You can't like did nobody just keep you don't do that
They only did that back in like the 90s
How much better the toys were too?
It was so much better than they are now
We would trade I remember when I was younger. This is probably I don't know maybe like three or four years ago
Friends of ours that we would get the Happy Meals and stuff and we would look at each other
We'd side eye each other and be like who's trading who and sometimes we would get the same things
Like let's say it was like a Hot Wheels thing two of us three of us would get the same car
It'd be like oh shit RNG. We would all start laughing
Oh
It's so funny I
Should I should dress up as the king in my next dream and do that dance?
And like present you guys like a sandwich. I don't have to do two more. Oh
So hungry got it. Can I get two in a row?
That's my favorite part right there. He does like the knees
I'm sad that we're not gonna be able to see it again
After this mission and I get this guy. Oh
Oh
Crap I run. Oh, I just missed it. This game is hilarious
I know and people forgot about it people forgot this existed
I'm the only one that remembers me and my friends on the couch
This is the only people that know this exists. No one else does only us only my four friends
Sitting on the couch with our large cokes. I did it. I can't do it anymore. It's too much for me
Stop I have to stop stop doing this that was going on for a while too
And I wonder how many people came and left. Thank God one more mission. I have to do seven
Lucky seven. I want to see them another map
Game. Oh my god. What a classic. That was so convincing
No, it wasn't at all. Actually, it was just it was so unconvincing that maybe it was convincing game books
HD it was concerning
All right. Hold on sometimes surprise and sneak ability on enough at those times
You need to pick up your robe and turn on the speed deliver croissant which breakfast sandwiches to three people
Why what's in the breakfast sandwiches?
30 seconds. I don't think I can do that. I was acting straight up from the room. It's pretty good acting in that actually
Oh shit, I got it. Oh mega love got it
Oh
It's like an angry cat
Now that was a real like that was a real joke that you would have heard
During that routine two minutes ago. I'm stuck in that routine. I think
Waiting to see I'm waiting to look over and see everybody laughing
What the fuck this game sucks moving on wait, I want to do it one more time. I can get it
I just want to see the laughing
Omega little not laughing aren't psychopaths usually good at acting you just said I was bad at acting therefore
I'm not a psychopath. Is that what you're talking about? There's no I frames there
So if you get stuck there when you get out somebody's next to you, you're gonna get caught. I got it. All right, I'm done
I have to get out of here. Why is the king so huge? That's enough. Yeah, that's enough
Let's go to Goblin commander. I have high hopes or Goblin commander. That's why I'm waited this long to play it
I have high hopes for the next game as well
That's why I'm waiting to play that one last because I feel like if I play that one right now like I'll get stuck playing it
Guaranteed so you think sneak King will be?
Well, okay. So do you guys think burger King will still be a company in 50 years or a hundred years?
I think about that sometimes if you think about like the games that not the games that the companies in the places now
They're probably not gonna exist in a hundred plus years. I don't think so
Doesn't three. Oh my god, it'll be the only thing left to eat
Goblin commander
Why does this look like when you get an iPhone game on your iPad?
They have to press the 2x button on the bottom right and that's how you automatically know to uninstall it
Actually looks pretty sick. I make this look any better
Is it an RTS? It looks good though. It's kind of bright
campaign
Humans won't be around in a hundred years a campaign
Do I have to make a name?
About her mom the three letters. It's more than three letters. Okay, there we go. Don't matter. Whatever
Only beasts will be left. I don't know what the hell is gonna be left. Probably just bugs and insects
It's gonna be insects and alligators
Was not so much born as we were created
Wrought through the power on stone by the human
Granted purpose granted life and made whole
Gonna come on this one. You can stop the cringe routine
Said anything a great machine that would grant us beyond our wildest dreams
I'm gonna verse the alligator which one wins
Alligator
What are the animals that lasted the million years from like the Jurassic period that's what's gonna still be around
horseshoe crabs crocodiles
Bugs like insects
Here we go
Time to create my I'm the bad guy in this game, right?
Take goblins and I try to go over the world
Higgins, I don't think chickens gonna last
Back into it there's plenty of work to be done
You hear a boss man say put your back into it
What happened to me the goblin commander this glowing blue character is the spirit form of grumble your goblin commander
To move your commander use the left thumb stick to move the camera use the right thumb stick
Oh to move your commander use the left thumb stick to move the camera use the right thumb stick
Says scroll, but I can't scroll
Okay, if you your mission objectives press right on the directional pad, right?
And the list has been updated the check mark icon located next to the right of the directional pad with flash
Stop laughing
Your first mission objective is to move the commander over to the help pad at the south end of the room
All right, here we go move my commander
This is a help pad to access it direct the commander over it and press left on the directional pad to exit the help
Press either left on the it's all the highlighting of the words
It's the I hate that just let me read it
Let's turn directional pad to exit the help press either left on the directional pad or the y button
As I said don't crush your clan we're finished here
Time to move up
My stomach. All right. I'm gonna start banning humans
Move your clan press the clan button
Okay, place a waypoint flag at the location of your commander to defend a structure place a waypoint flag on it
Okay, so we need to defend how do I move the camera? Oh that way. Okay defend this structure
Over there. Here they go. It is an rts
Remove your clan and press the clan button
To place a waypoint flag at the at the location of your commander to defend a structure place a waypoint flag on it
What do I need to defend this?
Am I attacking that?
I own this
Don't destroy that. All right, nobody's leaving till it gets rebuilt what that wasn't defend structure
Well, whatever it's tutorial. Let's go
Me and my goblin army
Come on, come on, you gotta get some snappy you gotta get make noises
He makes songs retrieve help on just about any object in the game move the commander over it or approach it while in direct
Control and press left on the directional pad. Whatever. Let's go the game is this is goblin commander. It actually looks pretty good
Blame this
All right, let's go
stone crushers
We go through this
How we open this this is what the germa community looks like. Um, it's like six of you
There's more than six people here
What is this?
breakable objects many of the
Objects found in the world are breakable to order your clan to attack an object place a waypoint flag on it
Sword icon will appear right?
All right, so break it what's in there?
points, ooh break it all
Break it. You like this game. I don't know. I have to play it first
Destroy all boulders in the area. That's the mission. Okay, I bet you like
It dirty rts lover
What is that but why
An rts lover that's bad to feel like the genre rts starcraft 2 still popular
Grind the vermin into pulp. There's a waypoint flag near them using the appropriate clan button. Okay, let's go
Attack this is what we would this is why are we playing this game?
Us too. Look at how funny this is. Look at how look at how many jokes it is you guys
Shit it is this is you guys
Okay
Direct to take direct control position the commander over it and press the y button
Oh shit, this game just got so much better. Okay. I got direct control over this guy
Let's go direct control pressing the a button while standing in front of an object will cause your clan to attack it
As long as it's breakable
and
Oh
Assuming to wait. I want to release how do I release out of this guy? Is it got to die?
I don't want to be the different. I want to be the guy with the whip. This is cool. I like this
What's the mission destroy all the boulders it's goblin pikmin, but you can actually control the pikmin
We're almost out of the tutorial
This game rare I think this is a rare game
I love playing rare games for you guys
As you can see like what it was like playing games that weren't rare when I was your age
Contact sensitive tool tips related to objects and characters nearby on the controller made to appear in the upper right center of the screen
Yeah, I say so it's like it's like legends of zelda
It might not even be like legend of zelda. That's just ocarina of times the only game I played
Why are you reading the tips?
Because if I don't i'm gonna miss something. I mean, it's gonna be horrible
I have 176 bucks
Is a lazy lump of a stone ogre sleeping on the job
Okay, we're gonna go get him
Might even put him back to work
I feel like i'm watching
a stream
Of somebody streaming a game back in like 2010. I don't feel like i'm playing this game
I feel like i'm watching the stream of this game
It's huge
all right
Prediction is this guy human or not?
Titans are powerful monstrosities that through direct control can be used to inflict heavy damage
To take direct control of a titan position the commander over it and press the y button Aaron
While in direct control use the various buttons in order your titan to attack to adjust the camera
Aaron Aaron use the right thumbstick
Looks like he's an injured need to feed him so he can heal himself. Holy shit
What did I just do health halo located around the unit's base?
Health halos represent the unit's current state when the halo is green
The unit is in good health when it's yellow. The unit is in fair health and when it is red
The unit is in poor health and will likely die if it takes any more damage
I need to get health I get to be this huge guy. This is perfect eat
well
That was funny when you killed me
How do I open how do I get out of here use the stone or go to eat all the critters in the room?
This is I love this part
It's like my favorite part
What if I eat the commander hold on can I eat the commander?
Oh shit. I'm the commander now. Why why am I yellow open the door to eat all of them?
Am I poisoning everybody? What am I doing? How am I my?
I had to eat all of them not just get to green
The debris is from that cave in should have been cleaned up hours ago time to get to work
All those all that money
All right, let's clear this out
Well, I love this this guy. Okay
This game when I first got in and I was looking at what the game was like
Oh, you have to like walk around
It was like a four out of ten for me and I was going to just move on in like 20 minutes
Now this changes everything. I'm just standing around and gawking get in there and help
Following Titans to instruct a clan to follow your Titan pull and hold the left trigger and double tap the clan button
Pull and hold the left trigger then press the appropriate clan button to place a waypoint flag
Oh, okay
So then they'll just go there double tap what's going on left trigger and then like they stand here
Break up all debris in the room
Didn't I do that already? No, it's debris over here. He had it you double tap to follow. Oh, okay
I don't I can't step on them and crush them. Can I?
Really fun place where it reminds me of this really funny game
Me and my buddies like called sneak kings check it out sometime. I think you'd enjoy it. Were you on the couch?
Are you on the couch all with lar extra large cokes?
down to the ice
If not, then I don't care about what you have to say
Instruct your units to follow the stone ogre and lead them to the door
Break rocks. It's a blade worm and it's stirred up more of those filthy critters. We must destroy it. Everyone doesn't care about chat
No, I don't all right. You got it out of me. It took you six straight fucking years. You finally got it out of me
I don't like it. I don't like chat
I've been bottling this up for 10 years. Okay
ah
my god
like seriously
I'm trying to keep it together. But oh that person said the burger king thing
And my teeth were just clenching the whole time. He said it
Uh
I won so was collected 44 gold collected 446 two units lost
This game's fun. I like this
Everyone sit down clip it clip it
We're doing our best
Here comes the here comes the meltdown. Here it is the career ending meltdown
You say psych you hurt my feelings
Rise in time time for work on the count of three i'm coming in there one
Two
Enter the clan shrine and create five miners
Oh, this is the stone crusher clan shrine here. You can buy goblins unlock caged goblins and upgrade your units
To navigate the clan shrine use the left thumbstick
goblins cost resources
Which are displayed at the bottom of the screen to buy the highlighted goblin press the a button
And it'll appear outside the clan shrine
Moving to the current waypoint for the clan
No clan can have more than 10 goblins at any time
Notice the stone crusher icon located at the bottom left of the screen
This indicates how many goblins are currently in the clan. I gotta retake that retake
That's bad take to exit the clan shrine plus plus the y button
All right, we need miners miner. How many do we need?
All right, five miners goblins
I want uh, I want rock throwers. Why not?
Well time is resources
Now that we slept half a day away, we need to scour the area for golden souls
I want direct control of this guy
If it's analog control, then it's not an rts for me. It's more fun to play
Fake gamer. Why do you hate real video games?
Do I have to answer that question?
You you want you need do you want me to answer that question? Why do I hate real video games?
I would like you to name me a video game. That's come out in the last year
That you would like me to play right now
That all of us can sit here and agree is a game that it should be played
That should be here. Which one?
Hades
I already played hades and it was great
I played I played street of lake three times and I played a shit load of it off stream and I got like the hardest achievements
In the game. It was really fun like gold by smashing them where the boulders
No games aren't good. Only old games are good
Go back to the shrine and strengthen the equipment
Only old games are fun
Oh tools and played jack and dexter it came out in 2001
I don't like want to play that. I can I be I have to be honest again. I don't
I don't know jack and dexter
Zack and wiki mike and ike
I I don't want to play. I don't want to play them. Not a big fan located on the front pedestals in the clan shrine
Each clan has a set of three upgrades
First to apply to all goblins in the clan while the last applies to the clan support unit
Each of these upgrades can be purchased three times. All right, cool. Let's get it
I'll say cameras are strong armor
What this is another one too, what's the other one this jack and dexter
What's the other one? It's like a it's like a little rat a little bunny rabbit guy
Oh my god, it has like all like the wacky guns
Insomniac made it
Ratchet and clank. Yeah
They all seem like the same like dream characters to me. All right, find additional any find additional souls. Let's go
Are they the same? I don't know. It's a isn't it like
Short small guy with like funny weasel companion, right?
There's like a and the in the weasel companion is like a technological like intelligent person and they have like funny lines
It's like a comedic comic relief
It's like the small small like guy with big like goofy weapon and then comic relief weasel character, right?
That like jack and dexter
jack and wiki
Uh ratchet and clank who's clank? No, I don't put banjo kazooie in that category because banjo kazooie don't have big uh goofy weapons
It's a robot. He's the robot. Does he have comedy lines though?
Does he does he pop up on?
The shoulder and say like a comedy line in a cutscene, right? I don't know if
If you have if you have and in the middle of your game title
I'm not sure i'm gonna play it or i'm not i'm not gonna like get too involved. That is what it is
That's what it is. That's what it is. Oh my god run run run run run run run run run run run run run run run
Run, I just walked into like a death trap get out get out get out. They're gonna die
Sly and cooper. All right, they're dead. I just like killed everybody sam and max. Yeah, but I didn't play the third one
Zack and cody. I never I didn't watch that show. I did not watch zack and cody. I didn't watch drake and josh
I didn't play zack and wiki. I didn't play jack and dexter. I didn't play
I didn't play ratchet and clank
Anything that has an and in the middle of it. I did not care about what are some other ones mac and cheese
I actually don't really like mac and cheese
But wait, I don't know
Mac and cheese is not mac and cheese. It's mac and cheese like this. It's like mac n
Apostrophe cheese, but I don't really eat it dungeons and dragons don't really like that
I'm not a big fan of that game simpsons hit and run don't no that doesn't that's that's not accurate
That's simpsons hit
And run a hit and run
Is like a thing happening a hit and run is like it's an action
It's not like something and something black and white. Yeah. All right, you might got me there
You might have me there rick and morty. I don't know. I'm not a i'm not a huge fan
What else no two names two names like two names?
Tell them do we have any more? I don't like two names
Am and jerry. Yeah, I didn't I don't want to watch that fucking movie. I don't want to watch it pain and lynch
That game's not fun. I played it because we're we had a timer tim and eric. Oh shit. There you go
Yeah, that's right. But wait a minute tim and eric the title of that show
Was tim and eric awesome show great job. It wasn't the show was not called tim and eric. It was tim and eric
Awesome show great job wallace and grommet. I didn't really watch it. I didn't really care for it
I thought it was like cool, but I didn't watch it because it was two characters with an and in the middle
Sex and the city. No. Yeah, didn't watch that fucking show either didn't care about it at all
I didn't want to watch one episode ren and stimpy and you've got it right there. It was not ren
And stimpy it was ren
Ampersand stimpy completely different. I would watch that show a thousand times. It's not rick ampersand morty
It's rick and morty don't want to watch it. That like actually is weird how that's true for me
If it was if it was jack ampersand dexter, I might like care. Why is that weird?
That's weird. Why do I do that ed ed and eddie?
I didn't I did not watch that much of that show. I think I watched like two episodes
All right
I need to make new people because I lost everybody
Problems like the rock throw that are not available appear in cages to unlock a cage like the desire goblin using left
I'm seeing presented to one two, three, four five
Okay, plenty of miners. Let's go. All right. I got ten units now hate conjunctions and english grammar
I mean, I it's just a weird thing rocket and ratchet ampersand clank. Don't do the same thing. I just did please
What are you doing? Please? Don't do that. What am I doing?
run away
Alvin and hubs. Oh shit soul fountains provide souls to the clan of its owner
Capture a soul fountain dispatch all enemies in the immediate area position your clan next to it for a time
When capture the souls that are released will turn from red to blue
Okay, so are they gonna get it? They're lying to everyone. I'm really not though character's name and character's name
It's just it was like a turn off for me all through my life. We get it destroy the blade worms
How am I gonna do that? I have to actually go kill those things
Dunk and donuts dunking and don't it's not dunking and donuts. It's dunking donuts
Like you're dunking your donut in the coffee dunk in donuts not dunk and donuts world and warcraft
No, that's wrong too bill and ted i've never seen that for i've never seen that movie start to finish ever
Hall of titans we must enlist a stone ogre to help with our work
I can have souls to enter the hall of titans and buy a stone
Ogre, how much do I need all of?
I have to do it. I'm only gonna do this one more time. I promise
No, i'm not gonna do it
Each clan will have one titan and one turret associated with it available in the hall of titans to buy a titan
Select the desired unit using the left thumb stick
When doing so the unit stats will be displayed at the bottom right of the screen cool. Yeah, they cost resources
We all know that all right. I have a ogre
Attack and titan stewie and brian. It's not the name of his show. That's the name of two characters
Lord and the rings. Okay, would it be as popular as a series if it was called lord and the rings?
I don't think so. All right, we're gonna go break this clear the debris and collect 125 gold
That still dramatically makes sense by the way lord and the rings
What about what about germa and stir that wasn't the name of our youtube channel?
We just played a lot of stuff together
Let's see. That's a lot of money
light and magic harry potter and the philosopher's stone
No, i'm sorry
the name of that the name of that series is not harry potter and ron weasley
and
Hermione it's not that it's not harry potter and hermione granger
You've got it wrong again
Who cares? All right, stop we gotta move off this. I don't want to read any more hands
I don't want to read any more of these. I told you my theory and it's that's it
Camper san andy
All right. We got to kill what do you what do you mean? What are you doing?
Return the commander to the hall of titans by three rock
Lobbers and place them onto the glowing orbs
I think I already have them
titan
titans
Eren Eren Eren Eren
Eren Eren Eren Eren Eren
I already have like five
I have I already have too many of these
What do I put them where?
Buy it. I have to buy a turret
three rock lobbers
Oh, this is like blending in with the ground. Okay and place them
Oh, come on. All right. We're gonna put and place them on the glowing orbs
Where is there a glowing orb?
ah
One finn and jake how many times do I have to say this the name of that show is not finn and jake
It's adventure time
Derma and sucks. Yeah star wars would have sucked. Nobody would have gone to the theater if it was called
luke and darth vader
You none of you would have seen the movie
No one would have seen the movie. I'm telling you. I don't think those critters will be showing their thorny hides around here anytime soon
Great job gay and silent bob never watched it. I've not seen that movie
What the
natarse
great frocks
It's gonna be another titan
I hope and then I can do my armin voice at least another three times before I have to retire it forever because everybody hates it
What's next rescue the three trapped workers, let's go
This game is actually really fun. I could see what people would play this a lot
But we're about to be done in like the next I don't know. Yeah, 30 20 minutes 30 minutes. I don't know
I'm still enjoying it. I think it's cool
King in the hill it's king of the hill
Suicide seen many episodes of that show
Yeah, can I eat the big plant?
Nice. All right, we got one
alvin and the chipmunks
Yes, and that that is one of the most
awful
Franchises ever all the new mood like you are you trying to tell me to go see alvin and the chipmunks and you're even that's not
Even right you have it wrong again. It's not alvin and theodore
Or alvin and simon it's alvin and the chipmunks
But that doesn't we didn't have to talk about that because that whole franchise is dog shit
We don't even need to talk about it that right off the bat. It's just a non watch
How much off the deck for you to get an alvin and the chipmunks tattoo?
It would take okay, i'll be honest with you i'm gonna be very honest with you. Let me be honest fine
Here's how what that would take for me to get an alvin and the chipmunks tattoo
And we're talking the 3d alvin and the chipmunks, which is way worse
The like alvin and the chipmunks from like the fucking 40s or whatever it was like the 60s
I don't even know when they first came out
That old style. Okay, cool. It's like i'd be like getting snap crackle pop tattooed on you
It's like, oh, all right. Well, it's kind of weird but like oh, whatever. It's like old. I guess it's like an old thing
getting the 3d
Reimagination of those characters tattooed on my body. It would it would cost a million dollars
I would need one million dollars taxed
Taxed one million not one million one million taxed already
So that would be like 1.4 million 1.5 million
It has to be taxed
That's what it would take deal. Okay. No, no deal. I'm not agreeing to it
A face tattoo of it. No, I would no not happening. There's no amount of money that would make me get a face tattoo
No amount set up a crowdfunding. We'll get it to 1.4 million. No, you will not that's a fucking absolute not it would never happen
That would never happen. It would never happen. I am so convinced that that would never hit 1.4 million
It has to go on my back like on my lower back
No way
No fucking way
That's not even worth one point what's not even worth one million taxed by the way
Right
And it would have to be that image that's on all the posters
Where you got like theodore on the left arms crossed leaning back
Simon on the right arms crossed leaning back and alvin in the middle arms crossed leaning back with sunglasses on
3d the 3d characters. That's I would need 1.4 million dollars to do that
What about waldo simbromet
That probably wouldn't be a million. I don't think I would need a million for that. They're like cool
That's like classic
Characters alvin and chipmunk are classic characters, but they're classic like money grab characters like they're like the smurfs
They brought back all these new franchises to try to like make them for kids
These are
Wallace and grommet is timeless. You don't need to like remake wallace and grommet to
Cater to like a 10 year old right now
You just make another wallace and grommet
You don't have to like remake then redesign them and bring the back for kids now
No, you just make another wallace and grommet. It's a timeless character. I would do that for fucking probably. I don't know
In that same spot
I have that 500k taxed. It's a stone crusher clan try also grab it holds up way more than it should
Why it's it's that's cool. It's really cool. It's claymation. First of all, it's really well done claymation
The characters are funny. It's like an old like man and his funny dog and they go eat like cheese from the moon and stuff
It's like that's timeless
Going to the moon to try the the planet's surface because you think it's cheese
And watching him spread it on the cracker and eat it
I wanted to eat it so bad when I was younger watching him take that gray chunk of that cheese moon shit and
Biting it. Oh my god. I wanted it so bad. I wanted to eat that so bad
I don't have that reaction when I watch alvin and the chipmunks
Lost at sea whatever the new movie was. I don't know. I want better uh better moves
Same and I don't even like cheese. Yeah, all right. What am I doing? Make contact with the hellfire clan
Chip wrecked the name of the movie was chip wrecked
That might be worse than putting two characters with and in the middle. In fact, it's absolutely it is. I need resources
Hellfire clan attacking they really they're they're rallying around the soul fountain after that soul
I need the tattoo fundraiser link
That's not how this works
It's not you guys make a fundraiser. No, it would be I would have to have an official an official account an official kickstarter campaign
Or official campaign onto my account name to do it
You know if somebody makes an account if somebody links you i'm gonna make this really clear
If someone links you an image
Not an image if somebody links you a link to a like fund page of me getting a alvin and the chipmunks ass tattoo
Whatever it was. It's not real. It's only real when I tell you it's mine
Do do not give any money to anybody
Don't give any money to anything
Only if I tell you it's my link and I link it and i'm the one that links it don't do that
Someone's gonna steal your money don't fuck around there's nothing to do with me and I am completely denouncing all of that
Don't do that. Don't fucking do it. I know one of you might think about it. I'll be furious if you do and I'd really mean that
I truly mean that if I do it you'll know
I'll have an official link in the channel. You'll know because I'll talk about it
I will say here is the link for the 1.4 million dollars to get a the alvin and chipmunks 3d
Ass tattoo or back tattoo here it is. You will only know that from me
I have to spend this much time on this. Do I have to really spend this much time here?
Why'd I have to spend this much time?
saying this
Huge omega lulls today, you're gonna sober up tomorrow and regret this bit
Fucking fine. I'm drinking water
Hellfire clans seek blood
I didn't agree to anything. I just told you if that ever were to happen
It would be coming from me and I have not agreed to that yet
All right, we gotta find the encampment. All right. I got a group here
Yet, I don't know him. I don't know what i'm gonna do
He's zonked get him
Okay, I find that I could find their lumber camp
And take it over
And then this game is actually pretty fun
Could you play this online with somebody if you could that's really cool
When he files for bankruptcy, he'll be back
To do that
Yeah, by the way, what's the um, how long do I have to do this? Like if let's say i'm retired
completely
Like five ten years go by
And like i'm like 50
i'm like 60
Can I come on twitter and say hey guys i'm opening up the uh,
The kickstarter for the alvin and the chipmunks 3d, uh back lower back tattoo
Please contribute here. Is that would you guys still do it?
No, what would happen realistically is that would get like two retweets
And like four likes on that tweet and there would be no replies
And no one would pay for and no one would do you guys aren't even they're not gonna be like on twitter anymore
It would be just a weird desperate attempt for me to like come back and just take money from people. It'd be weird
Get a time splitters tattoo
I don't
I'm not I don't have any tattoos
I told you guys the tattoo that I was gonna get a long time ago when I never did it and i'm kind of glad
I didn't
I was gonna get the venom symbol
on my
Shoulder and I swear to god something happens to your brain when you when you get like jacked
Like I was fucking huge. I was like 160 170 pounds and i'm like five eight. I was I was a inflated
Swole fucking massive person. I was huge and I was always lifting
I was really in shape when you get like that. It does something to your brain
I'm gonna get like the spider-man tattoo. I'm i'm spider-man like I really thought that I was like spider-man
Yeah, this is like what spider-man looks like i'm spider-man
I'm gonna get the venom tattoo because I've like looked like venom
I don't know what it does
It does something into like inside the chemistry in your brain and it makes you like think you're a superhero or something
So I was gonna get the venom symbol
Across the shoulder and like down around the back and around my arm and it would have looked sick
With like my shirt off like just jacked in the mirror
It would be this like like those lines and i'd be like fuck. Yeah, i'd be at the beach
It'd be like wow look at that. That guy's that guy's jacked and he has a venom tattoo that guy's venom
But I didn't want to be venom. I wanted to be I wanted to be venom suit spider-man
I didn't want to be venom. I wanted to be spider-man with the venom suit on but i'm glad I didn't
Because I've turned to the kind of i've gotten a little frumpy and that part of my brain turned off
I'm no longer like jacked spider-man
And i'd be like, oh shit, I have like I have like the superhero tattoo now
Maybe I wouldn't have stopped
Maybe that would have been enough motivation for me to not to like to get just to keep going to the gym
Maybe I fucked up maybe having the venom tattoo on the shoulder was what needed to be there
So I would continue to be spider-man in the venom suit. Oh, well, that's like getting a marijuana leaf tattooed on you
Because you like weed
Well
But why does anybody get a tattoo
Like what does anybody get like a tattoo like that?
It's because like you I don't know. It's like cool or it means something, right?
We tattoo for two million. That's not that's like not that big of a deal
You know a long time ago burger boy was gonna get wario tattooed on his ass
shooting a fireball like
To it like towards his like butt
I think that didn't happen
It would have been yeah, it would have been glorious
But that's the kind of tattoo that's like, okay
That's like funny and like wow about like an interesting
What an interesting person you may have you must have been right?
Like what a what a crazy cool fun life you may have had right?
Getting like the spider-man tattoo on your shoulder is like i'm jacked
In my brain at least
How much for a twitch tv tattoo?
What do you mean like the twitch like the whatever the glitchy the icon?
I'd rather get alvin than chipmunks. I would rather get alvin and the chipmunks for free
On the lower back then get a twitch.tv glitch tattoo for money. I don't know
I don't know something about that just sits weird to me
I don't know why like I just feel like I feel like that's a kind of
Oh, I beat it
Where would it be and how big does it have to be?
That the twitch glitch tattoo
How big does that have to be?
Because if it was small
Like if it was like a emote sized or something that would be kind of cute like get that like on like your
Like your wrist or something or on like your forearm like that's cute
I don't I don't have a problem with that. How big does it have to be huge?
No, I don't think i'd want to do it on your forehead. No
I wouldn't get any tattoo on my forehead. What happened? Oh head b oops
Oink oink boom
On your cheek
On your bald spot. I don't have a bald spot
Inner lip. Oh, no, I don't think so. No, thanks
Which url
No, I don't want that because that's not gonna be
That's a weird advertisement for something that's not gonna not gonna exist anymore mentally
Why don't you do that?
QR code tattoo and it links to rick roll
can't wait to
Do that a thousand times
All right. So now
Investigate the hellfire gunpowder factory
Not yet. I want one of these guys 140
All right
I'm gonna
I own this factory, right? Yeah
Oh, that's new
Medium melee. All right. That's good. That's a good group tons of health
Now let's go find it. What about a rat tattoo? Uh, that would be fun. I wouldn't be opposed to that
That's that does it for me. I think that's cool
What just happened I was laughing about chipwrecked can these guys eat?
I'm gonna get i'm gonna get i'm gonna get jack and dexter tattooed on my back
He's gonna be holding the chicken gun
This is the chainsaw sounds because I need more people. Hold on keep fighting
Everybody died
Oh, it's because the factory blew up
Homer simpson. Yes, i'll get okay homer simpson
Holding the pink donut standing straight up heels on the ground
Just standing in just a regular position with his arm up pink donut has a single bite out of it
Frosting side is facing the camera
And he has a little wad chew kind of in his mouth side of his mouth. That's pretty epic. Yeah
also the great tattoo and you're
My god like that's the kind of tattoo
That you just get up one day and you're like what the fuck is going on with my life?
What's happening to my what's going on?
right
Investigate the gunpowder factory. Okay, let's go back to sneak king
We're gonna move on to the next game
And the next game is gonna lock me there for a long time
And I think half of you are gonna be very excited and the other half are gonna be very pissed off that it's I even
Picked it in the first place
I guarantee
100 guarantee this game will be played for at least a full hour. I guarantee it
It's guaranteed
Somebody's still fighting back here. Wait. Hey, that's mine. Give me that
Hey, whoa, whoa, whoa
Can't see anything. It's not skylanders
Don't you guys feel like skylanders was like five years a little too early?
Just barely I still have that right? I think so don't have it
140 almost can get the uh the ogre like if they had just waited for technology to get just a little bit better even
It probably would have been a thousand times more popular than it is now, but then it was
We'll give me that
It's you have to claim sponsorship money. That's what we're gonna watch
Um, no, all right, bring on the big guy
I'm not fucking around anymore. Let's go
Game part of it sucked. I didn't play skylanders. I just knew what it was
I was like, oh, that's kind of interesting how that works
I can just eat people
Why play as any other character?
This is so much better
I lose health for eating these guys now
All right, you stay here and claim this
Can he claim this by himself?
Later levels get really hard to make kids spend money kind of weird to hear
Oh shit
All right, go get him. They dead wait. No, no, no, no, no, no, don't do this. I gotta get more troops
Upgrade their gear. What am I doing? Yeah, look at that. Now we're gonna take it over. When is the next game?
Um after my first break which will be in precisely after this level
I'm gonna go pee and come back and we're gonna move to the next game. The next game is gonna be wow
Really wonder
What the response will be?
Oh what they're already going over there shit. Hurry up
Eat eat them both. They'll take it over
This game's pretty fun. I could see how this would be really popular
I'm coming. I don't fit here
Wow, let's go
It's not world of warcraft. It's not an mmo
He's what you think I wouldn't you think I would do that to you right now?
Unlike the one stream you get a week. You think i'm gonna play world of warcraft for like two hours
All right, where's this gunpowder place?
Okay, I will make somebody i'm gonna make sure i'm gonna make everybody really really calm here
It's not league of legends. If you think it's league of legends and you're like goddamn it. It's probably league
He's gonna do a stupid joke where he plays league. He's like, oh once a week and he plays league
If league of legends shows up on this stream
I will get the alvin and the chipmunks 3d ass tattoo for free like immediately the next day
If you see league of legends
Show up on this stream
And what I mean by that is me
Playing league of legends
I'm playing it sitting there and oh, yeah league of legends. Cool. This is fun
I'm playing the game me streaming it not opening a video
Not talking about it. I mean physically sitting here playing league of legends on my twitch tv
Okay, here I am playing the game me if that happens
I will get the alvin and the chipmunks ass tattoo the next day. Now. Why is it always ass? It's like back
I keep saying ass
An ass tattoo perhaps there is another way
We still have not forgotten about three stooges in fortnight. It's gonna happen. It doesn't I could take a I could take five more years
It's gonna happen
It's gonna they're gonna open up like oh seasons eight
season 10 like
Gonna be black and white it's gonna open up black and white
They're gonna come over and they're gonna like
They're on season 18. It's too much. It's too many seasons
They're breaking the rule
More than seven seasons of any media. It becomes bad. We talked about this like a week ago. We already talked about it
Do I have to reiterate it for you?
Collect this
I'm for a reboot
That's when they rebooted fortnight
Destroy it. All right, kill these guys
All right. I'll get it next time. Maybe not maybe we can do it now
You stole that bit from community
I've never seen community
I've seen one episode of community
It's the one where they talk about like the chicken fingers being back at like the cafeteria or something
I was like, oh this is kind of funny. I've now i've only seen one full episode maybe two
That was good. It was very funny
That's the only like i've only seen two episodes. I don't really watch tv. I don't do it guys. I don't watch like media
I'm such a weirdo
Oh my god. I'm so weird. I'm such like a weirdo
All right, they have molten hammers
You can't get much better than that already come to me
You have to watch this guy he's so quirky
I know dude, you gotta you gotta watch this guy was wicked funny
He did he was doing a routine where he said those the three stooges were gonna go be into and put it in fortnight
He has this like bet with his chat and he started playing a song. He started doing the willy wonka
Golden ticket song as if it was a three stooges intro or something
Like how does this guy's mind work? Like what the heck?
That's so weird. What the hell why that's not even the right thing
Final battle incoming troll versus troll
You're piggy piggy piggy
Yep, let's go
go
It just gave me a headache i'm sorry
I'm sorry. They gave you a headache
Why did they give you a headache? Are you all right?
Does he listen to pokemon music before streams?
Yes
I've never played a pokemon game
I'm just mashing together the things that it's like an ai algorithm in my brain
I'm I took what I played in the smash brothers games the background music that was pokemon related
and ai
Quantum imagination to created it. I've got a quantum fucking imagination. I've never played a pokemon game
I'll watch out for the explosion. I need to eat something
Fuck
Everybody fine. Everybody's fine
Just take out their
Take this out
fight fight
They have cannons it's not fair i'm about to quit the game
Not yet. They fully upgraded why can only have 10 these guys attack
This guy's these guys defense is terrible
Can I upgrade these guys at all?
Where can I put this?
I can put this near a fountain, right?
Stay with this guy don't do that. We can remember every pokemon smash background music
We can't remember the u.s national anthem
What a liberal?
That's doesn't okay the pokemon background music battle music doesn't have lyrics
I can go
I can do that
I don't do lyrics. I i'm a bird
I just repeat things like this repeats sounds. All right, watch out. Watch out. Watch out come this way this way this way
No, no, no, no, no, no
God damn it
head to the cannon
rush
This game is a snooze fest bro
Ban him ban him and don't let him come back ban him and don't let him come back
ban him
This is my
You're gonna mess with my stream and talk about how the game i'm playing is not good
It's what I think is is fun and good. Okay, get out of here get out of here
It's boring
Well, it doesn't matter what is having fun. It's xbox 360 night
I'm just stalling to get to the real game because that's the game that's gonna
Oh, i'm gonna get trapped for like at least a few hours
This game's pretty fun
Do
Everybody find that clip yet of the joe and mac
I like love that game and I love that sound. Oh, that's a joe and mac
Oh, I think yeah, I lose
I lose gotta get the alphan the chipmunk's ass tattoo. I lose
Just trying to find reasons to get the tattoo
Oh shit, oh man, I lost. Oh, I have to get the alphan the chipmunk's tattoo on my ass
Oh, what the heck? That's so stupid. That sucks
Fine. I'll book it tomorrow. Oh
No, can I what can I do gonna do something I can do to make that not happen?
All right, let's go. This was fun
But i'm we're moving on and i'm not gonna even tell you what this is until you fucking see it
So let's go brb and i'm gonna open up on the next game and everyone's gonna be furious or happy. Not sure
See you in a minute
Okay, i'm back
All right. That took a little longer. I really wanted I wanted another coffee
I wanted a coffee and I was gonna make it
I did
Okay. So, um the next game we're gonna play
I will put on the music
So you can hear what the intro is. This is the next thing i'm gonna be doing. This is the opening
What could that be?
Yes, you can you can hear it
I don't even know sound yes, you can you can hear this
What do you mean you can't hear this it says you can
There's literally no sound what?
Oh, all right. Who cares about the surprise?
It's high rollers casino
You walk around and you play casino games
Oh, here we go
Get yourselves ready. I got a coffee for this one. This is the game of the night right here. You couldn't hear this intro
Oh, no, no, no, no spoilers. I don't want any spoilers
Uh, the screen looks fucked up though
Like not what I mean, it's like the bars on the bottom and top are too big
That good
How's that look? It's better, right?
No more to the left
Good
IGN gave this game a one out of ten. Did they really?
Oh here I am
All right. All right. This is important
It's just like a
guy
It's just hair color
Hold on. Wait, wait, wait. Oh, hold on. Oh god. He's like sims 2 characters
I like that a lot. This is my favorite one so far
Green green come on, it's gotta be green pants. Yes, of course there is
Wait, wait
Why can you do this?
Is that as far as I can go? Okay, that's as high as it goes mixing
Fuck this is a slot machine i'm making a random person. No, we need green pants locked
I don't know. What is it? How do you do hair with bald? I think that was a good one. Yeah, I like it
The shorts are locked
Okay, there's greens greens looks like a chad
Needs a tie. I I don't there's nothing I can't do anything about that
Oh, I guess it could be hold on. It could be this. That's fine. Let's go
All right. Are you ready to start our journey to go into the casino?
I can't make it any fatter. I tried
All right
I have a thousand dollars in bankroll
It's a third person game. Where should I go?
I feel like i'm just taking control of the character
One of the characters in casino inc
What should I start with or go to the manager? All right, i'm gonna talk to the manager
Welcome to the high rollers casino
See me again if you want to enter a tournament check out the special tournament bonus prizes, or if you need to pick up a vip card
Remember to go to the elevator to your left if you want to go to your room and change your clothing
I don't
All right. We're going to the slots first press a to play burger jim
Burger jim is the first game. It's uh, you gotta go. You gotta go to the first game that you see
This is dead rising
What's burger jim?
I have to be careful denomination. What's my denomination?
No, I don't want to do 25 dollars go back and what I just do
How do I go back?
I just did a 200 250 dollars spin
I didn't want to do that cash next. This is this this is the worst
Okay, I want to do nine lines
I don't want to do 25 cents
Stop, what the fuck? I'm no I thought that said I thought that said to the coins like two coins
Go that way to go to the coins
How do I change that?
Whoa
I win. Did I win anything? What did I win?
Casino warp to game. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no
How do I change this?
bet one
Line bet you can do 10 coins a line
It was four dollars. That's horrible
I have to i'm gonna have to delete my save and do it again. I'm confused. What's going on?
Bet one what happened?
What's going on? What did I just do?
Cash out. All right, get off of 25 dollars a spin
No, don't leave the casino. I want to get up get up go to the casino floor
You're gonna pre-record the stream. Why leave this shit in?
In
That was fucking funny, it's true though. All right back to burger jam
This is a really weird ui. I'll get used to it
Okay, denomination
We I want to do
five cent denomination
10 coins
I want to do
How many what's the max bet I can do?
How many bets how what's the max bet I can do? How many times did I do this?
What's the max bet?
Okay, whatever. Okay 10 coins
Oh bet max line bet. All right, I want all lines all nine lines
Oh
That's what we must do it's gonna be huge again
Again
Why is my bankroll not going down? Why is my bankroll not going down?
Up left. Yeah bankroll seven nine nine twenty five
How come i'm not spending any money?
You it's oh my credits, okay
I got a thousand bucks in there. Okay
Next I want what's bet max?
All right, this is max bet. Let's go
Again, it's like 80 dollars spin
These are credits this no, it's currency
Each credit is five cents and i'm doing okay, I get it
Okay, what nine lines right how's that not a line that's a line
Five these are five dollar spins
scatter
Oh, baby
fake excitement
Choose three items
You're losing credits. No, i'm not
All right. Should I do the spanish burger the kid's meal the kid's meal
Is there there it is?
1350 dollars
Uh the max burger
Triple meat burger. That's that was probably the worst one
All right
What's that get me?
That's like 2 000 credits
All right cash out
What?
All right burger gym sucks. They're worth five cents each. Oh
You started with 8 50. I started with a thousand
I accidentally did a 250 dollar bet
All right burger gyms not fun
You guys are all idiots for playing burger gym. It's the worst one rock and roll though on the other hand
All right rock and roll you are a human being with access to a computer which you appear to be
There are 100 million programs that can do this better before you seek them out. Please set me on fire some pain stops
That's an ign review
Okay, how about 25 cents?
a line
We're gonna do I just I just cashed it out
It's got this is so horrible
10 coins
All right, so I have 200 credits. I want to bet
All nine lines good go
Right there big big big money, how do you lose so much? I don't know how this works
Max bet
I win the same game
I miss burger gym
Um
This doesn't make any this is needlessly complicated. Yeah, why this is very needlessly complicated
For some reason this game makes me feel really sad it does why
It makes you sad
Bonus rock come on
I just got scatter. What happened? I just want a bunch of money
I'm up. I'm up almost 100 bucks
Cash it out. All right, let's keep going
What else is here? It's like 30 games to play
I would rather watch the templar game, honestly
Oh shit
Come on. I saw like I saw the third person guy walking around casino. I had to get it
All right. What about fruits jackpot?
It's gonna be the same one. Isn't it? This is 10 bucks, right? No, how much is that 50?
Oh fuck, okay, that's this is a lot of money
Nice
All right. Um, this sucks. Stop. Wait, let me at least get to a million. That's not gonna happen, man
Let me at least play blackjack. This is a bargain bin stream. It's original xbox
I didn't get a bonus
All right, this game the game sucks, okay the game sucks it's terrible it's awful
I'll give that all right. I give it to you. Hold on. Let me just put some more coins
This game's bad it's really bad
I've been playing for 10 minutes and we need another 20 minutes. It's lots of so confusing
Well, they're not really it's just for some reason this game decided to
I don't know why they added all these weird things to do. What does it describe the taste?
um
I'm like pissed. Look at my guy
I'm crying
No, this is I don't like this
We got to go to the blackjack table
I'm fucking furious
blackjack
One dollar stick. All right. This is this makes much more sense to me. What happens if I get to zero?
One billion off the debt if you can make it to one million from your current bank. Welcome to blackjack
Okay, here we go
add i'm gonna do a
let's do 25 to uh
50 dollar hands
Max it up
What is value plus?
Oh, okay
set bet
What the fuck is this menu? What are you talking about?
How do I put the bet up there?
What?
I didn't am I even playing?
You stand against the six
And i'm fucking lost
It's 11 versus 8. I'm probably gonna is probably 18
This is terrible
Stay
What the fuck come on, I got to get to a million
Walking into a casino with a hundred bucks and going I can't wait to turn this into a million
That's um, that's not it's not it's very bad. That's not gonna happen. That's blackjack should have been even more
All right, we're good. We're good. This is the very bottom again blackjack again
Player has a 16. No, I have to hit against a nine
Play this all night, please. I don't think i'm gonna do that. I have to hit against nine
You bust i'm never going to the casino ever again
Please reconnect the controller
go out of batteries
Dealer busts what I do
I should
Do the voice has a 15 15 versus four. This sucks, but i'm staying
No
I have to make a new character
17 versus four I have to stay
You didn't hit on 15. Why would I hit on 15 versus four? Are you trying to get me fucking slaughtered?
All right, we're good
Wait, how much money the person lost two dollars?
Am I the weirdo at the table that's doing fifty dollars a bet every hand?
Shit people are just here having fun. I'm like fifty dollars again
Yay player stands
There it is, all right go go go go go
Shut up
Blackjack i'll take the 20. Thank you. And then i'm gonna take it right back to the slot
player stands
I think I left
One dollar everyone's betting one dollar here, but i'm bidding 50 player has an 11
No, I don't want insurance. I want to
All right, should I double down?
What do you think I guess the ace that's the stupidest fucking thing ever
Let's go for it
Okay, now i'm coming back
Eight versus three just take a hit
This is honestly so hype. I don't know why because you're i'm gonna get back to a thousand
I'm gonna get to like five thousand. I'm gonna go to the high roller room and play thousand dollar hands
Do you understand? That's the point
Mr. Green does okay, you think mr. Green is gonna come out here
For three hundred and forty six dollar hands like it bankroll. Yeah, do you mind?
This like four zeros have to get at it. I gotta I have to get there
All right, i'll get a 10 here. You stole my 10. You stole my 10 player has a 17
player stands
Okay, well played
Bet more I have to go to the other table
I need to get to 500 bucks before I bet more
All right, we'll go to the other table
Blackjack all right, we're gonna do here comes the big hands
All right, here we go, let's see, whatever what are other people doing 18 dollar bets
200 a hand. Let's go
205 dollars
shit
Oh, no
This is bad. This is really bad
I know it's I I feel you. All right, give me 10
No, not a 15
No
Ah
How did that happen?
You suck. What am I supposed to do there?
Oh my fucking god, this is terrible
Oh my fucking lord
I would stand against a king. Are you out of mind? Why would I stand with a 12 or a 13 against a king?
Give me a chance
Fuck no
Come on. Look at that gets 10 every time. What's with tens?
This is ridiculous
Finally. All right, keep going. Let's go
No, I this is not fair. I get to restart
I I did like the weird like terrible dog shit ai
Not ai dog shit ui at the slot machine and blew through like 400 and I didn't even know I was doing that
That's not no whether I get to do it again
I didn't understand the game. I want my money back. Yeah, but whatever
Let's go
This is that I have one dollar remaining if I don't win
I need a 10 or it's over
Shit. Oh, no, i'm in trouble
Oh, I have a dollar that's enough to get like a fucking value menu item
Well, what do I do now? What am I supposed to do?
This keno. Oh, okay. I gotta do it again
How do I get okay? I want to go up to
I want to go to my room. Where's the elevator? I probably there's probably money in my room
I probably have like a 500 under my mattress
Where's the elevator?
left over here
All right elevators are there?
Maybe there's money in my room
Oh, there's a three line. Okay, I want to play those no I get I get to redo it again
I lost 250. I lost probably 500 bucks because I didn't understand the machine. This is my room
Where do I get money? No, just i'm not saying just restart the game
535 lost zero percent net income. Yeah
All right. Well, okay. What happens if I get to a dollar?
What happens if I get to zero? Okay, this is one dollar
I understand this one one. Why do I have ten cents?
You found a dime on the ground
Okay, I need to find a five cent machine to put uh two coins in it
I don't understand how you're supposed to keep playing the game
After you get to zero, why am I still here?
I'm just gonna walk around the casino with no money
Get a marker from the cashier. Wait a minute
What do you mean get a marker?
Where's the cashier?
beg for money casino manager
What do you mean from the cashier? Let's see. There's a manager right here
The poker manager. Where's the cashier?
In the center of the city. Those are the bar
Show what's this? What's this place called?
show
Hello, sir. Welcome to high rose casino. I see you are now new around here. Would you like me to show you the tutorials? No
Sure
Where's this man? Where's this cashier?
Oh, wait, there it is
Well, that's not called the cashier. That's called the change booth
out of the way
Your current bankroll is zero. Do you want a marker? Yes
Holy shit nice
I don't know what this is count kolbinski. I have 2,500 in debt right now
Oh my god, this is an expensive machine. This is really expensive ten dollar denomination
This is 100
Two three four. All right, 500 bucks
And I want to do nine lines. So that's is a place this
This is a 90 bet
90 right
Is it this would be a 90 bet. That's correct
No
What the fuck? No
That's 100 that is correct. Yeah, i'm going for it
Come on
Come on count kolbinski. I need two of those any three of those. Okay, that's 100 bucks
Come on count kolbinski
No, we need bats
Shit
Is that enough to stay alive come on bonus
Oh
Is it cringe?
I gotta hit one. I need to go to the high rollers table
That's a bonus right there. I win. I got it
What the hell's going on select a line?
Which one which one?
One, two, three, four, five six seven, right?
seven
five
Yeah, lots of fives and lots of sevens five. Let's go. It's five one two mean
You guys pick the worst one
This is the worst one
Seven I told you please say
That's wild, isn't it you lost a thousand dollars already
These slot machines are terrible. These are awful machines. They're terrible. This is the worst slot machines ever seen
Which is precisely what I would be doing right now if I was losing this much money
These machines are terrible. It's just they're not fun. Like the company that makes these are fucking awful
Like at least put effort in this is a terrible machine. It's not even fun not fun
How's that not a bonus
Dropping a thousand dollars in a slot machine and talking shit the whole time right when you get there the first dollar that goes in
Okay, account kabinsky. Let's put it in here. Mmm dollar goes in this game's fucking stupid hundred dollars
This game sucks. It's not even fun
Look at how sad I am. This is stupid. Wait
All right, we're going to double espresso. I actually don't know how to play spanish 21. It looks interesting though
Like you know
Video poker we're gonna play jacks are better video poker. He's been sad the entire time. He has been here. Yeah, I have been
The poker yeah video poker
Denomination five bucks
i'm gonna do
50 dollars
100 dollars a hand, right? All right, let's go. We got sixes
How do I hold these?
I want to do the double sixes
It's not what I wanted to do. Okay. Here we go
We're looking for what's three of kind. What do I get for three of kind?
I need another six
sucks
Hold the queens hold the queens these three queens four queens. What do I win? I won five dollars
What do I do here with the ace and the queen?
now hold the five
Oh, how much am I actually betting? You didn't get yahtzee. This is not yahtzee here
Hold the aces and the fives looking for a full house
It's a full house. Give me a lot. Come on
Damn it
What happened?
Go for the flush
Come on spade
I got it
All right cash that out
All right
That's not bad
Oh, fuck. I just bet everything how much was that? Those 300 dollars
What I just do i'm going for aces
Come on aces
What do I have
fuck
We're betting 50 call for it. All right max bet is 50 bucks. Let's do it
What do I hold here?
Gang gang the 10 go for a straight
Bingo. I don't know. I have no idea what that was
all threes
Go hold the uh, I don't know the the the the
I was gonna say twigs. What are these called clubs clubs?
Hold the jack and nothing else
Four three four. I need six
No
This game's not even fun
All right, i'm gonna get a royal flush and it's gonna give me four billion dollars or whatever the hell that is
Oh, no
What's the actual odds to get a royal flush? Isn't it like one in a hundred trillion? It's like impossible, isn't it?
Let's see four five six seven eight nine. What do we got ten nine ten nine eight seven six
It's one in two point six million
That's impossible
Sevens throw everything else away go
This is not even this is just a weird
Watch somebody just lose at a casino game
Vegas steaks for the snas was like funny
It would come up and be weirdos and stuff and you'd get like crazy scenarios
This is just i'm sitting at a machine just losing a hundred up five hundred dollars
Is that that's it?
There's nothing else going on
Just watch me lose at a casino
No shit. I wanted to select that
Oh my god
whole house
This is the turnaround writer
There it is what I get for that
I lost a hundred bucks. That's what I got
new game
You should have listened to IGN
Return to vegas steaks. I beat vegas steaks. I got to like 10 million dollars in vegas steaks
This is a very good anti-gambling psa. Yes, it should be
If you go to a casino you were going there to entertain yourself. You're not going there to make money
It's there for entertainment value
When you go into a casino any money that is in your pocket
Is not coming back with you. That's how you should look at it. You are there to entertain yourself and maybe a group of friends
That's it
Whatever is in your pocket. You should assume right off the bat is not going to come home
At all. This is where the big plays happen right here. That's 18 bingo right off the bat done
Got it
There it is
This is where it begins
If you suck
Hey shit, come on
No hit again
Oh, fuck you video game. I have to I have to hit again
Oh, I have to I have to right after
I never stand on I should hit I should this is why you can't stand on 16 versus 10
I know this i'm a professional card player
god
Why ace finally some fucking wins
This guy's not even trying to hide his cheating what do you mean hide?
Don't do anything to stay. He's gonna bust and i'm gonna make money
Don't do anything
Hold you
This game is this this is that?
Yeah, someone's cheating. I feel the same way
What is this?
Oh my god
Can I go back and get more money from the guy at the cashier?
Are you having fun?
Kind of because this is not real
And it's I guess it'd be kind of could be fun if it's not real
And yanners just came in with a rate of like 75 million people
Seventy two hundred people just came in from yanners
What's going on yanners? Thanks for the raid
Welcome everybody currently I am up
About uh, I have 545 dollars in my bank roll
And i'm not a casino streamer, by the way, if anyone's wondering, this is just this is not
There's a fun xbox game. I came in here with 100 bucks. I got 545 bucks right now. We are doing a big bet
Just this hand only
Welcome to the stream
Hope you had a good stream of yanners
You need a raid song
Okay, I need to be able to hear this
Hello, what happened?
here
What happened? All right. I I dropped the the golec. Lr. I lifted it up and I smashed it
Now I think things broke up
I think I broke the golec. Lr
What does that sound like I I looked it up I dropped it listen to what I did it's supposed to be just going
Don't don't don't don't don't listen how that's not broken that looks anyways
I can't do it anymore
This is the worst streamer. I'm trying to make this work
Hold on a b c d motherfucking g
Is it this is broken? Yeah, my like I I dropped the golec. Lr and I think I may have broken
Hey, that was the raid song
Thanks. Welcome everybody everybody left. No, don't fucking leave
Is my mic sound okay? It sounds like static
My mic is messed up
What's wrong with it?
I sound really far away
Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello. Hello
Wait, how about now?
Okay. Anyways, um, welcome to the stream everybody. Thanks for coming
Probably just loosen the wire. Well, I can't even click any buttons on my golecs. Lr
It's frozen
Yeah, nothing is like no buttons work. I can't turn on the fx or anything. Whatever
All right, let's go. Sorry. I was gonna do a raid song
stand
21 fucking this game
I should I just
Split you're about to be 5k in debt
This is where it turns around
All right, so I just double down
Even though it's a 10 who cares? Let's go
You're knocking it
Yo
This is very bad
Just sing fine
Uh
How's that is that good enough for you?
No, I didn't want to stand. I wanted to hit fuck. I have to go get my buddy for the guy that gives free money
He's gonna he can have blackjack. I can't even buy insurance. What are you talking about?
Get me up from the fucking table once you had once you take three markers a hitman kills you
No, you don't that does not happen. Ow
Wow
That does not happen
All right. The person wrote omega lol after that so I kind of feel like that it's real
Does somebody kill you?
You don't get killed, right?
Give me real
That does not happen. Nobody kills you
Shit
Everyone's having such a good time. This is all fake pumped in cheering
You know, it's don't understand that casinos probably do that shit. They probably pump in fake cheers
So half a mile down the casino you hear that you're like, oh wow, that could be me
Get a marker and go spend the money at the bar
All right. These are one dollar spins
Twenty five dollars spins two hundred and fifty dollars a spin
Go
No, this is this is hundred dollars. This is seventy five dollars spin. Come on. Let's go
Bah bah bah
Come on, give me a
King of chicago, what's that do?
It's a handle bar bar bar
I i've known you don't win on these
I don't it's not possible to win on a three
slot machine
Thanks for almost proving me wrong. That would have been great. Come on
Bah bah bah
What happened what just happened? What happened?
What happened?
What what did I just do?
Oh my god, seven thousand dollars. I have seven thousand dollars
Oh my god, it worked
Pay back your debt. No what I don't need to
I don't do that yet
I didn't pay back my loan
Wait, do I have to
This walk
They're all cheering for me
You want to return a marker? Yes
Return a marker. Yes
Oh what I only have 1900 bucks. That sucks
All right. We're taking it. We're taking it right
Taking the winnings right over to burger gym
Come on burger gym. Let's go. I paid back all my debt
This is all profit right here. You play normal games. No, I don't
five dollars
Load it up
Okay
Nine lines, let's go for it that max
That's something
That's big
That's big. That's huge
That's like 25 grand
Yeah, what?
What are you talking about? Oh, it's five dollars
Catch up. Nice
Good more
Catch up. All right, get out get out get out. I'm good. I got three thousand. I'm good
Please stop you've been playing this for more than half an hour
I I think I told you I was going to be here for like at least two hours
Before I put the disc in tell you telling me to stop playing the casino game in a half an hour. I
You could be new if you are new. Just remember
We always come out on top
always
Last time I had a slot machine in front of me. I went I went to 20 billion dollars in the chocolate game
Time before that. Mr. Green
Took walked away with 2.4 million. We always win always
Here's your silver vip card. This allows you to enter thousand dollar poker tournaments
It makes you eligible to receive the vacation tournament bonus prize
What should I do for a tournament?
Oh roll. I love roulette roulette's great because it's the slowest game in the casino
That you could bet ten dollars and it takes like four minutes five minutes to have whatever the outcome happens. It's very slow
The objective of the tournament is to be the player with the highest bank roll after the designated number of games
The winner receives four thousand dollars in the victory count stores winning a low level tournament bonus prize
All right
Let's go. All right set bet
I want to go
You always do right? You always do the the the right in the middle here
You got to get the inside the corners put put 50 bucks here
I'm going to go down here 50 bucks down here as well. This is it bingo. I'm ready. You always get the corners
I forget what numbers they were
It will in the 20s
There it is. That's it, right?
Oh shit
It's okay 30 spins
I'm keeping the same ones
Don't move another thing in roulette. Don't move
precisely why
I wasn't wait. Oh, i'm in 22 23 24
Don't move
32 33 35 36 20 we're looking for 30s
Don't move exactly. That's why you don't fucking move. That's not wait 32
Don't move just don't bet any money bet one dollar
Wait, could I?
There it is
What the fuck are you talking about? What?
Just don't bet I have to now i'm down 400
Don't move. It's gonna hit it just has to hit once and i'm up
Oh, fuck you
I'm not moving
Because the second I take it off, it's gonna hit one of these eight numbers. This guy's fucking incompetent
It's a game where you spin a marble around and random person wins
There is no skill in roulette. It's just throwing a dice in the air. What do you mean?
I mean, I know maybe you sit there and rub your belly before each spin, but that doesn't do anything
That's the one right there bingo
Do it 28
That's it
Why?
You gotta start looking for people that remember you
Look jeremy at the casino
I hope they remember you
Give me the minus two as I deserve it
Oh my god, what happens if you have no more money? Do I just leave the table? Don't move he says
That usually works. Look it hits like
Whatever. I won't do that again
Blackjack tournament, let's go. Why not just go to a real casino because this is not real money
This is just make-believe
You want me to go to a casino and just drop like five grand and just lose. I don't why would I do that?
All right highest bank roll
I need to win one hand here and then play one dollar a hand
Come on, I said to win one hand. All right, that's it. Now i'm gonna play one dollar for the rest of the game
One dollar I don't want to clean that
Okay, i'm gonna win the tournament now
This is four grand by the way
Honestly, you know, I gotta try I gotta try to screw over the person next to me. They're looking for what are they looking for?
I can play 45 hands
So if I take another card, I could just completely screw Evelyn over
But that's what you needed
Yeah, you lose I win
Again, uh people take a look around you go big first
I got blackjack with a dollar. It doesn't whatever I just have to survive
Kimberly's coming up here with a thousand two
You need to bet two dollars. No, I don't not yet
Where were these hands when I was playing 40 minutes ago?
Why?
Okay, i'm still in the lead
Oh, no, they're cowards. They're not gonna bet more than a dog. Wait
You double down over there. I hope she loses
Come on. Okay. It's all right
What's Kimberly doing three dollars?
Oh my god, what the fuck?
Yeah, there's a guy in the security window right now like mr. Green just currently betting one dollar instead of 250 dollars a hand
Yeah, just starting to let him win. So then he starts that something gets cocky and puts a hundred dollars on the table
assholes
1015 oh, that's she just bet five bucks
I still think she's gonna lose
But I took all the cards from her
By the way, the the profits are going right to burger gym. Hope you guys know that
Because i'm guaranteed to win this
21 shit, she's climbing
I don't like that
Is that 1018?
I think I might no I can't I have to just play the statistics that she's not gonna bet more
She's going four dollars now. Can I with like attrition here? Can I win this? Can I keep doing this?
I'm good
At two bucks. No, no way
I have 20 more hands of one dollar
Jerma read books or just chat
Probably just chat at this point
Hit again
Shit
Bet five. No, why would I bet five?
I don't have to increase my bet until kimberly gets up to
like
1030 1040
Why would I do that?
She's gonna lose and she did one dollar. She's trying to do the same thing. She's trying to bait me
Okay, all right, we know i'm the little we're almost halfway there
All right, how kimberly do let go five bucks lose it
She has
17 versus five fuck. Uh-oh
Slowly, she is closing the gap
At 250 to throw her off. No if I lose it's over
16 versus five she's got okay
Oh shit. Okay. She has 13
This is a hand all of us are gonna win. Oh shit. All right. I got what do I do?
I have to bet 10 bucks
What do I do? She's climbing. No, I don't have to do that yet. Stick with the strategy
I have to stay with the strategy. I'll be fine
Sorry, I gained a little bit of ground there. She lost two. I lost one
Bet all your money to throw off her rhythm. Oh, I don't have to do it yet
Go back to sneak jim
Are you combining two games you've seen today?
That was a four dollar bet
Oh, she's in trouble
She's gonna lose that four dollar bet
Hey
Yes. All right. We're good
If you win an all-in you're gonna win the tournament
Yeah
But if I just slowly burn one dollar a hand and she slowly burns like two dollars every other hand
I'm gonna win
She's gonna lose right there
Yeah, she she's fucked
That's four dollar lose. Oh, it's all right. Whatever
Can you please at least try to play as mr. Green's mr. Green has?
A hundred thousand dollars at least on the table
I'm not there yet
Shit. All right. Everybody lost
only like 11 hands
This should be a minimum bet because being able to do one dollar
I just bet 50 bucks the first hand and i'm just gonna coast to victory
Yeah, that's sealed right there I think
At 50 now. No
I don't have to bet 50 dollars. There's no reason to
That's fine. All right. Here we go. This is a lot to win
$4,000
Do a 150 dollar hand right now or i'm gonna resident sleeper
Go for it. I don't care
I'm not losing this tournament. I've been here for so long
No, i'm about to win four thousand dollars then I take that to burger gym
And we're gonna do huge bets
We're fine. All right, it's it's sealed
As long as she doesn't win like another five or ten dollar hand
standing
Okay, only six more hands
Playing smart is pog. Don't listen to them. I have blown more fake money on this stream
Doing dumb things like that, but it's a guaranteed victory
i'm taking the sure thing
I feel like michelle's gonna turn to me take the glasses off and go like
Like a big tongue's gonna come out let's split these let's split fives for fun
Yeah, two dollars
Michelle's uh getting desperate
That was eight bucks
13 versus four don't do anything dude. Stay there. Don't do anything. Don't fucking just get your hands off the table
I lost I know you love but that's what you do
I know you but you give yourself the best opportunity to fucking win, dude
You can't you gotta try to give yourself an opportunity and with a with a 13 versus four. You don't fucking touch anything. Don't be an idiot
What's that peter griffin? It's like every one of my relatives how they speak
Yeah
All right, this is it
All right, the lat i'm not no don't be an idiot
I'm about to win the tournament
He's got a four just stay don't do anything. Okay, take your fucking hands off the table. See
Don't be a fucking idiot about this shit. All right, here we go
Final hand after this right and then I win four thousand dollars in a bonus prize for my hotel room
He's gonna bet 50. She is not going to bet 50
The ai is not that smart
Yeah, I win
game over victory is mine
It was stewie, but whatever hey, uh, oh no, what do I do I surrender?
You won the thousand dollar blackjack tournament to win the counselor as a bonus prize. You must play and win another tournament to win the prize
That was for a thousand dollars. I thought that was four thousand. Wasn't it four thousand?
Yeah, i'm good. I got five grand
What's this game? All right. I want to go. I want to play. What do I play now back to burger gym?
How about back to king of chicago? That was a big win for us
All right, we're gonna play king of chicago
Another game not yet. Hold on. Just wait. I enjoyed this
okay
25 dollars per coin
that's
What's 10 coins?
Okay, this is stupid, but it could get us a huge payout
Oh
Ah, is it wait? This is only this is 75 bucks. This is 75 dollars spin. I'm fine
Come on king of chicago. Let's go
I need three guns
I'm up. Well, i'm way up. I'm fine
You got to do something crazy if you're way up just a little bit and then here we go like for instance
Back to burger gym. Hold on. What did I win? I just get like a
Sympathy money. What was that for?
uh
That's gonna be all right. That's
I think okay. I stand alive
You're a low iq slot streamer if you play slots your low iq
Shit, hold on. Wait
Hey, how's that for never mind?
Ah, that's it. Come on
Low iq slots river
What do you mean low iq it takes that much more iq to fucking
Sit at a roulette table
Come on do something
Oh
My god, that would have been insane
Let this be a lesson. Don't ever go to the casino. Go you you know
Go to i'm not gonna tell you not to go to the casino, right?
If you want to go to the casino and just spend some money to hang out with your friends, that's fine
But like this shit is just you're gonna lose money in the long term always
You're never gonna win a substantial amount of money and doesn't matter how many people they put as a cardboard cutout
Holding like a fucking eleven hundred dollar check
Look how much carol wine at the slot that that's not that's not that's not gonna do anything
You're not gonna win that
You're gonna sit here like I am you're gonna burn through a thousand dollars and you're not gonna be the person with a check in their hand
It's a lesson
But my grandmother won i'm a net positive from casinos
That's really good
Try to keep it that way
We just need another big hit so I can go back to burger gym
2k not 1k
And what you fixed it
My point still stands
Give me that way don't ever go back
Come on don't I've this is two thousand dollars in king of um
King of the casino or whatever the game is called
Come on do it
You've lost three thousand dollars. Have you not realized that?
This is it. That's it. That's it. We're gonna get it right here
No more we're gonna go to burger gym after this look at that bingo. Oh, come on
What did you want me to do?
This is I'm in a casino video game right now. Am I not supposed to play the casino games in the casino xbox game?
I can't take this out of here and go somewhere with this
Died to king of chicago
We're gonna get a hit right here. Oh, come on
Come on, please
I feel good when I see a big number on your screen
The opportunity for me to leave out get out get out. Yeah, fuck that game
Bah bah bah germa walk bah bah bah germa walk. Let's bah bah bah
Play keno. Yes
We're gonna go play keno and i'm gonna start to pull
Numbers from your guy's usernames. All right, what we got
How does keno even work? You just pick numbers and if they pop up you win, right?
25 bucks
Go big huge absolutely massive
How do I do this? Okay select
Uh, we got uh
There's a two in their name how many how many buttons do I do? Uh 23
what numbers
six
There's another three in their name, but it's it was supposed to be an e
Uh, I see 55
Do nine eight five
Okay, sure how many numbers can I pick?
uh the person has uh
Why can I i'm picking more how many numbers am I picking here? What do you pick?
I don't know how many numbers you pick in keno
I have 10 numbers
How many numbers can I pick?
Okay, 21
All right. So can I just go why is it why do I have to keep picking numbers?
All right. Let's go with this. How's that? Is that good?
Play 10
The hell just happened we win
Why is this going so fast?
four four four
Four four four is that how many is that credits?
three
five
I can't tell if i'm winning
How many matches?
Okay, so what how much did I win?
I lost
I lost how much is that? I lost a hundred bucks
No, no, no. No. Okay. Wait. Yeah, I lost a hundred dollars. All right put in
I want to should I do less numbers?
How many numbers should I do max for the most amount of profit?
Four numbers do one number. That sounds terrible
All right, we're gonna do 35 because that's how old I am
And this is how old i'm gonna be
this year
It won. All right. There's one. There's another one. There's i'm getting one credit for this
This sucks
one credit for each
You gotta do at least three. All right, we're gonna do all the corners
right in the middle and then
These two and these two all right go. All right, that's
I don't understand why that what's happening too much. I would rather play burger gym and
Cry he's playing this to the stream ends. That's not true. I'm just enjoying myself. All right. There we go
Come on, give me like a four. All right
Okay, I mean that's horrible
How would you ever play this game? Nobody enjoys themselves at a casino stop lying. That's not true if you win like five thousand dollars
And then you take a hundred dollars out and you play one dollar bets everywhere you leave with four thousand nine hundred and ninety dollars
Free car poker sucks, but i'm gonna play it. Please play the playstation connect wizard game to this. I would prefer that too
All right, let's do
25 in the ante
Let's go ahead and make the best handicap with three cards
Looking for a flush
I'm gonna bet on this one. There it is. All right, not bad. It's I got the high card
You guys don't understand how this works
I have king so I get the high card. I win everyone plays against the dealer. I hate this game, but i'm gonna play it
If I do if I put money on pair plus by the way
If I put money on pair plus if I get a pair or above that
I make a little bit of money a lot of money. Actually, let's go for a big one
Give me a pair. It's not a pair. I'm out. I have to fold if this hand sucks
And I would have lost
You're a moron
He's playing pair plus omega lol. I know it's a sucker bet, but whatever sometimes suckers win a lot of money
shit
Xbox sucks. The xbox is one of the best systems
oh
Three cards suck go all in I just gotta get one decent uh pair plus hand. It's not a pair plus
But i'm gonna play because I have a king and it's just a high card
Yep
This time we're gonna go even higher
What do you think? All right, i'm looking for a big pair plus
Wow, that's bad stupid idea
I'll do 70 bucks. Let's go pairs
Give me a pair
uh
I have to have to yeah, i'm gonna stay in
All right. I'm all right. I only lost 45 dollars
Get more omega low. I this is all I got i'm not going back to the stupid cashier
pair
What I lost
Then I said be funny ban that person for life
permanently
Damn it
I would have that would have been a flush
All right, just it's a queen. I get a lee i'm only leasing whatever give me something better than a pair
Give me something better than this so I can prove to everybody here that this is like not a sucker's bet every single time
See, why do you get the pairs?
For a second. I thought that said I was broke
But that person's name is brook old again air plus low iq. That's fine. But
Somebody's gonna come over to this table. They're gonna put 100 on pair plus and they're gonna win 15 000
Like me like me
Like me right now like me like me like this guy right here like me
I just won
120 that's nothing. That's that's uh, this is a sucker's bet
It's only two to one
Well, that was bad
It is a sucker's bet
Yeah, let's show you a sucker
How's that for a fucking sucker bet? Oh, I thought it was gonna be a straight. I thought it was gonna be a straight
Do it again
Come on. This is the i'm then i'm gonna leave it. I'm gonna play a different game
Oh my god. Sorry
My brain's turning into soup
Well, go get some crackers
I exit the game what just happened. He's trying to exit the table. Why do I have a thousand dollars?
Oh, I didn't save the game in like an hour and a half
Oops
Oh, we got that big. Hey, remember we got that big hit from
uh
chicago
Royale whatever it is
No value. Okay. I'm just gonna play like five dollar hands and then go into the pair plus and put as much as I can
Play this all night. I don't think I want to I don't want to play this all night
This game is not as fun as like vegas steaks was
It's not a pair plus
I'm gonna throw up because of this
Why did I not play that hand? I would have won at least five dollars back
Does it really matter if I want to win five dollars back at this point? Not really
All right. I'm getting a new game. We're gonna play into the game here. It's been two hours. Yeah, I had fun. It's been fun
You had a flush what?
Wait, I had a I actually had a flush
Wait, that would have been probably like three or four thousand dollars at least if I would have been like 10 grand. Really?
I had the flush
I wasn't even paying attention you streamed this for two hours. I don't think it was that long
It was not that long it was not burger gym is back. This is exhausting
We're not like doing sit-ups
I'm just playing in the casino game
Oh, there it is
There it is
Burger gym for three hours. No, i'm done after this
All right, that's it. What this is the last spin and then that's it and then one more after that
All right next game
God damn it. All right. I'm gonna pee i'll come back. We'll play another game
xbox
Night continues
We're back. Okay. This is another game that i'm not sure
How good this is gonna be but I saw the I kind of just saw the title
And I had to try it. I had to play it. I had to buy it
And that game what i'm referring to obviously
Is dyno topia the sunstone odyssey for xbox?
I wonder uh, let's see how this is
Dino topia, let's say safely. Look at it. It looks a little
A little broken in the middle there, but that's okay
apprentice master
apprentice
I know doi doi doi
I had a vhs of this show. Wait, this is a tv show
Holy shit
Hold on. Wait a second. Did that just go?
Billy west
That t-rex I swear to god that was like
I need to hear a clip of that
I'm not in control of the character
What was the point of showing that they couldn't just say get up. We gotta go
They show that
Here it is. Let's go inside
Follow your brother
jacob
Move in the direction you wish to go
Press b to jump
Okay, do I have attacks?
Ah, the gemini twins have been expecting you
Drake this is castor bollocks. He was a friend of dad's he taught me how to fight and I brought you here
So he can teach you the stick. It's good to meet you. Mr. Pollock's. I was so sad to hear about your father
Jonas was a good friend of mine. It's shrek. Thanks for your concern. Mr. Pollock
This stupid island's been nothing but trouble since we were how are we gonna find a t-rex with a broomstick?
It doesn't seem very good
Just because some blind dinosaur lets him ride around on her
You know, he was doing her a favor as much as she was doing for him
And then he felt like we owed dinotopia some big debt of gratitude
I'm not buying it. You know, there's more to it than that
Everything is happening so fast. Yeah
It's hard for her 24th birthday with the root that keeps these dinotopians alive for so long
He shouldn't have been out there by himself
But it was just an unfortunate accident looks like a typewriter
That has fucked up teeth whatever they're called. Sorry. It's my dad. That's no accident
Is what is he saying? He wants a dinosaur is gonna be tried for murder
You may have animals to defend dinotopia not to destroy it. Whatever i'll do what I want
I'll do it. Wait, i'll do it. I won't
Agree to train you because you've just faced a very traumatic event in your dinosaurs committed to murder
I hope they talk god. I hope they talk to teach you. This is why I ask you
Please be cautious with the skills that I teach i've already gone over most of this with jacob
So let's get my favorite tv show jacob and drake drake and jacob staff of yours
I'm also giving you a sunstone counterweight to place on the other end of your staff
This particular mallet head come on that was at least a plus on one very strong
But three sages who live throughout dinotopia who are former guardians of the island
They are far too old now to defend much of anything
If you ever meet any of them
I'm sure with some persuasion they'd give you other mallet heads
Who may find other smaller sons drake and for sand jacob? Yeah, that's right sunstones when placed into a mallet
Each collected sunstone will add to a pool of energy displayed in the upper left corner with the blue bar
This sunstone energy can be used for sunstone powers when you receive them
It is important that you are always aware of threats around you move in the direction you want to orient the camera
Press to reorient camera first. What is that a chocolate chip? What is that?
Let us go over a few basic attacks approach the training dummy and attack it
What's with that neck?
The super nerd neck that's it
Can't wait to beat the dinosaurs with this move
Okay, interact. Hey, thanks for teaching me. You didn't teach me anything if you target an enemy before you attack
Focus your movements on that. He made a training dummy and just said hey just do whatever you want to
Swing at it, I guess
This is not you're not teaching me anything
Hold to select closest next target
Hold to untarget return. Wait, hold on
You touch it and it targets
Hold to un okay. You tap it to go to another target
Hold to untarget
Okay, I got it. Hold down target a dummy and throw a hobby pepper
What?
He didn't even teach me that i'm learning on my own
Be careful when you use hobby peppers
Usually they'll blind an opponent though. Sometimes all they'll do is make them angry
The dino topia mini series is free and legal to watch on youtube right now. I do not believe that I
Just because something is free does not mean I have the rights to broadcast it
Acts will grow stronger who receive instructions for other attacks from messenger birds. I send out
Let's go. I've got to get going now zane and the other outsiders are waiting for me
Are you sure I can't persuade you to join that robin atkins downs?
I think it is
It is it is it is
Is it no way you noodle head get the same things. That's him. It's him. It's him
I still think it's a mistake for you to run off and join those thugs. Well, I am that's him
And if I were you I'd be careful
The outsiders might just have something planned that's coming your way. I think that after I think that actually is him
Is it listen drake be careful things could get hairy these are some pretty ruthless guys, let's see
I think it's him
Thanks for your concern video games. I can take care of myself
You should be careful too though. Is it him? I don't trust those ones come up
We might not see eye to eye on this dyno topia my brother when it's gone still care about you thanks
Goodbye. Well, thanks for your help. Mr. Pollock's. I should probably get going too. Oh welcome drake
I need to find that. This is him look up miss oxbridge. She is a wise old dyno topia
I think may have another
Bollock use your help with one last thing. I know topia. Where is it? He's placed my favorite glass
What the fuck it's not him in the cave if you find them for me
I will give you some hobie peppers to take with you. I understand if you need to get going though
shit
Pastor pollock's has lost his marbles help him find them what?
The hell is that you did that?
Okay, what the hell do I have to do?
I forget what am I doing kill the bird?
I'm trying I promise
He lost his marbles like in his house
Find miss oxbridge at the town center
Find the glass rocks
What?
Okay, wait while targeted pulled to dodge in a direction
Hold x to block. What is this? Why is there why is there a dinosaur in his house?
This is actually kind of cool. I like this
I get experience for that
This game's kind of fun. I like it. I can't wait to fight a t-rex
Stop hurting him. Is this his pet or something?
I have no idea where i'm supposed to go
I'm just gonna go back down go to the town center. This looks like um, what looks like this big darn asses
It was mr. Bollocks's dog
All right, i'm gonna leave
Let's go to the town center
You've not completed all quests on this level
What the fuck are you talking about? What?
Where's this guy's marbles?
Find his marbles
Is there sprint?
Are they in a chest or something?
You can leave without doing the quests. Can I?
Holy shit, that was a huge jump
I know it's a figure of speech, but why would it want me to stay here?
Nobody played this game. Nobody knows
Okay
Now what?
I'm miss oxbridge
Are these bad? Wait, are these bad? Are these?
Dinosaurs talk?
What?
That t-rex what that t-rex did go
I knew something was weird about the way he roared
Hi there. I wonder if you could help out a fellow dinotopia. I'm having a big party tonight
And I thought some apple pies would be nice to have
My friends are donating the apples and have placed them throughout town
But I've got to get my house cleaned and don't have the time so weird more
Would you be so kind as to get to collect all the apples baskets?
I'll trade you some of my hobby peppers for the apples
Okay, I see one right here
That wasn't his dog was that this
There's like friend
Or it's like
Significant other or something. I don't know. Uh, this is um
I don't know they could talk
This is neighbor
What's the look this little kid here?
You can't talk to the kid
This looks so strange
Where you go? Oh, there he is
skip
Dinotopia. Oh, hold on. What do you have?
Haven't found all my apples yet. I'm working on it
Breathe deep young drake gemini
Seek peace. Are you miss oxbridge?
Why yes, I will get the apples. I promise my friend castor pollock sent word that he has trained you in the use of a weapon
You must be cautious with a weapon after all
The code of dinotopia states that weapons are enemies
Even to their own the dumbest thing i've ever heard if you are to use this weapon responsibly
You must wield it as a guardian of dinotopia. You should only use it to help those in need
And never in a hateful manner. Tell me
Why do you seek to be a guardian of dinotopia?
Well, it's not like i'm really seeking it out
My father deeply loved dinotopia
Before he passed on he made my brother and me promise to defend dinotopia. It's like a
My brother's like a mallet. It's a broomstick with a fucking shoehorn on the end faced with life in this land all alone
The only thing i've ever really cared about is my family. No, all i've got left of it is the promise that I made to my father
So
Perhaps in time you may realize your family can extend beyond your relatives
One thing is for sure young drake. You are not alone
If you will face the perils of dinotopia's defense, you will need to become stronger
One thing you must understand is that the entirety of one's strength
Comes from a balance of one's mind body and spirit
In my you want the lore I defended dinotopia really I used a stone mallet to defeat
All those that sought to harm this wonderful land something about the way that their brains would squish mallet for what seems like
And their skull and brain matter would explode just did it for me within a strong box on a distant platform
As an exercise to strengthen your mind
If you can figure out how to get to this strong box and then return to me with the artifact
I will reward you with the mallet head
Okay
Oh, I just there's a jumping quest
Where is that?
Over here
I got the apples for that guy, too
Can't do it. Don't worry
smash a dino's brain
What is it back here?
Oh shit, it's another dinosaur doesn't talk to
What?
Was that just imagining him talking?
Well, i'm really going crazy
Apples, all right three four
He didn't talk dude. What are you talking about?
I'm the crazy one
Where's this thing to jump to?
This game's amazing
I'm i'm here for a while
I'm not giving up on this
Where is this thing to do?
Game's incredible. All right, i'm gonna play it
Just would oh it's up there. Okay, it's up. How do I get up there?
Help me. How do I get up there?
How do I get up there?
Can I go up even higher?
Who's your destination?
Uh treetop manor
A completely different area
It is but I don't think I could go anywhere in the last area
Why can't they talk?
Is this it?
Does it look like it was down? I mean it was up from where I was
I have no idea
This way
It was a prompt and you missed the area
Go back to the other
Go back to the other woman
Come on
Oh, come on. Really?
Do I just go back to that other area?
Is it in that that just same zone?
I mean, i'll be honest every single thing looks identical. There's no math. I have no idea where I am
I don't even know what that place was called town center
Yeah, I look right over here
Like not do anything about that
Oh, what the fuck is that?
Oh my god. All right. Here it is. So I have to jump to that
How am I supposed to jump to that?
That's really difficult to do this sucked. All right break these
Oh, i'm really glad I did that because it would have taken me a very long time. It just fell off the edge
I i'm fine. I'm good. Give me the weapon
Turn the statue and then I need one more thing of apples. I would like this
Apples good job young drake
You have proven to me that you are worthy of receiving this stone man in 30 minutes
I am not stopping until I fight at least five dinosaurs
Which mallet heads?
Um everybody get down. I thought it was a pterodactyl
But all animals talk in this world, right?
Oh my you'd better get to the hatchery hopefully the matriarch is all right
Remember drake
Only please this is not dyno topia. This is cringe topia
To help those in danger of being harmed
and never ever out of hatred
What would the difference be if I were to?
Punch someone in the face right now out of hatred
Does that change things?
Like if I were to punch you in the face right now because I hate you does that make it different because I didn't use a weapon
Travel between areas of the forest outpost using gondolas like the one you arrived in go to the hatchery
All right. I need apples. It's moral points
Is it really?
All right. I need this other guy's apples. Where are they?
Where's the final bushel of apples?
this is actually a
Good and evil system. That's pretty funny actually
To the right of these fucking apples
This is a book tv show tie-in game
Go back up
All right, I don't think there's another bushel of apples on this floor
This is not where the hell are they it's right there
It's not right here right here. All right. What do I get for doing this?
Great. You've got the hobie peppers now and get these peeled and into the pies
All right, so I got hobie peppers now let's go
to the hatchery
And rescue the dinos in trouble. I don't know
Is that what I'm supposed to do?
You're not wearing any pants. I think I believe i'm wearing pants
What's that exit?
Fuck close the get down
Where's the how do I get out of here?
Okay, here we go hatchery exit
The hatchery is under attack
It doesn't look like anybody's really
That concerned about whatever's happening. I'm not seeing any very much panic
Have you done fable two yet? I have not done fable two. I don't play I played i've beaten that game like three times
But not on stream
next game
Well, I mean it depends it depends if this is if this continues to be a snooze fest i'm gonna move on
Okay, let's go. Yeah, I want to see at least a dinosaur or two
Fable two would be awesome. That's you know, what? That's a really good idea
Get fable two on the list. I will play through fable two defend the hatchery
We've got so many games on the list already
Is this all right? Come on. Let's go. Okay. I feel like this is empty. It's like am I in the
Like the dev game the dev kit whatever it is like why is it nothing here
Fable sucks fable three sucks
Right from what I remember
Who am I fighting here
Who's the bad guy?
In this scenario, am I am I fighting the humans?
This dinosaur is the is the one getting attacked
This really is just like dumpy fable with dinosaurs
But not even fable. This is way worse than fable
Thank you for helping me if you had gotten here any later, this is so boring
But there's so much potential
Get away
There's so much potential here. Look at it. It's so it's right here in front of us
We can taste it
What's wrong with fable three?
Um fable three is you like open chests to make decisions
It's stupid
You go to like the the weird world where you like have to make decisions by using a currency
I hated that it was stupid
Unlock like the next like thing to try the next decision to make with like a fucking chest currency thing
The game is dumb. It was this dumb currency thing. I hated it
Make sure you got like followers to open the chests. No, I want to just like decide if i'm gonna execute the guy
Or not
Give me that decision. I just want to make that decision
Do I steal the bread or do I not steal the bread make it simple for me?
Your memory is terrible. I don't think it is that's yeah, then fable
I thought it was jar jar things
If you bring me three of these bright blue plants
I'll give you some information about a sunstone. I don't want to play anymore
I'm done next game next one. I don't want to play this one anymore
Wait, this guy's a hostel
It's a cave man. Yeah, I guess
That dinosaur looks like my school superintendent
Huh?
What are you talking about? How what are you even talking about?
Especially just want to play fable two
Should I yay? Should I?
Can I play should I start fable two?
Should I play fable two next week and just like beat it like play through it over the weekend?
Okay, but hold on though. It is fable
Is my brain remembering is that game actually good and fun and interesting and shit? Like I don't remember
I think it is right
There's a game called dyno topia and you just fight
defias bandits with shields
I fall down
What do I have superpowers?
You said you beat fable two like three times I did like 10 years ago. I don't remember anything about the game
All I remember is this one specific line
It'll be as normal as the sound of your own heartbeat
I don't know what the context is. I don't know where the character is. I just remember that line
I don't know what that means, but I know it's in the game
play fable three
Whoa, that's cool play gothic. I have gothic three. I think I have all the gothic games installed right now
I keep adding shit to lists and then I never play them
I have so many games that you're just gonna see trickled in over like months and years of time
Sometimes I forget I even bought them or installed them
And then it takes somebody to remind me like oh, hey, dude play gothic and i'm like, oh, yeah
I have fucking every gothic installed right now. I have all of them
All right, god doesn't play that
Three is shit. Yeah, I would play two before I play three. I talk to the
I can't talk to the one source
Please god do not play sneak king
I already did and everybody hated it. Yeah, I did too
Oh, I need to play nba street as well
nba street
I think one of my favorite games on xbox 360 and xbox
Oh fuck. I need to play that
I'm a street is probably the best game
That's a sports game. Let's make that clear and the nba street franchise
Was the best sports franchise that and slugfest and they just decided to stop making them because for some stupid ass reason
Every video game company decided that simulations and realistic take me seriously video games were what everybody I apparently cared about and nobody does
Where are the crazy fucking slugfest games? Where's where's nfl blitz?
Why I don't want to play madden. I want to play blitz. I don't want to play mlb the show
I want to play slugfest. I don't want to fucking play nba 2k. I want to play nba street
Why did they stop making these games?
They stopped making them
We have like a full two generations of consoles of new technology and new engines. That would be so much fun with these games
How would you stop making nfl blitz?
Dude nba street, it's not like oh, they wouldn't be popular. They're not popular. They weren't that popular. You're misremembering things
NBA street was so popular
It was one of the most fun arcade games ever. It was so good
I want to make like another one
And they've they've done a go nba jam. Yeah, remember when we like ported that to fucking iphones
No, no, no, give me another one. Give me a new one
That you didn't just like make it in flash
Hey guys, remember nba jam. Oh, you're gonna love this one. The only difference is we made it in flash this time
Well, you know, I don't like come on. You mean give me a real one
Please stop hogging the xbox. Your brother wants to play halo
Fuck halo
The matriarch is ill
Just look at her
You have to find the antidote drake
Relax just jesus with the spear has the antidote in a diamond shaped vial. It's blue
Get it and bring it back quickly to our beloved matriarch. I have no idea what's happening in this world
Oh, what is the matriarch?
You have to look for the leader drake
Hurry the matriarch is what did we miss a very important piece of history in this world?
Please get it
Yeah, and why is it?
Uh, I don't even get me going on this bullshit
I ever everyone wanted to take their game so seriously
No, no, no, we can't have anything like funny or fun or interesting or like not realistic in our like wrestling game
It's got to be a fucking
Guy with underwear on simulation where you like simulate wrestling and it's real
No, no, no, you have to go for a first down
Touchdown got it real. This is a real simulation
Give me the fucked up shit again. It was stuff was so fucked up. You could just do whatever you wanted
It was so much more fun
I don't want to pretend i'm playing a game of football. I want to drop kick somebody in the head
while they're running for a touchdown and then I want them to like
Just roundhouse kick me in the stomach
And have a fumble happen and then we both have to fist fight to get the ball. That's fucking fun
I don't want to sit there and play a fake pretend game of football
And everyone's saying blood bowl but blood bowl isn't blood bowl like a turn-based strategy game. It's not what i'm looking for
I want an nba street
You could do these crazy moves where the ball went under your leg
They went behind your back
You did like a backflip and then you did a huge slam dunk before you slam dunked
Right before the ball went in the net you passed it to your teammate
You were in the air then he goes in the air you pass it back to the guy that goes into the air
And he did two front flip slam dunks and it was like four million points
I loved it. It was like uh, tony hawke. It was like tony hawke with sports
Where am I? What am I doing?
How do I get over there? You're ranting
Yeah, I know I am because like what have they done?
To sports video games
I was supposed to switch games. Oh, right, right, right
What I just do
I want a wrestling game and you know, I'm
I want a wrestling game where the rules can be crazy
Like I want the ring to be covered in ice and just have ai fight each other and see what they do
You know, how fun would that be it'd be fun just to do that
And then you got wwe and wwe the last wwe 2k game was so fucking awful
That they stopped making it for like two years because they were like, holy shit
We gotta like try to make this even remotely good
I hope they do
I hope they go back
And do it the old the way that it was done like six or seven years ago
And that's not boomer. This is not like oh the way things are used to be I'm talking about like five years ago
Not like 20. We're talking like five or six years ago
This game is awful
Like i'm talking like 2014
How long ago was that it was like seven years ago, but whatever you get it. It's not that long ago. It's within 10 years
Why are you still playing it?
Well, because it's I don't know. It's a it's a means to deliver my rant to you
It's not a means to deliver a gameplay video
Well, what am I putting in next? Let me see watch this shitty
Cussing outside or drug you and drake here retrieve the antidote
I am very grateful to you drake
I know it is not much but
Except these gauntlets as a small sign of my appreciation
They will help protect your hands and forearms
I hate to be a bother
But if you are on your way back to the forest i would appreciate it
If you could bring this eggshell extract to the herbalist there, I am sure she will reward you for its delivery
Deliver the eggshell extract to the herbalist at the forest outpost
Well, I have to play this because otherwise, what am I ever gonna play this again?
There's no reason to I have it
This game's terrible. We thought there was gonna be a t-rex and shit and it's not it's just like
Talking animals the game
All right. Here we go
Uh turns out I did not throw it in the trash. I have it right here
And if there's ever gonna be like an xbox
dog shit grab bag night
This is the time to do this
So let's put it in
It's halo 2
Come on load
It's the other one the one that I thought I threw in the trash turns out it's right here
single player
Great character
Aren't you the king have it your way customize your character
Like am I I go ahead pickles and relish and mustard to my character like on the shirt
Okay, select character. How is this customizing? I'll be brett
hair hat helmet
You really want to save what this is not this is just just I don't why even put this in
I need to make like a lettuce tomato
Like pickles it's the joker your name for your character
I don't
Didn't you already have a name?
Arthur no, I don't care about this. I'm gonna play this for 15 minutes. Why I know I don't need to make him
I've done a name him. You're gonna forget about him tomorrow. You made jeff hardy. He does look like jeff hardy
Are you so i'm not angry what are you talking about?
I can't believe you said this is gonna be halo 2
Uh rides rides
Garage, all right. My car is gonna be green one
And then rides the broiler the deep king's court. All right, we're gonna go to king's court
You'll probably guess the way this is played to hit the puck into your opponent's goal
Wait, this did they make rocket league before rocket league?
This would be wild if this is what this is
This is rocket league chicken
I didn't even take a character. What who am I what team am I on?
I'm on red team. I just won
You're always the king
Well, what's the point of customizing a character if I always have to play as the king?
This looks like the floor of a public bathroom. I'll just tell you
What do you mean own goal
You can choose the characters. I don't care to choose the characters
Oh god, I can't wait to play blinks the cat
We gotta get we have to get the really shitty ones out first
I'm getting motion sick
I got one more. I want to play tonight
And this one could be really good and I mean very like incredible it's possible we'll see I have high hopes for the final game
Get out of here get out of my goal
It's the frame rate. The frame rate is making me motion sick. It actually is
Oh, this hurts. I'm actually my throw up. I just stopped playing
Yeah
I feel terrible. I feel awful right now
Oh my god, I feel awful
I feel awful
Are they all the same? Oh, they're all the same aren't they? This is just this is every every mario party game. I got you
That was way worse than any
Okay. Oh i'm done. I'm gonna play the game. I want to play
the game i'm about to put in
is
Uh, it had it has a lot of potential
Remember all these xbox games are all based on potential
Uh, we're gonna play omerta city of gangsters
This is yeah, i'm not gonna give this 30 minutes. This game's just horrible
Isn't this one on pc? It actually might be
I got it on my xbox. I thought we can play blinks. That will be for another night. Why do I do that?
What's the point of me doing that? What's wrong with this?
Get it in there. Come on. Let's go. All right read disk
Come on. Let's hurry up load it up
Download to human if this doesn't work. It's gonna take me like an hour to download that game through original xbox 360
Hold on. Why is that name familiar? What else did they do today?
Wait, they made
They made the templar game the first templar was calypso. Give it a try new game. Let's just do it
urge his name the boss
Uh, i'm gonna this part this I I think I connect with this guy the most I think
He's like he just kind of has he looks like it could be me
You grew up in a small village in sicily your childhood nickname was
Uh, obviously betty's
When you grew up enough you far when you grew up enough your father
Decided that you should learn diligence and learn a trade you became apprentice to
stones the shopkeeper
The most ridiculous feat you managed to pull off during your youth was
Stealing the key for the village mayor's wine cellar and drinking most of it before you were discovered
wrestling an enraged bull with your bare hands
Sweet talking a local loan shark to forgive your debt and give you even more money just until you get back on your feet
That one I've always said when you were 16 years old you fell in love with the prettiest girl in the village
Her brother challenged you to a duel
Since you were challenged you got to pick the weapon it was
Wait, just pick a gun and shoot him a knife
Bare fists you let your enemy pick confident. You can beat him with every weapon
Bare hands you decided to leave sicily and immigrate to america because
A don put a price on your head after you had an affair with his wife
A vendetta wiped out your family leaving you and your brother the only survivors
You decided to pursue the american dream in the land of opportunity
Let's go down and you're ready to select your difficulty level medium. Let's go negative one
Okay, why did I punch that guy? Yeah, why is the audio mixing is so bad on the xbox?
Select district main av
You can only go to main. Let's uh save the game
Okay main av
Okay
Squigs
What I have to do
squigs
Looks like tropico
Uh, I don't even know how this game is gonna play
buddy squigs
It's by the ex excom guys. Is this the tropico? Is it the same people? All right. All right. Let's go. Come on
Pan view zoom in and out and rotate the view
Where am I with the camera to explore the district?
All right
It's like your hideout. All right. Hold on people saying that the audio is horrible
All right, let's go. I'll take care of him. I'll take care of him. All right, get this shit out of here
I'll take care of it. It's better
All right over the hideout
All right. This is this panel holds important information about the selected building goes by pressing b
Take place to hide when things get rough
Since we're new in atlantic city boss, we should learn what we can about the district
I wish I had a neck like that one day. I really sometimes I do
There's a shop across the street from our home
You can use buildings with the question mark sign above them to gather information about the neighborhood
Okay, there's a shop
There's a red crab
shop the shop the shop
unknown building
Send the boss to gather information in the shop across the street
Okay, the shopkeeper has heard every rumor and knows everything about everyone
Either of these actions will allow you to learn more about the district
Big spender or cheers. All right, big spender
Send the boss on this assignment
Spend somebody to get the information you need the boss is a mastermind
I want to look like this
in like 50 years
I you you look at like old paintings of that's like a benjamin franklin issue. You look like old paintings people look like this
Just like well in fact that guy looked like he
That guy looked like he fucking meant business
You already do I don't look like that
Like that that's like what they they put the powdered wig on this guy and he's just like wow
That was a fucking that guy must have been important or something
Put a powdered wig on him and give him like a big frilly thing around his neck
All right, wait for the boss's return. Is he going in?
Where am I? Oh, that's me
Can I look in here?
It's a turkey neck
Okay
Looks like you found a couple of independent breweries boss. We can steal some beer from them
Okay, raid an independent brewery
Can I die?
raid
20 beer and gain heat a real boss ain't afraid to grow there are far too many opportunities for you to handle us
Why don't you bring in squigs to hell? Oh here comes squigs. We all love this guy
You can hire additional gangsters and send them on assignments. This way you can run multiple assignments at the same time
Portrait of a silhouette with a question mark represents an empty slot for a henchman
Use lbrv press a to view the available henchmen
Okay
There is squigs
hire
15 a day
All right kids. You got a pistol
He's very very
Take it by force, okay gather 40 beer casks casks. Okay, are we together?
How do I view in here?
Raid song for what?
Am I in there?
How do I send him on the mission? He's all sound like family guy characters. They kind of do
Do it yourself. Oh, I returned with 20 beer. Uh, do it again
Let's put raiding the brewery. Ah
Gather 40 beer
That's me right there. All right, we'll go back in there
Go in the brewery raid
each gang to precise
This action will take will be available in 270 seconds
I mean 270 seconds
It's a mobile game. No, it's not
it's not
Why is that in here? No, it's just that it's
Go to other breweries
Here we go. Rate it
Start the raid. I'm in a rush boss
Cool down so you don't keep reading the same place over and over again. That makes sense
You get it done
All right, there it is. I got 40 now we can sell the beer and make some real money
I heard some irishman is looking to buy beer. You should talk outside contracts
Okay
My contract have many contacts yet, but that'll soon change next game
Yeah, this is slow. This is kind of slow. Uh, I thought I was gonna be able to run around as a gangster
It's a little slow. It's a little slow. It's a little slow
I'm doing one more. We got i'm doing one more one more one more after this. I'm not going out
We got one more game. I'm gonna pick a random one over there. It's a console management game
Yeah, I know. I know I didn't I didn't I had no idea. I was almost hit by a brick on the road today
Now i'm rethinking my life. I should buy some beer open a pub. All right, sell it to this guy
All right, all right, that's all right. All right. All right. Okay. I'm gonna i'm vetoing this one cool idea
It's fun game, but not not right now
I just didn't didn't grab me. It did not grab me at all. Well, i'm not done. All right, give me a second
I'm gonna grab another one that wasn't good enough. I didn't know that one. Remember all the shit I just talked
I talked a lot of shit didn't I
We're going out on this one
I am actually incredibly excited for this. I've been waiting to play this
We're going out on one of the best xbox 360 games ever made
great
Not ratatouille
What were we just talking about?
half an hour ago or so
45 minutes ago. I was very very very very mad about it
nickelodeon nictunes mlb baseball
Haha, you thought we were going out on some boring time management game. I don't think so
It's time for nictunes mlb
Oh, there's no profile. I would love to create a new profile
All right pick up game
All right
Mix nictunes and mlb players for the best of both worlds here. You choose a team and mix that choose rotor. All right, here we go
I want to be a home team
Home team, let's go
So who should I be?
the goofballs
The comeback kids the boppers. I think it's gotta be the boppers the meteors the raccoons the sonic booms the orioles. What?
Oh, these are these actual teams
Oh, there's the boston red sox. No, I don't want to be a real team
I want to be the boppers
The boppers versus the red sox nice. I'm ready
Time to draft by nictunes
To play a game
Okay, so we have to we pick
Powder toast man first pick powder toast man first pick
I don't care powder toast man's first pick every time
It's absolutely first pick
He's a pitcher two seam. He's got a curve ball
Thank god I can play as part of toast man
Your first pick your first pick is sheen
Oh, this is gonna be easy win where the other nictunes sponge bob
Oh my god, godly puppy. Wow, this is got got quite the dream team over there
stimp ren
Do I have to have ren and stimpy who I don't know ultra lord. Uh, I see you're going with a theme. Okay
I have to have stimpy if I have ren
And oh he took the flying dutchman. I was I was I in the flying dutchman
How about gazz? Yeah, definitely gazz
Wow, not even real nictune fans
Uh, should we go to danny phantom danny fans? We're not even in the game
Planet sheen we're going to spongebob's land. Wait, do they have fenway park?
All right. Yeah, I we have to go here. This is too weird. He is how come why they weren't selectable some of these shows are
everyone
Hey, don't laugh too hard. They're doing this shit
They did that like nickelodeon game. What was it? What was it mba nfl? It's like spongebob would come on the screen
Ellsbury this is old
Okay, let's see
Throwing smoke to throw a pitch aim and select a pitch release the button at the top of the meter
Shut the girl shut up
Release the button at the top of the meter for a perfect pitch
Okay
What we got? That's okay. You don't want to throw it. You want to throw it in the cold zone, right?
That's not their hot zone, right?
What do I got for pitches? All right, we're gonna go two steam fastball
Herb was earned by throwing strikes or taking balls at the plate
When a segment of the meter is full activate a turbo pitch
All right, we're gonna throw we're gonna get a curveball to drop a little bit out of the zone. It sounds like a good play to me
There it is
All right. Now we're gonna we're gonna really challenge him. They're gonna go up and in i'm gonna go up and in in the strike zone
He's gonna be really tempted to swing at it. He thinks i'm throwing a ball
I don't
All right, I don't
I hate this character. I don't know. I hate I hate this character. I think this character's stupid. Can I throw at him?
All right, I can't do that
Let's go change up
Should I go right in the middle?
I'm going curveball dropping out of the zone. Oops breaking ball called. I have a turbo meter. How do I use it?
Throw a perfect game for a billion off the debt. I don't think I could throw a perfect game
I think it's possible. I'll try i'll try it. Can I get that as a deal? I'll try
Oh my god. No, no, I want to use that. I don't want to use that. How do I take that off?
How do I take off the turbo mode deal? All right, i'm gonna really try what what's the counter?
Three and two. All right, i'm gonna throw a change up right out here
That's not a perfect game fielder is automatically selected for you
Run him towards the ball and he will make the catch if he is close enough
Did you choose a base?
All right, how about a no hitter? How about a no hitter?
Because yeah, that's not a perfect game right perfect game. Well, I actually know it is throw the ball base press the action. Yeah
No one has to no one can make it to first base. Okay, wait, I thought the hot light
I've been pitching it in their hot zones. We go
Doers don't understand baseball
Dude, why don't do this shit? You're right. You want to get us to be interested in sports again?
They gotta like get
Yep, well just hold off. I'm working on it. Okay, i'm working on it
I'm working on it. It was supposed to be there a year ago. I'm working on it. Just wait right here
perfect pitch
Last august I was supposed to do a stream and just wait. All right, i'm fucking working on it
It's gonna be it's gonna be my favorite stream ever
It will be the my most favorite thing i've ever done
On youtube twitch doesn't matter. It'll be my favorite thing i've ever done strike three sit down
I got here. Perfect game is intact
All right time to get time to win
sponge ball
Great approach in the play, okay hit the ball
Aim your hit into the field and do a contact swing for a good chance at a hit
Allowing hits will cause the pitcher's effectiveness to decrease
All right. Well, how do we do a power swing?
Direct your runner towards the base that you want to go to use the base radar to see where you are
So, okay left stick aim towards the base you want to go to
That's a double
No, it's not no, it's not stay back
What's the power swing
Who's this
Okay, first thing i was like what cartoon character is this guy?
Aim your hit into the field and execute a bunt bunting moves your bad. I'm not sacrificing bunting. Why would I do that?
sacrifice bunt
Up there
That's the he just I just hit into a double play shit
Go go. What are you doing? What if you run the second base run the second base?
Wait isn't I've only been this happy in clothes once
All right power swing seems you're gonna hit a home run right now over the monster
Okay, left bumper is move all your runners the next position. Yes, that's what I want get down it. Everybody go
All right, here's a random person steal you have to first initiate a lead-off. Okay, who should I steal with?
It's a hit and run get in
Timpy is here. Why is Timpy so big?
For a second. I did not know who this was. I was like who is this weird ant character
shit
How weak is uh is ren?
Timmy get up why is Timmy sleeping?
Shit it's all right. This really does look like a gta mod
What
I can't get over. Okay, perfect game. Come on. I gotta throw a perfect game
All the time it would take to do this it would take so much time to make a gta mod like this
And why would you do this?
Oh, I need to build my meter
Who the fuck is the pitcher?
That's powdered toast man
Let's strike out
The pitcher is spongebob. Why would you think that?
All right, I gotta settle down I need to get a perfect game. Oh shit. He just turbo mode
Uh-oh. I'm I'm counter turboing
Eat shit motherfucker
Yes
Uh-oh david ortiz
Oh, I was gonna say why don't I get david ortiz? He's gonna hit a home run
Stay away from david ortiz
Oh, no
It's a foul ball
It's i'm good. It's a foul ball
only one in one
Curveball in the dirt. Let's go
Come on swing at that david ortiz had so much trouble hitting curveballs down
again
Curveball down
Come on swing at it
Oh, i'm in trouble
I'm good. If you feel I can't make the catch switch to the fielder with the next best chances left trigger
Oh gas
And everyone told me did not put gas on team
You see how fast that she just threw that ball
Oh get gas off the team who's gas who omega low, okay you who and now
What's this shit?
Whatever
I don't know who this person is. All right, i'm gonna take a pitch. Wow, they still do steroids. It's a good hit
Oh, I hate that character. It looks like it looks like it's like brian griffin or something
Indeed to bring in the left-handed pitcher here. Wait, they took out they took sheen out
Already subbing out sheen
That's gonna make me laugh i'm gonna be like in the bathtub tonight and i'm gonna be laughing hysterically
I'm gonna be just sitting with like just relaxing with my eyes closed and i'm just gonna start it's gonna hurt and start laughing hard
Shit
Come on spongebob
Get with it here
So, it's all right
Should I sub a pitcher in or should we keep um part of tostman?
How's part of tostman doing?
Can I warm somebody up part of tostman for s knight?
No, I don't know who that is. That's not a funny character
No, it has to stay as it has to it has to stay
As part of toastman, otherwise, it's not a perfect game
Oh
Oh shit
I have to throw a strike because he did turbo mode. All right, we're going we're just going up and in no not um
Change up down change up down and away. It's the longest you have to wait for a pitch got it
I'm safe
I can't throw a ball when he's in turbo mode. All right two strikes
Are you getting this from curveball in the dirt? It's gonna fucking swing and miss
I'm not gonna chase that low
Anything up and in fast?
Come on b slider get it
I lose
It is no perfect game
Damn it
How do I how do I pick off?
Oh, no, I don't get it. No debt wipe. I didn't throw a perfect game
Of course, it was patrick that did it
You lost to patrick, you're not adding debt. What do you mean?
He's lying touch me so bad. He's making errors in the field
Her bow hit activated. Oh, no. Okay. Um
Flip finger fastball down and in painting the corners there. That's a strike. I can't get over the gta mod thing
It's so funny
One in one count. He's got nothing. I'm going up and in fastball. Let's challenge him
Inside for a strike
Okay, keep in mind the flying they used two of their turbos on the flying dutchman and he's gonna swing and miss right now
absolutely pathetic
What a waste of two meters
Only two nothing I can still lose this is gaming. Oh, yeah
Sponge bob people thought it was spongebob. That's my favorite thing ever
Down god damn it. I can't believe patrick of all people
I want to hit a home run stepping in for the second time cj writer. This one is one for one
To try to get to that ball
Why did you do that?
There was someone you could have caught that normally you didn't have to jump across the whole game
This reminds me of the movie angels in the outfield
All right. It's all right
That happens in angels in the outfield advance the third. It's all right. All right. I gotta go on third
All right wren
shit
That's gonna get in there that's gonna get he's fast
God damn it wren looks. Oh, yeah wren looks like a bug
Looks like an ant
I can't believe I didn't get a shutout. That sucks
Look at all these perfect pitches perfect two-seam fastballs. Nobody can keep up with me
Let's go change up change up right down the middle let's fucking just let's fuck with them
Cut out still in yeah, perfect. Yeah, that's what I mean. Perfect game is off
This is so fun
So fun and then and then that no simulation. It's not real doesn't have to be real. It's just fun
Split-fingered out of the way mario super sluggers is better
They're all good
You know how much shit you talk with your friends when you play these games
I got more invested and it was so dead serious and so invested
Playing these cartoon baseball games against friends on the couch
Than anything else than any real baseball game. Let's get back to the game mario super strikers makes me livid
directory here it is
right to
mario strikers on the gamecube
That game is awesome
Paint it right on the edge
I almost have a full meter if I get a full meter is a guaranteed home run
That's what i'm waiting for
Character every time I see him it makes me angry tapping in for the second time. All right. Yes. Here we go
Damn it
Oh my god
Get out of here
What shit?
I want to see the whole run. Come on
That's the only fanfare we get
You want to do it? I'll do it too
That bitch was dancing maybe it's time for dinner on a movie you didn't even hit it it doesn't matter
I hate this guy. Just get rid of him. That's three. Nothing. I'm good
There's only one more inning kind of fun
Oh, they're so bad
A little bunk
All right sponge ball put it in the seat
Come on. That was right down the middle. It was not too late
That's down the line
That's a fair ball go go go go go that's a fair ball go go go go go go go back back back it up
Back it up. Go back
i'm good
Can I like substitute this guy for a cartoon character here's the pitch get in there
All right, this is it who cannot stop my swing
Of course, why does patrick have to ruin everything?
I was doing so good
It's not perfect not a perfect game. It's a shutout, but it's not a perfect game
I want to play another one. I'm gonna play another game. I want to see the other nicktoon characters
You have to pick a different team
Or is it just random like a random pool of the characters?
Here he is patrick
only reason
Postman is rolling right now. Yeah, he is. He's really good
All right, let's we have to embarrass patrick because he embarrassed me
Right free
That's it the buffers win final score that's so fun cat dog is in this game
With cat dogs in the game
What am I doing i'm unlocking what am I unlocking? All right, let's do the pickup game
Okay, i'm gonna be on the home team again and let's be on the uh, the goofballs the goofball goofballs versus the
Um the yankees, haha, I hate yankees
Okay, there's new people here annie phantom as again I want no I want I want another pool
How many characters i've seen before?
Sandy wait, who's the pitcher sheen's actually a good pitcher. It's all the same characters
How do I get new ones?
Is there any way I can get new characters?
you don't these are new danny phantom and uh, and
Nesmith weren't here before
I think I want the yak as a pitcher with that fastball
Pick your first basement any phantom was not here
They were they weren't all right first baseman. I want it to be
Uh sandy pick your second basement
um
prince zuko
Pick your third basement
Where's the who has an arm? They thought he took gas
I need somebody uh
fanboy
Something funny that you guys might not know about fanboy
The voice actor for fanboy is cricket and always sunny
Yeah, the same person
That you didn't know that
Uh, how about uh invader sim?
Larry larry lobster, I think this is a good team
Now to the stadium to play in I want to go swimming
Let's go to uh fanboy chum chum frosty freeze field frosty freeze field
Yeah, where's rocko and heffer and
There's are real monsters in this game. How do you get them? I want to pick those guys
To unlock them, maybe
This is like the germa 985 colors
All right, here we go
Maybe you could use a little rest
Just fastballs only his fastball is so good. I'm only going to do fastballs
It's 90 this thing goes up to 95
I have to do tournaments to unlock the other guys. Oh, okay. Well, I know what we're doing after this
I know how to play
Oh be careful transfer a new perfect game. Uh, I don't think that's on the table
97 miles per hour only gonna throw fastballs
Ha let's get back to the action stepping in for the first time today
Tara
Katara was available. I didn't know that I didn't see that
First pitch is a strike
Damn it. I thought that was gonna be gone
All right, let's go splitter
He was right there
All right, come on sandy
Home run first pitch I guarantee it
I guarantee it home run first pitch I guarantee it
He's in the kill bill outfit
Why why yeah, why is she dressed like in the kill bill outfit?
Here's the second pitch
It's bruce lee. Oh
Oh, I don't know anything about anything
All right. Come on fanboy. Here comes cricket
Here he is his power is terrible
Alex rodriguez up
If you have red sox fan, you hate a rod boo him
If you don't know who alex rodriguez is
Then we are not in the same generation
At all i'm probably like i'm probably like 15 plus years older than you
Which is weird to think about that in it. It's very strange
I want to unlock the areal monsters who watches sports anymore. I mean I don't
I did back in 2005
I got stimpy this time. Maybe he's got a lot of power
Nobody can hit this ball. Why is larry the lobster that color?
Was it red kill bill
Zero zero zero, this is what a boring game of baseball
All right, here we go, here's zuko probably shit a lot of power. Yeah, say goodbye way too late
I don't think that has anything to do with the game
Oh god damn it. I was he's a stupid 78 mile per hour ball
Get out of the park. That's gone. See you later
Holy shit, I can't believe it coming up next scott. It was unbelievable. What's in there?
Thank you
That ball was on fire. Yeah, that was going out. That was absolutely out of the park
Of puppies in the game, but fairly odd parents aren't I think they are
I think that's just the yeah. Why is larry the lobster looks ridiculous. That looks really just awful
It looks like a whoopee cushion
Oh you want to do that? That's fine
I'll get it right down the middle for you. Look
I've been waiting a great deal of life for this moment. What is this character from?
Is this jimmy neutron painting the corners there? That's a strike
Ladder open it. I think yaks the best picture
Says it's a ball in tip drag up
Nobody can keep up with this. I want to check out the tournament after this
I want to see if I can unlock people
The yak is juicing
Yeah, so wouldn't probably every single person you've seen on the screen so far
real people
You know back in like 2000 2000 like 2001?
for like 2006
Almost every single baseball player was on some kind of drug
like 1998 to like 2005 2007
Oh, he looks so weird
Finally some action
Larry, all right, let's do i'm going from back to back to back home runs
He's gonna catch him because he's daddy phantom gonna catch him because he's a daddy phantom. It just sucks
I don't know. Who is this person? All right, whatever. Whoever you are. You're hitting home run
back to back
Take that back
That was always the show that came on nickelodeon and I would just switch channels because I was like, yeah
Yeah
Chip this guy's name is chip monk
That's three home runs in a row
Got it
chip monk
Yeah, see i danny phantom time to hit the showers time to hit the 2 a.m. Block on nickelodeon
I'd see you later
Let's go for let's do it again that was a different person I might go out
Oh, no
They took him out
Where are all the nicktoon characters? These are all just regular people
Fuck I got greedy
How why is there no where are all the nicktoons? All right, there he is
All right, stop grunting like a weirdo it's nicktoons baseball, you're not like dead lifting 500 pounds
Settle down. What the fuck is wrong with me?
This player is over one on the day
Chill out venom
Uh, that one hurt that one hurt
You're a psycho you like fanboy chum chum. I know I didn't hate that show
I kind of did but I didn't like the john travolta character. I thought was just annoying
Yeah, the guy who's talking like this he was like a bully
He was like, you gotta get away from me
That was really bad john travolta
whatever
But that's it. I don't like that character. He was the best. No, it was it was I don't know. I don't like him
I like chum chum
Chum chum, I love chum chum's voice
This show is trash
That's how I feel internally what you just said about how what you just said
Down the line. All right, go go go go. That's at least two
That wasn't
Remember was a 27 year old man when chum chum first aired
Right, what was that's pokemon game that you bought?
Damn it
Here we go again
That's it get home home home home home home back back back back. What the fuck was that move?
Oh
25 year old relating to I didn't I didn't say I relate to chum chum. I said he thought he was cute
It was like a cute character
It's like a little like oh, he's cute. They like they like frosty freezies
I didn't buy chum chum merchandise. I thought the show was like cute
I saw like four episodes total. I was sick with the flu one day. Sorry
Unforgivable
Don't do that. I'll just do it too. Let's go for a challenge here up and in
This is it I win the game after this
He's the guy who says he like cartoons. We're all cheering spongebob right now
Are we really going to talk about?
That's not for you old man
It's a perfect game
Um, I think it is what?
There was no bet
Shit, why didn't I not do it for this game?
Play it on hard. Okay
Can I change the difficulty?
Stinky
He did just do though
Oh stop, it's a meme. It's a meme that's been all over the internet
Just all right, this one's for all the marbles guys
Okay, this is not all-star we're doing nine innings if I win this game
I get 500 million off the debt
If I lose this game
500 million gets added
This is it. This is this is a big one
Okay home team
I'm gonna be the sonic booms
versus
the um
You know just to make it fair versus like the comeback kids
Come back kids pick your starting pitcher
Okay, as is pitch in this game pick your first basement
All right first baseman's gotta be
I think i'm gonna take patrick
Your second face
Hmm
Chum chum
I gotta go with what I want
Third basement, I would pick danny phantom, but I don't that's I don't like that show
Third basement gotta have somebody with an arm
sandy
Sandy
No, no
No arm
Get third base gotta be somebody with a strong arm. It's gotta be sandy
Pick your shortstop. I'm ready. This is it. This is the team
This is the team for me to win this and we're gonna play
at
Danny phantom arena
This is a lot riding on here and this this is an all-star difficulty. We've got nine innings
Now i'm no longer playing for fun
All right sponge bob I should have picked sponge bob that was a mistake all right gas has a cutter
Oh my god
Gas is even cooler. She throws submarine
Even cooler. She throws submarine
And look at the ghost trail
sinker
Hey steady diet of sinkers means ground balls all game
All right, that's two
Steady diet of sinkers low
Ground balls all game
Shit full count
Victory screwball, you know, you know what a screwball is
Screwball is a curve ball that goes the other way
And you have to spin the baseball the other way you have to move your wrist
You have to flick your wrist to the left if you're a right-handed pitcher
If you throw a screwball, you just fuck up your elbow. Everybody's ever thrown a screwball has tons of problems
Because you do with a curve ball you come down and you spin kind of you the ball you spin
You're to the right side if you're a right-handed pitcher
You have to flick your wrist like left while you throw as hard as you can
To have the ball go the other direction a screwball is a curve ball that goes the other way
It breaks the other way
It literally fucks up your whole body
I think there's only like five people in major league baseball that's ever actually thrown a screwball because it's guaranteed to break you
I don't care about baseball lore
Oh danny phantom
Rolled at his head
Come on computer
Computer is not one in this game
Focus I have money on the line. I what about me?
I got ice stand to want to win this too. Let's get back to the action cutter up and in in the strike zone
Patrick don't power
We all have money on the line
m cannon
Oh part of toast man is so hard. It's a 70 mile per hour curve ball and it arcs from 12 to six
Oh, he's so good
Oh, it's so hard to hit that
Really?
Let's go
No
That's fine
The part of toast man's so good, why did I not pick part of toast man? Stop swinging at balls
That's like being in the corner of boxer and going. Hey, stop getting punched in the face. It's not as easy as you think it is
It's fine. It's fine. How did you bet on me? You bet on me because i'm gonna win
How do you dive? How do you dive? How do you dive? I don't know, but I got it
Oh god, he's so good. He's probably the best character
It's all right, how do you die?
I didn't I have to know how to dive
batting running pitching
Fielding turbo turbo defense feeling we just dive. I mean, there's definitely a dive. We've seen people do it
People have done it. We've seen people does it automatic. Is it a it's a button
Oh, it's action. Okay
I person person on first we got it. How many else one out?
Going for a double play writer
Double play way behind it
Split it down and in ground ball that pitch is taken counts two and two
Oh no
Um, oh shit somebody on base
Yes, I can't hit anything that was huge
That was one of the biggest plays the whole game I can do this still okay two outs
I don't have to worry about a ground ball
Take a chase
What do you say? What am I talking to?
All right, rand's gonna strike out right here, you're gonna leave a man on
What that's right on the corner that's
What the fuck is going on? I hate american sports
What? I mean, this is nicktoons baseball
It's a little different
All right, here's all you need to know about american baseball get out
Go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go go slide
All right. Here we go. This is it. Yeah, nice hit
Uh pitcher throws ball batter tries to hit ball
If you catch ball in air batter sit down
If ball on ground and batter not make two base
Well, let me hit a fucking home run real quick
On second i'm not gonna swing at a turbo pitch
now
Oh, that could be that's a run
Come on. You're so slow. Why are you so slow?
Get the third
Oh
Yes in the lead
How much power do you got? Oh my god, this is huge. This would be it
Get in there. That's another run. Imagine imagine betting a go to what are you doing?
What the fuck happened?
What just happened?
Why do they go back?
No, okay, all right, all right, all right, all right, it's it's going out one out
It's a ball. Don't swing it balls, right?
Oh, that's so slow. Good thing. I touched it
No
Relax, it's fine
Why did I panic turbo? That was stupid
Okay
What are you talking about? I want where's the replay?
Don't think that has anything to do with the game. I want to see the replay. How did I get?
Are we there yet? Nobody tagged me. What are you getting this from? Okay. Why does this person have full power in everything?
They're not even in nicktoon
Painting the corners there. That's a strike
All is smashed to deep center, right?
It's two to one who is that person? Why do they have full power in everything?
What is going on with this? What is this? What is this?
full everything
That's so unfair
All right, fine. I'm not gonna let it get to me up and in we miss let's get back to the action
How come they have that that's the two or three people in a row?
Ha ha ha burritos
Take a spongebob
A spongebob is even spongebob has a ton of wait a minute
I think gaz is tired
Gaz is tired. All right, we're gonna switch it. Uh, yeah. No, wait a minute
Is that accurate? It's only this third inning
There's no time to pretend. No, look at the stars down there. Spongebob has like two extra stars
Why look at the stars?
It's because it's on all-star difficulty. Oh, is that what it is?
Painting the corners there. That's a strike. Well, I don't know. It's the first time I've played on all-star
This is like insane
Yeah
I would use the power up right now, but i'm not gonna I don't have faith
You're not gonna hit shit
That was a great pitch too
down
Perfect throw cutter
Look at how bad danny phantom's tv show is even on all-star mode
look at those stats on the edge people like
Danny phantom
I thought danny phantom. I thought people didn't like this show
How's that a ball?
Maybe you could use a little rest girl
Oh my god, how are these balls don't walk anybody?
Yes, what?
No, do you know where I put that?
Oh, come on. All right. I got it's two outs. Just get him. Just hit just get it out
It's a classic. It's as classic as spider-man dude. All right
What the fuck did you just do got a third?
Why what just happened?
How did you miss that? Oh now it goes the yak. Oh, this is horrible. This is not good
Someone can get that right
No
What the fuck? All right. I gotta lock in next next
What the hell? How do you hit that ball? It was the dirt
Please
It's all right the gates. We're in the third inning everybody sit down and relax patrick's coming up right now
I swung so late
Fuck he's throwing so fast
All right, patrick get us back in the game
single
My points my points, it's five to two. It's not like 40 to zero. He didn't get it. He didn't get it
slide
No, don't hit do a double play you motherfucker
Oh shit
No, all right, everything's fine
It's the fourth inning. I got a lot. It's a lot of baseball left to play. All right
Let's get back to the game over the first almost didn't get him get him out of first base
Yeah
I'm all right. That was just an emotion that just burst it out of me. Oh my god. It's all falling apart
Shut up you fucking little weirdo
Why did you throw it into the stands?
I have to get a strikeout right now or it's our admin in a lot of trouble
Shit i'm okay. I i'm may as well be playing sakiro right now. I need to fucking relax
Yeah, this is gonna she's gonna come out of the game she's too tired
She's too tired i gotta bring somebody in
God damn it. I'm just building his meter up. That's right. That's stupid air horn. That's stupid air horn
Fucking air horn strike out. All right, let's get back to business here
It's all right, let him waste his meter
It's all right
Ah foul ball stay alive. I didn't want to swing. I I wanted to check swing. I tried to check swing
I tried to check swing and it didn't work
I hate this. Oh my god. It's part of torspin's impossible to play against he's so good
All right, come on talk
You see how insane it is to determine if that's a ball is that a strike or not
Don't worry. I got this
Oh my god. Damn it
Playing against all star back with like difficulty just means they all get like extra stars
The game's not harder. They just have a fucking 100% more stats than I do
What happened? No, don't restart the game
I want to take I gotta take gas out
Yeah, we're switching gas for e drives
Oh my god, he sucks, but at least he's fresh
Now it's one and one that's low and away two and one all right, it's only the fifth inning i'm fine
I just got to get some contact hits
It's this fucking character. They have on this team. This guy's in
This guy's insane. Look at that hot zone
really
Swing and a miss strike one
Outside corner, this is where we get make him greedy. We throw a fastball up and in just out of the zone
He's gonna freak out. He's just playing that ball exploded. He hit it so hard. Okay. Well new plan
Two and two swing at it everybody's head and we'll drop in the outfield he's done
Yeah, okay this guy sucks
CPU crew it was the bullshit when I threw the ball into the outfield that was when I just went into a total meltdown
Gas turned around. I went to go pick the guy off and she just threw the ball into the sands
Like what was that all about?
It's stepping up player on second two away rent. I don't think rent swings the bat by the way
I don't think i've seen him swing the bat. I'm screaming. I have homework to do fuck. Okay. He doesn't have a lot of power though
I kind of uh, what do I should I?
It's ren. We're fine
Come on i'm just giving him free meter because they don't swing the goddamn bat
Okay, I need to get a couple people on base
I'm not swinging. You gotta pull it that goes across the whole zone
Take it it's in there. It's not fair. Stop with it
Stop I feel like i'm watching a donald trump meme video
That's right down the middle stay at first stay at first
All right patrick's coming up i'm gonna get a home run right here bang first pitch home run
I got it back in the game seven to four game ain't over. All right now take him out bench him
Game's not over. No, it's not not even close breaking ball. I'm not swinging till I get a strike
That was the okay fine. You want to play that just throw it. I don't care
action put into these ranking pitches
Dude burn all your meter. I don't care. You won't have it next inning. It has to throw a strike. Oh my god
It's in jeff is a mess jeff is a big fat mistake
I hate that to get that off. I don't want to hear that. I'm gonna keep thinking of those videos
Oh my god, it was right down the middle. I thought it was going out to the right side of the zone
Oh my god. All right, it's okay
Can't wait this little I can't pick another pitcher
Um, all right, your power is pretty shitty. I'm going curveball down and then he's gonna miss
Shit, of course
I got fucking powdered toast man throwing these like monster curveballs that when I do this, I can't hit it
Uh, that sucks
I gotta get I gotta get three guys on base and hit grand slam. That's an easy chum chum
That's an easy play
You should have picked a better pitcher than who omega lol. No, I should have picked the yak. What was I thinking?
What was I thinking? I should pick the yak
I just used my whole meter of what happened was my meters all gone
What happened wait that uses the whole meter what happened? I'm wait, why is the meter gone? I was saving that
Turbo uses the actual turbo, but I didn't know that
I thought that was how to get a dive
If you hit a home run
The computer has so much ridiculous stats on all star mode. It's just what the fuck it it is not even possible
It's not i'm not coming back from this bullshit is impossible
I'm not quitting. I'm not quitting
I picked a shit team. I'm doubling down after this i'm picking the the dream team
From the corner right here
Oh my god
All right, can I quit and just take the 500 million? What the fuck dude?
Why?
These I can't even
This is this is absolute blowout now
Yeah, and why do they hit a home run every fucking single at bat?
What the fuck are you talking about?
This one is over three on the day
Oh shit, that's fucking stupid. Oh even ren from ren and goddamn stimpy is gonna hit a home run
So is he gonna go around the whole thing?
Hey, there's still plenty of baseball left. Don't worry
Fuck this is a close game. It's 15 to 4
What happened why is everybody have to hit home run every at bat
Is it because this picture I brought this picture and he sucks. What happened?
Why I it's not over yet I could still come back and win this
Okay, that's how you get the fucking that's how you get the juices flowing again catch like that. Let's go
Here it comes
Don't swing take a strike
That shit goes 67 miles per hour
This bitch is just so slow. This bitch is just so slow. You can't it's impossible
I gotta I gotta pick powder toast man. If i'm gonna double down. I gotta pick powder toast man first
This guy goes from like 95 to 65
Still got thrown out. No, he didn't. Okay, i'm good
Finally, he's out of the game
I quit i'll take the loss. I lose that's 500 million. I'm literally just calling the team back
Call the team back slaughter rule games over probably nothing. This is for a billion. I'm going to the boppers
I gotta get powder toast man off. I'm going i'm going yak
Yak pitcher don't take powder toast man
First base man, we're gonna do i'm i'm getting part of toast man the fuck off
Of this goddamn list
Bunch box pitching. All right
Locked in my two favorite players. Toph was good. We're going tough
No
No, i've refused to pick. I don't want dandy phantom
Pick your third basement
dandy
Stop getting a wild card in there flying dutchman. Let's go
Stadium
I'm going for a total wild card here
This is for a billion added or a billion off and i'm not i'm done after this. This is the real one
Let's get this one started. Here's patrick star
The patrick is here strike one good start
Really good start now. We slow it down go out of the strike zone
That's a strike. Let's get back to the game. That's on the corner
There
Yak is unbelievable
Nobody can hit this
97 miles per hour
I gotta get a strike out. Let's do slider
I'm gonna do split fastball down where he likes it
And entice him to swing in this
He just got these pure this massive brain
What the hell is this? I thought that was olive oil for a second from pup eye. I was like, that's not nickelodeon
Is one and one
again
Can't hit the fast stuff. We're going to split it down out of the strike zone swinging a mess
Oh it injured can they get injured
All right, you can't you they're gonna get a hit sorry is it this two outs it's fine
There it is sandy cheeks, what a fucking what happened did I get him? Okay. Yeah, I got him
That was a beautiful play by sandy that's why you have sandy at third base every time
Out of toast may lead us off with a nice single
No, don't go for two. Don't be stupid
This guy has terrible stats
Don't throw no double play no double play. Thank god
Spongebob, it's kind of hard to get the rainbow trail. It's really important. It's kind of hard to see
Oh my god, it's hard to see his pitch
Take it
100 miles per hour way behind
97 it's in there
Earth's pitch is a strike. I was spongebob throwing faster than the yak
Get it in sorry turn double play i'm gonna go with sinking sinking balls down the middle of zone
It's coming up. All right, we're gonna do split finger. Yeah, turn this double play. This guy sucks
Not even a nicktoon get out of here
Not even a nicktoon
It's that one. There it is. There it is. Nice job tough
Danny phantom's fast go for two go for second base. Don't try to get a double play
Can we get a girl out of here? Like how do I just remove girl from the game?
All right. Now I can play around a little bit here
Going right down here with a split
No
That was so close
Okay
I gotta get a strike out
Not gonna let you fuck with me on that one, buddy
Split her out of the zone swinging this one. All right. All right, whatever
What the fuck hold on I wait, oh my god, that was so stupid
Who's the catcher? Oh my god, that sucks
What the fuck it's cartoon baseball. Yeah, nobody punched it. Nobody attacked me, buddy
Okay, I have to uh
I need to relax
I gotta relax
That was so stupid
That motherfucker is out for the inside corner strike three. Come on don't do it
Patrick
That's a strike
Oh, okay strike two up and in fastball. Perfect throw. Let's go bingo. Oh, all right. It's only one run. I'm fine
Stepping in for the first time today. I'll swing to get a strike. That's what we did in little league
Wait a minute
Did you see that?
If you throw in their hot zone you get turbo if they if they miss
Did you see that shit?
Don't risk it
All right, that's it just I want to advance the runner flying dutchman
This is it
That's right down the middle that's a home no, it's not stay back
Stepping in don't swing. Oh my god. Oh my goodness
You gotta be fucking kidding me I swung at the perfect time
Oh my god, it goes fucking 60 miles per hour
High game dutchman down. What are you doing?
Why would you run for third? I didn't tell you to do that. You didn't even slide you fucking ghost imbecile
What an idiot. I didn't tell him to do that and he didn't even slide. I was smashing a
I get turbo for that
It's all right is he even trying it's a one-to-one game on i'm playing in the hardest difficulty. What are you talking about?
All right, well no, uh, they have some way to turn down play
Okay, we're gonna go double play time
Ignoring the runner
That's a strike it's right in the zone, what are you talking about?
I cannot let them do that. No way
Fuck you
No, he's gonna get meter
Powder toast man, you suck. How come like spongebob will jump 40 feet in the air and catch that ball
They dive across the whole game
He just did a daria. Oh, whoops. Why does he not launch across the whole game?
Like the spongebob guy does
Um
I can't believe it. Why does it have to keep happening?
It's not fair
Okay after like the for their third inning they just start hitting every single ball
It ain't over yet. Don't let it get out of control. Let's get back to the action
Okay, here we go I need base runners
I'm not swinging until I get a strike
That's turbo times three
Let him walk me in four pitches. Oh my god. I knew what I was doing too. Why would you swing?
I was about to scream in the microphone
Come on fill up that meter. I need it. How's that a foul ball? I was just perfect
Give me something to hit
The visitors have their work look at that little rinky dink bullshit hit
That was terrible
Oh foul ball. Come on
I gotta string something together. I gotta get people on base
Four runs is okay. I can deal with four runs
Should be an easy play and right one two three inning one two three one two three one two three
I got it. I'm good
That's a strike give me a break
I gotta fill up that meter and i'll spring together five hits
All right, come on
I thought that was a home run. I was like no way
Here comes the pitch taken for a ball. You know, the computer is stupid
Nobody takes that if i'm playing against another person they're swinging. It was scary, but I got it
I got three meters right now
down by four runs
We just don't just let him throw it don't even swing
But i'm wasted I got almost four of these damn things don't swing
Second pitch taken for ball two do not swing till I get a strike
Don't do it
Don't swing under any circumstance
All right, I got somebody on base and I have four charges let's go
Oh my god, if you hit into a double play, I will scream. Thank god
All right, don't swing till I get a strike that's down the line. All right. All right. All right, dude. Here we go
I can get to what I can make it a one run game
flying dutchman
Or just the one run game five to four. I got this I can do this
I still got meter too
Yes, all right. We're back in this i'll swing till I get a strike. I need base runners again
That's okay
I'm about to take the lead
I gotta get it done, right?
I don't even know who the fuck you are, but you're hitting a home run
I win six. I just took the lead
Six four six five. Let's go
Yeah, sponge bobby
And powder toast man coming up his contacts the best in the whole game
Don't swing
That's gonna be a tricky play no matter who you are
whatever
That sounded way more powerful than it was all right, we made some good progress here
It is don't blow it matters one for two. It's the outside corner
Stay strong. I'm I am I think I got this I just have to play smart already in the hole strike three
Sorry
Stupid air horn
Zim is there in time and has a base hit get upset computer down. Let's get back. I want to throw the third
Look, he's halfway down the baseline. I want I want to throw a third base
What why can't I throw the third base?
Look at him. I can't throw the third base
Like where's my I can't throw the race
Oh god, thank goodness
Yes double play sit down
Oh shit
Are you perfect in a row I have to
That's good enough for me. All right, this is it. That's what i'm pitching out of a jam. That's what I like to say
It's not a ball
Strike him up right here. This is it same place up and in challenge him. That's a strike
I have i'm going for it. I have to I need to secure the strikeout. That was a strategic place to do that
He gets a base hit. It's high game
This hitter is old for two don't say that
66 mile per hour goddamn changeup
Let's get back to the action. All right, he's gonna throw two balls in a row. I think good
Oh they they wha hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, what is
Excuse me. Who's this random guy that has all
Everything is maxed
Who the fuck is this person?
What let's get back to the game. Whatever
Are you serious? All right, I just gotta I almost have a meter
Oh my god the arc on that curve
mvp right here
That's a comfortable lead
Okay, I can't lose. I got they they scored like 15 runs in one inning. I have to be very careful
Don't get confident
Don't just hold off
All right, just let him throw it out and throw it in the dirt. I don't care
What a waste of turbo
Must be all-star just take the next pitch
Whatever. That's all right
Holy shit, that's so slow
It's so slow
flying dutchman
Wow
Are you kidding me
That's huge if I take a couple of balls, I might get another home run
Give me a meter
Come on throw another ball out of the dirt
All right. All right. All right. All right
Oh, fuck you. That was out of the strike zone. Whatever
It's I don't get that call
Okay
I think I gotta pull out. Uh, I think I gotta pull them
Oh shit. He actually missed he actually missed
Get that ball
That's okay
We're going home if it's a ground ball
Keep that in mind
Ground ball we go home
Flying dutchman, what in the name of god did you just do that for?
It was in front of you it's right in front of you
Oh my god swing that get up
Okay, we're good everything's fine he's got to come out next inning he cannot pitch in the seventh inning
There it is. All right, strike him out
I think I gotta pull him
I gotta pull him. I think one more batter
No
Oh my god, this pitcher sucks
So much they're gonna hit every single ball. They're gonna hit every single ball
He's terrible. I don't get six stars in every single category
I don't how are you supposed to do a nine inning game at nicktoons mlb versus all-star team?
He doesn't come in with five stars in every category
Easy play dutchman. Come on. All right, that's it
I can do this
I can do this. All right, here we go. He look this pitch is better than sponge bob
The fuck is this fair?
You
Went right into the hot zone, of course he did I gotta get somebody on base powder tostman. It's gotta be you
Beat it out beat it out beat it out beat it out beat it out beat it out beat it out
They're gonna hit everything I shouldn't pull the even though the all the yak sucks
I don't think I should have pulled them
All right, that's good
You better catch that
They're gonna hit everything why it sucks
It's not out of reach I can still do it
It's only three run game. We're good. Everybody relax
this is like
They just have
like I it's
It's not possible to play a nine inning game in this game against all-star team
They're gonna hit fucking home runs every other at bat. I can't even pull this pitcher. You only get two
What I can't even pull this guy
God damn it
I was up to and I had to switch my pitchers because you have to
And and now they're just gonna get a fucking great contact with every single at bat
Here's how germa can still win
That's not even a ball i'm not he gets those calls that's unfair he gets those fucking calls
I need five runs. I need so much more power somebody just fucking strangle that little guy
Turn it. All right, that's how you do it. Let's go
And they have this guy how does this any fucking fair
Why does this guy have max sponge bob didn't even have max stats?
All right, here we go
All right. All right. All right. Everybody relax. We've got three men on base. I got one out
This guy has no
Okay. All right. This is it
No, not swing till I get a strike. I'm gonna get I'm gonna get power. I'm gonna fucking bring this back
Ha ha ha ha ha ha ha what just fucking happened?
The game is broken
This is a broken video game. This is a broken video game. That was a double fucking play
This is a video game. You're not supposed to win. It's impossible to win all star
What I don't understand what happened
She lagged for a second and instantly teleported to the ball
And then apparently tagged the guy out at third base
It hit the runner. No, she caught it. She caught the dumb
You suck dutchman
Is now two for the eighth double looks the runner back silly girl
That's not a ball and I know it just get the sure out don't do anything stupid
I could have gone I couldn't do that a two to six to one double play whatever it was
He's gonna activate his power too, isn't he?
I have to he has to hit the ball. Let him hit it
No, let him hit the ball hit it. Don't activate your power before i'm gonna do before he can fucking do anything
Don't let him activate the power just pitch right away
I didn't want to activate the power
It's over oh come on
All right, you brought in a different picture. Ah, the game's fucking impossible. You brought a new picture and game's not fucking completable
Oh our picture we brought in. Oh, no, no, no, don't worry our picture
We brought in has five out of five on yelp in fucking possible restaurant score and he's not even a cartoon character
Isn't that something wings for strike two, let's get back to the action
Bring it to five or five five or five picture. Whoa
Wowie
Do you get a five? No, you don't your guy has like three stars and everything. He's terrible at everything
Four is not even
Huge game tonight. This one is three for three obsessed ball one and one picked up by cats. Well
Beat that shit out dutchman
Don't fall for it, you know, don't swing you let you and look at this turbo let's fucking go
Come on
Let's go
Go ahead throw it. I don't care waste it
This is the bottom of the eighth inning. This is where magic happens everybody get the fuck back to their bases
That's so impossible
Okay, I can
All right, that's three runs
What score?
This ain't over. I'm not done four runs. Let's go get two get three people on base
Come on sandy
Okay, I got plenty of meter there's a whole nother ending
Silly girl drum on first base. Yes
This is more exciting than real baseball
Right to pot just walk it over there
All right, I can get four runs. I look at my meter. I got two and a half meter
All right, let's go let's do it
I gotta get three men on base
This is not even oh my god, the slider is unbelievably it's unbelievably horrible
The pictures are so good
It's like insane
You can't determine where the fuck that ball's going
Not a million years
Look at that shit
Fuck it's it's like playing fucking wiffle ball
Well, dude, that is not possible to know where that's going
Get on base. We've done crazier shit with fucking two outs before haven't we get them on base?
We wouldn't crazy. We done crazier shit with two outs before
We done crazy shit with two outs before let's go
All right, let's go
back to back
Do it again again one more it's a tie game
This is it
It's a tie ball game
Yeah kick that dirt and we got powder toast man coming up
Oh, oh here we go. Oh, i'm on fire. Come on. I have turbo take another ball
It's not over I got another at bat
It's not over it's not over
Fucking I can't he's so bad at pitching
You gotta be fucking kidding me
You gotta be fucking kidding me. Why what the fuck? He's so bad
Oh, come on. That's so stupid
You this game sucks
This game fucking sucks. It's awful. It's awful
It's awful
Give me a break you motherfucker
What happened? I'm not done. Let's go
Now that was such horseshit
They're just hitting every fucking ball
That's insane. It's insane that they can do this back-to-back home runs on fucking contact swings
I gotta get a double play right now
Do not let him on base
Oh my god
It's unraveling
Fucking unraveling. Oh this game sucks. This game sucks
What a piece of shit game i'm so mad
And the fucking cpu gets extra goddamn power
I was gonna win the game too, but this fucking cpu
bullshit
They all get maximum stats
Who made this game?
How dare you?
I can't even change this picture out and I can't throw a fucking strike even if I put it in the middle of the zone
And catch up with that was not where I put that fucking ball. This guy sucks absolute asshole
That's not even where I put that pitch
Fuck you game
That's such bullshit. I had it with powder toast man, but the guy
Oh, i'm gonna throw them all it's gonna start at the top of the fucking screen and it's gonna end up at the bottom of the screen
Isn't that fun?
And then I don't make that catcher. I can't make that catcher the computer will
Have I have I I don't you know what i'm gonna say, how's that not a strike for me, but it's a strike for him
This is a game is dog shit
I like that. Look look my picture is so tired. It's gonna spring together a million fucking hits. I can't even do anything
Who is the fucking moron?
That thought that you shouldn't be able to switch out more than one pitcher in the whole game
And listen to my voice going like this. How what how could you be so stupid?
Why can't why can you only switch one pitcher in nine innings?
Are you insane?
Like I can't even do anything
I I can't this guy this pitcher is apparently so tired. I can't do anything
And wait a minute
Didn't he change pitchers twice?
He did didn't he he changed pitches twice?
What?
Like I have to throw a strike eventually and he fucking hits it out of the park
Oh my god
Yeah, it was 15 15 that started the ending and they hit a fucking base hit
Every time they made contact with the fucking bad
I
Is this a child in right field
Is this a kid in right field? He's missed every single one of those
This has to be an eight-year-old in the fucking right field has to be this person's six years old over there
This was so intense. What a fucking storybook ending this would have been but I forgot the game's terrible
Ah
Where's my storybook ending?
30 runs there are 30 fucking runs. I can't stop it
It doesn't matter what I do. They're gonna hit the ball every time
Oh my god, can I finally fucking play?
What the fuck
Oh, that's such bullshit. Why do they hit every single fucking ball?
that's
Unbelievably stupid that throws a hundred fucking miles per hour
He throws a hundred
And then the next pitch is a fucking like a curve ball that goes 50 miles per hour and arcs across the whole screen
Why are then why are there non-cartoon characters in this game?
That went 60 miles per hour
Going from 100 to 60
I'm breaking this disc in half
Great catch danny phantom great catch danny
Wow, he just jumped in and grabbed that he really just tell him just jumped into the ball danny
Dude come on
Where was why?
I hate this game. I hate this game
I hate this game
It's so stupid
Just cheating dumb shitty ai
No, no laughter. Fuck the nicktoons. Fuck. Nickelodeon. Nobody watches that shitty channel anymore. Anyways, you know, they deleted
all the nickelodeon they did all the nickelodeon shows that you like they don't even exist anymore all that's on nickelodeon is like is
It's like irl fucking sitcom shows
There's like two shows on nickelodeon. Anyone cares about anymore nickelodeon sucks. The whole network sucks
Snap it
Oh my god, it was so close. I had it
I just didn't swing with powdered toast man because the guy throws fucking whiffle balls
Oh
I'm so mad
It's stupid
I am sweating right now sweat is just dripping off my entire body
No, not triple or nothing I had that in the bag too
Nicktoons baseball fucking no wonder this has like a four on rotten tomatoes, whatever it is. What does this have for a rating two?
one
Fuck no, I'm done. I'm out of here. Fuck this game. Fuck the network. Fuck this game
Fuck nickelodeon the network the entire network
Uh, anyways, that was a lot of fun. I had a good time
Oh, i'm so mad
I hit like back to back to back home runs to tie the game and then the fucking computer
Pick your starting pitcher
Pick your breathing game pick your second basement
Pick your third basement
Pick your shortstop
Go
All right
Free inning game. Yeah, they don't fucking show they show this show at but that like three in the morning
Three, there's a three inning game. I gotta I can't just go out on that one. I'm not going out on that one
I refuse to go out on that one
Is this triple or nothing?
Can I do triple or nothing? What's that mean? That's
Two billion added to the debt or two billion off the debt
Can I all right? Can I can I uh
Okay, how about this? How about for can I do it for one billion? I'm gonna lose
Yeah, this game's impossible
How about for what just one billion? Let me let me win back this shit that I just lost right there
Go back to one billion one billion off
Deal give me that deal. Give it to me one billion off. So I go back to go back to zero
Come on. Come on. Give it to me. Give it to me. Give me this. Give me this one. That's only three innings
Come on, give me the deal
Let's vote. Let's vote for it
I can't fucking believe I lost that game
Okay, what is that? What go back back to?
Zero what it would be one billion off, right? Oh one billion. Yeah one billion off. All right, here you go with a face cam
It'll be a deal with a face cam. Hold on. I got I am disgusting right now. I'm sweating
Okay, let me fucking nick toons baseball
Fuck nickelodeon
All right, I gotta relax
Is that webcam not working, uh, what's with my webcam there it is, okay
Holy shit. I look ridiculous. Oh this glitchy
Uh, I don't even care what I look like. Here we go. I just have to hit one home run and then I end this
Wait, did you guys even vote? What'd you guys vote for? Oh, it's a deal. All right, like a caveman
I feel like a caveman right now super desync. There you go. Catch that worse. No, it's not
Shave please don't tell me what to do
Um, he's really slow. Yeah, all right. I have to capitalize on this shit right now
Don't swing
That's a base hit
Two men on
I tried to check swing fuck this game
I don't get those calls
I got it
What the fuck just happened i'm freaking out slow down
Come on give me a grand slam
Can I catch it
This is a worse game on steam whatever platform is on
He's got meter though this sucks
Bitch is a low strike
It's fucking impossible this is impossible
You didn't even make contact with that ball, how did you even make contact you can talk about baseball a one two pitch
Take it for a ball high
Easy fly ball out to right stepping in for the first time today
Doodle kramer
Challenge him with his strike zone takes a pitch below the knees ball one muscle
It's just that you can't play this game on all-star mode and expect to get do anything
I don't think this is actually possible to win on all-star
down the right side
Stepping in for the first time today
Larry lobster
I don't even know what that ball was you're only supposed to play this with your friends
No one's actually supposed to do what i'm doing right now. No one
How is that too late I swung so fucking early
Hey, thanks for the thanks for the help
You reject humanity up i'm seething right now blood is fucking is it's more red than normal
Extra red my blood is ketchup red right now. It's as deep red as it could be
I thought I
I thought I could get a fucking pitch
That tried to challenge
But I forget i'm not playing against a friend the computer is gonna hit that fucking out of the park every time if it's in the blue
this is not like
Dave my buddy that's sitting next to me. Who's like, oh, I wonder why he's gonna throw it the cpu just goes blue hit
And it's a fucking home run
Humans strike one. Here's the second pitch
One in one count her ball at the knees for a strike
With you stepping in for the second time. Yeah
Matters one for one. It's the outside corner
Right one. It's that one on a line to the outfield. Yeah, here's a board with a lead-off single
Bottom of the third nobody out
Cooled by the breaking ball one
The bystander he looks like a different person
What and he gets that call strike two?
It's five to two
Hello, who is up there?
the pitch
It's there strike two here jammer all locked up for strike three
Let's hit the second
It's impossible
It's fucking an incompletable. It's
incompletable baseball
Get back on that fucking field
If I don't win this add
10 billion to the debt 10
If I win everything from tonight is erased
No
Hate this game. How do you miss that pitch? I took one fucking perfectly through it. It's impossible to fucking play this
But waste your meter you fucking idiot
What a dumb shithead
Ball hit this motherfucker in the stomach
And it doesn't bounce off of them it does that to me
You catch that
Easy play that's an easy play we're good
Oh, thank god that was not a home run. Thank god. That was not a home run
Let's go
One hit that's right girl
So hard good wasted
I don't care waste your fucking meter. I don't care
Shit I hit it. It was a bomb and I fucking missed it somehow
How I don't even understand how is that too late? It's just not too late
It's either way too late. Oh way too early way too late. Oh way too early
Doodle kramer
There's no need to get upset put the computer down and let's get shit breaking ball call. That's not a fucking ball
If I slayer the lobster and shortstop his arm is terrible
Throw it in this player don't scream at me
Here's the pitch
See you next week. Oh my god, I hate everything nickelodeon sucks
You know when nick jr is better than nickelodeon the network at the it's they've crossed
Nick jr is way more cool shows like paw patrol and shit. It's so much cooler than what's on nickelodeon now
This is broken. Did I break this? I thought I was good. I I I did it
I went back to where we were at the beginning of the stream
Is the debt over? No
No, what I did today right there was I said let's go back to like a billion off
So it would be where we were when I put the fucking disk in that was not quadruple of nothing
That was just put us back to where we were
Oh
That was I hated that
That was fun though. I was way too animated tonight. I was so animated. I should have been that animated
Did I say anything I should take back at the end of the stream? Let's see. What did I say?
Did I say did I say anything that was like absolutely reprehensible? I don't think so
What I say nickelodeon sucks
Every show sucks on nickelodeon. There's one show that's worth watching. That's true, though
I said halo 2 sucks. No, I didn't when did I do that? You said you wanted to strangle gurr
Well, uh, that was wild. I hope you had fun. I did even though I got a little a little angry apologize to danny
What did I say to danny? Oh phantom?
This game this game is pretty fun. Don't let my bullshit fool you
I loved it. You were so lively. I was too lively. I don't know what's going on with me
I was like going like
I was thinking so many more adam sandlin noises than I typically do
I was I had like a my my blood was hot tonight
I'll see you guys on uh next Saturday
And I know a lot of people were saying like hey chill. You don't want to hurt yourself
I mean I did when when the motherfucker got tackled. I I I did I did
but
I don't know that
Going back to like six plus seven eight hour streams sometimes now
But i'm only live once a week
So i'll be okay
If I feel like kind of sore tomorrow, whatever i'll be all right with two days. Whatever
I'm able to do it. I'm able to get it done
so
Don't worry about me. I'm gonna be fine
I'm more hot and sweaty than anything else
I have a great rest of your weekend. Hope everybody has a good week
A burp has just been sitting in here
Yeah, i'll see you guys next week on saturday same time around noon pacific. Thanks for the subs a lot
There were a lot of subs tonight
Do a lot of community subs
Take care of yourselves. I'll see you real soon. Have a great week
See you later guys