Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with Scare Saturdays.
This Scare Saturday is going to be a little different than you're used to.
I'm actually going to be doing two games tonight.
And the reason for this is the first one that I do starts off really creepy and kind of scary,
and then just gets kind of gets comical. It gets like funny.
So instead of having just one short video where it's like four or five minutes long,
I'm going to do a second video as well. So this is like a double video.
It's two games in one. The first one is Lumber Island, and the second one is The Room.
Respective links will be in the description.
Let me know what you think about these two games.
The second one is pretty scary. It's a very, very, very, very bare bones independent project.
But we'll see how you guys enjoy them.
I'll see you guys all next time. And of course, take care, everybody. See you there.
Apparently I'm looking at a rock. Oh, well, whatever. That was weird.
Created by Dean Forge. I don't like how I can't see anything. Can I sprint? Not really.
Chapter one, the letter. I feel like I'm playing Slender right now.
What's up, bird? Oh, a campfire. I'm going to go toast some marshmallows.
A little teddy. OK, should I pick it up? What can I do here? Oh, I got it. OK.
What the hell? That's pretty eerie. It's just like a teddy rockspin.
Can I do anything else? I don't think I can even do anything else.
All right. Well, I got my teddy bear. What do I do now? What's that say?
Welcome to the Lumber Island, a place you will never forget.
And the brawny paper towel man is like here to welcome you.
Remember, use brawny when you got those big messes to clean up.
They came again. Now with the threats. I don't know how much longer I hold up, but I'll never sell my land.
OK, go back to close. Oh, right. That's the camera.
What? What? What? What? What? What? Yeah. Yes. What's with the music?
What is with this music? Oh, my God. I don't think he has a head.
Oh, my God. He doesn't have a head. What do I do? What do I do?
What do I do? Just run away from this dude.
The headless brawny paper towel man. Don't get stuck on a rock. Go.
What do I do? Is this going to be something like can I get like a gun?
Can I shoot this guy? Oh, it's like Michael Myers.
Oh, I put the I put the teddy bear down. What's why? What's with the mist?
Get away from me, bro. I'm going to I'm going to try and find his boots
because he's pissed off. That's why he's going. He's kind of slow.
He's not the fastest. He's not the fastest man, but he is big and he's got an axe.
Let's get a good look at this guy. He's really slow.
I kind of feel bad for this guy right now. Like he wants to catch me,
but he just he just ain't going to catch me. He's just not going to catch me.
What if I can I get back in the boat? Will he come like into the boat?
I don't think he realizes he can like come over here. Let's see.
Let's see what happens. Does he does he come in the boat?
Ladies and gentlemen, the slug monster. Don't kill me.
Sir, excuse me. So new game. Let's go.
I like the rain. The rain can clear everything.
Wash the dirty things from me. Dirty things like sand, mud, blood or sin.
This is like a bad teleprompter. Can I make this like go faster?
What I do. What can you see in this picture? A sad face, praying or a rose?
Um, I think I see if I'm not going to lie. I see a face. That's a sad face.
I see. And what do what do you think about this one?
What is this like a psychology test? A crown, castle or horns?
I kind of looks like I'm going to say castle. I would say castle.
Great stronghold. That's surprising.
Once again, it's a fairies screaming or a puppy.
I see a puppy. That looks like a cute little note there.
You can. Okay. So what the hell? What was that all about?
Simple metal table with some stuff on it. My bed. I'm not tired yet.
This is the guy's house. This is like a wicked screwed up house.
If you ask me. Get out of the way.
I have a giant poster of internal organs. What's that?
What's that? Oh, it's my daughter. Hello, daughter.
What the hell do I do? Can I like leave this room?
It is called the room probably for a reason. I don't like the FOV, man.
Closed. All right. I get it. It's closed.
Really? What? I really like the rain. Please. Someone can hear me.
It was just using, you know, that sound that was like the AOL instant messenger.
Somebody just signed off noise to move these boxes.
Simple wooden crates. I don't know why. What did that say? Why they're here.
A vent. You can always go in the vent. I know this from experience.
Move out of the way. I feel like I'm looking through. Yeah, the rain did stop.
Why? Did the rain stop? I don't like this.
I don't know what to do. This is not cool.
Picture of a little girl. I don't remember who it is. Who is she? I don't know.
This is your house. I can't move. Wait, one of the pictures looks different.
My memory isn't good. What? Hi. Over the window? What? What do you mean over the window?
Over the window? What does that mean? What's that mean? What's that mean? What's that mean?
I feel like the whole world's closing in. Can I jump? Shut up.
Can I go in the vent? Wind coming from here. If I can open it, maybe I can escape.
I can't even tell what's happening, let alone like there's like a crowbar I can grab.
Anyone's out there, please. No answer. Fucking bulletproof glass. No one can hear me.
So am I going like crazy inside my own head or something?
Crow. I'll go to sleep. Oh, I'm supposed to go to sleep. Go to sleep.
It's late. Bad day. Really need to... Okay, so I went to sleep, I think.
Geez. What? I'm like a murderer? Is this like my prison cell?
Who are you? Where are you? Answer me, you son of a bitch.
You want to play? Show yourself. It's written in blood. Are you kidding me? Yeah.
Stop with this. Stop. With. Your. Bullshit.
I wish I could... Huh? Yes? What is in there? What is in here?
It looks like a corpse? What the hell happened? Who made this? Where am I? I must escape.
A corp... Ah! Gina! Gina! Hi! Gina! Hi! Lady!
Lady? It's like my friend... My friend got smashed and she got hurt.
Go to bed. Go back to bed. Go back to bed. Go back to bed. It's just a dream.
This is a stupid dream. Small coin. I can take it.
Did I pick it up? Did I just pick up the coin? Shut up, baby!
I don't have time for you. Can I like... Can I now... Can I open this?
Maybe this will work. Okay, I think I opened it.
Oh! Yes! I can't go any further. Here lies a rat. Disgusting. But eat them?
Do I want to eat the rat? I don't think I want to eat a rat. No, I'm not eating a rat.
I have to eat this rat to go further? Okay, eat the rat.
Go! Go! Go! Go! What the hell? I can't do anything there?
Please tell me I can leave now. Whoa! That's puke. That's my vomit.
It's still closed. Can I go to bed now, please?
I'm not tired yet. Can I open these things with the coin, too?
No, it's locked. No, it's locked. What does this like throw up do for me?
What's this? Small bobby pin. I can open the locker. I can open the locker.
Guarantee it. What? What? Can I open the door with this?
I can leave this cursed room. Finally, I'm out. I can leave this strange place.
But what the? No one's here. Hello? Someone can hear me?
So there you have it, guys. That's a dual Scare Saturday today because the games are pretty short.
So we'll see how that works out. If you guys want to see more, please let me know.
Links will be in the description for both of these games.
And I'll see you guys all next time. And of course, take care, everybody.