Hey, what's going on everybody? Jerma here lost another bet. Yeah, Jerma loses bets every single one he makes.
I bet MLC Stealth that corn grows from trees, like it hangs from trees like an orange, and I have to play this game because I lost it.
So what happened was, uh, corns don't grow from trees. In fact, my phone's ringing right now. Hold on, it's my dad. Let me answer it.
Alright, so, take it easy everybody, we'll see you in there.
Hello? Hello?
Just a regular little gerbil. I'm so cute, I look like I have a bit of cute nose and I'm sniff-sniff-sniff. What's that?
You didn't think I was fucking Yoda? You didn't think I had a lightsaber like in Star Wars movies? Are you fucking crazy?
Oh shit. Look out! It's the George Foreman grills. We gotta take them out. That's a part of this movie.
The George Foreman grills got brains and they came after the hamster clans.
Go mooch!
There's humans walking around in this game. Can I can I shoot this guy?
What is this? Let me shoot this guy like right in the face. He's shooting. What is this laser beam?
He's shooting at me. Please tell me I can like kill this guy
Come on, I'm gonna climb up on you. Oh
shit
this is
No, this is so stupid. So, okay, I guess I can't hurt these guys. Oh
Shit spider vacuum. Oh, no a spider vacuum. I will kill you
Hey, hey
Put me down. What the hell is this?
Where's he taking me? I just don't want to play this game anymore
I just don't want I don't want to do this anymore boo
There has to be some way you can get me out of this bed, please in the rule book or something
Let me see here, please
Yes, according to section 54t paragraph 3 of the agricultural video games handbook
Right when one party accepts any type of corn agreement pertaining to and not exceeding corn corn syrup
Corn on the cob. Yeah corn flakes. Yes or corn meal. Yeah, neither party shall dismiss any form of the required conclusion
Less brought before the Cincinnati maze. No, no, no, no, no rip it up. Rip that fucking book up rip that book up
I'm gonna make the rules. Yeah, you do make the rules
What's coming down here? Oh
It's a razor. Oh you went through the you went through it
Go away, I don't want to deal with you
Why
Darling and make sure you jump on the controls and pull it down
Good work, darling
Watch he's gonna ready. He's gonna start talking in a second here. I'm all this dumb shit
I've been saying the last a couple minutes. You'll hear it any second now watch ready when I jump on this
There here he comes. He's gonna start talking
What the hell is that?
The giant coffee maker. Oh you want to fuck with the ice coffee machine?
How do I wait? I need to scan it find out its weaknesses vulnerable to most weapons
This lumbering behemoth forms its own shield for protection, but will redirect the shield
Energy into a power attack. All right, so just attack them. I can destroy this thing, right? Yeah, I can
Don't know if that's doing much
Yeah, it's gone. You oh
Boy, I'm almost dead
Almost dead do not
Oh, it almost killed me
Drop your shield. Yeah
Die
You're dead. No, you're not. No, you're not. I am just being missed right here guys
This is the most intense battle of the game so far
Gerbil versus coffee machine. You can't write this shit. You can't make a movie. Oh, this isn't moving forgot
No
No, come on god you fuck
He's you gotta be kidding me that no, no, no
Dial and I'm hacking into the database. Here he comes. Here he comes. Listen from the storage area any ideas. Yes
Sorry drugs use moves for a quick recall and locate the exit
Your replies
Do-do-do-do-do-do
Whoops
Yeah, I'm gonna take an early lunch
Yeah, the conveyabouts are gonna go backwards and we have a gerbil ain't gonna just jump on the keyboard and press the button to make
And we're not gonna lose two hundred million dollars an hour. Okay. Come on. I'll see you guys tomorrow
Bill
You're fired. I really don't want to be the person to tell you this but Bill you are fired dude
You look what you've done. Don't even show up tomorrow
all right let's make it count huh let's do it don't run out of juice perfect
now I'm gonna get the core core received what the power core is gone
because I fell where the fuck is the power core what because I fell off the
edge because I thought it was like a cutscene I didn't think I could actually
die and now I broke the game so that I did the use there was a core here that I
took it and I fell off and I I can't do anything now is it can I hover like
right here maybe it like fell down can I grab it from like this crack no I can't
and that's it I'm done that's gonna be the end all right we'll see you later
this has been gerbil quest and I'm gonna give this game for burger boy snot
booger pukes out of seven potential burger boy snot booger bugle boy pukes
out of eight