Oh, you're hurting the the defenseless heavy. You're hitting the defenseless like toupee heavy.
He's trying to holiday punch people, see? What'd you do? I didn't do anything!
This guy is just... you're missing... he's missing over and over again. Dude,
maybe you should get a little closer instead of just like shooting long-range rockets at me.
What the fuck are you doing? What? Dude, I can't believe... what just happened?
That was out... okay. Are people just blind right now? What is going on? That guy was a spy.
Oh my god, I've never seen such a well-decorated last point. Yeah, I'm looking at this right now.
I'm looking at it on Spectator, it's hilarious. Oh, that sick like surround sound setup you guys got
there. It's like Dolby 5.1 up there. It really is. I'm gonna do a coffee commentary of Doom. Oh,
you want to do a coffee commentary of Justice and Doom? Yes. Headshot. I want to show you how we
headshot, we headshot, and this is how we headshot. We should've been the face and we should've been
the bum. That is how we do it. One and a two and a three and a four and one and a two and a three
and a four. Three headshots in a row. What do you know about that?
Headshot. Headshot. Headshot. Headshot. Headshot. Headshot. Headshot. Headshot. Headshot. Headshot.
Hey, Star, where are you? You wanted to make save? Are you serious?
You freaked out and you like swept around. You weren't even there. You weren't even...
You're a ghost. Now I got balanced onto your stupid team.
Yo, you're real, okay. Lots of people down there, holy crap. I keep getting extinguished.
I was so scared. I'm so scared. Is there a health pack? No, it's a defensor!
This is the worst thing, dude. I'm stuck up here. How? Oh, okay. I don't know what to do.
How dumb did I look when I just ran, sprinted and clenched at your feet on fire. It was awesome.
Oh my god, this... Look, I had no idea I was there. If I can get this to level three,
you gotta be kidding me, dude. I'm building a nest up here. This is a very dangerous thing I'm doing.
This is very dangerous. This is too dangerous. I'm getting the hell out of here. Get me the hell
out of here. Get me the hell out of here. No, damn it, you fucking little mini sentry.
Fuck yeah. There's only one medic and a pyro. He didn't get... How did he not get hit by that crit?
You're dead. Did you have a sandwich? Did you just fall off the edge?
I did have a sandwich. And I just fell off the edge. I fell off after you.
I was so intrigued by if you fell off or not that I jumped off the edge too.
Who's the only one that made it out of that alive? Wow. I see. I have to check and see if you die.
I die. I can't see his body. You were on fire and you shot a cheeseburger body and fell down the
hole. Yeah, it just flopped off the edge while I was eating my sandwich. All right. Can I be on
your team? That was a double headshot. Hey, Heavy, when you come around this corner, I'm gonna... What
the hell is going on? You wanna get turned into a fried egg? You wanna get turned into a fried egg?
Oh, I have my buff banner on crap. All right. Thank you, medic. Who wants to get turned into
a friggin' fried egg? This guy right here does. Fried egg. You want a fried egg? Oh, that guy
didn't want a fried egg. Hey, you want some hash? Where are you? I can't hit this guy. Thank you.
Somebody killed him. Watch out. That's a spy. No, it's not. Just an engineer with a shotgun.
Watch out for that spy. Nope. Come on, come on, come on, come on. Cap, cap, cap, cap, cap, cap, cap.
Go festival, M. Quit drinking. We need to talk about that. It calms my nerves. We're gonna have
to talk about you drinking on the job every day. I've got a crown. I can do whatever I want.
Well, you could follow me. You're like, I feel like you're gonna backstab me. Egg. Oh, here we go.
Nice crits. Nice crits. Yay. Well, it looked like you weren't on my team. It looked like for a second
you weren't on my team. There is like two quick fix mechs on this team. On their team or ours?
I'm just like baiting people in here to like get killed by this entry.
No, you want to have a melee fight? Let's go. Come on, come get me. Yeah, come get me. Ow.
Oh my god, I've gotten this guy like five or six kills on this century. God. No. No. Where's the
engineer? Is he dead? Damn it. Well, that's not good. Run away. Spy is still alive, by the way.
Give me the health. Give me the health. Where is it? Where is it? Where is it? Where is it?
Bad move. Bad move. Turn around. Run away. I knew it. What the fuck?