So we're gonna we're gonna do righteous air vote for righteous air
We make sure we get the right amount of votes
Okay, let me get the guy with 3d glasses down in the lower right. Yeah, what no no red and green
That's not even like 3d glasses. Oh, yeah. This guy's just a tool
Like this paint job
Oh god
Why is it that much real estate on the screen i'm gonna land on you
I love we're both doing stupid spins. Oh, wow. This is shit
This is on the moon apparently we were in the air for so long gravity wasn't even a thing far behind you guys
Hold on. I want to see like where you are. Apparently an expert
I can't even I can't see there's a giant like no smoking sign in my face when I do that
Star fuck you
Go through like the teleporter
I don't have it. I thought you said I thought you said to do that
I thought I don't have to press space what I did meter. Oh, you see your meter on the side idiot
Learn to play carnage racing
I just I picked something up. I hit f and i'm in the first all this like
I want a missile
No, i'm fine. That didn't do anything that did not do anything to me
My screen that I nailed you and I didn't even want to
How do you just win
You won
I I
What the fuck just happened to me
Wait
I don't know you cheated. I was in front of you and you just like lagged. All right. I'm voting for and back again
Way to go sugar. I wish I wish I had like a face cam on right now. My hands are like i'm
So i'm getting really confused right now. Your name is purple. My car is purple and it's freaking me out
I feel like I should be over there. I feel like that's like my name floating above you
Maybe it is
What do you mean maybe oh, this is a time travel game I just I just hit you with something germa and it did nothing
I'm gonna land on top of star
Nope missed
Well, yeah, you have like the unlockable car
It's not unlockable. What are you talking about? Right? You like you do like download that for like 4.99
I don't even
Mail is just like in the back. I landed on the side and it just I just started sliding into the water. Oh
Baby, oh baby, baby. He's got blast oist
You just got totally blast oist
All right. So how do I go through the the super time travel thing space?
Okay. Oh, oh
No, it does nothing though. Don't worry
It does it does you have to go into one of the rocks
So this whole game's mechanic is based on
Teleporting in front of each other
Yeah, basically what the fuck is that?
Oh, yeah, let's make a game. Let's make a racing game where you just like teleport in front of each other
The track doesn't even matter. Look
Oh second place i'll be like fly in front of everybody
How did you get up there? I feel like I feel like you're angry
Oh, that's fine. That's fine. Like you think you're gonna win is what this is right now
I I think i'm going to fucking teleport in front of you right now
Because like here I am. Hi
Hi star
I'm in front of me. I'm literally like right in front of means
I'm gaining on you
What the?
That doesn't I
What is this device on my back? What is?
Hey star
Hi, I teleported behind you
Great. I'm driving
No, see ya. No
teleportation technique unleashed
No, what the hell just what happened?
Uh, i'm about to win. I have a very serious question incredibly serious question this needs to be addressed
Why?
Is this game named carnage racing and not like time travel racing? Why?
What the fuck is the point? Why is this called carnage racing? It's not like carnage. It's time travel getting it done sugar
No, the game would correct itself
You just came
from
I
Wow, you're just taking all my things. You're absolutely correct. Cool. This whole game is just a series of
Quote what the fuck just happened. That's this whole game. Like for instance, right like what the fuck just happened
Yeah, yeah, come come on hit me just
Come on
Oh, I can't wait to i'm just gonna be in by right behind star. Oh, hey, hi star. Hi
Hi
What just happened i don't know but i'm in first fuck you
You know what? I have an idea you guys go ahead and play
Go ahead play the game
You guys go play
and
Let me know when you're getting to the end of almost the entire race. Okay?
When you guys are looking at the finish line, I want you to tell me that okay
Okay, i'm gonna go get a drink. I'll be right back. Oh look
I'm having so much fun playing this video game with my friends
I haven't even moved one time. I looked almost done. This is a fun racing game to play
Especially with your friends. You should go through
Oh, hi
two
Oh, hi guys. Nice to see you
I'm gonna win the race
Now slow down slow down
I need to see if this works
What is this game
That's so dumb i'm done over game over we're done
I don't want to play this anymore
There's no reason to play this
There's no reason to play this if you guys can just if people can just do that
What's the point of ever playing this game ever?