Alright, what are we doing? Uh, Turmoil. I wanna try Turmoil.
Peglin. Yep, Peglin's on the list.
Listen, uh, Turmoil looks really cool. I'm really interested.
This is a game where you get oil or something.
Do a WoW stream and it's out.
Okay. So, start new campaign, right? Let me do the setting.
Graphics. Good. Very good. 60 FPS.
Uh, yep, yep, yep. Okay. Audio is fine.
Everything seems good to go. Okay, let's start.
Okay. So, select, choose your character. I'm gonna play as Joshua.
Howdy, partner. This dude has been herding cattle
long enough to know that nights on the prairie are cold and lonely.
Hope earning money with oil is as easy as throwing lasso.
Yes. Hi there, future oil baron. Welcome to my soon-to-be-lovely town.
The oil industry will be booming here. Let's get to work.
Click on the wagon and I'll show you the basics of oil drilling.
Hop on and I'll take you to the oil site.
Welcome to your first oil mining operation.
Just follow my instructions and the oil will be flowing in no time.
Before you can start drilling for oil, you have to know where to drill.
Hire a dowser to take care of this.
You found oil. It's time to start drilling. Select the oil rig.
Oil can be always be found somewhere below a dowser.
So, place the rig right here. Literally hit me in the head with a wrench.
Drag downwards from this point and release at the other point to connect the oil.
Drag downwards from this point and release at the other point.
How far down should I go? Oh, okay.
I know I'm going to love this game. I'm going to be obsessed.
You struck oil, but where should you take it?
The left ink, of course. Select the horse wagon.
Put a wagon here. I'll make like oil and unload it in my company. Cha-ching.
They wouldn't have said that back in like the fucking 1100s.
This introduction ends when you brought the cash amount back up to 1350.
Okay, got it. Back to town.
Good job. Now it's time for the real work.
Come to town hall and meet your rivals and get yourself a parcel of land for your next venture.
Oh no, don't make me do it.
Don't make me do the thing that won worst impression of the year last year.
No, I don't want to do it. I will.
Hello there. Does being a lawyer sound interesting?
Well, in truth, it's kind of boring and I couldn't handle it.
I've got a serious case of oil fever and the only cure is finding oil.
That's what literally lost.
That was the worst thing I ever did last year, apparently.
20 grand for what? It still is.
I know. I'm just reminding you.
You can't vote for that twice, though.
That's important to know.
Why can I barely hear this?
Oh my God. I just came to a really crazy realization about the way my brain works.
The reason why that's the way that I do the Daniel Day Lewis,
I drink your milkshake routine is because I'm skipping through the fucking video.
That's why I'm doing that.
What the fuck?
Yeah, don't come snivel.
This is insane.
It's from me skipping through the movie because I like want to maybe get to a scene
or maybe I'm skipping through a certain scene.
It's really weird to think about that.
Anyways, let's play this game.
It's like this.
Yeah, I've seen this. This is one of my favorite videos.
It's not possible for me to not laugh at this video.
I'll try.
I'm going to try as hard as I can to not laugh at this video.
It's cheating, though, because it's impossible.
I genuinely think this is impossible.
Let's see if I can do it.
What do I get if I make it?
What do I get? What do I get if I make it?
It's this fucking stupid like soy pointing meme.
God damn it.
He does the like the point thing.
God fucking damn it.
Really?
Unbelievable.
Un-fucking-believable.
I can't believe it, man.
Whatever.
Okay, I'm going to try from here.
I just spit all over this microphone right here.
Once Macho Man's shows up, it's over because I know he will.
Macho Man's is the best without a doubt.
I think I'm good.
I'm good.
Help them.
The same guy?
Banjo-Kazooie character.
Like a bellows with eyes on it.
You know what I mean?
Logan Paul?
What?
It does.
No, it does.
Does it?
Him in the back with like the thing.
Older Logan Paul.
Wow.
That's insane.
All right, I'm going to play the one that...
I'm going to move on in a second, I promise.
Let me get this one real quick.
This one's short, I promise.
Where is he?
There it is.
Why is there Superman in this?
Oh, for a second, I thought Superman was going to be like...
I thought they were going to do it with the Superman movie.
I was like, what?
I was like, no, they're not.
Ready?
What the fuck is this video?
Yeah.
Okay, I've had enough.
I can't do it anymore.
I wonder if somebody did that with my stream.
What would that sound like?
Would it be as fucked up?
It would be worse.
I'm trying to think of how I talk.
Like, hey, what's going on?
I'm delighted to make your acquaintance.
I made a nice living in real estate,
but it's time for a new business plan.
I do it.
Now I'm going to think about that a lot.
Okay, we have to play a game.
Okay, so let's get to work.
Buenos Dias, I've sailed the world as a ship captain for years
and I can't even swim.
I don't want to worry about drowning anymore unless it's in money.
Let me assign you to your own piece of land.
The first one is on the house.
Oh, is this a risk?
Good day to celebrate the opening of my brand new bank.
I've opened an account for each of you.
If you need to borrow extra cash
or come by to view a financial report of your last venture.
Okay, so this is me, right?
Let's get that oil.
We're taking $2,000 with us to cover the start costs.
Are you ready to go?
All right, let's do it.
I need dowsers.
Got something?
Let's go.
How far down should I go?
Should I go?
Wait, what did I do?
Did I screw this up?
What just happened?
How do I have no money?
I have 20 grand.
When did I spend $914?
I have to...
Okay, wait.
I found a way to increase the capacity of pipes.
Highly recommended.
Okay, so I have to find that shit.
All right, no, get out of here.
I'm not gonna spend seven grand right now.
I have a piece of land at the town hall.
Oh yes, I was expecting you.
What can I do for you?
Land auction.
Let's gather all the tenants together to auction.
Okay, let's go.
In turns, you decide which plot of land you get to mine next year.
On your turn, click on a parcel to bid on it.
You can outbid others by clicking on their parcels.
The numbers on the plots that have been mined,
they indicate how much oil was in that plot.
Okay, so there's probably oil here and here.
I'm gonna say here.
I'm going here.
That's it, right?
Okay.
Yeah, all you got no money left.
I got 17k left.
I'm gonna buy the width.
I feel like everybody else did that too.
All right, I understand how it works now, I think.
So to upgrade pipes capacity, just click on it.
Price is always right at right inc.
I mean, it is more, it is better.
I don't know, buy one cent though.
I don't really care.
All right, so where would it be?
Where should I dig?
Left and right Twix.
You got some?
Why would you make me do that for money?
Fuck!
Stop!
What do I do?
How do I stop?
Stop!
How do I stop the thing from going?
Did I not hit oil?
Oh, thank God I did.
All right, deliver.
85 cents go that way.
How do I do this?
How do I deliver?
How do I deliver to that way?
How do I, where?
Click the arrow, up arrow?
90 cents over there, let's go.
92 cents of gallon or whatever the hell it is.
What do I do about this?
What the fuck is happening, dude?
I just spent all that money on like a second drill.
I don't, I don't, I didn't mean to do that.
Should I do it over here?
Stop going that way.
Stop this way.
What does this swimming pool do?
Okay, how can I go down?
Branch limit reach.
Can I delete this?
Does that mean it's going to explode or something?
Stop the quad.
Stop, stop, stop.
I'm ready to go this way.
I got 2,500.
Oil is limited.
Yeah, well, there's probably plenty over here.
There's probably a shitload over here.
This is filling up.
That's for a year, right?
I got plenty of time.
Yeah, yeah, the one.
Yes, dude.
What are you talking about?
What the fuck just happened?
You're spilling oil.
Fix it by buying new wagons
or by reducing the number of wagons selling oil.
What do you mean reduce the number of wagons
when I want more wagons?
It's flown into here too.
I have three things that just don't work.
What does this do then?
I thought this was going to take the overflow.
Oh, they take from the overflow.
I thought this was going to spill into here.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
Fill it up, fill it up.
Take all the oil.
Take it all.
The buck 12 right now.
Get rid of all of it.
No, don't store it.
Why are you storing it?
Go sell it that way.
Sell the oil.
Why you don't?
No, pick up the oil and sell it over here.
I got 6K.
I'm all right.
2,500 in profit.
Paid more than this fucking moron.
What the hell did she do?
Okay, nice to meet you.
I'm Edward and I'm a bit of a handyman.
I like to experiment with stuff
that can help you find oil.
Make sure to check out my inventions.
Okay.
I improved the dowsing rod so dowsers can search deeper.
Tired of dowsers taking forever?
Would you like to have this lovely mole?
He'll dig for you, but he's kind of erratic.
Yeah, of course I want the mole.
I'm broke now.
I have no money.
I'm in trouble.
Going up here.
That's what I just bid on.
How much is this for?
3,000?
Oh my God.
He has a dumb.
Okay, I got five grand.
You have cash to pay back William
before your current loan becomes final.
You want me to go pay the guy back $5,000
that just gave me $5,000
and be left with $142 left.
How would I do that?
Okay.
I have a mole now.
Mole.
Look, somewhere in the ground,
the mole will uncover this spot
and then dig around to uncover five more random spots.
Okay, right here.
Let's see if this is worth it.
Worth it?
Oh, hi.
Yeah.
Yes, sure.
Okay.
Very important that I get this right.
I'm going to say right here.
Right here.
Perfect.
Let's increase the fucking width on this thing, please.
Extend, extend it.
How?
I don't know how to do that.
Open it.
What do I do?
The mole got eaten by an alligator or something.
He's not doing anything anymore.
What happened?
Why is the mole gone?
Is the mole dead?
Hold the end of it.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
Uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh, uh-oh.
I have no money.
Oh, I get it.
Okay.
Come on, dig something.
Shit.
Have one horse never sell.
Why?
So it just stores it.
Really?
Oh, I see what you mean.
So it just goes like boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom, boom.
Where is the oil in this map?
How much did I pay for this?
Finally.
All right.
We got double oil now.
Uh-oh, this is almost gone.
What happens if this bullet fills up?
Does this overflow?
It probably doesn't, right?
Why do you do that many horses?
Because they're not going to be...
I need to sell this oil.
And they are not doing it fast enough.
Okay, this is done, right?
So now what?
Just close this out?
Or is that it?
Should I douse?
All right, we got to get...
I got to get more horses.
I'm not going to be able to sell all of this.
I need to go deeper, deeper, deeper.
Shit.
Okay, that's right here.
Yeah, I found it before you did.
Why even use that person?
Can you fire horses?
Can I get rid of people?
All right.
Now we're going to get started loading oil up like crazy.
I need more.
I want more.
All right.
We need somebody to store some oil.
Let's store it.
And then...
Oh, shit.
I can do double.
This guy not found oil yet?
This guy's been walking around for 10 minutes straight.
Oh, final month.
Okay.
Sell all.
How?
Can I sell the horses?
Okay, I'm going to pay the loan off.
Immediately.
It's too late to change to the left side.
Oh, right side I'm in.
Sell, sell, sell, sell, sell, sell it.
Bullshit.
This is a lot of oil here.
It was literally two, three patches.
What?
Did I pay it off?
15,000 in earnings.
I spent five grand.
Banked at six.
I didn't pay the bank yet.
Oh, I'm Rainer, the trainer.
I take care of the horses to keep them healthy and ready for work.
Drop by my stables.
Maybe we can help each other.
Did I?
Wait.
I paid it back already?
Why would it cover my debt right away?
What if I didn't want to do that right away?
You track up how many horses you have with this handy horse counter.
Is it worth $5,000 to know that I have six horses?
Okay, here we go.
Depth.
Dowsers can search deeper.
They find oil faster.
Size.
Oh, I like that.
I don't have enough money though.
I don't have enough.
Okay, let's go.
I'm going up.
Up top here.
I think people are sleeping on this one.
All right.
Now I'm ready.
I'm ready to rock and roll.
Let's get some profit here.
No more loans.
No more bullshit.
Go find me some oil so I can get started right away in January.
And get the silo down too.
Immediately.
Right in the middle.
Go.
I'm ready.
You know what?
Put a mole down here.
Make it snappy.
Oh, mole found oil.
Look at that.
I'm putting one here.
I got to strike something here.
Thank God.
All right.
Put it down a little bit more.
I'm ready to rock and roll.
I keep saying that.
I said that like five times.
I'm going to get the guaranteed one here.
Oh, shit.
Come on.
Give me 150.
150, 150, 150, 150.
Dude.
Come on.
Just suck it up already.
Nobody.
Just deposit it for now.
Suck it up.
All right.
We're going left because I have to go left.
I don't care if I lose out on money.
It's the fastest way to sell so I can base more horses.
Holy shit.
This thing is flowing.
Look at how much this is just flowing.
All right.
I think we're in good shape.
I'm going to have two people sell.
Now we can start to really flow some money.
Here we go.
I'm getting the guaranteed one over here.
Expensive, but it should be all right.
Beautiful.
Nice job, mole.
Breaking the dough.
Nice.
Good find.
All right.
Start selling it.
I'm going to start to see a huge amount of flow here now.
This is going to get wacky.
I need more horses.
Prices are pretty much the same.
We'll do half and half.
Prices are pretty close.
Where is this?
Shit.
Yes.
All right.
Stop selling.
It's dog shit prices.
Dog shit prices.
Stop selling.
Prices are dog shit.
Uh-oh.
Jesus.
Okay.
Hold on.
Don't sell anything until it's at least a dollar.
You look green.
Gremlin.
That's fine.
Do I need more horses?
They're going to start taking from the reserves, right?
I need more horses, don't I?
They're not.
Look at these.
All these tanks are full.
This game is awesome.
I love it.
I knew I was going to get stuck.
The prices are crazy right now.
Come on.
Final month.
Everybody get over there now.
No more drilling.
And yeah, no more drilling.
Just sell.
Everybody just dump all your load over here.
More horses?
Put this down.
Hurry up.
Come on, come on, come on, come on.
Only like 10 days.
$12,836.
That's how we get it done.
Oh, I lost 50 cents.
All right.
I got $1,000 in fines.
Who cares?
10 grand.
Did anybody?
No one even came close.
I should get a prize for that.
Welcome to my bar.
Make yourself comfortable and mingle with the crowd.
They may have some interesting offers.
I like this game a lot.
Okay.
Kyle.
Tired of low prices.
Slip me some cash and the price of left ink will never go below 70 cents next year.
Okay.
At right ink, the price can be even more right.
For a small personal donation, a price will stay above 81 cents for the year.
That's not bad.
I can offer you a 50% discount on those hefty spilling fines for one year.
No.
How much is a fine?
I spilled 10 times or so and that's not worth it.
No.
Get out of here.
Although you can just...
Although you can fuck off.
All right.
More with three.
Double capacity.
I can have two.
Yeah, this is it for sure.
Yep.
This is it.
I won't have that much money left though.
I think I'm going to do size two.
Size two makes sense to me.
I'm going up here.
Why do I get to go last every year?
That doesn't seem fair.
I have to go last every year?
I'm not bidding more money for that.
Upgrade the mole?
How do I upgrade the mole?
There's no mole two.
Is there?
I don't think there's a mole two.
All right.
Let's go.
I'm ready.
Click the button above the silo to upgrade the storage capacity of your silo against a small cost.
Okay.
From now on, levels will run from January 1st to December 31st.
I think there's no more oil left in the ground.
Click on the calendar and withdraw your land lease.
Oh, so if I don't...
If I go to the last month and I don't...
Well, there's nothing left?
I get some of the money back.
All right.
Let's go for it.
What do you want?
Oh, there's a Sims fast forward button.
Okay.
Cool.
Get this started right.
Is that oil right there?
I can't tell.
Is that oil?
That looks like the edge, right?
Is that an edge?
Yes.
Right there.
All right.
We're good.
Good start.
Whoa!
Slippage.
Not slippage.
Spillage.
Oh, over here.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
This way.
Okay.
No.
Yeah.
This is expensive as shit.
Bring it over here.
Yeah.
No shit.
There's oil there.
All right.
I'm going to bring it back here.
Okay.
Start depositing it.
All right.
Stop bringing it right.
Okay.
How is there nothing over here?
I'm thinking this game sucks.
Play something else.
No way, man.
This is great.
This game is no way, man.
Come on.
This is fun.
I think this is great.
Oh, shit.
All right.
We're good.
Hear me out.
I'm not going to go all the way down
because I'm afraid I'm going to go through something
and screw it up.
No, nothing there.
Is this still sucking from there?
Is it still getting it from there?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Store it, store it, store it.
You do the big rush at the end when it's like $1.50.
The mole's down here.
All right.
Let's start selling a little bit.
78 cents a spine.
There we go.
Here we go.
Perfect.
All right.
Let's go sell.
I'm going to be taking a ton.
I'm going to be making a lot of oil now.
Sell.
More horses.
I need more.
All right.
Let's go.
It's literally $1.02 right now.
Speed it up.
Suck it out.
All right.
I'm going to end.
I'm going to leave after this.
We just drained the whole thing.
All right.
I got $22,000.
Watch this.
I'm out.
I'm going to get a refund.
Upgrade the pipe.
Wait, what?
Wait, it's only August.
September, October, November.
It's not.
Okay.
Hold on.
There's no more juice on the ground, guys.
Is there some?
Wait, there's some here.
A little bit of extra at the bottom of the thing here.
I'm out.
Good call.
It was a good call.
I just, there was one more over here.
That's fine.
It's a good call.
I got my, I got literally, I got my money back.
Look at this.
Look at that.
It's literally 50% off.
It was a big one.
It was, it was decent medium size.
It was okay.
Okay.
Mayor's tips.
That's a big deal.
Four grand to make it so it's,
left ankle only be always 91 cents.
I'm going to build everything over on the left side.
Nothing's even going to go close to the right side.
Oh, that's not bad.
400 bucks for the slippage.
Why do I keep saying slippage?
Does the lower interest sound interesting?
Pay me some cash and I'll reduce next year's interest rates by 42%.
I got 30.
Geez.
I'm fine.
I'm going to do this one though.
91 cents permanently on the left side.
I think that's a good deal.
Mayor's tips.
One of 20 Daphne's deals.
Pipes don't have to reach the bottom of an oil patch.
Once connected, the oil pocket will be okay.
So that's good to know.
Thanks for the tip.
Oil is only pumped as fast as the narrowest pipe in a chain.
And handle.
Make sure all pipes in the chain are sufficiently upgraded for the most efficient oil flow.
Okay.
If you don't see oil in uncovered ground below a waving dowser,
wait a while for the ground level to rise more.
You get more money for getting all the oil or selling all the oil
and withdrawing your land lease early.
Thank you mayor.
Appreciate it.
What else do I want to do?
Size three.
Timer two.
Wide.
Free wide.
Or more horses.
Mole sells two.
I'm begging you.
Where?
Mole sells two.
What's the moles?
Oh.
10 grand though.
All right.
I'll do it.
That's like the most money I wanted to spend in this entire time.
Moles dig faster.
I want horses.
Why did I just?
I don't have enough money.
I want this one.
Really?
You're going to outbid me?
You piece of shit.
How much is it going for?
Four grand?
Get out of my way.
You don't even have that much money.
Oh yeah you do.
Whatever fine.
Who cares?
I'm going over here.
Let's go.
Moles will now uncover nine cells instead of six.
I think they're probably better than the dowsers at this point right?
Let's get four going.
Who needs a dowser?
Left side only.
This is a huge one too.
Oh my god.
What a start.
Right side?
No no no no no.
I'm not doing that.
Yes.
No.
Right there.
There's nothing over here.
God damn it.
This is not enough.
Oh this is bad.
This is bad placement.
But whatever.
It's all right.
There's no oil on the on this side.
All right we're in a good spot.
Speed it up.
Excuse me.
Take it.
Don't take it.
Go.
What are you doing over there?
Look at that.
Look at that money coming in.
30 grand.
Oh let's go.
All right I need down here.
See where you see something.
What do you see?
You see something?
A dollar thirty nine.
Look at that.
Come on.
I need to make more money.
A dollar fifty per pound or whatever it is.
Come on.
This is so much.
Is there no more oil left in this goddamn place?
I think this place is dry.
I think it's dry.
I think I got everything.
It's dry.
Let me check one a few more places.
I think it's dry.
I'm pulling up.
Got it all.
Thousand for bonus early withdrawal.
Thousand for all oil.
Thousand for all oil sold.
Bingo.
Did it.
Feels good.
Okay.
I got money to play with now.
What should I do?
I think it's stable right?
Yeah so I can buy less horses makes sense to me.
So the horses can just take more.
And I want them to be faster.
That's twenty five thousand dollars.
I'm done.
Left is eighty nine ninety cents or I I don't get out of bed for anything less than ninety cents.
Sorry not worth it.
Okay let's keep going.
Thirty four.
That's not bad.
You know to fight all the people over here.
It looks like the trend is up here is more.
Let's go higher.
The higher you go seems like the more there is.
The green on this guy is crazy.
I'm green?
Am I actually like green?
Like my skin is green?
What do you mean?
Is it?
Shouldn't be.
All right let's move.
From now on you can upgrade your wagons to carry more oil.
You can buy it by clicking it here.
Remember this upgrade only lasts for the duration of the level.
Oh okay well.
Let's get our mole crew out here.
Nice job.
Good work.
You guys see anything else?
I think we're good right?
Don't sell left.
Well now I'm kind of hold on.
No more right here.
Okay we're getting right in the middle.
Looks like we got two.
Wagging capacity hurry up.
Come on come on hurry up hurry up.
Oh boy hold on.
All right speed is now a thousand bucks okay.
All right now we're going to start to make a ton of money here.
They can feel way.
Wait what are they doing?
Deliver it.
All right do not go that way.
Don't go that way either.
39 cents give me a break.
Right when I send all of you guys over here.
It's it's 80 cents on the right side now.
Yeah everybody start going here now.
Right there all right good good good good good good good.
That's a lot.
I'm going I'm gonna double drain that one.
Oh my god it's all a 37.
You gotta be fucking kidding me.
Oh shit I didn't even see it.
All right we're going to go full throttle here.
Everybody deposit.
Now hold hold it.
Let's sell to the left a little bit here.
Start selling left.
Sell left sell left sell left.
Sell left sell left hard.
Sell left hard.
Stop selling left.
Sell right hard.
Sell right hard now.
Right no not yet let it climb.
Let it climb let it climb.
Let it climb to like a dollar.
It's over a dollar.
Okay hold on and sell right.
Sell right go go go go go go go.
Sell sell sell sell sell sell right.
Sell right sell right.
I think it's dry.
I'm pretty sure this is dry.
Shit it's all right I'll take 30 grand.
It was good it was close.
All right what about um herd size.
Or no no I'll do the mole thing right.
People said do moles.
Sells three.
Moles will now uncover 12 cells instead of nine.
It's 20 grand.
Moles will dig faster.
I just spent 30 000 on moles.
They dig faster and they do way more.
Hope this is worth it.
I only have six thousand dollars left.
Wait anybody have anything?
No 100% discount.
Loans now.
Okay let's go.
Only four more places to go.
Stay right here.
This is it for this area.
Are we ready to go?
I gotta make money.
All right mole strats.
That's very good.
And they dig faster now too.
Okay let's get started.
Go my minions.
Good job.
This one right here.
Is this just a huge one?
Okay I'm gonna do.
You might think I'm crazy but I'm doing too.
All right stop stop stop.
Left side left side left side.
This one is just gigantic.
This is this big.
Got one here.
That's a long way to go.
Oh shit there's some right here.
I didn't even see it.
I'll get it.
I'll get it don't worry.
Nothing on the right side at all.
Wait I can connect them?
Did I not do this?
Uh oh.
Oh I need to sell it.
Oh hurry up.
Stop that bullshit.
I can't move these anymore.
Oh come the fuck on dude.
What do I do about this?
There's too much money to be made on the right side.
I can't store it yet.
What the hell?
Can I close this?
Close one rig.
What do I?
How do I do this?
You can't.
I can't.
I guess you can't.
Oh really?
Oh I think I'm all right.
I'm okay.
Let's start storing oil.
I think I'm all right.
Store store store store store.
Or go go left go left.
I gotta come back up and get this.
Dude this land sucks.
It's not my problem.
This land is terrible.
I got the worst land in the game so far.
You're gonna think I'm insane but I'm not.
All right store it.
Bottom left too yep.
This land is terrible.
I'm gonna have to go from here that way.
It's so long but it's gonna be the same length.
Do not sell.
These are dog shit prices.
Don't sell these are dog shit prices.
I refuse.
Don't sell.
We're gonna do a huge sell at the end.
All right I'm gonna keep going this way.
63 cents.
69 cents.
Oh everybody hold hold hold hold.
Don't move don't move.
Oh 84 cents.
85 cents.
87 cents.
88 cents.
89 cents.
Get the horses ready.
Once this goes over a dollar I'm going in.
And it's time not yet.
Okay the run is saved.
135 on the left too.
All right we're good we're good we're good.
Let's go.
What year is it?
Stop selling.
Store it.
I think that might be it.
Another couple of uh I think this is it.
120 cents.
I'm not doing that.
I think we're dry.
Just hold on a second.
50 cents.
I gotta sell.
Oh I don't care.
Final month is fine.
I'll make more money.
Hold hold hold don't no no no no no no.
The price is climbing.
Don't do that.
I'll make more money.
Five grand that was bad.
Okay if you can see a diamond you need a mold to get it above ground.
I can teach them this valuable skill.
Don't feel like going around rocks then go straight through them with the special drill
I'm offering at my factory.
Our need for oil brings us to the desert.
Here you can stumble upon rocks and diamonds in the ground.
All right.
Diamond hunting moles.
That's pretty cool.
I can work with that.
Anthony might be in the saloon to help you out in exchange for a diamond.
He'll point out an oil rich parcel to you.
Really?
What do you guys think?
I'm thinking right.
I'm thinking all the way to the bottom right.
Yeah the top right or bottom right I think is what I'm gonna do.
Right in the mid?
Should ask the guy.
Well I need a diamond.
I don't have a diamond.
I'm going right here.
Hope it was worth it.
All right I got some money.
Moles will dig even faster.
I can have a scanner.
If you want to know exactly what sits where under the surface use the scanner.
That sounds really good.
Diamonds.
I can train moles so they dig up diamonds.
It's expensive.
Left will never be 81.
Always over 70.
That's bad.
It's also bad.
I thought it was 20 bucks.
I was like wait hold on.
All right factory.
The drill.
Found a new drilling method which allows you to drill through rocks.
Uh oh.
That's not good.
Well I hope they find some diamonds.
This is a long stream for you Jerma.
I told you we were doing game gamer weekend.
I'm I don't want to leave.
I'm having a great time.
I want I'm gonna stay.
I'll stay for a while.
That's why I started early.
This game's I love this game.
Should I beat this game like right now?
Should I go eat food come back and just and just beat this game?
Put a mold directly on it if you find a diamond.
All right well get to work guys.
Mole friends.
That's rock.
I'm concerned about this because I can't drill through that.
Okay there's no I think I'm all right.
70 a dollar.
All right let's go.
Change sides.
All right stop.
Store it.
Now I'm gonna go here.
Here.
Slowly kind of make my way down.
Double this up.
Another horse.
I need more horses right now.
71 cents it's all right.
It's gonna it's not ideal but I'm gonna do it.
I need the money.
Okay store it.
I need more horses.
What's the point of the game?
Make a bunch of money and become an oil tycoon.
All right start selling left side.
Some more mole action.
I just don't want to hit rock.
It might break it.
This is a big one right here.
Oh all right start storing it.
Do I can I drill around this?
How do I get around this?
Or can I not?
I don't I think that goes all the way.
I think I have to go right.
Shit I gotta get down here.
This better not go all the way around.
So much shit over here.
All right 92 cents right side.
Start selling it.
Whoa stop go the other way.
Actually perfect.
All right we're good.
Now I can slow down a little.
Because I need to get around here.
Question is where do I want to go from here?
There's no rock here right?
There might not be anything else over here.
I'll dig.
I don't want to spend too much money digging down.
There's nothing there.
I could go this way.
I think this is stuck.
Spending money to dig a hole to make money.
I mean kind of.
I'm literally getting this game right now.
This is addicting.
It really is.
It just is.
It's great.
Not too complicated.
It's just kind of you gotta make you gotta be.
It's just some RNG right?
You gotta find the thing to dig into.
I don't I click oh.
All right I'm gonna go from.
What does that mean?
What does this mean though?
Why close and open?
Is it to divert or something?
I don't want to make another one just for a tiny little thing.
How much is it gonna cost to get over there?
$278.
It might cost the same amount of money.
To just build one.
Caught it on the way down but it's all right.
Left side.
Branch from second node on the middle well.
Uh I don't I don't have um I didn't upgrade that.
This might actually be it.
That was it.
That was a terrible plot.
That was such a bad plot.
The rocks all over the place.
Who picked that?
Okay that is the worst plot in the entire game.
In the entire two hours we've been playing this.
24.
Even the tutorial zone had more.
Do I want to upgrade anything?
77 cents.
Save for the drill.
Yeah I don't even use the dowsers.
They're too slow.
All right yeah I can't spend any money.
That was a bad one.
All right where?
What do you think?
I don't want you to see my like yellow stained armpits.
So I'm gonna move over this way.
I still like work out in this shirt.
If anyone's figuring that out.
Pop left.
Good.
We all picked one.
Okay hopefully mine was right.
This could be huge.
This could change the rest of the course of the entire game.
I gotta play efficiently.
Not bad.
Stupid you're an idiot.
Why did I do that?
Sell right.
Keep going.
Keep selling right.
Left side.
All right it's still pretty good.
Let's start putting this together.
I hope there's no rocks here.
That would be bad.
All right it's gonna start flowing pretty hard now.
Oh my goodness.
I need some more horses right now.
Not prepared.
I wasn't prepared.
I'm not getting a fee every time this happens right.
Why are you storing it?
Oh my god what a disaster.
What a disaster.
There we go.
This is huge.
I'm going this way.
A monumentally huge one.
Oh shit.
Okay there's more.
Connect these two.
All right this is looking pretty good.
Count some money over this say.
Hold on the left side.
It's a mole action.
Still over a dollar.
A dollar seven still over on left side.
Okay that's better.
I wonder if I should.
Okay there we go.
Right here.
All right I'm gonna stop selling here.
All right stop selling.
You go to the right side.
There's more over this way.
I might connect these two together.
Start selling right side.
All back on the right side after this batch.
Back to depositing.
We're gonna wait till it's over a dollar
and then we're gonna go for it.
We're gonna go super mode.
Oops.
All right start selling.
Uh oh.
We're just gonna do drain it from three.
All right I need more selling.
I need any more room.
Not an ideal price but it's not a bad one either.
Oil patch for our left.
I got it going for it.
I'm okay with 84 cents.
That's good.
September.
Unless let's is there anything down here?
Just if there's something down there
then you know what I mean.
We gotta be careful.
Now this is it.
Is it just this here
and then I gotta wrap back around and get this.
All right start storing it.
All right this one's almost drained completely.
I'm going.
I know I'm an idiot but whatever.
I need it.
I want the thousand dollar bonus.
Shit this one below it too.
Oh come on really.
There's nothing else over here.
700 dollars to get a bonus of a thousand.
I think that's it.
This looks like shit but whatever.
All right get it.
Hurry up.
Suck it up.
Quick quick quick quick.
Did I get it?
What should I do?
The rock drill is really important.
You know where's that factory?
30,000.
You found a new drill method
which allows you to drill through rock.
Yes and that's all I'm going to do for now.
Anything cheap.
Sure I'll get it just to get it.
Why not?
Okay I can go through a rock now.
Oh the branch.
Oh all right.
Okay remind me to do that next time
because I can't just not do that.
That one was really good.
It was like 40 grand.
I'm staying up here.
Probably right here right?
This is 48, 54.
This has to be at least like 50
or probably up here all the way to the top.
Let's try this one.
Outbid huh?
Fine I'll just outbid you.
Really?
Stop.
Who has more money?
I'm not going higher than 6k.
What are you guys doing?
What are you doing?
He scammed me.
He did it on purpose.
Okay what did I just do?
10,000?
Okay I'm in trouble.
Because it costs 2,000.
No I'm all right.
And I got the drill too.
All right we're good.
I'm just gonna get...
These moles gotta do work right now.
Put them strategically.
Okay let the moles do their thing.
Good job.
Nice work.
Excellent work over there.
Let's get started right now.
Wait this is gonna get us some...
Yep.
Wait you have to upgrade it.
I have to.
It's 750.
Okay all right all right.
Let's get this started right now
and we got some good good good good.
Okay very good very good very good.
I'm gonna go here.
Right here.
Right there.
A couple of horses.
I'm gonna do...
I'm gonna sell on the one-in-one.
I don't want...
Don't upgrade this shit yet
until I can handle it.
I do this every single time.
Start storing it.
I'm now prepared to upgrade these.
I'm gonna go with the second drill here.
No it didn't spill.
That's such horse shit.
Can we go this way?
I was scared that I wasn't gonna make it through this.
I thought there was gonna be a wall here.
All right we're good.
You don't have it?
I thought you did.
You do now.
All right store.
This is where we're gonna start to make tons of money.
I paid 10 grand for this spot.
There better be more than this.
It's a joke.
What's happening?
I was too lasered in.
I was lasered in to just that spot right there.
And I wasn't paying...
I'm in trouble.
This is bad.
So quick.
Everything's fine.
What a trash fucking place to do this in.
What a garbage place.
I paid $10,000 for the amount of oil that would fit in a Capri Sun.
Are you kidding me?
See anything over there?
We're at a standstill.
I think I got everything.
There's no oil to get anymore.
There's no more oil.
I paid $10,000 for this place.
There's one snot rocket down here.
Great.
This guy hasn't found shit.
Unleash the moles?
All right unleash the moles I guess.
You got something?
You found something.
Oh my god.
Okay dude.
Fine.
That's it.
Store it.
Do I just go over here?
November.
What happened over here?
That shit just crashed to five cents.
All right.
Start selling.
Go.
$30,000.
Did I get it all?
All right.
I think that's empty.
Let's see.
I think I got everything.
That was not worth $10,000.
It was empty over here.
I mean oh my god.
$10,000 for the land.
$7,000 for you know just do the math.
Down $17,000.
I want to see that.
$45,000.
I guess that was okay.
Not worth $10,000.
Sleepy talking?
No it's just headphone talking.
Just speech jams me.
All right.
Branch time.
So I can go.
I can split pipes.
There we go.
I got it.
Let's go for it.
I mean very obviously it's up here.
But there's no way I'm going to.
I actually can't spend more than like a few thousand on this.
I'm not going higher than that.
No.
Fuck you.
I'll go here.
Enjoy it.
Enjoy.
Hey enjoy your Capri Sun.
Because that's literally what you're going to get there.
Is that three pipes?
I kind of went overboard with the moles.
Okay well this is a big one.
Fuck.
Did it wrong.
Wait I could do this right?
Okay yeah I can do that.
Make some money.
Let's go.
No no no no no.
How do I stop?
So oh no we're good.
Okay this is not bad.
Very nice.
All right.
So this is just going to drain.
Get some mole action.
Got something on the right here.
Silo going right in the middle.
Directly in the middle.
Another one right here.
Okay when this one's done we're going to go down.
I might.
Should I do two here?
I'm going to store it.
That's too far to go.
I'm going to spill.
Maybe I won't.
I knew I was going to spill.
Don't do it.
Got it.
Okay we're good.
Now close the pipe.
Who closed it?
What?
What are you talking about?
What do you want?
Close the valve.
Don't.
What do you mean close it?
What do you want me to do?
Oh that's.
I can just do it right here.
I understand what that means now.
Okay okay we got a big one here.
I need money.
Start selling on the right side.
Of course the price goes down immediately.
Oh go left.
Okay don't sell right at all.
You look like Elmo today.
Oh do I?
Thanks.
You thought I was going to do it.
You were waiting for it.
Okay let's.
Okay actually keep selling on the left.
There's more down here.
I need more.
I'm gonna.
Yeah it's July.
I'm gonna double drain this one.
It is fucking July.
Like I gotta go.
Grab that right side.
Right side.
Come on.
It's a dollar.
All right stop.
Where are we going next?
I need some bowls.
Okay I think this is almost done.
What's with the oil?
What's with this terrible just non no oil here?
This is none.
I spent.
Did I spend money here?
No I didn't.
Pretty much free.
But this shit is empty man.
What a bust.
Unless there's something over here.
No that's it.
I think I'm gonna get out of here.
Everything's empty right?
All right let's get the thousand bucks back.
There's nothing else here.
This place is a fucking joke.
This place is a joke.
Okay 30k.
Somebody give me 76 is not enough.
Make it 90 and I'll pay five grand for it.
Which I do now.
No spilling.
Yeah that's right.
I really think I want that right now.
Dowsing rod.
I don't really use them.
We could do moles.
Faster moles for the scanner.
Thicker pipes.
Yeah that's probably the best to play.
With three size three.
With three.
Yeah we can really just drain it.
All right.
With three.
Yeah that was pretty bad.
That's where it just was.
Look at this.
First dig.
Second dig.
Third dig.
Terrible.
Maybe go to the bottom.
Should I go right down to the bottom?
I don't know if I want this.
I'm at 35.
28.
42.
The adjacent ones are gonna be terrible.
I'm just gonna go right down here.
Yeah they're gonna.
I knew it.
I knew that's what was gonna happen.
I'm not getting involved.
Oh they're upgrading stuff.
I get it.
Okay.
All right let's go.
I'm gonna upgrade pipes twice.
All right moles.
I like the moles more than the dowsing people.
All right don't go overboard.
I'm going overboard so bad.
Stop.
Start.
And here's my plan.
Is this stupid?
Because then I'm gonna go bang bang.
Is that stupid?
What's happening?
I fucked up bad.
I don't have a fucking horse.
Did I lose?
Is the game over?
Oh okay.
I'll take a $500 loan.
Thank you.
I thought I actually just lost the game.
This is dumb what I'm doing isn't it?
Maybe not.
Oh there's so much money on that left side and right side.
All right thank god.
Okay back in the game.
Let's go.
There's something right there.
No diamonds though weirdly enough.
Pay the loan?
How do I pay the loan?
Total debt 700.
Can I pay it from here?
I don't think I can do it from.
You pay it at the end.
Yeah that's all right.
It's not gonna be too bad.
All right this is level three.
I need to okay.
Is there any more oil?
This one's a lot.
So okay this is gonna be overflowing soon.
I knew it.
I'm trying to get in front of it.
Okay we're good.
Don't sell anything.
These are terrible prices.
All right I'm gonna go right here.
Got something?
Oh of course you do.
Why am I even hiring that guy?
I'm gonna be in trouble.
This is these prices are bad.
Please look at this.
What's with this price?
Just close it?
30 cents?
No you can fuck off.
I'm not 30 cents.
40 cents?
I have to dump it.
I actually have to dump this.
Because it's gonna start spilling.
I'm gonna have to pay.
Take another silo.
Just I mean of course.
Of course the price literally is fine now.
No I'm not selling.
Stop.
Stop it.
No selling.
Actually no this is okay.
That's all right.
Dump dump dump dump.
Get rid of it.
Dump it all.
Wait hold on.
No no no no no.
Stop hold on.
Don't do it yet.
95 cents?
It's gonna be up like a dollar something.
Okay hold on.
It's almost time.
Nope.
Oh yes.
Look at that one.
Oh we did it at the perfect time.
Perfect timing.
Let's go.
I need to figure out where more oil is.
All right hold it.
I think it's time to hold it.
All right stop.
All right stop selling.
Start storing now.
Take them out.
Check over here.
That might be it.
See anything?
It's a lot of wagons.
Yeah I kind of freaked out.
It's all right though.
They're only 150.
September.
Okay at the end of October I can start selling.
76 is a good floor price now don't you think?
Yeah that's true.
I wonder how big this is.
Oh shit.
That might be it.
Do I just hold this oil till November?
Because I don't think there's anything else here.
I mean I'm gonna check.
This is it.
That's it.
There's nothing else here.
22 cents over.
Yeah there's nothing here.
80.
Okay November.
Oh we're gonna get a good price.
20.
1.
25.
Wait till like 1.
Okay go go go go.
It's not coming up.
All right I'm good.
That was worth it.
The $1,000 I would have gotten is not a big deal.
That was like 10 grand.
There's nothing else here.
Another terrible one.
I keep picking the winners don't I?
That's sad.
This doesn't look correct.
This looks like I'm doing something wrong.
This looks like a weird food budget list.
Yeah what are you what are you getting for food?
Well you know 80% bread.
And then like a head of lettuce.
Here's the here's the cabbage.
There's a cabbage slice.
There's like a weird food pyramid.
Maybe I'm spending too much money.
Can't see the cursor.
Weird why not?
Have you guys not been able to see the cursor the whole time?
What?
Well that's weird.
So you were probably guessing what the hell I was doing this whole time.
There's been no cursor.
Has there been a point?
It was fine though okay.
We weren't even watching dude.
Okay.
I have an announcement to make.
I will soon retire as mayor.
My successor will be the one who has the most shares of my town.
Which I will gradually sell at the new stock auction.
What?
I'm selling my shares of the town.
Let's go to the auction and see who takes a step closer to becoming the new mayor.
Press the start button to start the auction.
The first one to press the buy button acquires 2% of the town's shares.
How much are they?
What do they cost?
There is it $36,000?
How much money do I have?
Okay I have 32,000.
Is it 36 grand?
I own this fucking town.
Let's go.
Did I pay too much?
Did I just pay way too much?
That was for only 2% of the shares?
That doesn't sound like a good idea now that I think about it.
I could have waited till like less than 5k probably.
Oh well.
Imagine getting 2% of the shares and you think you own the town.
Well I can't upgrade anything.
That was really dumb.
Do I do it again?
No.
Okay.
The town is evaluated at $800,000 so I actually just didn't really do anything.
I'm gonna hold on to the money.
Again look at this trash.
Junk, junk, junk.
I need something that's not junk.
These are all bad though.
I'm just gonna go over here.
Somebody said near the water.
Hope you're right.
Okay.
Right Inc.
It'll never go under a dollar.
That's ridiculous.
I have to do it.
Okay.
So I gotta be ready to sell because it's never going under a buck.
Let's do it.
Okay.
Let's go.
Hurry up.
Right Inc.
I hope it's all on the right side.
Get a dowser out there too.
We gotta go now.
Got something good?
Alright.
Let's start.
Go, go, go.
Let's go.
Sell, sell.
Just do.
I'm never gonna.
I'm not gonna even buy a storage unit.
Why would I?
Just sell permanently.
Always sell.
Where's this guy seeing this oil?
Move guys.
Uh, oh boy.
Oh boy.
Go and buy it and sell it on the market over there.
Oh shit.
Oh no.
Okay.
What?
I freaked out.
I've not seen a single diamond by the way.
This one was junk too.
Great.
I got a dollar.
You got anything for me here?
You do got something.
Finally.
My God.
What is going on here?
Thank you.
I would never would have seen that.
What do I get?
A diamond?
Got it.
You picked up a diamond.
If you're ever short on time,
use this button to play a little bit longer.
Exchange for a diamond.
Okay.
Well, no, I don't want to do that.
Dumb face cam.
Where?
Can't really go anywhere.
No, it blocks too much.
Left of.
Wait.
I guess it could go up here.
Here?
But then you guys can't see me selling stuff.
I just don't think I fit anywhere.
Maybe here?
I don't fit anywhere.
No, I don't fit anywhere.
It's too bad.
I don't really fit anywhere.
Put myself right in the middle.
I could do like here.
Next to the prices on the right.
I could just.
I mean, that's weird.
This is strange though.
No, I don't fit anywhere.
I'm just going to stay down here.
Oh, I shrunk it.
I shrunk it a little bit.
It's not enough oil here.
I got absolutely just ruined.
I think it's actually probably empty.
They're all just crowding this one thing.
Nice.
A dollar.
Fantastic.
We're in September.
I think it's empty.
Carrying nothing here.
Dowsers not finding anything.
Did you find anything?
15k.
I spent five grand to make it
so I could sell this shit for $1 each.
I got a diamond though.
All right.
Well, let's just end though.
How did you not find that?
He didn't find it.
Oh, stock auction.
What the fuck?
Who got it?
I clicked it and closed the menu.
1%.
Yeah, I got 2%.
Pound for pound, I spent less than you did.
I kind of want the scanner.
No, this is important.
It's important.
These things just get in the way.
I'm buying it.
What do I do with the diamond again?
I can give this to somebody, right?
Diamonds.
Your diamonds are worth $25.41 a piece.
Sell me one.
Get out of here.
Kidding me.
It's a solid diamond.
It's worth like $50,000.
Get out of here.
Looking for a piece of land with lots of oil.
Give me one of your shiny diamonds
and I'll point it out.
Is this guy a liar?
I also don't have...
I'm not doing this yet.
I don't have enough money.
Yeah, I'm not going to do that
because if I do that right now,
I only have 7k to work with.
I need 2k.
So I only have 5k to work with
if somebody wants to outbid me.
Does Mary have any more tips?
If a dowser with all the depth upgrades
walks out of the screen,
it means that there are no more
new untapped oil pockets in the ground.
Well, so that was the problem.
If you're running out of silo space,
don't forget you can also use
your wagons to store oil.
Yeah, I mean, I've been doing that.
Drilling around rocks can be cheaper
than spending money on the rig upgrade.
Keep in mind, however, that
longer pipelines are more expensive to upgrade.
Yeah, judging by the pie chart
that we all looked at.
Connecting pipes from an upgraded rig
to pipes from a non-upgraded rig
will copy...
Wait a minute.
Will copy all the upgrades to the new network.
Wait, hold on.
So if I just connect to this,
I don't have to buy that.
But you have to go a long way for that, though.
This is...
OK, going from here to here
is probably like six or seven hundred dollars.
How much would it be to upgrade this?
Three or four hundred?
It's probably cheaper than
buying the drill rig.
Probably.
Well, I'll keep that in mind.
Cancel the scan in progress
by clicking anywhere above ground
or just click the right mouse button.
Good to know.
Actually, pretty useful stuff.
OK, I should probably eat.
OK, I'm going to do one more.
Here's what we're going to do.
I'm going to do one more day.
So I'm going to do one more day
and then I'm going to go eat
and I'm coming back.
I need to eat something.
Well, hold on.
I have a question.
Question.
Would you rather...
Let's do a poll.
Would you rather me just to keep streaming
all the way for like
at least another couple of hours, at least?
Another like two or three hours.
Let's say like...
Let's say at least 10 hours.
10 to 12 hours.
Or would you rather we stop now
and pick it up tomorrow afternoon
and go again?
Like, would you rather have
like a 12 hour stream tonight
or would you rather have
like two six to eight hour streams
two days in a row?
So this is...
I mean, this is Omega Weekend.
Should we do 12 hours tonight?
And then I won't be live tomorrow
because that would mean
I probably would go until like
two plus o'clock in the morning.
And I definitely would...
If I would stream tomorrow
would be like in the afternoon.
What do you think?
Do tomorrow. OK.
I'm going to...
I want to play this more though.
Don't burn out.
I won't burn out.
I'll be all right.
I want to play this.
All right.
So here's what we're going to do.
It looks like it's pretty much...
It's decided.
I am going to do one more day here.
So I'm going to do another day.
And then we're going to start
with this tomorrow.
How much longer is the desert?
But what if I want to go?
What if we just go, man?
You know what I mean?
What if we just go?
And like, fuck it.
Who cares?
And let's just like go for like
15 hours or something.
Is that crazy?
Should I not do that?
OK.
Hey.
Hey, you over there.
Guess what?
Should I go?
I want to keep playing though.
But I don't want to...
It's been like almost nine hours.
It is Omega Weekend.
I'm staying.
I'm not going anywhere.
I'm going to go eat some food.
I'm coming back.
And this may be...
I'm just going to make it...
This could be...
This is Omega Weekend.
Can we stop on Omega...
Oh, it's Omega Weekend.
Let me stop.
You stop on Omega Gaming Weekend?
I don't think so.
I'm going to keep playing this.
I'm going to keep going as long...
Because I still want to play this.
I'm still really into this.
I think I'm having a great time.
So like, oh, I'm going to leave.
And all I'm going to be doing
when I'm sitting there eating
is just going...
I want to play that fucking oil game.
Right now.
I'll be right back.
I'm going to eat a little bit of food.
Get some water.
Stretch a little bit.
And I'm coming back.
We're going to at least finish the desert.
We're going to finish the desert at least.
You should refund those points.
Oh, yeah.
Turn off the channel points to re-vote again.
Yeah, because people are spending their channel points.
All right.
Here we go.
Let's plan this out.
I'm going to at least beat the desert tonight.
Can somebody tell me what my longest dream ever was?
What was it?
What was the longest dream ever?
You thought I was fucking around when I said I'd make a weekend.
I just want to prove this to you guys.
What's the longest dream I've ever done?
Was it 12 hours?
We're beating that record tonight.
I'll be right back.
I'm going to eat and stretch.
This is going to be the longest dream I've ever done.
I can already feel it.
I'm telling you right now.
This is going to be the longest dream I've ever done.
Stamp it.
I'll be right back.
I want the exact time that Lord of the Rings was
because I'm beating that shit tonight.
That will be...
Wait, hold on.
Wait, wait, wait.
All right.
Wait.
8, 9, 10, 11, 12, 13.
That would be 9, 10, 11, 12, 12.
Oh, we can fucking do this.
We can do this.
I'm going for it.
I feel great, by the way.
It's not like I feel okay.
I'll be right back.
So I didn't eat yet.
I'm having food is being put in the oven.
I did jog in a circle.
I peed.
I refilled my tea here.
Got a bunch of water.
I did zoomies.
I did the thing the dogs do.
I literally ran in a circle.
I'm kind of out of breath.
If you're going to sit down for like 15 hours
or like 14 hours or something,
you've got to get up and move.
Eventually.
Just microwave your food.
Well, no.
Holly is making French bread pizzas.
So I don't want to...
You don't want to put the French bread pizza in the microwave.
I don't rather be in the toaster or the oven or something.
All right.
Yeah, there's other stuff too,
but I think that's the fastest thing to make.
So yeah, I'm looking forward to it.
Okay.
I ran in a circle for like five minutes
and I may have tired myself out for the stream.
Wow, that was a mistake.
Why did I think that was a good idea?
Oh yeah, dude.
I've been streaming for like nine hours.
Oh yeah.
Let me get up and run in a circle for five minutes.
I'm kidding.
Don't worry.
I'm just kidding.
Okay.
Yes.
I got...
If there's ever a time that I'm going to break that,
like what?
12 hours, 13 hours?
It's going to be right now.
There ain't no fucking way I ain't going to do it.
Unless I shit my pants,
which I would just stay here.
I wouldn't leave and I wouldn't tell you.
All right.
Are you still streaming tomorrow?
That is a great question.
If I cross 14 plus hours
and it's like three o'clock in the morning Pacific,
I don't...
I'm going to say probably not on Saturday.
We'll see.
Okay.
Play Diablo 2.
It's my birthday.
You lied about Omega Weekend.
Hold on here.
Wait just a second.
Where everybody gets a little annoyed with me.
Omega Weekend.
I'm about to break the longest stream I've ever done ever.
I think that's Omega Weekend.
That's Omega Friday.
That's an Omega stream.
That's Omega Weekend.
We'll see.
If I get up tomorrow, I'll be fine.
Omega Friday equals Omega Weekend.
Well, hold on.
I'm technically...
I will be technically streaming on Saturday
for like three or four hours.
Excuse me?
Omega Friday?
Omega...
Omega Weekend.
But hold on.
Let's go over this really quickly.
We're going to chill.
This is going to be a chill.
Like it's getting late
and I don't want to be like loud
and screaming at people and stuff.
But I don't know what to mean.
We might play something else a little bit.
A typical stream that I do,
forget that it's Omega Weekend,
is what?
Between five and seven hours?
Seven and seven is 14.
That's like streaming seven hours on Friday,
seven hours on Saturday,
and then an extra epilogue stream on Sunday
to like just smoke a bowl and hang out.
It's not happening, by the way.
Semantics.
All right, let's play.
Let's play.
I'm having a lot of fun.
This game is fucking awesome.
Did this game come out this year?
Did this game come out in 2022?
Because it's like this is
one of my favorite games that came out.
This is great.
I love this.
Came out last year.
Oh, shit.
Well, whatever.
All right.
I'm going to go over here.
Pretty slim at the moment.
Pretty slim.
I'm going to stay here.
It was early access in 2016.
Really?
Damn.
Okay.
Geez.
Okay, let's go.
What are your thoughts on Internet
raising their double double price?
Well, you're eating it in and out.
That was the first mistake.
Okay.
Can upgrade silos twice?
How do you go?
Okay.
For the audio levels?
I mean, we're getting to the later hours, right?
Should we have like not the loud,
like, you know, the music,
the sounds in the background?
What do you guys think?
I just feel we should probably lower the lights here, too.
Don't you think?
Is it okay?
These kind of don't don't don't don't don't sounds.
You okay with these candles?
Candles?
Turn it down a little.
Okay.
Yeah, I think that's okay.
That's that's really good right there.
Get the nice music, the ambient sounds.
I think that you are.
All right.
Yeah, let me get let me turn lights off.
Oh, is that the better?
Although I'm kind of like low FPS, aren't I?
It's okay.
It's doing automatic gain adjustment.
So the lower I that's annoying.
Hold on.
Is that comfy or is that scary?
It's too scary.
Well, fuck.
Never mind.
I tried.
Oh, well, that looks so that's okay.
That's fine.
Here's a little weird, though.
Wait, I think I know what I can do.
Oh, I can do this.
This one is called hearth.
No, this looks better.
A little darker.
That looks that's comfier.
Yeah, that's that's much comfier.
That feels better.
My face is like flickering.
The camera is so bad.
I haven't said what this camera is because, I mean, why?
I don't really care that much.
But like this thing sucks.
It genuinely sucks.
It sucks.
It's because it's too cropped.
I don't really want to say what camera this is, but it sucks.
I just play the other camera and it doesn't matter.
I know I'm stalling really bad.
I don't mind if I do this still flickering.
Why is it flickering?
I don't get this.
Tons of flicker.
This game sucks.
Stop cropping it and do the zoom instead.
What do you mean?
Zoom?
Do two cameras.
Oh, fuck.
Hold on.
Don't make me do this.
That's so dumb.
No, it's too late for this.
It's too late for this.
I'm just going to go.
It's far too late for this.
Let me turn this.
This is going to help.
There it is.
Not there.
It's not flickering anymore.
The better.
I don't see the flicker anymore.
I mean, maybe a little.
For zoom game.
All right.
So let's do it.
So this is the new year.
What did I just upgrade?
I just upgraded something, didn't I?
Welcome to the cozy string.
We need two.
Got some of that right here already.
I'm going to go this way and then maybe that way too.
Let's get a mole over there just to make sure.
Looks like everything is on the right side.
I spent a thousand dollars on moles.
I know, but it's all right.
Should I?
I'm going to.
It's going to overflow, isn't it?
All right, we're good.
Okay.
So now let's build one here.
And I'm going to do the connect thing, right?
If I go like this and then I eventually connect these two.
Sell left.
I can't sell left 95, 98.
We're good.
I'm going to do silo right here.
That makes sense to me.
There we go.
Sell right, sell right, sell right.
Okay.
I need more.
It's time to upgrade.
This is where it gets scary.
I'm going to have at least five horses.
Be prepared to sell right.
There's so much here.
All right.
So now I'm going to keep moving this over here.
We're going to double drain this.
I'm going to split this guy this way.
Yes, we are.
We're going to split you this way.
I'm going to upgrade this.
Is that do I want to do that?
All right, question.
If I connected this to this,
is this going to become one pipe
or will they still be draining from here?
You just said yes.
Don't connect.
I'm going to need some more horses in a second.
Actually, no, I don't.
I keep buying a horse Andy over here.
Seriously.
All right.
Hold up.
There's a lot coming out of here right now.
I actually think I'm going to need more horses.
So far so good.
Mole action over here on the left.
Don't.
Okay.
Wait, wait, wait.
Let's do another one here.
Hold, hold, hold.
I really want this left side to be better.
Hold it.
I'm not.
No, hold it.
Seriously.
This is going to go to like...
This is going to come down.
This is going to go to like a dollar fifty.
All right.
This one here.
We're not going to money it.
Okay.
All right.
We got to do it.
Wait, I got to sell.
We got to go.
Go, go, go, go, go, go before it goes down.
Don't spill.
Okay.
Right side.
No, no, no.
Hold it.
Oh, my God.
There's no oil coming out.
Oh, shit.
Okay.
What do I do?
This way.
Hold that.
Check this out.
Connect this.
This is level three shit.
Right?
So that is going to do it.
Did that work?
Dollar fifteen.
I'm not doing it.
Did that not work?
What?
Isn't this going to upgrade everything to level three?
Am I?
Is that not how that works?
Sell.
Not yet.
Hold it.
Is it going to go to like one forty?
That didn't work.
One twenty nine.
One thirty.
One thirty one.
Thirty two.
Thirty three.
One thirty.
Yeah, that's good.
All right.
You can keep going right.
I want to go left now.
Let's have like a few of you be delivering.
All right.
I need some.
Did you look?
Are you seeing this?
Moles out.
I feel like this one sucks ass too.
Unfortunately, there's nothing on the left side.
That might be it.
I think that actually is it.
Ember.
I think that might be it.
Maybe check here.
What do you think?
Left.
Somewhere in the middle.
All right.
I'm spending a lot of money on moles.
Holy shit.
What was that?
Did I get a diamond?
I got a diamond.
So who found a diamond?
That's probably it though.
OK.
November.
Check over here.
Get a couple right.
OK.
That's it.
Sell on the right.
Final month.
That's it.
Oh, this is this is done.
This is done.
That's it.
Oh shit.
Doesn't matter.
Well, it's OK.
Pop middle.
I didn't even see it.
Oh, really?
It's OK.
I'll take 20 grand.
He's still streaming.
Yep.
If you are just if you're joining us for the first time
or you're joining us back from earlier,
the dude was waving you down.
Yeah, but I thought he was seeing the one I was already tapped into.
The longest stream I've ever done was...
Does anyone know the exact number?
I got two diamonds.
13 hours and four minutes and 13 hours, four minutes, 32 seconds.
If you're joining us, I'm going to break that tonight.
I'm going to...
This is going to be...
I'm breaking that longest stream ever in seven years.
I don't really do...
And then people go, what do you do a 13 hour stream?
That's really like in the grand scheme of things,
like people do 24 hour...
People do like 12 to 24 hour streams all the time.
Not me.
I don't...
I never do that.
Are you going to do turmoil the entire time?
I'm going to assume I'm probably going to beat this in the next few hours.
Maybe the next two hours or so.
And then we'll move on to something else.
You're going to die.
I'm not going to die.
Is French bread pizza a bad choice if you want to stream still?
Oh yeah, there's vegetables on it.
No, I'll be fine.
Get the food coma.
Eat a big French bread pizza and then fall asleep.
No, I'm up.
I'm not going to bed.
Don't worry.
Yeah, I don't really do this.
I never do it.
I'm a four to five hour Andy.
I guess I don't really have to explain why, but I am.
All right.
Is this worth it or no?
Because all the 50s are probably gone by now.
That's pretty good.
I think I'm going to do this.
It's never going to go below 83 left ink.
25 horses.
Dowser stops waving when you tap into what he found.
If he's still waving, you haven't found it.
That's actually a really good tip.
That's a good tip.
I have 24 grand.
It's mine.
One percent share.
Oh, but it's okay.
I have to start to make money.
Okay.
Land auction.
Let's move.
I'm going to stay right there.
Right in the middle.
And also I'm drinking a lot of water.
I'm doing a I'm drinking a bunch of super hydrators.
I've got my hydration.
There's a ghost in the room.
Use the diamond for the good land.
I don't think there's any good land left.
It was all up here.
It seems to be spreading thinner down here.
So I think I'm all right.
Yeah, let's just go.
I'm good.
I hope I got a good one.
Tell me to stop doing moles after I spend a thousand bucks.
Okay.
Thousand bucks?
What do you think?
Should I spend like one thousand on moles?
I don't want to go too far.
Jeremy, you should record the don't call the sus guy at 3 a.m.
This is your only chance.
All right.
What did I buy?
What's hey, hold on.
What side did I buy that was never going to go under 87 cents?
Was it right or left?
Because they both high left.
Okay.
So this worked out perfectly.
You might be thinking, what are you doing, man?
Well, oh, okay.
We got one over there.
I want to be able to start making money now.
Okay, let's go.
Start moving.
Okay.
No, I'm not doing a silo yet.
I love the moles.
They're so fun.
Silo is going right here.
Very close.
Everybody is going to be delivering to the left.
Okay.
Is that enough horses?
Oh, look at this.
This is a huge one.
I got to go to here.
This is a big one.
It's empty.
This one.
Okay.
I got to go here and then I'll go a little bit down this way.
Any more moles?
No, I don't want to do more than a thousand dollars in moles.
It's very possible that this is it.
There's probably only a couple more here.
The silo turned out to be kind of not really helping.
Bring a dowser out.
Easy.
Easy with this bullshit.
Some of you deliver and some of you store.
Did you find something?
More of you need to come over here.
Got something?
I need to start selling.
What do you got?
There's nothing here.
Sell right?
It's too late.
Nothing over there?
Nothing?
What about all the way down?
There's got to be something, right?
It's too late.
I can't go.
I can't go right.
It is too late.
Is there anything left?
Why do I keep getting such shitty ones?
Dowser didn't find anything.
I think I'm pulling out.
Should I pull out?
Would you pull out if you were me?
Would you pull out?
I got to do three more moles.
And then I'm pulling out.
I'm out.
Oh, fuck off.
Really?
It's fine.
I don't care about the shares this time.
I need to start upgrading.
Pizza's ready.
All right.
Let me go grab my French bread pizza.
I'm going to eat it on stream.
I'm going to be off cam maybe for a little bit.
I'll be literally back in two seconds.
Give me one second.
I honestly don't really don't want to spill this
or get this on anything.
I'm sure I have enough room.
What do you got?
You guys want to see it?
It's pretty basic.
It's pretty generic.
It's just the...
What is it?
Who makes this sauce?
Okay.
Hold on.
One second here.
I'm ready.
You want to see?
Oh, Pog.
Actually looks pretty good.
It's like a commercial.
First bite.
Let me give you a review.
This is what...
Who makes this?
Holly, who makes this?
We need it closer.
Red Baron.
All right.
This is Red Baron.
Peppers, pepperoni, sausage, cheese, tomato sauce, and bread pizza.
Real review.
It's been a long time since I've had a Red Baron French bread pizza.
Let's give it a review.
Here we go.
Kind of nervous.
It's too hot to bite.
Give me a second.
That's how you tell if it's too hot.
If I had just bit that, it would have been a bad experience.
Okay, here we go.
And I'm going to give you an honest review.
Very good.
I would get...
Okay, honestly, there's a lot of peppers flavor.
Big crunch.
Actually, I'm getting the peppers, sausage, and peppers.
Let's try over here.
Oh, I swallowed that way too early.
Oh, fuck.
Oh, I hate that.
You know when you eat something, especially something crunchy,
and you swallow it too early, and you just feel it just attack your entire insides?
Is that a soundboard or is that real?
Is it a soundboard?
Do you think that crunch is a soundboard?
Do you think so?
It's fucking delicious.
It's not a soundboard.
Let me try that again.
God damn, it's good.
I wonder.
Yo!
Minecraft dirt?
Minecraft eating sound effect?
Let me...
Mine's better.
That's way better.
They should use that.
Was it a soundboard?
I can record myself talking and play it.
I can play it back.
That was a real crunch.
I recorded that.
Damn, that sounds good.
Really?
That sounds great.
Did they make commercials for Red Baron Pizza where it sounds like this?
Because that actually happened.
That really happened.
So like, this is not horse shit.
That one wasn't good?
Well, that was a lot of sauce.
You're not going to get crazy crunches from the sauce.
It's not going to happen.
Hold on.
I'm going to try to get a fucking crazy one.
This is going to be crazy.
This is going to be the most ridiculous crunch you've ever heard in your whole life.
You ready?
Somebody has to do that.
I'm realizing.
This would be such a fun job.
Oh my God, I'm still wearing this.
What a cool, like, foley artist.
That sounds like such a great time.
You just get to hit bags of ice with hammers
and step on glass with boots and bite pizzas and shit.
And record it.
I think I could do it pretty well.
Do a foley stream.
That's actually a really fun idea.
Just get a blank slate of some type of video
or some public domain movie or something and do foley work to it.
This is good.
It's really good.
I haven't had one of these in a long time.
This is, I would say, pretty high up there.
I should have watched a video or something.
What am I doing?
Like a bunch of free sounds.
That is kind of a cool idea.
Just do a four or five-hour stream
where you just do a ton of fucking sound effects
and make them sound good
and just release them all.
Just creative, what, creative commons zero
and just anybody can use them for anything.
I like that.
I kind of like that.
That's a fun idea.
Just royalty-free Andy, yeah.
Just have like 5,000 things that you'll never get claimed for.
I don't know.
Open source Andy.
Do foley for Nosferatu this Halloween.
License it for free for three years
and when those sounds go viral for being free,
people start paying for them.
We'll just be free.
I mean, look, if you're going to buy
a signed baseball for 50 bucks from me,
a lot of you guys,
that's not going to be fucking, you know, you just,
yeah, I gotta give you something, right?
I gotta give you back.
You guys have been getting them, right?
I tried, my signature, I tried to, okay.
So way back in the day, I used to,
and if I was at a convention,
it was actually pretty rare for someone to come up to me
and be like, hey man, can I get a signature?
Be like, yeah, why?
You want my signature?
I just really didn't know what to do.
So a long time ago, I used to just write
in just generic print, German,
and then I would put a bit,
like a little swoosh under the A,
and I did that for a long time.
After a while, I kind of realized,
I was like, that's just the Amazon logo.
I don't want to do that anymore.
It's just, it was the A with the thing.
No.
So then for Dollhouse, I was like,
what if I did like a big swooping J in the 985, right?
I was like, okay, I can do that.
I can consistently do like a J.
It was like a cursive big, like 985.
I was like, yeah, okay.
And then I started doing them for baseball,
and I realized it's really hard to draw on a baseball.
And I know some of you already sent like pictures of,
hey dude, like the J's wicked fucked up on this one.
And I'm just like, oh shit.
And like the J's like kind of goes like this,
and then out and around.
So then I tried to change it a little more.
I was like, okay, what if I add like a little tail to the J
and then the 985?
I don't know.
I'm bad with this kind of stuff.
I don't sign stuff.
I really don't.
That's the best part is your shitty handwriting.
I'm stuck.
It's authentic.
And then I was going to do,
one of them was going to be just like a crack ball.
I was going to draw just fucked up stuff all over it,
just like crazy shit,
just markings and like hieroglyphics or something.
And write like in all capitals, huge across the ball,
you got the crack ball.
But one of you would have gotten it and it's not,
it would have been like, okay, who's,
who got the crack ball?
Because there's only one.
Dude, I could have gotten a better signature
at a little league game.
I don't think you could.
We got robbed at the crack.
No, I hope people are happy with them.
I really do.
Every time I sell anything, I just go like,
oh, this is suck.
People think it's okay.
I hope everything is all right.
I like doing it.
It was fun.
Hope you guys, whoever got one,
you're a scammer.
You know, I will sell you.
I'll tell you right now.
If there was, if anybody ever really,
like genuinely, like not fucking around,
if people were genuinely like,
dude, that he like, I feel like I fucking got scammed.
I got scammed.
And a bunch of people were like,
yeah, dude, we got fucking scammed.
I would be, I would be freaking out.
I'd be like, how do I fix this as fast as possible?
How do I make sure this is fixed immediately?
I would never want anyone to think that I genuinely
was just trying to take their money or something.
I would try to, you know, not scam people.
If people really thought that it was,
oh, wow, dude, this is like kind of fucked up.
I would, I would not sleep until that was fixed,
at least enough.
I hate that idea.
It just, it kind of keeps me up at night sometimes.
It's like, okay, wait, people are buying a bunch of shit.
Okay.
What do they don't like it?
You know what I mean?
I just, it kind of keeps me up sometimes.
Are you going to do the signed playing card?
Hold on a minute.
Are you going to do signed playing cards
for the Mr. Green stream?
Where'd you get that?
Who told you that?
Who told you that was,
that was going to be a Mr. Green stream?
I don't remember anybody ever saying that.
I did.
I don't remember ever saying,
I don't know who told you that,
that I was going to get into
five to $10,000 of prosthetics
to be Mr. Green's doing something.
I mean, why would you get that idea?
Who would, who would tell you that?
I don't think it was me.
Whoever it was, they're in trouble.
Whoever leaked that.
I'm not, I'm not happy about it.
Wink, wink.
That's the next stream.
Okay.
Hey, this is late night.
No one's here.
No one's, this is literally,
it was our, almost our number 10.
It's like 11 o'clock Pacific.
No one's even here right now.
There's 12,000 people here.
Yeah, but there is,
well, there is a lot of people here.
That's a lot of people still here.
I'm not going to announce anything about it yet.
Mr. Green's is going to do a stream
and it should be a lot of fun.
Wait, you said,
you said so.
You said you're going to dress up in a big,
a big fat suit and paint your body green.
And wait, hold on.
You said this after you smoked three joints.
When did I smoke joints on stream?
I did.
Is it going to be this year?
Trying to make it this year.
The hope is that somewhere into December,
this would be happening.
It's going to shove a decade.
You said this during the bug snack stream.
Yeah, but I know it was never real.
It's real now.
All right, let's go.
Let's play. Let's play.
But yeah, I, I'm not going to give any details on it
until I really want to.
But the next big thing to do is Mr. Green's stream.
And just like baseball, you'll know about it.
You won't really know about it until it happens, really.
So it should be fun.
A lot of, a lot of ideas,
a lot of things that I want to do.
Let's see if it works.
Okay, I have 30 grand.
What do I want to do with it?
What are your thoughts on sherbert ice cream?
I love sherbert ice cream.
It's fantastic.
I wish I was in the mood for it more.
I will tell you this.
No, no more leaking.
I just said, all right, that's it.
You're not going to hear anything else.
And now I'm just like, well,
you know what else I want to tell you?
32,000.
This is a 5%.
I want it.
20 grand.
Give it to me.
I'm at 8%.
I still got 10 grand.
All right, let's do it.
Land auction.
Okay, so look, I'm going to,
I'm going to say right in the middle.
That's the idea.
He wants to talk about it so bad.
Nothing will ever match the pain
of having to keep the dollhouse completely under wraps
for almost a full year.
It was so painful.
I want to just scream it every day.
But I think it made that show way more fun.
No more, no more leaking and no more moles.
Okay, not a bad start.
This is right here.
Perfect.
I need to make some cash.
Let's go right side.
I'm not going to upgrade this pipe yet.
It's probably a bad idea.
All right, right here.
All right, let's get some, go left.
Yeah, yeah.
I just don't want this to overflow.
Which it really shouldn't because it's only level, what?
Level two or level one.
Go right.
Once I get about two grand is when I can really start to do some stuff.
Well, I'm not going to do anything yet.
Over a dollar, man.
Okay, so now stay on the right.
There's no reason to stop.
Upgrade the vans.
Okay, let's get it now.
Bulls remind me to upgrade the moles after this.
All right, hold it, hold it.
All right, straight down, which I think I'm just going to do another one.
All right, let's upgrade these.
Okay.
Should I sell holes, moles, moles?
Oh, shit.
This is a huge one, too.
I'll connect this one down there.
67.
That's not up.
That's not terrible.
It's not great either.
Need money, though.
Come on.
71, 69.
Come on, 70, 70 cents.
70 cents.
God damn it.
Okay, okay, okay, okay, okay.
Right, not right side yet.
Yeah, this is a big one.
Let's double drain it.
Okay, double drain incoming moles out here.
That has 90.
I'm doing right side.
Close enough.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Let's do them all.
Just get them all out here.
Okay, well, this can go this way and this can go this way.
All right, sell.
Yeah, is there anything else down here?
What are you going to be for Halloween?
A ninja.
Is it even worth doing this?
Yeah, find some.
The good part about splitting this is
you don't have to upgrade the drill twice, which is good.
Although I know how much it really is left.
Should I upgrade the dowsers?
I feel like I haven't really been doing it at all.
This might be it.
November.
This is probably it.
70.
Yes, yeah, I got it.
Let's get out of here.
Sell it.
All right, is there anything else?
I don't think so.
I mean, I guess I could check here.
I think it's empty.
Zero planning, Andy.
What do you mean?
I got it all.
Yeah, I want zero planning, Andy.
I'm good.
I'm going to get the bonus too.
15 grand.
Oops, sorry.
Also too, you guys have had about 10 hours to hear this.
Is the audio actually better?
Is this mic, is this better?
Are we happy with this?
Is everybody think this is good?
Yeah.
Okay, cool.
Perfect.
It's so much better.
All right, that makes me happy.
Stock auction again.
I don't think I want to participate.
I want more money.
I already have 8% of the shares.
That'd be fine.
I mean, they're all going to be bad, but I'll try this one.
Never mind.
I guess I'll take the terrible one.
This is the end of the desert.
48%?
No, no, no, 4%.
This guy's going to buy it.
That's me.
Hold on.
I can just wait till it gets all the way down.
They don't have any money.
Okay, thanks for the 4%.
I got 12% now.
That's perfect.
That was me up there.
I got money.
I'm in a good spot.
Again, over here.
Pretty big one on the left.
All right.
I can just barely make it.
Need coffee?
Don't drink too much coffee too late, though.
It's actually really...
I didn't have too much caffeine too late.
Really?
Right when the price goes down.
I'm just going to farm this for a second.
Whoa!
Left side.
Get to about two grand.
All right.
There was one over here.
This is a little one, though.
I'm obsessed with the moles.
One there.
All right.
Right side.
Left side.
Now.
You need to go this way.
Straight down.
Can you put your channel on television
so I can watch with my parents out in the living room?
Go get the app.
There's a TV app.
You can put it on TV.
It's on Apple TV.
It's on Xbox.
It's on PlayStation.
You can put it on TV.
All right.
Good find.
Okay.
Stop delivering.
Start storing.
September.
All right.
Get the storage up.
I don't know if there's anything else over here.
It's probably upgraded.
Yep.
Store it.
Store it to the very end.
Here we go.
Check this out.
This is going to be huge.
$1.30 or $40.
Come on.
And not yet.
Not yet.
Oh, it's on the left side.
Hold on.
No, no, no, no.
Not yet.
Nope.
There's no more.
There's definitely no more.
That's a good haul.
Even if I missed it, it's too bad.
I just want to know.
Send a mole over there.
There's nothing else.
All right.
Yeah.
Give me that bonus.
$18,000.
You want to know where the gas is?
I'll drain my moles to sniff it out.
Gas.
Buy my new machinery to use gas to your advantage.
We move it again this time.
We're going to the plains which has the profitable but tricky natural gas.
Nope.
Not yet.
We're using a diamond.
Gas is not worth much if you let it escape through a rig.
Be sure to close valves to direct it.
Before you can sell gas to a company, visit Fred and buy the left link or right link upgrade first.
Oh, Jesus.
Really?
Let me do this first.
All right.
Point me in the direction of a insane.
Oh, that's good.
Right.
Okay.
So right ink.
Right ink.
Upgrade the moles.
What about this though?
Moles will look for gas near every cell they uncover.
Do I need a different thing to upgrade it?
Or do I pull it out?
Why does he look away every time chat erupts?
It's the natural order of my head movement to the screen.
You need the connector for 30k.
What else is available?
Oh.
Okay.
So it's from the bottom.
I don't have enough money.
I could take a loan out.
I'm taking a loan out.
I'm taking out a loan.
Because remember, I got that guy to tell me where the best place was because I gave him a diamond.
And remember, I bought this too.
So if there's gas down there, I want to be able to get it.
We're doing right link because the right one is the one that is at 80 something cents.
All right.
So just don't lose.
I'm not doing the stock.
Unless it's, I mean, why 5%?
No, I'm not doing it.
All right.
So I got enough to go for it.
Wait, I have to do that.
Oh, shit.
I have to do this.
What if they're stupid and they didn't buy it?
I could probably just buy it.
I can't believe it's a 5% share of the company.
I can't believe no one's done this.
You're not going to let me do it, right?
Oh, of course not.
I can't believe that.
I would have bought it.
I just want to take another loan out.
All right.
So he said that this is the place to go.
Right here.
All right.
They don't even care.
I got the insider info.
So there's apparently a shitload of stuff here.
This is probably a huge one.
Okay.
Let's go.
All right.
Let's come on.
Let's do it.
Use a pipeline to transport gas to Wright Inc.
And oh, no, we'll make the oil price more right than ever.
All right.
Let's do it.
Besides just oil, these lands also have gas deposits.
If you drill to them, the gas will escape with high pressure and bring any oil with it as well.
So act cautiously.
Wait, what?
So that's a hazard.
That gas, what does it look like?
It's a good blue, right?
That's a major deposit right here.
Don't go too far so I can't get it.
Right?
Because I could get in trouble here and not be able to cross.
I'm like, yeah, you can't intersect.
Shit.
So I got to make sure there's enough.
There's a path to go this way.
This is a huge deposit too.
We're going to do two here.
Yeah, this is a big one.
In fact, let's go like this because then I'm going to go bang, bang.
Gas.
Holy shit.
That would have been bad.
Go deposit it.
Look at this.
This is perfect.
Companies cannot drill.
What?
Wait, what?
What do you mean?
Left.
Hold on.
I can't connect this to what?
What are you talking about?
Left is 126.
That's fine.
You have to connect your pipe to it.
I do?
Wait, what?
So now this has to go.
So this, what have I done?
Is it okay?
What if I go like this?
Can I connect?
I'm going to connect these two.
I might have just blown this, maybe.
And then, oh, wait, I can do that.
Is this going to work?
Engine gas is now escaping through a rig.
Close the rig to prevent this.
How much is this worth?
What's happening?
Oh, it's a, it's a buff, a buff.
It's like an overheal to your price.
Okay, I get it.
Oh, that's kind of sad.
That was so much money.
What a waste.
What's going on?
At least I understand it now.
Yeah, that's true.
Let's store some of this now.
This is a big one.
Big money on the left here.
Don't let that spill.
All right, pull back from the left.
Pull back from the left.
No reason to do that.
People can go with the right if they want.
20 grand so far.
This is pretty good.
Okay, nice.
Is this even in there?
Is this in?
I feel like it's not sucking anything.
It is, okay.
26 grand.
I'm doing good.
What are these upgrades?
This looks fucking terrible.
This is real.
I just looked over it
and I'm realizing just how bad this looks.
I forgot that people were watching me play
because this is really ugly.
This is supposed to be a mega deposit.
I'm just going to go this way.
Whatever.
Okay, gas.
Almost got it all.
It's okay.
25 grand is pretty good.
I don't think I want to buy another stock auction yet.
28 grand.
Okay, this is for 1%.
You guys can have it.
Who cares?
I'll buy it at one dollar.
If you were a fish, what kind of fish would you be?
Who you are, the dumbest person in the world.
Okay.
Enjoy your 2% or 10, like $9,000.
I'd probably be an electric eel.
Seems like the funnest answer.
Moles will look for gas.
I think that's good.
I'm going to get it.
I paid my loan back, right?
Yeah, I did.
You'd be an ocean sunfish.
Hey, that's kind of cool.
Ocean sunfish?
Okay, do they know that this was great?
Can they see the...
Okay, they can see the same map.
Junk.
All right, now I understand how gas works.
That's what an ocean sunfish looks like.
I thought they were going to be this beautiful orange and yellow and fire.
It's been 10 hours.
It's going to break.
Okay, when a mole smells gas nearby, we'll uncover it for you.
Gas.
Okay, don't touch the gas.
Whoa, is that gas?
I don't know if that's gas or not.
I hope this is not gas.
Is it?
Don't be gas.
All right, nice.
We're good.
All right, hold off.
Hold off.
All right, I need to upgrade this.
Not yet.
Hold on.
Sell it.
Hurry.
There's so much to make on that right side right now.
Thank God.
All right, we're good.
Cool.
All right, I think I'm just going to double this up.
I'm going to start to get crazy here.
All right, gas.
I got to be ready.
Is it going to start to fill up?
Fine.
Both dog shit prices.
I'm not going to do that.
Terrible prices.
Can I get something better than 70 cents, please?
78.
Come on.
That's climbing.
85.
All right, go.
Good haul.
All right, now where is there more of this shit?
Could have done the gas.
I couldn't have done the gas.
I don't have it on the left side.
All right, I need some more moles.
Good.
Yep.
Okay, and this is rock.
Find something over here.
Let's pray that'd be perfect.
You're going to do it.
Go right side.
Anything?
Okay, there's something this way.
There's two gas piles right here.
How big are they?
I just got a diamond.
Nice.
Don't hit the gas.
Jit.
Use the gas.
It has to go this way.
It's all just too far away.
I guess I could put...
Can I connect?
I don't know.
I guess I could connect to here.
Now it's too far away.
Hold off.
Hold off, hold off, hold off.
Left side.
Crazy.
There's so much over here.
I dicked around way too much at the beginning.
Okay, I started on the wrong side.
The left side was so much better.
The right side was terrible.
There was two deposits and then no gas.
That sucked.
Let's get this out of the way.
Another 1% 40 grand.
Imagine clicking on that.
Just build more oil wells.
Yeah, I got to build more of those.
I'll buy it at a dollar.
Ricardo again.
All right, that's fine.
Maybe upgrade the joints.
I could do three.
That seems like amazing.
I think I need this.
I need that.
I can go one, two, three.
The branches just get so much bigger.
All right, save the rest.
That's a good upgrade.
Yeah.
Right here seems like a good idea.
Yeah, that's hot real estate right there.
Come on, dude.
Really?
I don't want that.
All right, I'm good.
All right, I can do three branches now.
I want to take my pants off so bad.
You have no idea.
Just sit here.
You can now connect five pipes to each joint.
Perfect place for gas right there.
This is a big one.
All right, I got to plan this out.
Look at how huge this one is.
So I'm thinking bang, right?
Like right here.
Yeah, so it's going to go bang right here.
Wait, wait.
Okay, so should I go short and then be able to have...
Okay, so listen, should I go...
Just don't go all the way down.
Should I go a little bit down
so then I can connect three to that?
That makes sense, doesn't it?
See what I'm saying?
Go like this and then be able to go one, two, three.
That's not dumb.
So I go like...
I'll go this way, right?
Just kind of one, two, three.
One, two, three.
This is the gas line.
No, I wanted a horse.
Yeah, so that's the gas line.
You know what I'm saying?
This one's going to go this way.
It could be another gas line.
He just wasted a year.
No, I didn't.
I'm good.
Same deal with this.
I don't want to...
Be careful.
All right, it's about to get real.
77 cents is enough.
Start selling.
All right, stop, stop, stop, stop, no, no, no.
Make some moles.
Two people sell.
I need the cash flow.
You know what to do.
Let's go.
Everybody, dollar.
The dollar.
Nice.
All right, back over here.
Right side, 80 cents.
Hope I don't hit any gas.
Shit, there's another one right here.
I need some more horses
and I need another one of these.
For sure.
You know what?
Just so I don't have a problem.
So much gas.
All right, speaking of gas,
I think it's time to hold.
Let's store a bunch of shit.
I'm doing gas
and I'm dumping it onto the right side here
in just a little bit.
Okay, so how am I going to do this?
I'm thinking, so I connect this through here
to there, right?
If I go like that, this.
Okay, so this is what we're doing.
Everybody, shh.
This is going to go like this
and we're going to start to dump.
It's dumb, but who cares?
Wait, I got to be ready.
I got to do this.
I'm not ready to do this now.
Am I ready to do this?
All right, wait, wait, wait, wait, pause the game.
What am I doing?
Okay, this is going to connect.
It's going to, I got to close the valve
because it's going to go.
I have to close this valve.
Close them now.
But wait, hold on.
If the gas comes through here,
then it needs, this one needs to be closed.
But no, this has to be closed.
And that's it.
So if I do this, I'm just going to try it.
Who cares?
Fuck it.
Here we go.
You guys ready?
I fucked it up.
I blew it.
I upgraded the stupid.
Go!
I mean, I blew it really bad,
but I made 27 grand.
I've really fucked it up.
Oh, I could have gone up here.
Is there any more?
I don't know.
I thought I blew it.
No, I got it all.
Okay.
What is that?
Is that a diamond?
I got it all.
You only wasted a little bit.
That wasn't that bad.
Stop spending money on dumb things.
I don't even know what that means though.
Like I'm a dumb person.
Okay, now the stock auction.
This is 4%.
So I'm going to be ready.
I would be at 16% of the company.
All right.
If this goes under 15, I'm doing it.
Shit.
Did he buy his own shares back?
This thing is...
I need more money.
Only 1,100 bucks for this.
I'm going to ask...
Okay.
One diamond.
Yeah, let's do it.
70 cents on the left.
No.
Now it's a loan shit.
Get the left link.
Actually a good idea.
Do I have enough money to...
Okay, I do.
I don't want to go broke though.
I have gas on both sides.
Ooh, really?
Okay, no one is going to go that way.
They're going to think I'm stupid.
Okay.
All right.
Let's do it.
Use a pipeline to transport gas to left inc.
And Kyle will raise the oil price.
Okay.
So let's be smart.
And I'm going to stop fast forwarding.
I feel like it's getting me in trouble.
Gas.
Gas in the middle.
Okay, this is kind of shitty.
There's a lot of gas.
Okay, please tell me there's like a big deposit right here.
Because I could go wham, wham, wham that way and make it like $5 a share.
There's one down here.
Shut up.
Really?
When I sell to the left Twix, the right Twix starts being a better price.
Okay, now stop fast forwarding.
And then I can go wham.
Gas is here.
I could go like that, that.
All right, I got to find something over here.
I get a little bit this way.
55 cents.
Fuck off.
Bullshit.
Better.
Have you people seriously been watching this for 10 and a half hours?
Not this.
Only been doing this for about two and a half.
Okay, I'm just going to go down.
Start.
I think this upgraded.
There's a ton of gas so I could really make like 50 grand if I do this right.
If I plan this correctly.
I need more horses.
All right, this isn't going to be, this is triple now.
Oh boy, easy.
Oh my god.
Okay, it might be time for gas.
But no, it's not.
And what am I talking about?
Dogshit prices.
Give me a break.
Can you not be 30 cents?
Go up.
Seriously, what is this bullshit?
Oh boy, oh boy.
It's gonna break.
Can I have a gas?
Do a rig just for gas.
But when I touch it, doesn't it start going?
I'm going for this.
I'm going to try this.
We'll see if this is a bad idea.
I'm going to go for gas on the left side here in a second.
All right, suck up some more oil.
Okay, here we go.
Okay, it's time.
Let's go.
Stupid.
50.
I got out 50 cents there.
Shit.
I'm going bang, bang, bang.
I have so many silos.
All right, are you guys ready?
This is going to be fucking crazy.
Right side.
It's November.
All right, I got to make this happen now.
Here we go.
Oh, I didn't even connect that.
Oh, come on.
Why do I have to just make 20 grand in the last five seconds?
Just plan it better.
Shit, he's pretending.
I wish that were true.
3%.
I'll do it under 10.
Need to go to bed?
I'm good.
All right, I got to be ready.
Under 10, under 10.
Ricardo, okay, he's actually climbing moles faster.
And I'm getting another diamond.
Close the valve before you drill into the gas.
I know, dude.
It's just like when you're on a timer
and you're a fucking brain slug like me, I get caught up.
Stop being stupid.
I know.
Pause to think.
When I pause to think, I just go, then I forget.
I am going to do this though.
Oh, that's junk.
Okay.
Show me where the best one is.
Oh, okay.
All right.
This one's apparently huge.
Don't bid on that.
I got to make at least 30 or 40 grand this time.
My moles are better.
Good.
All right, that's a big one.
Gas right there.
Okay, let's get this started.
This is perfect.
What's going to do, straight down?
Get the horses out already.
I want to make sure that I already,
I don't get a bunch of bullshit.
Look at how much is over there already.
This is going to be a big head start here.
That's a head start.
Actually, probably the best thing that could happen.
All right, slow down.
Now, silo right here.
That's three.
Okay, two of you start storing.
Gas here, moles.
Get back to work over here.
Got to find something on this side.
Stop selling over there.
Just store it.
Okay, cool.
All right.
So, oh shit, people are just sitting there.
Pause it this way.
I'm going to do some gas.
Okay.
Now, where is it?
All right, stop, stop, stop.
I hope that's not gas.
This here.
Not gas.
Okay, we're good.
Okay.
All right, so this is going to be the gas valve.
There's another one right there.
Yeah, fuck that.
Let's go.
Pick this up.
All right.
Start the flow.
Come on.
Fill it up.
Keep filling it.
Good.
5K.
Let's go.
Keep going.
I might do some.
I got to fill up.
Let's get another one of these.
It's only July.
I'm fine.
I got 10K.
All right.
Start storing it.
Because I want to be able to do a gas run.
Okay, there's more here.
August.
All right.
Okay, okay, okay.
Stop, stop, stop, stop.
Enough, enough, enough, enough.
All right, let's fucking do this.
It's September.
I got a full...
I got five Mega Man tanks full of energy.
I'm going for it.
Here we go.
Almost.
Not yet.
Wait, okay.
What do I do?
Here we go.
All right.
Wait.
I want to close.
What do I want to do?
Close this one.
I want to close this.
Oh, shit.
Pause it.
What do I do?
This is going to go over here.
And then I have to close this, right?
I go over here.
It sucks it up here.
And then I close this one.
And then I'm going to buy a fucking shitload of horses.
I don't even care about the...
I don't care.
Oh, my God.
I'm going to be in trouble.
Here we go.
I got to...
Okay.
I'm sure you could use a bit more oil storage capacity.
Guess what?
I've invented something for that.
You do.
A super silo?
I don't have enough.
Oh, man.
Okay.
I actually really need that.
It's over 2% on a whole lot.
Take the loan.
I'm scared of the loan because if I take the loan...
Let's say I take like 10 to 20 grand.
I have to make sure I can pay it.
Percent.
I have to buy the next one no matter what it is.
All right.
Should I just take like a $10,000 loan?
I have to make a big, big, big, big, big one.
This counts.
I actually have to get this right.
Okay.
That's a good start.
Really good start.
No gas yet, though.
Gas down here.
We put this here.
Let's go like this.
Gas can grab this way.
Not looking good.
Make some money.
This is going to go over here.
This one's going to go down.
No, it's not.
There's no reason to do that right now.
I know the omega silo.
The omega silo is going to go over here.
I just wanted to have more storage.
Good start.
Come on.
Keep it going.
That's a triple right now.
Really good start.
Come on.
Phenomenal start.
All right.
Actually phenomenal start.
Start storing.
Let's go straight down.
Okay.
Don't sell anything.
Hold it for another few minutes.
Go this way.
Then go this way.
Some moles out.
Okay.
That ain't going anywhere.
Nothing else down here?
I need some more moles.
Get over there.
Pick that shit out.
There has to be something over there.
I don't need money.
Gas over there.
Okay.
Right in the middle.
Start selling.
I need the money.
That was a good time to do it.
All right.
Perfect.
13k.
Now I don't know if there's anything else over here.
I'm going to go this way.
August.
Okay.
Good time.
Dumb ass.
I'm just kidding.
I'm not stupid.
Gas is here.
There's gas here too.
Left idiot.
I don't have any oil.
Okay.
This is pumping now.
Store it.
I'm getting ready for a gas run.
Gas run coming up on the right side.
It's October.
Okay.
Time for a gas run.
Is there any more shit left?
Oh my God.
I got to do a gas run now.
Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go.
What?
I think I got it.
I'm good.
I think there might be something here.
Or like down here.
But I think I got most of it.
One tiny little thing.
I paid the debt back.
All right.
I got 20 grand.
I'm consistently making more money than all of them.
But I have to win this auction.
2%.
I have to buy it.
Stupid.
I was supposed to click.
I just couldn't do it.
I couldn't pull the trigger.
Right.
Okay.
Yep.
92 cents on the right side.
That's a huge deal.
Especially if there's gas.
Somebody got screwed.
Did I get scammed?
Okay.
No, we're good.
Thank God.
Close the well before the gas.
You're right.
The right side is not ever going below 91, 92, whatever it was.
That's a good place for gas.
All right.
Come on, man.
This is going to be huge.
This is going to be a big deal.
Go like this.
I'm going to go wham, wham, wham.
I'm going to prepare the gas lane first.
You know what I'm saying?
Let's go.
Beautiful.
That's never going to go below 92.
Good start.
Very good start.
Okay.
I need a silo.
Yep.
It's going to go.
It's going to be an Omega silo going right here.
Okay.
Now it's time.
Yes.
I went overboard, but it's all right.
July, we're good.
Timing's fine.
There's nothing over here.
Hold on a second.
Did you hear this?
That was kind of...
All right.
I almost did it.
Please.
Please store it, you dummy.
It's $1.20.
It's $1.27 right now.
Now we store it.
Is there any more?
We're empty.
November?
Always $25,000.
Your camera looks like found footage.
Well, you just found it.
You're here now, aren't you?
All right.
This is very...
This is important.
I have to get this.
I've got the most money.
This is 6%.
I have to buy it.
I'm going to buy it probably around right now.
Like in one, two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight, nine, ten.
Fine.
Six percent.
I'm at 18%.
I can afford the horses though,
but I haven't really been using them that much.
Bright Ink is never going under $1.01.
All right.
Give me something good here.
Where?
I don't know.
This is right next to a $24,000 though.
That might suck.
Maybe right here.
Top middle.
This is probably the safest place that are over here.
It's not a shitty one.
We really want to uncover right because
that's where we're going to spend most of the time.
Gas.
Two gases.
Okay.
I could make up literally everything right now.
This is going to be a huge fucking deal.
Okay.
This is a big deal.
Here we go.
Let me plan this.
If I go here, I can go one.
I need to take a loan out.
Gas.
Here's the plan.
The plan is to go here and then here.
And that's going to, I mean, you could have a million dollars.
All right.
Maybe we should start the storage process now.
Whoa, half and half.
So I'm going to use store because I need to have enough for the gas.
11 hours.
Oh shit.
Nice.
Okay.
Should I store now in June?
Let's fill up one of these.
Let's fill the super silo up.
Perfect.
Dude, gas.
Three gases.
It's August.
All right.
I got to be ready.
Store everything.
It's August.
Okay.
Here we go.
All right.
So now this is almost sucked up.
Two super silos.
I got one, two, three gases.
You're going to fuck it up?
All right.
Let's fucking go.
You ready?
I've got two months to do this.
I got two super silos full of fucking stuff.
All right.
It's November.
Here we go.
Pause it.
So this is going this way.
It sucks up here.
Just close this.
This one's going to go this way.
Close this.
Fuck it.
Whatever.
Who cares?
This is going to come up here.
I think this is correct.
Just close the rig.
Don't do anything else.
Just close the top and yolo it.
Just close the rig.
Don't do anything else.
Just close this.
All you have to do is close the rig.
That's it.
My God.
Oh, clean 50K.
That's a clean 50K right there.
Oh, that feels good.
I'm good to go.
I don't think there's any more oil.
Actually, there might be one over here.
One right here.
But I'll take 50,000.
I don't care.
All right.
I'm way ahead now.
Bank's going to be looking to me.
Get loaned some money.
All right.
I was a little more efficient this year.
My pipes were not $38,000.
They were just $3,800.
Our mole expenses obviously are pretty good.
Sounds good.
3%.
Not unless it comes way down here.
I'm pretty far ahead.
Ricardo's the only one that I'm worried about.
I might just snipe it from him.
If it goes underneath 20.
That's 3% more.
About 21%.
All right.
I'm 10% higher than Ricardo.
That's all I care about.
Should I finish some of this stuff?
Hold on.
Longer timer.
I think I need it.
But what else can I do?
Oh, 79 cents.
He's never going to do scanner.
Expense too expensive.
I'm going to hold on to the money.
Right here or right here?
Everyone's going to go for right here.
Going this way.
Dickhead.
Thanks to the timer upgrade,
rigs will now take longer before they spill over.
Good.
Right side's looking pretty juicy.
There's nothing over on the left side.
Nothing.
That's good for me, I guess.
Gas are already right there.
Hold off.
Mega silo going to go over here.
Store it for now.
Any more horses.
Geez, 134.
Are you kidding me?
What's going on here?
What's going on with these prices?
Jesus.
Is there really nothing over on the left side?
Okay, this one's something right there.
All right.
Silo time.
85 cents over there.
Sell.
That's a lot of money.
Start the storage process.
Left side.
Yeah, sell it on the left side.
Why not?
Okay, I got 11 grand.
Start storing two omega silos.
I'm happy with that.
Hit the right side.
Okay, fine.
It's a sure thing.
All right.
I need more.
I'm out of juice here.
I'm out of juice.
Where do I go?
Gas.
It's blanked so hard.
Okay, wait a minute.
It's December.
We're good.
It's a little scary, but we're fine.
21%.
All right.
We're almost at the last part.
3% again.
So wait, there's only 100% of the shares are being sold.
So let me take inventory here because I think I could.
So I could seal the win, couldn't I?
With a certain percentage.
All right, Ricardo got it.
21.
When is it mathematically not possible for either one of these to win?
I just have to get to 51.
Oh, what if I can't get to 51?
20, 30, 31, 35.
So 42% of the shares are out right now.
You land before stock.
Why?
You need a majority or a plurality.
They have, it's less money each.
Really?
Okay, I didn't know that.
Interesting.
All right, what do you got?
80 cents left ink.
I think it's worth it.
More horses.
Timer three.
No, okay.
So I have more horses now.
All right, there's only two more rounds in this.
Then where's the home stretch?
You know what?
I'm going to...
Yeah, I'm bidding you on here.
That's 38.
This might be 40.
Yeah, this is mine.
Fuck all of you.
Fine.
There's nothing in there.
You're going to find an old shoe.
25 wagons.
Oh, left side was the one that's going to be good for what we're trying to do, right?
Left side is can't go under a certain amount.
Diamond.
I want to see more.
Big one over there.
All right, let's just get some money.
Okay.
Come on, man.
Hurry up.
150.
Come on.
You're killing me here.
Thank you.
Don't shut that valve off.
Nothing.
Should I get some more moles?
Yeah.
Gas.
Good.
Okay.
I can do a double gas on the left, which would be awesome.
Shit.
I mean, it was crazy what I just did, but whatever.
August.
All right, we're good.
Not enough oil to really do a silo.
I might just do gas now.
I'm doing gas now.
It's September, man.
It's September already.
I'm doing gas now.
Let's go.
Oh, there's a...
Whatever.
There's a rock here.
That's fine.
I can do it again.
Not bad considering.
I'll be honest.
Is there any more oil?
There is down here.
I want a thousand bucks.
One little spot left, but I got the thousand.
11 and a half hours.
Damn.
This is what?
Almost the second longest stream ever.
Getting there.
Okay.
Land auction first.
The last one here.
Did Ricardo literally have like no money there?
I'll go here.
I'll take the terrible one.
That's okay.
2% 40.
All right.
Ricardo's broke.
Can I buy him out?
Okay.
If Blanche buys this, I don't care.
It's nothing.
But if it does go below 10 grand, I'm sniping it
because Ricardo's going to try to get it.
I'll go for a snipe.
Sorry.
Blanche, you have 2%.
Congratulations.
I'm saving money.
There's no reason to do anything crazy.
This is one of the shittiest plots.
Not bad.
Not bad gas placement.
Just need a loan.
This one's going to have nothing in it.
It's fine.
Okay.
Gas right here.
This might be gas over here too.
I don't really care though.
Nice.
All right.
That was a good find.
Horses are good.
Take some money for a little bit.
If I leave here with 10 grand, I'm fine.
Okay.
Now, get some mole action here.
I'm good.
Why you?
Why?
Looking good.
I got three gases here.
Okay.
Three gases.
Sell a little bit.
September.
It's almost time to activate the gas.
Build a silo up for another month.
All right.
I want one full silo.
And then I'm just grabbing gas.
I'm going to grab gas everywhere.
Okay.
Here we go.
Let's just do it.
Don't go yet.
Pretty good.
Pretty good for Africa.
Pretty good considering.
Oh my god.
That was a huge one.
I didn't see it.
Whatever.
Pretty good considering.
What did I say?
I want a 10 grand from that.
That'll be fine.
I would be totally happy with 10 grand.
My factory is new equipment on offer
to increase the size of gas pockets.
What?
Winter is coming.
We're moving to the snow area.
At a smaller gas pockets.
But there's a way to make them bigger.
All right.
This is it.
75 cents.
86 cents on the right side.
That's good.
I'm going to take it.
We're going to get the best plot in the game.
So I got to be prepared for this.
Thermal.
Activate all joints in a pipeline that encircles gas.
This will cause the gas to expand.
I don't know if we're going to do that.
Drilling faster.
Yeah, that's huge.
Drill faster.
It takes so goddamn long.
I might take a loan out for this.
All right.
Well, apparently this is it.
This is probably this is one of the best ones.
Two percent.
Just go all in on the first run.
That's the plan.
Daisy.
Really?
I was waiting for it to get whatever.
Let's do it.
I got to go all in.
This is apparently one of the best plots
in the entire video game.
So I got to get this right.
Holy shit.
Look at that right side.
What side is never going to go under?
Which one is it?
Right side?
That's awesome if that's true.
Right side.
Perfect.
Look at how big this is.
I got to go double here.
Should I connect these?
Just connect them.
Where is that?
That idea.
No, just go right in.
I'm just going to go right in.
I could run.
I could absolutely run away with it.
Now, forget about the right side.
The left side, I mean.
Okay.
All right.
I don't see any gas.
A little bit of gas here.
Already at 16K and it's June.
Start storing.
It's only July.
We're good.
It's August.
Oh, okay.
Gas time.
Gas on the right side or left side.
It doesn't matter.
Um, hold on.
What side?
Right side, I think.
Shit.
What side?
What do I do?
I'm going to go.
All right.
I have no way to put anything.
All right, all right, all right.
Slow down.
Um, okay.
So 38 cents.
Not doing that yet.
You can't be serious.
It's fine.
I got to look at this.
I'm untouchable right now.
Almost 100K.
And the diamond.
We're doing that again.
81 cents on left.
You think it's worth it?
Yeah.
Anything over 80 I think is worth it.
That's mine.
I'm willing to pay at least 10 grand for this.
Sorry, Daisy.
Thank you.
Everyone's broke.
Look at how broke everybody is.
Four percent.
I can just sit here and wait.
All right.
I think I'm comfortable taking four percent
when this goes to 20K just to seal it.
Right before 20K.
25 percent.
And drilling speed.
I can do drilling speed.
I could do...
Finally get the scanner.
All right.
I got the scanner.
I'm going to upgrade the scanner size twice.
This thing better be worth it.
Try our new scanner.
Click the scanner icon.
Point your mouse cursor in the ground.
Wait until the size is right
and then click the reveal area.
What side do I want to be on?
Left?
What happened?
I just...
It's cost...
Oh, okay.
Left side, right?
Are you kidding me?
It's only 100 bucks to start that.
All right.
I got more horses.
I'm going to start to overflow a little flow here.
No, guys.
Okay.
I'm good.
Start some storage here.
Right side.
No.
Oh, my God.
This thing is fucking crazy.
There's no gas in this level.
Why did I buy those upgrades?
What was the point of that?
Sell.
Boy, that goes down.
Does rock crush?
Store, store, store, store, store, store, store, store, store.
The scanner is broken.
It's so good.
Gas.
All right.
What about down here?
We got double gas down here.
I need another omega silo
and we're going to get ready for the December.
Okay.
Don't sell anything.
Store only.
Forever.
Here's one.
We're going to go wham, wham and go to bed.
I'll go to bed when I break my streaming world record.
This is it over here.
All right.
This is it.
I got to focus on here.
There's three gases.
There's one, two, three.
All right.
Prepare.
September.
Don't drop down to 20 cents.
Oh, my God.
What a disaster.
I can ride this out till November.
Okay.
Here we go.
Was that $75,000?
$65,000.
Oh, I didn't get it all.
Shit.
Oops.
I forgot it was closed.
It's all right.
I'll take $63,000.
What am I over $100,000?
All right.
I'm on track to beat the game for sure.
Do I have any more diamonds?
All right.
Yeah, I'm $73,000.
Everybody wants this one.
Do you think this one here?
Which one?
Down here?
I'm going to save this one.
This is probably safe.
Or this one here.
Left up like this one.
Right of $73,000.
This like up here.
That's too good.
That's close to $34,000 though.
That could be scary.
That could actually be scary.
What's wrong with my elbow?
What is that?
Oh, it's resting.
Oh, it's because I'm resting.
It's fine.
I'm fine.
It doesn't hurt.
It's fine.
It's a rash.
It's from sitting leaning for an entire episode of this game.
I'm all right.
I'm scared to go to the top right.
Because oh, because you can't see.
There's a $34,000 right here.
That's scary.
I think I'm going to go right here.
Everyone wants the top shit.
That's fine.
I'll be fine with $60,000.
I'm way ahead.
Uh, herd size.
40 horses?
I don't think I need that.
Oh, yes.
Right Inc.
98 cents.
Can't go below it.
Perfect.
All right.
$64,000.
This is for 6%.
I got to buy this.
All right.
6%.
I'm going to pull the trigger right now.
I need, I'm going to do it.
I'm at 31.
I have tons of money.
I'm at 31%.
I cannot risk, um, anybody else getting that.
Especially you because that you'd be at 16.
All right.
I'm good now.
You look tired.
Um, I would.
I mean, I'm a little, a little drained.
I'm fine though.
I wouldn't say I'm tired.
Okay.
Let's make sure I don't blow this, uh, right side.
Not great.
Let's get some moles.
Okay.
We're going to go right.
There's a lot in the middle.
All right.
We're going to go right here and I'm going to go.
Wham.
Start getting some cash, please.
Come on.
I'm on.
Okay.
That's good.
Let's upgrade.
Ready?
Get another horse.
Staying on the right side.
I'm not, I don't care about left.
It's going to start to get funky here.
Look at that money rolling in and what I want to see.
It's all upgraded all the way.
All right.
Now let's do scan over here.
Look at the gas now.
Wow.
All right.
Holy shit.
Time for the big money.
Time to begin storing.
All right.
We're in August.
Fill those tanks.
September.
Fill them up.
All right.
Do I even do the gas?
There's only one gas here.
Is it really only one gas?
It's all right.
It might be one here.
Shit.
Wait.
Son of a gun.
Who needs the gas?
All right.
Let's go.
I have a gas.
Still on the left side.
Left side.
Go to left side.
All of you change it.
Right side.
We're good.
40,000.
I got everything.
I'll get the bonuses.
All of it.
3k.
At least you still got it all sold.
Yeah.
This is in the bag by the way.
There's no way.
I don't think I can lose.
This is too weird for me.
I don't think I even want it.
Do the super gas.
Thermal could be mega OP.
I'll try it.
I want to make sure I have enough money to not care.
I have 80,000.
I want to make sure I'm not going to buy anything.
60k.
That's...
No.
That's too much.
84 on the right side.
Sure.
I'll do speed three though.
Because the drill can go so fast I think.
Six percent.
Uh-oh.
You're not going to spend literally your entire net worth on this.
But you might.
I'm almost there.
Elbow.
I'm telling you it's also because the camera is set up a certain way.
Stop playing fart simulator.
Are you really saying this is a fart simulator game?
Start.
Good start Andy.
There's gas down here.
I'm begging you.
I don't know what you're begging me.
All right.
This is super drill now.
So now I'm going to only...
I'm going to use this thing, right?
Let's go over here.
I think that's gas.
Very nice.
Is it efficient if I put one of these things here and connect it?
Or is there any reason to do that?
Should I put one like another one and connect it here?
Would it pump faster?
Or no?
No.
Yes.
Left.
No, I don't care about left.
No, we're good.
We're good.
120.
I don't know.
I don't care.
Oh yeah.
So it's August.
We're good.
What?
Let's go this way.
All right.
Let's go.
Why is he sweating so much?
I've been obviously in the same chair for 12 hours, dude.
I'm not...
No, my hair just went down.
You're fine.
I'm fine.
You're going to be fine.
November.
I'm not going to fill that.
That's not going to happen.
Bottleneck Billy.
I just need to...
Whatever.
Where's the gas?
Bottleneck Billy.
I made it with 17k.
Okay.
So that's not efficient.
It's fine.
I got money.
Uh-oh.
8k for this?
God, dude.
10k?
She's smart.
I'm going up here.
This is going to be like probably 50.
All right.
I have to make sure I...
This is for 4%.
Okay.
Spend...
Do it now.
Spend all your money.
You can afford it.
Buy it right now.
Buy it.
Yeah, good.
$27,000.
I have 37%.
You'll never match my share count.
That's fine.
By the way, don't ever forget who vetoed the diet soda machine.
This guy.
Oh, you voted for that?
Yeah, we're going to have a diet soda machine.
We're going to have diet...
No.
I put my 3,700,000 shares.
I vetoed that.
12-hour Andy?
Yep.
What am I with?
All right.
I see gas right there.
Give me a loan.
I'll pay it back.
It's so easy to pay back.
All right.
I'm not going to be a bottleneck Barry.
Shut up.
Pow.
Okay.
Fill up that silo.
Now.
Canning.
Oh, there's no more.
Start filling it up.
Nothing.
Really?
This ones suck.
Not even worth getting that fucking gas.
Look at that.
Not even worth it.
I'm just going to sell, man.
It's not worth it.
There's nothing else.
Unless there's something right here.
Then I got to start selling.
What a terrible map.
What?
All right.
Just store until I get a good return potential here.
Left side looking pretty good.
Everybody go.
Left side.
Good.
Very good.
And I'm going to end early.
Look at how shitty this was.
Falling off.
The race for the majority of the stocks is getting exciting.
Remember that the first person with 50 plus percent becomes the new mayor.
Show me where a good one is.
Yeah.
No shit.
It's going to be that one.
Why did I give this guy a diamond?
Who has the most money?
Somebody outbid me on that.
Oh my god.
You idiot.
$12,000.
I'm just going to go steal this from you.
I think.
Who?
Everyone's snoozing on the left side.
57, 65, 59.
You kidding me?
I just screwed you.
You just got screwed.
Let's go.
8%.
I got to lock it in.
I got to lock it in right now.
I'm going to lock it in right now.
One, two, three.
45%.
I'm almost the mayor of the city.
It's going to be close.
And this is probably a really good spot.
Let's go.
Five more percent and I win.
That's bad.
It's actually really terrible.
I'm going to take a loan out.
Okay.
This is not bad.
Let's get some gophers.
It's all in the middle.
We're going to stay on the left side.
All it's all in the middle.
It's all right here.
Go somewhere with it.
I just sounded so angry.
We're going straight down from here.
How do I cancel that?
Cancel, cancel, cancel, cancel, cancel, cancel, cancel, cancel.
It's not serious.
It is because I don't want to lose the game.
I'm about to beat the game.
Bottleneck Billy.
This isn't it's not that bad, is it?
Fill it up.
It's already gone.
It's already worse.
Oh, my fucking God.
I didn't I didn't even pay attention.
I think that's it.
I think all the resources are gone.
I have to drain this.
Drain it, drain it, drain it already.
All right.
Are we at zero?
All the resources are gone, right?
Oh, fuck you.
He told me about that spot.
It's my secret place.
I win the game if I do this.
I have to make some money.
Could I have just taken out a loan of like 50 grand
and just been the mayor?
Oh, shit.
This is really bad.
All right.
This better hopefully chat was right.
I'm not going to blow like two grand with the scanner.
Seems pretty promising so far right in the middle here.
Seems pretty promising right off the bat.
Two big ones.
And a gas right there.
Don't overflow.
Not on me now.
Store.
I'll take the diamond.
All right.
This is all right.
I'm just going to go down from here.
Keep this one running.
A whole lot of nothing.
I need some money.
All right.
11 grand.
Actually, everyone keeps selling
because I need I need the cash bad.
Place is dry, guys.
Place is dry, man.
Place is dry.
Guys, place is dry.
Right, right.
What do you mean right?
This place is dry, man.
There ain't nothing here.
Sell right.
There's nothing else to sell.
There's nothing else.
Sell right.
The oil is gone.
This place was junk.
I got 40k.
All right.
I am in a position to get that.
Hold on.
71 cents on left side.
Not enough.
80 cents on right side.
No.
This is really okay.
They're going to think I'm stupid.
That's fine.
I got 34k.
Four percent.
All right.
I fucked up.
I clicked a little too late.
The Patriots just got like three safeties in a row.
That was that reaction.
Like Tom Brady fumbled the ball 15 times in the first quarter.
That's like what that is.
That's what I just did.
All right.
No scanning.
This is apparent.
This might be a good one.
We're doing gophers.
It's going to be the big one.
I see gas over here.
I'll take a loan.
I don't fucking care.
No.
I don't want to go in there yet.
I don't know.
Okay.
So of course.
This one sucks.
I know it does.
This is going to be two or three little dumps.
And that's it.
Start storing.
All right.
I need to make a move here.
Scan.
Is there anything down here that I can get over here?
Oh my god.
They look at all this gas but this place sucks.
It's already June.
I don't have shit.
There's three gases though.
This place is ass.
This store.
There's no reason to do this right now.
Just store and wait for the big thing at the end.
This place is absolute ass.
Fill up this silo.
Look at how terrible this is.
I bet you this is 15.
It's probably 10.
This shit's probably five.
It's going to be the lowest of the whole game.
I should have just bid another five grand
and taken it from that guy.
That might have lost me the game.
I may have just lost me the whole game.
All right.
Let's go.
Here we go.
This way.
It's time to open up the gas.
What are you talking about?
It's 21.
It's still bad.
I have to win this auction.
Whatever it is.
I need five percent.
Okay.
I'm just kidding.
I won the game.
I just won the game.
I'm at 50 percent.
I own the company.
You're fired.
You're all fired.
And by the way, I'm taking a vacation.
I win.
It's 51.
No, it's not.
He said 50.
What are you talking about?
It's gonna be a good one.
Oh, yeah.
This is a big one.
Let's go double here.
Oh, shit.
This is gonna be the big one.
I know it.
There's two huge veins right here.
Left.
I see like, I just have a meteor just hit the earth.
There's nothing even over here.
Really?
What the fuck?
Nothing.
I think this actually might be it.
Oh, there's a little one down there.
Dude, it's empty.
Forget about the gas.
I just need over like 30k or 20k and I win the game.
Yeah, this is it, man.
That's it.
30k.
I'll take it.
Unless there's something over here.
No, no way.
30k is enough for me.
That's fine.
Let's just check.
It's only August.
I don't think so.
No, that's it.
I'm out.
Yeah.
This is diamond right there.
All right.
25,000.
That puts me at 28k.
Do I not own the company yet?
I only have two more rounds left.
I don't own the company?
What were you doing all game?
All right.
I'm just going to try to bank money.
I'm going to try to bank money.
That's all that matters right at this very moment.
Only two rounds.
Diamond.
Hurry up.
Get some selling.
All right.
Store.
Sell on the right side.
I need a little bit of cash.
Actually sell everything over there.
Sell everything.
Got a buck.
Okay.
Hold off.
I'm going to do double super silo over here.
Junk.
Is it worth it?
Don't tell me that wasn't worth it.
Was.
I think it's empty now.
Let's check.
I have 32 grand.
This is the final round.
This is it.
I have to win this auction.
All right.
She's going to buy it.
Oh my god Blanche.
Blanche.
You're out of the game already.
Don't do that.
You don't land.
Okay.
I'm sorry.
But like you landed on like park place in Monopoly.
You have two random ass properties.
I have boardwalk.
And I also own monopolies.
I own three monopolies.
The other person over here.
My friend over here.
Has three monopolies.
And you just took park place.
And you just won't concede the game.
And now you just like ruined it for me.
I just got blocked.
Yeah.
It's I hate that.
It's like the three of us playing.
You have like 30 bucks after buying park place.
Now don't throw.
I can probably still win.
There's probably one more auction.
Drink some water dude.
I drank like 150 ounces of water over the last 12 hours.
All right.
This is dog shit.
It's absolutely terrible.
But I just I got to make a little bit of cash.
It's so bad.
I'm just trying to make some at least a little bit of money.
Check far right for oil.
I think so.
There is gas over here.
But I don't think I can.
I'm not going to be able to get enough.
I don't think.
I just figured out that you can go like this with the mouse scroll.
I've been like.
That might be.
Actually, I don't care.
Yes, 10 grand and I get the bonuses.
Very nice.
All right.
11 grand.
What does that put me at?
41.
What happened to um what happened to Blanche?
Oh yeah right.
Blanche you you bought park place and then you two or three turns later got up to go
to the bathroom and get a drink and then started talking to somebody in the hallway
at whatever family get together or at.
And you never come back and sit down at the table and then you sit on the couch
and the TV is on and then we just kind of say let's stop playing.
I guess it's over.
The game's over.
It's a tie plus two farming you know.
All right.
So do I win?
That was it folks.
I'm out of land.
Now let's see who would become the new mayor.
Did I actually not do it?
There is no winner yet.
This means the stockholder with the smallest share and the least money
in case of a draw will have to go.
But Blanche will have to pack up and leave and we will auction off their 11 percent shares.
Meet me at the stock auction to decide who gets the remaining 11 percent of the stock.
Oh I thought I was trying to take out like a hundred thousand dollar loan.
Hey.
Oh do you want it?
Hey hey oh hey Ricardo you want it?
Hey Ricardo you want it?
All right.
I'm gonna I'll get Ricardo do you want you wanted some shares?
I'm the mayor.
Great job you've secured more than half of the town's shares.
You've won the campaign and you'll be the new mayor.
I've got something special for you as a reward.
Meet me at the town hall.
What do you mean land auction?
What is this?
I have a special present for you.
See that island over there?
It's yours to mine.
We're done.
Let's go back outside.
Private island?
Mine?
Serious?
Are you ready for your final challenge?
Pilo.
Oh my god.
Hurry hurry.
That's 100.
I'm gonna break the counter.
I can't count that high.
Dude I can't count this high.
I'm gonna break the counter.
What?
105?
Did I win?
Who cares?
110?
I made a hundred thousand.
He's tripping.
Congratulations.
You've won the game.
You can now play turmoil on expert mode.
Where the characters have special powers and the competition is tougher.
Give it a try.
Great job.
You've worked like a horse.
You get some horseshoes.
Me and the moles are very happy for you.
Party time.
I'm sure you'll buy everyone around.
Well done.
I'm sure you'll make almost as good a mayor as me.
My hat is off to you in your 24-carat oil mining performance.
Your performance was even stronger than my biceps.
I'm gonna miss our trips together.
Before you go, test your skills in expert mode.
Pay a final visit to my bank to check out the overall statistics of your campaign.
Oh, okay.
That's interesting.
Let's check it out.
Oh, not one million.
So close.
All these goddamn blockbuster late fees that screwed everything up.
I would have had over a million.
Sorry.
Graphs not available.
707,000 barrels sold.
761,000 earned.
Average price of $1.08 per barrel.
That's pretty good.
110 per barrel on the right.
I think this is pretty good.
That's actually pretty good.
Right side.
Oh, right Twix ended up winning.
I went.
That's funny.
Not by very much though.
What's the...
Oh, this is total.
You've streamed longer than the viewer count.
That's funny.
All right.
This is interesting.
Poor dowsers.
I didn't do...
I didn't...
Okay, after the tutorial zone, I didn't buy them ever again.
What was the thing I spent the most money on besides pipes?
Pipe upgrades?
Pipes?
I think I feel like I did that a little less ideal than I could have.
Rigs?
Valve usage?
Half of those were mistakes.
Moles?
I thought that would be more.
I spent more money on moles than silos.
That's kind of crazy.
I spam so many moles.
Screenshot.
Oh, cool.
What's the thing I spent the least on besides dowsers?
Tier 3 silo upgrade?
Valve usage?
Pretty good.
Cool.
Really cool.
That was awesome.
That was such a fun game.
And I think there's DLC.
Maybe I'll play the DLC another time.
Stream is not over yet.
What's the countdown to beat the old record?
13 and what?
About a half an hour.
Dude, I got to beat the old record.
What does the DLC even look like?
How do I get there?
Start a new campaign.
Okay.
Heat is on.
I just want to see.
Lots of oil.
New area.
I just want to see.
Welcome to my town.
I'm the mayor here.
Is this book, is it me?
What happened to me?
Holy shit.
Wow.
Okay.
Yeah, I just wanted to look.
Start with 200 grand.
Well, that's a lot of content.
That's cool.
Yeah, they're all, we all start with like 200,000.
Okay.
Yeah.
No, I'm not doing it.
All right.
What can we do for like 20, 30 minutes?
That was a very, very enjoyable experience.
What do we got here?
No, I'm not doing a tier list.
Not now.
20 minutes till dawn?
Not a bad idea.
Yeah, we'll go back to that.
Although that's a little intense.
Is that too intense?
Maybe not.
I think I can just probably sit there with my mouth open.
Let's try it.
Let's see if I can do it.
That was really cool though.
What a great game.