Alright, let me make sure the stuff for the sponsor segment is ready.
By the way, oh, I gotta think of a good title. What should I title this? What should I title this?
There are drops gonna be on, by the way. If you want to potentially get access to multiverses,
by the way, the open beta, I believe is the 26th, do an apology video for being wrong about Ant-Man.
I already said I'm sorry. I already apologized. Alright, let's go. I gotta change the title to
something. What? I gotta think of a good, give me a good grabbable title. Something that I can,
something that's gonna grab people. You know what I mean? Let me make sure that's there. Hey,
can you guys confirm that the images in the bottom of the stream? Yeah, there it is. Alright, cool.
It's there. This should be a chat bot too. I can't believe you rides bugs. I never, I can't believe
it. Alright, so I cannot wait. I didn't practice that much off stream, by the way, but I will do
my best. Title, what's a good title? Multiverses. Okay, give me one more second. Rating the best
bugs and being the best bugs bunny player later. Oh, that's not gonna work. Alright, how about,
I can put my camera back on so you guys don't all freak out. That's better. Okay, how about,
how about, let's go for it. What do I put here? I don't know what to do. What, what's a good,
I need to get a good title. How about bugs in it up? How about bugging out? No, bugs Andy. Alright,
how about, let's go with, what should I do for, I gotta think, I have to think of a good title
in the next 10 seconds. Okay, how about, we'll just do back in the multi, back in multiverses.
Let's go. That sucks. Back, back in multiverses, bugs Andy. No, back in multiverses. Bugs, bugs,
bugs, bugs, bugs, bugs. That's good. How about I say drops enabled as well. That looks good. Alright,
let's fucking freaking go. Let's freaking go. Let's freaking go. Let's freaking go.
I don't think that's a problem. I don't think that's a problem.
Are you guys ready? Why's my face came so huge? Alright. Alright, I'm ready. Don't quit. We're
gonna do teams. I practiced a tiny bit. This is a sponsored stream by the way. Wait, what cross
platform? Yeah, that's fine. I'm so ready for this. But thank you. Thank you to Warner Brothers
Interactive. Seriously, sponsoring the stream. Drops are enabled. If you have drops on,
keep it on. If you watch for an hour, that's how you get access to the game.
By the skin? This is by the way, this is why I love this shit. Cross platform, cross progression,
PC, Xbox, PlayStation. You can play with each other. You can cross progression. It's fucking
awesome. Am I going? Oh, yeah. Let's go. Operation rabbit. Yeah, mods. Keep it on the bot.
There should be a chat bot. Yeah, I have drops enabled right now. Alright, me and Steven Universe
versus Shaggy and Garnet. I don't I think I'm level one. So all progression will carry over
by the way. Yes, it will. I don't think I think you guys are not. I think you guys are not ready
for how well I'm thinking I'm going to do here. Check it out. Oh, by the way, what's that? Oh,
excuse me. Bingo. That's right. Take a look at that. I thought it was the other character
for a second. I got to remember the controls and everything. All right. Keep it together. Keep
it together. We got it. We got it. Oh, it's gonna be a double. See you later. Come on. Come on,
Steve. Come on, Steve. I'm going under, going under, going under. Do it. Yeah, I see. What is
that? It's all good. We're good. We're good. We got the advantage. We're good. Nice job, Steve.
Damn, this might hurt. I'm all right. Sorry. I have to probably just peek the mic.
Multi-versus. Open beta on July 26th. Where are you? That was weird. Drop it.
See you. That's it, right? Trevor, you can't play video games.
Gee, you stinker. I got to tell you something. Let's go. I said this before. I'm going to say
it again. The net code in this game is unbelievable. It feels fantastic to play this game. You heard me
say this already. Everything feels one to one. One to one. A lot of times when I've ever tried
to play a fighting game like this or anything like this, hitting X and waiting 0.3 seconds
X. X. I can't do it. The net code is amazing. I don't know what they did or how they did it,
but seriously, it's so good. Yeah, no, that's it. That is my honest to goodness opinion.
Rollback net code. Yeah. And man, it's good. So from my understanding, I didn't know this before,
this game is supposed to be played with teams. Each character has, from my understanding,
different party moves. It's not really designed for 1v1. I guess it is, but I'm not surprised how
good the net code is. I'm not surprised. I played this already. Remember when I got cut off and I
wanted to play it so bad? Let's go up two for two. Here we go. Give me that shield. I don't know what
just happened. Sorry. We're good. We're good. We're good. Just pull it together. Pull it together.
Get two kills here. Don't let him do that. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're good.
Team. Give me some. Give me some. Give me, give me, give me, give me, give me, give me.
That's huge. Pull it together. Make it happen. Get these two kills and we're good.
Don't let them get away. This guy just bouncing around. Just get rid of them.
Whew. All right. That was a little sloppy. That was a little sloppy, but I'll take it.
That was a little sloppy. Should I try the new silent streamer? Dude, I'm just cranking out the
game. Do a backflip? Wait, I gotta tweet. Let's go. Tweet out. I had to warm up. I had to warm up a
little. So are you guys getting drops? Does it work? You have to watch for an hour? Okay. Just
want to make sure it works. All right. This is the new character. This is an iron giant.
Should I just get my ass kicked with iron giant? Is he any good? He's whoa. Okay. I'll try it.
I'm so, I'm so excited, man. I, you know, I've been waiting to play a game like this.
So I, I'm going to let my Batman down here. I have no idea what the moves are.
I don't have a single clue. You're going to make, yeah, you gotta,
you gotta make a WB games account and then link your Twitch to it.
You can't keep doing this. All right. Let's see. What do you got? These eats. What does he eat?
He's huge. I think I'm doing okay. What's a grab? I'm just like in the way. Oh my God. This guy is
cracked. He's got a big butt storm. Protect friend. What's that mean? I think I have a defense move.
Whoa. It's like, I do have two different forms. All right. I gotta go look this up. I gotta go in
the lab. I just like big booted drop. We're still good. What does it down? What is up?
What just happened? I have no idea what I just did, but that guy was trapped.
I hit the guy with like a hundred frames frame data.
Shit. Sorry. So this is a colossal character. It's the first one that that makes sense.
He's really slow. I like that move. The big right hand.
Reagan hurts, you know. What does the side special do? I've got the giant.
I think the side special is a grab. I have like a power up. I can protect the friend. He's really
good. Let's do that again. I guess so. I'll do it. He can fight. Well, is iron giant technically
fighting? He's like punching cars and stuff, right? I don't know. Should I do bugs? All right. I want
to level up bugs money. If you say so, I got to find out the scenario to use some of his moves
because the bugs is cool, but he's got a lot of cool downs. You're playing the little brother.
Well, guess what? Man, the little brother has not lost a match since starting.
This is, this is fun. This is fun. I'll do some one V ones after this.
That was a good stun right to start it. Be careful. Don't get too trapped over there.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no. Wrong move. Oh my, I almost hit him with the end of that rocket.
Hit him, hit him, hit him, hit him, hit him. Ooh, nice. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
Knock it over there. Yep. Denial area denial. Getting sloppy. No, we pulled it back. We pulled
it back. Bugs has an amazing up air. That bat swinging the bat up is awesome. By the way,
this game is going to be free to play. It's free to play. Buy an announcer pack. Okay. I kind of
want to take the iron giant into the lab. Should I take that? I want to learn how to do it. Let me
go back. I want to see, because I don't want to just press buttons. Okay. So that's his charge
move. That looks cool. What's the combo? The combo is just the smash, smash, butt bounce. Okay.
What about up air? I mean up. All right. So that's what I was doing. He actually throws something.
You can. All right. The projectile can be the longer you hold it. Oh, that's annoying.
That's going to be so annoying. You just be an annoying shithead here. Okay. So that's what
that does. What about down? So down attack makes these bolts that you eat. And what after how many
Okay. You have max of five bolts. What are the bolts do? Let's find out. Okay. So that's that.
All right. What is the standard? What does this do? So that's the grab was a grab. That's it.
He just kind of grabs. All right. I just used bolts. Oh, it's a shield. I get it.
Bro. You probably do it again, bro. Why is the computer fighting back? Okay. That's what you
want to do. It's up and X. Okay. So that's yeah, I can pick where this goes. Okay. All right. That's
why I was having trouble figuring out what that was doing. If you just do it in the air, you go
straight down. All right. And if you that's obviously dodge. Okay. So what about what is
the standard standard? Special is just is it hurt? No, I think it's just shield is the grab
the butt stomp is up special. Okay. I think that uses a bolt. Do I fly with this? Okay. All right.
Doesn't seem that complicated. I have a better idea what's happening. Protect friends. Yeah,
what is this? This is a whole new move set now. Okay, that's awesome. How did I get that to happen?
I think it is build a meter. Yeah, it's a meter you build. I can aim that kind of like a like a
helicopter blade. All right, I think I get it. Let's do it. Let's do it in the game. Does
exclamation point drops do anything? I don't think that does anything. I don't think that does
anything. Why is everybody doing that? Oh, it Okay, people are just spamming. I get it. Okay.
That doesn't do anything. What was I was? Where's my? Let me see. Okay, we're good.
I'm gonna try to play another game with iron giant. I think I have some currency too.
All right, teams again, let me let me do some one v ones free for all. Okay, I'm gonna do one v one.
Let's see how badly I get my ass kicked. Choose your character. Should I do? I'm not confident
with iron giant. But whatever, I'll get beat up. Classic. You're like a child on Christmas morning.
I've been waiting to get back into this for at least a month or two since it was last year.
I'm so excited. Iron giant is a good movie. Iron giant is a good movie. I agree. All right,
Harley Quinn. Prepare yourself. I'll see how annoying I can be with this character.
Oh, let's do it. All right, I gotta walk in for this one. Two ring outs.
We'll go for one right off the bat immediately. I'm gonna go for a crazy play here. Watch this.
What's on me? I got like a bomb on me.
Sorry. Sorry. I'm getting styled on right now. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry.
I got to learn how to do some of these moves.
Continue. No, that was a good fight. That said, that second heat there,
I got absolutely styled on. That was R. I got destroyed. You didn't use your shield one time.
Should I do Taz? No, we'll go 1v1 bucks. The earwig in your brain is getting to you right now.
Do a Taz impression. No, no, no. Sponsor stream. Whatever. Why not?
I was just about to... Okay, that Taz mania was just about to do that.
Somebody hit man style, like put a piano wire around his neck. What was that? What was that?
I was like... All right, let's go. Main versus main. You got your Harley Quinn. I've got my bucks.
Oh, best out of three. Let's do it. Both earbuds in. I'm going hard here.
I figured she was gonna jump over me. So I was like, you know what? I'm gonna keep up a
fall on the other direction. Figured that was gonna happen. Good job. Good fight. Good fight.
Okay. Read like a book. I almost did my starter mission, guys. Why did you take your smart pills
today? I think a lot of you might be concerned that I like a video game and I might be kind of
good at it. I'm really not, though. I'm just excited. All right, Superman's good. Oh wait,
I have perks, don't I? Can I put them on right here? You ate your Flintstone vitamins?
I mean, I had vitamins today. Maybe that helps. You're getting carried so hard by the earwig.
The earwig is in control right now. I don't know what happened there. That was weird.
Thought he was gonna jump. Oh, shit. He's bringing it back. Oh, what? Nice recovery. Holy smokes.
I forgot how to play video game. I forgot how to play it. I forgot how to play it. I'm all right.
I'm good. I'm good. I forgot how to play. I forgot how to play. I forgot how to play the game.
I didn't want to taunt. What? What the hell are you doing? What happened? All right.
I got to dig down into... That was a good fight. Let's do it again.
Paid actor. Paid actor. He probably dropped his controller on the ground.
Whoever that is, they're probably screaming because they had me. They had me right where
they wanted me and they probably dropped their controller and it probably smashed on the ground
and they grabbed it really quick. All right. I have to stick with bugs. This guy's got a pretty
good Superman. All right. Hold on. Wait. I guess I'll just put these on, right? Till I have paid
actor. The mods are having a lot of fun over here. They're saying the other guy's earwig died. Same
person. Yeah, that was a good match. All right. Let's go. I got my coffee. I got my controller.
I forgot how to play the game. What's happening? My earwig is fucking having trouble. My earwig is
pressing a bunch of buttons in my brain. Stop pressing the button that wants me to go get a
pizza. Didn't taunt. Good grab. Good grab. Good grab. Good grab. Good grab. Sorry.
Why is he playing with his whole body? Because I'm in the game. Paid earwig.
Lightning's going through my body. No, it's not paid earwig. I'm sorry I keep screaming too,
by the way. By the way, connect your WB account to your Twitch. If you watch here,
you got to watch for an hour. Be an active participant. The actual, the open beta is July
26th, by the way. PlayStation. I was holding that in for like 10 straight seconds.
It's on PlayStation. It's on Xbox. It's on PC.
Easy does it, old sport.
My earwig in my brain right now. He's just like, he's covered in sweat.
Yeah, exclamation point drops doesn't do anything. Oh, this is Ari Stark. I just want to make sure
everyone's aware of this. I've not lost a match yet the whole time I've been screaming in this game.
We are undefeated. I mean, yeah, we're in, we're in like the first 10 levels, but whatever.
Earwig Mom said it's my turn to play the Xbox. No, it's not.
Dammit. Whoa, are you serious? Bugs Bunny talking smack about Game of Thrones? You kidding me?
Best character in the game. Good dodge. Shoot it up.
I did that on purpose. I did that. I did. I did that on purpose.
Pretended to freak out every time I fall off the edge.
Show us the controller. We don't believe it's you. Oh, I got it in my hand.
What do you mean? I'm playing. Easy does it, old sport.
God. Okay. Playing fighting games online. I have to be very honest. I'm going to be
incredibly upfront and very honest. There's not been one match, one single match this whole time
that has felt off. This is a breath of fresh air. It truly is. It's been like 10 to 15 matches.
No input delay. God. I've been waiting for a decade for this. Didn't expect that.
That combo. Holy shit. Oh my God. Good player. Good player. Very good player.
I can still do it. I guess I still got it.
Damn. Oh, good. Good. Good. Oh, that was clean at the end there.
That was a good fight. That was a good fight. I slipped up a few times there. Slipped up a few.
Let's do it again. Let's do it again. He's going to get, he's holding back toxic Andy.
Toxic. What are you talking about? Choose your character. I unplugged my controller.
What do you mean toxic? Every time I got a move done to me, that was good. I'm like, good move.
Oh, great. A great throw. Prepare for my deftifying exploits.
All right. Let's try that again. That was intense. My, my blood is on fire right now.
All right. I pull it back. Let's go. Prepare yourself. All right. It's so fun. All right.
We got best of three here.
Face stolen. What the hell happened? Give me that. Give me that. Give me that. Don't let you have
that. Oh, all right. All right. 45, 45, 45, 45. There it is. Good fight.
All right. My dog keeps farting and I'm going to throw up. Please win this match.
All right. I just, I did. I'll just leave the room, dude. Why are you still there?
Just open up your door and walk out and just watch from the hallway.
You want the, no, the dog just check DMS. What? What happened? I have an ant man shirt.
Wait, what? Wait, check like my Twitter DMS. I don't have it. Oh, I do have a Twitter.
Jerma wanna play. It's Hassan. You want to play? I mean, I, I, I got a pretty mean bugs bunny.
Easy does it old sport. I got a Hassan DM to me on Twitter. He's like, hey, let's go. Let's
fucking play. All right. Let me, let me do a few more cracked out games. I don't even know how to
add somebody. Could you add them in like the WB account thing? Another Harley Quinn.
Prepare yourself. It's probably on the main menu.
Hassan, do you want a one V one or do you want a two V two? What do you want to do?
I hope this match is televised. All right. I'll pull it together here. Hello. Oh, give me this
bomb. What lap is this? Oh shit. I'm gamer fatigue is setting in gamer. I got, I got gamer fatigue.
Hold on. All right. Pull it together. Pull it together. Pull it together. Let's go.
It's a hundred degrees in here. It's a hundred degrees in this room. It's a hundred degrees in
here. Oh, how do I toast? Dude, did smoke just come out of his ears? That's the second Harley
Quinn that's kicked my ass. All right. We're good. We're good. We're good. This, I love this dude.
Did smoke just come out of his ears? They beat you. I know I got, I, my air game has got to be
better. Ear wig overheating. Choose your character. It's a hundred degrees Kelvin. All right. Let me
do one more and then what, what, let me, let me, let me DM Hassan and see what he wants to do.
You want a one V one bro or two V two. Oh, I actually wrote, I actually said bro. Oops. All
right. I gotta, I gotta, we gotta go back to the basics here. Tasmanian Delta. I don't even know
how to play. If we're going to play together, I want no talking. We silently sit in a call
and I clear my throat every four to five seconds. Do you accept those terms? I just stare. All right.
Tasmanian Devil. I think I remember some of the stuff about Tas. Yeah. He's got the salt shakers.
This guy is a horse. What's happening? Get out, get out, get out, get out, get out.
Anyway, I got to eat them. No, I want to eat you. Not the other way around. Come on.
Every time I go off the side of the cliff, I fucking panic, dude. I go off the side and I go
and I fucking die. That's part of the game, man. Okay. Hold on. So how do I add,
how do I add you? All right. Let me get, I'm going to add Hassan on Discord.
You have to 430. Isn't that like 12 minutes? All right. Let's go.
All right. Let's, let's get, let's make this happen. Dude, if I 1v1 Hassan. Oh man. I'll,
can you imagine? Show the, show the bugs bunny. Okay. Add friend. I didn't have you as a friend
on Discord. Okay. I send you a friend request. Okay. What if, what if I've just like juggle,
juggle, juggle, juggle, juggle, kick, kick, juggle, juggle. Juggle, juggle, kick, kick,
juggle, juggle, juggle. What if he beats my ass? He's going to, he's going to beat my ass.
I'm going to have to go full bugs on this one. He's currently in the tutorial. Oh,
we got this then. Oh, we got this then. It's calling me right now. Hello. What's up? Oh my
God. I'm a Germaniac and this is a very special moment for me. I'm just letting you know.
You want to do 1v1? I heard you're in this. Is that what you call, is that what you call
your fan base? Are they Germaniac? No, you got it wrong. You got it wrong. It's all right.
What do you call your fan base? It's, it's the Germamites. It's the Germamites? Yeah. I,
I don't have a cool name like that. Mine are Hassanabi heads. Prepare yourself. I just like
joined a game. I, I, all right. Let me, let me, let me, let me style on somebody real quick.
Okay. I don't know how to play this game at all. So you are going to destroy me if we 1v1. Oh,
then okay. Well, I'll go easy. I'll play a character I don't play. We can do 2v2. Can we
like pair up and like beat on other people and then you carry me? I mean, I'm, I'm not very good
at this game either. I'm just, you know, I, I've done, I've dabbled a little. I think you're being
modest. No, we're going to get absolutely on if we do this together. Did you ask your parents
before turning on mature language? Uh, yeah. Okay. Good. I didn't. I'm being a bad boy right now.
All right. Are you, are you watching my stream right now? Watch, watch me, watch me dunk on this
Superman. Ready? Check this out. Okay. Let's do it. Hold on. Hold on. I'm pulling you up right now.
I'm pulling you up. This is a test though. This is like a trial to see how good you are.
Is that communist Superman? Is that Superman? Is he red? Oh, he is red.
Yeah. You distracted me. You distracted me. You distracted me.
I won't make that mistake again. Hey, what happened? Don't you dare. Oh, I should have
ended it right there. That was stupid. All right. Everybody quiet, quiet, quiet, quiet,
quiet, quiet, quiet. You like that cancel play the game. I swear to God. Oh my fuck. It's all right.
It's all right. It's all right. Did I just turn the stream off? Hello. Can you hear me?
Your stream was on. Okay. So what, what happened there? You want to do a little
post game analysis there? What went wrong? All right. So what went wrong is I'm suffering
from a little bit of gamer fatigue. It's 125 degrees in my room and Superman is overpowered.
He's got like, he's got a bunch of powerful moves. And I, I tried to juggle, but it,
look at the thermometer above here. It's 140 degrees in here. That's what happened.
It's just too hot in here. Yeah. It seems like you're, you're making excuses. It seems like
you are failing on the front of the phrase. It's just the game is such a weak mindset. Jerma.
I had it. I had it in the bag. I really do. I swear. You are okay with what happened losing
imperfection of a craft. When you stop getting angry after losing, you've lost twice. There's
always something to learn and always room for improvement. Dude, I get, I get angry at every
little thing in the world. If the toilet paper has no toilet paper on it, I, in a rage, I grab
the cardboard and just crush it. You have no idea what I was referencing just there. Do you?
Well, you said, you said getting angry twice is bad, right? No, I said the phrase is just the game
is such a weak. I was just reading a Ninja tweet. Oh, I don't know any of this shit. I don't know
anything about anybody. Okay. It's all good. It's all good. Okay. I thought you were, I thought you
were helping me through that. I thought you were playing with a controller or keyboard and mouse
because why would you play with a keyboard about, I don't know. Some people are sweaty like that,
but the reason why I ask you is because like, I'm really bad and I've never, I'm, I need your
advice on this. You have an Xbox controller. Yeah. Okay. Xbox. I'm trying to do a forward air
special currently or wait, a down air special. Okay. I'm doing the tutorial and I lost doing
the tutorial at first. Let's use our strength. You lost in the tutorial. I died during the,
during the tutorial. I mean, it's a hard game. It's, it's a, it's like a fighting game. Have
you played a lot of smash? Okay. You're playing smash. I've never played smash. No, I've literally
never played really. So this, this is going to be hard to explain some things then. Yeah.
Yeah. That's what I mean. I'm like legit worried about this, but it'll be all right with you by
my side. I think, uh, I think I, I, I have all of the, the necessary tools. Okay. So how do I
add you as a friend here? Oh, I don't know. Hold on. That's a good question. Real quick.
I don't want to show your, uh, do you care about getting your name shown? Do you have like the
notifications turned off? Turn them off if you don't. Um, I don't know on what is it you
like the actual multi-versus client? No, I don't even know if I have it on right now.
Is that how we're a multi-versus client is what it's WB games. Yeah. Just, just, just like, uh,
in your settings, just make sure you have your like invite notifications off. Cause when they
see it, they're going to go, you know, you're going to get pinged. All right, let's do it.
All right. So how do you manage? Oh, okay. Here we go. What is your invite from friends only? No,
I'm just going to have it open for now. So what's your, I'll tell you what my username is. I think
you can find me that way. Okay. Right. I don't even know where to find, uh, friends though.
I can add you. It's so in the, in the top, right, there's like a tab menu. You open that up.
It shows you who you played with, who you're friends with, and, or your, your online steam
friends and all that stuff. Oh, we can do it through steam, right? I, we probably can just do
it through WB. Okay. Let's do it through WB then. What's your in-game name in, uh, in the
multi-versus? That's, I just wrote it in the discord chat. Oh, okay. I think that's what it
is in my WB. Uh, that's what it is. I hope this is right. I think so. Let's see. That's you.
You have open invites. Yeah. Okay. I just invited you to a party. Did you get it? Hold on. I have
a weird name. It's like a two V two. I think we can, I think we're going to do two V two.
Wait, we're just going right in. I mean, you invited me for a two V two, right? That's what
you invited me for. Oh, I just, I kind of, I just invited you to a party. It just said,
I mean, your name is about to show up. I'm just letting you know. Oh, it doesn't matter. It's
all right. Okay. You're, you're this, right? You're, you're Shaggy just like I am. Yeah. Yeah. I play,
I play Bugs Bunny. I'm a Bugs Bunny player. I've got a lot of experience playing Bugs or Taz.
Okay. My, my selection, my character selection process oftentimes revolves around who I think
is the coolest looking character. Who do you think? Um, Bugs Bunny. We're going to do dual
bugs. We could, but we're going to, no, no, no, no, expert. Oh no. Iron giant is expert. No,
iron giant is actually putting iron giant. It's good. It's really, really heavy. Really, really
hard to knock off the stage. I would, I would recommend it. Dude, just press every, just press
every face button, like just mash buttons. You'll be all right. Wait, I have a ticket. Okay. I
unlocked them. Wait, you got in trouble. Why do you have like a ticket? Do you have a ticket
like in the game? No, like I unlocked them with a face ticket or something. That's what it's. Oh,
it's like, oh, I got a ticket. All right. Iron giant classic. No, let's go with the default.
Look. Okay. We're, I'm ready to go. We're going to get, we're going to get annihilated.
All right. Do I say wait in lab? I don't know. Yeah. It's two v two. Are you ready? This is,
this is baptism by fire, man. You ready? Dude, I'm so ready. I don't even know what the,
what the buttons do, but I'm ready. All right. So what do you have for a controller?
I have a, uh, a PS five controller. Okay. So square is your kind of regular attack.
If you hold square and not move, you'll do a power charge and that's a big power charge move.
If you hold up and X or square places, do you have, uh, do you have perks by the way? Yeah.
You got, you got to level a character up first. Oh, damn. You have, you leveled your character
up already level seven. Maybe play for like an hour, hour and a half. Damn. You're so good, dude.
I'm telling you, you're going to like this game. Okay. So all you got to do is just get in front
of them and what this person has something here. What is this? They have all the per this one has
the Velma has all the perks. Prepare your shot painted target. Okay. The coconut mints coming
out for this one has on. Okay. Just tell me what buttons to press and I'm going to press them.
You're, you're going to be pressing triangle in directions and a square and directions up and
triangle is a recovery move. If you fall off the stage, why am I talking into the camera? Like
you're here. Let's go. Oh my God. Oh my God. Just stay in the way. Really powerful. What is this?
Yeah. He's really good. No, no, just don't fall off stage. Yep. You're good. I can fly. Oh,
you know, it's awesome. I get to be the big brother in this scenario. It's the first time
I've ever experienced something like this. No. Okay. He's 76. Good. Or is that bad? You don't
want your number to be higher. You want to stay low. Good job. Good job. So far. Oh,
a hundred and seven hundred and 10. Oh my God. Am I kicking ass or what? Yeah.
Good. Oh my God. That was actually perfect. That was actually perfect. I swear to God. Oh,
no, no, no, no, no. Don't push me. Don't push me. We're gonna lead. Oh, wait, I can pick them up.
That's crazy. Let's go for the bully. They got armor too. So we can break through. It's crazy.
It's like it's getting me in the mood. Yeah. It has no business going this hard. Oh,
shit. Oh crap. Watch this. Goodbye. Where am I finding the cars to crumple them up? I don't
know how you still on the stage, but oh, there we go. Let's go. Okay. Well, it's fine. I died
once, but they've died multiple times, right? Yeah, we're good. Oh, get absolutely destroyed.
Velma, where are your glasses? Velma. Oh, I need those glasses to see how high I can throw you
up. That's it. That's it. That's it. Is there a dance? Can I do it? Can I do a dance like,
uh, uh, uh? Am I a gamer? Am I a gamer chat? It's cool. I just wanted to impress you,
Jerm. I was lying. I'm actually a professional gamer. I've played this game so many times.
Have you actually played this a lot? What? No, no, dude. Should we rematch? No, right? No,
why not? Let's do it again. I declined. We need someone better. Hey, they were good.
They knocked us off the stage. That was a good showing. That's the first time you've ever played.
Fired up right now. You have no idea. You got drops on. Yes. All right. Same deal. So yeah,
I enjoy. Okay. Once you get to a certain, you fill this bar that he has underneath his health.
If you hold triangle, you'll turn into kind of like a war machine and you have other moves.
Yeah. They're pretty, they're pretty good. Right. I, I'll be honest. I have no idea.
I think that's how it works. This is so sick. I'll go Taz.
Imagine not believing. Yeah. I mean, I didn't, I thought we were going to get destroyed,
but we did pretty good. You know, you didn't believe in me, but more importantly,
you didn't believe in yourself. No, I didn't. Am I going to get, are you going to get any more
gamer quotes to me that I'm going to misunderstand? No, it's fine. That was the last one. I'm never
doing that again. Do you have currency? You are, I forget that you are my age or in my,
in my age group. And therefore these kinds of things are impressive to zoomers, but not to you,
not to a esteemed gentleman such as yourself. Are you 30 31 32? I'm about to be 31 on July 25th.
All right. Well, happy early birthday. Thank you. I'm going to go with iron giant again,
because it says expert and I'm kind of an expert, I think. Right. He just gets in the way. He's just
really in the way. Yeah. Oh, I don't have enough gold to unlock the variant. Okay. We'll just keep
Do you have any skins? Oh, how do we know? Oh, wait, hold on. I got a perk. Let us put it on
Batman and Shaggy. Do you have any perks or just probably not? No, I have no perk. I do.
This was literally the first match I've ever done. I didn't even finish the tutorial. Oh, wait,
I do. Wait, do I have perks? I have a defensive perk, boundless energy. Now I have perks.
Well, you actually don't really need the tutorial. It's itself. Okay, here's just don't fall off the
stage. That's it. The higher your number is, the more you're going to travel when you get hit hard.
So if you're at 200 150, you're going to it's going to be easier to knock you off the stage.
Just don't fall off the stage. That's the entire game. Okay, got it. That sounds really simple.
I'm still going to mess it up. Probably. But I think the reason. Oh, no, this stage has a hole in it.
Oh, I'm so bad with holes. It's all right. They are. They probably will. They probably will be too.
No, this guy's name is noob destroyer. Isn't it? I mean, we're new. He's going to destroy us.
Oh, even better if we beat him. Batman is beating me senselessly and mercilessly. I got it. I'm
coming. Let me let me take aggro. Let me take aggro from the Batman. Oh, God. Oh, Batman is
noob destroying me pretty hard through Batman. Oh, yeah. Batman get absolutely destroyed.
Batman, what happened? Oh, no, it's all right. We're good. One time. No, no, I die. It's all
right. We're good. We're good. We're good. While I was trying to push him, that was a silly.
That was a silly death that happened right there. Good juggle. Good juggle.
We're good. Pull it back. What is a juggle? We're tied up. It's like when you juggle them,
like when you throw them off. Yep. This way, they bounce, bounce, bounce. My hands are hurting.
That's like how little gamer that's a little gamer muscles I have. It's all right. They're
getting some work today. Oh, be careful. Wait, what am I doing? You said be careful. I'm talking
about me out loud. Oh, it's anybody's game right now. Whoever falls off next is over.
Oh, well, I'm close to falling off then. No, we got new destroyed. Okay, we have to defeat them.
We have to defeat them in the marketplace of ideas. That was that was so close. That was so
close. Okay, my I'm weak. I'm weak on this map. This map has a lot of holes in it. Sorry. That's
hard. They'll just take a look at this and go. They'll fucking go run. Wait. Oh, crap. I think
I declined on accident. Damn it. I pressed X because I saw X. That was so close to that was
actually insanely close. We were down three to not three to one, three to nothing. We pulled it
back to three three. So don't worry. We just keep your channel. Thank you. Taz is good.
Let's get a learner play. Sorry, I failed you, Jerma. No, I got knocked off twice.
Go back to bugs. Should I buy this thing? That's half the fun. I'm gonna do that in a little bit.
Dude, I have this. Look at my damage control. No dumb mistakes. Oh, chat's doing gamma right now.
Let's play some damage control. No dumb mistakes. Get some good hits in and you'll win for sure.
Yeah, all we gotta do is keep recommending Shaggy. I didn't like Shaggy. He's too slow for me.
People say he's good. Arya Stark expert assassin. Hyper Game of Thrones. You know who is who was
good? Superman is actually really good at when I said that he's got like powerful moves pretty
easy to play. You just kind of have to float around and do the freeze breath of people.
All right, I'm unlocking Superman. Let's do it. Let's go. Let's go. I want communist Superman,
though, like the the red one. I'm sure it's available. Just use your unlockable ticket.
I did. I just did. I'm ready to go. I'm Superman. So you're so you're going to be communist Superman
and I'm going to be like rich bugs bunny. There's only one in the bathroom, man. I don't think I
can unlock communist man yet. I'm rich bugs bunny in the bathrobe when you're going to be
communist Superman. Yeah, it's yeah. Together we you know, it's the duality. You know what I mean?
I think we got it. All right. So you're Superman movement speed. I'm going to do defense stuff.
I don't have any sense. Yeah. If you start playing with the same character, you'll unlock stuff.
So what we said you had something to be like at 430 or something. You had something going on.
Prepare yourself. What is it? I asked this guy's toes. We wanted to play with me
because I found out that he was one of the people who was doing the hashtag ad,
which by the way, this is a hashtag ad. I think I need to say like the FTC thing.
But is it in your title? Yeah, it is. All right. This is an ad. Although, although the game is
fit. Oh, oh, get absolutely destroyed. Garnet. Oh, oh, oh, my God. I'm bouncing her off the wall.
Good. Good. You found your character. You found his car. Oh, shit. Okay. Boom. Boom. Oh, no. Oh,
bugs. When he's a mage character, right? That's why it's like got so many cool skills and stuff.
He's fun. Oh, I tossed their ass. Oh, shit. Get out of here. Get out of here.
See ya. Oh, get out of here. Oh, yeah. They're both. They're both down. They're about to get
blown up. Watch your head. Garnet is down. Good stuff. Oh, yeah. How about an adventure?
That was quite a line. What is she doing? Is she all thing? No, nobody has any old.
They bounce me off the platform, dude. I'm beating ass. I'm beating cheeks. I'm beating cheeks with
the Superman. Did you feel old when they asked you what how old you are in the beginning of the game
and it only went up to 22? Yeah. What's up with that? Yeah, that was weird. Oh, no, no, no, no, no,
sorry. I'm going to come back harder and stronger for that one.
Oh, they got speed up. What the hell? Don't matter. We got it. We got advantage. That doesn't
matter. I will give you a faster ticket out of here. Let's go. Wait, what does that do? What does
the star do? I don't know. All right. Go for the stuff on on on fin. It's all right. We got
we got match point here. He's done. He's done. He's not going to make it. Oh, yeah, he did make it.
Oh, just one hit. He's gone. He's won it. There he goes. All right. Let's go.
That was awesome. Dude. Oh, my God. Victory sounds so sweet. It feels so sweet. How fast can you
clap? Incredible. We are the greatest team. Can I hear a fast clap? How fast can you clap?
Wait, I want to do a rematch. I am down to defeat weak people in the marketplace of ideas now.
It's all right. I'll do it. Thank you, Warner Bros. for Warner Bros. Interactive for sponsoring
this. Yes. Thank you. Sponsored by Warner Bros. Interactive. That's what I was going to say. Yeah,
that's what we need to do. I've done it a few times. Hey, open beta is July 26. Yeah,
PlayStation access the open beta as long as you get, you know, you click the link in your chat
and create your WB account and you get drops. Drops are enabled on the stream. All you need
to do is watch for an hour. Dude, I'm so good for someone who never does hashtag ads. I'm
I'm doing it. I'm doing the damn. That was it. That was pretty good. That was a good ad. Thank
you. It's because of you. You're giving me the power to do it adequately. I think we got to,
I think your Superman is your guy here. I think you got a good Superman. Yeah, it didn't even hurt
my fingers playing Superman. Yeah. Do I have perks on that? You're talking about your hands were
hurting? When I was doing Iron Giant, I think it's because like, you know, it's a muscle. Like,
people always say, like, oh, gaming, like, it's not that, you know, it's not physically
strenuous, but they don't understand, like, you have gamer hands. You know what I mean? Like
the inside of my hand hurts a little bit from flexing so hard. Yeah. My sometimes my the thumb,
uh, like webs hurt, you know, you know what I mean by that? You have webbed thumbs like the web of
your thumb. Really good at swimming for that reason. Oh, this map, this map is good. This map is easy.
Yeah, it's like, uh, just nice and flat. I like that. Dude, I am bouncing. Taz is actually,
I got to learn how to play Taz. He's awesome. Okay. Nice. This game is freaking flying, brother. Oh,
crap. Oh, he's a turkey. I turned her into chicken dinner. We got him. Dude, that's what an awesome
power by Superman. You turn people into turkeys. That's I can't believe it. Did I do that? No,
yeah. Yeah, you did. He's got, I think there's a power of probably. No, that's a, you don't
remember the Superman cartoon. He would do his, uh, his heat ray and they would turn into dinner.
Oh, he's in trouble now. The people were playing bad or am I really good? Like,
I don't know what's going on. I think we just, we're just stringing it together. That's all.
We're, we've got good team chemistry. Oh, it's game over. Dude, what is that? What is going on
right now? Oh my God. You may, we're just playing well. We're playing well. Or you think we're just
beating on 11 year olds, which by the way, they deserve it. Okay. If you come at the king,
you best not miss. Okay. I don't care. These are equal opportunity hands that Superman has.
I mean, what time is it? Isn't it? What's, what's today? Tuesday at four 30.
Oh, I got an unlockable. What was it? Toast gold earned. I never, you know, what's really,
I don't know. This might be because I'm old, but like, I never know what the, the gold I
earn. Like, I don't know what any of this stuff is doing currently. I think you can use it to do
triple jump. Let's go. Okay. Did I have, do you have the premium pass? I don't know. I might.
It is that, is that what we got with like the unlock or no? I, maybe I think so. Cause I,
I hit it. I hit the unlock button. If you go to your battle, I got hella gold. Wait, what am I?
Oh my God. I didn't do any of the, I didn't realize that like, I had a bunch of gold from
and I have 2000 property Gleemium. Oh, we got to finish the starter missions. So you have to beat
the tutorial. I think. Oh my God. There's a taunt. I'm unlocking this taunt. Oh my God. That's crazy.
I can do pushups with my one finger. Maybe I'll do Velma. Velma's fun. Oh, I do. Yeah. I do have
these character tickets. That's right. Velma's interesting. She's got some fun moves. I unlocked
an announcer pack too. I don't know what that does, but like he kind of, the guy kind of looks like
you badges, max character badge that I've unlocked. Okay. I don't have any general, but edit perks.
I have triple jump, dude. It's probably like 500 degrees in here. Do you not have AC? What's going
on? I do, but I don't know. I just, I think I generate so much heat. Okay. I don't, I have a
Trump Tower Superman. What? How did you get that? One in a million, one million. It's a variant. It's
an epic variant. I think they gave it to me because I'm, I might be the best that they've ever seen.
That's what I'm getting a call from Warner Brothers Studios. They're saying like, I might be able to
make it pro. Really? Yeah. It's crazy. They're on the line right now. That's actually a really
cool skin. People are going to think you're really good at the game. So you're going to have to step
it up here. You're going to have to step it up. You don't have a gold skin and be bad at the game.
Can we do 2v2 with other people? I don't know. Is that possible? Lyrick is playing too. We could
get like Toast and Lyrick and then do a 2v2. I mean, I would do it if people want to play. They
would whoop our asses, I think. I mean, I don't know how sweaty they are. How? I mean, people
really haven't had access to the game in a while. I think everyone's kind of on the same playing
field. Here we go. Toast is a sweat. That's what they're saying in the chat. And Lyrick is a sweaty
gamer too. I think they would probably destroy us. This is the all-Boomer team. You, me, Lyrick,
Toast. Everyone's a Boomer. But it's all old? I don't know how old Toast is. I mean, I am sweating.
I wore a tank top specifically because I knew I was going to be heating up in here.
Wear tank tops is your thought, okay? B, F, E, 4, R, the elite, feared goblin. What do they mean by
that? What are they, like a clan? I think they're queuing. Well, we're queuing together.
This almost was a mirror. Should it be a mirror? Oh, it's too late.
I forget pretty much all of Velma's moves, but I'm going to try. I got you. I got you, King. I got
you. Let's do it. I hope we don't get destroyed by this clan. I love this song. What song is this
from? Let's do it. Wait, I thought you were golden. Why are you silver now? I am gold.
Just for you. What? I am gold. What do you mean? You're not gold. You're like 1930s Superman,
like black and white TV. No, I'm gold. On my screen, I'm gold. Oh, maybe it doesn't. I don't
know. I'm confused. Oh, God. They're beating my ass off. Oh, God. Superman. Chill. Chill. Chill.
No, no, I had triple jump. We're good. Wait, how do I pick up the power up?
Left trigger. No, don't die. Don't die on me. Yes. Oh, nice. Oh, Superman. Come on. Come on,
Gwen. Come on, Gwen. Oh, God. Oh, he's beating my ass. He's beating my ass in the QRTs.
I don't know. What does this mean? Oh, it's down. No, wait, what the fuck? Wait, how?
That's crazy that that happened. I don't know what I just did. Dude, what? Are we busted? Oh,
I think I killed him. No, we're okay. Wait, how is he not dead yet? We're good. We're in the lead.
Hey, they got gamer fatigue. We're good. Oh, God. Sorry. Match point. Match point. Let's get it.
Oh, no. Enemy team advantage. Juggle. No. Sorry. Sorry. Sorry. Superman. Bully Superman. Get
Superman. Bully Superman. Get Superman. Bully Superman. Get Superman. Bully Superman. Bully
Superman. No, this is tough. This is tough. These guys are good. Dude, we just got to hit him one
time. I got him. I got him. I got him. He's gone. He's gone. Oh, he's not gone. You got it. He's
gone now. Let's go. We did it. We're good. Let's go. Let's go. I choked. I choked. Oh, crap.
Dude, I'm doing so many YouTube faces. I've never tasted the sweet nectar of victory before.
I get owned so regularly normally. I know. Doesn't it feel great? I've never been good at a video
game my whole life besides Elden Ring. And in real life, if somebody threw an axe at me, I would
dodge it. Are you? Wow. Okay. I'm bad at video games, but if you if somebody swung an axe at
me in real life, I would dodge it. Really? How are you so confident in that? Just trust me on that.
Lyric is the Emmy. He said, yo, I'm down to group if you guys actually want to group. Not sure if
Chad is trolling. Can we actually physically do it? I don't know. Can we do a four cube?
Wait, I have a new move. Oh, shit. I don't. I don't know why I'm not unlocking any new perks,
honestly. I don't know what's going on. I think the game is basically saying like,
we don't want to give you more perks because you're already so cracked. You know what I mean?
Yeah, I feel that I do. I think you just have to get to like level 10 20. No, I like I'm pretty
sure the game is like we noticed that like, you know, we don't want to hit you with a vac ban.
Like we noticed that you're too good for the game. Like we suspect that you might be cheating.
No one is this good. All right. Pencil pencils down on paper. Let's go. Oh, I hate this. I hate
this map. This map is complicated and confusing. I don't like it. It's good. You want to be you
want to catch them when they're on the top layer. What the hell? Adventure time is turning into a
horse. Oh, no. Wait, what the hell? No, no, no, no, no. Pulled together. We're good.
Oh, that was a good hit. Superman kind of messes me up, though, because like I'm Superman. So when
I say I got him, I got his ass. When I'm Superman and I see another Superman, it freaks me out a
little bit. You know what I mean? Yeah. It's weird seeing your own moves. Yeah. And he's got more
perks to me. He's a Superman with more perks to me. So that makes it worse. You know what I mean?
Oh, God, no. Oh, my God. I'm beating his ass. We're good. We're good. Wait, what? Oh, chill.
Well, I just flying off the screen. That was insane. I'm cracked. I'm cracked. I'm cracked
with it. I'm nice with it. I'm nice with it. I'm so nice with it. Oh, nasty. Nice. Oh, I died.
But it's OK. It's OK. We got more. I've got a better idea this time. I'm nasty. Nice with it.
This dog. Nice job. Nice job. Nice job. Wait, why is that not working? Zap.
Laser. Get laser, goblin. Get fucking laser, dude. No. Take a whack at it. Throw him down.
Nice. There it is. Nice. Game over. Oh, wait, it's not game over. One more. We got the advantage.
Get fucked. Get fucked. Oh, shit. No. Oh, shit. It's all right. We can attack the K. What does
that mean? Oh, don't do the same attack more than a few times in a row. You get a it decays the
damage it does. That was actually pretty sick if that knocked him off. But awesome. No, no, no.
He's behind me. Oh, he blew me up. Shit. It's all right. We're OK. Fully Jake. Get him. Jiggle him.
Jiggle peak. Oh, yeah. Oh, shit. No, no, no, no. Oh, oh, my God. They're bouncing my ass.
That skateboard bullshit. Oh, that's it. It's game over. Nice. Nice job. Let's go.
Oh, my God. Toast and Lyric are ready. OK, how do we add them? Do you think we're ready?
Do you think we're ready for a 2v2? I think we could be ready for a 2v2, but we got to figure
out how to do it. OK, let's see. What's the what's the process here? Just add to party.
I just toasted them. They just toasted us. I don't know what that means, but.
Oh, that was you. You did pretty good damage. Your character. Whoa. Thank you. I have an invite.
Should I do this from disguised toast? Is that actually disguised toast or is it an imposter?
Wait, what is happening? Oh, I'm hitting control on my. Oh, God. Is this a fake?
Is this a fake or is this the right one? I don't know. Hold on. He said those made a game. Him
and I are in it. He's trying to add you guys. Oh, oh, wait, I found I found lyrics. Oh, I think
is it I think this is correct. I don't even know how to add people. Let me see. Let me see. I think
I can invite you. OK, I got to I got to confirm from disguised toast. I think that's him. All
right. I hope it's him. I hope it's him. Oh, yeah, this is this is it. This is true. This is
this is them. So we got it. We got to be ready here. I don't have any friends.
Once again, at the top of the hour, I'm going to run an ad or one minute outbreak here,
but also reminder that is an ad we are playing a video game that is our FTC requirement.
Thank you to Warner Bros. Interactive for sponsoring this stream. Your character and also
the open beta is July 26 on PlayStation, Xbox and PC with full cross play and full cross
progression. Everything that you unlock during this period will stick you with you with you all
the way through early access and open beta. Where you go? I did that joke a week ago. It's a good
joke. It's fine. All right. We joke. I was moving my lips. All right. Another player and I unlock
the reward. So we got we actually bring your game here because this is against other streamers.
Bro, they're going to beat our ass. I'm going to be honest with you. I'm pretty sure. I mean,
they're both sweaty as hell. They're sweat lords. So they're level nine. Dude, Lyric is already
level nine with his Batman, dude. That's fucking bullshit. I'll just say it. I'll go ahead and say
it. That's not cool. It's all right. We got it. All right. I got I got perks. I have no perks.
You're level eight with the Bugs Bunny. Yeah, that the fear of me having a skin,
I think is going to put some fear into their hearts. Yeah, me too. They're going to be like,
whoa, that's gold. Gold Superman, like unheard of, you know, that that sort of thing, I think
is what's going to happen. I'm very ready. Should we? Should we? Oh, shit, I should add them in a
Discord call to why did I not do that? Hold on. But we didn't want to hear the strategies, though.
No, no, it's fine. Let's go. I'm adding them. They're playing. Wait, are they playing? I'm not.
Why are we? Why are we? Why can nobody hit each other? What's going on? All right, we're good.
I don't know. I just added them into the Discord call, which is a tactic I was doing,
but they didn't fall for it, Jerma. The classic Discord call before the game tactic. But
I thought it was foolproof, but turns out it's not. You know what I mean?
I'm going to I'm just going to be quiet and play because I want to win.
I've got this. Why am I weakened? Why am I weakened? No, my bones are broken.
Batman broke my bones. Wait, what is he? He's always in a fucking.
Just stay out of that cloud. No, he's attacks are decayed. Wait. Oh, my God.
Oh, my God. Lyric is beating the doors off me, dude. I can't get him. He's a crack. He's a pro
gamer. Just kidding. Get fucked. Oh, dude, you're destroying this guy's toes. Trade, trade. Oh,
no, no. Sorry. Good. Good. Good. Wait, how am I healing? He's up. He's up. Yeah, let's go. Get
one. Get fucked. Oh, the collapsing route. That's two this time. No, no, no. Oh, no. Oh,
he body blocked me. Sure. You're not using. No, no. Oh, wait, how does he weaken me?
To be to hold together. I fucked up. I fucked up bad. No, I got stuck. You got it. It's fine.
Don't worry about it. We got this. Don't feel discouraged. You got this, King. No, no. Oh,
my God. I almost fall. Nice. Wait, what? Wait, what happened? How did I? I don't know what
happened. OK, well, they didn't add it. They didn't get on the call to my home. Did I stay
too high or something? I think, yeah, I think you were too much. I did the same thing, man.
OK, wait, tell them to chat. Tell them to turn on the discord or pick up the call. I called them.
We both got caught in the same exact spot. I think I think we got in the exact same spot.
Yo, yo, what's up, guys? What? I worked you. Oh, my God. After this, you can't even you can't
claim to be a gamer if you get worked by us. I don't know. I saw a victory screen on my.
I know. I just I mean, you got carried by Lyric. It's fine. It's not a big deal. Yo, what up?
What's going on? OK, this time it's for real. We were just like going easy on you guys. We're
professionals. You know what I mean? Oh, no, I feel you. OK, I was. Yeah, my control wasn't
plugged in. I got oil all over my hands. You did beat the doors off me, so I don't know how
that works, Lyric, but OK. Did I swear bug? I swear you like act me up and I just like tagged
you. I went flying up. You set me on an elevator. I don't know how you you guys have like hella
perks and stuff, right? I mean, I mean, I can take them off. I mean, they're like, OK, no, no, no,
keep them on. I think it's all right. It's good that you have the you need all the advantage.
You have a level three. Isn't that a level three perk? It's an X three. I don't know what you're
talking about. I keep perspiring out of my hands. I don't have any perks. It's just fine. OK,
you guys know everybody, right? Germa, everybody knows everybody. I think so. I know of Germa,
but first time playing same with you toast. No of you, but you know, don't be afraid.
Let's go for it. All right, let's see. Oh, I love this music. This is my favorite music.
This is like a Hercules one or something. It's the Steven Universe song. Oh, OK. Oh, yeah. Get
fucking destroyed. That's so much damage. I know. I love I love juggling with Batman. How do you
weaken? Do you know how that happens? I think just some attacks, depending on the character,
has weakened. My ex does weaken it every time I hit. What is the smoke cloud? Is that what is
that? If not cheating. I don't know what it does to you guys. I just you get. How do you
how do you how do you enable like that? I just need to have, you know, you know,
you're hacking, which is fine, I guess. But oh, shit. It's unlock it with the key they gave you.
Oh, the cheats. Yeah, I guess I missed it. Oh, wait. Oh, yeah. No, I didn't want to do it because I
didn't want to just try it so hard, says the guy with laser eyes. Yeah, well,
you're back. You're the only one in the game. Protect me. Protect me. I need a contraption
to fly. This is like a backyard turf. I think Wonder Woman can fly, too, no? Oh, can she?
I can show not in the game. So this is from Steven Universe. Yeah, the song is from Steven
Universe. I was thinking, like, where is the song from? And I just remembered it is from Steven
Universe. Oh, my God. I got that. Dude, this is so good when you juggle. It's like it's crazy. I
mean, when you when you get a string of combos, it's so stupid. Oh, like that. That was silly.
That's cheating, too. You have contraptions. That's literally cheating. Oh, it's a remix.
That's cool. It's a good dodge. That was a good dodge. No, get out of here. Oh, my God.
Where is she? Why are you blinking? I'm so mad. I'm so mad at you. I'm so mad at you. I'm so mad.
Oh, shit. Yeah. Where's your kryptonite now, dude? Huh? Where's your kryptonite?
Oh, God. Oh, I'm in trouble. Oh, shit. Watch your head. All right. You guys got to get out of here.
All right. Oh, no. Germa, avenge me. You're good. You're good. I don't know why I'm talking like
Batman. But hey, you know what a tactic means, right? It means you're using your spam. You're
a one hit Andy. Although you're talking to me, you're just screwing with my brain.
I thought you called me a one hit Andy. I was like, wait, why are you saying that you're my team?
Wait, I thought that was them. That was friendly fire. That was friendly fire.
I'm just glad there's no shaggy mains in this lobby. He's okay. Is he? Is he actually low?
I fell. I'm trying to do a cool thing and I didn't do a cool thing and instead I did an uncool thing.
Yeah, give me, give me, give me, give me, give me, give me. Watch me. Watch me resist it. Oh, shit.
Huckum, you got Mr. BC. Get the fuck out of here. Oh, God. What? How is that even possible?
How is that even possible? Oh, God. Toast. Get his ass. Get his ass. Get his ass. Oh, God.
Oh, come on. Oh, my God. Oh, my God. I can't, I can't catch you. Oh, hit it. Oh, what? How did
you dodge that? Oh, my goodness. Got to be fast. Swan diving. Oh, my God. We can't do this. I don't
understand. Yeah. Get over here. Oh, shit. Dude, that was a launch. Oh, that's safe. All right.
We got Batman, Batman, Batman, Batman. Don't worry. We got this. We got this. I'm chilling.
I'm chilling. No, no, no, no. Shoot. That's bullshit. That was cheating, but it's fine.
It's all right. Good game. Dude, this game was actually a lot of fun.
We were chasing you around, Toast. You were slippery. Yeah. I wonder why we lost. And then
I look at how much damage I did, and it's 200. Hey, but you got the KOs. That's all that matters.
Just wait till the sweaty, really good players, they know how to use their supports
and just work together insanely. Oh, my God. It's going to be completely different.
Most of these characters just have those combo moves. It's going to be crazy.
People are not going to fall off the stage. I bet the dog is low-key one of the best supports
or something. Whoever that weird dog with the stars. With the pole, right? Yeah. The tutorial
dog. If you utilize that. The character has a team move. Choose your character. That helps
the partner. The dog has two of them. Should we switch up teams? I'm good this way. I'm good
this way. I don't mind. We're going to get a dub. We're going to get a dub. We're going to get a
dub. Wait, wait. You're not competent. You're not like you think. I'm so confident, dude.
Listen, you need to get lucky every game. He didn't even finish the tutorial. Oh, yeah. Oh,
no. No, I've been, but I've been, but we've been clapping cheeks nonstop. We actually have. This
is the tutorial. Yeah. Trial by fire. Trial by combat. No, I respect that. I do the same
shit. So you just got to throw yourself in and then figure it out when it's like,
you got to be in the midst. Have you guys tried the new, uh, iron giant character yet? Dude. Oh,
no, he got iron giant. He knows, he knows our strategies. He knows our strategies. He's good.
He's really good. I versed him. He's sick. He's massive. This guy was with stream sniping earlier.
I think what an iron giant was. No, I was using stream sniping in a game. We're all on the same
stage. No, I'm saying like he was stream sniping our earlier fights. How I was slapping people
with the iron giant. I should do that. Wait, can you do two of like, can you do Batman, Batman
or only one person per team? I think you can do whatever. Yeah. Do us whatever. I think you can
do as many as you want. You can have two V two all iron giants. Oh shit. God, he's so big. Oh my God.
Oh, iron giant literally like does not get hit. I mean, he doesn't, he doesn't take damage.
He's really good. Oh my God. Toast already incredibly tanky. Oh, what's the fuck,
dude? How do I keep getting weakened, dude? It's my hits. My hits. The first time I've ever like
gotten weakened, like you're, is it the cheats? Is that what it is? She's unlocked. It's the cheats
plus. I think Batman's just every move weekends. I think that's just like his thing. Yeah. Okay.
That's cheating. That's I got it. No, that's what I was wondering. You just like the sheets
unlocked. It's really heavy. Oh, come on. Like after this, I'll give you the file to extract
anywhere but your steam director. What is he doing? He's got bolts and shit. What is that?
Dude, they are beating the shit out of us. Oh my God. No, that's a double kill.
These are the platform. We did not just get double killed off the platform. Oh, we, oh, we did.
I'm so hurt. I'm so hurt. I'm going to hide behind the dude. He's huge. Oh shit. Wait,
what the fuck? Oh, be careful. Oh my God. We can't get four out. We can't get four out. It's on.
Yeah, this is all you toast. You're like a raid boss. All right, we got it. Never mind.
It doesn't matter. He's so powerful. That's why. That's why I said the iron meta. The iron giant
meta is crazy. Everybody knows this. Please don't season me. All right. I'm not food.
You turn into a turkey if I get enough on you. Only, only. Yeah. Only sweaty, sweaty boys.
You're the iron giant meta. Oh God. I was just going easy. Oh yeah. What the fuck? Wait, how?
Holy shit. I'm literally fucking body blocking you and you're just going up. You're tanking the hit.
Yeah. All you toast. I'll give you a smoke bomber. All right. All you. No, no. Get fucking fuck.
Get him. I'll move you over here. No. Wait, why can't I hit you? Hey, we can pull this back.
Do you have like a double health bar or something? What is that? Yeah, I can.
Oh, you're so heavy. Let's go get fucked. Oh, they're down here. They're down here. They're
down here. No, just punish, punish, punish, punish down. Downward moves, downward moves.
We're so screwed here. Dude, he's fucking, he's bouncing me. Oh God, he's bouncing me.
Ping pong ball. Oh, that's it. I had 180. That was close. Were you covered? Really well. And
that's what matters. It's almost like winning. Dude, this guy, he probably has like 500 damage.
All right. His hit box is so big. All right. Everybody go iron giant. We're going to do full
iron giant. Okay. 379 damage. That's insane. You guys got drops on? Yes, sir. Excellent. I
got to unlock it, man. I got to use the current. Yeah. Yeah. You got to use the coupon or whatever.
Oh yeah. Oh yeah. The coupons are actually good. All right. All right. Oh, I don't have enough
polimium. No, no. Use the ticket. You have 30 tickets, right? No, no, no. I already have that.
I'm looking at the different variants, but I want to, I wanted to unlock the, uh,
Oh, the one, the last one's nice with the, with the shades.
How much is it? Wait, you have a different, oh, the beach giant, right? That's the one. Yeah.
The last guy. What did I spend all my points on? Donnie Avon team up. No, no, I can't, I can't
betray, uh, German for the clean boys. I don't have enough currency. The clean boy loyalty is
strong, man. Are you guys both, are you guys both beach bums? Oh, okay. Oh, no, I didn't unlock.
I'm saving a little of my currency. Can't take you to the grave, brother. Waste the way, spend away.
True, true. This is going to be actually pretty interesting. A bunch of nuts and bolts everywhere.
Out of all of us, toast knows exactly what he's doing. We don't, we're just going to be
pressing buttons. You got to guide the way. I mean, are you guys on keyboard or controller?
Controller. Are you playing keyboard? I'm playing keyboard. No, you're not.
Holy bro. What do you really do? Like toast literally is like unlocking shit that I didn't
even know existed. Like, I don't know how he's got like bolts on and shit. I'm already dead.
Who cares about the attack delay? Just do down, uh, down special. Oh, oh, okay. Oh,
this is actually kind of cool. Oh, that's so stupid. Get fucking destroyed. Oh my God.
I got confused. I thought I was toast. Yeah, no, that is a problem. That is definitely a problem.
Oh, you guys are both, are you guys both red? Yeah, that's very confusing. How'd you do the
missiles where I turned into like a terminator? What was that?
Wait, what am I doing? I don't know how I did that. What does that do? I can bolt you.
No, it's just the Rockham Sockham robots. What does this do? Oh, I couldn't even try it.
I swear you're like locked into one mode. Is this our move? Oh, come on. Oh my God.
Over the boot. You destroyed me, dude. Whoa. How are you going to blow up? What's happening?
I don't know. I just, they were in a green, uh, sphere. I don't know what that was.
How have I not fallen off yet? I think it's like his ammo. He can shoot out.
It's like, Oh, God damn it, dude. Oh, this is so dumb. Oh, come on. Come on. Are you fucking
kidding me? Oh my God. That's slam, bro. What was that scream? That was like somebody was pulling
teeth out of your mouth. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm sorry. I'm
feeding. I'm feeding. I don't like it. I'm sorry. We're good. We're good. We're good. We're okay.
We're okay. Bro. Toast is like literally fucking doing like, it's like playing it. Oh, come on.
It's like an entirely different game that Toast is playing than us. I think he's like,
I got like three fucking hits, three moves. Like, I don't know what the fuck I'm doing.
Protect friends. Oh God. He's glitch guarding me. Yeah. I'm going to suck him up. I'm going to suck
him up. All right. Attack. Why are we all in slow motion? You deal with him while I deal with Toast.
I deal with Toast. You deal with him. I'm going off the stage very quickly. What the fuck, dude?
That thing is what? Dude, that was an endless spam. I'm dead. No, no, no. You're good. You're
good. You're good. You're good. You're good. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm dead. I'm so dead. I died.
That is an unreasonable amount of stun lock. You definitely did like 700 damage.
You guys are just defected models. How much damage? Yeah. 556 damage. Are you kidding me?
All right. 1v3. All right. Toast, you're on your own team. No, no, no, no, no, no. Wait,
can you even do 1v3s? No, I don't think so. Oh, let's see. We can do a free for all. Wait,
who left? Oh, that sounds fun. Wait, someone left. Auto party request cancel or something.
See, it says there. Yeah. Dude, you know what? I'm going to try. Everybody's in right now. Whatever
you want to do. I'm going to try Shaggy, dude. I think Shaggy is the only one who can stop.
You're trying to the dark side, man. Choose your character. I don't even know what Shaggy does, but
he's fast. He's like he's a brawler. So he's all about just like pure damage. I don't think he has
like a sandwich he throws. Everything else is like melee kicks, like all fighting brawler. Are you
still in Japan? Like, where are you right now, Toast? Yeah, I'm in Kyoto right now. Oh, damn.
Yeah, I'm screaming. What time is it over there? 9 a.m. So I started at 6 a.m.
Damn, yo, gamer. Dude, it is 6 a.m. Oh, wow. I wanted to potentially go to Korea,
but like I feel like the time zone difference is so severe.
Do you try and keep your schedule all the time? I try to do it in England. Wait, wait. Oh, you guys
are trying different characters. Okay, this is the time to do it. Yeah, yeah, yeah. All level ones.
Man, nobody knows what's going on. Japan Ping is still winning. Yeah, no, Japan Ping is helping
him, actually. That's why he's still cracked. Yeah, is this hosting up a toast or is this
dedicated server? It doesn't feel laggy. I picked any server. Oh, you can choose? Okay.
So you're at the disadvantage or at the advantage. This game plays so well online. It really does.
Yeah, it's just that Japan Ping is helping him become unhittable. You know what I mean?
Oh, wait, we're doing like all free for all. Oh, okay. Any other video game? If you were
playing from Japan and we are in North America, we would be literally teleporting ground screen.
This is like actually crazy that we can play like this. Oh, come on, bro. German, German. Come on.
Don't hit me. Everybody hit, hit everybody. Hit this guy's toes. He's hiding. He's hiding in Japan.
Garnet. I'll beat you with a sandwich. Oh,
what are we doing here, mate? Like a little bit of RP. Oh, Chuck Scooby. Oh, no, I just fell off
the map. Hassan, do your best Tasmanian Devil. I don't know what the Tasmanian Devil sounds like.
What? Oh, I got that one. That was a dump for me.
Oh, wait, no, it wasn't. It wasn't. Oh, God. That actually wasn't bad. Yeah, it really wasn't.
What is this? Oh, Shaggy. Oh, Shaggy's fucking broken. I told you, man. No. Oh, shit. I lost
me. No. Oh, come on. Oh, no, Chuck Scooby. Why'd you do that to me? What was that? That was
that was a weird graphic. Harley Quinn's graphic just kind of jumped up. Was that you?
Harley Quinn? Yeah, I just saw there was like a Harley Quinn death screen. That was kind of cool.
Oh, shit. Oh, that was a huge health pack. I know.
Yeah. Time. What happened? Oh, Chuck Scooby. What happened?
Is the real villain was me all along. All right. All right. It's not Shaggy.
Let's go. Let's fucking go. Oh, here you go. Here's a dose for you. People are saying that's
Morty. No, Morty would be more like. Oh, that's Rick. That's Rick. Yeah. My favorite anime.
I can't believe we have fucking pro gamers in this lobby and the worst loser one. What the fuck?
Okay. Shaggy's. Hey, free for all. Literally free for all is just like the sneeze game mode.
It doesn't matter. It doesn't matter. Okay. Okay. I didn't realize it was like that. My bad. Okay.
I just want people to like me. Are we doing free for all again?
To be sure. Oh, to be to our to be to whatever. I think that's what. Yeah, let's go for it.
To be to mods. If you want to adjust your Gamba accordingly. Right. We got to win one of these
Hassan. We're getting kind of dunked on by. Yeah, no, I know. It's fucked up. It's because,
you know, Japanese ping and also cheating. So it's fine. I think. Okay. Says the guy whipping
out Shaggy. Oh, all right. Shaggy. Got a mirror. Not perks though. Don't worry.
Did none of us do. We're all level one. Oh, wait. Your Taz has the perk. Okay.
Turbo's rocking it. It's 5% increased damage. That's basically 20. Shaggy superpowers up the Zaza
is what people are saying. He's just super saying the Tasmanian devil is the most misunderstood
villain. He's not a villain. It's just like Looney Tunes are just weirdos. They're not bad.
Are they bad guys? Taz just wants to eat. He's just like a weird. He's a weird guy.
All right. Oh, Scooby. I'm off the Zaza. Oh, shit.
Come on season season. Oh, wait, what the fuck? Oh, shit. Hey, yo, one's almost a turkey.
No, don't turkey me. Oh, what just happened? That was bad. Wait, what the fuck? No.
What happened? That's such a dumb way to die. I hate that's the worst thing I hate about these
sorts of games is like you just like accidentally fucking get locked. Oh, I get stuck on the ledge
or whatever. Yeah, there we go. There we go. There we go. That kick. Bro, he's got the knee,
dude. Holy crap. Oh, sorry. Wrong game. Wait, what? What just happened? How? Oh, you guys got
Tasmanian devil. Yeah, dude. Taz is crazy, dude. I'm feeling okay. Okay, we got this next round.
It's a wrap. It's a pepperoni pepperoni round. Thanks for the carry. You did double my damage.
I got annihilated. That was teamwork, man. Oh, we got. Okay. I'm going back to the main
main character. Oh, you're going main. Okay. Okay. All right. By the way, at the half hour
mark, once every 30 minutes, we have to remind everyone that thank you Warner Bros for interact
Warner Bros interactive for sponsoring this stream. Wow. Thank you for doing that for us.
Yeah, no problem. An FTC disclaimer, July 26, the open beta PlayStation, Xbox and PC full
cross play full cross progression as well. Don't worry, boys. Me and German will carry the hashtag
out here. We got it. I finished my portion, but all good drops are enabled by the way. How long
have we been playing this game for? I feel like I'm playing like four hours. This game's fun.
It flies by, man. It's like, you know, yeah, no, this is, this is like one of the most breezy
hashtag ads I've done. Actually, it taps into your childhood. Like, come on now. I can't wait for
some of the new characters. Prepare yourself. Warner Brothers has so much. Oh, they can pull.
Oh my God. There's so many. They say who they're going to do or anything. Or I think they just
kind of leaving it up in the air. But I'm very excited. They have so many cool characters.
Are you guys going to play again on the 26th? I'm going to play again on the 26th, I think,
or 26th or whenever it is. Yeah, we should group up again or something.
Oh yeah, they should add Gandalf. Yeah, lyrics like lyrics like, yeah, let's group up again
so I can beat your asses with ease. This is a lot of this is like me and German,
like beating the crap out of 11 year olds earlier. Hey, come on. They were 12.
Did you guys get did you guys get weirded out by the age thing too? It's like,
are you below 10 or like, are you below 10 or 20 plus? It's like, well, OK, I'm 22 plus.
Yeah, that was definitely like a weird range. Hey, hey, hey, what the fuck? What happened?
I saw you like lose track or something. My controller just unplugged. Oh, never mind.
Oh, no, German. No, no, it's fine. It's fine. It's fine that your controller's unplugged.
We still got this. My guy just ran off the screen. It's the last action I did.
Oh, my goodness. Wait, what? It's tied up. Wait, what? I can't tell if that's your fog
or if this is the game fog. No, this is the level fog level fog. Mine's like more white.
What? You just ate me. Oh, what the fuck was that? Bro, you got so many moves. Like,
I have no idea what's going on at the time. He's made out of like clay or something.
I don't know the lore behind Adventure Time like that. All right. Good. Oh, no. I'm failing.
Get him. Get him. Get him. Get him. Get him. Get him. Get him. Get him. Get him. Get him.
He's a weak link. He's a weak link. Get away from him. No, I'm the weak link.
Oh, my goodness. Oh, God. Don't pull off. Don't pull off. How are you doing that? How are you
doing that? Just crush him with the fucking iron.
Oh, excuse me. That was fucking fake. What happened? I did a clip in like 0.25 speed.
What was that? I don't even know what happened. What happened? Did we lose?
What actually happened? I saw toast fall, you falling and then toast back on the main stage
and then we won. Yeah. What was that? Was that like, okay, that was unironically Japanese ping,
I think. I saw myself winning. You guys saw that, right? Like I saw me kicking toast off.
No. I have no idea what happened. It was fun, though. Whatever it was.
Yo, guys. GGs, though. I'm going to chill here. Yo, I'm down to play if you guys are on another
time or something. Yeah, good play. Until next time. Nice meeting you guys. GGs. Have a good one.
Yeah, good game. This was wonderful. Once again, thank you, Lyric. Have a good one. By the way,
guys, they're doing multiverses. Make sure you experience more multiverses on their channel.
That's right. Who else is still staying? Who's still playing? I'm good for a little while.
I love this game. I'll keep playing. We can't do like, we do 2v1, give toast a chance to.
No, I'm not that good. Bro, what do you mean? You're cracked, bro. You got 300 damage. What
the fuck is going on right now? I played during the last beta. Wait, really? There was another beta?
Yeah, there was. Yeah, there was the early alpha. Oh, wait. Play with moist critical. Is he playing?
Oh, Charlie is like insane. Is he cracked out? Yeah, he has like at least 100 hours.
Okay. I don't even know how. This game is not even out yet. Let me see. Is he live right now?
Is he in? I'm going to add him to the call. I mean, he owns a Smash team. So, right. Or not a
Smash team. He owns a Rocket League team, right? He's an e-sports gamer. So what's what's his
online? What's his plan? Play with Ludwig? No, I'm not going to play with Ludwig because I fucking
text. I sent him a text message saying, do you want to play? Do you want to play multiverses?
And he did not respond to me. Oh, moist and letter playing. All right. Okay. Nevermind.
Now I'm going to step out and do some solo practice and you guys take the 2v2.
Okay. Very good. It was good to play with you though.
Yeah. GG's guys. All right. GG's. Jeremy, do you want to keep playing?
Yeah, I'm good to play. Let's do it. What up? How's it going? Oh, shit. Wait, did you add?
Wait, no, don't add Ludwig to the group, dude. Don't do that. What are you talking about? Why?
I hate that guy. Why? What's wrong with you? I'm kidding, man. What are you talking about?
Thanks for responding to my text message asking you to play video games together.
It's not a big deal, but hey, here to play against you two. Hassan, I'm sorry. I just
didn't think it was real. I thought you were hacked. Wait, what do you mean?
I just couldn't believe that you were playing a video game. Hey, how is not having drops on
YouTube? Is that cool? You don't speak to my teammate that way. How's that?
In the fucking ring, bro. No, no, no, no, no, no shot. You're like a fucking sweaty
smash player. And so is Charlie. We have to separate the teams. Hassan Hassan.
This is not smash. This is multiverses, by the way. I know. But like, you know,
they're different games is what you didn't recognize that Jerma did. Idiot.
Okay. By the way, we got my Bugs Bunny. I've been working. I want to free for all actually
against all of these pros. So I've never played the game and I'm playing on keyboard mouse.
Just play us in in in stuck it up. Do I do I have can I do it? How do we invite people?
Oh, yeah. Would you write your usernames in there so I can invite you?
My username is air coots 31. Okay, just write it because I don't know how to spell.
Nobody add me except for Hassan in Jerma. Okay, I have no idea how to.
It's air A.I.R. Okay, I'm just adding voice. Oh, T.S. Oh, wait, we can do it off steam. I think
it has to be WB name. Yeah, you have to be in game and give WB just one more time.
Those air coots 31. No, I'm searching. I'm searching moist and adding him.
I well, I don't know why everything you do is offensive, but it is moist. I sent you a request.
All right. Are we doing free for all? Are we doing to be too? No, we're doing to be too.
What do you guys means? Shaggy Shaggy. Oh, I'm Shaggy. Oh, what?
Oh, no. No, we're going to get so we're going to get three Shaggy players here.
Three Shaggy players. I'll switch. I'll switch. Who's your second? Okay. Okay. Okay. I am going
to add moist to the lobby. I'm doing it. I'm adding moist to lobby. You moisture. You got a request.
I'm coming. And then I'll bring in Ludwig. Okay. Oh, actually, he came with me. Are we both here?
No, I'm not seeing him. Add me. Oh, you're right. Okay, I got him. You should play as the WB frog.
All right. The second day, the second they add that, that's my main for the rest of my life.
Actually, a great main air coots 31. Shocker. Was it hard to spell? Come on.
I don't know what you meant when you said air coots. I thought it was like,
like E R K U T. Like, I don't know. It could be so many different ways. I don't know what the
fuck air coots is. I don't know why you make things difficult. I'm sorry. I did not realize
that you, you know, have a named it after your cat, which was also once on mogul money.
Dude, I know what I want to drink, like a like a 32 ounce Gatorade right now.
Okay, let's do it. So bad. Let's are we are we ready to go? And I'm talking about the gross
orange one. You know what I mean? Am I the one who, am I the one who's controlling?
Am I the one who's controlling the lobby? No, no, no. Jermez Jermez. Oh shit. Okay.
Are we good with this, this format? Yeah, this works. This will work. All right, cool. Let's
just do it. I used to, after soccer practice, suck down a Snapple in about three seconds. Oh
God. That's big. That's awesome. What kind of Snapple? What kind of Snapple? Yeah, there's
like 500 flavors. Wait, there's like a, there's like a main one. There's like the Snapple,
like Apple. Is it, is that it? There's like a main, like the original Snapple. I always thought
that it was kind of like, it was 12, 20 different flavors. I think there are, but like, it's like,
I think there are, but I think there's a main one. Is it peach? I think it is Apple, right? It's
in the name, isn't it? Wait, we have odds in the chat right now. Will Lassan and Jermez win? No has
9 million points and yes has 1 million or 10 million points now. I will, I'd like it to be
known in the, the alpha for this. I was ranked 1000 in the top thousand across the whole game.
I am, I am going to shut my fucking mouth and try as hard as I can. Oh, I'm sweating. I'm,
I'm actually out here to prove a point. Don't embarrass me. Don't, don't embarrass me in front
of, in front of Jermez. I'm in here with a bad attitude and something to prove. So I'm coming
at you hot. Why dude? Come on. I'm not a gamer. I have never played and I'm on keyboard mouse.
So I'm not feeling particularly, um, confident. We're going to get forward. No, no, no. If we get
one kill, it's a wait, he's already sandwiching it. I don't even know how that happened. I just
got intimidated. Yeah, I'll do that to you. That's my hidden passive. Your other hidden passive is
like looking like me and my boomer brain doesn't comprehend that. You know what I mean? God damn
right. It's my camouflage. I'm just going to chill here for a while. You got this. Whoa,
God damn it. How does that not kill you? How does that not kill you? I just dodged.
Are you guys going to do this again on the 25th or 26th? Yep. 20. Yeah. Yeah. 26. Okay. Well,
we better start by then. By then I'll practice and get so much better. Wait, can we? Oh no.
Germa is so slippery. It's nuts. I just, I'm tossing us on like a rag doll.
Yeah. It's because I can't hit women. That's why I just. Oh my balloons. Oh my gosh. Get the
double, get the double, get the double. Germa's nuts. Fuck. No. My God. What are you doing? What
is that even doing? Oh, Germa. He was fucking with my brain. He was fucking with my brain.
We're in a good spot here though. Oh shit. I thought I'd make things a little spicy.
Good news. The fuse is lit. Oh, that's safe. Shaggy. I love that safe. It's so fun. Come on.
Oh my God. My tactic almost played off. What? Yo, we're good. We're good. There was no problem.
Oh, I jumped away. Oh, that was so clutch. Oh my God. I was fucking. Oh my God. I was looking at
moist. What the fuck? I'm sorry, Germa. That's too fucking. Okay. Okay. I died twice for no
fucking reason. I died twice for no fucking reason. Still got more damage than Eric Coot's over there.
Why does it say I got the least damage? I was wondering that. Is that? It's a known bug, known
bug. Okay. That makes sense. Oh, is that what it is? Yeah. Yeah. Yeah. Oh, that's crazy. Oh,
yeah. That's something with the mouse. Oh, okay. Okay. Yeah. Makes sense. Because when you left
click, the inputs are a little off. The known bug is just being bad at playing games. I'm playing
Batman my main now. Prepare for my dectifying exit. My boy. Hey, you still good on Shaggy or
you're going to walk off the stage another three times? Oh, come on, dude. Come on. See the guys,
we had something great. Okay. You know what? I'm going to go with iron giant. Fuck it.
I'm just kidding. I'm just kidding. He's not. You are bad and you should quit. Yeah. I know I'm bad.
I know I'm bad. Okay. I'm very upset about it. You know, going normie shit. Germa's very competitive
and you don't recognize it. I do recognize it. I've been, I've been trying to impress him this
entire time. Like I've literally, that's the only reason I was doing all right. I'll be really
completely upfront. You said you, can I go back? I want to try Superman again.
We can't go back. I don't have any perks. He didn't even do the tutorial and we dug down.
He's been playing actually really well to be honest. Thank you. Is that who you've fought
before? Yeah. But toast was actually kind of cracked and also Japanese bank saved him twice.
Okay. One time it definitely saved them. Like that's not even a joke. Like we beat his ass and
then the game just delivered him the w for no reason. Was that a frog? What the hell was that?
No, it's just what I thought of that statement to be honest. Oh, okay. Oh, okay. Oh, okay. All
right. Let's pull it together. Okay. I have no, I have no dog in this. I have no state. Okay. I'm
not good. I know I'm not good. Oh my God. I'm not letting you up. Excuse me. Wait, why am I not able
to hit you? That makes no sense. Good grab. You said fire giant. I hit the iron one. I said fire
giant. Whoa. Ooh, easy. That was nasty. The thing about me is I do nasty things. Nice. Well, that
was nice. Shit. Oh, what the fuck? Oh God. If you were like one second sooner, Jerma, I was dead.
I killed you to be honest. Me? Yeah. No. No, I was weak when you threw me and you were in range.
Honestly, the whole time. Yikes. Oh, come on. I was on the screen still. Yeah. How do you like that?
The taste of defeat? I mean, we just need to work on Ludd's recovery. I think it will be golden.
I don't even know what that means. Someone in the chat was saying that to me and I have no idea what
those words mean. Oh my God. I killed you. I'm so sorry. I don't know how to explain that.
Is that what happened? Yeah. And you didn't move and it killed you. You had like 50 seconds to
walk forward. That was so funny. I don't even know what that was. I was just like flying.
You were in slow motion. Dude, that was slow motion, man. That was so funny.
The joint! The iron joint! The iron joint's got me! There we go. Wait, what? How did that? Oh,
shit! What happened to you at the end? We needed that. No match-up knowledge doesn't
gain plus ratio. Yeah, I don't know what I'm doing. I might say most damage to me. Dude, I
didn't do any damage. It looks like the glitch got fixed because I'm not last this time by a
point. Oh, that's crazy that you outdid. You outdid yourself by one damage. It usually lasts for
like one game lead, so it should be fine now, I think. Yeah, that's good. Yeah. I think you
infected my computer, by the way. Like it's not, it's kind of annoying. It does feel like that.
I have, you guys have cleaned out the believers. Okay. They're done. They do not believe in me any
longer. Are you happy? No, no, I'm not. That doesn't make me feel good. Okay, good. Then go
easy on me this round. Okay. All right, I'm playing. Oh wait, do I have enough for Finn?
The street still believe in you, I can confirm. Thank God. I should play Jake. Would I like Jake?
Jake's pretty cool. Jake used to be kind of busted in the tech test. I don't know if he still is.
What's Jake? From adventure. You don't know Adventure Time? Oh, okay. Dude, that you riding
the rocket up to death is replaying in my head over and over again. I'm going to be thinking
about that like all night. That was kind of traumatic to witness. I'm not going to lie.
It just hurt my feelings and he wasn't even on my team. He's just going, what's happening?
What's happening? It's just floating up to death. Yeah. You, I mean, you cooked me, but it's all good.
They need all the advantage that you get. You know what I'm saying? Like we got it.
Hey, you, you are golden Superman at this point, so we're good. These have been close games. I mean,
we were on last stock. All right. This is, we're playing for real now. Let's do it.
Yeah. Yeah. No, no. The training, the training wheels are off. I'm, I'm, you know, pulling on,
I'm taking out the weights, the sandbags. This is the good song. Yeah, this is the good song.
I love the song. Can you guys hear me? Yeah. Oh my God. I'm getting absolutely slammed and jammed
over here. My bombs already. I'm a better superhero than Batman. No, you're not. What are these
coins? Oh shit. Oh, I'm weakening the pootie out of these two. Holy. What's my finisher? Like,
how do you do a finisher? I, I think it's only for certain players. Yeah. Some people actually have
one. What the fuck, dude? It's called the tornado. I'm enraged. Yeah. Oh, you snuck away. You snuck by
that. God damn right. Maybe my recovery is nasty. Recover this. I'll never find me here.
Oh, he found me. Wait, how? That's fucking me. That was me. Spacing, bro.
Having a hard time. I'm not going to lie. It doesn't feel as good as he did back in the alpha.
Get him in the sandwich. I'm not sure. Oh, how did I miss? I'm warming up the fin.
Wait, what? How does that even happen? I don't understand.
Like when I'm, when I'm flying towards you with an attack, how does that not work?
I don't know what spacing means. You have a certain distance that your moves travel
and you're doing it too far away. How about that? Did I travel well? I'm starting to lag a little
bit. Oh, come on, Gwyn. No, no. How is he still alive? I don't know in my, in my up airs.
It's been absolutely got here. Okay, German killed himself. My controller.
Hey, what are coming? Gifted subs are coming. Hey, we appreciate that.
Fucking. Dude, blame the USB mini standard. Okay. The USB standard. I will keep it a stack.
Hassan. It was just superhero gap. Yeah. Oh, oh, you were worse today.
Only an amateur blames his tools as they say. Dude, only, only a professional. I don't know
what happened. I am. I blame my fucking tools. That's how you did. Great. Believe in yourself.
The USB micro standard. The thing is like a toothpick that sticks in it. No, it it's unbelievable.
My controller unplugged itself and I walked off twice.
It's just better tactics. I think is what it boils down to.
Oh crap. Crap. By the way, July 26th open beta begins. If you have drops. Good call.
Also, thank you. Warner Brothers for sponsoring this stream. Absolutely. Damn.
Lud, you're not even saying that ever, dude. What's going on? He's muted right now. I don't know.
He's focusing. He's muted. I think he's probably saying that right now. That's why.
No, actually cool though. Cross progression, cross play, cross everything. That's cool.
Boys, the plan is simple. We're going to beat the doors off of Ludwig today.
Now, let's get in the hang of it now. Just give him. He just needed like four matches to warm up.
Now he's going to go nuts. If I walk off the edge one more time, I'm going to eat this controller.
Oh, I can't believe I still hit Jerma. You make me sick.
You make me sick. Dude, just wait till they add Daffy Duck. What are these gold coins doing?
Is that your character? Is that Jay? Oh, what? Wait, did Jerma die again? My controller. USB
standard. USB mini standard. We take that. Oh my God. You just styled on me. That was kind of big.
Yeah. I got you with a nasty combo. Oh, you just repeat it. I thought you were going to grab the
edge. Your spacing is trash, right? Your spacing is trash. No, don't make me do this. Oh, they have
specific voice lines against each other. Oh, and it was disgusting what you just did to me. Oh,
it was disgusting. It was disgusting. I chased it down, baby. This is a blowout and I hate it.
If Jerma's controller wasn't broken, you guys would be so dead. Not even funny. It would be
sad how badly we'd be beating you. I'll keep it a stack. If Charlie teamed with Jerma,
you would still lose. Wait, really? Oh, well, yeah, you are the worst player on the map.
And Charlie is the best. No, you. Good response, bro. You're bad.
Give me, give me, give me, give me, give me, give me, give me, give me. I'm coming. Oh, God.
What the fuck did I throw off the cliff for? Oh, I almost had you red. Oh, yeah, I'm terrified.
I'm actually terrified of you right now because I don't want to lose the game. Oh, my. What? Wait,
what? Why did I fall off? I fucking melted you, bro. No, you didn't. Jerma died. That's the same
thing. It doesn't matter. You were fucking trash. Let's look at your damage. Look at your damage.
It's better than you. It's better than you. No, it's worse than the wood. I crushed you, bro.
I'm getting super glue and I'm super glue in this USB micro. 381 damage every more than all of us
combined. Gorilla. This is my shit. I'm just kind of nasty at these kind of games. I'm not going to
lie. OK, OK, OK. What do we let's do one more. One more to be to. We've got to try to pull this back.
All right. One more to be to one more to be. Then we can try some frieze. Sounds good.
I'm going to accidentally gorilla glue my hands to this controller. At some point, I have to one
of you when you has on. Why is my dude? I'm so down. I mean, you're going to be on the keyboard,
right? Yeah. OK, good. I think I'm going to change it up here. Oh, man. This is a bold move. I think
it's I think so. We're playing as the we get 20 percent more damage if we play with the same
characters from the same universe. Oh, you're playing as Jake? Yeah. Oh, that'll boy. Jake's
good. I was just trying to mess with you. I'm not playing with Jake. Oh, you just like what you told
a lie. We're playing with the mystery machine group. Oh, it's kind of fucked up, though, to lie.
Oh, my God. OK, I was I'm a liar. I thought it was friendly art of war.
You guys know why my when I all tab it state it's like sticks.
Oh, are you and when you are you in windowed full screen?
No, when I all tab it just like shows the all the fucking instead of like showing it for a
second for the duration of the all tab it just like it just has all of my programs right there
on screen. Are you playing in full screen mode or windowed mode? I think I'm playing on.
Never mind. It's fine. We'll figure it out. All right. See if we can pull this out here.
Oh, this is a good map. I hate this map. You press windows tab instead of all that.
What's the tech button? Is it just watch? Yeah, it's dodge. Oh, man, German slippery.
He's amazing. I'm ashamed. Who is the development? The Shaggy shit. Shaggy shit. Oh, that's really.
That's weird. Who are you talking about? You say who's amazing on the Shaggy shit.
That's crazy because you thought it was German and you were complimenting Shaggy.
And now you realize it's me. No, I think it's really bad.
That's so weird that you feel that way because.
Oh, my God. Guys, clip that clip that Ludwig professional Smash Bros player
said that I was amazing on Shaggy. I'll take it. Oh, come on. Oh, how did you survive that?
I don't know. I'm not going to lie at that for sure. I was dead. How is she dodging everything?
The double kill.
Getting double sucked.
It's not canon. They don't say that. The show. They do. They do, dude.
Are we just OP because we're playing canonical characters like literally tie
20% more damage, dude. They don't know that same universe.
There's nobody in the Batman universe here.
Superman?
Yeah, they're in the same universe.
Are they?
Yeah.
Is it, like, is it?
Metropolis isn't this?
Well, Metropolis is always referenced in Gotham.
Oh my god, Jerm is nasty on this Velma.
Oh, I gotta get that call in.
Oh shit, that's basing.
Dude, you have dodged so many times, I don't know why.
Oh boy!
I don't know how you keep a voice.
My body!
Let's go!
Let's fucking go!
Every hole filled at the end there.
I could not recover on that.
Jerma was popping for a minute.
Dude, that was incredible, Jerma.
That was a clinic.
Oh my god.
Hey, come on.
That was a fucking clinic.
Wait, Ludwig, I think your bug is back on.
Yeah, I gotta just...
Yeah, just check the forums real quick.
I'm sure they have a solution.
This game is fun, man.
This game is fun.
This is a lot of fun, yeah.
Especially Victory, the sweet nectar.
Oh, yum-yum-yum-yum-yum-yum-yum-yum-yum.
You know what, I don't...
Yum-yum-yum-yum-yum.
Wait, wait, wait, I gotta mention something here.
Stop yum-yum-yum-yum-yum.
Okay, will Jerma, will Hasana Jerma win?
Yes, got fucking four million points and no 29 million.
Oh, what a big believer moment.
When was the last time you guys drank a Trenta
from Starbucks?
I've actually never ordered one ever.
I did one of those today.
I've never even heard of it.
You've never ordered what?
You ordered one?
This is like the secret large.
It's 32 ounces.
What did you order?
It's a Trenta.
Choose your character.
I have no idea what that is.
Okay, Starbucks has tall, grande, and venti, right?
That's small, medium, large, but you can order a Trenta
and it's an extra large, a 32 ounce iced coffee.
I love that.
It's on the secret menu.
What's your Starbucks order?
Oh, bro.
Trenta, hazelnut iced coffee with three pumps.
Wait, this is a lie.
So Trenta iced coffee with three pumps of brown sugar syrup
with a splash of oat milk.
That's insane.
That's not bad.
Splash of oat milk is good though.
Good call on that.
Hey, Lud, are you having a hard time
because there's no Jigglypuff in this game?
Dude, just because you know a reference
doesn't mean you need to say that a lot.
Oh, I'm sorry.
Are you upset that I fucking nailed you?
It's okay.
All right, let's just put $5,000 on this one.
Wait, hold on, wait a minute.
Dude, okay, dude.
Are we on Taz?
This is between you two.
Nevermind, he's on Taz.
Nevermind, nevermind, nevermind.
By the way, people are freaking out.
They think you get no sugar syrup in it.
You only get three pumps of brown sugar syrup.
Three pumps is standard.
They put three pumps in a grande normally.
We're playing friendly games
and Lud's like put $5,000 on.
No, there's no classic in here.
Excuse me.
That's the only way I got this one.
Oh my God, I didn't expect that.
Oh, best song of the game.
True.
What song is fire?
What is it from?
Steven Universe.
I think Steven Universe, yeah.
Yeah.
Oh my God.
Oh my God, that tornado's disgusting.
Tornado's kind of nasty.
It's disgusting, it really is.
Just metanite.
Oh shit.
Oh, chew him up.
Wait, did you eat him?
That's sick.
It's hard to get though.
It's hard to do.
Oh boy, what a combo.
Tossed him right into it.
What?
Oh, you slippery, slippery bastard.
No.
Oh my God, he's got 152.
No way.
What the fuck?
Oh my God.
No, how?
With 158, how?
With a double KO?
Okay, we'll get fucked on that one.
Oh shit, that thing is bad.
I'm gonna get fucked on this, I think.
I can't believe that.
Peace.
Bitch.
Who said that?
That was Matt, man.
Oh, I thought that was Taz.
Imagine, Taz is full anime.
He just speaks full English.
Wait, Taz can speak English, right?
No, isn't he gonna go like,
what the fuck?
No, he's like Scooby-Doo.
He's like, right, right, right, right, right, right.
Scooby-Doo does not speak full English.
Yes, he does.
He doesn't speak full English.
Oh, Jesus Christ.
He'll do like little grunts and then like throw in a word.
No, he's like, Taz want action.
Right, he says more shit.
He has never said, Taz want action.
Yes, he does.
I used to have a toy.
You pressed his chest and he went, Taz want action.
Taz want action.
I swear to God, somebody's gonna find a clip.
Oh, what the fuck?
Let's go.
No, no, no.
What the fuck was that?
Wait, is that Batman?
Or is that Tasmanian devil, for sure?
Definitely Batman.
Oh, that's scary.
Dude, you're abusing that, okay?
I absolutely am.
You're so abusing me.
What just happened?
No, baby, yeah.
Oh my God.
I couldn't jump.
Why did Batman say, you wanna slobber all over me?
It fucked me up a little bit.
To get to the other side.
I played so poorly that round.
I played so poorly.
Oh, scary.
I think we all did pretty good,
except for Ludwig, honestly.
I literally got more damage than no one.
You got a KO than a Lud, that was crucial.
Lud, do you have a controller?
No, I do, but it won't connect.
I cannot figure out
how to get my Xbox controller to connect.
Is it the USB micro standard bullshit?
I have the controller.
I have plugged it in.
It is plugged in.
It just doesn't work.
You guys wanna do FFA?
Yeah, let's do it.
Let's go for it.
Okay, I gotta pee real quick.
Stop saying remove the batteries.
Choose your character.
Can we do a pee break?
You guys wanna do a pee break?
Uh.
You have 38 seconds.
After this we can.
Yeah.
It won't look any different
if you're playing or not today.
Okay.
I'm gonna try this dog.
Oh, the original content dog in here?
Yep, original content dog.
That guy's nuts, actually.
Is he good?
Yeah, he's actually really good.
Guarantee Hasan doesn't wash his hands.
There's no time.
No, he'll do it.
He'll make it back.
Two shaggies.
Yeah, I'm busting out the main for this one.
Okay.
All right.
Did they both go pee?
I'm not sure.
So what's your assessment so far at this game?
Oh, I love the game.
I played it a lot during the tech test.
So I'm pretty well versed on it.
I think it's great.
I love the game.
And we're no longer in ad hours.
I'm not contractually,
I'm not contractually obligated to say that.
No, it's just a great game.
It's just an absolutely fun game.
Prepare yourself.
All right.
I had an argument with my chat about this.
Wait, what the fuck is that character?
What?
It's OC for the game.
You don't know Rain Dog?
You've never seen Rain Dog coming home?
How do you not know his name?
Grandma got run over by a Rain Dog?
You've never seen Rain Dog coming home?
I've never seen Rain Dog come anywhere.
It's like, it has like a hundred million views
or something, whatever.
Oh, I'm getting destroyed.
What the hell is that?
Oh shit.
Okay.
Oh, it's fire.
Yeah, you have like a projectile and then like a fire.
Why would I grab you?
Oh, come on.
You're insecure.
That was an easy one.
You got it.
You're insecure.
I was working on him.
I haven't seen metahuman activity like that.
Oh, the flank.
Yeah.
I think I got to take this guy into the lab.
No.
Wait, what?
Oh my God.
That was nasty.
What are you doing, Batman?
Oh, what the fuck?
How is that?
Oh, I'm so fucked, dude.
What the hell?
Why did I chase you?
Oh my Lord.
I can't believe it.
I'm killing myself.
Yo, can someone fucking kill Big Moist, please?
I just died twice.
I've killed myself like twice now.
Does that mean ring out double bonus though?
I don't, you're speaking gamer words
that not even I know.
Gamer words.
What is popping right now?
Oh my God.
Why do you get to kick when I pull?
Why?
I knew that.
Get ya.
Oh, you have 19 points?
Wait, did you get that one too?
Dude, what the fuck?
You already just got it.
What the hell?
23 points?
How?
I have zero.
What?
Even fucker controllers aren't even plugged in.
I just killed myself.
I have zero points now.
Fuck me.
I'm worse than Ludd.
This is devastating.
That felt good.
That was so bad.
I wonder who won that one.
Oh man, you gotta love those kinds of matches.
I gotta tell ya.
Dude, you are the king of kill stealing, Moist.
I don't know.
No, no, no, no.
The damage says otherwise.
Okay, bro.
Our damage is not even remotely close.
So yes, you are right.
But that was fun.
Yeah, I use numbers over here.
Is your bug also transferring over to your points as well
as your damage?
You wanna check that?
Choose your character.
That was nasty, by the way.
We got all, we got absolutely slam dunked on.
Ludd.
That was, yeah, that felt good.
It felt good for me.
That was a nice match.
All right, people want me to play as Jake.
I'll try it.
Is he don't-a-walling me
because he's the worst person on this lobby?
Just by being a sweaty smash player?
1v1 me.
1v1 me right now.
I will after we're done, you know,
after I'm done wiping the floors with you.
I would watch that.
I'd actually really like to watch that.
Is there spectators?
After I'm done whipping you like a towel?
I mean, we can do, we just do free for all
and we just stand away.
Oh, true, true, true.
Stand on the side.
Do you guys wanna hash that out right now?
You could.
Yeah, let's hash it out right now.
Let's hash it out right now.
Come on, big man.
Batman versus Superman.
Old school.
Okay, that's canonical.
Adventure time crew's just gonna hang out in the bleachers.
You're canonically dumb.
Oh, hey, Ludd, you gotta go like this.
Fucking so good, dude.
You're gonna go like what?
Do you believe?
Prepare yourself.
Are you doing Batman?
Yeah.
No, you gotta go, do you believe?
You know you're not doing it.
You sound like Batman as a stoma.
We can't do free for all when you guys stand on the sidelines
because accidentally we're gonna get points.
No, no, we're on the bottom.
We're on the bottom.
Yeah, here.
We'll come up, we'll come up.
We will.
We'll go all the way to the top.
Wait, wait.
Wait, what?
What are you?
Oh, what the fuck?
This is gonna be embarrassing.
Yes, I'm excited.
Hassan, freeze breath.
You have freeze breath.
It's really good.
I don't know how to do that.
How do I do that?
Standard triangle.
Oh shit.
The weekend is too powerful.
All right.
Oh, good movement, Ludd.
That was actually really good.
What the hell?
Bro, you're using items in a one on one.
I'm in the lead.
You dead ass just picked up an item
and healed all your health.
Wait, am I not allowed to?
Wait, is that bad?
I actually don't know.
You've been using items?
No, I get it, I get it, bro.
I get it.
You dragon ass diss, come on.
Wait, what?
I'm sorry, you've been using items?
No, no, bro, I get it, bro.
Hey, I get it.
You've got him now, Ludd.
I just need to wait for an item to spawn.
I'm the most annoying guy in the movie theater.
Oh, that's you laughing?
Wait, what?
Dude, come on.
What?
Oh, I thought you got that kill.
I'm just being annoying.
You have a smoke screen, by the way, Ludd.
You might want to use it.
Oh.
What was that?
That's all right.
Maybe I should have brought my clip tonight.
I feel like I haven't done damage to you in an hour.
That smoke screen's good.
Nice.
Good up air.
Stop healing, you son of a bitch.
Watch out.
No!
Jesus Christ.
This is so fucking lame.
He's full healed like three times.
Yeah, he just keeps getting the giant med packs.
Oh no.
Should we keep going?
I mean, it's over now.
What was that for?
$5,000, right?
No Jigglypuff.
It's fine.
Disconnected.
I'm disconnected.
I'm going to get my fucking controller working
and I'm going to come back.
I'm not playing another second
with this cheating keyboard mouse.
Let's go!
That was a good fight.
That was a good run.
Hey, good game, man.
Is what I would say if you played a good game,
but you played a terrible game.
I'm sorry.
I must report.
You just sit there and all you do
is just accumulate the wealth of health packs.
Medicare for all, baby.
For one.
Yeah, well, I mean, you know,
if you need to use it, you should be able to use it
is my argument.
All right, what are we doing?
Are we continuing?
Yeah, what's the plan?
You get that controller set up?
What's going on?
You guys, you do a free.
Free for all?
That's a bad winner.
Okay, guys, I'm not a gamer.
Like, I'm not being serious either.
Ludwig could fucking wipe the floor with me in every game.
Wait, hold on a second.
Except for this one.
Hassan, you beat Elden Ring, didn't you?
I did.
I was better than Lud on that too.
But you can't, you're a gamer.
If you can beat Elden Ring.
If you can beat Elden Ring,
I think you get the gamer card, I'd say.
This non-gamer beat me multiple times.
All right, I think we have to make a new party, right?
Yeah.
Who has everybody on a friend's list?
I think it's, is it you, Hassan?
I believe so.
We're all in the recently played though,
so you can just invite through there
if you wanna host again, German.
Or Hassan hosts, it doesn't matter.
I guess, like this?
Dude, when I alt-tab, it's so annoying.
It just like, is stuck.
How do I?
Doesn't say anybody else is online.
Go to tab, recently played with.
Up on the top right corner is his social.
It should come up as Commodore Pack.
Oh, there it is, okay.
Yeah.
Which Commodore Pack, I sent you a invite.
Wait, no, that's not, who's Commodore Pack?
Wait, oh shit, oh wait, I think that's, is that Lyric?
That might be Lyric, yeah.
I'm probably like, oops.
I'm not pressing win-tab chat, I'm not.
They're gonna be like, is this Germa?
Like, why is, Germa's like pinging me?
Are you guys getting those invites?
No, I haven't got it yet.
Mine's the big moist.
Yeah, I should, it says party invite.
I tried inviting everybody.
Am I like still in your party or something?
I'm not seeing it, and I'm also not able to,
I don't know how to do a, I don't know how to do a party.
Oh, okay, custom, okay, okay, create all my lobby.
Oh, you have to actually make a custom game first.
Yeah, yeah, I'm making it right now,
I'm making it right now.
Okay, hold up, hold up, hold up.
Wait, oh my God, my fucking keyboard is broken.
Wait, there's something wrong with my keyboard.
I press escape and the windows button works.
Like.
Dude, you need to get a whole new computer.
Wait, what the fuck?
That is weird, hold up.
Yeah, dude, I think your graphics card, your hard drive,
your memory, it's all gone.
I'm not kidding, I'm like literally pressing escape.
That's why it was locking whenever I alt tab.
When I press escape, the windows,
it triggers the windows key for no reason.
Really, that's weird.
Yeah, my control is not even on right now,
but it thinks it's like, no, my control is not stuck.
Maybe just restart the game.
Yeah, it might just be like memory leak or something,
I couldn't tell you.
Just try reloading.
Oh, okay, it's working.
I just like, I unplugged it and I slammed it a bunch of times
and it's working now.
I'm going to the lab, I wanna check out something.
Yeah, I mean, Velma, seriously,
Velma's standard attack is a projectile and it's awesome.
No, your Velma was nasty.
Scarlet Otter is you, right?
Yeah.
Okay, big moist, added, invited player.
The only person I don't have is Ludd
and I think I added him, but Ludd,
is he there?
He's furiously going through cabinets
to try to find a way to plug a controller in, I think.
Isn't he sitting it out?
He said, you guys, did I beat his ass so mercilessly
that he had to fucking rage quit?
That's crazy, that's so sad.
You actually just spanked him so hard
that he's now spending like 20 minutes
to getting a controller to work.
That's wild, that's a wild state of affairs, man.
You hate to see it.
We're not even in the title, Jerma.
It just says big stream for Top G's only,
multi-versus with big man, Penguinzo.
Who?
You see that?
What, my stream title?
No, I'm saying Ludd's stream title.
Oh, Ludd's stream title.
No one's in my stream title.
My stream title is dog shit.
I freaked out because I moved to the sponsor segment
and I was like, I don't know what to title this.
So I was like, let's go bugs, bugs, bugs, bugs.
I don't know.
You don't do a lot of sponsorships, do you?
Like gaming sponsorships?
I mean, recently I have been.
Kind of a new thing.
It just says bugs, bugs, bugs, bugs, bugs.
It says add the title.
Ludd is working with his tech for the control.
This is why Ludd doesn't hang out with you.
Okay.
That's kind of fucked up.
That is fucked up.
And the real reason is because,
wait, hazards enabled by the way or no?
No, and then I turn those off
if we're going to be doing some FFA.
Actually, just let it be wacky.
You can do some hazards.
Let it ride, fuck it.
It'll be wacky.
Free for all time, two and a half minutes.
Yeah, it says bugs that many times
because I'm a bugs main.
I'm going to take this moment to use the restroom.
I'll be right back, boys.
Actually, you know what?
That's probably a good idea.
Are you looking for a time to go pee, Hassan?
I already did.
Oh, okay.
I'm so quick with it.
I do gamer pees.
Dude, I'm such an old man.
It takes me like two minutes at least to pee.
My community times my pisses,
so mine is like around a minute and 12, I think.
One 12.
Yeah, I am.
It's a little bit faster than my 500
on the rowing machine.
Rowing machine?
All right.
Jeremy, you work out, right?
Right, go piss, go piss.
I used to.
All right, I'm not going to mute.
I'm not going to mute this call,
so make sure you behave, please.
Sponsor stream.
Okay, I'm going to say so many gamer words right now.
You dare.
79 seconds last time, good looks champ.
You got it.
Oh, by the way, chat,
I completely nailed it on the Tucker Carlson thing
that I said he was going to say.
Apparently his segment came out
and it's identical to what I said he was going to say.
Yeah.
Even with the Sandy Cortez lock, that's crazy.
Oh wait, I should mute myself.
All right, I'm back.
How's everybody doing?
Everybody just chilling?
We good?
No, but seriously, honestly, seriously,
let me just say the same thing three times.
Warner Brothers Interactive,
thanks for sponsoring the stream.
The ad segment, I guess, is kind of over,
but we're still playing.
This is really fun, really cool opportunity.
I'm really happy to play it.
The game is great.
Again, I'll say it one more time.
It's free to play.
It's got tons of cool characters.
If you're watching and you have drops enabled,
it's kind of this early access period.
July 26th, it goes into open beta,
actually open open beta and get it on anything.
PlayStation, Xbox, PC, full cross compatibility,
cross progression.
You can play wherever.
People are going to think I'm a weirdo
when this comes over here.
I mean, it's kind of weird what I'm doing, but whatever.
I didn't have any clean cups.
Wait, what does Hassan do?
Hey, you were, what, you here?
How are we doing?
I'm here.
I'm just doing a little bit of politics,
having some fun.
I muted myself, don't worry.
I did not radicalize the Germaniacs.
Excuse me.
They're not the Germaniacs.
Fuck, what were they, the germaphobes?
The germamites.
The germamites, damn it, okay.
Now, do you think, I think Ludwig is probably
putting holes in his drywall, looking for a chord.
Okay, that looks good.
Hello.
I mean, it's kind of weird what I'm doing, but whatever.
Jeremy, you want to, you want to one we've honored,
one v one?
I don't know, you know what I'm saying?
We can one v one.
While we wait.
You want to just invite me?
Yeah.
I'm drinking it out of the pitcher.
Let me finish this fire tweet.
You got a good tweet?
Well, I just, you watch Tucker Carlson?
Are you familiar with his rhetoric?
I'm familiar with the man, Tucker Carlson.
Yeah.
Well, earlier today, someone in the chat asked me
what Tucker Carlson is going to say
about AOC getting arrested at Capitol Hill
for protesting outside of the Supreme Court
or the United States.
And I basically nailed, I mean, nailed his exact speech.
Word for word?
With like one minor exception, not word for word,
but down to like the psychotic joker laugh
that he was going to do.
There was a joker laugh involved?
Yeah.
He likes to do joker laughs.
You want to, let's one v one.
Okay, let's do it.
I need an invite.
Hold on.
Okay, let's do another lobby, custom lobby.
Do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do, do.
I got a picture of ice cold water.
No, I don't want to drink it on camera
because it's like really bright glass
and it's going to like reflect off the screen
and show my dick.
I just invited you.
Dude, I just said something so crazy that the chat froze
because people just spammed question marks.
What did you say?
I talked about it like that.
Oh, your dick?
I just said the word dick and everybody freaked out.
The chat actually broke.
It stopped functioning for like three or four
straight seconds.
It happens, dude.
Okay, we're, we're doing, should we do two v two
against people or should we do a one v one?
Oh wait, he's back.
Where's Charlie?
I think he's hanging out.
Yeah, I'm here.
I'm ready.
Okay, everything works with one weird exception.
Jeremy, you got to leave again, I think.
Oh, okay.
So that I can, so I can,
cause I don't know how to put you back in the,
in my lobby.
Oh wait, I'll just remove you.
I can leave.
Wait, wait, here, hold on.
And I'm going to add you again.
Oh, if me and Ludd are going to do one v one
in free for all, and you guys are going to watch,
it doesn't really matter what team you're in, right?
No.
Did you get a controller?
Yeah, we're not going to do two v two.
I got a controller.
Oh hell yeah.
Only weird thing is it has a insane amount of lag,
but you know, I'm sure that's fine.
What kind of controller is it?
Xbox.
Xbox one, Xbox 360.
Ludd, you have to, you have to accept my friend request
on your, on your Warner Brothers like account or whatever.
I refuse.
And moist, I added you as well.
I'll be there in just one sec.
Oh here, I just added, I just sent you an invite.
Put down the picture.
I almost saw it monkey, whatever.
Can you imagine like a reflection off the screen,
off this and like, just me naked.
Are you?
No.
Hassan, you friended me, smiley face?
I did.
The only time where we actually, you know,
you should be in your friend advice,
but you probably have a lot right now.
But I also sent you an invite to the game.
How do I scroll through?
This is the only time where we're friends.
I like the mystery machine profile picture Ludwig.
Yeah, that's, it's cause I love Scooby, but also do.
What's new Scooby Doo coming after you?
Gonna find that mystery.
What's new Scooby Doo?
Isn't it Scooby Dooby Doo, where are you?
I'm referring to the other, the newer one.
We got some, I never was a big Scooby Doo fan.
Are we waiting on big man?
Yeah.
I always thought that Scooby Doo
would be a great serial character.
Why are my fucking things showing?
I already, I thought I shut it off.
Scooby Snacks would just be a great serial.
They should have just made Scooby Snacks
and they would do two commercials.
He would be the coolest one out of all of them.
He would kick the shit out of Tony the Tiger.
Scooby Snack cereal?
People are saying they already did that.
There are multiple Scooby universes.
Yeah, but it was a limited time probably thing.
It's not like Tony the Tiger presents Frosted Flakes.
Yeah, I don't know why I'm getting party invites nonstop.
I thought I ended the.
If you go into your settings, the left side.
I did.
Oh, you did?
I did that already.
Yeah, party invites from friends only.
Oh, okay, I should do that.
Show friend invite notifications, I turned off.
I guess party invites from friends only.
I'm ready.
All right, I invited you again.
They have Scooby Snack cookies?
That's probably, why do I feel like
you're making this up and I'm gonna go buy dog biscuits?
This is not right.
Well, I mean, if they're dog biscuits,
doesn't that make it real?
Actually, Scooby-Doo eats a lot of human food,
which is bad, it's not good.
It's like a bunch of scubs and shit
with like garlic and onions on it.
Your dog will start baking.
That's right.
I heard you weren't a cat person until recently
and now you have toxoplasmosis.
That's fucked up.
Is that true?
What?
Well, I don't have toxoplasmosis,
but I have become more of a cat person.
Interesting.
Okay.
Where's the toxoplasmosis thing coming from?
Toxoplasmosis is when you like,
it's just like cat poop makes you love your cat
and become like servile to your cat.
Yeah, like brainwashed.
I thought it was nothing that makes you take more risks.
I don't know about that.
I don't have it is something that someone
with toxoplasmosis would say though, for sure.
Anyway.
I don't know.
We'll see if the new game Stray that came out,
if that'll make me love cats.
Everybody's playing that.
Is it cool?
It looks pretty cool.
A cat simulator game.
It looks cool.
Are you not a cat person, Asan?
I mean, I'm not like a huge cat person.
I like kittens,
but I do think that cats are too like hot and cold for me.
You know what I mean?
I like the companion,
like the lifelong companionship of a dog more than...
Superpowers Batman.
So are we doing a just free brawl?
Oh my God.
I don't know.
Is it a 1v1?
Was it 1v1?
All right.
Okay.
Well, get me away from that edge.
Shit.
Oh God.
How did you even die?
There was no, nobody attacked you.
My control is on Bluetooth and has three second latency.
You're on a Bluetooth?
Jerm, it's been a rough day for me.
Oh my goodness.
Yeah, dude, imagine getting owned by me.
That's fucking really rough, dude.
All right.
Come on, man.
You survived.
I don't know how.
Blocking in this game?
Just dodging.
So perfect dodge.
Oh.
Oh, can I get the follow up?
Can I get the follow up?
Shit.
I needed that.
I needed that bad.
I needed that so bad.
Oh, I'm dead.
I'm so dead.
Oh, slide with the edgeguard.
I can't.
Oh, I couldn't get back.
Oh.
Well done.
Wait, was that me?
Did you ring out?
Okay.
I'm having a rough game right now, boys.
What do you mean?
Aren't you?
Oh no, it's actually, oh shit.
Jerm was killing it.
Yeah, Jerm was going nuts.
I drank a pitcher of water.
I'm bad.
Wait, that double ring out was you?
I thought that was me.
Oh.
Oh, did I take it at the end?
Oh no.
That was close.
Yeah, it was close.
Where's my, where's my, oh.
GG, GG.
Good shit, Jerma.
Congratulations.
Good work.
It's the first free-for-all I think I've won today.
You know, congratulations on kill stealing
the entire game.
It's fine.
I mean, not a big deal.
Top damage.
Whatever.
Ludwig, you good?
Are you there?
I think steam is coming out of his ears.
Are you there, dude?
Are you okay?
Stop talking to me, man.
So you guys want to do your 1v1
or do you want to keep doing free-for-all?
What do you guys want to do?
Are you, are you okay with doing a 1v1
or what's happening?
He's looking at his controller furiously.
I just found a new one.
Okay.
Let's shoot out a free-for-all.
Do you get banned from like all the Smash tournaments
going forward if you get owned so mercilessly
by like someone as bad as me?
Like, how does that work?
Damn, Lud is just hitting you
with a cold shoulder real hard right now.
I think he's going to punch you.
Yeah.
This sounds like it's about to be
like a schoolyard fight here.
Oh no.
Oh, that's, that was definitely a bunch of batteries
that just fell.
This is bullying and bannable.
Dude, I'm just taking out,
I'm just taking out all my frustrations
because I asked Lud to come with me to the UK
and potentially Amsterdam.
And he was just like, yeah, just ask Cutie.
Wait, he left the lobby again?
Dude, it sounded like he was rolling dice
for damage to you.
Oh no.
Demand and everything everywhere all at once.
Moist meter from Charlie.
Why?
Oh, I still haven't watched that movie.
Dude, it's so good.
Not to, not to impact the integrity of the moist meter,
but it was brilliant.
It was great.
I've heard nothing but good things about that movie.
It looks good.
I just never saw it in theater
and I still haven't watched it on streaming.
Yeah.
What about the Black Phone?
I heard that's really good too.
I missed that one as well.
That one also came out when I couldn't go to a theater.
Wait, you thought that was good?
I heard that, I heard, I don't think Will liked it.
And Will is like my go-to for horror movies.
I haven't seen it.
It's got pretty good reviews.
The audience score is pretty good too.
I don't know.
It's pretty positively received,
especially for a horror movie.
Wait, Charlie, did you watch RRR?
No, I love Bollywood though,
so I'm definitely gonna watch it.
Movie of the summer, movie of the summer.
Well, if you already like Bollywood,
you're gonna fucking flip.
Oh, good.
I'm excited.
I've seen the clips on Twitter.
They're so hype with like the tigers.
Dude, it is so dumb.
It's so good.
It's so fucking good.
It was bad.
I think, really?
Yeah, no, it looks really good, Jerma.
Do you watch Bollywood at all, Jerma?
I feel like you'd be a big fan.
Oh, no, sorry.
People are saying that Black Phone was bad.
No, I feel like I would love Bollywood films.
Yeah, they're right up your alley.
I feel like something like Gentleman or something
is so good.
It's iconic.
Give me a list of your top five.
I'll watch them.
Dude, Gentleman.
Or top three.
I think Gentleman, and then there's,
what's the one with, this one's for Chad.
The one where the bad guy has a bunch of clones
and they all form a giant cube, a giant sphere.
What?
It's so cool.
I can never remember the name of it.
Is it Singham?
Oh, I know what you're talking about.
Well, they all get, all the cops get together
and they become like a giant human cube
and they start like rolling through town
like Katamari Damasi.
It's amazing.
That movie is, that whole movie is good.
That's just one scene.
I can't remember the name of it though.
Oh my God.
All right.
I'm interested.
People are saying Bahubali Indiran, Indian Terminator.
Is that what it is?
Might be.
A lot of people are saying robot
and I think that's the one.
I think it's robot.
Hey, can I get a quick invite, guys?
Your ELO level's too low, I think, unfortunately.
Your ELO level.
Isn't that, that's not what you're supposed to say, right?
You're supposed to say ELO.
That's how little of a fucking gamer I am.
I'm freezing right now, Hassan.
Here, I just fucking accept my friend request
so I can easily add you.
It's getting heated.
Oh shit.
Did I do too late to do it?
All right, give me free.
Free for all.
Is this one we want or are we doing just let's play all of it?
I don't know what I did.
Good old fashioned free.
You got it.
Here, I'll go Superman this time.
Do you still have latency or are you good now?
I'm on my third controller.
It's worked this time.
Why'd he censored?
Oh.
Is it maybe your cable, Ludd?
Are you using the same cable for every controller?
I, no, it might be, so it didn't work with cable.
Oh, it is free.
It only worked with Bluetooth.
Oh, gotcha.
And I tried two controllers and neither worked.
So I just called it quits after a while.
Well, then I found a Nintendo Switch Pro Controller.
Oh, that, I love the Pro Controller.
I think it's a Pro one.
And here on, and here on.
That's the one with the forming the giant.
That's what she's not saying at least.
I don't know.
Okay.
That's the one?
Yeah, that one is amazing.
And then another great one is Sing Am.
Ludd, I have a recommendation for the controller thing.
Like I have a fix.
Ludd.
You versus me again, Clark.
He's dialed in his sign.
Is he not talking to me?
Like, what's going on?
Is he like actually mad at me?
I don't understand.
It's called, it's called getting good
and not dying like that.
You just did the way you died just now.
I have not landed a hit right now.
I am getting absolutely worked.
Oh, that was a good pickup.
You know, I really appreciate being able to grab the wall
because I would have died a thousand more times
than I already have.
Yeah, that's huge.
It's crucial.
Oh shit.
Oh.
I got you with that last hit there.
That was a good wall up.
Ludwig, Ludwig, incredible, brilliant technique.
Oh, fuck you, dude.
I needed that.
Trying to get the, the,
the blow the kiss thing is hard to land.
Yeah.
It's good though, when you do.
Wait, who got the ring out?
I think it was Jerma.
What the fuck?
Jerma is cracked, bro.
Yeah, Jerma is going nuts.
Sometimes, sometimes when I'm, when I lock in,
I pretend to be a gamer for an hour or so.
Oh no.
Oh, the, what, the screen is closing in.
Holy shit.
What the fuck?
Dude, this is insane.
The screen, I didn't know that.
I just lost, I had it and I lost it big time.
I got like kicked out.
That's a pretty funny feature.
You actually, the screen.
Wait, where should I put the camera?
Where are you guys putting the camera?
I did bottom left.
Holy shit, Lud.
Okay, one second, one second.
Hey man, it's.
It's all right.
It's okay.
It's all right, what, it's.
It is, yeah, no, you're, you're doing great.
More thief, more free.
More free for all?
Yeah, you can, you can run some more thief
while we wait for him.
No.
Choose your character.
Dude, how much water is in a pitcher of water?
That's like 60 ounces or whatever this is.
Excuse me, what?
Nevermind.
Everyone forget I said anything.
How much water is in this, do you think?
Like how much, how much water do you think is in this?
Like 60 ounces?
Yeah, yeah.
Wait, Ludwig left again.
Send me another invite as well.
I'm gonna restart my game real quick.
All right, I'll remove you.
Ludwig keeps leaving.
Why are you drinking out of a pitcher?
Because I, I don't, I don't have any clean cups.
Earwigs are eating his grave matter again.
Do your dishes?
Dude, they're all in the dishwasher.
Holly and I have been sick,
so we just ran a dishwasher and it is,
this is not a vase for a flower, dude.
It's a, it's a pitcher.
You're too sick to press a button.
I just told you that everything's
in the dishwasher right now.
No, I didn't shit in the dishwasher.
It's tying people up for saying that.
Why would I do, I'm gonna like do a shit
in the dishwasher prank thing to my own dishwasher.
What are you talking about?
Dude, what are you saying right now, Jerma?
What is happening on your stream?
I'm fighting, my chat is, has lost their mind.
They keep talking about how I've,
you heard me, I didn't just repeat it.
Yeah, shit in a dishwasher prank?
They're saying, they're saying that like I did that
and it's making me very upset.
It was one guy.
What's that on stream losing to you,
put him in a mental crisis?
Oh no.
We gotta get Ludwig a wired controller
that has point zero milliseconds.
Someone in my TTS just asked,
Chad, who is Jerma, is he a criminal?
What do you think, Jerma?
What's your answer to that?
I'm just a guy in his late thirties.
That's exactly what a criminal would say.
Hey, Hassan, I got a question for you.
What's up?
So when you're done, when you're not streaming, right?
Mm-hmm.
What do you do for the other,
how much free time do you think you have after a stream?
So I just, I stream usually like around eight hours
at a minimum every day, right?
Right.
And I will, before I start streaming, I wake up early,
I read the news and I throw on, you know, like the NPR,
the NPR links, like the radio updates.
You know what I mean?
Okay.
It was just like straightforward.
It's like read it.
It's like an AP readout basically.
But after stream.
What?
Like after your stream, like when you're done.
No, no, no, before my stream.
I'm giving you everything.
Like in the morning I wake up.
This is his whole day.
I get the whole day.
Yeah, you're getting the full day.
You asked for it even though you didn't ask
for the full day.
Okay.
That's what I do.
And then I go work out.
I train with a trainer and then afterwards I do more reading
and like get, you know, finish whatever the fuck
I needed to do, like to be an adult.
And I start my stream at 11, 11 to usually seven,
eight, whatever I'm streaming.
And then afterwards, once I'm done,
probably watch like anime, movies, eat dinner,
so that's about an hour or two.
Yeah.
And then I go to sleep.
So you end the stream, you watch like two or three episodes
of anime, eat and then go to sleep.
Not two or three.
I watch a lot of like movies and shit too.
So you're watching probably, let's say.
Very routine.
Four or five movies a day?
No, no, no, no.
So what are you doing with that other time then?
I don't know.
I just like, I literally just chill.
I, like I said, I eat dinner, I watch some movies,
I watch some anime and then I go to sleep.
God damn it.
It sounds so fucking bad when I just go to sleep.
Yeah, it was actually kind of sad.
Like I was just on the sidelines listening and feeling bad.
But my point-
Holy fuck.
Okay, I do a lot of cool stuff.
Yeah, but you can't even explain it, right?
I have sex with women.
Yeah, but you can't explain it.
You can't explain like what you do,
just normally just kind of hanging out, right?
No, literally that's all I do.
Like I just, I watch, I watch anime,
I watch movies and that's it.
And I eat food.
People-
Sometimes I'll link up with some friends.
Like I'll go out to like a restaurant or something.
Yeah, people thought I was crazy because they were like,
oh, what do you do for the other time you're off stream?
Like you mentioned like the, oh, he's a killer, right?
Oh, that's something a killer would say.
I said the same exact shit.
I stopped the stream.
You're being a little too defensive there, okay?
That was like, sounds like what a killer would say.
But you can't explain what you do in a day.
You're just kind of like, okay, I do this
and then I hang out for a little bit.
Jerma, why does it sound like you're looking
for an alibi right now?
I don't need an alibi.
I'm playing multiverses with some buds.
No, not right now, I'm saying.
You mean like later?
Yeah, what would you say if like,
let's say like, you know, cops knock on your door, right?
I mean, I'm just in a hypothetical situation
and they're like, hey, where were you during, you know,
8 p.m. and 10 p.m. when this person was murdered?
Like, where were you?
Like, what would you say hypothetically to that?
That's what it sounds like.
Probably in the bathroom, if I'm honest.
Probably, actually probably in the bathroom.
I was in the bathroom.
Jerma legit kills people.
There were 984 previous Jermas.
He ended them all.
Is this true?
No, don't believe everything you read on the internet,
especially in a chat room on Twitch TV.
Wait, you mean to tell me that people lie on the internet?
What the fuck?
I lied to Charlie earlier.
What did you say?
What did you lie about?
I remember you caught me when I said
that I was playing as Jake.
Oh, that's true, that's true, yeah.
That was a bold face lie for no reason.
That was just bad manners.
See, deceit, deceit is in the blood.
Is Ludwig in an engineering room
crafting a controller right now?
Is he like soldering a chips?
Where is he?
Bro, this is what happens when you can't do react content
because you're streaming on YouTube, L.
He sent Cutie to GameStop to pick up
an old Xbox controller.
He's playing?
How does he not have a single fucking wired controller?
Hold on, he's playing another game?
What?
He's not?
No, he's not, dude.
No shot.
Hello, hello.
Are you playing a different game?
Are you fucking joking?
Were you training?
No, I haven't.
Okay, you guys are misrepresenting me.
I haven't had a-
Hey, no way are you fucking training right now.
I was trying to figure out the controllers.
Bro, you are literally the sweatiest motherfucker
I've ever seen in my life, dude.
Are you okay?
I played one game with controller today.
I don't even know what buttons I'm supposed to press.
Are you fucking-
Did you get one working?
Dude, I don't know how to play video games at all.
You've beaten Elden Ring.
Stop misrepresenting yourself.
Dude, what the fuck is wrong with you, bro?
Stop playing more games
and get in the fucking lobby, Lon.
We're waiting for you.
I'm ready, I'm ready.
True.
Hold on, let me finish beating this kid
and then I'll be there.
I want to see it.
The music in the background makes this conversation
way funnier, by the way.
Oh my God, is this like,
are you giving me a gift today or something?
Because you feel bad that you betray me all the time?
Like when you gave the shirt,
our friendship shirt to Crazy Slick?
No.
What?
So you're just delivering L's to me
to make me look like a better gamer or something?
Is that why?
I think you are doing really good today, sweetheart.
I'm just gonna start inviting Lyric to this party.
Yeah, I bet Lyric wouldn't be fucking,
I bet Lyric wouldn't be like,
dicking around playing in like other lobbies,
waiting for us to cool down.
You know what I mean?
I would say, when you cool down like there's a meter,
you have a certain meter of ability.
Yeah, there's a moist meter, bitch.
Okay, hold on.
You still have not accepted my friend request,
which is fine.
I'll just keep doing custom game invites.
I'm kicking my legs under my chair right now.
I think Shaggy's good.
Shaggy is really good.
Shaggy is nuts.
Yeah.
If you know how to play.
I'll use Shaggy if you're a real one.
All right, I'm ready, I'm ready.
The music's so spiritual.
It's really good.
It's like John Williams in the booth.
All right, who is your most sought after potential,
like we're talking the whole Warner Brothers universe.
Who would you like to see in the game?
Remember, Warner Brothers owns a lot of property.
Yeah, I think.
I'd literally have to go Google.
I think they have Cartoon Network,
so Courage the Cowardly Dog for me.
That would be awesome.
That'd be so hype.
You own all of Cartoon Network?
I think so.
Do they own Hanna-Barbera, too, like all of it?
I'm pretty sure.
Do they own Toonami?
They do.
I want Cowboy Bebop.
I want Spike Siegel.
Oh, LeBron James would be kind of nuts.
Yo.
I just want Daffy Duck.
Send me another invite.
Be honest.
Did you say, give me an invite?
Yeah, send me another invite.
Daffy Duck and Fred Flintstone.
Here you go.
They own TBS.
Okay, I'm in.
The Road Runner?
Oh, that would be awesome.
The Road Runner would seriously be awesome.
Dude, I miss desktop streaming so much
when I was doing the IRLs and stuff
and doing desktop streams from the hotel.
It does not hit the same
when you're just sitting in your house and doing it.
Okay, this was feedback.
I was looking for feedback from a lobby full of streamers.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
I want to be like, oh, I don't know.
It's crazy.
I don't feel that way at all.
That is just kind of nuts, actually.
Dude, I was in my own world.
I was literally in my own world.
I wasn't, I'm sorry.
No, it's cool, guys.
I'll just fuck myself.
I was just reading everyone in chat's most wanted characters
and I was going, that looks good, that looks good,
that looks good.
I just thought of a genius one
and it's because TBS is owned by the Warner Brothers
and they streamed Ely Counter-Strike.
So I want Tarek from C9 Counter-Strike.
Just with a sniper rifle.
Thank you, Reany, baby.
Dude, the mask?
No way.
Well, I did not pick Shaggy, so you shouldn't either.
Is the mask Warner Brothers?
Wait, I snap-picked him.
I also have a, oh God, I don't like perks,
but I guess you get them pretty early, so it's fine.
Perks are pretty helpful, yeah.
Just auto-equip them.
You don't need them.
Dude, the mask would be insane.
I don't have any promote characters.
At level 10 for Shaggy, you'd get a great one.
I want that there's a leak
that LeBron is going to be a DLC.
That'd be great. Prepare yourself.
I can see that.
That makes sense.
I wouldn't play any other character
if the mask was in the game.
I would have like a thousand hours on him.
Steve Urkel?
Steve Urkel is not, is Steve Urkel Warner Brothers?
Maybe.
They have their hand in a lot of pies, I think it could be.
Oh, Jesus.
I think it's a 1v1.
Oh, is it a 1v1?
Oh shit, I'm sorry.
What the fuck?
Jesus, leave me alone.
Is it a 1v1 or not?
Is this a 1v1?
Have we confirmed?
Wait, what do you mean?
It closes in.
Oh, are we doing a 1v1?
No, no, this stage sucks for that.
All right, all right.
You know how it closes in and stuff?
That's every stage though, when you do a free roll.
This one specifically goes to the edges
in the middle island.
Oh shit, no!
George Costanza?
I don't think that's Warner Brothers.
Don't do that, don't do that.
Come on, Mois, why are you edge guarding?
Oh, that was the right term.
Well, you're kind of a gamer.
Dude, dude, I know.
You said I'm a gamer twice today
and it's made me feel so good.
You're using the right terminology.
Oh, what the fuck is that?
It's called Velma.
I want that health.
Yabba dabba doo.
Oh no!
Okay, now I'm playing like shit.
It's not good.
Gotcha.
Oh my goodness, all those bounces
were exactly what I needed.
Oh my gosh, what a dumpster.
What the fuck, Velma?
There I go.
What the fuck?
How are you doing that?
I'm coming for you.
Oh my God.
I'm getting fucking destroyed right now.
Everyone is, why is everybody farming me?
Everybody calm down.
Don't hit me anymore, please.
Oh, no jumps.
Oh boy.
That's not good.
Oh my God, what just happened?
God.
All right, I still held it even with that chaos.
I think I clutched up in the last second,
but then I died.
I got annihilated.
I don't know.
I actually don't know what happened.
Is there a stock game mode?
That'd be swag.
Hey man, I'm really glad you fixed your controller,
by the way.
That was really good.
It was a good performance.
I mean, 12 points.
So here you go.
I'm gonna, you know what, I'm gonna toast you.
That just means you are better at kill stealing,
which is fine.
You sure you want to leave the lobby?
No, I am not sure.
Tony Soprano is Warner Brothers?
Yo.
I don't know how accurate all these are, by the way.
I'm just saying what people are saying in chat.
Warner Bros. characters.
Let's change it up.
I'll try something different.
Yeah, I'm gonna do a different character here as well.
Yeah, definitely don't do Shaggy.
Wait, Harry Potter is Warner Bros.
Imagine?
In Neo from the Matrix.
Do you guys want to change the game?
Oh, fuck, I started already, but wait, hold on.
Back to the lobby.
What do you mean by this?
Yeah, you can put stocks on.
Here, I put Moist.
You're the party leader.
Go ahead, do your thing.
All right.
I don't know where to do that.
Oh, you get like little missions, this is cool.
Can you put stocks on?
Highest score win.
How's Aria?
Is Aria good?
Yeah.
Well, she was in the tech test.
Teen Titans, yeah, be tight.
John Oliver is technically HBO and WB, so.
I don't want to do that.
I don't want to say that.
And I don't want to have a turtle wearing a hat.
That's pretty good.
Thank you.
It's way better than your Batman.
I don't know if this worked, but we're going to try it.
It's fine.
Okay, let's ride.
Wondervere is going to hit me up and be like,
hey, why was 30 minutes of your two hour stream
technical support?
Choose your character.
Uh-huh.
So are we-
Do we get like obscenities at the screen?
Are we doing, are we doing-
No, they're going to be like, hey,
we're no longer going to partner with you
because you got fucking your shit pushed in
by a political streamer.
1v1 right now, 1v1 right now.
Stocks on, real gamers.
What is stocks?
Instead of like getting random amounts of points
based off kills, you have a certain amount of lives.
Yeah.
And when the lives are depleted, it's over.
Oh, there's a list of incoming characters.
I mean, I don't know how that's done, but sure.
I'll play it.
Let's just play it as first and then we'll do it after.
No, I think this is stocks if you guys want to 1v1.
Seems like he's a little scared about doing it this round.
I mean, I'll try it.
But wait, you do understand that it's a win-win for me
regardless, right?
Because like, I'm not a gamer.
No, I've never played this game.
They're totally separate.
I'm not a gamer either.
I literally stream.
It literally doesn't matter.
You played more games on stream than I have in the past year.
Even if you win, even if you win,
you owned a 31 year old dude
whose community blames him for never playing video games.
Prepare yourself.
You are hedging every single alternative of you losing
with a different excuse.
I mean.
Sack up and play your best in winner-loose.
I'm doing that.
But also, I'm doing that,
but also I need you to remember
that like everything I said is true.
You bailed on your friends going to Korea.
What?
I said you bailed on your friends going to Korea.
Okay.
Also, that's not true.
How do you turn off items?
I turned off hazards, but items are still on.
Oh God.
Oh, you just got the credit for that.
I don't know.
I can't tell.
So I'm just throwing myself down to see.
Thank you for that Moist.
Yeah, no problem.
It's definitely not stocks.
We can just keep track of stocks.
We can do like a two stock game here.
Dude, what is happening?
Can anybody hear me?
Yeah, yeah.
Dude, what's going on?
I got stuck in the void.
I literally, my face cam is frozen.
My computer crashed.
How did that happen?
Wait, are you just taking free kills now?
Cause you noticed Jerma's AFK?
They're irrelevant.
No.
What do you mean they're irrelevant?
I'm here.
You said we count stocks.
Wait, so the rules of the game changed all of a sudden?
Like, I don't understand.
Yeah, yeah, yeah.
We're just counting stocks.
Hello?
Hey.
Dude, my webcam is fucked.
What's going on over there, Jeremy?
I don't understand.
So what are we doing right now?
So right now you're winning.
So Ludwig's down a stock, you're up a stock.
Wait, I just watched first set.
Yeah, but you haven't killed Dasan yet, have you?
Yeah.
Oh, you have?
Oh, that's tight.
You have?
Yeah, do it again, do it again.
Oh, you're so shameless.
That was good.
But so was this.
What the fuck?
What?
How?
No, don't take that.
What the fuck?
Honest man.
Oh, you scumbag.
Oh my God.
Here we go.
Oh God, what the fuck?
Sorry guys, I had some technical problems.
My whole computer crashed.
No, no, no, it's one v one anyway.
Yeah, yeah, it's just a one v one.
I'm gonna try to clear all the items myself.
Shit.
Oh, fuck.
The box is breaking.
Oh shit, no.
Wait, is that two?
What are we doing?
That's two.
We got one stock left.
We're doing a three stock game.
No, Jesus.
Oh my God.
That's game.
Yeah, that's great, great game.
It's all good.
Let's play some Tootie Toos.
Tootie Toos?
That's another ring out.
Do you want more or are you done?
Oh, I'm jumping to my death every time.
I like this end of the game here
where you get the Fortnite dome.
Yeah, it's pretty cool actually.
I like that a lot.
There you go, you got one, Lud.
Good job.
Let's try again.
And you had the cheesiest character is fine.
I mean, it's not a big deal, but like.
I'm jumping to my death.
Nice shot.
I won't let that happen again.
Is this game similar to Smash Bros, by the way?
It's like, I've literally never played it.
Almost a one-on-one clone.
Okay.
Should I start, should I play Smash Bros?
You should, you'd like it.
Hold on, hold on now.
Before anybody says anything too drastic here.
Smash Ultimate, I'm gonna say this right now.
I have to, I want opinions
from the people that played a lot of Smash.
Smash Ultimate has way too much shit on the screen.
What?
When you attack somebody,
it does these like giant particle effect lightning smoke
on every single move.
Boys, are you gonna add me to your e-sports team?
Yeah, I'll recruit you for the Moist e-sports
multi-versus squad once we pop off.
Let's fucking go, dude.
After I destroyed Ludwig,
who I thought was like a professional at this.
You were looking pretty clean there for a minute.
I'm not gonna lie.
One of the best players, man.
I'm just saying, I'm just saying.
I disagree, Jerma.
I think it's the right, unless you play with items.
Are you talking about like with items?
No, I'm just, okay, so you're gonna notice this now
and you're gonna be like,
why the fuck did he have to say that?
When you do like a regular attack
or a special attack, doesn't matter.
It creates this gigantic explosion,
a huge smoke light show explosion
anytime you touch anybody.
Anytime you move around,
there's just like smoke, smoke, smoke, smoke, smoke.
It's a ton of particle effects and it messes my head.
I don't think I've noticed.
I know there's sparks.
So like sparks come out when you deliver an attack
that'll probably kill.
It's like a really strong attack
and a high percent of little sparks will come out.
And run.
Yeah, like in wave, not wave dashing, dash dancing.
You get like a little smoke that pops up.
Hey, I'm not saying that Ultimate's a bad game.
I think it's a great game.
I just-
But if I were to pick my favorite game
in the world, it'd be multiverses.
Is your ad still going?
No.
Oh. Yeah, I got five minutes.
Hey, I didn't say anything.
All I said is that I'm an old person
and the less stuff on the screen
that I have to look at, the better.
Is this a me gap here?
Oh, waiting for lobby leader.
Oh, wait.
No, you're not even in the lobby.
It's just me.
For some reason, it's just me and Jerma
in the lobby right now.
Yeah, I see it too.
We should restart it.
Hold on.
I'll do another custom game.
I'll do another custom game lobby
and then I'll give it to you.
I'll hand it off to you.
Yeah, that's fine.
Yeah, do that.
Okay, invited the big moist.
We still has not accepted my friend requests.
I'm not cool.
Aren't I here?
Oh, there we go.
I'm air coots 31.
I know.
We're friends.
We're not in the game.
No, not in real.
Why did you specify like that?
Are we now friends in real life?
No, not anymore.
But yeah, okay.
No, it's cool.
Oh, I've sent you a friend request.
You have not accepted it.
That's not true.
I sent you one.
You guys call these teams.
We go with this.
I'm ready to ride.
Oh, what the fuck?
I see it now.
I'm going to bust out the bugs.
You want bugs?
All right.
Yeah, let's see it.
I feel like you got a good box.
Fuck, I forgot to hand it off to you.
And I just press play.
God damn.
Oh, no, no, it's all it's all good.
Back to lobby, back to lobby here.
No, no, no, no, no, no.
The settings are right.
You're good.
Teams to be to four ring out seven minutes hazards enabled.
That's good for going to be to I got to play something I know.
You can play bugs.
It says you guys are refreshing.
I exited out and went back to the lobby and I can't start the game again.
We got to back out.
We got to back.
Yeah, no, back out.
Yeah.
And now we can boot it up again.
No, moist is still not backed out.
But how do how do you back out in this?
Yeah, how do you back out here?
Just press the button.
No, it doesn't work for me.
Yeah, I think I think we're in here.
All right.
Leave Lobby around two.
OK, we actually might just get booted.
Probably have Lobby going to restart it.
Taz is very concerned about how long that was taking.
There we go.
OK, inviting, inviting.
I think I got I got a solid
another three or four games in me.
I'll play with German. I'll play with German.
Wait, what happened?
We're in. Do you want to do this?
We're good. Yeah.
OK, I'm sorry, German.
Hey, we we had a pretty good run.
Choose your character.
Oh, I love that.
Look at this guy.
You guys playing canonical friends?
We both have similar hair color.
Oh, that's big.
Yeah, and I am I just I mean,
the Tasmanian devil is not a dog, but close.
It's not that you can.
Oh, it makes sense, I guess, that you can't fucking upgrade.
Like you level up when you're playing 2v2
because your friends will let you cheese. Right. Yeah.
Prepare yourself.
I really I feel like this would be a crossover episode, though.
Like Taz would replace Scooby for some reason.
And it'd be like a really funny door one time and then pop out
and it'd be Scooby coming back in.
Oh, the hallway scenes. Yeah.
They eat a lot, doesn't Taz.
Taz eats a shitload of food.
He's perfect for a crossover of a hungry bear.
Oh, my God.
Too hard. What's different about this game mode?
Tasmanian devil is crazy crack. Holy shit.
Yeah. Taz is kind of scary.
Watch out. Oh, my. What was that?
That's the. That was my. Missing me.
Oh, shit. No.
Oh, shit. How is yours?
Wait, what the fuck?
What just happened?
Oh, I'm dying. I'm dying.
You're fine. Not good. We're good. We're good.
We're good. I'm playing bad.
It's nice. Nice.
That was bullshit. That was fucking bullshit.
Oh, that's that. That's a bunch of baloney.
It really is. It's absolute baloney. I agree.
OK. Doing that from off the stage is just oh, it's hard.
It's horrible to deal with.
Nice catch. Oh, good tosses on.
Whoop. Get fucked.
Get fucked. Oh, that was unbelievable.
You just destroyed me. That was unbelievable.
Perfect placement. Stay there.
Oh, shit. Oh, oh, I'm done.
Oh, that was in his mind.
Blue team. Oh, come on, dude.
Patience on the close game.
The music at the end is like Batman.
Oh, my God. I just got Molly walked.
Yeah, you did. Oh, you did.
What? Oh, it's all right.
Let's go. Let's go.
Good shit. Oh, oh, oh, oh, oh, shit.
I thought my down B was about to go.
Hey, moist these boards, baby.
That's how we do it.
That was a clue.
We're close there, Jerma.
Yeah, that was a close shit.
Dude, you had all those KOs, man.
I got a few, but we didn't take down the goat.
Tricky. Are you talking about me?
Yeah, it was the damage.
But the KOs is the easy part.
People say that choose your character.
Bugs kind of nuts.
That bat is so good.
The bat has such an insane range.
What are you doing? You're in a bit of a bit of a bit of a fist thing.
Oh, yeah. That's pretty good.
That's hard to break through life.
Yeah. That shit will stun for a minute.
I am using too many specials.
I have no idea how to play like what is that?
What is the assassin character like?
How do they?
I assume they're good at KOs and have a lot of hit moves and are easy to kill.
It's like, are you?
Yeah, I don't know. I've just been playing bruiser characters or tanks.
Also, you know, I didn't know beforehand is when you use your dodge,
if you use it in succession, it gets worse, right?
Yeah, you have a little meter underneath your character.
Oh, I thought it was just when you land on the ground, it's reset.
Yeah, you deplete it and it gets shorter and shorter and shorter.
If you go all the way down, that makes sense.
Which makes it because there's no block, right?
There's no whole block. Right. Yeah.
Dude, I was supposed to when I got done with the hashtag ad,
I was supposed to go back to doing politics because I haven't covered it
in a while and I just got totally hooked on this.
Playing video games with friends is great.
Well, you're not doing that.
So playing video games with friends plus Ludwig is great.
I agree. It's good.
All right, let's go for it.
Come on for Steven Universe.
Oh, it's a knee.
Oh, I didn't even see that coming.
Great teamwork right there, moist.
Good work. I saw that.
Oh, shit. Oh, wow.
What's kind of going in?
Oh, well, OK.
Wait, what?
Wait, what just happened?
I had no job.
No, it literally broke like I jumped.
And then the game.
Wait, what is going on right now?
I did jump.
My safe didn't get off.
Yeah. Oh, no.
Oh, what the fuck?
Damn it.
That was big. That was big.
I don't know what. Oh, fuck.
OK, I need a hard carry here, Charlie.
All right. Hold on. I'm coming.
No, I'm just saying, because I suck.
No, you're fine.
I am in trouble here.
Oh, I thought I lived that.
How am I still alive?
How are you alive?
You're the goat. You're the goat.
No, that's it's over. Right.
What? Oh, I missed the bet.
Dude, not living through that one.
Oh, shit. Oh, shit.
Oh, no, no, no.
It's not what I meant to do.
Oh, you're so slippery.
Red team.
Wait, what?
Missed?
No, I got it. Oh, my God.
You're so slippery.
Me? Mm hmm.
Oh, that safe came out of nowhere.
Look, Minecraft Steve.
Come on, baby. I'm trying to dial in.
Oh, oh, my God. We can win this.
Oh, no. Hang in there.
Oh, I died. I died.
It's fine. It's fine.
Dude, what the fuck? That's done.
Oh, oh, yeah.
No, you got so lucky, Ludd.
No, no, it's over.
We got this.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Wait, no, it was one kick.
I got it. I got him in the sandwich.
I got him in the sandwich.
Jerma, it's a great finish there.
That was a big sandwich.
I played so poorly in the beginning.
I totally cooked this.
It's fine. No, no, no, no, no.
I should I shouldn't have risked it.
I shouldn't have risked it.
Claw's not strong here, Jerma.
You staying with Shaggy?
No, I'm going to switch it up.
Choose your character.
I will, too.
I'll switch it up to iron giant again,
even though I'm not very good at it.
I know he's my last game.
All right, LG, LG.
All right.
I got to get some food.
No, you kind of nutty low key.
Thank you for this for the marbles.
Dude, what sucks is Assan's actually good,
but he's able to be like, no, I'm a political commentator.
And so losing four times is bad.
I'm not good. You're actually good.
You actually seem to be pretty competent.
And I think you play well.
The iron giant is cracked out, though.
This is going to be hard.
I have no fucking understanding of how this game operates.
I'm just literally pressing random buttons, bro.
Your side B's are godlike.
No side B's have been clutch.
What is a side B when you kick someone off the map or something?
You do your omega kicks that swing left and right very far.
You do it like Superman and Shaggy.
Old man Jenkins house again.
This one is like really technical and I don't know how to do it.
I don't know how to unlock a bunch of the shit.
It's going to be really hard to tank.
I don't even remember what Jake does.
Oh, fuck. I went the wrong way.
I remember this ups.
Oh, geez. Oh, he's in trouble.
Walls open.
We've got a burly man done.
Finish that up.
Oh, I tried. I tried.
Oh, come on.
I got to go. I got to go.
Oh, what the fuck?
You live that. Oh, God.
I can't believe I can't believe that hit me.
Yeah, it was it was in a bad spot.
It was like right stuffed in on the left side.
Grabbing this game?
No, right? No, only this character can.
Oh, you got me.
You got me. I was trying to be sneaky.
Oh, what the fuck?
Oh, you fucked me up.
Oh, I'm going to die soon.
You can't die.
How are you a lot like a rag doll?
Oh, match point.
Red team.
Oh, that's right.
Oh, shit.
Oh, don't you do it.
Don't you do it.
Oh, no. What?
He came out. No.
Oh, no.
Oh, finish it up and finish it up.
I'm trying to grab. I'm trying to grab it.
Yes. Oh, it's not.
It's over. Oh, fuck.
He got out of it. How?
He's so close.
Get it. Oh,
I couldn't get there in time.
Fuck. Oh, my God.
Unlucky.
That right side broke at the worst possible time.
Oh, dude, the amount of damage.
Bro, what was I doing?
Damn, Hassan was stacking on those.
You just stand still and spin and grab a hundred damage.
But I don't just kill.
Yeah, I couldn't finish off Jerma at the end there.
I got I got towards the end.
It was so close.
I was trying to grab him so I can fucking do the toss.
But it's your it's your job, right, Charlie?
Because I don't think Iron Giant can even kill.
I don't know. I don't know anything about Iron Giant.
I bounced around.
I bounced up, down, up, down like three times at the end.
If that roof was any if it was if
there for any shorter, I would be dead.
Yeah, the map, the map definitely was a bit.
It's a bit of a map gap there.
That was that was awesome. That was a lot of fun.
All right. Same time next week.
Yeah. Same time next week, boys.
Multi versus. Let's go.
I will grind every single day, eight hours a day.
Hey, man, maybe maybe next time we 1v1 like you can actually,
I don't know, be competitive.
I'm going to lie in bed, eyes wide open, thinking about every single hit
that happens. He's going to read the what's the
God damn it. I saw it on Twitter.
People were reading like the medas or your list to skip it ahead.
I'm just going to get Andrew Tate's Hustler University course.
Oh, yeah, baby.
I'm coming back a top G or I'm not coming back at all.
That's a wiki, bro.
I see you guys later.
A lot of fun. Thanks. Yeah.
Thank you. A lot of fun.
This is about the tech errors.
No, that was that was a lot of fun.
We should do it again sometime.
Absolutely. That was good to me.
Take it easy, guys. Have a good night.
See you later. That's fun.
That's fun. That's fun.
Yeah. So that's multiverses.
Again, thanks to Warner Brothers Interactive for sponsoring the stream.
We played it for a long time.
How long was this? How long was I playing?
Six hours. Damn.
Hope you had fun streaming for long enough.
Hopefully some of you guys got the drop into early access.
Damn, it feels good sometimes just playing that.
I'll see you guys later.
I will see you guys on Friday for Sorcery.
We're going back to Sorcery this weekend for one million Twitch followers.
It's one of the first games I ever played on stream.
Should be a good time to hang out and chill.
We're going back to Sorcery.
But those of you that weren't here at the beginning of the stream.
Yeah, we're going back to Sorcery.
And then green screen movie night is Sunday.
So we got some pretty fun stuff coming up this weekend.
Thank you so much for watching, everybody.
There was a lot of people here earlier.
Hopefully it was entertaining.
It was a really cool opportunity, so I'm glad I was able to do it.
Thanks again to Warner Brothers Interactive.
Good night. Goodbye.
Well, actually, we'll do this to the actual leaving thing.
Obviously, thanks for the subs.
I think if they're still playing, go spread out to their channels.
Obviously, Hassan, Charlie Ludwig.
I think they're probably going to keep playing.
Go spread out, go hang out.
Not going to raid anybody in particular, I don't think.
I don't have the drop yet. No.
How much more time do you need?
How much do you need? Like five minutes, two minutes.
How much more time for the drop?
I think there are the streamers that are doing this that have the drop enabled.
So you can just do it there, too.
I want just a carry over. Oh, my I'm like a lightning rod right now.
I just like gaming, man.
Just playing games and just like, oh, that like kind of bottled up
gamer energy, you know, you know, you know, I'm talking about, right?
It feels good. It does carry over.
You don't need to do it in one go. Oh, there you go.
So just go watch somebody else that has drops enabled.
We will absolutely be playing this again.
There's not a chance I don't do this again.
You turn 25 during this stream.
Well, happy birthday. Happy 25th birthday.
Come on. I just burped. Yeah.
And we'll see you Friday. Good night. Goodbye.
Take care of yourselves.
Call your mother. You know how it works.
Thanks for watching.
Thanks for supporting the stream, all the subs, obviously.
Have a great night. See you later.