Why hello. Good afternoon, good evening, everybody. Good morning for some of you, probably.
I am Jeremy. Jeremy D. Elbertson. The D is for Daniel. We are going to play Kenshi again,
but a few things have come up that need to be addressed, that are very important, and just
came up with the idea two or three hours ago. So it's going to take a little bit of planning,
it's going to take some time on my part and on yours. You guys aren't doing nobody's in trouble.
What? Why does everybody think they're in trouble? No, it's about New Year's Eve. So before, well,
well, you know, hold on, just give me a second. Let me just open my soda off camera, because I
don't want to blow out everybody's ears. So let's just open that up right. All right, got it open.
Put it in your sippy cup. No, this is, I can drink out of a soda. A soda is a giant sippy cup.
Well, I mean, it's a regular size sippy cup, but it's just a, it's a sippy cup already.
It has one small hole to enter and exit. It's not a giant empty void at the top of a cup.
Anywho, I'm going to wait till people get here, because this is the last second thing that I want
to do for New Year's Eve. Long story short, before we really get into the meat there,
I have the studio for New Year's Eve. I'm going to do a New Year's Eve award show,
based on the worst moments of the last 12 months. So you guys are going to be nominating,
and I'm talking very quickly. Not yet, though. Not yet. We'll go over it. I'm going over this
in real time, because this shit just came up, like, like I said, a couple hours ago.
So there will be categories to nominate some of the worst moments of the year. We're talking
worst joke, worst overall stream, worst hair on stream, worst noise, best use of cardboard.
You know, there's got to be a couple best of categories. Worst gaming stream, like we're
talking, I want to get all of them. There'll be probably 10 or so, maybe 15 categories.
And we're going to do an award ceremony on New Year's Eve to count down the New Year.
Why not make all best? Because that's, we already talked about this last night.
Have best streamer, and I'm not even on the list now. But how this is going to work
is that the channel is currently locked. I'm eight hours behind you for midnight. It's 8am.
Well, it's not that I could do about that. I'm not I'm not Atlas. I can't like spin. And I'm
not talking about the video game. I'm talking about like the guy that holds the earth.
So let's just wait for people to get here. I got the game set up already. We're going to play
Kenshi again. We got the frog friends. But we're really only going to have you're going to have
one day to nominate stuff, because we're going to I'm going to give you all the categories here.
We're going to write them out on stream a little bit later. Then you're going to have a day or so
to nominate in a discord channel that's separate. Same thing that's going to happen like happen with
the Christmas stream. Oh, and then I'm kind of torn on how the voting is going to work,
because you're probably I'm not going to stream for the next two days to get this already.
So the voting is probably going to be for one day only. You got to make sure you get your vote in.
But regardless, we will once we get about halfway through here. It's a Coca Cola classic is what
it is. Hey, look, it's Kenshi. This is exactly where we left off last night. Can you wait four
hours so I can watch the VOD? No, just just put it on times 10 speed, and then add subtitles. I
haven't forgotten on me, but I just stopped it last night. So let's get in here. I haven't paused
if you missed the last stream. We ended up with these three thick up top thick on the bottom.
And the dog that is no longer starving to death just a little malnourished. So not bad. I still
have 1600 bucks. I don't have food. I have some decent food here. Name the squad. Oh, yeah, the
frog. How do I name them? Can you name the squad? Oh, yeah, that forgot that they look like they
could survive in a crash. What was that guy? That weird guy that crash test dummy thing.
But anywho, here they are. So the last thing that we were doing, click on SQD. Oh, here we go. So
let's go with does everybody have to be like a little frog? Right now they're just frog and dog.
Well, frogs, frogs and dogs. I'll get another dog. Three out of 20. Great Canadian just came
with 10 community subs right off the bat right now. Thank you so much. 10 community subscriptions.
Nice. I haven't even pressed unpause yet. But anyway, so we're working together. I did a little
bit of research. I read some things about athleticism. Athletics is just run speed.
So that's doesn't mean anything else. I don't think I looked up some stuff about attack,
defense, strength, how to strength train and all that stuff. So I know a little bit more.
So I need to go into a building that has a training dummies. And I'm not sure where they are here.
I gotta get out of here. No, but hey, hold on a second. My mind's running a mile a minute right
now because this whole New Year's Eve thing is has to happen real quick. And I got to put a
lot of time into it over the next couple of days. So I will explain the title in full detail. We're
going to go over that soon. This stream, I'm sorry, this stream is not going to be like
eight plus hours. Like I thought it was going to be, it's going to be cut short to lake.
I don't know, maybe four or five because I have to do a bunch of work and we got to get the
nominations in because I got the studio. It's confirmed. I'm in studio on New Year's Eve.
I got the confirmation already. So right now my brain is like, well, what about those categories?
And no, we're not into the stream. I'm going to go for like a good four hours and then we'll talk.
Okay. So let's go train. Jeremy, you forgot about something. Oh, are you sure about that?
I don't think I did. You think I forgot about this? All right, let's go train. We need to find,
what do we need to find here? I got to find training dummies in this town and it said look
for a dome. Look for the dome building. Every major town has one and has training facilities
upstairs. I mean, this is a dome building, right? Just go in here. Facecam as a bonus character.
What city am I in right now? I'm currently in, this is world's end, I believe.
Nope, this is blister hill. Pump up the base. You sure you want me to do that? Put on the facecam.
But what if I don't want to? Where is this camera anyways? I don't even know.
Here, I'll turn it up. Here, I'll give you a little boost of audio. Where do you want the cam?
I don't want to put the cam on. Where should I put it? Where even is it? I got clothes on, right?
It's in like a weird, it's too like far that way. You know what I mean? You're just, you're getting
like the side profile. What kind of like, what kind of facecam is this? I'm like clearly looking
just straight ahead. Don't need to be like in the gamer zone where like I'm, you can tell I'm looking
at the game. I feel like I should be on the front of a gorilla's album. No, it's going off. Let's go
train. Uh, up one floor. Are there training dummies in here? No, they're not training dummies in there.
Training dummies. Looking for training dummies. I saw them before, didn't I?
Fuck. What do they look like? I thought they were training dummies. Fuck. Training dummy? No.
I need to do this before I leave. Just buy a house and put a dummy in it. Does this town not have a
training dummy? I thought we saw before. Just hit people instead. No, I can't. Fuck. They look like
stick people. Yeah, like from like base or barracks or something maybe.
Not gonna let me look in here. I don't know. Outside the walls. Are there some outside the walls?
Are you sure about that? Outside walls. You see any? I gotta find them. I can't really leave.
Outside walls. Outside walls. Fuck. Check the garage. I would think that maybe down here.
Right there, dude. It's right there, dude. Where? I'm getting a lot of right there, dude. And I'm
like, where is that? Did I build this? Yes. This is my first city. Spent about two days making it.
That building. That building. That building. This building. Like this building.
Right there, dude. This is public. No, the other one. Not there. Bars aren't for... Yeah, this is a
bar. From my understanding, they look like they're like on top. Maybe this is not training dummies
in this town or something. Click on the map. I mean, wouldn't it? Should be here, right?
In the second gate, the building to the right is the barracks. Oh, yeah. All right. So,
am I allowed in here? This is open to the public. Let's go. I'm allowed to come up here.
We are allowed up there. Where are they? How far away is this place? Oh, there we go.
All right. So, we got... We have these training dummies. I'm allowed to use these, right?
So, let's go with Kandroth. We're going to train. Let's take a look. Start training.
There we go. And you, you are... How are you? Are you already trained high enough? I think you can
only train a certain level on these. Maybe not. Maybe I should give him the weapon. Can I not train
the dog? No, the dog's just constantly hungry. Back away from there. What? Are they talking to us?
That's private equipment. What? Why? Can I get one point before I leave? God damn it.
Come on. One point. One point and I'll leave. Stay away from there. That's private equipment.
One point. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go, go. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
You just need one last little bit. Come on. Okay. Okay. How did I go down? I went down and
attacked. Somehow. Doesn't that make no sense? Wait a minute. Hold on. What? Combat. Melee attack
two. See? Okay. I got, I did it. So, what did he, what is he at now? He's six? Okay. So, this is the
guy that needs that good weapon. Yeah. Well, that's not a bad weapon, but still. So, I need to open
up both of their inventories here. So, you need to put this away and I just go like this. How do I
have both open at the same time? Trade. Okay. So, you need this weapon because you are way better.
Let's trade. Because the other one is actually going to be doing damage. Let's see.
Five plus nine. What was it before? Six. Was it, was it more on the other one? Because he had.
So, that's nine defense now. So, what's the problem? You can't use this? Too heavy for you?
Ten. Attack point is minus two because I can't even use the damn thing. All right. Well,
whatever. He's got ten attack. Well, I illegally up, leveled up my two carriages once. All right.
So, let's all go meet up and let's go try to make some money. I forgot how good this viral soundtrack
was. Are you coming, dog? Let's go. All right. Where are we going to go? I got, let's buy some
food. Let's get a good supply of actual food. I'm going to save it and we're going to go on an
adventure. Let's set up a bar. It's the closest bar. Over here, probably. Right here. Yeah. Yeah.
Yeah. A little, a little band of weirdos. I love it. All right. Let's get in this way. Holding alt
highlight. Yeah. Wait. Right on the ground. All right. We need to trade. Let me see what you got.
What you've got. This is expensive. You don't have any more little meat sticks, do you?
It might be worth buying a few of these because they're very, uh, nutritious.
I mean, like, carry them both at the same time. Carry them both at the same time. So, I can afford
three, three, six, nine, twelve. I can afford to buy all three of these. Or no, actually, I can,
I can afford two, but they're very nutritious. And that's it. I got 200 bucks. I got the backpack
already full of food. Now, as long as one person has, uh, has stuff, they can, like, for instance,
I have a bunch of stuff in my backpack. This is, this will feed everybody, right? I got a backpack
full of food. So, we're good. Time for, let's go. I'm ready to move. I don't, no, the dog's good.
We're good. The three of us are ready to go. We have weapons. We have a giant sack and it's time
to go. So, we're gonna go from here this time. I'm gonna go, we're gonna go down river and we're
gonna end up at some point over here. I don't know where this is gonna bring us, but we're gonna go.
Increase the music. Um, no, we're good. The music's fine where it is. I don't want it to overpower.
Here we go. See you later, suckers. Humble beginnings, guys. Eventually, they all have
30 people in a city. Are these bandits or? No, Holy Nation, that's fine. All right. What a perfect
RPG party. Following right behind each other. This is just my voice. We're gonna get a mining
stream out of this? Uh, it's possible. That all depends on, uh, on a few factors. Everybody's
doing good with food. Except, why is it, uh, no, no one's eating. Okay. All right, slow it down.
Slow it down. Food. Now's our chance. Run them through. Wait a second. Hungry bandit leader.
Hungry bandit. Starving bandits. What do they have for, their attack is not that good.
Four, five, turn around. Turn around, turn around, turn around, turn around. Go, go, go. This way.
Same, same way we came. Come on, bring them to the gate. They're cutting us off. I didn't save it. I
didn't save it. I didn't save it. I didn't save it. I didn't save it. We're not fast enough.
I didn't save it. Where's the gate? Where? Come on. I need right here. Make it to right here.
Just run into the fucking town. We can make it. It's going to be fine. Go. Come on. 26 fucking
damage. Really? Come on, dog. Why am I so much faster? The dog's gonna get left behind. I just
fed him. Come on, hurry. Get to the gate. All right. Bring it in. No, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Fight the, fight the bandits. Just bring them in the town. Bring them to the storm and guards
quickly. What the fuck is happening? All right. Let them fight. All right. We're good. This is
loot. Everybody's body. Perfect. Oh, you got a little bit of armor. I'll take it. Pants better.
Not really. Thanks for the free stuff, guards. Armor. Who doesn't have armor right now? We don't.
Pants. What happened to my pants? A little weapon stick. What happened to the portrait? All right.
That's good. We got a little bit of armor out of that. You're under arrest. How are we doing? Okay.
Head. Dog is fine. Stomach. Right arm. I don't need to manage anything. We're fine. I don't think
it's necessary. Actually, right arm. Right arm going down. I'm going to need to heal that.
I don't have a med kit. Well, I do. First aid. There we go. Take their weapons. They're not dead.
They just KO'd. Really? Okay. Well, no. They're doing, they're doing good. All right. Back to
what we were doing. What we're doing. We're going this way. I'd be able to losing blood.
No, we're all safe. Let me F5 it here. Wait, hold on. Okay. That just crashed the game. Thank
God I pressed F5. Thank God I pressed that button. Lorag just gave $50 right now. Thank you, Lorag.
Hope yourself and everyone in chat enjoyed the holiday season. Wish you guys nothing but the
best in 2019. Thank you. Thank you so much for $50, Lorag. 50. Hope you had a great holiday season
as well. Again, if you're coming in and you don't know what the title means, New Year's Eve,
in a little bit, we are going to go over the whole thing again. I just want to make sure
people weren't confused. Thank God I did that. Awesome music. This is the Spyro 2 official,
official soundtrack. But yeah, Lorag, you've given a shitload of money. So thank you so much.
But yes, I'm going to have to talk about it a handful of times on stream. No, no, no,
I was going to do that. Hey, whatever. Let's go. It's okay. Continue what we were doing before,
this way. It's going to be an award ceremony on New Year's Eve. Yeah, I'm going to be in the studio
again. So should be a lot of fun. I'm going to, we'll talk about categories in a few hours
and the nomination process. And then there'll be a essentially like a 12 hour voting period
tomorrow. Awards for worst moments of 2018 on stream. So we're talking worst stream in 2018,
worst joke, worst hair, uh, worst brand of soda, worst, uh, worst joke, worst joke that took more
than five minutes to make. It's going to be about 10 categories. There might even be more than that.
Uh, there'll be a, maybe like a couple of best dubs, but I'd really want to highlight the worst
of the year. And then I'm going to present them and each one of the categories is going to get
its own nominee video clips. And I've got, I already did the Amazon order. I'm going to have
polio. I'm going to be in a suit is going to be going in front of the green screen.
There's going to be a presentation for each one. So we're going to go, because this was so last
second, let me just make sure I'm safe to talk about this for a minute. Yeah, I am. Save it right
there. Is there ore right here? Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. Hold on. That's a, what is this?
That's huge. No way. Frog must get over here. Look at how big this is. What is this iron? No faction,
no workers. That's huge. That is a massive iron vein. That's a hundred percent quality.
They can both do it at the same time. How many people can you have? Three people at a time
can work on this. Let's, let's do it. Just get a few of them, right? Just like make sure I have
enough money. Just give me a minute. Give me a minute. I'm going to put it into, now I'm going
to put it in my backpack because I'm the strong one. I don't think I should fill the backpack
though. Have frog carry massive moon so he gets it. This dog is not going to be able to ever walk.
May as well fill all of them to train spring. Yeah. How are we doing on food? We're good.
Everybody's fed. We're good. Just got to get to another town. It's all about consistently staying
healthy while the whole keg gives up five community subs. Thank you. Okay. Five more
community subs. Sweet. Very, very, very kind of you. Thank you. But I'm so scared to walk around
over encumbered because when you do that, if somebody gets the jump on you, we're just going
to die out there. He's building a worker strength, right? Yep. Should be. You're going to die either
way. Not with that attitude. Can you buy a horse or something? I don't know. I'm not sure.
I really don't know what this game has to offer. You can sneak while mining without a downside
to get sneak points. How do you sneakily mine? Tap the whole vein. That'll take all day.
All right. That's okay. I'm going to fill up his inventory with rocks so he can walk slower.
Holy shit. Squards just gave out 10 community subs. That's like at least 30, 20, 30, 40 or
something community subs in the first 25 minutes, 30 minutes of the stream. Thank you guys so much.
What, he ate cookies? I don't even want to, where did I get cookies? Sign people jobs to stay
together? Yeah, that's a good idea. So a significant portion of this stream will be getting all the
categories set and giving all the rules for nominating and voting and everything. Holy shit.
Thank you Lake Drinker for five community subs. Thank you Anonymous Gifter for five community
subs. This is the high quality content. This is why everyone's given so many subs. Watching me
mine a iron vein. Thank you for that. Really though, guys. Thank you. He's way over encumbered.
This is it. We're out of here after this. That's good for now. Let's give you guys some jobs.
Everyone's over encumbered, right? They should be struggling to move. No, they're sneaking.
Well actually, if I sneak, doesn't that just build? Sneaking? It does, right? Hold on. If we just all
sneak together. Stealth. All right, so hold on. So we have a shitload of weight down, so we're
building strength. We have sneaking, so we're building stealth, right? Yeah. Now that's a
900 IQ play right there. That's probably like what you're supposed to do. So I'm just going
to sneak all the way to the next town. Let's get a quick save here. All right, let me get a good
look at the map because I want to make sure nothing crazy is going to happen. So I'm going
to stay on the road. There's no reason to go off road, although there might be for whatever is over
here. What is this? A vein? What is it? A copper vein? I don't know. Now stay on course. Build up
stats. Sneak all the way to the next town on times 10 speed. Bet three with five community subs.
Thank you so much for the fucking subs. Now let's stay on the course. A hem hack. What?
What's wrong? Is he all right? Harm unthrow, harm unthrow. She lived a life of anguish.
Oh, he's about to sing. For chained in rebirth, she was condemned to languish. Till one day,
she'd been ravaged by the high paladin, most vile, and she swore her dark vengeance with a
murderous smile. Who the fuck did you get this song? She stashed a long nail, forged a blade.
Great- oh my lord. Great Canadian fuck club, 20 community subs, five community- five community
subs, a maxi Kaspersky. She killed all the guards. Uh, that- what the fuck? Who just gave 50- somebody
just gave 50 community subs. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. This is happening too fast.
What happened? Wait, wait, wait, wait. Who's looking at us? Who's looking at us? Uh, I don't
understand who's staring at us. I'm panicking right now. Okay. All right. All right. Wait, wait, wait.
This is uh, I gotta say, I gotta look at this for a second because what on earth is going on? Did,
did somebody just give maxi Kaspersky five, great Canadian fuck club, 20, Torah tea, 50, and then
is it 100 or 50? 50? Wow. Uh, Torah, you guys are- you guys are out of control right now. Thank
you. Rampaging Scruppa 5, Torah 50 community subs. That's- that's two- what, 250 fucking bucks?
You just spent 250 dollars right now. Holy shit, guys. Did I ever say the F word? I'm sorry.
My goodness. I did not expect that today at all. I did not expect- I never expected, but
I appreciate it, guys. Thank you. And if you had a- if you got a community sub, awesome. Thanks a
lot, guys. But the real question is, what is- what is looking at me right now? Is there something
here? I don't know what I'm looking at. Wait, wait, wait, wait. It's a dog. Bone dog. Can I-
Goal is attacking others. 14 attack and 12 strength. Why are you so good? What?
He's gonna kill us all. This thing's gonna kill us all right now. Is there, like, something I can
do? Oh my god, this is bad. Uh, we're all over encumbered. Wait, hold on. 6 plus 4 minus 11
and 5 versus- what's the defense on? What do you got for defense? Dexterity, toughness 14,
strength 12. Should we try to kill it? I think we have to run, but nobody can run. All right,
stop sneaking, everybody. Um, do I have to drop everything and run? I think I do. Drop all the
ore on the ground. Drop everything and fight. Fine. Okay. Okay. Ready? Drop the backpack.
The backpack has so many vital things that I can't drop the backpack. Drop the backpack. This is too
much important stuff. Oh my god, but what if- what- I don't know. Okay. I'm at minus 2, 5.
Let's go. I think I'm ready. Get everybody selected here. Let's take on the dog. I'm ready.
So make sure everyone- we got everybody here. Everyone's selected. All right. Attack target.
Are we ready? Okay, here we go. Frog not selected. Oh shit. Why is the frog not selected? Oh, because
you're all the way back here. What the hell are you doing back there? All right. Nobody's sneaking.
Here we go. Attack target. Three, two, one, action. Get him! Hit him! Somebody hit him!
He's so much bigger than my dog. Somebody hit the fucking dog. Get him! Nice. Okay. What's his
health at? He's almost dead. Left leg. Left. Cut his leg off. Cut his leg off. Cut his leg off.
Well, he's distracted. Get it! Do it! Kill him! Is he dead?
There's no winner in this battle. I don't- what do you mean I don't have a med kit?
How do you not have a med kit? What? Oh, for the love of fucking god, everything's in the backpack.
Is anybody still alive? Dying. Dying. Dying. The character's unconscious. Character's unconscious.
How far away is that? That was 10 minutes ago? What do you mean no scumming? I have to scum this.
That was right when I was about to get on the road. Welcome to Kenshi. Welcome to the stream.
Yeah. We're fine. We're fine. Look at this. We're back here. Same deal. Everything's good to go.
I'm sneaking. Building power. This time that dog's not going to be here because it happened
right here. So I didn't lose any time at all because that was- there was a shitload of community
subs and I stopped. Yeah, we're good. We're fine. We're good to go. Dog is fine. Everyone's nice and
fed. Everyone's happy. Discovered Holy Farm. All right. Let's take a look. There's one here.
Holy Mines and Holy Farm. Let's pay a visit to the Holy Farm. I'm gonna save it right- hold on. Make
sure there's nothing here, right? Because if I save it here, we're good. Save it. Aren't you
wanted at the Holy Farm? I'm sure we'll find out. I don't see any enemies or anything. All right.
What's the next OST? To be fair, I'm on day 100 something. I have about 20 people. Tony Hawk.
You want to put on the Tony Hawk OST? But I'm gonna get the whole- the channel- this is gonna
get shut off. Too late. Yeah, rip the vlog. Oh, I'm not gonna put on the Tony Hawk soundtrack.
All right. How about just play it at like times two speed and pitch it down?
Dodge the filter. So I thought somebody said- somebody said Starbound. I thought you said
Starbucks. I was like Starbucks does not have an OST. The Starbucks OST is like- now that's what
I call music volume eight. Put on Sneak King OST. Oh, that's the Burger King game. Who the
hell would upload the Sneak King OST? Do you sit in your chair and you're like, you know what?
I think I'm gonna upload the Sneak King album today. No. It doesn't exist. It doesn't exist.
Yeah, I did Animal Crossing before. Simpsons hit and run. All right, I'm just gonna pick one. Let's
go Starbound. Starbound OST. This is six and a half hours? This is six hours and 40 minutes
of music in Starbound? What the fuck? Holy God. All right, here we go. We've saved it.
Holy military base. All right. I need to train. I need to get my characters leveled up. They're so
shitty. Holy military bases here. Holy farm. Was I here before? No, I wasn't here before, was I?
I was over at that one, wasn't it? Wait, what's wrong? What's going on here? I don't get it.
Heal yourself? I'm okay. Should I? I mean, if I'm at 93, 91, that's my left ink is bandaging. It's
not urgent. This is so dumb. Sneaking everywhere. Why do I have a pelican mouth? It's red. You're
bleeding. All right. Well, first aid. Wolf den 657 has been wiped out. Wolf den. What does that
mean? That keeps popping up. We can stop sneaking now. Let's just walk. I still have all the ore,
right? Yep. Somebody here want to buy it off me? Can we all go to the bathroom at the same time?
I mean, did I just hear shit noises? I think I actually did hear that. Did I? Am I making that
up in my head? Hold on a minute. Did I make it up? Is he going to the bathroom? I thought he was
doing it too. That's just the way he stands. I might be just, my brain might have just been
making it up for some reason. All right. I need to get these guys jobs to follow. Follow me. Follow
the job. That's good. It's just shift click. You stay close to me. You also stay close to me.
And also bodyguard. Staying close, bodyguard. Staying close, bodyguard. That works.
Let the dog go to the bathroom. The dog doesn't need to use an outhouse. Let's go back to
no reason within the music because obviously there is none right now. What is this music?
Starbound OST. That was a good one. Public building. For sale? Whoa, whoa. This building's
for sale. Some buildings are available for purchase. This panel will tell you how much
the building costs. I could buy this for 12,800 C's. You can also often buy destroyed buildings
for a cheaper rate. You must repair the building before it can be used. Really? That's kind of
cool. Play at 0.5 speed. Can I steal this? All right. Well, this is, I can buy this building.
What about in here? This is a public building as well. Holding alt. Oh. Who is running this
place? Oh, this person up here. I can't do that, man. I'm sorry. I can't handle that.
That was funny for five seconds. I need some good ambient, like Lord of the Rings music is
going to get this channel turned off. Uh, what about like, okay, Lord of the Rings royalty-free
music? Did somebody make a version that's royalty-free? Just do Skyrim. Hold on. Lord
of the Rings mix. Let's put this one on. All right. That sounds okay. Uh, looking to trade.
Let's see. No, this is not Lord of the Rings. This is a fake Lord of the Rings soundtrack.
Okay. Sell price. Sell it all. Get some money. And change over to you. You got lots of stuff in your
backpack. Speaking of backpacks, I wonder if I should have, uh, buy another one. This is designed
to fit a bowl. You got raw meat? Oh, I will take that raw meat. Cotton. What am I going to do with
that? Arrange that again. I got some more food. I'm, I need to kind of get in a major town here.
He's, is he still mining iron and not? Oh, yeah. Hold on. Let me fix it. That's, that's times two.
Normal. There we go. This is not Lord of the Rings. All right. So that's all I can really do here.
I do have some money. I don't know. What about animals? I can buy animals from this guy?
Talk to. Uh, got any animals for sale? Oh, would you look at that? What is this thing?
Look at this, this attack on the, I got what's 9,000. That was so good. 13 strength,
nine melee attack. I only have 1600 bucks. Can I buy like a baby cow? Anybody else want to join
me on my journey? I can't talk to you. You just like, you just get out of the way and stay out of
sight. Holy shit. What's in here? Oh, not worth it. Oh, there's a backpack. Bread. Oh, I didn't pay
attention to the, I just figured it was, I keep forgetting that when you open up a, when you open
up a box, there's a chance to steal. When it's on a table, you just, there's, there is no chance.
You just take it. Whatever. I really do want this though. God damn it. I keep forgetting that.
Simpson's hit and run OST. I think that's all I can do. I sold everything. What is this doing in
here? Wait, stay together. Stay together. What's wrong with you? Why can't you run this? All right.
No more Simpson's songs. Okay. I need something ambient, not like TV show theme songs blasting
in my fucking ear. That's just the McDonald's theme song guys. Where do you think they got it from?
No, no, no, no. Slow it down. A halo OST. McDonald's OST. All right, let's go. I sold all my shit.
I need to move down here, almost to this river. I'm maybe, go through like the purple zone maybe.
Let's go boys. I'm loving it. The Simpson. All righty then.
This is just Ace Ventura. Did you say boomer show? Ace Ventura is a movie starring Jim Carrey
And it is a classic. A little post here. I feel like I should build a little town or like at least a shack
What is that though? Hold on. What is this?
Is there a campfire over there? No
Song? A fly flew up my nose. Just get a grip
All right, there it is
Small copper resource. That's worth a lot of money
And the sandstorm
Let's get some copper
because
Uh, this one's 80. So don't mind the one back there
Same thing
Line it up. Sell it in town
Train
Both work together on this, please
Excuse me. Work together on this, please
Excuse me
Is there a reason why you're not working on this, please?
Only one work is allowed on here
Oh god damn it really
laboring 37
What do you have for laboring stuff?
Nine
Uh versus 37. Yeah, you're gonna be the one doing it
Send the other guy back and forth to sell stuff
All right, well that's a good soundtrack
But I don't want to hear it anymore
Is this gonna do anything?
This is a this is a silent video
This is a screamer
Okay, that was that video was 15 seconds long
And after nine to ten seconds that played
Is this better?
What the fuck
Is this from like the 80s?
I don't what that was that a
You can't apparently find it
How does how has nobody uploaded a high quality version of that? I have no idea put halo back on
Zootopia
How about how about super mario rpg? That's a good one
That's what i'm talking about. Let's go
Let's go. Can I get some hypes in the chat, please? Can I get some hype in the chat guys?
You know what I'm saying typing like hype space. Yeah, baby
You know what i'm saying?
Fucking worst word in the english dictionary
That's it. What what happened to my youtube player? What it broke? What?
How am I still on the internet? Am I still like alive?
Okay
Can I get some hypes in the chat, please?
Holy shit make the other dude do something
But I don't have anything for him to do. Is there another? Oh, but there's a vein right here
That one's like a low quality vein
Well, he can get the low quality one
Me and me
I'm serious. What was that? Was that me talking?
Who was it? All right, you're on that one. You're on that one
Here we go
Do
Hey, what a great stream I got a nomination for worst stream of 2018
I wonder what you guys think it's gonna be sneak. I'm sneak. You're right. Good idea
tmnt
Hey, like can I get like a quick, uh hype in the chat if you think this is cool
How okay? No, no, no for real. I don't do that. But I think a real question. How often do people ask to do hype in the chat?
like on other like youtubers
Is that like is that actually a thing that people do there's no nobody does that right?
Am I like i'm making that whole thing up
Like nobody actually says that people always make it like the joke
I only got one it's the menu theme
I'm just gonna fill one bag and then we can go
But this is how you get everyone stronger except for the dog who's just eating food
I have a food consumer. That's all the dog has done so far
No more osts
You don't like osts
How about just something easy in the background?
uh, let's do
ambient
relaxing music
Calm space ambient or deep sleep help
It's supposed to help with you to get you into deep sleep
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Whoa. Hold on pause it
Oh
Thank god, we're sneaking everybody stop what you're doing. Where'd you go? Don't start singing here. Where is he?
Are you right there? You're like blending with the ground stop what you're doing
Don't hit that don't mind that
both of you stop
Wait for these bandits to pass
This is not good. I'm warning stop talking to each other. I think we're safe
Well, I don't know what what does this wolf den thing mean? I think I gotta move
No, don't go that way. Are you crazy?
Are they just gonna stay on the road?
All right, they're gone. All right, good back to what you were doing both of you
All right, that's one full bag of copper
I feel like we should get maybe a couple more and then after this we're going to turn off the ost
Both of them and then we're going to play in-game sound effect
So who can hold this?
I can
Mind all day, but it was worth it because now i'm gonna have a lot. I remember I need money
Selling two full backpacks of
ore is gonna be
You're talking about
Two four six eight i'm gonna make like five grand four or five thousand
cats for this
And then guess what I get to hire another person or I get to train
And these guys are leveling up their skills
What song is this? This is called the name of the song
is
Calm space ambient relaxing music deep sleep delta waves background for meditation yoga is the name of the song
For those of you wondering
Or let me in more easier to understand terms put every single tag possible
Every search possible in the title of my video
It's brainwashing me
Why?
germa craft 2
You you're pretty much watching that right now. I got news for you
How's everybody doing?
Well, not bad two full bags and then we're no
Do just do it just get it done save it three full bags of copper ore
Just get it done. So I don't have to do it later
Somebody just said no. Yes
Yes, I have to
Save it now sure thing
That's not much more. That's only like that's another one bag and then I got seven or eight thousand then I can buy a cow
You guys will not be complaining once I get a cow as part of the frogs and dogs team
Why am I sneaking because it doesn't matter as long as you're sneaking and doing something you get points towards stealth
All right. Now just fill the backpack and we're done
That's one two three four a lot, but just bear with me
Bear with me here
Put them both in the same one. I can't
Only one worker is allowed
On these veins
All right, it's got an all capitals message. Please play this please play this please play this please play this the best song, please
Okay
It's working
Wait, are those bandits?
No, they're mercenaries. Wait, they're mercenaries
No, none of them are friendly. It's so much stuff
Don't encourage people to do that. Well, isn't that to me discouraging, right?
What's happening barf? Hey look out for barf
Is he a hostile?
normal
He's a drifter. He's patrolling
Okay
strength 10 martial arts 2
That's not that good
dodge bad
I think we can take this guy. I got attack 10
toughness 1
Toughness 1 no attack at all. Okay dog is going to taunt
Okay, I want taunt on dog
And then you frog bus is going to be main attack
As his dodge is terrible and i'm just going to be the healer
Make sure I don't have any more pieces here. I need to make sure I don't fuck this whole thing up
All right, everybody stop what you're doing
Stop sneaking
Nobody is sneaking. Okay
Let's just play this out for a second
Uh, um, when is it? Let me i'm gonna save this
encounter
Now let's move over here. Wait, that's too fast
Can I talk? I don't think there is a talk button here. I got no bubble
Follow bodyguard
Get him
missed
Well, this guy this guy's got nothing we're gonna finally get our first kill and i'm leveling up top this and shit
Just don't let him have anything just continuously get him
He might have like coins in his pocket or something
Good. He hasn't hit anyone
Perfect. What a perfect training dummy. This guy really is barf got him. Okay. Now what do we do with him?
What do I do with him?
Uh, I thought that was his inventory. I was gonna scream
He's got armor. Uh, what kind of armor do you have? That's pretty nice armor
That's cut resistance efficiency
That's harpoon resistance. They got okay, that's coverage on the arms
Uh cut resistance 80 somebody else needs this
80 pause it for a second valley. What about the pants?
50 blunt resistance two two and then 50 percent
I'll be taking those on I need to put them on frog musk because he's the one that's actually going to be fighting anything
out of trading range
We need to be closer. So we're gonna go with uh pants
What do you have for armory? Zero zero eighty three four seventy. This is better
shoes
Okay, what is this shoe sticks? Yeah, take it
As much as we'll steal his food
Okay head
These are
1.1 times
1.1 times and what hey you you need those take them
Faster and get the helmet
Didn't even have a weapon. You have a shirt though as we'll take that and wear it
Yeah, he had a chew stick in his boot
Give the hat to the dog
The dog can't wear anything
Okay. Now let's what did I get for strength and tough? Okay. He is good to go now. Look at the six. That's 10
three defense finally
three strength
I mean this yeah, it still sucks so much but you get dexterity from swinging. All right back to what we were doing
He's gonna wake up, isn't he?
How do I make sure he doesn't wake up?
What should I do with him?
Save him
What do you mean enslave? How do I I can't enslave somebody? How do I put him down?
Well, there goes the hope of doing that
How what am I supposed to do?
Pick him up and sell him
Well, he's dying. I'm just whatever
Welcome to kenshi
I've been there before it sucks
Don't worry. You'll just like get mad and make a new character anyways, like I did
All right back to it. All right. That's good. Speed it up again. He's not gonna get up. Right? What is his he's he's dying
He's gonna die right?
All right. Got okay copper coming in
Let's go
Sell him sell him sell him
Well, let me just fill up my bags first and then i'll take a look at what I got
Use him to train up your first aid
Wait, hold on. I can heal him kill. I figured out what we're gonna do with this guy
Okay. Yep
Where is his body?
He's dying
Let's heal him
And then kill him again and then heal him and then kill him again and then heal him and kill him again and I'll level
up my
Like welcome to welcome to kenshi dude. Sorry
You got all the heals?
Uh first aid you come over here you get behind him
So how we doing? He's
Currently being healed
Am I healing him?
Yeah, I am. Let's take a look at my first aid stats
first aid field medic
Ha ha ha
That's so funny level up the come on first aid skills 4.1
Level up. All right. He's gonna get up after this
Is he just waiting for him to stand up?
He's in a recovery combo
Well, then i'm just gonna this is gonna be my training dummy
I'm just gonna carry him around until he wakes up
How many of these am I using not very many? Okay, he's almost at full health
All right, so now he just has to come out your head is in the process of healing
Just pick him up and let's bring him over here
This poor guy look, i'm sorry you were the one person wandering around
All right, let's get
How are we doing on uh?
All right, I can get like another few
All right, that's fine
It's just gonna recover on my shoulder
Almost there
But desperate times call for desperate measures, you know, okay
Use him as a spare ore backpack
All right, one more. That's it one. Nah, look at that could get a whole entire inventory and then have tons of money
I wouldn't mean I can
You know what? I can you're right. I could just put it but what if I what if he gets up and runs away somehow?
He can't run away with all the ore on him because he'll be weighed down. You know, that's true
He'll be too
Like
Uh, why am I getting tired?
Why am I slowing down here? Excuse me
All right, let's put him down
Uh put his body down
Okay, let's see
He's on he's on. Okay. Wait. Wait. He's on. He's gonna wake up. He's gonna wake up
Everybody get ready
He's gonna get up
He's gonna wake up in
Quick weigh him down weigh him down quick in case he runs
Okay, you ain't going anywhere
Now let's get everybody selected just gonna get up in a second here
uh
Nice day. Hey
All right. Well I did what I wanted to do
You get over there and mine this one again
That freed up the backpack
keep an eye on him because
I if he gets up and runs away, i'll be very very sad
Save it now. You're right. Yes, you're right
So I got so many backpacks full of money i'm gonna be able to buy a house for us to live
finally
Second backpack guy is perfect. And when he gets up I can take this stuff off him and then we can we can hurt him again
We level up our sword skills
Recovery coma minus 34. I gotta be ready for when that happens
Should be pretty close
You so bad at mining dude, come on
Dog yeah, we need some more food. We gotta get to a town
We should be fine until we get there though. How you doing minus 31. Let's get a while
whoa, whoa
Hungry bandits. I don't think they can see us though. They're too far away
Yeah, they stay on the road. It looks like unless don't come down here
We're not coming down here good. We're safe. Should be sneaking. You're right
This is day two in a row of mining
Almost done and we're not gonna have to do this again for a long time
Trust me
Save the game. I did
How's our friend doing 27
Uh for litty
Thank you for litty for the five community subs
Thank you. Thank you. Thank you. Thank you
There's a lot of those tonight
It's time to go in about 25 seconds
Maybe a little less
We have enough room for one two, three, four, five six
All right. What do they stand up when they get to zero, right?
End of the mining voice. Yeah, it's getting close
What am I gonna do about the guys weight?
I'm gonna carry him. Someone's gonna carry him
Packable holy nation. Okay, that's fine
This guy's not affiliated with the holy nation. So
My labor has to be so high on this character at this point really
One two, three three more
Minus 28. Okay, I got time. You know, we're gonna put them over there and just kill them again
Collie Brady, thanks for the five community subs collie brady
Thank you
community subs
One more wait
I just i'm sorry. I actually got scared. No, it's me talking
I saw the text and I freaked out. I'm sorry. I just screamed one more and that's it
Okay
Done
I have so many we're good
Everybody regroup
So let's take a look at what we got
Everybody's sneaking still right? So
We have one
one, two, three
four
bags
This guy's gonna get up very soon and when he does we kill him again
So who has the strength to pick him up? Probably you
Stealth ko him. No pick him up. I got my four backpacks
Let's all stay together
So i'm gonna give you the job to follow
you
follow
All right
Let's move save
Here's the real question. Where the hell am I gonna go?
I could go back here
to blister hill
I could could I build a base should I build a base here?
I could just keep going but i'm out of food though
I mean, this is the easiest one. Although i'm not sure where a town is
I can go down to this. Let's just take a look and see what's on this road
Wait to this guy's gonna get up in a minute. I need to be prepared when he does
Explain the rules for new years
Not in a minute
Minus 15 still out
Are we all sneaking?
Now we are safe before the trip. Yeah, I will
Let's make sure everyone's ready to go
I'm sure I don't I gotta be careful on the road though because of bandits and this dude's gonna wake up soon
So I kind of need to go off the road
Yeah, there's gonna be a new year's thing. We're gonna go over it. It's gonna be a significant portion of this stream
discovered stack
Well, there's stack
Looks like we're going there
All right. I don't see anybody on the road, but uh, i'm gonna keep an eye on i'm gonna keep my eye on him
Because once that gets to be about minus 10
From my he's when is he actually gonna get up minus 10 or zero?
in a second to load
Because this was such all right. Let me just break it down because there are quite a few people here now
So I might as well just go over it
So there was this was a very very last minute thing
I don't know if whoever was here yesterday
We talked about what was the worst stream that I did this year
And people were saying oh this one this one. It was just a joke, right?
but then
earlier today
Sitting in the chat
And it was
Hey, like wouldn't that be kind of funny?
If we just did an award ceremony
Where I go to the studio and I set up a podium and shit and I get in a suit
And we do a full 10 to 15 category
Worst stuff I did this year
And as like maybe like a couple of best of what happened this year, maybe
And we're talking that's the thing about categories is because this came up so
It wasn't very long ago, right? It was so recent
that
A significant portion of this stream is going to be coming up with categories
so
That we're going to do that. I have like probably seven or eight that I want to do
But we need to come up with some before the stream is over
So then you guys can nominate there's a channel in the discord that's currently locked because it's not you know
Whoever's not ready to do it yet
So after we do the categories
Then you guys are going to give nominations
And then a day from now
I'm going to close the nominations
You're going to vote in the discord because i'm going to put a poll up in the discord because i'm not going to be streaming over
The next two days
Because this is going to take a lot of time to get ready
so
After today's stream the next stream will be on new year's eve
Because i'm going to cut up videos
with all the nominees
So let's say it's like worst overall stream of 2018 is the final obviously final
Award
I'm going to just whatever the nominees are i'm going to it's going to be here are the nominees and here is a presentation of
the worst streams
the worst jokes
You know, i'm going to do 10 15 different categorical videos
That's what's going to happen and i'm going to obviously give a speech for every category to talk about what I feel about it
Worst frame was your wow one. That wasn't 2018 though. I'm pretty sure that was 2017
Stop the yoga music. All right. Yeah
Worst new character is going to be one
Yeah
Yeah, the worst joke there's going to be worst overall joke of 2018 and then there's going to be other categories as well
as if
What was I trying to say there like?
Ie is what I was trying to say
Worst joke that took at least five minutes to set up
Worst noise like the fucking worst noise i've made
all year
Worst voice impression there's plenty of categories we can come up with here the worst haircut. Absolutely
And then you'll see clips of all the different worst hairs that have happened over the years
And you're gonna pick what the worst fucking one was
No, let's turn that off now. Turn it back on
worst category
All right, let's go to
Let's get something else
How about gym music?
best workout music mix
Is this uh, is this allowed
to jock jams
WWW dot memers club. Thanks the five community subs
Thank you so much
Oh, yeah, worst chat experience stream. I can nominate a couple of those
Like the worst stream where the chat was the worst on in that stream
Nominee all of them and you guys have to accept the award
No, I don't want to play that. I'm no okay. No ost for a little while. Let me just play
All right, so let's go. I gotta watch his health
Minus 10. Let's go
Hey, hey, hey, hey, hey, excuse me. I'm gonna go to stack. I should be able to kill him again outside of stack
At least I think so
Get in there
Whoa, this guy's gonna get up and get all the fucking ore this guy gets free stuff
Really? And there you come. Hey, hey, holy nation. Welcome. Thanks. Welcome to the party guys
What's he gonna do when he gets up? I loaded this guy full of stuff dying dying unconscious dying
I just want i'm gonna reload it but I just want to see the hell he does
You know what happens when you wake up like this your bag is full of gold
You have money in your bag and there's three people dead and they all have the same material on them
Wait a minute. We're okay. I can level up my first day. I don't have a med kid
That's we're okay. What's about what he's coming up with? Come on. Okay first day
He's gonna stand up. He is at full everything don't kill in front of the holy guys. I'll follow I have to follow him
He's okay. This is leveling up the toughness to remember. I gotta level those up. I can't just reload every time
the dog, okay
Holy shit. Come on
No, he's waking up. No, no, no. No, come on
What's he gonna do?
Just keep an eye on him. The dog is dying
Heal the dog. I need to you don't have a weapon take out your weapon. What's take out your weapon?
Why am I not using my weapon? Wait, it's because my arms are both
Broken and i'm flailing them around like spaghetti
I got him. Do I have a splint?
That's it. Are you alive?
They're dying and shit. This is not I have to let him go. I have to let this guy go with all the ore
I have to what do you mean? No reload. Hold on. I gotta run like there's nothing I can do about this
I have to let him go. I got attacked by wild wolves and then that was it
Congratulations, I hope you enjoy. I hope you enjoy all the fucking free ore because I can't I have
I gotta go back and heal everybody
I'm too weak. Yes. I am too weak. All right, who needs it the most?
You're all right. You are not all right. Give me another med kit. I need to drop some splints
med kit
Med kit
All right, pick him up first aid
on dog
Reload and pick up ore before he wakes up
No, it's too no I gotta
All right dog is in recovery coma
You need to be healed as well
At some point. I can't just redo every one of my mistakes
Plus I need this to happen
Because I have to take the damage you have to get better
Toughness is important
Okay, do I have it? I got a splint
I need to have splint my arm
How do I splint my own arm? So i'm all right candor off is fine
Needs to recover
I'm gonna have to pick up both of the animals. I mean both people
I'm all fucked up. Give me some
Well getting the use out of these that's for sure
Can I carry both people? I think I can carry them both
But I have one fucked up arm
Okay
Splint my injuries
Uh, is it not splinted? How many splints do I need?
No, it's splinted, right?
Okay
everybody's
Good just hungry hungry
Okay
Why did I splint the wrong arm?
I can't I can't pick him up with this arm
Well, hold on what's wrong with me
Oh boy, there's food
I need to that's worth money
You need to get up
This is so dangerous being on this road with I can't just stay here. I have to all right
You're gonna get up. We're gonna hide over here
Away from any bad bandits
I'll make a campfire. We'll eat
Right here
And then I need okay. I got some food
I need to go a little further out right here
Up. Okay. I just splinted the dog campfire
Campfire camping camp bed doesn't cost anything but a campfire here anywhere in the wild
Uh, oh that was weird. Okay right here
And then we're gonna make a campbed
right here
Make three of them
Building why are you standing in the fire? All right building. Wait, I didn't did I can't make those
Three of them for three people to be in the bed
Select a construction to check its status
This shows how many building materials I need to complete the construction once the condition is bar filled the construction is complete
build
I need
What do I need?
Sleeping bag one more building material will be needed. Why need one sleeping bag? Well, all right, whatever cook the food
Don't eat them both
All right, how are we doing recovery coma with dog recovery coma?
All right
Uh, I guess now i'm just gonna sit here
I'm off the road. I should be away from anybody
I don't have any sleeping bags. So I can't do that take off taunt
They're gonna be in a coma for a long time
Save the game
So this is like post attack. We got attacked
All right now
We times three idle
Wait, hold on. Is there anything I can get?
I need to go maybe look for supplies or something
What's over here?
Is there anything I can do here?
Right arm is getting better
very slowly
I don't think this is anything. Can I fit any more stuff?
Because I know that there is
A few things over here animal teeth. I think I can pick them up
um
I can't
I still have this meat. I need to get rid of uh, I need to put this back on him
I need to go back
Okay
trade
So I need to put away some of this stuff
He's stacked, right?
Why not?
Oh fuck who ate it? Did I eat that? He's the only person that's eaten
I need to be able to take the skin and there's another thing of meat over there
Can't pick that up. Why is it longer than that? I mean what was that all about?
All right, that's good
Okay cook the meat
Should just do it automatically, right?
Yeah
What was that noise?
Seriously though, what was that?
Whoa, no get away from me
What are you doing over here? Why are you over here? Uh
What are you doing here? Is he gonna know?
I have to sneak away, but is he gonna see these two?
He smells the meat you asshole
I have a crippled arm. Can I play dead?
Hold on. How do I play dead?
Where's play dead? He's going the other way. Oh, come on
RNG, please be in my favor go the other way and I get that meat out of there
Okay, that's fine. Good play dead play dead. What do you guys got on recovery time? So long
You not so much but can carry the dog
Okay, I think it's time. I'm just gonna sneak back and forth like this while I do times three speed
Fight with honor. You can't fight with honor with a broken arm against 15 people
We gotta move cam. I gotta pick some I gotta pick you up and we gotta go
Maybe not RNG. Come on
He just needs to wake up and then we can get the hell out of here minus 35
There's no way I can speed that up at all
Food. Oh free food. Come on
Somebody's dead too. Come on kill the kill them and move on put out the where are they they're coming this way, aren't they?
They're right there. I could kill these three easy. No, I don't have I can't even use my weapon. They're all killing each other
This is perfect
Let me sneak over there because they get on the road and I got free supplies right here
Hold on. Let me I gotta dump this stuff over here
Temporarily, I got a bunch of shit. I'm gonna just put it down right here, right?
Make sure nobody comes over here because this probably supplies and food
Okay, i'm gonna go for it. I'm gonna save it right here. There they are. All right, come on get up there
We have a couple of bodies. Yep. Come on get over there body number one
You got nothing important
With the wolves the body too right here
Nothing worth taking nothing. Where are those wolves?
Right here. Come on. Really?
Yes
All right, go bandits are these bandits are these holy men holy men? Okay, we're good
What about some more supplies back? We should be fine after this
Get another camp built campfire. All right, get the food up there. It should be already doing it, right?
All right
Are we good? I don't see anybody should be fine
What is all this? Oh, that's my okay
Well, I need to it's fine food's more important right now
They can still eat right if they're unconscious
Or they have to wait till they get up
These pelts are worth. Okay, what's worth more money?
the pelts or the
Let's see
We're good. Save it again
How do you fix your arm? I need a splint and I already used it
I don't think I have any more
I do put it on the ground here
Didn't I already do this?
All right, so that leaves me with
Yeah, these are 175. So that's okay. I'm all right with that
these sell for
Not very much each. I need to free up some space
I'd rather have two more
coppers
Let's open up your bag
We need to trade with you
Let's put these in here
All right
get these on
you
Rearrange this I can take some more
And that's good
All right. Now you just have to recover and we have to get the hell out of here
You've been healed
All right minus 28
Save it
Where are you going make a plan now? That's true. Okay
I mean, I already had a plan. I was gonna go to stack. It's right there. It's right here
Maybe I should just run him to stack
Or run the dog to stack and then he can get up later
That might be worth doing
Dog is not going to get up for a long time
Neither will you
splint the dog
Uh, did I already did I thought
I'm gonna have a splint right here. I have first aid here
splint
No, I can't
Can't splint myself either
I mean, I don't know how far away that is though
I wonder if that's a good idea. Just you know, I think that's what i'm gonna do
pick up the dog
Get to stack put dog somewhere safe
And then when he gets up eventually here block to stack
That's the plan. Let's hope nothing goes wrong
stack
Good luck canned roth
Let's go. I gotta move. I can't just sit out here
The sacrifice needs to be made
I've got the material
I need the backpack. Fuck
Give me the backpack
Just in case something terrible happens to you
backpack
All right
Get on there. Let's see. We got
We got all these materials. All right. Good luck. See you later
let's head
to
Stack it's right here. Hopefully this is like not a hostile town or something. That would be a horrible pain in the ass
Good luck. See you soon. Take care of yourself
I hope you're okay in like
15 minutes
Everybody on the road
I think we're safe the dog. I think the dog. No, the dog is not dead. The dog is recovering
Everybody's fine
Sneaking. Yes. I'm sneaking because it gives you points
Take a look
stealth stealth is increasing because i'm sneaking
Or it was
Is it not anymore?
What it was doing it before?
It only increases when you're near people
Well, never mind
Okay, i'm almost there. All right. How you doing over here
What?
Who is this?
What did you?
He still has everything. He's fine. What did he take? He didn't take anything. I still have all the material. What did he even take?
Food did I even have any food? He took the food
Where am I? All right. Hold on. I should have put out the fire. Just get up there. I'll make you still let you good
I'm gonna get up soon. All right, I made it drop dog off. Holy sentinel get are you kidding me?
free food, um
Why can't I stack it in my inventory?
Damn it. Are these they'll stay here, right?
They'll stay i'm gonna go right to a shop. You're still okay 917. No bandits or anything
What love and devotion brother your time for a moment? I don't have time for this
Divine blessings brother darkness tries to make its way to our hollow lands only through vigilance can be defeated. I need to check your belongings
Holy brother, may I
you fucking assholes
Take the book, huh? Take the book take the book bring the book take the book get the book
You need the book. I stole this book and now they're gonna know you need it not to get kicked out. It's stolen
I stole all this stuff. I understand good. Let's see. Ah the holy flame
Well, just a quick check brother looks clean. I was supposed to have the book
Uh
Get me into it. I need a saloon
stat
Right over here. Come on. Just go to the bathroom
Quickly get over here sell this stuff
We demand an apology
All right. Look do I have to say i'm sorry?
when
There's been like eight out of ten times
You guys made me do something that I wasn't supposed to do
It's like the boy who cried wolf
Let's see your wares
sell
Look at that money
Not not even half of it 6500 bucks
We accept apologies in the form of doom osts
Well wouldn't oh wouldn't you wouldn't you? Yes, you would
And I don't want this weapon, okay
So that is 6700
How are we doing over here?
Minus 15
I might have to come out and get him just put the dog down somewhere to hang out
The stream that cried book
Yeah, it's he's I gotta come out and get him
I have to
Now i'm gonna put the dog down
Thanks for the money. See you later
Dog will just hang out over here somewhere
Put down dog
Dog is just recovering dog doesn't have any items or anything. So
And i'm bringing it all the way back here to go. I can run now. I actually can sprint
So let's save it
And get here turn it on. I need to go pick you up because yeah, I don't think you're gonna get up in time
It's riskier
Who's on this road?
Probably servants. That's fine
What a disaster. I haven't done anything. We put on osts
And then I got killed three times
All right, make sure there's nothing on the ground here
There is some animal teeth
Might as well just get it
All right back it up
Nothing else on the ground
Let's go
the front door
out
And is that is it?
these raiders
pack beast
um, i'm
Am I gonna cross the bed? There's something out. Wait, we got a potential we got a loot situation coming up here. I think
Because we got a fight brewing
between some
The holy servants and are they raiding this town or something?
Nomad trying to be running over to them. Something's gonna break out here
Are these competing factions?
No, they're going right to the front door
The dogs are just a lot like the weird animal pigs that just can go in. Okay
Wait, what is going on over here?
Well, that was quite the distraction free meat
I thought they were coming to me
They were not coming to me
Well, I gotta get this meat
Give me give me give me
They might they already take it. No, they didn't
Let's go
And meat on these guys too. Probably this would be good
Oh, yeah
Can't believe they're not taking this this up. So valuable
That's even more money
Cool. Let's meet up with the dog and go from here
Okay, I gotta put you down
How cool easy
All right minus seven. Let's go ahead and swap out
a lot of stuff
Nobody will steal these if I leave it on them, right?
it might
For the first time i'm gonna have more than 10 grand. I think
save
Put the guys in bed. Yeah after I get up after I get
Liquid cash is when i'm gonna i'll take care of the the two
And we'll go from there
Buy a second dog and breed dogs
Can you do that?
Ninety eight seventy two. That's too bad
oh well
An idea two dogs
That is an idea
uh
I don't think it's necessary actually because he you're almost up
Yeah, they're they're gonna be fine another minute or two
Uh, let me just go pee
I'll be right back
and we will
Uh, actually, let's take a look. Is it time?
No, not yet
another like another hour or two and we'll do the
The new year's eve stuff we'll get it prepared
So well, we're not done with the game quite yet
But i'll be right back. I'm gonna take this see you in a minute
Okay. So yeah, let's now we're guessing germa's height in inches at 69
I don't mean that as a funny look at how funny that was joke. That's just how it's just how many inches tall
Okay
Back to it. What time do you need? Not very much for both of you
I'm gonna take this opportunity to go buy
first aid and food again because
I have
These don't do very much
The nutrition is really not good
so let's go
either
Maybe to go to I should I all right. Here's the thing
Should I?
Should I get gear should I actually have them put on real equipment?
Should I get more first aid?
buy better backpacks
Get another companion get another person
buy a house
I think I need a house
Because I need to I need to reliably train somewhere because I can't keep walking up there
Hey, you're not supposed to be here. Get out of here. All right, kill him now
Just get a house
What do you got in here? Let's trade. What do you have?
Um, i'm not gonna buy this shit
mind stone
It's my arm still screwed up
it is
you could buy the rundown building near me and then
Repair it
Let me go in here one more time. I want to see just i need the traveling store. No traveling store
traveling
Man, where is it traveling?
This one where is it?
There's an inn the bar
The hell is this a bank?
general store
Rob a bank. I'm like, I can't rob a bank
i'm looking for that
traveler
So I can buy the backpacks
Where's the backpack store?
I'm gonna take a look in here and see what's in it
Almost up. They both almost up
Invest any people to talk to welcome customer
Trade goods, let's see what you got. Why am I running all the way around?
simple rug
fabric
straw flower water
research
Well, here's some basic first aid kits
Look at that price markup though get up
Yeah, get it. No
That's too much right 112 percent
Travel stores leave this other side of town quality
Five out of a hundred. Why are you these this those are so bad
Let me just see if there's any others
other side of town
so like over here
and that's
The like food store, right?
There is the traveler. All right
Get in there. I want to be banned ban me ban me you won't
What are you doing?
Why would I ban you what are you talking about?
All right, this is important. I need to make sure I get this right
Because these are expensive so
large backpack
This backpack is huge. Don't even think about fighting with this on your back
The thing weighs a ton just when it's empty
Do you seriously think you can fill it full of iron or something and be able to lift it?
Let alone carry it across the desert go get a smaller one
traders wooden backpack
A wooden backpack with a built-in sunshade. It's the height
Of luxury for the traveling trader
traders backpacks stack items
Okay, so I should get three of these how much are they 400?
Mmm, she's a dog enough. Can the dog have a backpack? Can the dog have a small backpack?
Look at this reduction. They all only one person should have a backpack
Get rid of the dog already
This one's 400 i'm gonna buy it. I got this one
Let's see. I'm gonna go like this
You can just drop a backpack before every fight that kind of scares the shit out of me though
Okay, so that's now
That's a smaller backpack
How much what's a full stack?
What is it 10 20 for a full stack?
What if I do backpack inside the backpack now that i'm not doing diablo 2 for roger cube bullshit
I could sell this
No, that's all right for now. No, what about these boots?
drifters boots
Blunt resistance cut resistance. These are pretty good
I'm only 149
Athletics effect. Let's see
coverage right leg left leg stealth effect is worse
athletic effect
so the sandals
Give you combat speed and run speed
whereas
These are actual protection
I could keep both of them. Just how many pairs do I want?
So these are plated long boots
These are these are less these are worth less. Okay
so harpoon resistance, they're a little worse, but
Oh, it's just a high grade
Standard grade high grade. I get it
save money
Save money for a house. Yeah
That's probably I need food and shit too and I don't want to go broke. So
What and what is this thing?
I really am wearing the nintendo labo
You're almost up
Oh, wait, wait, wait, wait. Hold on. I wanted to go in the other building here because this is the
Oh, I want to go in like one of the bars of the food store or something. Right. Let's just go in the bar
There's some people in here too. I could get another companion. I could have four
human mercenary
I want to hire a bodyguard 2 000 per day
Get out of here. Where's the chump that can do it for?
Plastic surgeon you can redo how you look. No, thanks
Gecko
I'm not too forward speaking to you brother, but you're from the outside, right? I'm looking for work outside the city
How much are you charging?
Just a standard 3 000 cats
Should I get gecko three that four?
new friend
Done. All right new band
of outlaws
Do you come with a weapon?
Oh lord
No
Very tall
Oh god, no, no, no, I like that other way better. No, that's not okay. I like that's too much
There's tiny legs though huge legs
I'm making a chadet
Chadet that's not a bad name. Hold on
I have like a a drip tray underneath my chin
Okay
Now we're making like we're making like jab of the hut
a big head
big chad head
Big chadette head no small head tiny head cheeks
mouth size
mouth width
Fine looks all right nose position
That is weird
No, this one
Making schnoz. Well, what about the other way? What does it look like? No, I think I like it right here right here
brow position
up brow tilt like that eyes depth all the way in eye narrow
Eye closeness get a good eye tilt eye height eye size
Jaw chin depth all the way out big chin wide chin
It's adam sandler
Madam sandler
No, give anime hair
Well, if you're part of the frog team, you gotta have green hair. That's very important. Can I get a full view here?
Oh, man, how tall is this though? This is gonna be obnoxious
Max leg length. I don't think I can do that. Where's leg length?
No, this is fine leg
Uh click confirm I need a name madam sandler
Chadette is really good too though. But now it doesn't even look anything like adam sandler
But that doesn't even look like adam sandler. How's that? You got a middle name chadam. Madam sandler
Oh my god. All right. What about
I don't know if I want to confirm this and we have to live with this for a long time
This is not just like today or tomorrow all the way back. Yeah. Oh my god
All right, you have to join the band of merry idiots attack. I need gear
All right, let's get together
Follow let's go
No, I was supposed to buy shit at the bar
Who sells stuff here you?
let's trade
Meat sell value. Is it 38 or 77? That's no, that's bad. Get some fish
Buy a rundown shack. I need a place to be able to stay because we can't just
Oh, we have roth is up. So you good here. What about dog?
Mass of moon is almost ready
Let's just meet up
You can buy a house in this town for really cheap
Can you I need to find a little dumpy?
Can I buy this?
What can I where can I buy?
You have to rebuild it
It's only four thousand for a little shit dumb place
Oh, is that it right there? Oh
Let's go
Wait, somebody get the dog
That's only fifteen hundred
Let's go
new house
Are we all here?
This one is fifteen hundred
Oh boy, are you ready time to?
Level up our game here
for sale small shack
Buy it
Do you want to buy this building? Yes
Look at that
Wait, no, I have to fix it
Power 400 battery charge. Why does the house have a battery? I need how do I fix this open to the public? No
Turn that off
nice house
um
repair
What do I need?
Building material three more building materials would be needed to complete the construction
I need three more building materials
You know where to go go to all right. Everyone just get in there
Everybody hang out here. Actually. No you you got the dog. So you stay
All right chadam
I need building materials
trader
Is it just general store for materials or do I have to go somewhere special for that?
Building materials. I just take them too. I'm just gonna take them. I'm gonna take them. I'm gonna steal them
Why pay for them?
Um, all right. What do you got building materials?
Building look at the building materials
I see one right there
I'm just seeing if I could reach it from here. I can't okay
All right, how much are building materials?
building materials they are
How much money do I got? Those are fucking 85. That's all right. All right. I've got building materials bring them back
Those aren't that expensive
Let's go
Why are you oh you're walking? That's why
All right. So then now I need
Two more go ahead and bring them over
adding materials
Five out of five building. All right, everybody get to work
Go on all of you
Doors closed
Doors unlocked
building condition five building small shack construction complete
new house
Everybody get in
We're gonna put beds in here
I finally have a actual location
So now what?
I guess I can build
lights torch post
Okay, let's put two in here
Oh, I need more building materials
Buy some sleeping bags. Okay. What else can I?
private
Small shack. All right, so I can do what else can I do buildings?
camping
Farming vegetable farm lights mining tech small research bench
My research bench is vital to enabling new weapons and technologies. This little one will fit in a small shack. It is good for getting started
I need three building materials
That's gonna go right here
So I need some building material three more
Go get it
How much is a bed?
What do you need? What do I need for beds?
tech mining lights farming camping camp bed
need
Four three or four sleeping bags
How do I turn a tilt?
An item how do I rotate?
He doesn't even I don't know how to rotate
So this is gonna go. All right. Hold on. I need to redo this
Uh dismantle because I didn't even do anything yet dismantle
Block this out
Uh, you guys get out of the way
build
tech research bench
Get it right against this wall
Now I think I want it over here
This thing's so huge because you can't even open the door. That's the entryway
Sleeping bags will be back there
So i'll spin this around this way up against this wall
Can I get it here?
Now you got to get out of the way, man
Everybody get out
Everybody out
It's good
It's kind of in the way, but it's all right
flush against the wall
Stop the v's
I can't stop the v's
They're just in the game
All right, so I need
camping camp bed
What's the problem get in there?
You you got an issue with this placement game. What's wrong?
two
three
Three is fine. All right, three sleeping bags
three building material
Go to town and get it
general store
Oh shit, it's closed
When are they open?
She's building up her lock picking. It's fine
I thought the dog could see me do this but
Holy shit, this person doesn't see me doing this
Well, that's good
You see me why I want to make sure people have skills
Save I already did I saved right when I got to the front door
I hit f5 right when I got at the front door
That's okay. You can see me, but that's fine. Doesn't matter
I'll do it again
What is this thing?
Whoa, what are you? All right. All right, you could see me but
You're doing something else
Did the great canadian fk club just come in with another
10 community subs
Oh my goodness
Thank you so much canadian
fk club
Add it to your
In how many do you have at this point? I didn't I didn't catch it. How many community subs do you have now?
It's got to be at least
Like 40 or 50 or more
I think I got it. Okay. I got it
And that's fine. You can see me then i'm not i'm not doing anything
I'm not doing anything
Thank you, dude
Really?
I'm gonna save it up here
Make the main character a master thief
Yeah, but I just in case something happens
You know, let's just say
I don't this is not a person. They're not gonna care
All right. Here we go. Let's take a look
building material
This is one for free
stone
Fabric steel bars. Let's get the steel bars. Who are you?
I don't think I thought the guy was upstairs
I thought he was upstairs. I thought the guy was sleeping upstairs
whatever
Go in there and kill him. Why would I do that?
No, 30 nothing just sitting around here
I gotta leave
I got one and he's gonna get up and i'm gonna walk in the door
Shit, what time is it five? Oh shit
All right. I can't go upstairs
keep playing
re
I'm gonna get this one for free because I know I can get it and that and i'm gonna leave and then just do it
It's still night time. I got it get out
Okay, the whole purpose was to come over here and get this stuff. So
I don't need to sneak anymore
Hey, look at that save
Steel bars. I it's I can't
When does the store open?
five minutes
6 a.m, right
steal the door
You can't steal the door 6 a.m. Hey
I have some things i'd like to buy my favorite customer. That's me
How are you?
building materials
One two, and I also need
oh
sleeping bags
You don't have them
I think I have to go to the other part of town, but that's fine. Thank you for that
At least I can build the research bench
How's everybody doing over here? So let's get some of you guys to work
No, get up there
And then you go get the sleeping bags
How long is that gonna take?
very long
Where's the dog? Oh in my arm still. Okay. All right
frogmasco
to the
adventurer's store
Which is down here
Welcome back
Building small research bench is complete
Let's get why do they always do this?
sleeping bags
uh
I don't see any sleeping bags
You're too short to talk over the counter
I mean that that makes sense
Well, you don't have any
All right, how to research tech to learn new tech you can buy blueprints from merchants or you can research the tech yourself
The research you must have a scientist
Assigned to your research bench select a squad member hold right click on your research bench and select a use machine
Research people depend on your assigned scientist science skill stat
That is a tongue twister
assigned scientist science skill stat assigned scientist science skill stat
Next you need to select tech to research like tech from the panel
Select any tech you want to research by left clicking it. You can queue up as many as you want
So somebody kind of has to stay back here and do that. The question is who?
i'm gonna say
can't rock
My original character is terrible
The dog can't do it
The dog cannot be a scientist
I'm, sorry guys
Can the dog be a scientist?
Dog cannot be scientist
I can be a scientist
Hold on. Let me look at the stats here
so we got
chattam-mattam
is
default for everything brand new character frog musk is
labor medic
labor medic, uh
can roth is
huge labor athletics huge and
I think he just I think can roth is just gonna have to be the
The one that does all the stuff that has nothing to do with fighting
strength 28
10 1
Or I don't know
You should mine. I need another character
I need another character. I need to go buy another character to be a scientist
All right. I'm gonna go buy a scientist
I'll be back
Everybody hang out
I gotta find another person to be in the squad
Let's go with the bar. Let's go this one start at the end
If you're searching i'm a bit of a scientist myself
That's all right, though. I mean
plastic surgeon
No, nobody in this one
Check the other ones
a lot of people in here and the
fence
No
a lot of people
thief
Thief fence. Do I have any stolen stuff to sell?
No. All right, which one of you?
human mercenary
Oh none of you are
What upstairs?
No, none of you want to come with me
So that's these two bars checked
Are there any more?
bars
What about in here?
Who are you holy servant?
Let's do business
Oh food
Yeah, I need food
Just already ate it bread. No, it's too much money
Why do that when I can just take it?
honest to god
raw meat cooked vegetables
dried fish
Dried fish dry. It's so expensive
Make william defoe
Everybody up here
Nobody up here. God damn it
Well, I need to find somebody to purchase first
those are
both
Empty of people. What about down here?
you
No
Barman. No, I can't afford to make another character
My fourth now. I maybe I don't I did spend a lot of money. I don't want to go broke
Somebody's gonna have to stay back and be a scientist
And it's can't be the dog
More I just got a new character
You know what? I'm gonna stay back frog musk is gonna stay back
For now. He's looking his arm. His arm is still all screwed up. He's not gonna he can't do much right now
I'm gonna have a splint. He just needs rest
use
show research
gear storage item storage public sales
crafting
Two hours I need a book
farming industry training
Simple training dummies. I need two books
What do you mean books?
storage box or storage box
Things will go a lot smoother if we organize an efficient method to store and distribute our raw material. Otherwise things are going to get jammed up
storage or storage steel bars steel iron plates copper
Books are next door
There's so much going on here
You sell books
What you got?
Okay book a book from the university of
Machinists everything they need they learn is compiled in the books like this one
So how many I just I have to buy book. That's it
Nothing else just book
Steal it
There's nothing here to take
Stealing is bad. I'm just gonna buy the books. How many don't need three two. I need the training dummy three books
Was it two or three?
Because that's three six nine
three six nine
Because I'm gonna need these for other stuff too, right?
three for lockpicking training two for okay
So that's
I need five
All right
That's all i'm gonna do right now so I can at least I can do lockpicking practice
Let's get done frog's gonna stay back his arm is all messed up
so use
so research
training
what
Okay, simple training dummies damn rookies are useless keep getting beat up because they can't hit anything a basic training
dummy would let them train their attack skills up to about level five
and then
Learning to pick locks is hard to get started. It's too late to learn once you're locked in a cage training
Is needed to get you put in the ladder
Okay
Get it
three hours lock picking three hours like real time or in game time
Who's working on this?
Am I working on this?
Engineering right
Science, okay
He's got it. So where can I put the training dummy?
I want privacy
So we've got show the research. All right, let's speed it up
Wait ever people can we can all do it at the same time, right?
use
No
No, only one person can be here. Okay
Only one at each bench
So we do just kind of have to sit here
sit here
There's a huge fight going on and i'm not seeing it
where
Huge fight. There's nobody out here. Like I didn't get baited. Did I?
Almost done. There's no dog bed. Well, that's all right
Who's training science?
Uh, it is frog musk is the one that's doing it
Specifically because frog musk is currently very injured
And it's gonna take a while for them to heal
All right, we got a training dummy
Well, hey, why are you doing that?
Not because I moved him
So now build let's just see what happens here build
training dummy
Need four iron plates. Shit. What if I put them outside?
Oh, man, this is such a small shack. I can't put them anywhere
Where am I gonna put this?
It's gonna have to go right next to the bed
Make a second floor. I can't afford that
So I need four iron plates
Now all of you leave it alone frog musk is the one that's going to be using it
The rest of you
Are gonna have to go on a mission here
There's the auto save
These buildings are unexpandable. Okay
so I have this
group here
I need
I need to think of where the hell I want to go from here
Because I have I need food. So we're gonna stock up on some food
buy another shack
Take the backpack from musk
Lee i'll leave the dog here. No, but the dog is fine now and the dog has actual damage
I'm gonna say from here. We're gonna just explore down here. I want to see what's over here
We'll go with the three of them
So that would you know, let's get some food
Let's make a frog musk does not have any jobs, right?
Go mine some rocks
Go look for stuff. Maybe another town
Lock your door before you go. Well frog musk is going to be in here
so you
follow
bodyguard you
Everybody walk together
You got it
Time to let's close the door
Uh, don't I have it set to their move they move together?
Why is it going so much faster?
All right food
Close the door on your way out. He's he'll be fine
backpack shit
Trade give me your backpack
There is a little bit of food and some
Okay, so I need to
This is frog musk
give that to canned broth and
Frog musk you just put that on doesn't matter
Maybe I should give the other backpack to madam
All right. We're ready
four seven one point two
Uh, this is actually
This katana is better
Tack bonus. Yeah, this thing's terrible
All right. Let's do it
Close the door
It's time to go buy supplies
So i'm gonna say let's go to the bar. I need to buy a couple of things of food
We're not gonna go very far. I just need to go far enough to get some money
I need iron. What do I need iron?
Bars or something
Let's trade. Here we go
and i'm gonna get
Two of these
We need it. We're gonna go out
I know I just spent all my money, but it's necessary. I'm gonna get it all back. Don't worry
I need four steel plates
Out into the wilderness we go which is down here. Good luck
Are there no quest givers in this game? There are not
this is a
This is a sandbox RPG
There are quest givers where what?
Why does this guy have three and a half thousand viewers?
Hey, stop pretending like you just got here. I see the sub. I see that you're a sub
You can't like pretend like you just got here
gifted sub
Come on. That's like going to the movies
And you've got you're about to go see
No, no, no, no, no, no better example. That's a going to a restaurant. What are you? Yeah
It's a restaurant that you like you've eaten at this restaurant before you sit down you order the food
The food starts to come out and the whole time you're going like why does this restaurant this restaurant sucks
Why does this restaurant have four stars on yelp? This place is awful
They bring out the food you cut into it. You eat the first piece of steak. Oh boy. Oh
Who comes here?
Why would you ever sit here and eat this? You know, can I talk to the manager manager comes out? It's me
Yeah, hey, how are you? Hey, did you make this steak? I did. Did you like it? Yes, but fuck this place. It sucks
Okay
Manager, why am I running so much faster? I have the like don't I have the thing where we all work together
Is somebody sneaking?
Um, excuse me. Somebody said why did you say a five star steak that I said four?
I said a four star steak. I didn't say five
Hold on. We got a problem. This thing sucks. I should be able to handle this. Is it like a mother around?
He's a pups. It's only a few of them pups pups. They only have three attack
That's an adult. They're not faster than us though, are they?
Can I outrun them?
Uh, i'm matching their speed
No, fuck is this acid rain?
They left. Okay. I'm in acid rain right now. I think
This blood what is this?
discovered hive village
where
Um, everybody's fine
Hive village, but that's where we're going
Hope they're friendly
Buy that shack. No, i'm not gonna buy the shack
Save it here. I'm looking for a vein. I just need a vein a vein preferably that can have two people on it
What was that?
So, uh, you know, we got to get one of them lanterns while we're in vain
lanterns
Lanterns what lanterns?
You know the lanterns them lanterns of radians
It would be like going to the swamps and not buying drugs or fish. Why do you want drugs?
Why am I stuck on?
You got to buy a lantern
You mean lantern of radians?
All right, stick with it stick together, please
Yeah. Yeah lantern of rodents
Somebody ate raw meat. That's not good
Why would you eat the raw meat?
There's food in there already. It was the dog. I mean the dog likes raw meat better
Uh, is this it?
Is it bug people here? I feel like they bought their bugs here. This is a store. This is a store
Hold on open to the public hive
How do we get in?
Uh, hello. Okay
Well, let's go to what do you guys sell?
There are a few stores
Store is store over there
What's that?
Copper and there are two workers available for that
Hey, see you see you in two hours when I get this thing clean who owns this?
No faction get it
It's a hundred quality as well
price markup
Can I stack these? Yes, I can
That's gonna be this. Hey, this is what we're doing. Hey
You know, I got an idea. So now that
Now that we have a minute here
a lot of minutes
Check on musk
Well, this they will stack in here, right?
What's wrong with them? You're okay
Why did you stop doing this? He has no food
I locked him in the house and said work on it
I took his clothes on his food
He's standing in the dark
Oh, yeah, yeah, he'll be all right. I'll just go buy him a snack right now hungry
Standing naked in an empty room
Work on it
Work on what sir?
Uh, i'm gonna
Yeah, they're possessed by robots
Weird. Okay. I'm gonna go buy. Uh, I don't have any money
So I can buy like one piece of beef jerky and that's it
Need to go to a bar that sells it
um
I'm gonna say i'll try this one
I wonder what barth is doing right now
That's a great question steal it
All right. There's a can of cooked vegetables over here
It's very possible that I can sneak
And get the can of cooked vegetables
And just eat it
If I just wrap around here
Got it right over here
a literal
Rat i'm gonna be just fine. I got plenty of food now getting that raw meats pushing it. All right back to work over here
To lock lock picking trainer, which is in my house
Close the door behind you lock it. What's wrong with me? Um, my uh arm seems to have healed itself
That's good
All right. So you got food you got some bread you got some grog and cooked vegetables. You should be fine for a while
Back to work
Lock picking training good. Let's check on this
Look at that. What does it say?
Your your machine is full
Your machine is full machines are buildings
Only have a maximum of materials I can hold after they produce them
You won't be able to produce. Oh, this is the this is technically a machine
Okay
Back to it. So five can be in there before I have to take it out
Close the door
He's he's fine in here
Lock pick training is done
I have so much room. Um, this is gonna be a lot. I'm gonna have probably twenty thousand or thirty thousand dollars
That's very possible
Uh, I can I I they're just gonna have to sit here all day forever
I'm sorry. They're gonna be here forever because i'm gonna get like a 400 steps
All right. What else can we do?
use
Show research pause it. Don't just idle here. Don't be an idiot
Okay core
gear storage
It doesn't require anything
Do it
item storage
Public sales it would be it would save us a lot of running around to sell goods if we could just get the customers to come to us
Crafting defense electric. Okay storage boxes. This is no requirement
Just queue it up farming boxes more storage
Smithing training. All right. I got a huge queue here. You got enough food
You got enough food. Good luck. Um
What do I what do I do with the dog?
The dog doesn't have a job
Going to dog adventure
All right, the dog is going to explore the universe a little here
First I want to save it and then we're going to get a dog song
We'll get some dog music. I got just the thing
So we got these are the ones that I was and look what everybody's going to contribute to this. Why not?
We're all just sitting here. So categories for the new year's eve stream will be
Obviously, we'll do let's just get them written down worst overall stream
Actually, I need to make this bigger. Let me just do that real quick
Stick it over here
All right, so worst overall stream
worst joke what worst overall joke of the year
worst hair of the year
Like a portion when I turned a camera on it was like that was the worst hair i've ever had
worst
joke
Taking more than five minutes to set up
worst new character
worst
I'm gonna die. No, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I'm good. I'm good
Whoa
There is a monster here. I gotta put my headphone back in
What is this?
Free
No, no, don't tell frog bus to get it. He's all the way over here. What's wrong with the dog?
Did the dog get hurt?
Who got hurt? He's all right. Okay back to what you're doing pick up this stuff
No, what are you doing? Don't fight another like fucking slime monster
Run away. Let them do it. What are these things doing here? Now? They're bleeding good thing
There's a store right there. Maybe I can level up a little bit here. No, okay. Take it free. Okay
Go back to what you're doing
Okay, we're good. You're still working on stuff, right? Yep public sales
Okay
Back to what we were doing again. I gotta stay here just in case that happens again
To like a bombable snowman's attack at the same time. All right zoom it out so I can see better
Okay
So worst, uh worst chat experience
What stream it was worst chat experience?
And I know i'm spelling these terribly but that's fine worst overall stream worst overall joke worst hair worst joke taking more than five minutes
worst new character worst chat experience
worst noise
and with and i'll give you some examples like
Like uh, whatever you can nominate whatever you want from last year
worst
new meme
from 2018
Worst worst streamer. No, no, because i'm not gonna put other i'm gonna just that's gonna be my name on it
All right. I got I will we gotta add some bests bests. Okay bests
Best overall use of cardboard I would say
That sounds pretty good
uh best
flavor of ice cream
Okay, make this a little smaller
um
worst
Worst category
I like that. I don't know why it's such a stupid thing
Spelled cat doesn't matter
So that's one two, three, four, five, six, seven eight nine ten eleven. I want about 15
Worst stream worst joke worst hair worst joke that took more than five minutes worst character worst chat experience and that means
What experience you had right? We're talking
Uh, like octogen like how unbearable was that chat, right?
You can nominate the worst chat experience best noise best noise. Okay, so we got best worst noise best noise
Stop no best characters
No, we're gonna have worst new character
I think these are all right because remember each one of these i'm gonna I get to cut together a presentation for them
So for over for if for instance, so the nomination process is only we only got about a day to do this
So i'm whatever it's probably going to be about six to ten nominees. I'd say somewhere around six is probably good
And me and the mods are going to pick the nominees based on suggestions
Whatever ones, you know
If people are writing a bunch of the same one people have different suggestions
The nominees are going to be put into the categories and we're gonna be i'm not going to be streaming over the next two days
This is very important. Very very very very important. I am not going to be able to announce to you guys
Hey, uh, so the you can vote now go and vote right? I'm not going to be able to do that
So just know you got to know this after today
You won't see me till new year's eve because i'm going to be working on this for the next two straight days
So the voting is going to happen
Off stream when i'm not there
You're just going to have to check in on the discord over the next day or so
Because the voting the categories are going to be up there. The nominations will stop tomorrow night and the voting will stop
uh
Not even probably 12 hours after that because then the whole next day i'm going to be working all day to cut up these presentations
So let's think about this worst stream worst joke worst hair best noise best overall use of cardboard
Uh, best flavor of ice cream worst use of music and best use of music
Oh, hold on. I gotta get back over here and collect these
Oh, that doesn't stack. It's not a stacking backpack. Shit. Okay. That's good. How you doing frog musk?
I mean, okay this work this worst we could do
Who the hell is this?
This the mechanical shop owner quick get out there get go go go get that stuff
Fuck you. She did it right when I got there. Ah
Get back in here
I mean this is also you could also do worst. Okay, worst overall stream worst overall joke. What about worst overall moment?
Right close the door. I got it. Don't do too many categories
Yeah, I mean because each category is going to take about five to ten minutes to get through them
Coming up with these on the fly. Oh, yeah, because this this came up less than four hours ago
Five hours ago is that and I got the studio time so it's happening
Uh worst internet
Problem, that's a good one. That is a really good one actually
worst
internet issue
best internet
worst overall stream
I can make sure but I don't think I want to do best overall stream because that's like oh
What was the best stream? I want to know what the worst fucking stream was
Best clip. All right, that'll tell that's all right best clip. I think that's pretty good
One two, three, four, five six, seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen
That's just the most used clip. Yeah
Uh, I got a better idea. Yeah, best clip is not going to work out
Find that one for me guys
Okay, here's the two categories that are coming up
I hate this category so much but it's going on there. I've done it so many times that you could like very I don't know
I'm gonna be up in a suit at the podium like going over these
We're gonna have to sit through and watch those
They're all the worst
All right, we can't get too crazy because I only have like I gotta i'm gonna put in like triple time to make this a reality
So I don't we got literally today into tomorrow afternoon
to nominate and then from there forward
less than a day
For voting so we really can't go. This was just a last second idea that I thought was gonna be fun. So
Let me make sure we got 15 right is it 15?
1 2 3 4 5 6 7 8 9 10 11 12 13 14 15
Biggest furry moment, but that doesn't make any sense
How the my oh shit, I you're right. Hold on. All right, you're working back on this you are
You guys are still mining. They got two i'll stay back here again. Okay
most worst sweat
Where has it been enough times that i've had like sweat all over me on stream?
Worst sweat
Okay. Now that yeah, i'll put it on there
So let's go with worst
worst
sweat
Or greasy moment
No, just worse that you get the idea worst sweat
worst game no, I don't the worst game that's
loudest scream, but the loudest scream doesn't work because all you have to do is just
Listen to which one was the loudest?
worst breakdown
On stream, that's a good one
All right. I think we're good. I think we're good. This is a lot
This is a lot of categories
best
best gnome
That no, what do you mean best? No, i'm not gonna do a best gnome
I gotta put these back in a better place here. So we got best
Let's cut this because the best is gonna be on a different section. You know what i'm saying? This is gonna be like this
Anything that's worst has to be I don't want that many best
Okay, so it's all worst worst worst worst
Get that here
I can't wait to do this one
I can't do the worst the worst peter and best peter on like on
On new year's eve
That's gonna be hard not to just crack and laugh my ass off during that because what a stupid fucking category
Best green screen. No, no, no because that wasn't a contest and I don't want to say that it was you know
I mean to work how you guys doing on food worst analogy. Well, we don't want to get super crazy specific because
There's only really
You guys remember like the worst analogy. You remember what stream it was
Because think about it you've got there's the archive channel that has every stream of the last year, right?
But like you're gonna go back and figure it all out. You only got like one day to figure that out
Do not underestimate best gamer moment. Oh, I like it best game. Okay, we're done here
Best gamer moment worst gamer moment and that's good because I can tell you there's been at least at least two
Best gamer moments i'm gonna oh wait, they might even be like one or two
But that's even funnier to me that there's only one nominee or two and there's like 20 nominees for worst
Yeah, best best jex moment and worst germa gaming moment. Yeah, and that's it
I gotta call it there because it's gonna take a lot of time. So and some of these categories
I might have to just straight up delete like the ice cream one's fine. I want to know what you guys think. There you go
Let me move this worse. All right, let's go over these one more time
So we've got oops wrong thing
So here are your categories
One two, three, four five six seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seven seventeen categories
Worst so here you go worst overall stream. What is the worst member?
What is the worst fucking stream that i've done in the whole year? Think about it. There's a lot of streams this year
What is the worst one i've done that you were just like that stream was fucking terrible, right?
What is the worst joke that i've done this year that you were just like that wasn't funny. That was just not funny
Uh, I didn't think it was funny to you. That was awful. There's been a couple of those probably at least one worst hair
You turned on the stream and you saw the face came and you were like, whoa, holy fuck
That looks really bad worst joke taking more than five minutes to set up
Sometimes I will pause the stream and I will go do something and in five ten minutes
We'll go by and i'll come back and like press play on it
And it's awful that's happened sometimes and to even it out. We'll do okay fine
We'll do best joke taking more than five minutes to set up as well to you know, even it out because that's 18
All right. So you got worst joke taking more than five minutes best choke taking more than five minutes to set up
Worst new character. There's been a handful of characters
It's been about five to ten new characters that you've seen on stream, which is the one that is the worst
What was your worst chat experience where you were looking at the chat room and you just
Holy shit, man. You guys need to chill the fuck out. Like what are you guys doing? This chat sucks
Like one of those moments. So think about that
What I don't know how i'm gonna do that by the way
Because I don't have access
It doesn't matter
Uh, worst noise that i've made that you hated that you wish I never make again
worst new meme that you guys say
worst
new meme
Okay, something that came from just something that on the channel or something that we said that you say that I say
Not a joke, but like a reference meme thing
You know what I mean the worst category of the year here
Why is that up here? It's kind of i'm not even
Worst internet
issue from last year
Where it was unwatchable to a point or you just hated it and it was awful and you left the stream
The best noise that I made all year in, you know contrast to the worst one best overall use of cardboard
There's been a couple a few times where that's happened, you know, what's your best flavor of ice cream?
No, just delete this one. This one sucks
That's gonna win worst category keep it. That's the best one
No, but like that's good
All right, find best flavor of ice cream nominate your favorite ones
We need the worst peter and we need the best peter and then we need the worst
Worst one is more fuck. Uh worst sweat moment for you
I just was disgusting to look at and you couldn't take it and the worst breakdown I had on stream in 2018
Remember these all have to be
2018 you can't go back
like oh remember when like he told stardom
Remember when he made that video? No, no, no, no 2018 this last year
No, we can't I it's gonna take so much work for me to put this together already a good 18 categories is gonna be fine
I can't even say that out loud because I don't want to give you bias, but somebody just said something really funny
Uh
All right, no, no best jebait worst jebait. I can't this I this isn't your categories
I can't do much more
One two, three, four, five, six, seven, eight nine ten eleven twelve thirteen fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen
no gamer moments, uh
Where are they? Did they not get in?
It was best and worst gamer moment. Did I type it in?
Apparently not
All right. Now that's 20 categories
Let me separate them again so you can take a get a good look at it because best needs to be done
I'm actually gonna do this
Uh, yeah, let's go like this instead
We'll start with the best just because that you know, obviously
Worst internet issue or it's noise. Okay
worst hair
Okay
Because the the culmination of this whole thing guys is the worst stream of the year is the big award
That's the big one. So that everything's there, right? One, two, three, four
Eight, nine, ten, eleven, thirteen, fourteen, fifteen, sixteen, seventeen, eighteen, nineteen, what happened to what happened to one?
Did one get removed?
Which one got removed?
Best best flavor of ice cream peter. All right. There you are. There are your 20 categories
so
in
We're gonna have rules here in there's a channel on the discord right now. The channel is called nominees
what you're going to do
is
You don't just like spam
In that channel you have to do just like in previous setups
You need to post your nominations in that thread in the format of what the category is
category
And your nominee, right? So you have to type it in
What's the category dash?
Here's the moment i'm talking about dash
Where it is because it's you can't just write
Oh go to uh, remember the stream you did when you like fucking bit your finger and you like farted
I have no idea what you're talking about. You're gonna have to give me a link to either a clip
or to a a timestamp to a video and again, there is the
uh
The vod channel has a shitload of these almost all of these streams that i've ever done in 2018 are on that channel
So we need to know
What stream it was?
And a timestamp if you have it or clip because it's going to be hard to figure that out if you just write a random sentence
So either if it was something that happened in the last 60 days twitch is fine
You can clip it if you want if it's happened recently and you know put it in there
But if it's something that happened a long time ago back in like january or february something then we're going to need timestamps
which is on the uh
There's a channel that is the archive channel, although it's not an official channel. Uh, i've talked to the
Owner of the channel a few times then that is it's a huge resource. So again
That channel is not for talking. It's currently locked right now
But that channel is only for nominations. Remember you got it. I'm gonna let's paste it here
I think you grump clump with this great format here. All right. Here you go. Bingo
That's what you need to do
And if the hour minute seconds I did that can someone put me back in the discord?
What
What about worst category is worst category is right. It's there worst category
You gotta pick whatever category that you hear that you think sucks. I want to make sure everyone gets it
Do we do we get it because i'm not going to be able to talk about this again until new year's eve
so once
Me and the mods whoever wants to help work on it. We're going to pull out nominations
There is no it's just like the christmas stream
We're gonna find you know ones and maybe uh, oh this one this particular one like 10 people have nominated this
20 people have said this same thing
Oh, you know like this guy said, you know, we're gonna pull them out for just like the suggestions for christmas then
tomorrow night
Voting is going to be open for about 24 hours. Not even maybe 12 hours because I gotta start working on this
So I will not be able to tell you this again discord discord. They will be that channel is going to be there. They will be another
Major there'll be another channel probably put up that is
Voting and there will be a link to a voting website
It'll be there within the next 24 hours
Yeah, and i'm that this channel is going to open in about probably like an hour or so probably like an hour or two
Post an example for the channel. Okay here is here's an example for instance category, uh worst
stream of the year, right like well or we worst, uh
Worst overall stream make sure we keep we keep them
You got to use the the text that you see on the screen here
So worst overall stream make sure the text is correct take a screenshot right now if you have to worst overall stream
Uh link to the moment. Let's say that's uh, you know
Hey, I i'm just I pick this stream because and then maybe maybe like uh, for instance like link to moment
I'm going to fake website link like a hyperlink, right?
And then if you can do a timestamp in there as well
That's good, and maybe you could give like a dash maybe like a sentence, you know, he
was shitfaced
and couldn't
figure out
How to open the door?
And you know you give like you can give like a small maybe like one sentence reason, you know what I mean?
Timestamp hour. Let's see like for instance like one
At 34 here's a perfect example of why I think this
You know like here let me go category worst overall stream link to moment fake website link
Oh, he was shitfaced and he couldn't figure out whatever timestamp if if you can do it
Hour 34 right for a reason
And that is also the reason why this stream is going to be cut short tonight
I'm not stopping now, but please don't post if no, no, no, I mean like i'm you don't post any fake links
Thanks for making a copy pasta
Yeah, it'll be the rules will be there. I'm in studio on New Year's eve again 7 pm eastern. Sorry 7 pm pacific
I already have a bunch of the stuff ordered that's ready to go. This is the only thing we got to do
And we have about three days to get it ready. Somebody just wrote already got the worst noise boys
Are you allowed to use clips from other streamers points of view?
um
As long as it happened in the last year and it's somebody that I know personally, you know what I mean?
I can't spell cat. It doesn't matter. I just wrote it. I did fast. I don't have grammarly installed
So, uh, i'm i'm before the stream is over. I'm gonna put this back up. But here are your categories
That channel will open in an hour or two
Just getting set up. So think about it now, you know, think about it while you're here
You know while you have a moment, you know, like one person
What?
kim
italics
Star, I don't I don't really know. I mean very many people
Vinny
burger boy
Are we both hitting this?
drake
But yeah that I mean when we talked about earlier, but cutting the stream short it is to get that ready
Because once I know the timestamps once I know the clips once I know I have to make them put them together add effects to it
make little presentations for all the categories
And that's going to take me at least a couple of days to do
Will drake be at germa con there is no such thing as germa con
Dabs for dinner. Thanks for the five dollars
And we're almost done doing this
I'm not going to fill the whole inventory. There's only so much hit
Uh rock with stick you guys can handle
So again, i'm sorry for like it's gonna end up being like a five hour stream tonight
But this will be fun. It will be a fun night
Five five five community subs not five dollars. Thank you for the five community subs
No, the sound isn't even on all right who has
I can still load this. I have a lot of stuff. It's time to sell
It just is
That's it. Yeah. Yeah, let's go. Let's go. I got plenty of shit
People are getting hungry. I got to feed myself
It's the store, right? Yeah
Masamune is still alive. Yeah
and fairly healthy
buy the lantern
Human welcome human human welcome human
All right, show me what you got
You have a lot of odd stuff
All right sell value. Okay
That's not bad. These prices aren't that great, but it's okay
1751 we got a lot of these
All the money I spent is back. That's good. It feels pretty good
Almost a 10 000 again
No, what do you have?
building materials spring steel steel bars. Don't I need some of this stuff?
Leather high vest
Nobody has anything else. No, uh
Spal you wait
Just sell it cares
building materials
price markup 77
I need iron plates
How many do I need?
I know I need at least probably five to ten of these
It's four for the dummies and then I should just buy the whole store
because these are
No, okay, whatever. There's a lot of other weird oddities in here. Look at all this fish
Books, dimminy you just regular food. Whoa, that's a lot of food
Hello. Hello. Um
What is happening? What's happening here?
um
error, uh
Why do you do this to the hive?
Let's trade
um, hello
Jesus I don't even know where they came from. Okay
Well, I sold everything
I got the plates I need
I can go back
Home with 8900 bucks
Then they have 9300
Who took 300 bucks from me?
Me
It was weird. I'll pay you back. Oh, hey. Hey, thanks, man
Let's get out of here
Uh, can you
Why are you doing this?
There we go. So we have plenty of money again
Got the plates for the dummies. It's time to go back and train
Are they raiding me?
I hope not
Take us back to stack
Probably nothing gets buy the lantern buy the lantern buy the lantern
You're right. I should buy the lantern
It's hard to see through this rain
Show me what you got
Where's this lantern?
Lantern of radiance
An old lantern. It looks pretty beaten up and barely functions. There are some worn out scratchings on it
Which look like the crude drawings of a child
Um, it's 40
It's only 45 cents
Should I get a bulb?
Okay
Well, this is a standard first aid kit. Yeah, i'll get this
I don't really need any of the other things
All right back to town with the plates to make the training dummies and then bank the money
I need the lantern for the lore. That's the most important part
Save it
Not again
What? I mean not again. What did I do? Is this this is porn and chat again?
Am I am I gonna have to like revoke links in chat?
Am I gonna have to stop that?
Have we've gone over the edge here?
All right, uh, I I really don't know what to say about that
But do I have to do like white listed links now? I might have to
Oh, yeah. All right. It's saved. Let's go. Don't click on any links. Never click a link
Unless I explicitly tell you to in chat don't you understand if you don't
If you don't hear from a mod or from me to click on this link don't do it
And I might have to edit permissions for links. What is oh, that's just frog musk is down there. Okay
Let's build the training dummies
Don't ever click on anything
Just for no reason don't ever
All right, we've made it. Wait, wait, wait, wait. Why are you stopping?
That's weird
All the research is should be done
I would assume too many link. Oh my god
well
Links are probably going to go. Bye. Bye forever. Hey, can I nominate something?
What do you got show research? Okay, so
Training the training dummies are here. I need iron plates. I got them. Let's make them
I don't have the building materials. Uh, yes, you do. Oh you do. Okay best porn link in chat
No, you're not we're not doing that
Everybody work on it
What is this gonna take?
No, this does not count as best porn link
Okay
You can forget it
Stream is going off the rail
Throw it on yeah, throw it on emote only it's got to be done this guy it's got to be done for temporarily for a few minutes
best porn link
No, you already got your categories. You already know what they are
All right training dummies are done. We can actually actually fight enemies now probably so who wants to use it?
It's only one
It's one training dummy. Oh my god. All right, get over there and start it training
Well, you'll be fine skin. No only one person to be on it
Jesus
200 iq
Now we've got to hit the cooldown zone right now
So let me look at the tac tac one. That's good
At least they'll be not totally useless
Hold on somebody got people are getting timed out by putting too many emotes in emote only mode
How do you get timed out in emote only mode? That's like impossible
How?
There's no way
You can't get like auto banned from emote only
What the fuck?
I'm just trying to level up my characters for crying out loud. I just need them to
Just make sure you get some good category. Make sure you get some good nominations
guys
Make sure you get some good nominations. Take a look again. This is happening in two. This is happening in three days
again
Today into tonight nominations in that format rules will be in the discord tomorrow voting
There will be a link for you to vote to vote for
Nominate to vote your your nominations, which you do you want to win in those categories? It's going to be one
Poll it'll be ready for you. All categories will be available. You just got to click a box then hit enter
two days then
from there
Bingo new year's eve stream pick your favorite one
Not to pick your favorite one, but you're gonna we already talked about it. You get it
It's actually kind of hard to talk when I hear this noise
These guys have to be all right. All right, so here's what's gonna happen emote only mode can now be taken off
I think that they've calmed down a little bit
Figured out that they can't just spam
They're gonna be fine
Uh
Your boy just gave about 10 community subs
Thank you so much
to do okay, there was seriously like
There were like two or three hundred the two hundred community subs today
All right. Well you train somebody has to go buy food
You can do it. Did anybody see my spam of the smiles?
I
I don't maybe I don't know
Food I got some food. I want some more food
And we're gonna go from here. I need some more supplies
You guys got me all you guys got me all twisted up
I can't afford that we might be able to afford another person
That's very possible
Get down to business. I will buy both of these
and
No
I really should just steal the fish
Steal the fish steal the bread
Chunky baloney with 10 community subs
Community subs from chunky baloney. Thank you
even more
Subs even more community subs
You guys are
awesome
except when you put pornography links in the chat room
And I know that only one guy did it
And one guy apparently has done it twice
So I don't I mean it is one guy but
Double d thanks for the five community subs
Thank you so much double d. I kind of want I want
Right click click click click click click click click click
Seven no, no, wait, can I this is a well? No, I don't want that
I feel like I want some more
How are you doing on training?
I'm gonna sit level five
Give frog musk a shirt. He'll be all right
He'll be all right until next time
We got three almost at four
Two people can use the dummy
Uh, it says one out of one this machine is fully staffed
I can't right? I don't think so. No
Buy a new house. Can I buy this one?
No, I gotta make sure that I gotta get all the essentials because now I have a lock picking kit, right?
So, let me see
Training locksmith training box. I need two iron plates
Stick this in the corner here
And put this that's not gonna be a problem
Do I have the materials for that? I don't have the building materials. Who does? I think I think she does
Come on. Hurry up. Come on. You have the materials in your back pocket
You don't have them either
Didn't I buy maybe I didn't looks like we're going over here
I need how many do I need?
I need two iron plates. I wonder can I buy them in here?
Well, can I steal them in here?
No, all right. It's from me. Where is iron plates?
One two, what do they two right?
Thank you
All right. Why do I feel like let me let me just okay. Wait, wait, we brought up a category
Of worst chat experience, right?
I feel like subconsciously
A lot of you guys are trying to make it this one
It's subconsciously up here. It's not even intentional
Two people are working. What are you doing?
I need way more than that. I guess I could do storage or let's see storage
animal feeder
Wait, does this mean I can feed the dog will feed itself?
Bolt box armor storage. There's so much general storage. Oh, there's so many things
Well, it's all right. Don't worry. The stream is turning off in like 20 minutes anyways because I have to get started
No, no
What the fuck? What the fuck?
I told I told you guys earlier
I have to I need to get working on the new year's evening at the beginning of the stream
I said this is only going to be like a few hours because I really need to get working on it
We need to get started on this shit. I got to start buying things making
Presentations I got to get a suit like I got the podium
And it's still early enough where I can get some of the stuff done now
It's gonna be worth it. Trust me. All right you
Train on that lock box you what do you go? Mustard five. Am I gonna stream on the 30th?
I'm not you'll not see me again until the stream turns on on new year's eve after new year's eve
Because there's been a couple of these streams
That have been that took more time to do at the end of the year kind of holiday stuff
We're gonna who the hell is this? Okay, a hung hungry bandits are just here. What are they doing in here?
Because he's leaving he's gonna get shot with a crossbow. I don't understand
Why do they take so long to attack him?
I love when they do this shit. They all freak out when somebody dies
Work on your training. God damn it. Can more than one person use this? No, but
Yes
But we're just saying the game looks awesome. The game is very fun. It's okay. Here's what I was gonna say
Oh, don't be calendar
You guys get a calendar handy right now
So
Again new year's eve is the next time you're gonna see me
after new year's eve
There's not going to be a stream on
new year's day
But there will be a fuck. Hold on. I got like other shit to do
Uh-oh
Uh, what am I gonna hold on? I gotta think about this. I actually have to think about what i'm gonna do about this
Because I have to
I got something I have to do on
third
Of january
I was planning on so
31st 1 2
Shit, ah
So new year's eve is it gonna be a stream new year's day
There's not going to be a stream. Oh fuck, but the new uh, january 2nd. There's gonna be a stream
January 3rd. There is not going to be a stream because I have something I have something I have to do on the third
For all right. Listen to me. This is important december 31st stream
january 2nd stream
january 4th 5th 6th
7th and you know what and the 8th in a row right because this is going to be really erratic over the next week
We'll do four days in a row because it's been really all over the place with these
Other streams that have been worked on right? We'll do four in a row
There's a lot of shit that I want to do. Uh, there's visceral cleanup detail. There's
Uh the frog crew
There's i'm trying to think of the other things that I want to do
There's metal gear rising
There's
I don't know. There's a lot of things to do
I need to look at like a list
On the 23rd i'm going to be in a full goalie outfit. So that's obviously happening
i'm that's going to be an irl stream where I sit there and just
In a full goalie costume just scared for like four hours
this
I haven't played metal gear riot. No, I haven't that's why it's gonna be fun to do
I feel like roth is being really really useless right now and you know, who else is being useless this dog
The dog has not done anything the whole time just exists, but that's okay kids a companion. All right, what's your uh, you
You are looking you need to go do something while everybody trains. What can I do with you?
I have some money. I'm gonna look for another companion. I could go on a stealing shopping spree
Get another companion somewhere lock myself in a cage and see if I can get out
I go treasure hunting
Nobody in here
It's a plastic surgeon
Let's head this way
Check this one
You'd better play metal gear rising with a controller on easy. The parry system will be too jarring for pc only
oh
Played on easy played on easy
Why play it on easy?
Is that a true statement? Should I be careful with that?
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no because i'm bad
We'll just wait to the uh, best gaming moment
Shit, I can't wait to see that collage
of moments
Anybody around for me to I have to go to another town. I think
Although this is public right? Yeah, let me check in here
I'm going to play it on easy. Why would I play it on easy?
any recruits
That would want to join me
High inquisitor. Let's see
Okra's light shines brightly today a good omen. Do you have any work?
I'm here to bail out a friend
Ah to pay for your friends heathen sins in the eyes of okra and their time in incarceration
Has redeemed them of the evil ways, but to shorten their penance the price will be steep
pay bounty for
Of no one this guy got work
Do you have any confiscated goods to sell?
The holy lord phoenix himself blessed be his name has marked us for the heretics
Has marked for us the heretics of okra look up for them and bring them to me for holy judgment
Has it marked for us the heretics of okra? Thanks for the info
What no do you have any goods to sell? Oh damn you do
But I don't think any of this stuff is worth taking
Bring him bounties. Uh, okay
heart protector
Can't wait for jerma dying to pinwheel in worst gamer moment. Well, here's the thing about that guys
Uh, you can't just write that
You need to have a document you need that needs to be proof. You need to have a time stamp or a clip
you
How are you gonna how's that gonna happen?
Worst gamer moment when he died to pinwheel. Okay, you just said that where's that I have to show it on screen
It's not as simple as just that's what i'm saying. You can't just be like remember that time when he shit his pants that
when
To be nominated
All this stuff is way too expensive. Although not this is not that bad
Yes, it is. It's too much
No, I don't want to spend that kind of money here. I'm just looking for a new companion
Somebody in here you have shit your pants. It was right after you lost a pinwheel for a second
I thought you were gonna say
Just shit your pants right now and then load up dark souls and lose to pinwheel right now. So it's on video
That's why I thought you were going with that. See if I can open this
Do all these things now
All right, let's open
Success. We're gonna save it
Oh, and that's a 55 chance to steal. That's it
Really? This is on this character
There's another one right here, isn't there?
This is weapon cabinet
Those cubes are so good, but only 55 percent
that's bad
moon jupiter moon jupiter
Just unlock everything
Yeah, it's kind of what i'm trying to do
I would have figured it happened with a 33 chance to open but apparently we are okay save it
55 percent these are all so expensive
I'm gonna be here. Look at all these locked more locked stuff
metal chest
This is safe
Got a first try. All right, what should I I gotta find the important things first
That's pretty important
Holy chest plate
A plastic spork just gave out five community subs
redemption
Redemption making amends
All right, I come but all right, but once all right, but twice
two times
How am I supposed to react to this?
You know what I mean? Okay. So if you're in front of the judge right now
You know you you you're walking down the street
And you like rip a bag of chips out of somebody's hands. Okay
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Hold on. Hold on
Somebody you're walking down the street. Somebody drops a bag of chips
And then they kind of walk away for a minute you grab the bag of chips as they're continuing to walk
And you take them and you eat them
You then the lady turns around says hey, what the hell are you doing with those chips?
Those are mine. I just dropped them like a minute ago. I came back to get them
What are you doing? You eating them and then you come in front of me. I'm the judge
You get arrested for that and you say it was a mistake. I'm, sorry
I didn't mean to do that. It was a mistake and I go. All right, you know, it was a mistake
That's okay. By the way, I have a bag of chips in my hand. You can just be more careful while i'm talking
You walk up to the podium
And you take the chips out of my hands
And you eat them in front of me and then you tell me that that was a mistake again
How am I supposed to believe you at that point? Worst analogy category? No, i'm just saying
You how do you make the same mistake twice?
And when they're supposed to be accidents worse and that there's no worse analogy nominee. It's not up there
So you good luck
There is no worse than allergy and I fucking forgot. Did I save it? That wasn't a joke
Well, how is that a joke? That was me explaining how absurd it is
For you to get caught doing something and then do it again and say there was a mistake again
How am I supposed to judge that? Is the judge gonna you know, let's say there was a judge here
He'd be like, I don't know about this one. That was kind of fucked up. Jeremy
Somebody said, you know, German it makes sense
Thank you. Oh, come on flip a coin
If I had these odds at the fucking blackjack table, I would be a trillionaire
No, I would lose all my money
Oh, that's the worst analogy in 2018
Fucking god, I need this shit. I'm gonna crash the game
Come up to me with a bag of chips and I sit there. The lady drops the chips
Somebody got it. I uh, whatever
There's no worse than allergy category. Oh my fucking god go to vegas
He come to me with chips in his hand
Yes
finally
It only took five six coin flips
You're in vegas right now. What the what?
Where the fuck am I? What where am I? I'm serious. Am I all right?
Uh, this is uh, I like this heart protector
Oops got it
Somebody wrote haha
What is going on? Who are you over here? Why are you over here?
Why did you sneak in here?
I did not tell you to do that
Now we both have to hide
Well more room, I guess
It's not worth taking
I mean it kind of is this stuff all that pretty have better armor
got caught
Can I get a list of the categories again? Absolutely you can
There are categories. We're not gonna get caught
There were more categories. No, there weren't
One two, three, four five six
Seven eight nine ten eleven twelve thirty fourteen fifteen sixteen seventeen eighteen nineteen twenty. There's 20 categories
Where's worst analogy? It was never on the list is what you're referring to
Best shpe moment. Oh my god. I would know I would never put that on here
I'm not gonna put on best shpe moment. Okay
The best shpe moment. Oh my god
I'm still hidden
This thing is worth so much
Why is a rusty chain shirt worth?
Save it. I said it 30 times this year. I I did no such thing
You'll put on best and worst peter, but not best shpe moment
You know why because peter is a relevant thing from this year
Shpe is a video series I made in
There's nothing to do with
2018 new year's eve for 19
Let's try this again this thing's expensive get it this time
Are you blocking me?
All right. Got it
good
All right. We're almost done
Saved it got all the good stuff. I'm just gonna put all this equipment on
And then take the food
Got it. Okay. Nice
I'm going here
Oh two in a row
Take the take the categories up
Did somebody see it? No
And let me get the categories off the screen
so again
When the stream is over in just a few minutes here, that's I i'm
Best loud shpe moment. I can't even man
I need more categories. No, this is the categories that I can do in two. I gotta set this whole thing up
I got two days to do this
All right, get them off before the stream turns off. I'll make sure to show them again, but the first let me steal one more
thing
Make sure it's saved
Who has a higher chance to do this?
You do not what about frog musk? No, he's not he's too far away
I got an okay. Nice. You got another one
I think jeremy's addicted. I I think you're right
Did I find some weird work around here? Am I getting lucky where if you put it in your backpack, it doesn't
trigger an event here
Well, there's the answer to that question. I'm gonna leave this is supposed to be a three hour stream
I know i'm now i'm i'm getting out of here really really soon
Okay, got everything I wanted save it. Let's get out of here
best green screen edit, uh, there's not going to be a best green screen edit because
That was never supposed to be a contest in the first place
So i'm not going to do that
So i'm i'm good
I I do have to stop streaming though if I have any chance to get most of this done
It's only 8 30 here. I got some time. I got the next couple of days
We've got some food. We're good to go
Been live for about just over five hours
Yeah, give me some time
I'm gonna keep the categories on the stream. Let me just make sure that this is ready to be done
Are we good to open the channel?
Are we good? Should I am I am I good to let people be able to put um
Text in here
Holy shit. Look at all these emotes underneath the one sentence. I wrote
This is a weird stock market ticker go look at this look at these increasing prices
On these emotes in the nominees channel some of them are decreasing somehow. So let me get this back on screen
And again, we're going to talk about a couple more times because you're not going to see me again
But I do have to turn the stream off
To get this ready. It'll be a lot of fun
I'm gonna put a lot of work into it
You'll see me in a couple days if you're leaving i'll see you new year's eve
7 pm pacific time. We're gonna start we'll count down the ball. We'll do the awards. I'll see you there in studio
By the way, let's get this like in a good spot. Yeah, there you go
No, i'm not i'm i'm gonna do the bits bits and subs. Absolutely
I'm not gonna skip out on those
Only live for just over five hours that we should be good to go. It shouldn't take too long
Why is the mouth breathing because the he's sleeping and he's breathe he breathes
Why is he breathing
I'm, not sure if that was a comment about why why is he breathing or what? I don't understand
great canadian
fk club
Thanks for the five community subs. Thank you to all the people that gave the nearly more
I think over one to two hundred community subs tonight. Holy shit
I have to give uh grump permissions
Juggling all kinds of things give grump permission i'm going i'm going i'm doing it
Did it work?
Not even work
No
Okay, um
How do I do that? Thank you. Hi. Thank you you boy again for five community subs
I did this before I forget how to do it
It's the cog. Yeah, the cog next to nominees i'm in there
Oh, okay, hold on here we go rolls
Channel let's see here rolls members
Okay, there we go
Twitch moderator can do that
That should that should be good are you good
You good
We good
Oh, I just probably peeked the mic. I'm sorry about that
All right. We good
so again
Before we go over the bits again, you know the subs just be aware
Take a look at this
There's gonna be a good set of rules in that channel that channel's not
For discussion that channel's not to talk about what you think if you want to talk about that
What you think nominees should be then maybe we should i think i'm gonna have i'll make a new damn channel right now
right
That channel will be called
Maybe nominee discussion, you know i'm saying
Nominees channel is only for your exact
What you want to nominate? No
What do you guys think about this?
Plastic spork, thank you for five community pornography subs
I'm sorry, you know that
Thank you
No, no, how many submissions per user how many oh, oh, oh how many submissions per user?
I don't know how many submissions per user how many submissions per purpose. I don't know
Because there's a lot of categories and what if you had the things you want to nominate for?
Oh man one per category, but that's a lot
Is one per category can can that be handled do you think that's handleable over the next two days
Well, all right one per category
You have to nominate one per category
We can do it
We're uh, well i'm telling you i'm i'm putting in like triple time until this this stream on new year's eve. So
Have fun
Good luck
And I think i'm gonna make another channel here
Uh, i'm gonna say nye
Discussion
or like
nominee discussion
I'd spell everything is so wrong how I just felt that nominee
Discussion you can talk in here about it. Let me go into here
Here we go
So sending you can you guys use it? Are we good?
Okay
Good if you want to talk about stuff talk about it there do not talk about it in the nominees channel only the nominees discussion channel
And if there's anything else I need to do
For I think that's good
Grump clump has put rules
in that channel
Go take a look
And make sure whatever you're doing is from
2018 not like
It has to have happened this year
Is there only there's only gonna be one winner per category
There's gonna be like six plus nominees per category, but only one of them is going to win
What flavors of ice cream were invented this year? Oh boy, uh, whatever
It don't matter
Vote on discord entries with emotes or repost
I would say if one's already there
Like thumbs it up. You know what I mean?
Because if you if it's the exact same moment the exact same thing you're talking about
Just make sure that it's seen make sure that me and the mods know that a bunch of people wanted that one
You know what I mean?
If you have to put it again, then I mean we're gonna have to deal with that
But if you see it already because it's gonna be a lot of submissions. So
If you see it already try and with that have a great rest of your night. I'll see you on new year's eve
Let's do the bits
Shoosh room and by the way, thanks for watching kenshi by the way before we're gonna i'm still into it
It's a great fun game. It seems why I I would give it the stamp
Of a recommendation at this point. I would I think it's fun
Maybe we'll come back right to it after new years. I don't know
But maybe we'll take a break from it for a day come back. I I want to play it some more so
I'd like to make my whole community of frogs and dogs
But thank you shoe shrimp for the three dollars. Hey germa. Remember how I said my bird was dying
I went to the vet and his liver is somehow all better
The vet said it's nothing short of a miracle
Just comes to show that things always get better. Thanks for getting me through the bad moments in between
awesome
That is fantastic news
Really happy to hear that
No issues good. Thank you for the three dollars and i'm really happy to hear about the bird doing. Okay
Thank you divas for the three dollars again. No message from divas just always giving three dollars
Consistently constantly almost every I think every single stream. Thank you
Timmy tim tan thanks for the one dollar during the christmas eve stream
I saw a guy come in and say oh this guy again, and then I assume he left
Thank you to lorag again for 50 dollars
Hope yourself and everyone in chat enjoy the holiday season
read the message before but
Thank you so much lorag if you're still here
You are incredibly generous. Thank you
I really appreciate it
Thank you jewels for the five dollars. Hey germa. I don't know if you talked about this yet
But have you seen a doctor for your gluten intolerance or digestive issues? Did you receive any good advices?
I have the same issue. So hope you're doing well germa heart. I had a ton of tests done last week
And because of the holidays i'm waiting back for results on a couple of them
But for the most part my blood work is very normal
I had food allergy test. That's not back yet
I have
A couple of things that it was a breath test that I did to check for bacteria in my
Stomach or intestines or something. That's not back yet
But the general blood work was fine
And i'm just kind of waiting for a few things, but i'm not going to know till after new years
Uh, so I don't know that I don't have very much good advice for
Uh gluten intolerance because i'm not sure if that's what I actually have
I mean it would make sense if it was true, but I just don't know
Uh, but digestive issues I've had for a long time
I've had IBD for seven years now eight years
Almost a decade
And the best advice I could find is because it's so different for everybody
Just you got to find the things that you shouldn't be eating and just try not to eat them
There's a lot of foods that just randomly trigger IBD symptoms and they're different for everybody
Try to substitute those things
I got breathalyzed at the doctors. No, it was a
It was a Healabac to pylori test
and then I did another one which was
a like sucrose
breath thing
Whatever it was
I didn't get breathalyzed at the doctors
Vinny's playing mother three. See ya
Well, thanks for coming. I'm sure that'll be a fun time
Sure, that's gonna be pretty interesting. So what happens when I drink too much wine? No
But take care of yourself jules. Hopefully you can figure it out
trying to figure out medical problems is
It's the worst thing ever because it could just be anything. I've had this weird back and stomach pain for
Seven months. I've no idea what it is. I've absolutely no idea. I might just be getting old
Is this a symptom? Is this something is this is nothing actually wrong with me? Am I just fucking old? I don't know
I don't know
We'll find out soon enough. But thank you. Thank you the whole keg for the five dollars
We're just spreading belated christmas cheer
Yes, this game is great for your kind of streams
Yeah, I like just kind of hanging out but sometimes it don't have to be crazy. You know what I mean?
there are some moments in this game that can be but
it's fun sometimes to sit there for five to eight hours and mine stones and just chat and hang out and
You know what I mean?
It's a great game for that
But thank you the whole keg for the five dollars
Hey another huge thank you to all the gifted community subs
tora t comes to mind here with
right here
That's so much
That's a lot of subs to give in one second
And I think there was even more after that too
my god
So many community subs and then 420 squid. Thanks for the one dollar. Spyro music is the key to subs
I did play the Spyro 2 ost at least a portion of it
But thank you
Thank you the yellowest for the one dollar can't stay around but i'll see you in the vod boy
Always remember your time and effort are appreciated here
Thank you
Hopefully if you catch this or if you see the new year's eve stream, hopefully we catch you there
That should be a really really fun night
Even that stream is probably only going to be a few hours
I'll probably do like a pre-stream thing maybe before
But it'll be like a little three hour event
And it should be a lot of fun
Thank you to smelly boy for the one dollar save before risky decisions. I did I did I've saved quick saved like a thousand times
420 squared. Thanks for the four dollars call of duty round start compilation
What call of duty round start compilation? I don't know what that means
Is that am I missing something?
He doesn't get it call of duty round start compilation
Can fail, I don't know. Oh, thank you for the four dollars 420 squid
E dragon. Thanks for the two bucks. Thanks for the spiral ost. Wish I could give you more
But this is all I have for now. Don't worry about giving me money. Thank you for even attempting
Thanks for even a dollar. Thanks for even a cent. Thank you for two dollars. Thank you
Appreciate it
It's time for slime. Thanks for the one dollar. Welcome back time for slime spiral ost appreciation bits
Maybe you wanted me to look it up
Garfield the Monday killer. Thanks for the one dollar you
Right there in the back. Come on down. What's your name, sir? German on eight five
Well, congratulations. German because you're on america's favorite game show spider. No, that was a lie
Say it with me folks garf or no garf
Now the rules of the game are simple
Just look at the screen up there and tell me if it's garfield or not garfield. Are you ready?
Look closely. Is it garfield or no focus now?
There's no there's no garfield on the screen
Did I win?
Correct now tell arlene
Tell him what he won. That's right. One whole garf buck. I can't believe it folks. See you next stream
Thank you garfield
Magical rodent. Thanks for the one dollar. It's good to see you streaming
I've had a really rough day today with my grandfather dying on my birthday as always these streams get me through the day
I'm really really sorry to hear that
Happy birthday. I'm sorry for your loss. That's terrible
Thanks for hanging out
Hopefully you feel better. It's tough
Much love to you. Thank you
Happy birthday magical rodent sir feline. Thanks for the one dollar. Why wasn't the rat song?
Even considered during the music part
This is an outrage
Um, what do you mean for the osts? It's like one song
It'd be on repeat
Well, that's the point
Oh, I see
Uh, hey g flota. Thanks for the five dollars
Hey, could you put on the kenshi ost? I got a feeling you'd like it. The game's ambience is similar to this one's thanks
It would be fun if I did that. Uh, thank you garon ninja for the one dollar germa heart. Thank you
Thank you nipple for the one dollar. Yo, yo, it's my guy
Thank you nipple
You have the second part of your name, but
Thank you for the dollar c4g. Thanks for the one dollar
Uh, they just say bisexual pride
Thanks for the one dollar
Let's see, you know, let's see it in the chat right now
Thank you so much
Captain worgen. Thanks for the one dollar follow your dreams germa. Don't cave into peer pressure like all the other kids on the playground
Well, it's hard
When you're one kid on the playground and there are
5,000 other kids on the playground all throwing rocks at you
Right, you know, I mean when there are 5 000 kids on the playground all screaming at the same time
Comment on the right side of your screen equals
rock
Yeah, that was that was way overkill. Huh? That was way overblown. That's not even close
That was great, but what was that person's name? Oh, that was good
Remember that person
But yeah
Thank you. Thank you captain worgen. Thank you dark star 700,000 games the one dollar. Hey, man
I want to say sorry about my bits message yesterday at the time
I thought this was this game was just some poorly made piece of junk
That vinnie would play on a sunday trash stream, but I am actually quite enjoying this game now
Sometimes you got to give them a chance
You'll know if I think a game is just not worth playing. You'll know it
We've started and stopped
to shit terrible games
In three hours before
I think there's something here. I think there's something fun here
and I
I think we're close
to seeing it
It's already been very interesting and very fun so far just weird and
elaborate things happening
But you can build whole towns
This whole area is a map that have not been seen
It seems really interesting and
For the price that it is
I can't really complain, you know
this is not
a 60 game
Currently it is I believe it was a 20 30 bucks
It's 29.99 for this game
So it's kind of like
It's a little rough around the edges, right? It is
But I think that adds something to it
Derma is like 10% of the game at the moment in the newbie town
Yeah
I'd buy it if it was 30. It is 30. It's 29.99
One cent off
It has to be exactly 30 or I don't want it
Oh, well, sorry
But it's it's like whatever you want to make it if you can
If you want to like role play as certain characters if you wanted to make
There's a bunch of starting characters. You can just pick from and screw around with
If you talk like pound for pound just how much time we'll just look at the time i've spent in the game so far
I have what?
15 hours in the game 14 hours in the game something like that
and
Some games guys that are 60 dollars. I spend four hours in and I go this was terrible
Or uh, this was all right
so
I mean, but it you know games like this are not really for everybody
Because they kind of just don't you don't get to do anything really at the start
the whole point of this entire game is
You have to start from nothing. You're gonna lose every fight
And it's a little rough
around the edges, it's a little
wonky, but
You just have to play it and just see how far you get
Oh, you're very forced into mining
maybe you are but
You know, i'll look into it. You're right the evil within two if I could put a worst game of 2018 up there
When did evil within two come out?
That came out this year, didn't it?
damn it
I would have just given it to
Evil within two if it was 2018
And it goes last year
I wouldn't even have like a category of nomination. I would just give worst game of the year to it
Are you gonna tell me that you thought that game was worse than the quiet man? Yes
because the quiet man was made on probably like a
Four million dollar budget and evil within two was probably like 60 to 150 million dollars
That's so much
You may give up numbers out of bias i'm just kidding
The evil within two was an awful game
It was the worst game to come out in the last 50 years and i'm talking i'm talking when the tron video game came
out for regular nintendo
That's how far back you have to go
I respect i'm fucking around guys
I'm actually just kidding around. Don't worry. Nobody go but well, i've really liked evil within two. Why is he doing this?
Just kidding. It's a joke. He did truly hate the game though. No, it was a 2017 wasn't even the same year
It doesn't even count anymore
anyways
Uh, yes, kenshi is I would give it. Yes, I don't give like letter grades. I don't say well, that's like a no
Just there's a stamp
It's worth playing it is it is worth
Purchasing you could probably have some fun in it
That's kind of how I judge any game. I play
Hey flim flam. Thanks for the ten dollars worth every cat. Thanks for ten bucks
Worth every cat. Thank you so much for the ten dollars blim flam. Thank you
To neon five eight twelve for the one dollar category worst german nine eight five creations
I mean the thing that that's worst new character. I think
Pits in that category
You give letter grades all the time
Back up us back in like 2017. I did that we're talking about 2018
Which is a different year
Uh neon again, thanks with three dollars have the wasps returned
What's that buzzing?
Is the bird house a character?
No, the bird house would be that would be classified as a stream
Right. That's an overall stream
Why are they more worse than bests?
That's I guess kind of the point of the whole stream
Thank you neon
Hey dark star. Thanks again for the dollar amen. He's doing the end of p voice germa pluto
Yeah, he did
All mu thanks to the one dollar. Hey germa i've been a long time viewer and I love the content you make and we'll always
Be here to keep supporting you
But the last joke you made was minus two
This was two hours ago. I don't know what I did
But uh, even the best baseball players in the world that have ever lived, uh still
Failed seven out of ten times
so
I mean
Come on. Hey binary man zero one one zero one zero. Hey, thanks binary man for the one dollar
A category for the new year's eve stream should be loudest. Oh god. It's so loud moment of 2018
I don't think there are very many of those this year
It happens often, but I don't know if that happened if there's any been really crazy ones a couple of years ago
Back when I didn't understand how to properly configure obs and stream decks and stuff
Maybe happened a lot more frequently. Sometimes I still can't catch it
But no, this is the list that's 20 categories
That'll take us a few hours to get through
Hey super sale. Thanks for the one dollar. No message. Just thank you
Walnut cast thanks for the ten dollars walnut cast best and worst green screen
Jesus
Thank you so much walnut for the ten bucks
but i'm not going to do a green screen category because that was not supposed to be a contest
And making a best and worst green screen
Makes it a contest
There were so many great submissions. I would not want to just be like yours was the best
No, that wasn't the intent of that whole entire project
And i'm not going to make that the intent
But thank you for the five dollars here best green screen you son of a bitch
uh
Again, see my previous comment. Thank you for the fifteen dollars
Hey damona cucumber. Thanks for the one dollar
Best mental breakdown on stream best chat in multiplayer game
Um, we really haven't done that many of those
There was the hold fast streams. There was the mmo
Stream where we played like three or four of them
There hasn't been very many there would only be about three nominees anyways
And balloons tower defense five would win. They just would
So congratulations to balloons tower defense five
For winning in that category that's not on the screen
It's not there
But congratulations
mental breakdown. Yes
Does those happen quite frequently?
Franklin jr. Thanks for the five dollars best mcdonald's hamburger
That would be the big mac don't even need a category for it. Thank you for the five dollars. I really appreciate it
Five dollars is a lot of money. Maybe we'll give it all the time. So thank you
Dark star. Thanks for the one dollar. Please don't ban spork. He's just a silly
Billy who sometimes misses the c and control c. Well, I would ask
spork why why are you
copying
and pasting
All these pornographic pieces of material
I je why do you need to do that? It's not it's it's unnecessary
Did he do it again? Did it? Yeah, he did. He did it again
this
I might have to just like put a cooldown on links for now
Maybe that'll be a 2019
improvement
Although i'm not sure it's an improvement because I don't want to do that. You know what I mean? I don't want to have to do that
Don't make me have to do that
Thank you smelly boy for the one dollar orc no understand why two orcs wrestle
no clothes
smork
No, okay. Thank you captain worgen for the one dollar
Leave corn not porn the picture of corn that
Captain worgen put in
Thank you honey chain for the five dollars. I won't be around for the new year's eve stream
So I want to wish you a happy new year's now
Hope the new year brings you new joys and I want to thank you again for all the laughs
You've given me germa heart
Thank you, honey chain
If you have plans for new years
Uh, hope you have a lot of fun
Be responsible if you do
That goes for all of you
Thank you for the five dollars and we'll see you in the new year
Thank you, honey chain
Getting close to the end here. Hey lard ass. Thanks for the three dollars
Been watching you since early 2012
Want to say thanks for the years worth of incredible funny content and I hope you have a great 2019
You as well. Hope you have a great 2019. All the best to you
Thanks for sticking around for
12 13 14 15 16 17 18 19 remember I can count 19 now soon. That's seven years
It's a significant portion of somebody's life. Thank you so much for sticking around as long as you have
And thank you for the three dollars
Thank you. Double d for the one dollar top spie voice moments. Nope
Thank you pp vortex for the one dollar. Hey germa realistically speaking
How long do you think you would last in a fight with a gorilla the gorilla knows wrestling?
I would lose I would I would be dead in about one second
The gorilla would just double-handed just grab me and smash me into the ground. I would die instantly
So not even two seconds. I don't think
Thank you. Iterus
Thank you. Iterus gara for the one dollar. Hey handsome germ boy
Uh found this video
About you from a few years ago
By the way, I better see you using those goddamn sippy cups soon these goddamn sippy cups soon
There's an interesting uh, it's an interesting short film. Uh, I I can't even click it. It's a link doesn't work
Sippy cup should just be the default cup
It's a gnome. That's a gnome
You know, I don't want to click it out on but i'm gonna i'm not gonna gnome you guys. Why would I do that?
Uh, thank you though. Iterus
For the one dollar and you will see the sippy cups very soon
Thank you clueless sniper for the one dollar. You should make a fake clip for one of the categories
I already
I can't just throw in fake shit again. Like I did that last week
Just throw in fake stuff. That's not there
Just one may we'll see it depends on how
How long this takes me to make these categories in the videos for them?
Hey, thank you klyvvvv for the one dollar. I made a video using a green screen footage. It's called ultra compact
Dream streamer. Thank you
Thanks
Thank you for the one dollar. Uh, thank you. Dubski dude for the one dollar. Hey jim a long time fan
Thank you so much for giving me these bits
Uh, i've never heard of a twitch streamer giving his fans free money
But between your own generosity and your supportive community, you're making it happen
Just don't feel obligated to give me money. Okay, it's not about the bits. Here's the 2019 being an even crazier year
Hashtag free auto hashtag beater
Thank you to monica cucumber for the one dollar. I don't I can't even
I'm just like stumbling all over myself right now
Thank you to monica cucumber for the one dollar worst best streamer between bill crazy officer gx germa and bf bugleberry
Now those are characters
Those are characters
Park follow me. Oh, thanks for the one dollar germa. I make this. Do you like it? My hand hurts
Yeah
Okay, of course that's some that is some good shit
Thank you for that
Thanks for the art. It looks fantastic. Thank you par follow you and thanks for the one dollar. What is the penis in there?
Shut up. Don't say that
Shut no, there's not I didn't just link that did I?
No, there's no there's not there's not there's not don't tell me that don't be like that
Don't be like that not after the last like hour of
All right, that's good. No, that's just good art
Thank you par follow me. Oh, thank you the great canadian
fk club
For the 15 dollars
Eat the dog on the next kenshi stream. No
I probably you know, we'll do next time. Maybe i'll say no
rewinding
Save scumming is okay, but no. Oh, let's go back fly when I didn't die 10 15 minutes ago
I can save scum like 10 seconds
I'm not gonna eat that dog
But thank you
Uh great canadian
For your monumental amount of money this week
And your huge contributions
Thank you
Three more to go and then we got the credits
Thank you gabby for the one dollar. Thanks for everything germa. I've been feeling
Lonely lately and i'm so glad I found you in this community
Love you, dude. Keep doing what you're doing
I will
Thank you for the one dollar and i'm glad
That you can hang out in this community because it's a great one
A lot of funny people a lot of talented people a lot of great people here
Welcome. Thank you
Thank you devlon 2 million for the one dollar
Just a heart. Thank you devlon
And then finally here a double d for one dollar. Thank you
Really appreciate it
And no, that's not even true
There's a link here from double d
And no, we just came in with three dollars 33 cents right now. Thank you. No, b
No message. Thank you
Let's go ahead and throw up the credits
Because there are going to be a lot
I mean a lot
A very large amount of subscriptions
Thank you so much everybody
While these go up the screen in a weird
fashion
I want to break down one more time
It was not a gnome. It was this
Uh, let me break down one more time
See you on new year's eve at around seven o'clock pacific
I will not be live until then
So take the opportunity to figure out
From the categories on here
You get to pick one nomination per category per person
So that means you could put up to 20 but it has to be on one category
You can't just put you know, 20 different worst
Gamer moments you can pick one but you can do it for all of them
These nominations will be picked by me
And a handful of the mods
a day from now
Pretty much one day from now
Maybe even tomorrow afternoon there's going to be another link there that will be a poll to vote
For the winners of those categories which will then be put into an envelope and opened on stream
The poll is not there yet. We need to have the nominations first
You'll see the disc it'll be in a discord. There'll be just just jump in the discord over the next
24 hours or so. You'll see it. You're just gonna have to click a link
The link will be in the discord. It will take you to a survey which you will take it'll be
Every nominee you just got to vote for them get someone else to make the envelope. So you're surprised
Um, that's probably what i'll do
Look at all these subs look at all these subs coming in right now. That's insane
So i'll see you on new year's eve
I'm gonna be in the discord for the next couple of days
Lurking checking some stuff out talking to the mods getting stuff prepared because i'm not i'm not going anywhere
i'm gonna be sitting here doing working on this so
Much love to everybody
How many subs were tonight let me see I think it was like 300 at least two to 300
Jesus
Thank you everybody so much. I hope you're enjoying the kenshi streams
They're a little bit more relaxed and just chilled than some of the other ones
Wait, what's playing?
My god, look at this. Something else is playing
What is playing now, oh
Okay
It's auto played
All right, good night everybody see you new year's eve get your nominations in follow the rules see you soon