Hey, what's up? Sorry, I'm a little late. I had to do my get ready thing I do in front of the mirror that all streamers do.
If you don't know, after you get out of the shower and after you do your hair and you get some to eat, you have some water.
I, like many others, go in front of the mirror and just point at myself and I go,
own it, own it, own it, own it, own it, own it, own it for about 25 minutes. Really get myself pumped up for the day.
That would get in the way so much if you really had to do that. Just sitting there yelling,
own it to yourself in the mirror. But anyways, hi, how are you? Today we're going to play a game
about traveling through time. The game is called No Time. It's a game about driving around in a car.
That car has time travel capabilities. It is a car game. Just to let you know, this is a car game.
Could be very fun. Travel back to an hour ago when you weren't late. I think you can, I'm, all right.
From the description of this game, I think you can put in any date in modern human history.
As long as it's 1 AD. So I, maybe we can go forward. Go back to 23 years ago. Oh no.
The title sucks. It doesn't matter. You guys are still doing the 20, yeah.
You still on the 23 thing. I have a question. How many of you guys watched the movie yesterday?
You guys have had one full day in between the last stream. Anybody watch the movie?
I have to assume some of you have. Why would I do that? I don't know. I thought about it. I was
pretty close to, you know, is it on, can I get it on like Amazon or like iTunes or something?
What does this person say? I don't know. Whatever it was that got removed. I think they're asking
what the best VR headset is. It depends. Do you want to save some money to get one of the small
wireless ones? You know, or do you want to have the wire going into the back of your head and then,
yeah, I don't know. Have the index. I would say the index. The only problem is my index was kind
of screwed up. My left ear of my index just kind of stopped working randomly. So I don't know. I
don't think I can say that. Can't wait for 2023. How do we, how do we end that joke? Do you know
how unbearable 2023 is going to be on this channel? If we don't end that joke, we have to find an
exit for it. I can't wait till 2025. We got to come up with a new thing. We got to give you guys a
new number because otherwise next year is going to be hell. All right. You guys ready? Let's go. It
took me long enough. I do have to say this. I know a lot of people are going to, they're going to
pog sad in the chat when they hear this, but after this stream, streams are going to be a little
sporadic over the next couple of weeks. I've got a lot, I've got a lot of work to do. I've got a
lot of work to do, but seriously, I'm not going to be streaming this weekend. I'm not going to be
streaming. They're going to be all over the place. The green screen will happen in the next week.
I'm going to give you a hard date very soon within the next 10 days, but that June into July is
going to, it's probably something, it's probably going to be the busiest I've been
since 2021, a few months, two or three months before the dollhouse. There's a lot of stuff
going on. So don't worry. I'm not going, you'll see me. I'm not going away. I'm going to try to do
one or two streams a week until July, at least. So don't worry. I'm not going anywhere. What
happened? I was playing fallout. The streams are going to be sporadic. That's it, but not too,
don't worry. It's not like I'm going to stream for like, don't worry. Since 2022, all through 2021,
I was kind of a once a week Andy. That's probably not going to happen. So don't worry. It's not like
I'm going to go to once a week in the next month. Don't worry about that. They already are once a
week. No, no, I do like, I do like two or three times a week. I stream three times a week since
2022. I went back to the old pre Vegas schedule three times a week or so. I actually, the pre,
the first like year in Vegas, wasn't I streaming like four plus days a week?
You should stream two, oh, come on. Stop, stop it. Two to 23. Oh my God. I'm going to give you
another number. Six. Six. Isn't that number six? Cool. There's so many things that you can add up
to make six. Two plus two plus two is six. Seven minus one is six. Six times zero is zero. But
six, six, six, that's the devil number. Isn't that a, that's a crazy number, isn't it? That's
a scary number. You know what number I really don't like? The number six. Cause like six, six,
that's devil. I'm scared of the devil. No, don't meme that one. Don't, don't meme that one. Don't
do that. No, I fucking hate that. Did it work? All right, let's go. How you doing? What's up?
Uh, this is no time. Is it my camera? Just making sure. Nice evil hair. Yeah, it's all right.
All right, let's get it up. See what would have been really funny is if I had been in a back to
the future costume with goggles and a big lab coat. And before I turned the stream on my webcam,
I was like, Oh, here we go. And, Oh, we're going to go for it. We're going to find a future. We're
going to go back to the future. And it was, I was in a back to the future costume and that would be
funny. I think you guys would like that. All right, let's go. This is a driving game. Is this a
controller game? This is a car game. Maybe I should use a controller. Thanks for your disappointment.
That would be Richard Nixon. That was not, that was not Richard Nixon. I can't, you can't do.
All right, listen, this is important for all of you watching at home. If I do a doc impression,
I'm doing a Rick impression. And you all hate that. I, nobody can ever do a doc impression ever
again. Cause you're just doing Rick from Rick and Morty. You understand? Like I would have tried to
go into it and really do it, but it would have been, uh, it would have been Rick. Let me try to
do a doc. Oh, Morty, we're going to be careful. Put that, get back in there and we're going to
go back in time to shave. Actually it is different. Morty, Morty, we gotta be careful. I don't know.
Guys, I've never seen all these movies. I've never seen them. I just know, I know Christopher,
Christopher Lloyd, right? His name's Morty, not Marty. Marty, not what? I just dropped everything.
All right. Stop. Let's go. All right. Let's play the core game. Play the official story
campaign of no time along with all side stories and secrets. Sure. Why not? You guys ready? Can
I drive? Sir Adam, the energy source of the future requires a fusion reactor. I gotta put my headphones
in to understand. PLC entry. Hello and welcome to no time. A lost in days experience. If you've got
a minute, I'd like to take you through the basics of the game. Why is there crash dummy stuff on
there? All right. Let's go tutorial. Double the, double the, double the, double the, double the
W A S D. Pretty good. And left alts to crouch. Is there a punch? Left alt is crouch. That's changing.
It actually got to come down to like 30. Crouch is left alt. We're going to make that C is compass.
Use is F. When did this change? Use was E for 50 years and they just, everybody collectively all
decided it was going to be F. Why? Please help me with this. What happened? E, E, E was for everything.
It was for use. It was for interaction. Now it's F. What everyone collectively at the same time said
that was a good idea. I don't, why? There has to be a reason, right? Because Q and E is for leaning.
Oh, that, whatever. That's all right. All right. I'm going to, I'm going to make this what I want.
So it's going to be E. Take is going to be F. Sandbox, that's fine. Full power mode G. Zoom,
X. Punch. There is punch. Holy shit. Okay. There's a throw. This game's already pretty much a nine
out of 10 so far. Crouch is going to be C. Compass is going to be control or tab. No, compass. Compass.
I don't know. Two, four. Compass is going to be four. I don't know why. Cause it's like four
directions. North, south, east, west. That makes sense to me. Zoom. That's fine. All right. I think
this is good. If I need to change it again. Car. W A S D. Space. Fly mode. Thrust up. Up arrow.
Time conductor. Cooling. Okay. What about ride? All right. I think we're good.
Pick up the uranium next to the car. Press E to pick it up. Uranium. Did you say E? Wait, what?
Now put the uranium onto the reactor. Didn't I say, wait, didn't I say E?
He said E. What's going on? Am I going crazy? No, seriously. I'm going crazy.
After just saying that. What's going on? What? Oh, it is F. Okay. All right. Put the uranium
on top of the reactor chamber. Use number one to seven to scroll through your inventory
or mouse wheel. All right. So put it in. What? What? Okay. I have to eventually come back to 1984
day two at 000. Turn the volume up. I will. Okay. Now read the useful notes.
They should be on the front of your car. Oh, that's loud for me. All right. Useful notes.
Like fucking Jesus. Why can't I just, I want to grab it. Can I grab it? After you finish reading
the notes into the vehicle by using the steering wheel. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. I'm on step.
What step am I on? Step one. Insert uranium sample into reaction. Okay. Step two. Get in the car.
We got one lamp in the test zone. Step three. Check the reactor temperature. All right. We've
got to get in the car. It's fucking dark in here. No, I need those notes. I don't know what to do.
And you can save and the game above. Oh, and if your reactor temperature is above 300 degrees
Fahrenheit first. Okay. Cool. The nuclear. Oh, and you can look up the controls in the pause menu.
All right. So we can't go over 300 degrees. I have talked for long enough.
Good luck and have fun on your adventures in no time. Lost a day sandbox experience.
All right. Let's go. Drive. How do I drive? I need those notes. How do I get out of the car?
I need the notes that are on the top. Find an advanced source of energy for the reactor.
Estimations would be around 2014. I think or a little later. Okay. Uranium samples as temporary
power source are in the luggage space. Do not travel through time if the reactor is
temperature is above 300 degrees. Avoid yourself at all costs. Okay. I repeat. Avoid yourself.
What about the actual useful notes? Give me this. Step five. Talk with the time conduction and
enter the date into the timetable that order. All right. Step six. The travel sequence should start.
That's month, day, year, and then hmm. What is hmm?
Travel sequence should start at about 70 miles per hour. Okay, let's go.
Get in the fucking car. All right. Here we go. Let's time to set our destination.
We are going to go to type a date and time. Um, I don't, what am I pressing? Date a 12.
What did I just do? Type a date and confirm. I just shot me. What? What? I just explode.
I don't understand. What just happened? Why am I like fucking three feet tall?
What a terrible nightmare. Hello. Open up. Hello. Shut this off. What? What happened?
Oh, that's me doing that. Turn it down. Hello. Who is it? Finally. Have you been sleeping on
the floor again? You better had made some progress by now ever. But tell me you finished the reactor.
I did, but awesome. Come on now. There's a little, there's a little time. Our supervisor will show
up soon. We need the machine to be ready. Holy shit. This guy, the time machine. Come on now.
We got no time. All right. Grab the reactor and follow me to the elevator. All right. This is a
reactor. Drink that coffee. A stack of books. That's a reactor. Give it to me. Let's go.
Put your hand in the door. I dropped the reactor. Put your hand in the door. All right. Let's go.
Where are we going? I'm holding the reactor. You press the button to go to the lobby for the,
oh, give me a break. Why would I have to do this? I'm holding a fucking nuclear reactor or whatever
this is. I'll do it. I'm sorry. If somebody has one of these, they go and let this and they're
going to be a person in front, a person to each side and a person behind walking with them,
all moving step by step at the same time. And there's going to be somebody literally,
there's going to be something attached to their stomach, like a big umbrella underneath them.
So like if they drop it, it just goes right into like the big chute, like under like an umbrella.
There's no way somebody's holding it in their hands like this. All right. This is the,
this is it. Quest turn in. Edward looks proud. Wow. Mach three. Yep. I modified it to reach
speeds of up to 90 miles per hour and to also give you a nice clean shape, cleaner than a
single blade. Let's hope it will last longer than the Mach two. I heard that C Corp is working on
nuclear fueled cars. We're going to beat them to it. Oh, stop. Let's assemble the rest of the car
first. Hope your reactor works. Open the reactor hatch and insert it in the front of the car. All
right, let's go. Let's do it. Oh, got it. You didn't say I had to open the first car we had.
We didn't have to do that. All right. Now the time core is what makes time travel possible.
It converts a frequency of time stream into an actual date and time. Where the fuck did you go?
How do I close this? Presently, you can only compute the dates in between roughly 4,000 BC
and 2030. But I'll figure out a way to mend it. The time frequency just oscillates. Though currently
you can only input dates after one AD anyway. Okay. All right. So what's the deal? He sounds
like Peter Griffin. Let's do a test run. Oh, fucking come on. I know, I know. I promise the
time displacement procedure will occur this time, even if you crash the car into the wall. I've had
nightmares ever since. I'm lucky to be alive. Or maybe the rest of the island, the accelerator
could have gotten destroyed in a nuclear blast due to the impact. Don't worry. I made the car
very sturdy. So the probability of a nuclear explosion. Yes, but first retrieve the personal
log computer, please. They're on the table. Yeah, it's like if Peter Griffin was an undertale.
I know what you mean. All right. Dress in the hazmat suit. Should I be in this? What is this
thing? What am I looking at here? Okay, I got it. Oh, no. What do you want me to do? Did you say
there was notes or something? What do you want me to do? What do you want me to do? You say there
was something on the table? This is what it was on the table? What do you want me to do?
I don't remember. What do you want me to do? A computer. Okay, thanks. It's the the Pip Boy.
Okay. Prologue. Edward gave me his newest PLC, a few bug fixes, and so on. Let's talk to Edward.
Oh, this music. Isn't it great? It works. Made a few bug fixes and cleanups. Hope it'll help
you with your work in the future. Looking cool. Thanks, Ed. This game is random. Can you strap it
on my arm? This thing weighs like three kilos. I don't think you want that kind of strain on
your wrist. Anyways, you see I'm strapped. I'm not suffocating, right? Am I just suffocating in a suit?
Okay, what do you want me to do? I've strapped a meter on the right side of the PLC. It tells
you whenever a temporal shift occurs. Remember our little theory session? This shift happens
when your activity in space time reaches a certain threshold. Time itself morphs around your actions,
wiping your past selves, since you or anything you left in that time weren't meant to be there.
Oh, of course. It's the grandpa paradox. I think. The grandpa paradox is if you go back in time
before you were born, you technically weren't born, so therefore your grandfather had to have
been alive first for you to be alive, so therefore you can't exist in that time frame. Let's go to
the grandpa paradox. It's something like that. No, no, no, no, no, no, no. It's if you go back
in time and kill your grandfather, then you can't exist, so you disappear and you fade out,
like in the movies. Why would you do that? I don't know. Oh, yeah, I got a time machine.
The first thing I'm going to do. Oh, man, I could go see anything in human history. I could go
forward. I could see what the world looks like. I could see what happened back when the dinosaurs.
No, I think I was going to go kill my grandfather and disappear. What? Well, yeah, why would I do
that? Why would I do that? That's a Chad move. No, it's not. Okay. Giga Chad goes back in time
to kill his grandfather. If you drop something sometime in the past, it would vanish. This is
the grandpa paradox, right? Bigger changes would probably... Oh, no, the grandpa paradox is if you
go swat a mosquito on your arm, then your grandfather never meets your grandmother because
everything can change, possibly. And then when you go forward in time, you look out the window
and it's raining donuts and you wish you would have stayed in that timeline, but you got really
freaked out. It's something that happened at the family dinner table, so you left before it started
raining the donuts. I understand. I understand. It's a fucking Simpsons episode. You say I'm the
one that's not a cultured media viewer. That happened in The Simpsons and all you question
marking me and everyone says Simpsons is the best fucking TV show ever made. And that was back when
The Simpsons were in the first 10 years of its existence, not the last 20 years of its existence.
To me, the last 20 years of The Simpsons existence has been like an iPad ad for like a mobile game
from like trailer. That's the same thing for me. The last like 10 to 15 years of The Simpsons
has been like an iPad trailer. I just like, I skip it. I don't want to watch this. What were we
doing? I don't know. Leave me alone. I'm fucking relaxing. You need to fix the fragmentation. I'm
just sitting here like breathing in my own like carbon dioxide. What's? All right. I said I was
going to chill out today and that's happening. So stop fucking saying the number 23 or you're
going to be fucking banned. Back to it. You need to fix the fragmentation of time for me.
So during some tests of the core, I ended up making rifts in the time space continuum. I sent
boxes with items through time, but they came back empty with strange letters inside them.
Just keep that in mind. Don't lose sight of your boxes while time traveling. I should make a box
that's a mailbox and like I put it in one place and if you put stuff into it, it goes back and
forward in time. And then I could have a pen pal who communicate with somebody from a different
time period. That'd be cool. Somebody said play the fucking game. I had to be honest. I'm very
confused. I am playing the game. This is a lot of dialogue. Okay, let's go. No time for that.
Drive the car into the acceleration tunnel. Move the car to the starting position. Then wait for
my signal. When I open the gates, the mod chip, which I inserted earlier, will send you exactly
one hour into the future. Make sure to remove the chip afterwards. It blocks the time input. Okay.
Okay. All right. Let's go. Yeah. One. Why one hour? Okay. So he said it already.
Did you set it already? Did you turn it on?
Save the game. All right. That's good. Save it right here. The save system's not turning on.
Can I help you? All right. Let's go. Turn it on. Is it on? Okay. Here we go. Oh fuck.
You need to put the uranium in. Didn't I already do that? It's in it. It's right there.
Didn't I already do that? I already did that, didn't I? Oh, it's okay. I didn't know it was
the second thing. All right. Let's go. Here we go. So get to the starting point, which is where we're
here. I'm imagining this is probably the starting point. You're going to open the door. All right.
Let's go. Everything seems to be active. Activate them. I think they're active. Reactor. On.
Accelerate to 70 miles per hour. Time conductor. On. Get ready. Let's go.
Oh, I suspect located. You're coming with us. I got one. I got one. What do we do?
Drive the car down the secret door. I can't fucking see anything with this stupid suit on.
You just skipped over that hour and here you are. Incredible. Are you all right? Like,
do you feel weird in any way? Don't worry about the guys back there. I'll be explained in due time.
Do you want a gun? What is this place? Yes. My personal invention. A stun gun to be precise.
The first prototype that works. Open this place. This is my secret hideout. I installed a secret
door, entrance and so on. I knew it would come in handy someday. Is it even legal? I don't know.
What's going on here? Do you want the short version or the long version? Whatever. Agents,
they broke into the facility and are raiding all our research. We need to get the machine out of
here. They call them that on the news. C Corp has made no comments on whether they got attacked too.
How do we get the machine out unnoticed? Unnoticed? Not possible. I know how to give
you enough time before they catch up though. This room leads to the drainage tunnels of the facility.
From there you can move on the main road which leads to Pine Island. Just go as far away as
possible. Jump some time into the future just till things cool off. We'll meet each other somehow.
What about you? Someone needs to distract them from you and our invention. Don't sweat it. I'll
make it out. This is only one of many hideouts. Someone needs to hold the flood gates open for
you and I have my stun gun. Don't worry. We'll see each other on the other side. Outside you'll need
to open the first gate. There's no time. Hurry. Open it. Let's go. Let's go. Give me out. Give
me up. Don't worry. I know a way out. All right. Open it. Let's go. Good luck. I need to put a new
date in, right? Reactor is on. Okay. Put a new date in. Type in a date. Month? What is it? What's
April? April four? Oh four? Dude, what am I looking at here? What is going on? No, I don't
understand. Cool it off. Cool it off. Cool it off. How do I actually do this? What the fuck? Set
destination. Four one one two. How do I actually use this thing? Time target. Present departure.
How do I? I can't. How do I punch this in? 41 o'clock. I don't want to actually go to
this time period. It literally set. Yeah, but I can't. I don't know. There's one, two, three,
four, five, six slots. How am I supposed to know which one I'm doing? Okay. When I just typed it
in, it did this one, this one, then this. It like jumped around because this is the present day.
Set departure time. Type in a date. Okay. Like month first. 04 is April, right? Why is it not
working? I'm just fucking driving. It's the letters. What are you talking about? Letters for
month. APR. No, the guys, it doesn't work. It doesn't work. Nothing works. APR is April. Yeah,
but I can't. I don't understand. I can't change it. It doesn't make any sense. Type a date and
confirm with enter. Okay, let's try this again. I need to remove the override chip. All right,
let's take it out. How do I get the fuck out of here? Okay, let me try this again. Time target.
All right, the reactor's off. Everything's good. Should I travel now? Do I have to go 70? Get the
chip out. Hold on. Dude, can I? How do I rip the fucking chip out of the thing?
Give it to me. All right, let's go. Okay, I made it out. Quest complete. Don't pull that up while
you're driving. Okay, sounds good. Oh, that was just scripted. I just, okay, I get it.
This is not an ending, right? In the heat of the takeover, planned by his group, one of the
inventors managed to... No, okay, I got it. I shouldn't even been touching anything. This was
all the scripted first, like, 20 minutes of the game. Everybody, like, wants me to go back to,
like, fucking 100 AD, but, like, I can't even do that. Now I have access to this stuff.
Take this off. It's gonna give me a fucking headache. Okay, so I made it out. Now let's get
in here. Get that thing out of here. Do I have a trunk or anything? I can put this stuff in. I
feel like it's gonna fall out. Okay, save the game. The autosave cannot be overwritten within this one.
One. All right, cool. So we are currently April 15th, 1984. 13. Parture. What does that mean?
Well, where should I go? Set date. Type a date and time. Okay, so I'm gonna type in...
Should it date some month first? Which would be 04, right? Okay, yeah, it is 04, not APR.
So let's do 04. 14. Let's go yesterday. 1984. And then we're gonna do it at 10 o'clock. We're
gonna go to yesterday. That's exciting. I'm just testing to see if the machine works.
I'm... Guys, know what? Fuck that. If you had access to a time machine, you are going to just
go back a day or so, man. Like, this... I'm not going back a thousand years. What if I... What if
I get stuck? What if I get stuck? I need to test to make sure it works. Let's go for it. You ready?
Let's go! What's happening? What's happening? I didn't hit enter. Yeah, it did.
Oh my... 04. 14. 1984. 10 o'clock. Enter. Reactor. Let's go. I don't have any uranium left?
Shit! I need to put the chip back in? Where is it? Where's the chip? Oh, fuck. I thought I had to
take the chip out because that was like the safety protocol. Oh dear god, where the fuck is it?
Where is it? I don't think I need to do that, guys. It wasn't part of the game that I take
the chip out. No, it's not relevant. It's not. So do I have... Am I out of reactor fluid? How can I
tell? Is there a way to tell? Okay. Why am I moving? Why am I moving? What's going on? Why... The car is
moving on its own. I mean, I'm driving it now, but that was weird. Why was it doing that? I will need
to... Okay. I always wanted to visit the distant future of 2014. Okay. Remove that mod chip.
Afterwards, I can input the destination if the time conduction is active and confirm it with enter.
Do I have to go to 2014? Is it just scripted? It said to get some snacks first. There's a donut
shop right here. I don't have any fuel. Where was that donut shop? Back there, right? Yeah. It said
get snacks because I have like a hunger meter. Uranium is at zero percent. Oh, okay. That makes
sense. So I should have one more uranium pod or do I have to actually go find one? All right,
let's get out of here. I have no money to best donuts. I don't have any money. Can I just take
them? Sell the car. All right. So what does the quest want me to... What does it say? Go first.
Buy some snacks. I don't have any money. Where am I supposed to get... You're telling me to buy snacks,
but you're not telling me where I get money. I have zero dollars. Do I have something in the trunk?
What the fuck? Why there's so much... There's so much back there. You don't have your hazmat suit on.
I don't care. I don't give a shit. No, that's wrong. Somebody pulls up. Hey, can I give you a hand,
stranger? Yeah. Come in here. Can you hold this? All right. We got a hundred percent uranium. I'm
ready. I'm ready to go. Okay. We've got uranium. I'm going to April 14th, 1984 at 10 o'clock
at the morning. I'm just... I want to see if it works. Here we go. All right. All right. I'm back.
It is currently April 14th, 1984 at 10 o'clock. Look at... Everyone's... Don't be alarmed.
You'll be talking about this for centuries, motherfuckers. This would be the number one
article on top of every webpage. You know what's... Yeah. I got out and I punched that guy. Yep.
You know what's funny though? That guy will be on every... That guy will be interviewed for every
major news outlet. I've probably made that guy fucking at least $100,000. That guy's going to
write a book and everyone will buy it because you're the guy that the time traveler interacted
with. Oh, fuck. I'm going to be... Turn it off. Okay. All right. All right. All right. All right.
I almost just fucking exploded in like a nuclear reaction. Can I do anything? Don't cut off the
time traveler. That's a big mistake. There's got to be like a quest I can do, right? I'm back
a day ago. Should I go back to the facility? I want to go back to the facility. It's been...
I'm going back to where I started. Back here. Wait a minute. This is literally a donut shop
tomorrow, right? Because there's a bridge. All right. I want to go see what's going on at the
facility. Your quest was for 2014. Yeah. But I wanted to... And now I understand how it works.
I'm not going to fucking finagle around and flop around like an idiot. Oh, there's the donut place.
It still sent you... No, it didn't. It didn't send me there. It's 1984. 1047. Close the door.
Close the car door, please. Because I want to see if he's there. There's money in your trunk. All
right. I'm very interested now. Now I get it. I understand how the game works. Don't worry. We're
good. Relax. We've got plenty of time. The reactor's off. I wish I could close this door.
Am I going to be in here? It's literally 1984. Go to 420-1969. What do I do? Just get out,
walk around and wheeze laughing and get in the car and leave.
There might be a material in here. All right. So there it is. It's not on fire. Can I just go in
the front door? Find yourself in the past and kill them. All right. Well, here's the front door.
I wonder if I can open this. All right. If I'm looking at the security camera right now,
then it's me in this car trying to get in the door. Jerma, I miss when you played games that
had substance. Now you just play dog shit fart simulator games that are made for the purpose
of being a meaningless, shallow novelty to fill up your... Dude, I don't know where you've been for
12 years, but this is like the thing that I do. This is literally what I've been doing for like
the last 12 fucking years. What was that person on about? My like fifth video I ever made on
YouTube was Insane Aquarium. What are you, you're supposed to crack? All right. So I don't think I
can get in. I'm going to go in the trunk though because now I can... Let me try something else.
It's a grandpa video. There's 50 bucks in here. All right. So I'm going to take this out. These
things are finite. I got to be really careful with this. Go to 2012? Let's go somewhere fucking weird.
Right? I'll buy food later. I got to be careful. I'm going to run out of stuff. All right. I'm going
to go to 2014 because that's the quest and I know I'm going to fuck this up. I'm going to soft lock
myself. So here we go. Let's just go to like, I don't know, July, July 4th, 2014. I guess. I don't
know. Was it, was it June? It's not. All right. And then I don't know like 10 a.m. July 4th. I don't
know. Let me get a good straightaway. Let's go. I'm ready. We're going to do the quest and then
after that I'm going to the dinosaurs. All right. So I, I went into the future. It's July, it's 2014.
Oh, okay. What's going on? Stop moving. Okay. So now what do I do? I always wanted to visit the
distant 2014. Okay. Just have to lay low. This looks kind of the same. This looks like this looks
identical. Nothing changed. What did I do? What? Wait, what happened? Why did I just time travel
to the same spot at the same exact time? Wouldn't I have just crashed into myself and we both would
have died? Oh my god. I wasted a fucking reactor. I only have two more of these. I'm going to,
that I did. I, why was, how would that have been a bit? I, I thought I was going to, what happened?
July, enter, right? Okay. Let's go for it. My trunk? What? What's wrong with the trunk?
What? Don't scare me like that. Seriously. What the hell? Let's go. July 4th, 2014. It is 10 AM.
Okay. I kind of, okay. I would, this is what I would do if I had a time machine.
Okay. If I had a time machine and I had unlimited uses on the time machine,
I would go into this donut shop, right? And I would go there and I'd be like, how are you? How
are you? Good to see you. And I would be like, and check that out. Bring it back. I'd say something
really like odd, just specific. And I would hand the money and I would leave. And then I would come
back like five years later and I would do the same exact thing. I would just be a fucking customer
at that point. Who cares? That person wouldn't even remember that you were there. They wouldn't
give a shit at all. You would just be a customer coming in again, like after five years. Why would
I time travel to do that? That would be stupid. They would have forgotten that you came in and
it would have been like, Oh, that guy was kind of weird. I met, that guy maybe was in the area.
Maybe he doesn't live here. That would be fucking dumb. Nevermind. Okay. I want donuts, chocolate
donuts. Oh, thanks. Can I pick them up? What will be friend? I make the best donuts. You know, this
would be a cool indicator to see if you went to a place and you went back in time, five years and
forward in time, five years, did the donuts taste the same or did the, um, go bring that donut back.
What time is it? July 4th, 2014 at 10 28. Come back and eat it again. All right. Well,
there's a new quest here. The future. I wonder what new inventions I will find here. Maybe I
can find some familiar faces. I should take a look at the town square. I remember Edward saying he
wanted to open an inventor shop somewhere. All right. Town square. Go back and stop yourself
from eating the donut because they changed the recipe and it's not as good. That's a cartoon.
I don't want to do it because I don't want to run out of material. I can travel one more time.
And you know, the joke where if you got three wishes, oh, I know what I would do. I have this
crazy elaborate plans for each one. I just had five wishes. I'm down to one. I haven't done it.
Fucking anything. So I'm full of shit. You know, I, I, what have we done? I've accidentally went to
the same place twice. I wanted to eat a donut again. What is this? What the fuck is that? What
is that? What is that? Why is this here? Does it drink that? Why the giant radioactive crabs in
2014? Who's doing that? What the fuck is this? Is nobody else seeing this? Is nobody else seeing
the giant crab that's attacking me? Hello. Wow. It's the future. Uh, okay. Wow. The future. Bye.
Where's the watch? Get that thing out of here. Oh, I gotta go. I don't like that.
I really don't like that thing. All right. I'm looking for a technology center.
I'm gonna get out of it. You have a quest. What is it? Any rumors? I've recently read about the
bank robbery in the 1870s in a document in Pine Lakes archives. It's worth a read. It's what
led Westwood into defeating 20 bandits single-handed. You remember the story. 1870s.
Okay. Eight. Somebody write that down. What just happened? That's two bucks. What can I get you?
You don't have anything to buy. You don't have any products. All right. I'm technically not
going to steal it. I'm going to throw it out the outside. How much is this? I would like to buy
this please. And what is this? Turns organic material into fuel. I only have $47. Box. This
box fits a small amount of items. I probably should get the flashlight, right? Yeah. I'll take a
flashlight. Oh my god. And a radio. What's in your favorite radio stations? No, I don't want that.
I'll take another reactor. Okay. This is what I would like to buy. Thank you. Can I take this?
I can take this out now, right? You're not gonna get pissed? I have 10 bucks left. Do other people
have time machines? Get the radio. I don't want the radio. I don't have enough money. Okay. Do I
have to hold it in front of my face? I have to... Who holds it like this? Can I not just put it on
my... Okay. All right. There we go. There we go. There we go. Put this in the trunk too. All right.
I gotta keep looking around because there's apparently a technology thing somewhere. Wait.
Is this it? Build the second mechanic. I'd like to modify my car. Can you repair my car? Park it in
the garage and then I'll take a look at it. All right. This thing's probably beat up. How much
health does it have? Can I tell? What are you doing? Why are you dumb? Turn the flashlight off?
Why do you care about the flashlight being on? There's no battery in the flashlight, dude.
What are you talking about? All right. What if I put my destination to 10 seconds ago so that
my car pulls up and then there's a huge flash and another one of my cars pulls up? What would he do?
What would he do? Okay. This thing's fixed. I want to go to the 1870s. Get out of the way.
All right. I need to... Let me do this quest part. I'm looking for...
This is the town square, I'm assuming. All right. Can I fast forward like one minute to when I...
After I did that jump because I'm gonna do it. Job requests? Oh, okay. Here's a new location.
There was a bank robbery in Pine Lake during the 1870s. Maybe I'll get some money. All right.
Where am I? Money drop head? Okay. This is definitely the town square. What else was in
there? Oh, nice. A sandwich. Sheriff Westwood. Deeds of Sheriff Pine Lake. Okay. So the first
quest is to go back. Oh, where is it? Hello. Welcome to my workshop. I am E.R. Aether Inventor.
Are you here for a scientific con... Oh, it's him. It's um... It's the guy. Hey. Wait a minute.
You look rather familiar. Have we met before? Never mind that now. I'm in the middle of something
big. Hey, is this something I've got to... We'll have plenty of time to talk later. I'm afraid this
takes precedence. Okay. I'm building an atmospheric motivator. A device that transfuses the very
particles of high and low temperatures at will. English professor. I'm building a weather machine
and all I need is a couple of items to help with its assembly. What do you need? Okay. Here. Take
it. Copy it into your personal log. It shouldn't be too hard. There are only a few more things I
need. Magnetometer? It's a di... Device which meters magnets, of course. It's obvious. Besides,
it's the MacGuffin. For most inventions these days, there should be some down the road at 612.
That they're pretty pricey. I suggest that you get it from Burns Scientific Store at Bridgetown.
Bridgetown.
The northern end of Cape Dun, a town located on top of a bridge, quite literally.
Sea Corp is behind that monstrosity to copy St.
Andry, that ugly megacity just on the other side of the coast. Anyway,
his shop is located on the top floor at the back. Okay, so we gotta go. We gotta go to
northern end of Cape Dun. Take a hover train to Bridgetown. I have a time machine. Okay.
Uranium is perfectly safe. Well, almost perfectly safe since ever since the
prismic ceiling glass was invented in 1992. Ten times stronger than lead. Okay. I need something
that can conduct enough gigawatts to power the machine. Okay. A what? He's thinking.
Too much lore? I think it's just enough lore. Okay. What could do the job?
Unless you someone get back my family heirloom pocket watch. Did I? Could I have gotten it back
when I wasted a time travel device? Okay. One of the first settlers had a pocket watch of set
quality. Let's just go to one, right? Let's just do it. I'm gonna go. Look, I could buy. I got,
I got a, I got a limited amount of money. I got, I could, I could go. I could do the quest later.
Let's go meet Jesus. Okay. Back then, the Park Hill was our estate and he lived just next to it.
He never told me this story. I did just now. All right. Okay. Let's do it. Yeah. Yeah. Like
you never seen a fucking time travel machine before. Car flipper. Do I have a map? Okay. Am I
flying? My car can't do that. That's not fair. That's bullshit. I I'm from the past, man. I don't
understand this stuff. Why am I stuck? Yes, it can. I'm actually stuck. Use the car flipper.
I'm going to fall off again. Go out the other door. What the fuck have I done? I'm going to fall off
again. And this time I'm probably going to die. I think I can get out eventually. I'm just loading
the game. Here. Here's real time travel for you. I'm loading this save file. Done. Okay. Let's load
up the car. I'm not going to use it. I just want to make sure it's in there. Okay. Let's go. What
are you guys doing? Stop. So should I go? I got to go to the northern end of this area.
There's there's three. There's two or three quests. I can go get the stuff for that guy.
What is that? Okay. His heirloom brass clock from 1795. Uranium from 612.
Or the. Okay. Let's go. Let's go to 1795. Go to year one. You said one. Let's go. Fine.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on. Come on.
Come on. Come on. Come on. Where are my headlights?
Whatever. Shut up. I just got a little startled. Where's Jesus? Jesus. Jesus. I have a lot of
important stuff to tell you. Can I get lost? I can't see anything. Where's the snow in 1 AD?
Don't you feel like that all this stuff shouldn't be here? I know that's not that far away, but it
kind of feels like it should be, right? I feel like there wasn't grass. Think about that, right? I feel
like there wasn't grass in like 600 million BC. Isn't that weird to think about? I'll drive around
for a minute. NA education. No, I know that it exists. I'm just saying it's weird to think about.
I keep taking this fucking thing out and I'm an idiot. I'm going to start holding on to these
because if I go back in time, maybe it'll be Phil again. All right. I'm going to drive around for
a little bit. Do I have my, where are my headlights? Okay. They're on. Are they on? I can't, I really
can't tell. I wear my headlights. There we go. I guess it's really not that interesting. What's,
what would be so interesting here? It's just outside. That's it. I don't know what everyone
was expecting. It's just outside. Even if there were dinosaurs or even if there were other animals,
it'd probably be pretty hard to find them. Even right now. Wait a minute. Wait a minute. There's
a structure here. What's going on? What is this? Okay. If you, if I, if you walked into the woods
right now and your goal was I'm going to find a bear, you probably wouldn't. Like what are you
talking about? That's, that's just not going to happen. They could, they could, there's so much
surface area. They could be anywhere. They could be anywhere. It would take like hours potentially
to find one. At least an hour, which I'm not giving them more than an hour to look for a dinosaur.
Airbag just fucking hits me in the face. I'm just unconscious.
How would this change the course of human history? Because there's nuclear shit in here. Somebody
would find this and I would change the complete course of all history. 120 FOV Andy. What's wrong
with that? Is this water? I thought this was slate. Let's go to like 9999. No, not that's too easy.
Let's go somewhere weird. I don't want to go to one and then 9999. Okay. I'll go to 2323. That
sounds fun. And I just said to not do that number of whatever. We're here. Okay. Here we go. Okay.
Let's go to 1225 Christmas at, I don't know, somewhere in like the evening. Let's go.
My FOV is not 120. It's 90. Oops. Oh no. Civilization. What happened? No, this is a bad,
this is not a good Christmas. 25. Wait, what? This thing bugged. I don't, the difference between
one AD and 25 AD is not that long. I didn't type it in wrong. What? What happened? I did not type
that in wrong. Was it a typo? It's set for December 25th, 1225. The maximum is 2030. Oh, that's right.
So what did I just say? I just nuked the earth. Oh, this sucks. Christmas doesn't exist in 2525.
Whatever. I didn't cool it off. Oh, whatever. Civilization didn't exist anymore. All right. I
want to go, I'm going to, okay, I'm going to put it all my favorite numbers. You ready? What are some
of my favorite numbers? Okay. I like, I like 10. I also like, I like seven and then think of a few
digits. What's some of my favorite numbers? I like the number 10. No, I like the number five.
I like five. I also like three. I also like seven. No, I like seven. Okay. I also like the number 10.
I also like the number five. Let's go. Okay. Where are we at? 540, like year 537.
Holy shit, that's always really loud. I just, whatever. This is the middle ages.
So this is probably like a town, right? Try just look for a town. I'm going to find a settlement.
I'm going to run around screaming. You'll never be the same. You'll never be the same. None of you
will ever be the same. I'm going to go like this with a lighter. Then I'm going to show my phone
to everybody. I'm going to go like this and I'm going to leave. Settlement? No. Oh, the world was
really boring before fucking Twitter, huh? This is in the middle of nowhere in Arizona. Check your
world map. Do I have a world map? M? World map. Ancient ruins? Guys, this ancient ruins. How do I
get here? Oh my God. All right. Fuck everything else. We're going to the ancient ruins. Shit.
All right. So I got to turn around and go this way. So just turn the car completely around,
just drive this way. All right. This is cool. I'm very excited now. Let's go. Maybe I'll run
into some people. Don't drive into the lake. I'm not going to drive into the lake. Not again. All
right. Don't go a hundred miles per hour. Being stupid. All right. This pine lake, old forest.
Where are the, wait, when the ruins? What happened to the ancient ruins? They're gone. There's no
ancient ruins anymore. Lower your FOV. It's not that high. It's literally 90. What do you want it
at? It's the first ever McDonald's. What actually is this? This is a tree? Why is there a tree made
out of weird like banana leaves? What is this? Should I take a sample or something? That's kind
of weird. This is tar? Were there really tar pits like this at five, six hundred A.D.? I don't know
why, but like a big tar pit to me sounds like it should be long, long time ago. Something right
here. What the fuck? There was just like a settlement. All right. Where are those ruins?
There's the lake, old forest. Let's go to the old forest. Why don't just please go to A.D. 69.
I'm thinking about it. All right. Old forest. I think I'm there. Yeah. Ancient ruins. Stop. Oh
my God. I think I'm going to get on foot. So don't smash up the car. It says they were here.
What's that? There's an animal. Any supplies or anything? They don't have, where's anything?
Wait, now travel from here. Oh, wait a minute. Dude, if I travel right here and I go either back
or forward, this is kind of, this is cool. I'm actually into this. All right. Let's go. Let's
go forward. What? A couple hundred years or go backwards a hundred years. Is this the ancient
site? I would imagine it is, right? Kind of has to be. It says it's like here. Yeah. These are ancient
ruins, which means like two or three hundred years ago. Let's do it. I'm going to save the game
because I want to make sure I don't get this wrong. I want it on. I want unlimited. I want to explore.
I don't want to do the quests. Only two or three hundred. What do you mean? I'm almost out. Go to
300. Will that be there when I come back? OK. All right. You guys ready? We're going to find out
who this ancient civilization was. So we're going to go back a hundred years ago, October 7th,
or, I mean, September, whatever. Let's go to September 7, zero, 200, zero, 100.
100 years, dude, is barely one generation. But you know what I mean? Let's go 100 or like,
I don't know, 20, 50. I'm going to try 50 A.D. Let's go. Not enough speed.
I'm just doing donuts at the ancient site. Whatever. I'm just going to go this way.
I didn't hit enter. Like, boom, it disappeared. It's fucking left here. All right. Wait, wait,
wait, wait, wait. I did. Yes, I did. I hit enter on 5 a.m. There. What the hell was that?
Come on. I got to get speed. All right. All right. All right. I'm good. I'm good.
Oh, all right. Let's go back to that place. See what's going on. Get these fucking trees. I'm so
mad right now. OK. I'm not going to bang a right. What's why is it so weird looking? So why is so
green? There it is. All right. Humans have been around for 250,000 years. I can't I can't go back
that far. Go negative. I can only do zero, zero, zero. All right. Let me load it. I'm going to go
forward and see what happens. Go B.C. I can't. I don't think I can. Yeah, it's only A.D. right now.
One A.D. would have it maybe. Yeah, I can only go to one. I want to see what happens in the future.
So what do we think? Maybe like a thousand, like 1200 A.D. Do the quest. I'll do the quest,
but I just want to do this one more time. Let me load the game because I want to see if anything
actually changes here. Does that be cool if it did? Yeah, I'm going to lap my ass off if the
ruins are the exact same and it's like the year 2000. OK, here we go. I think I need to put the
I can't leave the car. Stop doing that. All right. After this, we'll do the quest.
I just want to see if it was possible. All right. We're going to go to
1210. OK, what? 1500, 2000, 1500 at during the day. So like noon. You think that's good? Let's
try it. Oh, come on. We didn't go yet. No. Although I could pretend if you were in the car here,
get out and look around and then see if you, you know, oh, hey, yeah, look how different
everything is and see if you're like, holy shit, wow, everything's so different. Let's
drive around a circle five times and tell somebody you actually time traveled. It's got to get under
300 and then I can go. Can we get ice cream if you're good and you haven't been very good?
It's a fucking dinosaur. I'm in the car. I'm in the car. What are you talking about?
I'm literally in the car. Did I kill him? Did I kill him? I don't know if I killed him.
I'm sure that won't affect anything. Why can't I kill it? I can't. I don't think I can kill it.
Wait, I come in peace. I have a cheeseburger in the backseat. No, I don't. OK, if I fed this weird
alien creature a cheeseburger, would it change genetic makeup throughout all of history of animals?
What the fuck is happening? Like, what do we use? Let's go. No, I didn't mean to punch. Can I ride
it? I think I bugged it out when it went into the car. I can't. I want to like bring it with me.
I'm in the car. Get in the car. Get in the car. There's a bunch of sciences that definitely want
to see you. All right, whatever. Fuck you guys. I'm going to 1500 AD. See you later. Have fun
with the fucking meteor. All right, we're at 1500. Let's go check it out. I have to bring the car,
man. Quick, dude. Make Among Us before the other people do. You don't understand. If I made Among
Us, it wouldn't be successful. Nobody would play it. No, it doesn't work like that. My Among Us
would be just barely slightly different and it would not take off. You should go. That's the idea?
What? So I go back and make Among Us and make it shitty so that nobody cares about it. You guys
really don't like that game. Of all the things we could change in all history, you want me to go back
and make sure Among Us is not popular. Okay, this is a fun game. What's wrong with you? All right,
so this is this is where 1500 AD. It's been about a thousand years. Here we are. What does civilization
look like? Why is it so radioactive here? Everything's, everything's radiated. Have I
been doing it too much here? I've been traveling through time in this one location too many times
that I've, I've irradiated the- there's nobody here? Holy shit, the whole world is green. What did I do?
Too many times in the same spot?
What's happening? It's even worse. What is happening to the world? What had, what happened?
Did I, I've ruined civilization. I just wanted to see if there were any people in these houses.
I fucked up everything. Wait, what if I go to the- what if I just go to- okay, wait a minute.
It's the year 2000. What if I just go to one of these stores? Did I really ruin everything?
I'm gonna just drive this way. Did I fuck up the whole world? Do I have to restart the whole game?
I'm gonna go touch that. I'm gonna go, I'm gonna put my face in that. You never know guys,
it could be like the Matrix. I might put my head in here and like know how to fly a helicopter.
What? It was a collectible. Oh my fucking god. Did I seriously just kill myself? That's so fucking
dumb. All right. Should I, I'm gonna, all right, I'm gonna go back. I think I fucked up a lot of
stuff here. Let me just see. I gotta, all right, I gotta get out of here. This is, there's nobody
here. There's no civilization here. There's just these squares with holes in them. That's it. I,
Jerma fucking hates the Lorax. I've never seen that movie and I never read the book. I don't
know what it is. I just know Danny DeVito is the main character. I want to go here. We're gonna
check one thing. I'm going to do the mission, but I gotta turn this way because this is where
the town is. I'm going up there. I give off Lorax vibes. What do you, what does that mean?
I don't know what that means. You have to elaborate. I don't know what you're talking about.
Okay. So it's 537. That's the year. Droppings. Some kind of droppings over there. Okay. Now I
gotta bang a left. He's short and orange. I mean, I am kind of orange today. I'm not wearing
concealer. No, I'm, I am a little orange. You're right. This is a good place to do it because I
want to go to the, I'm going to save it. We're going to go to the year 2000. We're going to
go to the year 2000. No, we're not. What do I want to do? It was a bank robbery in Pine Lake during
the 18 seventies. Supposedly this led Westwood discovering the secret hideout of some 20 bandits.
The courthouse archives in Pine Lake supposedly have a document on it. All right. I'm just going
to time travel again and load like save number one, whatever it was. Cause I kind of, I'm interested
in that. I want to know what that means. Um, this one here, drink some more water. I got it right
here. What do you think this is? Yeah. All right. So this puts us back here. Let's go to the archives.
I want to, I want to look at that up. So this is, I need the city archives. This looks like a city
building. This time don't dump nuclear waste everywhere. I didn't, it was empty. All right.
This 612 store has it, but where do, it said to go up, right? Cape Dunn. That's for the other guy,
the old guy that used to be our friend. Uh, I want to do the 1800s one. So I need to go to the city
archive where I don't know where that is. Oh, it's probably here, right? Recycling station.
Thanks. I really did not want it to go the other way. Who's talking to me?
All right. I need the, I need the courthouse or something. Wait, what do you have?
Huh? Yes. Why are you sad? Uh, well, I don't know if I should even tell at this point.
What's about her? Yeah. Well, Sandy, she works in that ice cream shop just across the square.
Lowers his voice. I mean, yes, I want to ask her out. Why don't you just ask her out? I thought
about making a nice present of sorts that would fit her. Okay. A flower, just one flower. No,
it's a special one. It's called the Eleanor. Seemingly everybody tells me I should stop
dreaming. This particular plan is extinct for hundreds of years now. I know I can find one.
I'll have to search really, really hard. Am I really going to go back in time and pick a flower
for this guy? Sure. Yeah, I can help. Okay. Look at the bookstore. Okay. I think you can look at the
bookstore just next to the mechanic. Get that flower book and see if it can help you. I want
to go do the bandit thing. All right. No, no, no. I want the courthouse. I need that map to show me
where the courthouse is. Fucking burping and y'all and you can hear it. I hate that. Do the flower
plot line. No, that's boring. I want to go fight the bandits. I'm not hitting the tree. Okay. Town
square. It's probably where the statue was, right? I'm going to assume that statue is over here.
Oh, information. This is definitely it. 100%. Okay. Post office archives. There it is.
What's that? Why is that a health bar on the screen? Okay. This is nice. I'm looking for info
on the robbery that happened. Nevermind. You're not going to help me. Oh shit. After a lengthy
interrogation, I managed to deduct that the thieves have been hiding underneath the well
known waterfall in the west. That's when I ambushed and defeated the 20 bandits in their boss.
My new friend helped me in the ambush by his clever distraction.
I recovered a load of redacted material from the cave. All the captured bandits are to be relocated
to Isla de los Tontos charged for robbery. By the speedy aid of my friend. This is,
they're talking about me. There was a minor altercation afterwards with
Diego's gang. They tried to steal our recovered goods from the bank. They weren't much a problem.
I suggest also moving them to Isla de los Tontos charged for it. Okay. So this is 1871.
1871. The robbery of Pine Island Nashville occurred March 15th, 1871 at 1 20 p.m.
So we should go there at 12 and just wait. Write that down. Yeah, you write it down for me.
It happened at the well. All right. 12 o'clock, March 15th, 1871, 12 o'clock. Pine Island National
Bank. Write it down. Let's go. You write it down. I can't. My hands are occupied. All right. Where's
the bank? Fuck. Where's the bank? I see. I didn't know where the bank is. Park train station. It's
not on here. I said to find it. I know you have a quest, but fine. What is it? Any rumors? I heard
back in the 70s there was this accordion man who you would not want to meet at nights in the forest.
I suppose you could try it in the town archives. I don't care about the accordion man.
Where's the bank? Ice cream. Where's the bank? Is this a bank? No, it's like a recycling center.
Where's the bank? Books, hoverboards. I don't know. I'm not doing accordion man. I don't want
to do that right now. If I zoom in, will it say? Do it after the bank? Maybe. You didn't read
homestuck. What does it have to do with anything? This is not a bank. This is a library. There's the
lab. Where's this fucking bank? Oh, bank time. So this is where I need to be. I'm going to get here
at noon. That's let me look at the map because literally I've messed this up. All right. It is
right below that pine lake thing, right below it kind of to the south western area right
into the ice cream shop. Let's go. All right. Where's the car? All right. I'm just going to
drive down this street and I'm going to get there at noon. We'll be there about an hour early
for me to stop the robbery. You're disgusting. Why would you say something weird like that?
All right. Here we go. Get in. I'm ready. Let's do it. What was the date again? It was something
something is March 3 15. No, what do you? Okay. Three. I'm trying to do the fucking month. What
is it? Oh, oh, three. What is going on right now? Oh, it won't accept. Oh, three. Oh, three.
I just did that three times. Oh, three. Stop giving random dates. 1871 at 12 noon. Let's go for it.
Let's fucking do it. Let's get to the bank. I need a better straight away. There we go. What even
happened? Too much juice. All right. The bank. They're going to rob the bank. Turn that off.
Turn that off. Turn it off. All right. They're going to rob the bank in an hour. I want to sell
my no. What do I do? How do I stop them? I'm going to do anybody suspicious. I don't have
a weapon or anything. Go tell the sheriff. Sheriff. Sheriff. Listen to me. Am I too late?
What exploded? What did I just do? I didn't just blow up the bank. Get out of the fucking way.
Sheriff. Sheriff. Everything's safe. No, it's not safe. Oh my God. What time is it? Four. Wait,
they already robbed it? Is that them robbing the bank? What? I did it. Wait, why were they coming
out of my car as if I brought them here? I backed up the car into the bank and they all started
getting out of the car. Everybody wants to rob it. Okay. So I went to... Wait, what? Oh, it's an auto
save. I'm getting in the car. Should I get a gun? They haven't robbed it yet. Why did the month and
day change? Throw uranium at them. Year 2000. Wait, what's going on? How come the dates are
different? I'm so confused. Oh, okay. 120. I'm ready. Oh my God. Go talk to the sheriff. I tried
to talk to the sheriff and he didn't have anything to say. He just said, oh, all right. There's no
options. Here we go. That wasn't the sheriff. Why was he standing behind the counter? I can't
interact with him. Sorry. What fucking time is it? What? 13. Oh, right. It's not a regular clock.
It's a 20. What the fuck? It kind of works. Five minutes and then another wave. Excuse me?
Excuse me? The car won't turn on. What? You can't be fucking serious. Why is it so dark?
Why did the fucking car turn off? I'm getting a gun. What is that? Did it run out of gas? I don't
know what happened. I need to go get a weapon or something. $4 back in the 1800s is like $50
million. So I'll be fine. Two bucks. What do you? I don't think I can get a gun. So how am I
supposed to? There's a lot of people that come in. Can I get like a melee weapon? Blacksmith. Here
we go. Can I buy something? Ooh, revolver parts. Okay. 20 bucks. I need money. Motherfucker. I'm
going to go back in time again. I gotta go find gold or something. Go back another. Oh my God.
I gotta go back like three days and find gold and sell it. I gotta find gold here. You should
just rob the bank. Okay. No, there's gotta be gold, right? Rob the bank and then travel back in time
and pay with the stolen money. But wouldn't I always rob the bank if I kept going back?
What about their hideout? Don't you have a bank to rob? Why is everybody chasing me?
They're not robbing the bank. I'm preventing the bank robbery. They're shooting each other.
The fuck? What happened? I think if I wrap around and eat a barbecue sandwich, I think I'd be fine.
Where's the barbecue place? Get out of here. There's people attacking town. I got it. I got
it. I got it. Quick, quick, quick. Go, go, go, go, go, go, go. No, I want to order a barbecue. I want
to order a sandwich. I can't have a barbecue. This is the barbecue place, right? What's going on?
Barbecue. Get rid of me. Fuck. Where are they going? Bill Banker said, what was that?
Bill, if you're not paying attention this entire time, where's the gold? My gold. I guess I have
to open up the reserves in the bunker. Wait, why does the sheriff not have a gun? The sheriff
doesn't have a gun. This is fucked up. I have to hide the car. These are the time police. Why are
they? They're not the time police. They're time agents. What are you talking about? They're
time agents? I'm so confused. Let me bully you. Wait, what?
Why did they kill that guy? What's happening? Why they're dressed like they're from this time
period. All right. I have to hide the car. I'm going to hide the car. I'm going to hide the car,
hide the car, hide the car. I thought that was an entire group of people coming to get me
that they are dressed with their have like they have bandit masks. What do you mean? They're time
agents. Get the car out of the way. Hide it. Okay, here we go. They're trying to blend in.
Okay, Bill Banker. What do you have? Buy a dollar for 210 coins. Buy 100 gold for 100. I can't even
look at that. My head hurts. Look at it. All right. Now I got to protect it. Fucking time agents.
They thought they were bank robbers. What time is it? All right. They'll be here any minute.
I don't know what time it is because my fucking car is over there in a ditch. So I don't know
what time it is. Okay, cool. All right. They're going to come in a minute. What is this game? The
game is called No Time. It is on Steam. It's early access. I think it's actually really fun.
I am confused about it a few times though. Once you get used to it. I think this is really cool.
This is a really great idea. All right. They should be coming any second now. Yep. Did they come?
From what direction did they come though? What a beautiful day. Bill Banker. What? Go, go, go.
Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. What's going on? Why was he already in there? I need a
fucking gun. I'm so red. I'm so sick and fucking tired of waiting. I'm not waiting anymore. I'm
just getting in the car. No, get out now. Get out. I'm going. I don't care. Put me back. Take this
fucking thing out. Time agents. I'll show you how we're going to handle this. No, not 11. No, not
1150. You piece of shit. No, not March. Why can't I do 115? At this point it's already...
Just give me a fucking calendar. 03. 15. 1871. 0115. I don't care. I'm not waiting. I want to see if
this works actually. I'm testing something. It doesn't work. Fucking never mind. Reload the game.
Reload the game. Reload the game. I was trying to send it and just not even be in it.
Okay. How come the trunk is closed? All right. I guess the correct way to do this is to get a gun.
Right? We're going to find a job. The blacksmith pays well. Really? Wait, I can work there?
Need help? Grill steaks. Holy shit. Okay, cool. Prepare the steaks on the grill. Take an order.
I'll take a steak, please. What do you want?
What happened? Prepare the steaks on the grill. Once they're done,
put them on the plate and ring the bell. That's what I did. A steak, please. Yes. Okay. Here's
a steak. Why did the guy leave? What the fuck? What? Don't order food and fucking leave, dude.
The fucking bank. The bank, the bank, the bank, the bank, the bank.
All the time people are... Why is there no juice? Oh, because I didn't load it. I have to go back.
I got to go back. I got to go back here and I got to come back here like a day early.
I got to go back a day early. I can't be hit 15 minutes before it happens. I got to be here
like a few days early. Go and stop it potentially at the hideout. Why are you forcing yourself?
I'm not forcing myself to play this. I actually am having a good time.
You suck and this game sucks. Why don't you go rake some leaves then? What are you doing here?
Why don't you go rake some leaves? If you don't like the game and you don't like me,
what is keeping you here? Why don't you go fucking rake some leaves?
What do you want me to do for you? It's summer. So go rake some rocks. Okay. I am going to do
this mission. Dude, your stream sucks. This game sucks. My computer sucks. I have a virus on my
computer. Something smells in my room. Something smells in my room too. Oh, by the way, I ordered
something from Amazon. I didn't get here today. It was supposed to get here. I don't know, man.
What do you want me to say? Spray some air freshener in your room. Go play Scrabble.
All right. I have an idea. This game doesn't suck. You just don't have an IQ like I do to
understand it. Okay. March 14th, 1871 at 12 o'clock. This gives us plenty of opportunity
to make some stakes. We can make some money. I'm going to buy a gun and I'm going to stop
the robbery. Let's go for it. You ready? I am. We're here a day early. I have a day to get
enough money. I'm going to buy a gun and I'm going to be prepared this time. Sometimes you sound like
Peter Griffin. It's because Peter Griffin and I, Peter Griffin's a fictional character from
fictional New England. He has a fictional New England accent. Sometimes I have a New England
accent. I grew up there. So sorry. Me and Peter Griffin are from the same fucking area. I'm sorry.
I didn't. I'm sorry that I sound like Peter Griffin. I'm leaving that there. We're doing
this without the time. Hey, nobody asked for your life story. That's so stupid. Where are you from
in New England? It's from Rhode Island. It's called Kohog. It's like a small town. All right,
let's make some money. You look like a man that could use a stake. Can I help you? Anybody want
any food? Nobody's here. Do I have like all of my clothes on? Everyone's just sitting here looking
at me. What's, nobody hungry? All right. That was fun. All right. What about the blacksmith?
He might've bugged out. Actually something really important. Oh my God. I forgot. It's going to take
me a fucking whole day to go back to them. I didn't save it. I got to go back to the car.
Oh, I got to go back to the car. I will be, what's going on? What? I'm here a day early.
You fucking assholes. God, leave me alone. I didn't save it. Why can I kill them with a car?
I didn't save the game. I have no health. People were tougher back then, dude. How do I get rid
of these guys? You're doomed. Okay. At least the game is saved. I'm going to eat some food.
I don't know if they're going to follow me or not. Probably not. Okay. I have a save game.
Back to the town. Okay. Blacksmith. Can I do some work for the blacksmith?
I got to be able to eat, right? Yeah. Okay. Need help? Good luck. Your task is to craft
tools on demand. You'll get a guide with every new product. Okay. A woodcutter's axe, please.
You got it. Woodcutter's axe. Okay. And then you hit it with a hammer. Okay. And then this
goes into the water. Okay. And then this goes on a stick. I got it. Where's the customer? Nice.
All right. What do you want? Hammer, please. You got it. Hammer. Hilt. How do you make a hammer?
It's literally the same exact thing. Good. All right. Anybody else? Can I use an axe as a weapon?
Maybe I can. All right. Take a woodcutter's axe. And I... All right. Let's go. I made it with an axe
hilt. I don't know. Whatever. It's fine. Is it not ready? Let's go. Let's go. Come on. I'm gonna make
like 50 bucks. You made a block of cheese. Kind of. I'm running out of time. I got enough to do one
more. What do you want? Hurry up. Axe. Done. Go. Quick. What was wrong with it? What's going on?
Whatever. I'm making... I'm taking it. I'm making an axe myself. $65. Go get my gun. Who sells the
gun? The blacksmith sells the gun. All right. Buy bitcoin right now and cash it out in 300 years.
Okay. And I want the cowboy costume. That's too much money. All right. So now what do I do with
this? What am I supposed to do with this? How do I make it? Revolver parts. You have to build it?
How do you... How do I do that? I have to put it together? Put it together. Is there instructions?
Press the build button? I don't think there is a build button. Is it just junk? I don't think it's
junk. He's pretending. Dude, I got a box of junk on the ground. How am I supposed to turn this into a
gun? Is there a gunsmith? There might be. Not in this town. Unless the sheriff can do it. Maybe
talk to the blacksmith again. Press eight on the number pad. B. Eight does not do it. Can you make
anything with this? All this guy sells is props. Okay. Two and then three. Somebody has to be able
to put this together. All right. I've maybe I should bring it to a different time period.
Oh my god. Leave me alone. E doesn't do it either. It's definitely something I have to make.
I probably need a recipe or something. Yeah. Put it on the blacksmith's table.
Use the bossy. I don't know what that is. I don't think I can do anything with this yet.
I probably have to unlock it. Unless somebody else can make this into a gun. Okay. Do not travel to
666 AD. I don't even know where the car is, man. Do the main quest. Okay. Um, is crafting hidden?
Wait, so I can take this with me to and make it and then come back. Let me go in the car.
How far back and travel? You can go to 0001 AD. One AD. Jeremy, say hi to my grandma. She's 82 and
loves your streams. Um, hi grandma. All right. I'm gonna I'm giving this game like another 30 minutes
and we're gonna move on to something else. Hi grandma. Wait, is it what day is it? Do they
attack the bank right now? Go to the future where the gun is already built. All right. Hold on.
I don't have any more fuel. Okay. I need to reload. Was that way too dank? I'm sorry. Way
too dank. All right. You know, my favorite part about this game is this. I love the traveling
around. I want to find a good place to go. I'll do 2023. My brain is too small for this game. All
right. I'll be honest with you. See, for instance, I just tried to type in 15 for the month. There's
not a 15th month. Let's go. Wedged in somewhere. How did I go perfectly into a wedge? What the
hell is that? I can't, I don't think I can get in the car. All right. We're good. Headlights. Let's
go. So here's the donut shop. Are the aliens or something? What is in the road? Is that mine?
I'll take it, I guess. God, stop. Oh my fuck. I keep thinking it's a fucking monster.
What's going on these days? Watch out for the crabs. There we go. Okay. I want that. It's like
flying spaceships. Derma likes this game. I really do. I like the idea of this game a lot.
Was there a giant laser? What the hell is that? Is that the track? What is that? I'm investigating.
Don't read into it. He likes it. No, I think it's a really, really fun experience. I think it's a
really, really cool idea. And I commend the devs for trying something different. My brain just can't
handle going into like three places at the same time. Stop being so nice, Madge. Why? It takes a
lot of work. I'm still here playing it, aren't I? I want to know what the laser is. I'm going up
there. The flashlight. What the hell? All right. I'm going up to the laser. Drive up there. I mean,
you think I'm going to drive up this hill? That's not going to happen. Oh, there's a waterfall in
2020 AD. Oh, this is not a laser. This is a track. I'm going to find the laser beam. It's not what
I think it is. Very futuristic. This is 2023. All right. Now I'll do 9999, right? I will do the
coveted 9999. Oh, no, we can't. It stops at 2030. Right, right, right, right. All right. Well,
that was fun. That was a cool little game. We're going to move on. I just wanted to play it. I saw
it and I was going to play it. Whatever. I think it was really cool. I think it was fun. I think
it was interesting. There's a whole main quest line if you'd like to try it yourself. It's called
No Time. It's on Steam currently on Early Access. It seems like there's a lot of content in it so
far. That has been Checking It Out Thursdays. We're going to check out something else. Go back to
Wheel of Fortune. Whoa, what's this? Oh, it's a lighthouse. Okay. Maybe I should have got the car.
That does not hurt. That doesn't hurt.
Shit. All right. We're going to move on. I'm going to take a break. I'm going to pee. I'll be right
back. That was No Time. There's a lot in that game. If you want to check it out for yourself,
give it a go. I think that was a fun part of the stream. We're going to move on to part two,
which that's going to be. What would you like to know? I would too because I don't know.
I'm going to go pee. I'll be right back. We'll figure it out. See you guys in two minutes.