Hey, what is going on, everybody? Jerma here with a Team Fortress 2 gameplay commentary, and tonight I'm gonna be playing as the Spy with the default setup, completely default.
It's a short gameplay, but this is gonna be a pretty short video. I want to just address something that's gonna be happening this weekend, something I'm gonna be a part of, and you should too.
And what that thing is, is the Tip of the Hats charity event is going on Saturday, starting tomorrow. Today I'm recording this video on Friday, and it's going up on Friday afternoon or Friday night.
So if you see this video, like next Sunday, then I'm referring to this weekend, the 29th, starting the 29th.
The charity is gonna be the One Step Camp, which is a charity. It's an organization that is designed to help young kids with cancer go to camp and have a good camp experience.
It was started by some doctor and some oncologist in Chicago, and it's a pretty good charity, so I'm glad that we're benefiting that. Glad we can help out some of these kids.
And it's all starting 12 p.m. Eastern Time, or 4 p.m. GMT is when it's starting on the 29th, Saturday tomorrow. I'm gonna be there. I'll be there for at least some of the events.
I'm gonna try to pop in as much as I can. I'll be in the chat for a while. You'll probably see me at some point this weekend. It's all getting streamed.
It'll be on Twitch. It's gonna be going from Saturday until late Sunday. So if you think, oh, well, it's tomorrow afternoon. I don't have time. I'm not gonna be able to make it.
You can jump in at any time during this weekend and join in on the festivities. That's the great part about this is you don't have to. It's not like a one hour thing.
This is going to be going the entire weekend. And on that stream, there's going to be some pretty interesting stuff going on.
First of all, there's going to be some pretty high level jumpers and surfers. I remember last year I was just mesmerized at some of the crazy shit these guys could do.
And that alone is worth going to watch. And I'm not exactly sure when that the schedule is on the website, which the links will be in the description.
But besides that, there's going to be competitive matches that are going to get streamed. There's going to be pubs. There's going to be random little events, random cool little things.
It's going to be a really awesome event. It's going to be a lot of fun. So I recommend you show up there. All the links, all the relative links will be in the description for you to check them out when this all goes live tomorrow.
And again, if you're watching this tomorrow, then get over here. We're like having fun raising money for some kids. What are you doing?
And last year they raised somewhere around thirty five thousand dollars in like two days. So that's just remarkable to me that this community is capable of something that amazing.
And I really hope we either match that or even surpass it this year. We'd be making a whole lot of kids happy. And that's the most important thing of this whole weekend.
So with that, I'm going to wrap up the video. Just a quick little shout of what I'm going to be doing this weekend. And I'll see you guys there. I'll see you guys next time. And of course, take care, everybody.