What's up? How's everybody doing? How are you? Good afternoon. Here comes illegal movie night. Nope, that's not even correct. We're gonna go we'll talk about it right now. I should probably wait. I've only been live for about 60 seconds. You gotta wait for people to come in. I'm fucking I'm excited today. I'm full I'm full of vitamin D today. Now just be clear. Just the sun was just in my face. Like 15 minutes. Now I just I could just find the vitamin D is flowing through my body. I was just I was there was a shade open. I just stood there and just let the sun hit me
in the face through the window. I feel great. We can tell he's a what he's a photosynth he's a photosynthesis streamer. That's probably true. I'm at the peak. The height of my energy. When the sun is at its hottest. And at its complete and total apex. I definitely I'm probably made I'm probably part plant. Yeah, I'm like 40% human 25% dog 10% goldfish.
And then to one. Hi, how are you can see? And probably like, I don't know, 18% humidity. And then maybe three or 4% of lily or something. That makes sense. Definitely not a cactus. I drink too much water. I gotta move this. I gotta move this thing. I mean, and I will. I'm gonna get this on like a big I'm gonna get like a professional streamer hook. You know, those things that come down, like the old like 1980s radio stations, the thing that hangs down in front of people's faces.
I'm gonna get one of those. So I never like elbow you in the head of her again. I can't believe you won't finish beautiful Joe. It's all right. You take your losses and you take your wins. Beautiful Joe was a loss for me. It's okay. I have the second one too. I was like, people are gonna love this.
People are gonna love beautiful Joe man. Beautiful Joe one, I got beautiful Joe too. People are gonna be clamoring for this. Exactly. They can't wait for beautiful Joe too. I got 40 minutes into beautiful Joe one. And it was like you guys would, you guys were beaten up by it. And I keep talking about this too. I keep talking about beautiful Joe. This is like day three in a row where I've talked about beautiful Joe. So this is it. We're not gonna talk about beautiful Joe anymore. This is where it ends.
Okay, but let's go over what's gonna happen next week. I've got a plan for next week. We've got the whole thing locked out. Are you ready? So starting on Tuesday, Tuesday is going to be the movie night. So what's movie night? What do you mean? What are you talking about? We talked last night and a couple nights ago, we went over it. I was going to try the twitch prime movie watch party thing. But I looked at it. I looked at what was on the watch party as like 15 movies and then 40 or 50.
Amazon TV shows that they desperately want people to watch. Like, like Jack Russell, whatever it was. What's that show? Jack Russell? No, that's a dog. What? What's the show that like Amazon wants everybody to watch so bad? Jack Ryan. Okay. Yeah, I mean, I'm not going to watch Jack Ryan. That's it. It's like Jack Ryan. And then like seven movies. So until they fill that catalog up with hopefully a bugs life at some point, we're going to watch a public domain movie on Tuesday. We might even watch two depending on how long they are. So Monday,
it's going to be public domain movie night. And there is the watch party on twitch right now is only for people in the United States. You have to have Amazon prime, you know, twitch prime. And maybe in the future, we'll try it out. But I do want to try it eventually. But we're going to do public domain movies. So tonight, after Casino Wink, we're going to go back to Casino Wink because I want to play it again, because I think it was really fun. After we're done with that, after maybe a few hours, we're going to spend a little time. We're going to pick some of some of our top picks for public domain
movie. And that's the plan. So Tuesday's public domain movie night, Wednesday is going to be community content night. There we go. Future me does not now have to go back and go, what? Oh, I didn't know. I'm holding future me accountable. Wednesday is going to be community content night. Thursday will be mystery game and throw mystery game in there. And then Friday, Friday is going to be the Easy Bake Oven stream. Hopefully all the things that I need will be available for it. That's the plan. Plan is to have Friday be the Easy Bake Oven stream. If Friday cannot be the
Easy Bake Oven stream, if for some reason it's not ready, then it'll just be on Saturday or Sunday. It's going to happen this weekend. I'm looking forward to it. Why does somebody just say we to do? Does that make any sense? Oh, because I said the word bake. Right, right, right. Today is Friday. Yeah, I'm talking about like for next week. Movie night, community content night, mystery game, Easy Bake Oven is your plan for next week. But for now, we're going to go back into Casino Wink. And the reason why I was going to think about doing a movie
tonight, like I was going to do it tonight, but I don't want to rush through Casino Wink. I feel like there's at least a few more hours of stuff that I want to see. I'm having fun with it. I don't want to put this. Oh, I got to, I got to hurry the fuck up and get off Casino Wink because we got to watch that movie.
So Tuesday is going to be the movie, maybe even two. We'll find out. We'll figure it out tonight. So let's see how much more stuff there is to do in Casino Wink. I those of you that missed it, we're going to pick up where we left off. I'm going to try
to stop the bleeding. I'm going to try to stop the the never ending money drain. I'm going to try to get a second property and we're going to make the second property, the Chuck E. Cheese. Because then I can, I don't have to, I don't have to delete anything. I'm going to try.
So without further ado, let's get started. We're not going to get something called Chuck E. Cheese. It's going to be like a Chuck E. Cheese styled restaurant. It's going to be arcade games. It's going to be pizzas. And I'm going to permanently have a Rhino on staff to walk around and be the Charles E. Rhino. Whatever the, whatever the Chuck E.'s name is. It's Chuck E. Cheese. It's Charles Cheese. That's the name of the rat. Of course it is. What am I talking about? Let's go. We have to make sure this is getting captured. Doesn't look like it is. Let's try this. Oh, there it is. All right. So which one of these
is right? His name is Charles Entertainment Cheese. That's so funny. All right. Which one? This one is 1646. This one is 1728. No. Wait, what? How was this? February 7th, 1970. Oh, right. That's the date in the game. All right. Which we're not doing this auto save. We're going to do from here. We're going to see where we were. There's a clown convention coming in. The window is too big. Hold that thought. Let me fix it. There you go. All right. So where we left
off was there was a problem. There was a, there was, I had a problem with one of my chefs. I got rid of him. He was, he was removed from the company. The doorman was a, there was a problem with the doorman. He was also removed from the company. And then we ended up here. Okay.
No, it is no longer a puke casino. It's actually fairly clean, but we had a lot of people leave the company recently. And there was a restaurant problem. Don't ever get into the restaurant business. It's just a never ending hole that you put money into. It's just don't ever make a
restaurant. There's no, don't do it. It was a hotel. All right. Here we go. I need $44,000. We need to go over our staff. This hotel makes a lot of money. $21,000. I got fined twice by the police for having too many prostitutes. And then for having too many fights, which I changed that.
Oh, there's no sound. I got it. Um, I fixed that by making the drinks, not $3. That helped, I think. So now let's take a look at our staff. What do we need?
Fuck. I can't collect. No, no, no, we're not. No, I can't do it. Just imagine this there. Put it on your screen and like look at it over on the, on like another window every few minutes. Hold on. Wait, I can't. I'll tab right now. Just hold on a second. Wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait, wait. This guy's making $240. Do it now. I'll do it later when I have a minute.
Just hold on. The hotel is doing fine. I need to go down to the second floor. We got to figure out what I want to do here. Okay, so who needs to stay? We have, you guys are still here. This is the burger factory and the ice cream factory. The bar. There's two bartenders that don't need to be here. There's only no, there's only here. The last thing that happened. Okay, the last thing happened was I accidentally. There's a convention starting. Okay, biker. No clowns. Oh, yes. I remember. Yeah, I asked the Garfield accidentally shot one of the technicians. I now remember.
Okay, so we need a new technician here. Seinfeld. Oh, okay. We need a technician, a cheap one. You can get to work. We only need one. There's not very many machines that are really in operation. All the waitstaff can go. We have to get rid of the waitstaff. We do. There's no, there's nothing. There's no, I don't know. Restaurant. There's no, nobody here. We have to wait till people actually start coming back to the casino. Just, just get rid of all the hookers that come in. Do I have any other counselors? I don't think I do. I don't. Just get rid of. Okay, you. Don't shoot him.
Just get rid of them. Eject. Every time I shoot somebody, I lose an hour of progress. Okay, people are starting to come back. We're not going to do that anymore. We're going to slowly build our empire back up to like, I make money and then I'm going to make a Chuck E. Cheese. It's going to be slots and lanes too. And there's no slot machines in the whole place. Okay, looking all right so far. Now what else do we need? Let me look at the staff menu again. Cashier wants more money. Where are you? Up here with the sports betting. Um.
City average is 36 bucks. Should I really give this person like five times what the city's average is? Just get. Get out of here. This is the dealer. You want five times. You want like at least twice double what everybody. You're a five star dealer. I have to keep you around. I have to keep the five star dealer around. Don't shoot him. Oh yeah, right. I shot him last time. Don't, just don't shoot him. Just get rid of him. I know they're asking for a raise. Don't shoot him. We have a second chance here.
Just fire detective curvy, whatever his name is. Goodbye. You're no longer working for the company. The doorman's not happy either. 95 dollars. I'm sorry. I'm doing it right now. And then we'll give a bonus to everybody that gets a bonus. All of you. Of two dollars. That's enough. Now let's go. No, I'm not going to blast him. We need to, we need to build our customers back up. All right, this wall is fucking with everybody's brains apparently. Okay, get, just delete it. No one's even using it anyways. We can have something else over here.
Well, I know, you know, this is more room for gambling. Yeah, get rid of these tables. I'm sorry. The whole waitstaff has to go. Where are you going? I don't have enough money. They have to go. No more waitstaff. I know. I know. I know the person. Okay. So the person making 270 dollars quadruple what everybody else is making. Sees somebody gets fired and goes, Oh no, I'll die. No, you just fired that person. Now you, therefore you freed up more money to pay me. Are you fucking kidding me? Unbelievable. I'm, it's, I know you're a five star dealer,
but there has to be somebody at the table. All right. Sorry. Ike is going to be losing. All right. 290 bucks. That's good. Okay. Here we are. We're doing all right. It's not bad now. We still have an opportunity. So we got to bring in some more customers. I got rid of a lot of, uh, overhead here. I got 24,000. This casino blows laughing my ass up. Yeah, it does. Because I had to do, I had to get rid of a bunch of shit because I had to delete a bunch of stuff because I wasn't making any money.
And four people were killed. Do you understand that? I'm trying. Here we go. Sit at this poker table. I got to come sit over here and play. I wish they would keep the noise down. How am I supposed to do that? Wait. Now you keep it. Now he's had causing a disturbance. Is it unlike the slot machine sounds? Get out. No, he don't get out. Go play one of these slot machines. There you go. There you go. Good, good, good, good, good, good, good, good. Okay.
Good. We need the porn theater. Oh, we need more staff. No, the porn theater is doing just fine. 30 bucks for a porn video. Two trailer trash up here enjoying it. That's 60 bucks. Every movie. I need some people to work here though. And I need the janitor to come up and clean this fucking mess up.
Okay. Why do you guys want so much money? What the fuck? Oh my God. You guys are bleeding me here. Everyone take a bonus of $5. Everybody's pay just increased. All right.
Inflation. It's been one day. What do you mean inflation? It's been like 16 hours. All right. I need people to, that's a five star. No, no, no, no, no. You just need, look, I don't need a five star cashier to have, have somebody go bowling the sports betting.
All right. All right. Good. Good. Good. Good. Okay. We got more porn enthusiasts. That's good. It's the only thing keeping us in the green right now is the porn enthusiasm. Now I can start accepting bets up here.
Do I have any janitors? All right. I have to get some. Okay. And I got to buy ads. I need to buy some more ads, even if they're shitty. I need them. Ads. This is a lot of money for an app, but I need it. We need people in here. I'm spending a little bit of money. I know. Cheap ads everywhere. Get money in the door. Cheap ads fucking everywhere. Now I can start living the money rolling.
It's the end of the day. Wages have been paid.
No, no, no funny business. No bullshit. Let's just start to roll in now. How cheap are the drinks? That's important. All right. We'll, we'll make them, we'll make the drinks six bucks. They're all in the same spot. All the ads are right next to each other.
There's three ads on the same road. What am I? Like a local, what am I? A local lawyer? Call the law officers of J.R. Tooley. 555. And then just back to back to back to back on the same road. Have you been injured in an automobile accident? Call me. I'll, I don't know what I'll do because I don't ever say what I do. Who's cheating? Get him out of here. Get him out of here. Then bounce into discipline. No, no, no, no, no. Wrong person. No, no, no, no, no, no. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop, stop.
That was a paying customer. No, you're leaving for the crypt casino. God damn it. Just go beat this guy up down there. Ooh, he's got a level four skill. All right, we got a level four skill, a cheater. Good. He's on our team now. Okay, let's go get some money from the cheats. Go cheat at the door. Everyone just get have a modest sum of $1,500.
There comes a biker convention. Heavy rock music is going to go upstairs. All of you go to the toy box casino. Every single cheater that I have and just everyone try to get $1,000. One of you will make out with it. They can't catch you all. Okay, that's a fact.
What are we waiting for down here? Why is there a police officer in the elevator? What? Why is there an officer in the elevator? He's not in there anymore. What? Hold on, did he climb up? Wait, did he change clothes? He's a biker. He just put a fat suit on.
You have a sting operation right now. Oh, it's the beer. Oh, wait, we got to go upstairs. Bikers are in. Okay, this is going to make sure this is porn. Okay, and it's 10% off porn night. Good. Oh, the dance floor is gone. Oh, whatever.
18 bucks. Say the line. The teens are in here now. He just wants to bowl. All right, he just wants to bowl. It's eight. He just wants to bowl. He's not like drinking. He's not gambling or anything. Okay, he can bowl.
Okay, how's the hotel doing? $55 a night. Let's try to fill these rooms. Nobody's playing these games. Where's the biker convention? Get here already. You forgot to do the voice. Do the voice. Yeah, I don't forget. I'm like an elephant.
We need to fill this place up. Come on, let's go. Where's the convention? Somebody died three days ago. I know. I know. I know that's why. Bikers went to the better casino. Fuck, they're all leaving. It's all right. Just wait till I open up Chuck E. Cheese. I got to stop saying that. Wait till I open up Cheesy Pizza. No, wait till I open up. I don't know. What's the name of the restaurant? Slots and Lanes 2. Pizza's here.
Finally, somebody's playing poker. Sit down on the floor. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. Good. All right. I need I need the need to be happy. Need to be a good dealer. So fucking expensive. Everyone's gonna be happy. Staff just make them happy. $15 race for everybody. Everyone needs to be happy. Need to make money. Get this poker out of here. Where's my floor man? Go over here and like investigate everybody. Go stand over here. Nobody's even playing over here. You fucking dope. Why would you go? You're a pit boss. No one's playing at the other terminals. Just hang out here.
He's sitting here observing. It's like hmm. I wonder what's going on to the blackjack table where no one is sitting. Investigate. Here we go. There's Daphna. Daphna Weedman. Investigate. $19,000. Where was the $20k again? The advertising is working. Leaving.
An attraction has been damaged. Clear. An attraction has been damaged. Who is damaging? Lopet8. Oh shit, a biker fight. Who's gonna win? Trailer trash biker or trailer? Oh, jumpsuit trailer trash.
Whatever. We have really cheap ads and Bernice has to stay. Because Bernice is about to go play money into this machine.
An attraction has been damaged. Who the fuck is doing this? Is it her? Wait, are you doing this? Is Bernice destroying stuff? Hold on. Go check on Bernice. She's beating people up and stuff.
An attraction has been damaged. Oh yeah, it's her. Oh yeah. Yeah, she's fucking shit up. Get her out of here. No, you know what? Send a message. You're not sitting down. Get the fuck up. Time to send a message.
We need to fix these. They're all broken. No, don't leave for the crypt casino. No, I don't hear the crypt casino has rats. Oh, okay, the cheats are there. This is how we're gonna make the money. He's a four star cheat.
They're all here. One of them, who cares if one gets caught? As long as some of them make money. I don't care. They're all at the toy blocks. It's fine. Nobody's getting beat up there. Let's go back to my hotel.
Good. Yeah. In midst of working for the Royal Stage Productions as a troublemaker. Get the fuck out of here. Royal Stage? Wait, that was like a movie theater? That wasn't even a casino. That's not a casino. It's a local movie theater.
I'm losing money because of the whole... Wait, you're already getting ejected. Look, it's real easy to run a casino and have a bunch of fun, cool things going on, but nobody's fucking here either.
February. And nobody here. It's a slow season. Why is he unconscious? What happened? He got to the table. He was very dehydrated. He walked all across town and didn't eat or drink anything. Is he drunk? No, he's not drunk. I hope he's not drunk. He's the only people that can make us any money besides the porn theater.
Wait, somebody attacked him? I made $3,000.
Alright. Can you... Oh, this guy sucks. Alright, sit at this table and cheat. Cheat. Do what you're supposed to be doing. Here we go. 600 bucks. Increase his limit. Sit back over there. Sit back over there. There's no floor man over here. Get over here. Where are you? Okay, you're over here.
Be a distraction. 750, good. Get out of here. That's not a floor man, that's a host. Where is their floor man? This is important. They don't even have one down here. This is going to work out so well. Oh my god, they must have fired him for some reason. He's not even down here. I'm going to make $50,000. Which changes the limit to 20 grand. There's no floor man. This is easy. Just take it all. I'll be able to finally afford Chuck E. Cheese. No, stop saying that. I'll be able to finally afford...
Slots of cheese. Slots of cheese. As I can't wait to afford it. I'm going to increase his limit to $25,000. We have to have this happen. I have to sit here. That's the only way it's going to be working out. He can stay here forever.
Casinos are 24x7, guys. There's no floor man. He can just sit here and clean them out. The guards don't know shit. They don't know anything. There it is. Keep going. Do a fast forward here. I've got to be careful with fast forward because somebody might cause trouble in my casino.
Okay, wait. Another cheat reached their limit. Nice. Bring that back. Guard. Oh, this is a disturbance. I knew it. Garfield Weller has found a disturbance. Garfield, where are you? Garfield, make it happen. Don't let them go upstairs. Are they going upstairs? How are they causing a disturbance? Are they together?
Wait, are you going to sports bet? I mean, at this point, I don't care as long as you're giving me money. Did you pay? Make a big bet over here. That's fine. Yeah, I don't care. I don't give a shit if you're doing a disturbance. You're betting a ton of money over here. Yep, betting. Yeah, I don't care. How's the toy box doing? Act innocent. Act innocent does not mean sit at the table. Where the floor man is. He's still winning. Is he cheating? No, he can't be.
We want a raise. Level five cashier. Fine. Where's the floor man going? Over here. Just act. Just hang on and play at that table. That's fine. You can stay there for as long as you want. How are we doing? 23,000. Technician is still doing alright. Where are you going? I think she's just harassing everybody.
Alright, just get rid of her. She already paid, right? Yeah, she already paid. Get her out. Let's go back to the cheating casino. Are you going up there, right? Go get her. Thank you. Go get her.
Point theater doing good? I just put like three here. Ow, I did it again. Wait. What are you looking at? Get out of here. What happened? I just dropped her. Oh god. Well, when she gets up, we'll get rid of her.
Firefighter has been called to the cafe. Okay, maybe they'll come here. When she gets, eject her when she gets up. Get out. You are no longer allowed in this establishment. Leave. Leave! Good. Okay, back to the cheater.
Okay, where is he? Right there. Back to cheating. Acting normal. He's acting normal. Here we go. God damn it. There's a floor man here. How do we get rid of the floor man? Alright, we got rid of the floor man. Where's he going? Go up in the elevator.
Good. A thousand bucks. Alright, they're cheating. No, no. Wrong guy. Stop, stop, stop, stop, stop. Don't. No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no. Don't. This guy's a high roller. Why? Why? No, leave him alone. You don't have to do that. Stop. Leave him alone. Leave him alone. Tell him he's fine. Tell him he's fine. He's fine. Don't go down and beat this guy up. He didn't do anything wrong. Stop. Stop, stop. Just go over here. He's fine. Leave him alone.
My reputation. I know he's a technology, techno high roller and he's pissed. Sit back down at this table, sir. I'm sorry for the apologies. There we go. Order something on the dinner menu. May I recommend the filet mignon? Just kidding. Detective Curly is dead.
Alright, cheat. Just go home. Just go home. Just come home. You have thirty one hundred bucks. Just get out. Just come home. Okay, good. Good. Send him home. Come home. Come home. Gary, come home. Gary. How's this doing so far? I need more. It's alright. It's doing okay. Two hundred seventy five dollars a day. The teens just come up and play bowling. Alright, we're going to move the bowling to the other arcade. I'm slowly climbing. Just don't hurt anybody. People are playing at poker.
Everyone loves the poker tables. They're the best in the city. They really like this dealer. You're so expensive though. My God. She's expensive but she's keeping everybody at this table. You on the other hand, nobody is playing for more than five seconds. Check this guy out.
The best poker in town. Slots in lane. That's right. Slamming. Well, sorry. Let me correct you there. It's slamming slots in lane. You need to Garfield her. Alright, we're going to have to. I'm going to have to do something here. We're going to have to do something. Just hold on. I have to change something. We're pretty dire right now. We need customers. So we need customers. Just don't serve me. Oh no. Another fire. Add pasta Italiano.
Can you imagine? There's five chefs. I would never eat at this restaurant. Can you imagine eating at pasta Italiano when there's a fire once every four days? This shit better be almost free to eat here. This guy's still cooking. Wait a minute. Why are you still cooking? I've got to taste the soup. No, it's not ready. Another few minutes.
Nate, you got to get out of here. No, no, it's been simmering for 24 hours. Okay, fine. 26,000 turning up the heat, turning up the heat. Fire done. That's kind of very low brain way to say that. Fire done. Hotel. Look at this. Hotels. I should just do only hotels. $20,000 in profit. Are you kidding me? I should have just done
your cheat just got back with some loot. Nice. 29,000. Why should why did I make a second floor for the casino? Why did I make this hotel? What the fuck is wrong with me? I'm not losing money. I'm up to 30,000. All right, here is the here's the moron play. The moron play is to just turn floor two into a hotel, right? Just get rid of all this shit and turn floor two into a hotel. That means we lose porn theater, but we might need to. Well, guys,
when I get my third property, we'll eventually just make a porn house. We'll just make like a pornographic building. There's like two porn theaters. There's like a porn show. I can separate it here. Okay, time for renovations. Sports betting does make a lot of profit, though. I'm going to move this downstairs. It was a good spot for it. Sports betting does really, really, really well. Right here. Right in this corner. Get rid of the lava lamp. Sports betting is going in the corner. Save it. Good idea.
Making moves. All your profit is from the second floor. Yeah, but if I if I have another hotel and I can make this potentially a two star hotel on top of the one star hotel, which that's I mean, I that's kind of a dumb idea. But just have five floors and have floor two be one, two and then three and then four star hotel. I mean, yeah, they all have to go in the same elevator. But who the fuck cares? You don't have to go on the top floor. Like, are you really going to be
I guess like the guy that's been spent $500 a room that's in like the business suit on on some business trip is and is it going to be bad that there's like free crack heads in the elevator with them for the room that's like $25 a night? Probably.
Oh, fuck that guy. Who cares? I'm making money. Let's go.
Fuck whatever. OK, here we go. It's $30,000, but I don't need it. We're going to move the sports betting. You saw where I was going to do. We're going to sell this lava lamp. It's there for no reason. And let's move the sports betting downstairs. Perfect. OK, it is now downstairs. Sports betting is now in the corner. Now let's go back up here. You have a job downstairs. That's right. We're going to get rid of the bowling alley, wait for her to pay and I'll let her
play for a one fucking ball. Thanks for coming, Sally. You are now fired. I'm sorry. I'm really sorry. We'll let the point. Well, OK, we'll let the porn theater run for like in a few minutes because these people are going to stay in here.
Sally, Lili. Wait, can Sally Lili do anything downstairs? What's available downstairs for Sally? Anything? Can we give Sally a job somehow? What's a job that Sally can do? I don't have one at the porn hotel. Keep the porn theater. I have no room for it.
It can't go up here. It's too big. What am I supposed to put the porn theater? Should I get rid of roulette? Get rid of OK. Should I get rid of unprofitable blackjack and put porn theater over here?
No one's going to, but people aren't going to even want to go there. I'll try it. No, that's so awful. Fine. OK, I'm going to go right here. In fact, we're going to move these slots. OK, wait till she spends all of her money.
Where can I put it? The porn theater. I don't want to move it yet. They're still watching. This is remember this is like this. It's twenty five dollars per movie and the movies have 10 seconds long. This is seventy five dollars a minute. I gotta wait till this is empty. All right, let's get a janitor up here to clean this shit up because I mean, look at this. This is a mess. Travis, you're doing a very good job, Travis. Can I say Travis is three dollars because Travis has never complained about any money or anything. All Travis has done is just do a good fucking job. All right, let them stay in here for a minute and then we're going to get OK.
All these chairs. I'm getting there. I'm getting the forty four. I didn't do anything drastic. I'm just going to make another hotel. All right. We're clearing out. All right. You two. You're going to have to leave. I'm going to move the movie theater downstairs. Get out. Can I clean this? Could we like spray the floor with a hose? It's the end of the day. We need to like spray this whole thing down with a hose. All right. So that has to move over here. I put it into storage. I got to store this for now. Clean this all up. Get this guy out of here. I'm going to make this. I'm going to make this a another one star hotel.
Or a two star hotel. I made twelve thousand in profit. Doing good. A two star. Can I afford a two star hotel? All right. I don't want to. Let's move the roulette table over here. You can sit down. No, you don't. OK, move the roulette table. We need to make room for the porn theater and just move this right here. Right there. Right there. Right there. Right there is all right. OK. And then we move these and we should have enough room. Get these in this corner. Nice.
Wait till he's done. OK, I got all day. This lack of symmetry. Symmetricity is pitiful. This is temporary until I get everything done. Don't you understand? I was going to sell the porn theater, not move it downstairs.
Convention. A hippie convention will start soon. All right. Get off. Let's go into storage. Movie theater. This is so bad. Like right here. But that like sucks. Oh, that's so ugly.
Move the slots. Maybe I should just sell those slots and put it over here. It's got to go. It's got to go like in that in the corner like this or like this. Right. It has to put a wall around it.
These aren't making any money. Just get rid of them. It's going in this corner. There we go. Like that. There. Let's make it 20 bucks a movie.
And we need a cashier with this review of the sports betting. You are not. Come here. You now work there. Oh, there was a spot for her. Look where she sat. Look, Sally Delaney. She does have a job. That's good. OK, let's start running that movie theater again. Back to upstairs.
I want to move these. They're ugly and in the way. Plus, I don't want this in a way where people can like watch that. I could also want to put I should put a wall right here, too, like a right with the beanbag chairs in front of the bar.
Imagine that to sit there and just to have a for. All right, let's go to the third second floor. All trash has been removed.
Scratch that. We've got to remove one more person upstairs and eject this hooker and then I'm converting this to a hotel. See how expensive this would be. All right. Get him out of here, please. Just do a bunch of movie theaters. No, there's not enough people at the forty four thousand first. How much does this cost? Just do it first.
We have a very important decision I need to make. Garfield, come on, really? He just walked right by you. You were in the same elevator. It's starting to fill up.
Eject and then eject her, too. I think she's leaving, but no, she's not. Eject. Get out. Leave. The janitor's not really doing a whole lot, but it's OK. Go empty that trash can. It's 52 percent full.
I need, like, a place to sit on, too. I'm going to put, like, a table, a couch or something. How are people going to eat? This is doing pretty well.
Travis needs a break. He is doing it. He is on a break. He's on an almost permanent break right now. Where are my cheats? How happy is everybody there? Everyone all right?
You guys could use a little bit of a bonus. How about 10 bucks? How about 136 dollars a day?
We have a puke. How are the drinks doing? Good. We're starting to fill up. People are starting to actually remember that we were the cheaper, nicer, more porn-filled casino than any other casino in the area.
They're starting to remember now. He's losing a lot of money. More throwing up. OK, why? What's the food? Holy shit! How is charging 8 dollars for a 1 dollar hamburger?
Oh my god! OK, that's why. How are the drinks? The drinks are OK, right? Charge a little more for that, please.
Stadium food prices. Yeah, I know. Are people using this? Yeah, kind of.
All right, banking high roller. Go play roulette. I wish I could sit down and play. I wish I could sit down and play at my own casino with my money. Check him out.
44. All right. No, I lost it. How do I lose a thousand dollars? Someone's cheating somewhere. Where am I losing this much money? 42,000. OK. No, I think somebody's hit a jackpot. That's all. Yeah, somebody hit a jackpot. We're good.
OK, good. I did it and I didn't have to do anything crazy. Let's fast forward a little bit. Shit. I went down. OK, good. That high roller is a cheat.
Is he cheating? He's being watched by the floorman. I don't think he's cheating. Take a look. Watch this, please. Are you sure? No, no. He's spent a thousand dollars. He got a thousand dollars back, I guess.
I don't think he's cheating. We're bumping again. This is good. This is good news. No floors for people to come mess up. I'm going to drop the price here to 50 bucks. No, 45. 45 dollars a room. Let's fill every one of these rooms.
I'm out of ads. I'm completely out of ads. Stay up over 45, please. 23 hours. We'll be fine. Here comes the convention. What are hippies like?
Hippies like expensive drinks or cheap drinks? Cheap drinks. Cheap drinks and cheap food, right? What are they like for betting frequency? Jackpot frequency medium. Let's change all of our machines to medium.
Medium, jackpot, low. Let's go nuts here. Return percentage low. There's a big convention in town. Actually, I'll keep these the way they are.
20 more hours. Stay above 46. Come on. I almost forgot to say that one. I forgot to say that part. Why is there a commissioner by the front door? This is the doorman. He doesn't do anything right now, actually. He does nothing.
In fact, I'm not sure why he's still on payroll. Because he's supposed to block certain people from coming in. And I have allowed teenagers into the casino. So he's just a guy that stands.
19 hours. Here we go. 47. Where's the hippies? Here they are. Here they go. All right. We need extra staff. We need staff on duty and on guard at all times here.
We're about to give hippies really cheap drinks and cheap food. They're all checking in.
Mr. Janitor? Is that Puke? This table is making a lot of money. We'll get the other one. It's right next to it.
Here comes the Puke casino. Wait, hey. Wait a minute. They all checking into my hotel because it's the cheapest hotel and then leaving to go to the other casino.
Uh, well. All right. Then I have to. That's fine with me. I'll be the hotel. I'll be the hotel. That's okay. All right. More people coming in.
Porn theatre is not doing. Wait. What are hippies like? Hippies love porn, don't they? Make it cheaper. I knew it. That's why you're here. Get ready.
Get ready. You might as well puke into his dustpan. Come here. Come here. Come here. Come here. What are you doing?
Just puke right into his dustpan. All right. Cheap porn incoming. $12. You've done that. I can tell. You think I've puked into a dustpan.
It would just go everywhere. You wouldn't even be able to do that. I got a lot of money. Look at how much we've turned this around.
Uh oh. Uh, ma'am, you can't come back here. And that's for staff only. Evicted. And evict this guy too. Eject. Look at this old lady.
Trudy Coffee. Oh, good old Trudy Coffee. I love Trudy Coffee. What a great name. No, stay. Well, $5,000 in income. $5,000 in profit. That's good.
Trudy Cheetos. Well, should I throw them out? Maybe I shouldn't throw them out. Because they're going to just spend a bunch of money.
Uh oh. Ever since I threw away the two belligerent drunk people, I lost $2,000.
All right. Two more hours. One, two, and that's it. Did it.
Remember how I did this last night? I sold every single thing in the casino.
All right. I now have two hitmen. Our rivals are shaken up. We need to purchase real estate. That's my new objective is to buy real estate.
Save the game here. I got $50,000. I'm in the green. Things are going well. I can either make a hotel on top of here.
I could do a five-star hotel right here. That's $225 a night. That's $15,000. I'm going for it. $225 a night. Five-star hotel. Look at how nice this is.
And there's a bathroom in here. These ones don't even have bathrooms. That's pretty good. These ones are worse than prison cells.
It's just a bed and a bunch of walls.
All right. Just wait for the money to start rolling in. $225 a night.
In fact, it's our inaugural opening. Make it $205. Open a new casino. Here we go. How much money is it? What do we have available?
Okay. We can go Wasteland Manhattan Road. Wasteland Boston Road. Oh, these are all, this is all like, this is bad. This is all like out in the middle of nowhere.
Quick stop motel. Quick stop motels. And I'm going to put a Chuck E. Cheese over here. It's $30,000. What else do we got?
Red light. Should I put a Chuck E. Cheese style to kid's restaurant next to a red light brothel? Oh, yikes, as they say.
No, it's got to be, what about, look it, this is a nice place. No one's going to go there. Parents will drop them off and then go there.
That's not how that works. Well, I can't, I'm not going to do it yet. I don't want to be completely in the, I don't want to be completely in the, I want money.
All right. We got out of two hotels. The casino's here. Who wants money? The doorman does. I mean the doorman that hasn't had to do any work.
Actually has not had to do anything. You don't have to even do anything. See you later. That frees up some money that I can pay everybody else.
What do I even need a doorman for? I'm not blocking anybody from doing anything. Everybody can get a $5 raise now that he's gone.
What, are you, ma'am, leave the staff alone, please. Leave the staff alone. What, do you want to work here?
Okay. Here's the third cashier. Mimi Stemmer. Okay, yes. We're going to get you that new trailer. Come on. Yes, yes, you do.
The convention has now finished. I don't think that guy's real. Hold on a second. Hold on a second. Put it in slow motion for a second.
I need a new trailer.
The visitor you just beat up denied it.
Holy shit, she's still going. No, get it. She's going to stop.
I'd like to talk to.
Stop it.
I need a new trailer.
No, come here.
Get in there and stop being so fucked up. Oh my God. Just get her in here.
One moment.
Wait, what? Are they fighting each other?
Why are they fighting each other?
Why is he hitting him in the face?
The visitor you just beat up denied it.
What the fuck is going on?
Oh my God. Just get rid of her.
Hold on, what?
Staff are asking for a raise.
Okay, fire somebody.
I need a new trailer.
Why are they still doing this?
No, no, no, no, no.
No, we can't. I can't.
I can't.
I crashed the game. Fuck.
I need a new trailer.
This ain't no firecracker.
Father, the visitor is on fire.
Excuse me.
No, that's not the right image.
Oh God.
Where's the image of me standing?
I saved over it. Where is it?
I'm not having Bernie Pog.
Okay, hold on. No.
Oh, this one's disgusting.
No, no, this one's, I don't like this one.
I don't want this on the screen for more than like three hours.
No, no, no, no, no.
No, this one's fucking horrible.
This is horrible.
It actually is terrible to look at.
That hurts to look at.
All right, here we go.
This is only going to stay on for like 20 minutes.
That's the wrong one.
Now I have to fire all these bouncers that I hired for no reason.
Yeah, hold on. Is this the right one?
They're all fucking gross.
All right, it didn't crash.
Good. All right.
Now I have to fire these guys and stop this.
Just get out of the way.
They're going to do this one more time.
I made five grand a day.
All right, just let her go back upstairs.
Just move out of the way.
I need to fire this.
No, no, this guy's one of my best bouncers.
These two have new hires.
I just hired them to beat up some lady.
Who's just the one that got hit in the face with a wrench?
Where's my second hitman?
There he is.
Okay, we don't need these yet.
All right, both of you stop this nonsense.
All right, Malvin.
He's doing this on his own.
All right, now go back upstairs.
No, you both fired.
This guy here, you're fired.
And this bouncer right here, you're also fired.
Oh shit.
Okay, now everybody, wait, wait, wait.
Money, money, money, money.
Look, money, look, money.
Look, look, look, look, look, money.
This dealer is almost, this dealer is going to make more than money than I will.
Why are you still down here beating up this lady?
Are you seriously still beating up this lady down here?
Tell her to leave.
Okay, 39,000.
How's the hotel doing?
Nobody is here.
Not one person.
Staff are asking for a raise.
You're gone.
Imagine seriously continuing to ask for this much money, but this table makes $21,000.
How much does this table make?
Okay, she's a five-star dealer.
She makes $367 a day.
This table takes in like $2,500 a day.
I've got to keep her around.
Does people come here for this dealer?
There's a good dealer.
$50 bonus, and that's enough.
I can't believe I just gave you $50 and you don't even care.
Holy shit, how much fucking money do you guys want?
Everybody wants a raise.
All of you want a raise.
Staff are asking for a raise.
Don't give weak bonuses.
That was a $50 bonus.
All right, I got 41 grand.
This needs to start taking in customers.
This shit's not taking in any customers.
All right, I think I'm ready.
This is generating enough money.
Ban the trailer trash.
Ban trailer trash, and then people will use it.
But that's my number one customer base.
I should convert the one up.
I shouldn't have done a five-star.
I should have done the one-star.
Promo.
I need more porn theaters.
I'm doing pretty well.
I'm making actually pretty decent profit right now.
Look, this theater's doing so good.
These old people in trailer trash are my number one.
All right, I think it's time for me to buy a property.
Or should I wait till like $60,000?
Well, clean it up.
Buy a brothel.
Get a brothel.
Buns Burger Bar.
So how does this work?
So there are 12 hookers in the Crypt Casino right now.
That's $4,000 to do this.
That's a ton of money.
I can minus take one away from there.
Where's my casino?
Slamming slots and lanes.
All right, I can either have more hookers come here.
Or get rid of them.
Send them to Pasta Italiano.
Should I just send like ten prostitutes to Pasta Italiano?
Well, that place is going to be a mess.
It burns down every other day.
And it's just all prostitutes.
What does that even do for me?
Send the hitmen to Pasta Italiano?
For what?
Why would I?
Why am I trying to destroy their business?
Send hitmen to Pasta Italiano?
Why would I do that?
What's the point of sending him to Pasta Italiano?
What the fuck?
Okay, go to Pasta Italiano.
Is this a mob movie?
I don't understand.
Where should we send him?
We'll send him there.
He eats lunch every day.
We all eat lunch every day.
But he specifically eats it.
Pasta fucking Italiano.
Wait, what? He spotted a cheater.
That's Trump?
All right, it's one step removed from Trump.
Fine.
Here's Trump.
You know, it's me, Donald.
It's me, Donald Trump.
And then this is me, Donald the Donald the Don.
It's one small degree of separation.
You know, the fucking guy.
Get him. It's me, Don.
All right, it's true.
Fine, whatever.
Wait, he arrived at Pasta Italiano.
What's he doing here?
Okay, he's in Pasta Italiano.
For what reason?
What's his purpose of being in Pasta Italiano?
Why would I do this?
Why would he do something like this?
No!
I don't want to do that.
This is not like a mob movie.
I know there's a fight.
Okay, Henrietta.
She's putting the cigarette on his face.
Oh, she's a cheater.
She's a cheater.
Get rid of her.
Nice work.
She's out.
Hey, don't put a bomb in the spaghetti.
I can't.
Can't?
I can't even go in here.
Save the game?
Hold on.
Hey, Jimmy the Fish sends his regards.
And the fish family.
Okay, well, that's a rewind.
Why am I here?
Why can I do this?
Why would I ever come into the Pasta Italiano?
After a wage war?
On what?
What's the?
What am I doing?
Who owns this place?
This is a competitor?
I got a better idea.
We're going to keep Frankie the Fish here.
So I can...
There's an Elvis convention coming in.
We're going to keep Frankie the Fish here.
Because I'm not going to have to do anything.
I will make a casino bet with you here.
I don't have to do anything.
That within the next 20 minutes,
this place will be on fucking fire.
And these people will all be dead.
And I won't have to do anything.
In fact, let's just test this theory.
Let's see how long it takes
for Pasta Italiano to catch fire
a seventh or eighth time.
Wait.
There's a lot of chefs in here.
Really?
Hold on.
We'll go back.
Nightspot is out of business.
Good.
I'm still here.
Oh my God.
Just hold on.
Two days.
It's been two days.
On the third day.
He's just standing here.
It's going to happen.
This place catches fire fucking twice a week.
What the fuck guys?
Just to shut you up.
I need a new trailer.
How many people are in there?
This place is getting overrun.
Oh my God.
It's getting overrun.
Is this why?
They want to...
Wait a minute.
What's happening in my casino?
The people at Garfield are going to quit.
What?
Wait.
Wait to stay.
Oh my God.
They're everywhere.
Come on.
Do it already.
I want to drop a match.
I have $62,000, man.
Alright.
One more day.
And then I will admit defeat.
And a clown convention starts in a couple of days.
Perfect timing.
Yes.
I didn't have to do shit.
No.
I'm not going to bomb now.
I told you.
These fucking idiots.
We're going to light this place on fire in a few days.
I told you.
He's burnt me.
You just burnt me.
Who's this guy?
Police are going to an opponent's place.
Oh shit.
No.
Leave.
Leave the building quick.
You're going to be dying.
Oh, you fucked up.
There was this police out here.
But I didn't even do anything.
I didn't do anything.
I got the thing burnt, the place down.
The lady lit me on fire.
So I raised my firearm in self-defense
when the lady is doing it on purpose trying to kill me.
And then I get shot by that guy.
I knew it.
I told you it was going to happen.
These guys suck.
Reset it.
Who do I have left?
Oh, I still have one.
I'm good.
I got Otis.
Otis is good to go.
I don't need to correct the timeline.
I got $62,000.
I need a new trailer.
All right.
We're good.
I got tons of fucking money.
We can buy a new property.
All right.
Let's make the Chuck E. Cheese.
Stop saying Chuck E. Cheese.
It's not what that is.
Slamming slots to extra lanes.
I don't know.
What was it called?
Slots of cheese.
All right.
This is still generating fucking cash.
Good.
Look at this.
All I had to do.
Drop the price even more.
$195.
Where are the clowns?
I told you this shit was going to burn.
I didn't think it was going to happen.
Let's have these people go cheat.
Toy Box Casino.
Looking for two grand from each one of you.
Go to the Crip Casino.
Two grand from both of you.
Is that $1,500?
I made $624.
Yes.
I know.
I think somebody's cheating.
Who's cheating?
Somebody has to be, right?
Did I get big bits?
Oh shit.
My thing is fucked up.
Hold on.
I'm going to make a new save here.
This is going to be called After Fish.
Crash?
Don't crash.
I'm good.
I don't think it crashed.
We had two very, very, very big bit donations.
We had one $69 bit donation.
6900 bits from Vilemi.
Thanks for the 69 fucking dollars.
That's a lot of money.
Nice.
Yeah, okay.
Jeremy, why would you send an arsonist to burn down Vinny's restaurant?
That wasn't Vinny's restaurant.
What are you talking about?
That was Pasta Italiano.
That place just sucks.
I don't have to do anything.
They'll just destroy themselves.
I can't believe he died.
It's all right.
The timeline has to stay the same.
That's not even Vinny's restaurant.
What are you talking about?
That's not Vinny's restaurant.
What does that mean?
I don't even know what that means.
He literally doesn't know Vinny.
What?
It's the Vinesauce restaurant.
Yeah, I know who Vinny is, but you think I just don't know who that is?
Who's Vinny?
Who are you talking about?
Vinny?
Vinny like Vinny the Cheese?
Frankie the Fish?
What do you mean?
Yeah, mob movies.
Vinny the Pasta Italiano.
That's not what it is.
Anyways, thanks for the 6,900 bits.
That's a lot of money.
And then Phylacter Lich gave 5,000 bits too.
Another 50 dollars.
Germa, you should really send your Hitman to the Crypt Casino.
It's your biggest competition.
Also, shout out to the pre-stream chat.
We all have one thing in common.
An unhealthy desire to see Germa stream.
I have an unhealthy desire to stream.
That works.
Thanks for the 50 dollars.
A thousand times.
And then Lime Liquors, thanks for the 5 community subs.
That was earlier, but thanks guys.
Thanks for the 120 dollars.
150 dollars almost.
Thanks guys, seriously.
Thank you.
Who's cheating?
Where are we losing the money from?
Why is this place empty right now?
No, it's not.
You're overpaying staff.
Yeah, you're right.
Fuck.
Oh, you make 600 dollars a day.
It's time for you to go.
Time to go.
Fire.
Cashier, you're fired.
Our staff level 4, you're fired.
Who else is making way too much money?
This Janet is making, I know Travis.
Travis, you make too much money.
Travis, you're fired.
Burek, you're fired.
I know, I know, I know.
I gotta free up some money here, guys.
Who are you?
You're a level 1 dealer and you want 180 bucks fired.
Level 1 Floor Man and you want 72 dollars fired.
Level 4 Bounce are 160.
Alright, I'll give you 175.
I'll give you 200.
I'll give you 180.
This dealer, level 1 dealer, wants 3 times the city average.
You're fired.
Bar staff, want twice the city average, you're fired.
Server, you want 3 times city average, you're fired.
You have 1 guard?
Wait, that's Garfield.
Yeah, Garfield, you can stay.
This level 4 bouncer though, let's make you happy.
I'll give you 215.
Bounce events is starting.
Alright, now let's get some new staff in here.
New staff, we need a poker dealer.
We gotta get people here now.
Level 4, it gets to be a little too late.
Level 5, you're 220 dollars.
That's good.
Good starting.
Are you a poker player?
Good, right here, roulette.
And then we need some bar staff.
That's good, we have roulette.
We need a server over here.
We need some bar staff.
Level 3 bar staff is fine, and a level 2 is fine.
You guys can both get to work.
Here come the clown.
I thought that guy was a clown for a second.
Look, it's that easy.
I need a cashier.
Level 1 cashier.
You just keep doing movie tickets.
That's running now, we got one over here.
Here come the clowns.
Get the fuck out of here.
All the rooms are almost occupied up here.
Getting some good occupancy here.
There's a clown.
8200, that's a lot so far.
This one's been here the whole time.
That's not bad.
Now we need a floor manager.
Mr. Ransom.
Be our floor manager, please.
And now we're not bleeding money through staff anymore.
Where's the janitor?
I fired the janitor, right?
Level 4 janitor, that's pretty good.
Actually, we don't even need a level 4 janitor.
There's no trash.
Nice.
What are the burgers?
There's a convention in town, let's overprice everything.
Brinks as well.
Let's go open our Chuck E. Cheese.
Stop saying
that name.
It's not...
It's fucking
slots of cheese.
Anyways, let's go.
Time to buy...
This is too much.
30,000.
The wasteland.
I can't afford anywhere else.
This is not bad.
I can buy the gym and turn it into a Chuck E. Cheese.
I can buy the bookstore and turn it into a Chuck E. Cheese.
Buy the pawn shop.
The cupcake bakery.
Frankie's Fish.
I'm eventually going to have to own that.
How about right here?
The bookstore.
That's a prime location right here.
Go buy Pasta Italiano.
Where even is Pasta Italiano?
Right there.
Can I buy Pasta Italiano?
I definitely can buy Pasta Italiano.
Where is it?
No, I can't buy Pasta Italiano.
Alright, I'm going to buy this one here.
The bookstore.
Candy store or bookstore?
Drug store?
No, this isn't a much better location.
The candy store is right next to the toy box.
That's competition.
I don't have that money.
No, I'm doing the bookstore.
I'm bidding $31,000 for it right now.
You good?
Just open up a Spite store next to Pasta Italiano.
What is this?
It's an auction.
I'm the highest bidder.
Oh, it has to take a day or two.
No one is going to outbid me for the bookstore.
Make Pasta Italiano go bankrupt and then buy it.
Well, that's never going to happen.
Considering Pasta Italiano has
burnt down ten times and rebuilt
100% every time.
Whoever owns Pasta Italiano
has hundreds of billions of dollars
in money to spend.
It doesn't matter what happens.
I want to make my arcade.
Got it.
And
I got it for free.
I just got $30,000 for doing that.
Wheel of Fortune has been unlocked.
And I can get a large sport betting bar now.
You must control the majority of
Fortune Falls gambling.
I need 45% market share.
Holy shit.
Alright, I got another.
Here we go.
Colston's Bookstore.
That's ugly.
Firefighters have been called to the toy box.
Your cheat brought home $1,500.
Clams.
One floor.
I made $935.
Alright, here we go.
Arcade machine.
Endball machine.
Pool tables. Big bowling alley.
Small dance floor.
This is going to be a fun place for kids.
Arcade machines.
Row. And then another row.
Make this the porn house instead?
The title of the stream is Chuck E. Cheese.
I'll buy another property
and make it a porn house.
Arcade machines. Line in the front door.
When you walk into Slam and Slot's
cheesy style,
you are met with an incredible array
of old classic video games.
Take a step by.
Line. That's a line.
And see the...
E. Cheese.
It's got to be like...
I can't wait.
Let me do the thing I want to do.
The competition just bought
another property. Who did?
They just bought the Slam and Drinks bar.
Oh, fuck off. What do I have in storage?
Oh, cool.
No. I don't know how
I want to do this.
Somebody said, what is happening here?
I don't know. I don't know how I want to do the
layout. I'm going to store these.
Okay, I want... What's the big attraction in here?
It's obviously... It's obviously
the bowling alleys. Yeah.
This is... Shuuuuuuuuuuuuut
uuuuup.
Bowling alley. Walls first.
Walls first. I don't have any walls. Oh, make
walls, you mean. Okay.
Large wall. So you come on
in the front door and you're met with
the first line.
Run! Just run!
Oh, no. He's going to...
He's going to get beat up.
Walls are a waste.
Whatever. He's going to get his ass kicked and he's going to fucking turn.
Whatever. Who cares?
Alright, let's go to uh...
Oh, here it is.
Your cheat has changed sides.
Alright, so let's do a wall coming in.
You walk in the front door and you're greeted
with...
Why am I... Oh my god.
That's... Free striking route.
This is changing as soon as possible.
I'm thinking like arcade machines lining
both walls. Yeah.
That would be sick.
It's just machines. Machines.
God damn it. I can't do that. I need so much
space. Fuck does anything look like?
You know what I mean?
Anybody else have trouble doing this shit? Like,
what does anything even look like?
If I walked into a store or I walked into
an arcade or something, it's like, oh, this is what it looks like.
Looking at it from the top without
anything there. I don't...
How the fuck does any of this shit even make any sense?
I don't even know how this makes... I don't even know how this
works. Like, I don't even
know. Oh, fuck my game.
Okay, maybe separate it a little more?
Like this. It's gonna just be like
fucking toilets back here. Who cares?
No, this doesn't even make any sense.
What the fuck does anything even look like from above?
What does anything even
look like? Like, I
couldn't explain to you what a arcade...
It's just like machines
everywhere. There's no, like, walls.
It's like this. There'll be like a wall
in the middle to separate, like,
one thing. Like, there'll be machines over here
and then there'll be like machines over here and like a
fucking skeeball. The walls are usually made
out of arcade machines. Yeah.
Well, this will be the restaurant side.
Yeah, this is like where you get your pizza and your fucking
fruit snacks and shit and this is the arcade over here.
Yeah, that makes sense.
I get it. Just look up a reference.
One would look up a Chuck E. Cheese
blueprint. Okay.
Chuck E. Cheese floor plan.
What do these even look like? Okay,
here we go. Alright, how does this work?
We'll see what this looks like.
There's a Chuck E. Cheese...
There's a floor plan for how...
Alright, let's see. Let's see what this looks like.
I feel like this is
impossible.
What are you doing? You'll suffer,
Jeremy, with, like, you just, like,
scribbled on a piece of paper.
Let me open this. Does anybody
else fucking hate Windows 10?
You know when, like, you have a
file on your computer
and you go to, like, the
home screen and you type in the search bar
but you know the
title of the image or the title
of a video or something that you have on your computer
and the search bar is just like, I have no fucking idea
what the hell you're talking about. That doesn't
exist on your whole computer.
Who made this and why is it so bad?
Like, that's the title of this thing.
Why is... I can't get mad.
What am I going to do?
Alright, there it is.
Is my computer crashing? Don't even crash. You better not.
Okay.
This isn't even a floor plan.
This is, like, a view
of the... I knew
this was fucked up. This is
of, like, a strip mall and Chuck E. Cheese
is one of the squares here. No.
No. That's, like, a place.
That's, like, a specific Chuck E. Cheese
and specific business.
Oh, no. I don't want... I'm not showing that.
Where is it? Just a floor plan of
arcade floor plan.
Here we go. You got one?
Is this a SpongeBob thing? I see...
Sponge in here. Backstage.
Freddy Fazbear. What is it?
Okay. Freddy's dining hall.
Okay. Let's see.
So, pirate, pirate.
Break room. Alright.
So, boss. Ladies are...
Freddy's... This dining hall is in the middle.
So there's two walls.
I'll use this as a reference for a little bit.
Freddy's Fazbear. Is this like a...
Five Nights at Freddy's, like, fan
plot? Or is this, like, the actual...
This is the...
Okay, this is just a plot.
This is just the Five Nights at Freddy's security
images that you go to.
Right. This is like somebody made
a fan one. Okay.
Well, I'm gonna use it, because it's what I have.
So we got the backstage area, but that's the
elevator, so we can't really do much there.
Okay. Arcade.
The dining hall is here.
I can't even... I don't even know what this looks like. I can't even do it.
Break room. Okay. There's a break room
up here. Okay. Break room.
Pirate cove. So there'll be
a pirate cove.
Supply closet.
Okay, so supply closet,
janitor. And then this is the break room.
And then pirate's cove
goes out this way. So this is pirate's cove.
Which then goes like this.
Feels like little tabs.
Okay. And then there's like
a pirate's cove there. And then there's an
arcade this way. This is gonna
have to come up a little more. Okay, that looks
alright. Yeah, that's
alright. And then this goes this
way. I know, I've lost eighty seven
hundred dollars.
You come in.
Free arcade machines.
And then there's the dining hall.
And then over here can be...
Alright, that's actually
okay for now. That's fine.
Alright, that's good for my arcade machines.
Why is this one little? Oh, that's a seat.
Alright, now we need a
movie theater.
No, a dance floor. No, no, no. Where is it? A media...
A stage, right? Cause it's Friday's Fast Burst.
Got it. Alright, small stage.
Oh, you motherfucker. Come on.
Come on.
Just have to move it. Fit in there. Small
stage. Alright.
It does fit right there, but this other side
has to move. And I'll put like trees
over here. Wanna make sure it fits.
Police are going to an opponent's place.
That's what I was saying. Staff are
asking for a raise. Uh huh. Yeah, yeah, yeah, yeah.
Yeah, that's fine.
So fucked up. These walls
are bad, okay?
It's not my fault that these walls suck.
They're so bad.
They don't even make any sense.
This shit doesn't even make any sense.
Let me just get it in there first.
Okay, there we go. Nice. How much was that?
$6,000. That's a lot of money. You wanna
raise? I'll get it somewhere else.
Actually, you know what? You wanna come work here?
Now I can bring this up.
Cause now the thing's actually in here.
There we go. Okay, nice.
I can put some seats in.
Why is there a
clown in here already? Get the fuck out of here.
Hey. It's not even open.
This place doesn't even open.
Is it open? Oh shit.
It's Freddy.
Right, I don't even need this. Put it over here for now.
Alright, will you fuck off?
I'll put, like, plants over here.
Look, you're gonna come in for the show. The show's gonna be $100.
He's gone.
I think that guy was in our imagination.
i don't think the guy was even real why can i not do this it's just it's the
fucking camera angle why can i not do this oh it's because the stupid thing is in the way
same deal arcade machines down here in fact we don't need that many the main attraction is
this thing and we can do three let's do three on each not centered i don't it who cares all right
let's make this a uh small stage yes 50 bucks and we have an adult dancer magicians and circus
we need a circus and the magician circus let's get some good high quality entertainment here
uh adult adult magician and then a singer no majurka and another circus circus magician
magician circus but 50 max pressure what oh that was a person's name okay what about the
arcade machines all right so they're just five dollars well now there's six across the board
six dollars to play one game of pac-man um this is in the future where it is 150 dollars for a
loaf of bread another arcade we can get pinball too this is fucking sick okay oh all right there's
our little arcade place nice we're gonna buy let's get some fruits over here the fruits and
vegetables hanging up plants and you know just to make it look nice uh like you know like something
like this like plants like fucking plants i don't know i don't know what the fuck i'm doing all
right cool you have zero sense of interior design no i don't i don't why would i why would i have
any good interior design i'm a fucking e-clown i didn't go to interior design school to learn how
to be an architect or something no i i do like poses and dance in front of a camera and do like
backflips and fucking juggle and blow up balloons and pop them and stuff and you say look at me
that's right it's important okay uh we have arcades i need some staff because nobody can
do anything here uh wait pinball machines where should those go wait what's let's
what's the book say oh we need the pizzeria yep okay get rid of these walls they're useless uh
self he's not gonna do anything all right so the pizzeria actually you know i'll put a once i'll
get the restaurant at the end of the day all right gonna be a big restaurant medium kitchen
we're gonna have a medium kitchen with like four chefs are going to an opponent's place
like over here and then we'll have a bunch of seating over here this is the pizza restaurant
right there and then a bunch of tables at the restaurant you know we'll put a couple arcade
machines over here how can i put this here dining hall okay it's not centered dining hall
okay that's that's good we'll put a wall here steal the chefs from pasta italiano this game
got a five out of ten this guy just came in and broke a machine and left and threw a soda on the
ground if there was security i've there was somebody i would have shot him if i had a gar
if i had a garfield around here that guy would be dead okay now we need some we need some pin
we'll do no pinball up here yep that would be cool pinball and then candy machine oh right here
it's perfect right next to the kitchen or a secret hidden candy store over behind freddy fazbear it's
not freddy fazbear's pizza and it's not chuck e cheese stop using licensed material in your
unlicensed stream jeremy there's a convention starting soon yeah the little candy store right
behind the fucking thing that the kids are watching good candy store this is look at this is there
look at how cute this place is gonna be pinball machines a couple arcade arcade arcade arcade
let's staff it later so i can thought of exactly what i need pinball oh yeah just a couple you know
wow wow what am i doing and a pool table down here guys this place is fucking awesome
and in case you want to get married no pool table right here and then i can fit a couple
down right right against the wall nice we need we still we need some more arcade machines i'm
taking another small wall one two three one two three or a wall that goes down here i need a new
trailer let's see does that work that works yeah that works check this out we can do another
couple one a couple a little arcade section we'll put something right here too uh is there another
game i can put here like a pinball here maybe another big pool right in the middle no somebody's
cheating at poker let's deal with that first wait the dealer is cheating is what you're saying
what where are my bodyguards do i not have any bodyguards in the whole fucking place
oh shit i fired him off look at this no there's no employees that are left oh ask him a question
he's cheating all right let's go back to the other property pool table a couple more arcade
machines let's get that rolling that's not scratching my brain that's okay we'll put a
plant i'm gonna put a little plant here please something tiny yes pretty good arcade section
pizza restaurant pinball candy we can put some more arcade over here maybe some more pinball
machines staff are asking for a raise all right this one two let's do one two over here how much
space is in middle right like i love it i love this place okay let's staff screen garfield's
about to leave and i will pay whatever garfield wants if i'm honest with you your chief has taken
a beating save the progress okay now this is this one's called arcade arcade continuation
okay now we have to staff it and it'll be open let's get some staff we need a technician
not very many left uh how about we're gonna need a good technician so i'll pay it i'll pay for it
we need at least one we need one janitor we're not gonna need any prostitutes that's
not we don't need those we need uh waiters oh shit there's only there's only three total waiters that
exist uh-oh there's nobody left to take jobs we need to go we need a good friendly cashier
oh i hear the machines turning we also need a few chefs well somebody just two chefs there's no chefs
left that exist okay mr uh mr nicholson and mr nicholson what the brothers okay slots and fun
is open for business come on in anybody that wants to have fun and eat pizza you are
kill this person kill that lady too staff run you have been i'm about to fire these two
if you want more than 20 dollars raise then you're gone i'm trying to make my which you go 12.6
percent i'm still getting some gambling share all right let's go back to sloth cheese and lane
all right we come on in we're open buster cherry is a whoa this is
where i need a doorman i need someone has that establishment for kids we need a bouncer there
are no bouncers they don't exist we're out of the day okay mr schnodgrass mr schnodgrass welcome
aboard and mr christian welcome aboard it's time to and we're gonna do a big ad campaign ad campaign
oh he's leaving for the casino there's no drinks okay well i can put a little drink place over here
for the parents so no soda kiosk for the kids new server mini f but i did my stream die we good
we good okay with soda we you get a triple soda for 10 dollars and then you get a how much candy
did you get a big box of chocolate no how about just little sweets yeah for like five bucks okay
mr doorman let's edit that policy we need this is a place for teens no trailer trash um a few of
the sports fan can we want just a place for kids so seniors and teens so uh okay socialite seniors
and teens no vacationers teens there we are let's make a big ad campaign the delegate there's a
convention that's just started wait a sports convention just started wait they're allowed
in that they can vacation is one of the arcade it's a family place okay hold on all right i'll
open it up i'll open it up open up to seniors teens vacationers and sports fans and delegates
and no socialites okay and socialites too fine all right everybody only sports boys
all right let's fill it up time for an ad campaign here we go um look at this buy up
i'm filling this place ads everywhere fucking everywhere on every street on every corner
you're not going to be able to go anywhere without seeing one of my signs here we go
come on in everybody it's good old family fun oh and the food right it's it's going to be like
french fries pizza and shit it's still going to be 15 bucks though it's like a it's like a
kid's pizza plate look everybody's here watching the magician wait somebody's cheating at the other
casino where's the alert message uh all right who's cheating somebody's cheating who don't see
anybody cheating do you oh the floor plan is still up shit hold on we need buses we need routes
and limos and stuff yep okay that's another issue all right we need buses and shit let's go
route one with another route and this is going to go from slots of cheese and lanes to an attraction
has been damaged i know pasta italiano and then to the bank and then to my other casino let's go
i want this on route three how do i put make it on route three
so you know fuck we'll just buy another one good all right we're good we're good we're good
done now let me go back to floor plan back all right we got so let's look at all these things
going on get some people in here who's causing problems who carolyn chubb is your three thousandth
visitors slamming slots and lanes had three thousand people come in that's crazy uh no one
here how's the hotel doing holy shit this hope wow okay you know what to do back the price up
you just want 230 why are people coming in here and being dicks i don't understand what this guy's
problem is staff are asking for a raise can i have a way you mean you want to oh because you got
yelled at i know all right here we go there's our first kid there's definitely a cheat here oh my
god stop it's the dealer remember when i i already did this i already disciplined this guy and he
said i'm not cheating and he is the spawn still playing in here oh for 12 dollars no no no
where's the janitor who is this oh that's the circus okay um guys this is 50 dollars a ticket
get some candy come on somebody order food leaving for the casino leaving for the casino
leaving for the casino you want a drink god uh yes ma'am will that be one pizza one pizza
coming right up staff are asking for a raise this is the guy that was the guy that was wrongfully
caught cheating fire everyone no not yet i'm i'm not bleeding money i'm gaining money
i need the art how did trailer trash get in here yes all right this is our first kid our first kid
customer welcome to lots and lots of fun i see you're checking out pac-man is free
that's a good one can i tell you about our loyalty program for every five dollars you spend in lots
of slamming lanes you get 10 cents free don't tell your mom and dad about it all you have to
swipe your card put in your birthday your email and then you're gonna get spammed every day
and your phone is never gonna stop ringing off the hook all for you to get 0.2 percent back
when you come here once every three years have a nice day it's the end of the day wages have been
paid arcade machines are pretty popular here comes the circus performer oh wow this place is
making money this place is making money you can't see what i'm doing this place is
oh they're around this place isn't making money it's chasing an old lady around to beat up
it's been six days i just said to hit man over here and shoot him oh no i don't need to he said
he's going down with this ship in pasta italiano hey by the way does anybody else now understand
why there were no chefs on the list of available hires it's because they keep coming to pasta
italiano and dying i have to but wait there's no more available chefs how are you gonna have a
pasta restaurant when every chef is putting his body out that is fucking horrible how do you have
a pot okay how do you have a pasta restaurant where there's no chefs available to buy this place is
about to go on the market and i'm gonna buy it how much is it gonna be worth i'm gonna buy it
it can't be worth more than like 20 or 30 000 turned into porno italiano are you seriously
still here should i go shoot this guy so they have to sell the one remaining chef in psycho
city and then i'm gonna turn this into a pornhall it looks like there's a fight he punched a senior
in the face man now but wait till he gets there check out our other establishment which is doing
pretty well it's doing pretty good let's take a look at the book the real book oh i don't have
any gaming machines hold on damn the stage is making some money where's my hitman okay
all right he's in oh my god look at how many guards they desperately are trying to protect
the last chef in the restaurant it's all guards it's because they know if anything happens to
this guy the whole thing ends he has a full security detail hold on no no no i can't do a
bomb i have bomb has been planted they're all so why are they all so many here we go
shit where's the bomb where's the police are going to an opponent's place where's the bomb
wait i have another one how do you have another chef what there's a backup chef
i don't i can't i don't have any more how do you get a hitman i don't have any more
i tried i put a i put a bomb right here it didn't do anything
decoy i tried to i said plant bomb and then when he when he went down i said
shoot one of these guys just blasted him in the fucking head how do you get hitmen is there
anywhere i can buy them is there a hitman marketplace just send garfield over here
i don't think i can send garfield here the convention has now finished can i oh my fucking
back hurts when he shot when he shot him and i didn't even shoot him like that my whole body
hurt and there's a decoy chef that's unbelievable oh my god how do i get a hitman all right i can't
alt tab does somebody just look up how to get a hitman in how to get hit in casino inc i have to
reload it's still february i know reload the auto save where was the auto save 55 this is 53 this
is 55 you can't you can't google that no you can't google that don't google how do i get a hitman
don't do that dude don't don't google okay oh oh how do i get it oh how do i get a hitman
in casino inc the video game for pc and cd rom what the fuck i only have nine thousand dollars
i don't know i don't know how to get one the cheats work no cheating the cheats work hold on
type in load the dice oh shit okay now what do i do now enter the following code hitman
okay well that's easy all right get just get a bunch and get over there hold on wait
how many can you have what no no no don't go fast oh god storm storm the pasta
ataliano okay guys to pasta ataliano we got a corner the chef market looks like a cheat
because then i'll be the only restaurant it's yeah it's a heavily guarded fortress
this is an rts now your hitman okay your hitman your hitman everybody's here peter baldwin
mr hoffman mr nolt mr bingham paul strebling rudolph madison is all stand over here
an attraction has been oh who cares i don't care about anything right now besides wait
they i think they're getting keen on this all right who's gonna take the shot who's
gonna make the first shot here all right uh all right mr jargons mr jargons chef
bako is in your sights mr jargon fire but oh my god they're all
how many am i putting down wait wait wait
i love this job
oh my no no don't don't i here's a hundred dollars get out no no more hitmen stop coming in
oh my god okay if a chef walks out that fucking door if a chef comes out that door then then this
is owned by a trillionaire doesn't even matter if a fucking chef opens this door
it looks like there's a fight one of your staff just died the police are on their way to the
scene
okay i need to fucking relax
he just walked in he just walked in who was the old guy that was shooting people
in my new family friendly place no it can't be it can't be oh god damn it fucking god
oh my god
oh one of your staff is dead what what are you talking about excuse me oh one of your staff
is dead again what who how does what happened oh my god i gotta take a break i'll be back
i'm gonna get some water i'll be right back i gotta throw water in my face and shit man
my my whole body hurts i'll be right back oh boy okay i love how running the casino turned into
the shittiest mob movie on earth killed the chef and then i got a chef retaliation kill
the last thing that guy did before he died is he killed the chef that was who he was going for
this is back and forth killing each other chefs oh man oh okay so uh i'm gonna just chill for a
little bit we're gonna go back in and i'm gonna try to salvage this for a little bit and then
probably in the next 10 to 20 minutes i'm gonna save it i'm gonna quit and we're gonna pick the
movie we're gonna watch next week i laughed so hard during at least this last part that oh
i'm hurting jesus it was it was this oh my god what movie what movie we're gonna watch a public
domain movie on tuesday of this coming week but let's get back in and try to recuperate uh i don't
know how i do that because a bunch of people are just dead now my staff i have my i was like a
place was burnt i only have 15 grand i gotta check on the hotels is there gonna be a restriction on
who can watch the movie no it's just gonna be a public domain movie and we also have to make sure
that it's not only is a public domain but it fits into a t.o.s as well there's a lot of old
public domain movies might uh be pushing it i think oh all right what is going on now police
are going to an opponent's place let's go back and take a look at my yeah this is all fucked up i
mean look i look at this thing is making tons this place is making money all right is there
wow we got a surplus how did we get this many you've been fined by the police what oh
what did i for what i got attacked why did i get fined i'll make it back i'm gonna make it back
poor security do i even have a bouncer here wait i thought i bought one oh he probably a bunch of
people quit during that bullshit at the pasta place but we're in debt anyways it doesn't matter
make everybody happy minus nine thousand nine eight five wages have been paid oh god what are
you doing i don't have enough money oh an opponent is in financial trouble me too man can we work
together just push the casinos next to each other and take the wall down we can work together
at least i made five dollars from this how's the food hey i want to go play the slots oh that's how
the food is this place is making money leaving for triple what isn't that a teenager all right
i need janitor i wait to like get into green again oh cheat well i don't want to but cheating is
it's where i already i'm not losing money i'm getting good yeah i already did cheat but not
use my cheats to rob the casinos yeah well i mean we just had a couple of major things just go down
i only have one what are you doing down here by the way go upstairs an opponent is in financial
trouble bars and bistros oh well we're i'm okay look i made two thousand dollars in like five
minutes why are you down here seriously what are you doing well can some of you go to the other
casino use a ufo attack please read the convention starting soon fetishists convention will start in
a day okay they're not coming to the the cheesy slots right i'm actually making a lot of money
let's check out up here our things how's staff do i have enough staff i do 20 bucks up
let's making money this is making money there's lots of doing well this casino is running very
like a clean engine ufo pasta taliano all right you do realize that when i do the ufo attack
that's when i have to stop playing the game that's where it's over i won't let me see the fetish
convention first i think that's important make sure this is on adult and make it 25 bucks well
let's go over everything let's see what's the what's made the most money the most money i've
made has been from poker poker has made 30 grand and then this little small sports betting has made
12 and roulette and then a few the one of the medium slots and then all the high slots have
made a shitload of money what has made the least amount of money that makes sense though
large sports betting somebody's empty what about food uh the drinks bought the bar obviously 3200
burgers and then at the table candy kiosk has made nothing obviously the porn theater has made the
most amount of money but small stage one is approaching fetish waiting room just hold on
it's coming up now uh by the way because that hold that convention is coming up
i think those prices a little more steep than you say uh there's no janitor here is there i need a
janitor clean uh when's the convention i think tomorrow did this make so look at this this is a
full theater let's watch this sucks no here comes a performer what does he do no stay stay are going
to an opponent's place all right waiting orders cheat cheat at the casino look at how much this
is insane look at the guards got so securities beefed up so much oh oh my god hold on just get
it the fuck away from me get it away from me get this thing away from me like why don't it keeps
happening in such a bad spot all right here comes the convention let's see this might be the most
people i've ever had in the casino it's doing so well 10 grand in like only two days 12 000
dollars in profit it's the end of the day wages have been paid how you got 1500 good
have you have you where
all right when when is the fetish convention are they coming in there's a convention that's
here we go actually ice denies doing anything wrong and is outright by your actions whatever
inventions coming in you know what that means fetish convention uh-huh what do they have
written on what was that they're walking around no shirts on check the other property
you know it's just people having some fun yeah see there's nobody from like the fetish convention
here nobody wants to eat this food maybe it's because it's 15 dollars for a shitty pizza
how much are the sodas a little cheaper empty tables i know it's bad it's okay this is propping
us up god a lot of people drunk here this guy keeps me all right get rid of this dude he keep
okay do you just have a problem with this guy every time i check if this guy's cheating
he's not you've just been staring at him all day he keeps thinking he's cheating and he never is
i gotta fire you you're gonna do a terrible job man this guy's like the five star dealer
at this establishment you don't even know what you're talking about oh i want an ice cream all
right i think it's wait i want to see what this is um is this guy uh a diaper this guy a baby
yeah they sure are yeah let's be generous maybe you'll stay now hey everybody hey everybody
merry christmas just made it back now i'm going to pick it up i have the best advertising and i just
got two thousand dollars for it thank you i told you guys now we just go through and reduce everybody's
pay by two hundred dollars people are beating each other up a minute there we go see
all right fine you can have a little bit more money
the other like fetish people besides the people in suit and the guy in the baby costume
i think that's it babies and people who lay deck everyone's vomiting yeah because this is like
fetish party and the drinks are actually very expensive this is actually good for me
check slothy cheese place all the old people love the magicians i'll tell you
and they love soda too they love magicians old people and love the soda all people playing
pinball no one's bought a single thing don't gross don't say that okay let's save it here
a new day how about that okay you're ready how do i do the ufo use ufo and attack please
okay well so on post alien first tape uh type in load the dice now and then type in ufo
it has to be outside okay so load the dice ufo flying saucer is attacking the city
dude that just seriously went
there's a cheat over here how do i send it to the pasta place it's the end of the day
wages have been paid send it i can i the city is being attacked
right at the same time pasta italiano pasta italiano capping the point
what if this what happens when there's nobody left time has been added godzilla
oh wait let me see there's other cheats i can do that i like this let's see godzilla
big heads puke puke more oh game crashed game crashed game crashed that's a bad crash too
i have to do this hold on i want to come back i want to do puke more we'll load up the save
i'm gonna go in pasta italiano and do puke more do godzilla and then turn and then burn
playstone and then we'll be we'll be over we'll transition to uh picking a movie for tuesday
you're a monster can't let pasta italiana survive uh it was a new day
okay pasta italiana let's go check it out what if it wasn't on the list anymore
it's not it's gone it closed oh it didn't yes they did yes they did all right what is it
there's a chef already coming out again he's angry there's no more what load the dice puke
puke more not working puke more it's the end of the day wages have been paid
technically casinos i mean there's nothing here it's the kind of visit but here's the thing i can't
tell if this is more puke or just a normal amount of puke that i've seen the whole game
no it's definitely more wait that was just coming out of his ass oh god that was insane
oh family guy oh
was the next one uh dance for me dance for me that one didn't work oh fuck
oh my god it really did oh my god oh my god it really does do that what oh my
oh this is so fucked up the city is being attacked oh watch out for the giant lizard
oh shit he's coming for me no go get this old guy wow you're stupid that was a gta driver sidewalk
driver your hitman has arrived at pasta italiano why do i care does he do anything
hey one of your opponents has just gone bust i don't know where he is the city is being attacked
you see no one's being raided by the police for bad hygiene wait you can get arrested for bad
hygiene this he's too slow this is just a guy in a costume there we go he's not getting away
okay the final thing i'm going to do this is giving me five every time by the way
whoa who is that
lucky
i don't know what this is gonna do my computer's gonna crash the computer's gonna crash
my computer's gonna fucking crash
you're all washed up but that was casino ink yeah i gotta reel it in i've i gotta reel it in
let's take a little bit let's find out what we're gonna watch that game this is fucking awesome
this is such a fun game i'm so glad that it turned out as good as it did all right we're
not done we're gonna start looking at some movies to watch public domain movies we're
gonna take a look and see which one i have seen a few of these that people are already linking
i'm gonna find a good one i have seen captain alex i have seen the bean one too i have to pick
something else i want here i'll give you the kids of criteria let's go over let's get out of here
that was casino ink if you were watching casino ink i played it yesterday as well and it was
i haven't laughed that hard in at least at least six months without a doubt so let's go uh abe
cashim thanks for the 20 community subs that's a huge amount of subs thanks for the 20 fucking
subs dude that's a lot trolls 2 troll 2 troll 2 is troll 2 is not public domain is it i don't
think troll 2 is public domain i do not think so uh let's anyways hi how you doing uh all right
so did you see my new star wars shirt it's a periodic table of villains shave i'll soon
shave today let me shave tonight you're a nerd whatever oh okay we're on twitch.tv sorry don't
shave my face why not all right so let's take a look but what are some good options remember
they have to be in the public domain and they have to be tos friendly there's some non tos
friendly public domain movies all right what do you what do you got there's a lot of free shit on
youtube let's take a look well free does not mean public domain just because a movie is free doesn't
mean that i can like stream it we need a list of good public here we go list of movies in the
public domain i want like a 60s monster movie like a 70s monster movie that just sucks annoying
orange is not a public domain movie let's see annoying orange attack of the clowns
hold on there's uh let's see we got what's the the amazing mr x please no annoying orange um why
would i watch annoying orange attack of the giant leeches attack of the giant leeches let's put
that one in the tab there's also uh do charlie chaplain stuff night of the living dead the
original night of living dead is public domain isn't it it is the night of the living dead
hold on let me take a look what about carnival of souls let's put that one in the tab let's put night
of the living dead in the tab there's also uh dementia 13 as little shopahar is in i don't
think little shopahar is a public domain is it little shopahar is is a fucking great great
movie and it's also a great play too right the old one is now the original one is the three other
three stooges in public the three stooges are in public domain they have to be right
let's watch a bunch of three stooges there's so many three stooges things
and we're going to see some real comedy all right let me get that a tab three stooges we did that
already um we watched like three minutes of a three stooges turkey episode there's like 700
hours of three stooges material we didn't watch any we didn't watch the three stooges we watched
a clip from the three is wwf in no it's not why would like the undertaker versus stone cold be
in public domain should be it's the same thing all right so i got attack of the giant leeches
carnival of souls three stooges episodes manos hands of fate i yeah but that's like i that feel
like everybody's seen that one i don't think anybody here has not seen that one land nine
from outer space let's take a look and that's not even that that's not i don't think that's
to us friendly i'm not sure i could do that okay hold on a minute there's a movie called the gorilla
and it looks like there's just like a gorilla that like attacks people 1930 it's going to be
a guy in a gorilla costume like throwing punches at actors right i'm going to put it in tab
i'll take a look at it is that the one is it the gorilla i feel like the gorilla might have might
be the one that i feel like the gorilla it could be the gorilla king's bride there's a movie called
slugs all right get get slugs on the list let's get slugs on there hold on yeah i don't think i
can do manos hand of fate unfortunately i don't think that's possible chicken run chicken was
there an original chicken run that was public domain before the claymation one that's not
accurate is it wallace and grommet is a wallace and grommet a grand day out is public domain
i gotta get night of living dead up here no it can't be hold on land knife of outer space hold on
metropolis this watch sneed metropolis so i put metropolis on here what about the screaming skull
let's see i'm gonna put the screaming skull on here a star is born oh no they that was like a
remake right okay is it the original one is the same movie wait the superman cartoon
the 1940s superman cartoon is public domain are you shitting me gonna have to watch a couple of
those all right what are you guys seeing wallace and grommet i don't see wallace and grommet under
here they are not seeing it they just want you to watch wallace and grommet wallace and grommet is
like paramount or something where's metropolis is that public i don't see it on here killer bean
yeah i've seen i've seen like almost every clip from killer bean i mean i'll put it on the list
just because but i i feel like most people have seen that captain alex i've i've seen captain
alex already take that off the list well this is this is just a preliminary list i'm gonna i'm
gonna do some research after the stream and i'm gonna pick a few of these that's what we're gonna
do might even be able to hold on to some of these and charlie yeah charlie chaplain charlie chaplain
movies oh wait charlie chaplain movies are like four minutes long each aren't they the technology
back in like 1908 it was like 400 million dollars to do like three minutes of video okay yeah we'll
do charlie chaplain we'll get those on the list buster key what's buster keaton buster keaton
sherlock jr all right i think we've got a pretty good preliminary list here the gorilla night of
the living dead land nine from outer space the screaming skull superman original 1940s cartoon
attack of the giant leeches the carnival of souls the three stooges buster keaton and charlie chaplain
a bucket of blood all right i'll look into that one you should watch a narrow toe yeah put that
on the list narrow toes in public domain so it's it's in there the leech one would be good yeah
killer clowns is that i don't think that's public domain i'm voting for gorilla gorilla might be
the i think it's gonna be gorilla so here's the i have a question so this is a oh let's just watch
public domain movies until we can't fucking take it anymore right should there be a scenario what's
the cutoff what's the cutoff if after 20 minutes or 30 minutes it's like this is sucks it's not
even funny it's not even interesting it's not scary it's terrible is there is there a cutoff
we can do after like 20 minutes to be like we gotta we gotta go or something we're gonna do
something way to move on to the next one 40 minutes and we're going to do at least one or
two i told you the way that i watch some movies sometimes is yeah we're gonna we're gonna we're
gonna do at least three or four of these at the the germa 985 technique i've told you about before
the germa 985 watch the movie technique that you don't give a fuck about is you skip 10 minutes
and watch 60 seconds skip 20 minutes watch five minutes skip 30 minutes watch two minutes skip
10 minutes watch 10 minutes that's that's the technique and you can get the whole fucking movie
that way we're gonna do that with with at least one or two of these you get the whole movie i'm
gonna have a bingo chart for the movie that might be fun too just to have like a bingo chart for the
each individual movie of what could happen it's effective and it's efficient it is i know did you
guys don't hear the first part of what i said i didn't say yeah i really i watched infinity war
like that no no i said a movie that you don't i don't do the quotes people hate that a movie
that you don't give a shit about that you don't even want to watch like dad's home too that's
what you're doing too and you end up watching about 25 minutes of the movie and you you don't
who cares you saw will ferro like shit his pants and change the thermostat and somebody got hot
and they were like sweaty and they were mad and you got you to see that part i do that at all to
save yourself like 65 minutes it's daddy's home okay so what's worse 25 minutes of daddy's home
too or watch all of daddy's home too and not get that time back and have 67 minutes to do whatever
the hell you want you could fucking go you can read a book you could like do dishes you could
go for a walk you think about all the things you do and say you can play like a a full rage induced
please surrender at 20 minutes what the fuck i'm not stuck here for 45 minutes league of legends
match you could do that please don't watch it at all idiot all right i got a good list if you have
any other ones throw them in the chat or throw them in the recommended i'll take a look at them
too no one said idiots they did they said idiot they called me an idiot but make sure that they're
actually in public domain otherwise i can't stream them all right we're gonna wrap it up here this
is where the stream is going to end i'm going to go take a bath a long one because right here
right here is fucking killing me in here am i going to stream tomorrow the next stream will
be on tuesday we're going to go tuesday wednesday thursday friday and probably possibly saturday
i'll give you the what's going to have tuesday is going to be movies wednesday community content
night thursday mystery game friday easy bake oven stream and maybe we might have to move it to saturday
depending on if i can get everything set up oh what about that guy's birthday yeah i'm coming
in here on monday and i'm gonna sing happy birthday in the chat attention attention can
we do this every month well that all depends on if this is fun i mean if we do this on monday i
mean on tuesday if we start the stream on tuesday and we get the movie going and it's like wow here
we go and it's like that was dumb that like wasn't even any fun and nobody that was bad nobody liked
it and neither did i then we probably won't but if it's fun and we can actually have a good time and
and yeah i'm down i'm down to do it whenever i mean there's plenty of movies that you can watch
in a public domain so the worst stream incoming well if you have that bottom you got that bottom
mentality we can only go up from there what about dos nights what happened alone dos saturday
no well no i'm not going to say that because i don't i don't like to tell people things that
don't happen bottom energy chat all right i'll see you guys tuesday thanks for sticking around
again we're gonna do this thing where i stream at least four times a week but between four to
five hours each time and they'll probably end up happening in a row so it'll be like four to six
hours like monday tuesday wednesday thursday and maybe friday or something like in a row
rather than three times for like six to seven hours thermal light about playing doom um i still
can it's just that we we had a lot of these things that were seemed like fun to do when you can do
sam and max season three i abandoned it and i'm totally okay saying that i abandoned sam and max
season three i wouldn't feel in it didn't think it was didn't grab me like the other two did it
has been officially has been abandoned officially why why why finish beautiful joe i know i know i
know i why no trust me you know when i turned that stream off a couple days ago i sat there
for like an extra five minutes and i'm just like like that why i like that game wow i can't believe
it it's all right but we'll see you on tuesday thanks for sticking around hope you have a good
uh rest of your weekend what about no more heroes 2 we're still gonna play it we still got all these
games you're saying we're still gonna play because we're gonna we're gonna take a we're gonna do a
non-gaming week except for thursday first there will be a mystery stream and by mystery stream
you know it might be it might be soft for xbox 360 just saying it could be that it might be
something else it could be that though i don't know we'll see i'm right at the very right here
right now savov savovsky gave 50 5000 bits and that's it's been 50 dollars has been dropped
like five times thank you savovsky i say enjoy your bath you filthy animal thank you for providing
great content day after day those stuck at home really i'm making a big difference i'm glad you
think so i'm absolutely happy to do this and hang out as long as i'm able to thanks for the 5000
bits stay safe take care of yourself take care of your loved ones take care of your friends
thanks a lot uh philateral which gave another 50 dollars earlier they said please god do that to
the crypt casino i think they were talking about um just melting an entire building but i don't i
don't go that i don't cheat that way germa what about the joke germa the joke i know i know don't
worry i know don't worry i got it's i it's it only can happen on the movie stream it can't happen
anywhere else i didn't forget it i would i i didn't forget it trust me thank you both of you
thanks by last week for that another 50 dollars and savovsky for 50 dollars both of you let's go
back earlier let's go back to eskilo thanks for 250 remember at 985 i want to record you a public
domain movie on youtube called who killed captain alex already seen it it's a very funny movie and
the production only cost 200 people made it with passion it's the first action movie of uganda
you can donate to them if you want they give you a hand-painted t-shirt they love when people
share the movie because that would mean the world to them the movie starts with some info i can't
put here support it i know it's it i've i've seen captain alex so i mean i'll i would shout it out
and just be like just fucking watch this and support this movie right because it's awesome
but at least for the first view i'd like to see something that i haven't seen yet because then
i can give you at least for me too like i want to be able to see something i've never seen and
you'll get a real reaction it'll be a real reaction stream watch breaking bad nice yeah
i have seen it uh hey jason thanks for the 250 jason i requested to watch auto's big adventure
for movie night when you mentioned the idea but you said instantly i still stand with this
suggestion for wednesday and chat would also like this too we must watch both videos yeah but i
already did that but this this is not youtube movie night this is like public domain real movies
we will do another watch old videos stream again it's not on wednesday or not on tuesday
auto is a real movie well auto's big adventure was not a movie made by a production company
and didn't release in theaters although god damn it should have we will watch them again i promise
just not on one of these streams teepo thank you teepo for the thousand bits appreciate it
everyone just had my first major nasty breakup today i want to thank you in this community for
just being there i don't talk much and chatter in the discord because i'm very shy but it's
always very comforting to come back and watch you live what everybody has to say in chat and
it always makes me feel like i'm not truly just alone and depressed in my room all the time hope
you're handling your condition well and sorry for the long and filthy message i love you guys
oh that's all good man sorry to hear about the breakup first major nasty breakup it's always
tough that you'll be back i've been there a couple times over the 30 years that i've been on the
planet 35 i know don't correct me so i can i feel you but thanks for sticking around thanks for
hanging out we are well we are absolutely happy to welcome anybody that wants to hang out here
that's kind of all i care about on this channel is having just people hang out
laughing talking shit about random stuff talking around is having a good time that's it that's
pretty much the number one thing but to know that it's somebody's doing that it means a lot
here was 35 despite looking 19 i look older than 19 i get i get carded at bars guys wait that means
oh that is what that means i don't know where my brain was going with that i think it was trying
to say i don't get carded but i do every time no matter what like i get carded because i look
younger than i do yeah okay so i'm wrong it's all right hey mostly lost thanks to the 250 i think
it's adorable how you always pronounce the full words when you see laughing my ass off lmao doesn't
sound correct to me lmao no that's i don't like that lmao i feel like i'm texting like
lol lmao brb g2g lmao no it's laughing my fucking ass off lmao lmao hey hot gamer thanks for the
five dollars this whole chat trashing beautiful joe kind of reminds me of when uh hideki kimiya
tried doing focus testing which was mostly composed of children lmao or beautiful joe in
they said i think the whole focus group thing is not the way to make a game because you start to
bring in other people's opinions and lose some of the originality for beautiful joe we brought in
some kids to do a focus test and asked them what do you think of the characters and all the kids
said oh his head's too big or silvie is annoying i just want to kill her they were just trashing
the game so i just got pissed off and said i'm not changing anything and i'm glad he did because the
game is fantastic it's the best game maybe you should try his method and play whatever game you
like regardless of what chat says i do that i do that though so times when i because you gotta
remember i do like to play the things that i want to play and i do it most of the time it gets to
be a point where it's very evident that people are just not don't want i don't like my goal here
when i broadcast is i want everyone to have fun and have a good time and i want to be having a
good time and when people are like this is boring or this sucks this is stupid i don't like this
game this game's and it's not just like three people it's like hundreds of them it's harder
for me to be like look at how much fun this is oh gosh check this out i'm having so much fun
hey everybody it's a fun time and you guys are not having fun i feed off of people's energy
right like i feed off of what you guys say and the things that you guys are laughing about or
talking about um that's that kind of i'm a creature of that kind of habit he's a demon
but call me whatever you want that's what a monster does that's call me whatever you want
but if i'm not feeling like the chat vibe and i'm not having fun having fun with you guys and
having you understand that we're you know having you guys have fun and there needs to be this like
mutual kind of understanding that what we're doing is what is fun to do because otherwise it's me
just like talking at a wall while people scream about how they hate what i'm doing and it feels
odd oh it got that power up nice okay what's that 10 000 power ups this game sucks this game's
fucking stupid jeremy this is so bad please do something else god this sucks so bad okay so
that's 10 000 points all right i guess oh i do a spin move there what are you guys saying what's
happening over here oh okay that's cool all right um nice so um guys this door here needs to be
yeah it's hard for me i i feed off of fucking chat the dreamcast sucks lab that's different
it's different you should do straw balls sometimes to see if chat really enjoys this
yeah but i also don't want to just hand you guys the keys to my car you know what i mean
if i want to if i want to do something and it's something i'm gonna plan to do like i'm gonna do
it i'm not gonna be like guys tell me what to stream every day like i'm not that's like i have
the keys to the car you guys are passengers in this car now i can take suggestions for where you guys
want to go but at the end of the day i'm the one with the wheel in the hand we're in the baby seat
maybe some of you are there's at least one of you that might be we're not gonna crash we're fine
i've got my eyes on the road but the point still stands is i like having that balance of you guys
having recommendations and influencing some of the stuff that's done but it's not just going to be
like i do polls in the pretty stream chat all the time it'd be like what do you guys think is what
do you guys want to do today they're like choices that i have made right anytime you guys have ever
seen a poll it's always been here's like three or four things that i would like to do and then you
guys like oh do this this sounds good this sounds fun i don't know about that one those are all
things that i want to do but i like that i would probably want to do but if i start handing you
guys the keys then it's like i can't um i can't really make decisions for myself anymore you know
what i mean it's like well i guess i'm not doing this because they told me i can't but i don't
want that to ever be a possibility it's gonna turn this car around yes no you're not getting
the keys why does it smell like piss because you pissed your pants you're sitting down and
it's sitting in your own pee or peed your pants in the car all right moving on that was hot gamer
for 500 bits thank you miami hotlines thanks for 250 hey king it's me again heart your casino is
still so ugly i might barf well we can add you to the list of the hundreds of people that barfed in
the casino so it's not really not even a big deal at that point thanks a lot though hole of one
zombie thanks for the 500 you mentioned you could live in a casino howard hughes actually did that
he also made his fortune from drill bits made movies like rat movie and he genuinely spent
most of his time naked in his hotel room not making that up germa hughes spruce goose bird house
i mean you can live close to casinos or close to the strip but nobody i mean unless you're like
a celebrity or an athlete or like uh boxers or ufc fighters have permanent rooms in some of the
hotels down there but people don't you don't like live in the belagio you don't like live in circus
circus you could but you don't people you don't or a streamer yeah or a streamer that'd be so weird
i would never want to live in a resort or hotel or something just think about that somebody does
your laundry somebody cleans your room every day i would lose so i you know oh yeah somebody's
going to come in and just do a bunch of shit for me in my room people take out you if somebody
else takes your trash out i feel like i would be i'd become so complacent and then you know i would
just turn into like a slug because then after like after like five years of that it's hard to go back
to like doing your own bed and cleaning your own sheets and taking your own trash out each human
slug would be living in a hotel it's true hey thank you pigeon for the 500 bits they say germa
read it's a very a germa the time has come for me to write you a very long letter okay let's see
uh i'll be 20 years old tonight okay happy birthday at 12 a.m have a good 12 a.m birthday
feels birthday man uh this marks seven years of my enjoyment of you and your content
i've written a letter written a paper about you i've met you in person in fact the symbol of the
moment is now the highlight of my room's decor yes you can show this what you do you have like
a picture of me and wait what is this this is like hanging in your room oh sick so there it is
yeah i'm a signer i sign no it's not like a fixed guys it's not like a picture of my face or
something oh wait is there one up here no it's a twitchcon badge it's not like he's got like a
shrine of my face i said people are gonna make fun of this signature but i'll show it because
people gonna i know it's bad i have such a shitty handwriting and everything
i'll just save this as where is it oh that's the blueprint for freddy fazbear's pizza
okay there we go so here look i have really shitty handwriting and it's kind of hard it's
really hard to draw when you're standing up and holding your hand underneath as a pad and i'm
very much aware that that i know i do a thing under the a and i didn't know this until very
recently that i just have subconsciously been stealing that from amazon that's how i do every
single one i've signed probably if i'm realistic i don't know is 80 things i always do the certain
the thing underneath the a and it's just fucking amazon and i just i don't just do it i'm just
like oh german okay whatever let's put a smile on that box god damn it and the smile well yeah i
don't know i just did it they say german nobody on the internet can offer what you do nobody can
pretend to you offer a hilarious and personal experience when i watch other streamers my
experience is immediately halted as a bit donation is read as it is given ironically reading the
donations which is supposed to serve to make the setting of twitch chat to streamer more intimate
but instead it works to disconnect those who aren't the bit messenger well i do have something to
do i will tell you this though that there probably always will be a disconnect i think that's
important to mention too and to remember as well that there's always going to be a disconnect now
it doesn't have to be a situation where i just hey thanks for the ten dollars okay bye right
but there will always be a disconnect between anybody who's ever really on this channel
and fluter did just say um that's not true plenty of other good streamers that is true too
but it's not just i'm the only person on the whole entire website that says thanks in a way or gives
some kind of attention in a way to people that give money to the stream there's plenty of people
that do that but there always will be a form of a disconnect between anybody on this channel and me
that's just kind of the nature of this whole platform but i do kind of see what you're saying
what do you mean i'm not as close to i'm not as close to people i'm not as close as people
to you as in real life well my understanding is we all are in this community together this is a big
place there's a lot of people here and personal attention is impossible it is i'll be up front
with you it's impossible there's no way for me to give any of you any real personal attention
ever give me attention okay sure but when you have a large community like this everyone kind
of everyone's kind of is in the same spot and everyone kind of thinks the same things are
interesting and just because i i can't and won't give anybody personal personal attention doesn't
mean that we all can't enjoy the same things together and have fun in this space that's what
it's for and of course if so if like if you go to a convention and i'm there we can hang out and
shoot the shit for a little bit right but we're in that same space disable donations you know
it actually took me a pretty long time to come to terms with stuff like paypal and bits and stuff
it actually took a long time i never had a paypal for bits or anything and when bits came then i
was very even reluctant to turn it on i'm constantly evaluating this stream like i've never
it's never well when you're not recently have i thought oh maybe i should turn off
donations and just like let's just hang out whatever and he's under constant evaluation
but i never want this stream to be a scenario be it up i don't i never want to be in a scenario
where people want to pay me money to talk to me it shouldn't be like that you understand i don't
that never sat well with me and i know that there's a lot of he hates scenarios i know i
say the word scenario scenarios one of my favorite words it's happening now and that been and that's
the thing when you get to a point when that's when that happens that's why i always want to
kind of evaluate where i am and what i'm doing and how comfortable i am doing the things that i do
remember i come from youtube where i would just make a video and there it is and if you liked it
you could tell me to go fuck off somewhere in the comments but we didn't it wasn't real time
and nobody really sent me any any direct personal messages that i addressed in video or anything
and then we get to the scenarios ah i said it again then we get to the thing where because more
and more people are on this channel and more and more people are sending money that i read at the
end of streams or read whatever well let's just say like you're talking about other streamers
you have to increase you're gonna put some you're gonna put the gate up and make it so it's harder
to do because you don't want the whole stream just to be talking to people for money that was
one of the main reasons why i moved this to the end of the streams because i don't i want to
broadcast and i want to like i said collectively do something fun and hang out and have fun
and enjoy ourselves together i never wanted this stream to be like for a dollar i'm just
gonna start talking to you you know what i mean i don't want that and i hope that doesn't sound
like like i'm some kind of dickhead or something i really hope it doesn't oh this is still yes i
do sign shit like that it sounds like you hate me no i just i never want it to get to a position
where the stream takes a back seat to just being paid money to just talk to you that's why i
i took it away from the middle of streams i put it to the end of streams i raised the
bit amount that needed to be read at the end of streams and but that can come off as well now
he's putting he's making us spend more money to say anything to him at all fuck that get you a
money no but but this channel already does this channel already makes a lot of money it does
that's very obvious and very plain for anybody to do any basic math to know how many subs this
channel has and i don't i don't want to like pretend like that's not happening but i also
don't want it to become the one thing that matters for me to just drain people to just send me fucking
money and i just hey thanks for the fucking 20 bucks you got to say the one thing to germa see
you later so that's why i do like to give some personal attention but then how far does that go
how far does that go in that regard right it's something that i like i said i constantly evaluate
quick clip it and cut the sensible part oh my god but anyways they say uh pin says uh please
keep working hard like you do know that every important and unimportant birthday i will somehow
make a time to celebrate me stumbling onto your channel all the way back in 2013 thank you
seriously they say also say uh sorry about structure i'm pretty high while i write this
it's all good it's all good dude fucking we but i really appreciate it i really do
that so the fact that somebody would write a letter like this to me it's shocking to me i
i still have trouble realizing and believing that this that people think that is surprising
so thank you for even considering that i'm somehow some major influence in your life thanks i i hope
you're taking something good or i hope you it makes you i don't know hopefully you can
enjoy this stuff going on here and maybe it maybe and maybe i shape one of your views or
something and then i'll be like 70 years old looking back and i told those kids about that
and they are they started pissing in the shower i remember when i told them that you take a shit
for 45 minutes and they didn't believe me and how they do all of them but yeah it's it means a lot
thank you moving on we'll move on now we had where am i right here gnarly thanks to 250 if
you were born in 2000 would you make your username germa 000 that's probably that's
pretty that's pretty cool that's cool yeah hey charco supreme thanks to the five dollars
logan brothers vr waiting room logan brothers vr if logan brothers ever comes back
either video game or television show i will drink a full vial of piss no i won't that's t.o.s i will
um i will i'll do a sleeping stream i don't know that's never gonna happen so i'll be fine
hey autumn dragons thanks for the 250 hello king can we please watch the original tom and jerry
cartoons on amazon prime pretty please a cherry on top thanks dad i want to test out the amazon
prime thing eventually but for this trial run i'd like to have as many people there as possible
more fun that way thanks for the 250 whole of one zombie thanks for the 250 i don't remember
titles of files i just have a file on my desktop with like five pictures of your face
with your eye slightly moved to the left and i'll laugh at like a lunatic somewhere someplace
i'm in somebody's files on their computer nice peaceful hailey thanks for the 250 hey jeremy i've
been streaming resident evil 2 and honestly it's the most fun game played in a while the remake or
the old one big difference they need to stick to making their games like that instead of how
resident evil 5 and 6 were the remake all right there you go i think they're leaning now i think
they're learning now that they should stick to what they've always been good at anyways have a
good night yeah resident evil 4 is really good too but resident evil 3 remake apparently sucks
help me help me i keep people tell me that the game's not good it's like a bad game and it's
not worth playing i keep i'm nobody tells me it's good i think i've heard by maybe one or two
accounts that it was like oh yeah that's rarely really good is it good should i do should i play
it it's not is it good it's fucking great it's good it sucks it's worth playing once it's not
as good as two but it's good it's short it's decent who the fuck cares it's good resident peepee
from your own form your own opinion sheep it's good but short eat my ass uh cash grab
omega low it's okay who the fuck cares it's not that and it's short all right well i could pretty
i got a pretty good indicator what chat thinks about it maybe i'll play it hey goiki thanks for
the 50 dollars haha almost at 45 percent sharing gambling people happy yeah i was pretty close to
like beating the game that's probably when you beat the game but then we spawned 100 hitmen and
they started shooting each other that was where i had to end thanks for the five fucking thousand
bits huge money thank you goiki another one that's just contributes huge money to the stream every
time blue dkrf thanks for the six dollars thanks for being one of my favorite streamers thanks for
being one of my viewers i was i've always said favorite viewers but then i would have made a
lot of people probably really sad thanks for being one of thanks for being here thanks for the six
dollars even in these times when i'm considered an essential worker in a hospital i've been amazing
for making things more enjoyable and getting to laugh for a while with what's going on you're very
essential we got to give it up to the hospital workers they are doing double fucking time
without people like you the whole world would be fucked forever but thanks and thanks for the six
dollars geo love thanks for the 12 dollars wallace and grommet i don't think wallace and grommet is
public domain it's not public domain we could probably watch like the rube goldberg machine
opening where like it goes like and then it like the balloon pops and it lands on the toast and the
toast gets butter spread that's peewee herman that's the beginning to peewee herman that's
peewee's uh big adventure yeah okay is that a public domain that's a great one that's like
one of the best movies ever peewee's big adventure is one of the best movies ever made that's too bad
go watch it if you've never seen it it's great um that's one of the you want to talk about like
put it in the wiki the lore that movie is one of the reasons why i'm such a fucking weirdo
as a i'm a very very highly influenced from peewee herman's movie like extreme influence
from peewee herman i say we stab him and then we got him and then we hang him and then we kill him
i say let him go that's one of the classic parts of that movie if you've never seen it
maybe you'll think it's funny you make this joke every like 10 times a year
yeah i know because it's so good it's so funny it's like total perfect the scene is perfect comedy
he knocks all his fucking bikes over and they try to kill him and then he dances he does the dance to
the tequila song and all of a sudden everybody loves him that is peak comedy that's peak humor
and i refuse to believe that it's not i love large barset yeah oh and by the way
yeah it's the scariest face ever and i was scared of it when i was a kid large marge large marge
should that's like a germa rumble character you know i'm saying i'm only here for the drops can
you turn them on what well what do i have drops on my channel how do i give it to you here you're
gonna have one i guess how do i do it hey soup gg thanks for the 250 germa please seriously consider
watching plan 9 from outer space it's a notoriously bad 1950s sci-fi horror and it's the first so bad
it's good movie it's hilarious i think you'll love it i thank you chief it's on the list i've
got it on the list right here thanks for the 250 goose goose thanks for 250 germa you watch movies
like i watch your streams 99 background noise one percent wondering what the hell is going on
not a bad way to watch get those credits rolling all the subs if i can figure out how to do it
what the heck is it what the heck what the heck what the heck what the heck what the heck
my god what the heck watch it what the heck i lost it what the heck idiot idiot
pulling dynamite everyone loved that thing for like two years idiot isn't that coming back am i
wrong is aren't they doing like another napoleon dynamite i think they're like another one are
they doing i think they're actually doing that it's funny when it came out um okay i just like
reached behind me and on the chair so i just reached behind me and sitting on the chair
i like i was like what the fuck have i been sitting on all because i haven't gotten up really
i was like what am i sitting on and i pulled this out it's the universal studios game cube game i
was sitting on at the whole stream it's weird i was wondering like something is weird and cold
and doesn't feel right and i didn't move it oh right right right uh the subs rollo thanks for
subbing everybody as always thanks for being in the oil that makes the stream move forward
was that the joke no it was real life thanks everybody appreciate it we also had 250 from
silent serenity hey germa i know you're a huge fan of porn i recommend that we watch the 1978
classic debbie does dallas who was released into public domain after a copyright conflict
uh you can watch that on your own time thanks for the 250 though hey peaceful hailey thanks
to 250 hey again there is a maybe transparent image of the mst 3k silhouettes i don't know what
you plan on doing for movie night but something like that would be funny just like half of me
sitting in the seat i wonder if that like could i just could i do that i still have like a camera
pointed at the back of my head oh don't give me ideas i would want to like set a bunch of dumb
shit just have like popcorn like fucking throw it at the screen movie suck all right well we'll see
i'll see if i have enough time to get some of that shit done that's fucking funny though it's
a good idea thanks to the 250 thanks to the idea hailey snoozing copper thanks to the 250
hey remember who i am that's right i'm your long-lost brother that wouldn't be the first
thing you forgot now is it i have god hand over uh and it's crying on my couch because you won't
play it but hold on if you can pronounce burgundy correctly you don't have to play god hand i know
it's your weakness i just pronounced it correctly thank you it's burgundy well uh i uh think i got
it right i'm still gonna play god hand though because uh you know uh thanks for the tip hey
fitting thanks with 250 it's lameo dude not lmao uh potato potato hey the plushie thanks for the 250
germy you may not remember but you gave me some advice a few months ago he said you tried to
stream for my birthday a few days ago this is the guy i want to let you know that after that first
one i wrote a message i wanted to give you but i couldn't find any way to contact you and couldn't
get anyone to pass the message along i'm too embarrassed to send it now but basically it said
how you held me through a very tough if not the toughest time in my life even if you don't know
it happy birthday this is the this is no this is the guy that you lied to the guy he lied to you
no i didn't i said i was maybe gonna stream on monday i was thinking about streaming monday
was probably gonna be stream on monday but there's not gonna be a stream on monday i'm gonna be here
in the chat i can say happy birthday in the chat i will i'll be here on monday at exactly the time
that the stream was supposed to start i can say happy birthday happy birthday chat stream chat
message who's lmfao will all be there you gave him a lie for his birthday i did not i am gonna
be there i just though i won't be on the camera and i they won't be in the stream going i'll be
in the chat for at least a few minutes he hates birthdays i don't hate birthdays i love birthdays
especially good ones like everyone is here liar liar liar liar now thank you plushy appreciate it
happy birthday and i'll see you on monday happy birthday on monday we'll see you on monday pixel
mike thanks for the five dollars hey germa someone on the sub is saying i was breaking sub rules by
asking you to stop playing beautiful joe i just want to apologize for trashing the game super hard
but like you just said it really wasn't fun for me and a lot of chat apparently but it was just
it looked like one of those games that's more fun to play than stream regardless have a good one
you're in big big trouble you're in big trouble big big trouble run he's running he's running
he's running come here come here stop stop there he is you stopped how dare you that's all i had
to say now you can get off get out of the get out of the car get out of the train wherever you're
going bye bye yep see you
see you next dream man oh that's fucking i like that guy that guy's fun hey
Friedl Schlitz Friedl Schlitz thanks for the 250 you should definitely look into Buster Keaton
he's a silent comedy legend on the same level as Charlie Chaplin or Harold Lloyd
add reefer madness to the movie list check it out hey the plushie thanks for 250 from my other
message also included a code for the game death road to canada i already own that game actually
to be honest with you it's i was gonna play it a long time ago but it just sat in my steam library
oh you might like it i can gift it to a random chat member if you don't want it thanks for
being who you are i would just throw it in there just throw it in there just go copy paste
somebody will get it death road to canada give it to me give it to me replace a letter or a bot
will get it yeah so copy the code and change one of the uh numbers of letters to a different letter
there's bots replace how would a bot just doesn't mean that's crazy uh can of Shawn's thanks for the
250 you're missing that you enjoyed beautiful joe i'd recommend you watch dead leaves the pretty
nice sore shortest short sort short that sort of fits the vibe of that game or red line people
will tell me to do red line and watch red line it's just another neat movie anyway have a good one
i have gotten recommendations to watch red line i wonder if it's any good i'll add dead leaves
to the list of the animated shows that i'm allowed to watch each year and by the way already watched
seasons one through four of spongebob so running out of some space hey dubsky dude thanks for the
250 i've noticed more people suggesting games and chat being unruly with your game choices
no offense but i think it's because you've only been playing boomer games in the past two months
i think doing a straw poll you pick streams once or twice a month could help well also there's
no games have come out the last three months besides like the last week what what what games
have come out in the last two or three months doom animal cross yeah but i've thought like
when doom come out why would i play the final fantasy 7 remake have you ever heard me ever
all i've said i've done is talk shit about that game there are new people here no not to get
uh i gotta rephrase that i have i've all i've done is make fun of the trailers and tell you how i
don't play final fantasy i'm not gonna play final fantasy 7 remake i didn't pay five bucks for this
bullshit i just i it's a what a fantastic okay backtracking barry coming in hold on a minute
is one of the most influential most respected series ever ever but i never played them never
got into them i actually really don't like turn-based rpgs they i find them boring they
kind of bore me and that's not just with final fantasy that's with everything that is a turn-based
rpg i'm just not into them i need the laser beam to go
dodge rolls i need fps any blood any characters that have funny voices time wait for an attack
what about chrono triggers the best game ever made it is to marry rpgs the best game ever made
it is those are both turn-based rpgs they are i know jerma could you say something like that
and have that opinion love those games so much i had to close my window hold on okay listen
important um i turn-based rpgs they gotta really do it for me chrono triggers one of the only
ones super mario RPGs one of the only ones you good you named the only two turn-based rpgs
that i actually liked to play i that's those the only two even played that many yes i have
i've played golden sun i've played final fantasy one two three four i've played final fantasy ten
i've played advance wars i've played what do you mean that's a war what are you talking about
golden sun is a bad one i've played i'm not googling what do you mean google what have i
googled i'm sitting here this whole time i'm starting to final fantasy i final fan look let
me ask you this the one reason why i was gonna play final fantasy seven and i i don't know if
this is a spoiler for anybody or not but did i i don't want to did they did they remove it's
a spoiler for a remade fucking game that's like saying is it saying charlie wins and willy wonker
in the chocolate factory at the end of the movie like you who the fuck doesn't know that by now
there's memes about it they deleted they deleted one of my favorite characters they deleted the
only character i care about i don't mean what the fuck it was a book in the 60s it was a movie and
then in the 70s or 80s and then there was another movie in 2000 like two and every meme with willy
wonka you get nothing good day sir you've read that fight you know that story already when did
when did charlie and the chocolate factory two come out the the the squeak will remember you
if you didn't think that it's like a kid's movie what do you guys oh i got another spoiler for you
um in the movie cars too oh lightning mcqueen he oh he wins that race in the end
what unpredictable there's no way that lightning mcqueen wins the race at the end versus the evil
no he was made by disney channel for fucking eight-year-olds i thought there i thought
lightning mcqueen's car was gonna explode and his head was gonna get thrown off into the stands
i thought that's what was gonna happen what do you mean the car he is the car he is the
when somebody driving the car no they're just cars well whatever same thing lightning mcqueen
doesn't get out he's like it's me lightning mcqueen oh they have mouths and their mouths talk yes
who knows it could have been a fucking like i could have been like this hey it's me lightning
mcqueen talking through the he didn't know i why would i watch cars i've watched the good one
planes dude i'm just kidding fucking willy wonka willy wonka at the end of the movie puts some
battery acid into the chocolate factory thing and gets arrested where were we where are we doing
what was what was the point of this oh right final fantasy 7 i'm not gonna play it i respect
it i'm not gonna play it though it's not turn-based i isn't that game like 75 hours long 40 it's 35 to 40
hours i'll lose interest you know how long you know quickly i'm gonna lose interest from walking
down a hall okay let me go back what's that over there what's that
no no no no no what's up i got it kid hey heads up
after that a thousandth time i'm gonna stop that doesn't mean it's a bad game that doesn't mean
i don't respect the franchise it is one of the best most influential fucking incredible franchises
in the history of video games it's the reason it's the reason why you have some of your games
today is because final fantasy paved the way for fucking everything it's like the dungeons and dragons
of modern fucking video games and rpgs and shit i know i know trust me i do i love it this is just
to prevent anybody from throwing a rock at my house that's dragon quest yo the remake is hot
you have to play it ah okay here's the thing if i play the remake and i really love it
i will i'm gonna be eating my words all stream i'm gonna be like wow this is so much fun this
game is fucking awesome holy shit this is so good and then like i will i will be the bad guy i'll
be the bad guy and i will admit it and i will say guys i am so fucking wrong i was so incorrect and
i am so i would i will heavily apologize i will say i'm so sorry for ever saying that i didn't
think i was gonna like this game omega low cope cope doesn't want to be wrong there's a nice demo
this ego maniac won't risk being wrong lie and pretend you hate it why would i pretend to hate
something that i like okay here's what i'll do are you ready i will play no fuck no i will
hmm i'm gonna play the demo off stream and then i'm gonna come back and either apologize
at the beginning of next stream or i'm gonna be like yeah i'm not into it and that's okay
and that's okay i don't know how we got here oh let's talk about uh new games um i'm gonna play
doom this is so many this i have so many things i want to do that's the right answer apology in
bound valorant and i think my brain might be too small for valorant and plus you need to get like
a secret key you need to get a secret like what how do i how do i get a key for valorant
don't play valorant no don't play they would give you a key is it any good is valorant any good or
is it just like a it's just like a like a cartoon cs go don't play it it's called it's cuck strike
anyway i'm not gonna like it but i don't think i like it moving on hey sticks renegade thanks
to 250 hot take jackie chan stunt master is greater than resident evil 3 uh i would put a
rock defense up in front of your house hey dinosaurs rex thanks to the 250 also how did
you develop so much confidence confidence is something i've been struggling with for a while
now and i wanted to let develop more of it any advice for me and the rest of chat i think i think
i'm just honestly i think i'm just too fucked up to even care does that actually make any sense
i feel like i don't even think about like confidence or anything at this point because
i'm so my brain is so all over the place i don't have time to even think about it i don't even
think i am that confident considering uh backtrack barry just told you like four different things
about the final fantasy series in the span of about five minutes is that confidence or is that
i'm not sure no shame is no that's a lack of shame he's too stupid to be shy
i think here's where here's here it is right it's comfortable it's being comfortable confidence
comes from comfort because you're comfortable in any scenario that you can put yourself in
and how you get yourself more comfortable is the real question music is gone monkey
having no shame makes you a psychopath i took the psychopath test i'm only like 60
i'm only like 62 psychopath or something that i'm fucking 38 angel okay the test was 150 dollars
got it online but uh how do you how do you build confidence you just have to be comfortable in the
thing that you're doing and that takes time takes time that's really the only advice i can give you
because um i'm something wrong i skipped a bunch of bits here john cena is killed thanks to three
dollars i missed the whole stream because of work can you do the whole thing again i don't want to
be a vod watcher uh that's an easy solution just watch the vod and pretend like it's live
just and just but do like chores or something so you can't like chat i can't chat tonight
because i'm doing chores there you go hey sub wob thanks for the 500 bits seven years ago i
saw your h1z1 video for the first time and hold on oh sorry when i like have like a burp in my
chest and i have to it kind of hurts as it goes like i saw your h1z1 video for the first time
and you've inspired me since you pushed me to experiment the ways i'd never imagined leading
me to get into a college i thought i'd be impossible thanks for all the laughs and positive vibes oh
good to hear that you got into the college that you wanted to get into it sounds like
thanks for watching for seven years that video was a fun one playing that game was uh a ton of
fun i think that's me and star will be able to tell you that was some of the most fun we
probably had in a while playing that game a lot of fun but good luck to you thanks for the five
dollars hey abnormal abnormality thanks for the 1500 bits i had the pleasure of saying hello at
twitchcon when you signed something of mine i never noticed the a swoosh and just went to check
and it was there i just laughed for 10 minutes straight god yes i okay this is proof that people
are thinking i'm making that up for those of you that think that this is this is bullshit
it's not it's not a classic germa swoosh i remember to do something else yeah i remember
i remember you taking all that out of your backpack it was really really cool thanks for
the 1500 bits hey pigeon thanks for the 250 the fact that you have a hard time grasping
the amount of positive effects on your viewers lives is the reason that i keep donating and
writing i just like i just like having a good time man i just like fucking having fun is it
that's it that's all i was that's all that's all i'm doing here i don't have any other
reasons to be here besides hey how do we have fun today and yeah i mean people pay a shitload of
money every month it's a lot of money but i never want that to be like the hey and give me
more money to talk to me give me more money pay me money to talk you are gonna pay her to talk
you just paid money during the stream let's have a conversation you and me thanks for the
10 20 dollars i like to focus on what i want to do what are you it was you're spamming something
i'm getting more link spam and i told you i didn't like that he looks like germa wait what this is
wait oh wait wait wait wait what the fuck not the music not the music not the music
all right now he looks like germa
am i dead germa after the carnival stream
germa has mako poisoning i don't i'm not poisoned i'm fine i'm gonna get up i'm gonna be just fine
i'm gonna i'm gonna get up and i'm gonna be i'm gonna get up i'm gonna be stronger than ever
i'm gonna beat the shit out of cloud he looks like germa no i'm gonna get up i'm gonna fucking
haymaker cloud once in the face and break his jaw i'm gonna be the most powerful person in
final fantasy 7 i gotta get a haircut i'm gonna get a haircut i'm gonna get a different shirt
i'm gonna i don't want to be the guy in every game you know what i mean i'm gonna i'm gonna
god i'm gonna give myself a hulk hogan after this anyways you secretly want to do that kind of it's
fun anyways uh let's keep going uh that was just in the chat sticks renegade uh we got that one
about john uh junk uh junkie no jackie chan stunt simulator what the fucking game is called
shit thank you for the 250 hey silent serenity thanks for the 250 hey king it's me your favorite
viewer do you think you could make a motivational tape for us like cheers to you germa edition
chat productivity would increase by 200 that might be fun to do maybe yeah if i have some
time i would do one hey amber wisp thanks for the five dollars hey thanks for streaming it's
my birthday today but because of isolation i couldn't do much it was nice to have a distraction
instead of being alone and sorry for myself love your streams they're always they're very always
a bunch of fun happy birthday what are you talking about we spent all this time in the casino
there was a birthday casino everybody's birthday was there especially yours thanks to the five
dolls and happy birthday amber wisp have a good one hey raddest raccoon thanks to 250 germa say
popcorn i think it's cute how you say it popcorn popcorn i want some popcorn anybody have any
popcorn popcorn popcorn popcorn we'll see you on tuesday thanks for coming out uh i hurt myself
laughing today i have to put like a device in my body that once i start laughing hard enough it
just shh it turns it off somehow but we have a few more bits to do but we say our final goodbye
guillotine somebody said put a bomb collar uh so you want you want my head to explode
that's not good guillotine senpai thanks for the five dollars the first video of yours i watched
four years ago was the naked fire watch video i watched it 10 times it was so bernie pog then
i watched almost your entire channel and then i cried when i realized you hadn't uploaded anything
in like a year and i found second germa watched almost every video and eventually actually
started watching your stream before i kind of thought streaming was weird and wouldn't be as
fun as youtube vids i was a genuine fool gotta love adhd and you oh that's a bernie pog moment
right there uh yeah the second channel does a lot of great stuff main channel still there
there's almost 800 videos on that channel i think still it's gonna be a nice gonna be a nice uh
archaeological dig site thanks for watching thanks for stopping by and
maybe you'll catch some more streams if you now you don't think it's weird thanks for the five
dollars uh bail and then and then and thanks for the 300 bits hey germ it's my brother's birthday
today a lot of birthdays what's today a lot of birthdays today 10th april 10th
shit what a birthday what are you guys born in april they say it's my brother's birthday
he was the one to show me your channel on youtube about a year ago i thought i would
donate well i appreciate that thank you i found your twitch and now i watch every stream a lot
of stuff's been going on in my life because of the pandemic because i may not get full tuition
for college since my exams were cancelled thanks for being your funny self helps more than you
know also there's a nancy drew movie from 1939 that's public domain are you serious that is that
accurate wow i have to look into that because that's the ultimate quelling of the drew crew
that's that's the ultimate thirst quencher for the drew crew i think if that's real what's going on
the list oh yeah happy birthday um to your brother and thanks for the 300 bits uh geo love thanks for
the 300 bits jerma i was wondering but will you be interested in playing any more point and click
adventures maybe you playing the neverhood could be a fun stream anyway thanks for these streams
they are really fun to watch if i played the neverhood it would be one of those me just
clicking in all the places i know where to click and talking about how much i love the game although
there are a couple of genuine impossible puzzles in the neverhood that require a piece of paper
even if you played the game a thousand times but there is a bug in the middle of the game
that i would need to circumvent somehow yeah maybe i'm not against that idea i those games
are a lot of fun we'll see maybe we'll do another we did didn't we do like a week of point and
click games at some point maybe we'll do another one hey zek martin thanks for the five dollars
thanks for having fun buddy thanks for giving me five dollars hope you had fun too do a raffle
where the winner gets a timeout for you oof why did i read that because it was the first thing
that popped up it was the first thing that popped up in my feed all right i'll see you guys on
tuesday for movies movies we're gonna watch movies and some tv shows it's gonna be fun
i thought the raffle prize was a timeout no the the raffle prize is not a timeout
you're just in trouble you're just in trouble great ray raid the guy that made all made all
those made ray the guy that made the jokes yeah sure why not and i want you to tell them
i want you to tell this person you're gonna tell this person that i'm gonna be this after the
poisoning come back i'm gonna be the strongest motherfucker stronger than everybody in the whole
game i will be able to beat the final boss with i'll just touch the final boss's nose with my
finger and he'll fucking explode let me show you the name right still playing final phase
all right playing final fantasy 7 still all right well you tell me if i you tell me if this game
looks any good i will see you guys on tuesday have a great night take care and goodbye